SUB BY bLAC  ( *****AKA LOSMAI****** )
This movie was inspired by a true story.
The characters, names, events etc. are dramatized.
Seriously
You Should have slowed down
We have crashed
Are you Okay ?
Yes.
Are you okay ?
Yes
How do you drive so fast at night ?
Did you keep your eye on the Road?
what ?
You don"t need to take pictures
what are you saying ?
It is very important to get the photo for insurance
Later don't admit it
It will be an evidence
The Gangster
The Cop
The devil
8 August 2005
A murder has taken place Near Cheonan in the early hours of the morning
Since Last year there has been numerous murders and disappearances in cheonam area..
But police have not  solve any of the cases yet......
We want to solve the case too
Solve a case
Be congratulated
Get Promotion
Turn off the siren
No one in this city cares
Not a single person
It's a dirty world
You're right
Look at those hooligans
Those guys needs a good beating
Where are you going ? our case.. sir...
Case ? and this is not a Case ?
See you at the site
- MAN CHATTERING-
Really
Please go over......Please go over
I am a police officer
Brother
I told you not to let me see you
Blocked the entrance
Move Aside
It's So hot today..Why are you here Again ??
Do the police need permission from bastard to come here ??
Brother
Please come back another time  today is not a good day
What happened today ? huh ?
Its a mess on the road , you're also a mess
Okay
Here...please go back..okay
Asshole, what do you take korean police for ?
You dare to bribe me...
Huh ?
Here you go
Well darn thing
You should be more careful
Why are you gangster trying to obstruct a policeman ?
Carry on
I hope you win
Boss
The Bastard police came again
Cut him down
Wrap it up nicely.
yes
I received a $ 200 gift certificate
when i subtract our 10% share
Your winning is $ 180
Ah...Which bastard ?
Open
Loyalty
You have been accused of illegally trading Gift Certificates
You have the right to remain silent
The right to a lawyer
Let's go
Brother
Come iinside the room
please come inside sit it
Okay seat there..
Put it on Obediently
Good morning boss
Yes it's me
Your Bastard kid is bothering again
what ??
I sent him to the crime scene
What is he doing there ? ........Bastard.......
Go and ask the Bastard about that yourself
Tell Heo Sang-Do that I am going to pass
You cannot do this to me when  you take a share every month
Because you have pocketed too
Don't you thing your men shouldn't disturb my work
I told you not to deal in stocks
Open a currency exchange office in the name of someone else
Or share the Profits You know the rules of the game.
I don't do small business
I am busy making machines and opening new stores
Can't you stop him before he comes over?
My boys have families to feed
Okay keep the phone I'll deal with him
shit...what's is it ?
what ?? What is it ??
Am I your friend ?
Where are you
I'm going to the crime scene..I'm hanging up
I don't want a friend like you
Let me atleast turn off the Fan
come here....come here
Parked it over there
Okay I understand
Thank you for the ride
Thank you
Brother..why are you doing this seriously
I drove till here...
Give and take
Fair ??.....Bastard..
kneel on the ground
I will call the cops
Damn traffic jam
Where the hell have you been ??
There are a lot of people here
Tell them to go away
Reporters and gentlemen, please wait....
Sorry sorry...You can take pictures later
Later please.... Sorry..
Clear the path
Properly secure the scene, what are you doing?
hey..hey..hey ! Go away..go away..
You're too late
More and more people are gathering around there
People are crowding
Hello there
Have you checked his identity?
We are checking his license plate number, there will be news soon.
He just died a few hours ago
Between 3 am and 5 am in the morning.
The cause of death is excessive blood loss
Or  heart attack
This is my preliminary judgment
Newbie, come take a picture.
Cha Seo-Jin...come here
Also look at this
I told you not to call me by my name at the crime scene
Sorry Chief Ch. Loyal please have a look
what is it ?
This is beacause of accident..right ??
It seems like accident also
It doesnt look like accident also
I hope he didn't die because of this
I wish it is an accidental killing
A few days ago ,Thank you ,
You made my men become crippled
The existence of rules has its own causes
Anyway
Although we do business separately, machines and engineers are shared.
Okay Buddy
We still have to solve the matter of territory, right?
Be Flexible
Shan-do
Yeah, Dong-Soo
If you  eat sweets only , you will have toothache.
Don't stir up trouble
Manage the trade I assigned to you
Everyone has their own bottom line
If you crossed that line you're dead
I don’t even have a road.
Steve Jobs said
To stay very hungry
I have no capital or investors,
So I'm still very hungry
Brother
My boss is generous, because both of you are friends.
That's why he provides you with technology and engineers.
Slot machine business
It’s not the same as fighting for bars and clubs.
This bastard Are you shouting in front of the bosses?
Give us something, to make us comfortable bastards
I've had enough
Scoundrel
That's how you raised your guys
Look how he stares at me.
Dong-Soo
You're all-powerful now and You only gave me  breadcrumbs.
How do we coexist peacefully like this?
Come here
Yes boss
Don't you see that we are Talking
Come here
Look at this bastard
Now we can live together peacefully. Right ?
Drink up
It taste good
46-year-old Cui Zheng Liu
No enemies, debts, litigation, anything like that.
The autopsy report is clear.
He died beacuse of dozen stab wounds
It appears to be an amateur killer
He just crazy
But if it’s an amateur killer, it’s a bit strange.
Because there is no evidence left behind
No footprints, blood, hair, fingerprint, just nothing
The wallet is missing. It may be a robbery.
But the amount of money is not big, so maybe not
People will kill people even for a little bit of something
The briefing is over. Call the team captain.
Okay
Yes sir
This case is likely to be a robbery and murder case
Look for someone with a similar criminal record
Yes i understand
And you support your team
Three cases were committed by the same suspect
What case ?
Here, July 15 Western Hills reservoir
July 23 Boryeong Sunny Beach Motel
As well as last night's case
In these three cases, the tools for the crime are all knives.
From the point of view of the length and width of the knife
It maybe the same knife
No its the same knife
This is a serial killing case.
This is not the United States
Koreans can't get guns. Every murderer uses a knife to commit crimes.
There are more than 1,000 murders a year
According to your logic, half of the murders are committed by one guy
Are you crazy
What do you think you are mixing cases of other jurisdictions
Will the murderer care about the jurisdiction?
If we don’t catch him as soon as possible, more people will be killed.
He is too careful to kill people indiscriminately
He could attack again  anytime anywhere
You do this job too easy
The is not a case of homemade
You can not just mix them together
No
I am not mixing them together. Look
These cases occurred in the Chungnam area a week ago
Our informants have nothing to gain
This is instinct
To hell with your instinct
Did Your instinct  bring you to the gang in the arcade?
You got so much time ?!
Aren't they criminals?
Gangsters and murderers are the same asshole.
Jung Tae-Seok , what's wrong with you?
Are you so desperate for promotion?
Damn it.
Yeah, that's what I want
When I arrest the killer.
The discussion is over, Come out..
Lets catch the murderer
I am not drunk, I will drive myself.
But Brother
Go back with the brothers
Okay I understand
Yes, Mr. President
Shan-do is a bit reckless but he is a smart man
He won't get into trouble anymore
Yes, Don't worry
Good night
I am sorry
The road is very Slippery
It looks like its okay....... you can go...
what
But after all, I hit you
I'm okay you can go
Are you really all right
Yes, I'm all right
Asshole
hateful
what the..
Who are you ??
come here
Who is there ??
It's not Shan-do
I've Never seen him before
Its Shan-do boss
He is not a gangster
His attack is cold and without feeling
It was different
Who else wants to kill you in our business line ?
Give me that
It was too dark to see clearly
White sedan, License plate 23XX
Anyway try to find it
Be careful
We are friends
Sorry
The patient looks really comfortable.
What happened again ?
I brought you a box of Energy drink
I heard that you were stabbed
I received a call from the  hospital
You must have felt very shameful of it
After all, you're a gangster
Likewise, After all, you are a policeman.
The police too incompetent
So the model citizens are still being hurt.
seriously
Model citizen Jang Dong-Soo
So Tell me what happened last night clearly.
I'll help you catch him
Maybe I can catch him faster
Really ?
Want to bet on it ?
Well bastard
I'll help you catch him
Okay I bet you will...come closer..
Last night I stumbled and got hurt.
Sure, last night.
You have to watch where you step
Where did this unlucky bastard fell on to have so  many stab wounds ??
Jang Dong-Soo car is black Mercedes license plate 3849 right?
Call you later
Bastard
Rear-end
White car
I was right Dong-Soo
what to do with this ??
Are you ok ?
Sit down
No need
I feel so miserable, I can't even look at you.
What will happen next?
The ink is not dry on the contract and you suddenly attacked
what do you want me to do ?
I now have a lots of brother crippled
Pay the hospital bill and give compensation.
And Then hand over the flagship store and those in the province
I'll compensate your brothers properly
Those stores ??
That is what you plan to do ??
Dong-Soo
If I really do
would you be still alive?
Think about it
I am also very curious
Who would do this to you
I am leaving
Really embarrassing
A gangster was stabbed..... if it was me I would rather commit suicide
Trust me and give me two men for this case
I'll close them all at once
Why don't you ask for vacation ?
The staff in this department is not enough.
Why are you trying to clean up the mess of others?
Sir This is a big case
I'll close one and the next will follow.
Like a long train.
Get lost
I have a witness who survived the attack.
Did the witness come to us?
Jang Dong-Soo
What Jang Dong-Soo ??
A few days ago he was stabbed
He did two hours of surgery and barely survived
Listen to what you're saying
come on, Think about it please
What kind of fool will attack a gangster?
The killer is not a gangster.
I'm sure he's a serial killer
Shut up
This is a gang case, I will assign it to the other unit
I'm warning  you not to get involve
Get Out
Save it, don't cover  him
It's not the time now
What ? I cover him ?
What else is it ?
You bastard
Let's say you're right,
But Jang Dong-Soo is a victim.
Will you apply for an arrest warrant on a victim?
Or go directly to arrest him ??
How many crimes did he commit?
We have to catch him and pull him down.
He is searching for the person who stab him
If we don't do anything, he'll kill the murderer
and there will be three open cases.
How will Jang Dong-Soo find him?
He is a gangster, not a policeman.
It’s not a matter of letting his man find someone.
And Jang Dong-Soo...
Saw The murderer's face
Get Out
Your words are unreasonable
Why don’t you tell the landlord?
Then what should I do ?
I have to work hard to make money
What ?  birthday ?
Why the are baby's birthday so important?
I'm exhausted
I haven't slept for two days. what baby's birthday are you talking about.
I think its your child's Birthday..
What?
The child you were talking about now.
show me
Sharp face
Cheeks are thin, chin's quite angular
Straight and long nose
His lips were bigger than his nose.
Quite accurate
You shouldn't have children.
It's not his fault
Find him before the police
Okay  boss
Where are we ??
who are you ?
Thank you for your cooperation
From now, We are seizing the illegal slot machine game room
Everyone should stay in place
Where is the boss ?
Its going down
Oh Really ? wait
Okay.. Continue..
Jang Dong-Soo crafty bastard.. you are quite something..
63 out of 97 machines are tampered with
Should I get an arrest warrant today?
Wait a minute, I'll ask him
So what? Should I obtain an arrest warrant ?
what do you want ?
The one who stabbed you
Tell me everything, I will look for another way.
What if I don't?
Since you bribe my boss, so I'm nothing for you, huh?
Listen Jang Dong-Soo
The one who stabbed you
Is a serial killer
He is a bit strange
He is different from other psychopath
You are a witnesses
What are you talking about ?
Otherwise, why do you think he wants to provoke you?
Most psychopath murder girls
Or people who are weaker than them
But this idiot kills indiscriminately
If we don’t find him as soon as possible, more people will be killed.
What is your problem?
Give me the information and continue your gangster stuff
This is a win-win situation
I'll catch him and bring him to justice
Let him sit in a hole
and then
Nothing. That is the end
that's all
The country's largest luxury casino is built in
the penthouse of this skyscraper
The entire area around our Zeus building
Will become the most popular place in town
Don’t talk nonsense, I heard that this place has been scrapped.
Its annoying
People who are interested before the construction are gone
Investors naturally delay and does not give money
After your accident Weird rumors are spreading .
Chungju area is another problem Boss..
Sang-Do men are entering our territory
Still haven't found him yet?
We found his car on the highway.
His car ?
The car stopped at the rest station for a few days.
My men found it
Where is the car now?
We brought it back
A few days ago there was a murder in Shaintajin
and this
Discarded or lost
They found this 3 kilometers away from the car.
Save it properly
Yes boss
Hello
I'm Jang Dong-Soo
What a surprise
You know the murder in Shintanjin right ?
But why ?
The bastard did it.
what ?
How did you know ?
We found his car there.
I'm the best in my game.
I risked my life to come here.
When someone came and grabbed my ankle
What can I do? I can only cut off his arm.
I can't cut off my ankle
But after the guy destroyed the reputation of a gangster
Disappeared without a trace
Hey
Whoever provoke me, must bear the consequences.
Reputation is everything for a gangster
I'll chop that Bastard
and then set an example for the public
Are you telling a policeman that you want to kill?
We do things for which the law is short.
Will a bad guy catch another bad guy?
No
Two bad guys will catch the worst person
This is the Bastard car keys
Don't you treat me as a policeman?
I can arrest you right away.
You cannot..Because..
You want to catch him more than I do.
I'll give you guys and I will take care of the expenses.
We will Share the Information
help each other
And at the end?
Divide him into two halves?
Whoever catches him will have him
So if I catch him first, it will be by law,
If you catch him than you bury him
If you have so much confidence, then......
Okay.. Call
You will regret this
This guy is quite handsome
how old is he ?
About 35-year-old
I can not see properly due to the rain and darkness
Use this to keep in touch
The gang and the police teamed up to catch the devil
This is exciting
This Bastard
I'm in the same boat with you, I have to protect myself
We can't draft a contract again.
You bought a High tech and you recorded me?
..S..h..i..t...
This villain wants to use his brain
That's why I can't trust the cops.
I was too indulgent with you
Listen bastard
Once this is over, I will Beat you up..you bastard
He also stabbed Jang Dong-Soo
Then he committed a murder in Shintan. What does it mean?
If we act according to my way
We can solve 5 cases in one  swoop.
About 35-year-old male of average height
From his mode of crime, he only kills at night.
Not affected by location and only use one knife
This is one of the two knives
Stick to the knife or the face to catch the murderer
So far there are no other clues
I made a deal with the police
We will catch him
Of course, we will not tell the Secretary
How can we trust the police ?
How can we believe the gangs ?
Who believe ?
We need manpower to catch the murderer
This is not a case  we can handle Ourselves
Let’s tell the Secretary.
And then what?
The squad will intervene
Media will get  involved and take away all the honors
Not only that, the Secretary is protecting Jang Dong-Soo
This is the only way to solve the case
The Secretary is a mess
Jang Dong-Soo have seen his face , his car.
Only his portrait painting is not enough
We need his fingerprints and DNA.
We'll use gangsters to find the killer
and then we catch them.
I will use them first and then throw them away.
We are also citizens paying taxes
Let's use police help once
From the outside it looks like an abandoned warehouse,
But tens of thousands of gaming machines are manufactured here
And Then sent to all parts of the country
..son of a bitch..
We'll find some clues
Maybe  his hair, his fingerprint, or even his breath.
we must find something
We'll search every inch of the place
let's start
Leave all the dirty work  to Jang Dong-Soo
and let's go through all the cases again.
This is a security cameras record  from the murder in Shintanjin
His mode of operands is
that so far in all the cases of the murders he used a car.
He's always on the move, so it's harder to catch him.
We know about 4 open cases, but there must be more.
Don't forget to look at them from the perspective of a serial killer.
If you find any information, report it to me.
He is a ticking time bomb
It can appear anywhere. Go through the cases from other areas.
And don't be too noticeable
Okay ?
Okay
When we close the case, we'll catch those gangsters too.
Nice and clean.
Ultimately its up to us to catch this murderer
Before that, let's get rid of Shan-do
Bastard
Are you crazy ??
What are you doing here ??
What the hell do you think?
I'm waiting for you
I think you hurt my back
You should not scare me
I was shocked
I want to drink too
So Refreshing
Can you look at this ?
Its urgent
what is this ?
It is nothing special
I found some hair and blood
Help me find out who it is.
Jung Tae-Seok
What's wrong ?? It's not like you..
what happened ?
This is a dirty world
I want help too..
Right, It's a dirty world.
This murderer is very strange
He left the weapon to to be found
Murder and police disappearances at sea
Crying over spilled milk
Now a gangster boss is dead
What would you do ?
If you have a mouth, Speak up.
Jang Dong-Soo case was handed over to the second team.
They will investigate
What are you doing ?
Don't stare at the computer.
Get Out
what are you still doing ?..Go out right away
Go out and Look for evidence to solve the case
At least pretend to care
Hurry
Well yes
Hey!
You want to die
what happened ?
This stuff is nothing special about it
I just got the results
I don't believe this
Come on tell me fast what is it ?
The DNA was identified as the last victims of the Chungnam murders.
Really ??
There are other people do
Was there any other in addition to that ?
No
It does not make any sense.
Did you check it properly?
There was no other DNA.
But that is not the problem
Something strange happened.
wait wait
go on
On the murder weapon that killed Heo Sang-Do
Heo Sang-Do DNA Truck drivers and Dog owner DNA were found
what ?
All this is done by one person.
This will be officially classified as a serial killer
I have to go
Jang Dong-Soo... is it you ?
It's you
brother. I call you back later
Answer me bastard
Are you crazy ?
Your idiot is back.
Here is here at home
Who else like that?
Let's talk later
A policeman and a gangster This is what you are doing
You're not a cop ?
Tell me bastard
You killed Heo Sang-Do right ?
Yes..I killed him
Its my fault believing a gangster
You believed in me
Even a fool would laugh at it.
Nothing has changed
We'll catch him together
do you understand ?
you
After this is all over
I'll investigate you nicely
Any time you want , asshole.
Since July this year, there has been murder in this region
It has been confirmed as a serial killer
The cases have been transferred to the police Crime Unit and the Cheonan police joint investigation
So that these cases are no longer stagnant
The murder case is handled by the regional police stations
But through a centralized investigation
There is new hope in solving the case
I hope this ordeal will end and let the residents return to a peaceful life.
Let's connect to the reporter on the spot
You come early
Dong-Chul
I was outside the hotel of the murder that took place on September 3rd.
It is said that the victim of this murder is Heo Sang-Do
This person is the leader of a violent gang in the Chungnam area.
It is said that he was involved in a dispute over.....
If you have given  the case to us from the start then
nothing would have develop to this point
Murder is not a child's play
You guys just destroy the investigation
Still say something nice to others here.
Bastard.. Do you have any problem?
Am I wrong ?
Bastard ?
I have a problem, you bastard!
Come here
In Heo Sang-Do murder scene a knife was found
There are other victims of DNA
The Ministry of Public Security has set up a special task force to investigate the case of Heo Sang-Do
And all the murders that have been committed may have been done by the same person
that's not done by me
The Task Force consist of the Regional Crime Unit and homicide team
As well as the country's best  serial killer profilers
Will conduct a thorough investigation
There is also the help of a forensic doctor.
The police also expect a large number of gangs to attend Heo Sang-Do's funeral.
So they will be vigilant
I am surprised to see you here.
I will certainly come. He is my friend.
hello
come immediate now
Why should I ?
To clean up your mess. come fast
who are you ??
Someone used my knife to kill Heo Sang-Do
If you want to kill him yourself, you better find something.
If the Crime squad first catches him, you and I will be finished.
Is this how you spend your life?
I really sympathize with you poor police
So Don't commit any crime you idiot
If there is no one like me, you will be unemployed.
That is life, there are prey, there are predators.
of course.. There are also victims of stabbing
He attacked me from behind, I am unprepared
But I still stabbed him with his knife.
stop
what is it ??
You stabbed him right ??
Yes.. why ??
I seem to find something
what is this ??
Bastard
Jang Dong-Soo what  is going on ??
What is going on ??
A group of bastard
get out
bastard
Hey... hey... hey
Bastard
Its over.. stop
You go away fast.. I'll take care of it.
it's OKay
He is bleeding a lot
It's just blood
Go away fast..Bastard
The police claimed that there is sufficient evidence to arrest the perpetrators of the killing Heo Sang-Do
and that catching a killer is just a matter of time.
The suspect’s fixed killing method and his active area are...
Honey.. where are you ?
when there's such a mess, you are taking a nap.
What's with his face?
Wake up fool
What have you been doing ??
Bastard
Where are you going ??
Here..Take this
This is a case of abduction
Soon-Hois  already there, better go fast.
Kidnapping? Why is it so important now?
We have a serial killer to catch
This Bastard is at it again..
Can't you see the Crime Unit in the office  ??
They are working with a team, so deal with this kidnapping case.
I told you from the beginning that this is a serial killer.
Now a team of Crime Unit ?
What the hell do they know?
Hey Bastard
What do you just say ?
Shut up
You did say it was a serial killer, but there was no evidence
Did you have any evidence or witness at that time?
If you are so powerful, why is he not in prison now? Bastard
shit
The victim is a venture capitalist
Brother
The attacker should be close to him. Hurry up and investigate.
By any chance Did you provoke Jang Dong-Soo?
What is wrong with you  face?
Certainly Something happened
Enough talk
Get infomation from your colleagues  about the woman's situation
How many times has it been?
Why have you been changing the meeting place?
Is he Really alive?
If you want money, let him answer the phone.
This is the last time come at Wal-Mung-du snack shop
Right now
What are you doing ? go inside.. please
Are you coming here to drop the bag?
Ah yes
give it to me
what ? Why did she give the bag to the woman
Damn
Are you telling the world that you are working with the cops.
Who is on the roof?
He is on the roof
Dong-Chul he went to the north
Where ? where ?
Bae...lure him on the main road
Hey
What are you doing?
Soon-Ho intercept him from the side
Hey
I cannot see him..I cannot see him
He is on  the Main Street
Bae...where are you Bastard ?
Stop there
This bastard
I will go down
Quickly....Quickly
I do not see him here
He is fast... where did he went ?
I'll Keep going
Go Upstairs..Go Upstairs
He is here
He just turned in the corner...blocked him from the front.
Which way does he go?
Over there..Over there
Go that way
Why are you holding the bag maam? You don’t know what is inside.
Why did you Yell at me?? what I did wrong ??
I was asked to take it
So Who is it ?
Tell us  fast otherwise you have to go to jail
I've never seen him before
He was eating alone and he asked me to take the bag.
He gave me $ 20
how does he look like
Just... He Looks very ordinary
Did he only eat ??
Ah.. he also drank a bottle of Soju
Chamisul brand
Where in the Soju bottle ?
Only the labels are different,
All bottles are the same.
I wish you have fun
Damn label
hey Dong-chul ?
Yes
Only Chamisul brand....
Find only Chamisul brand
I don't believe this
The bottles are the same
Don't work too hard
Are you serious ?
So what about the steering wheel cover ??
The results will not be available today.
So I charge $ 2000 per machine
Thank you
I will provide you with technical support if you need it.
That's not very cheap, Jang Dong-Soo
If Jang Dong-Soo fulfills his part
we'll all be happy, right?
I do not know whether I should accept such a bargain,
knowing how Heo Sang-Do ended up.
Be careful everyone
After Jang Dong-Soo was stabbed,  Heo Sang-Do was killed
His assistant also disappeared.
Stop it and continue with your food
What are you doing here ??
Find this person first
We found a strange fingerprint
It wasn't completely damaged
He could have completely erase it
I only identified him with a bad print he left
His whereabouts are unknown
His blood sample was also found on the steering wheel cover
He didn't come back for about 3 months
Did he say where he was going?
If he goes to work, he will go for one month.
This time he went for a long time.
I reported this incident, I thought that something had happened to him..
Were there any problems with him?
There is no problem at all
The rent is always paid on time
And he doesn't even drink.
He is a faithful Christian
He lives an orderly life, he's a good man.
We found a strange fingerprints
It wasn't completely damaged
He could have completely erase it
017-684-2784
Find all the information for this number
Do you have a recording of the kidnapper's voice?
Sent it directly to me right away
I heard that you spent a lot of money on his funeral
You're a loyal friend
Do me the same favor. okay ?
I told you to eat and stop taking, isn't it?
Why did you ruin this delicious lunch?
For your benefit, I am careful everywhere.
Eat your meal
Please continue
I have sent you a photo. Check it out now.
Listen to this
This is the last time come at Wal-Mung-du snack shop
Rght now
I am sorry
The road is very Slippery
But after all, I hit you
Kang Kyung-Ho..Age 35-year-old
His Father was abusing him, so he grew up in an orphanage.
No criminal record
He Call his 70-year-old mother every day
They Both use  disposable cell phone
Until August he called her only from Chungchong
But then he called from all over the country.
We tracked his phone call mainly from Anshan City.
But mostly from the region
Dekjung?
Yes
There are several universities there.
So there are  lots of cheap rooms and apartments
There are thousands of old houses
so troublesome
So  this Bastard
He hid there after stabbing Jang Dong-So
You son of a bitch.
Where is your manners?
Jang Dong-Soo
Is  he a friend of yours ?? bastard
Damn gangster
What makes you cops out of us?
You son of a bitch
Let me go Son of a Bitch
You want to die
come here
If we do not catch him
We are all finished, don’t you know?
If we are in the same boat
In any case, we have to tide over the difficulties.
Let's  just go
Do you have photos?
Yes
From now on You have only one task
To find this bastard At all costs
Yes
Be unobtrusive
and when you see someone who is similar to him,
Immediately Call one of us right away.
Create teams of 5 pairs
The person in charge of each group should report once every 8 hours 3 times a day.
We start in Dekjung
Search the designated area and then expand the search
Cheap single men's room motel and inn
Never seen him
Short-term rental, lease, long-term hotel..
Be sure to check these places
In the afternoon go downtown
Market dock and other public areas.
Search bar game room, Internet cafe
Search at karaoke rooms and other stores in the evening
do you understand ??
yes
seriously
Yes, I am outside, hurry up.
Ok
When does the bus come?
Hey, student . Come here.
here take this
I'm fine.
Take it
Ok
Thank you
What about you ??
Study hard.
Hey Jang Dong-Soo
We don't have time to organize
bulk dinner!
I have to feed them,
when you overwhelmed them with work
Kwon Oh-Sung will soon come
where is Your umbrella ??
Don't pretend to b a saint
hey student
yes
Don't take things from strangers
He is a gangster
You look more like a gangster than him
what ??
Don't laugh
Goodbye
...be careful..
Thank you
We may have different pairs of hands
But we  have only one heart
Until the end of Time
We're one
Thank you, boss
I really want to join you.
My life is a mess
I can't believe I work with you.
Hold on to your cop shit.
We have to work hard to get paid for it  its not easy task
We have work so hard together so as fighting! give me your Glass
We say thank you to a good drink you son of a bitch
I brought it, so drink as you please.
You have mastered all kinds of business.
Do you want to join?
Should I ??
You should join
Look at your looks, you will fly in the gang bastard.
Shut up and have a drink
okay pour it
No
I did not turn back
I have oil in my cup.
Hey uh-dha-roo sing us a song, the mood is not very good.
Brother, I used to be a trainer of a men’s band.
I sing you a great song
1   2
1 2 3 4
Hello quiet
Turn that up
A High school girl, while returning home alone,on the way
She was murdered
Because of her very young age,
The police ruled out the possibility of revenge or retaliation
And pointed out that the motive could be sexual assault or murder
Oh-Sung....
Get the hell up
Yes
Search every corner near bus route 32
What did we missed ??
North District, Dekjung, West District, Mopo, within 1 km of the Central Square
Hurry up and search
He must be vigilant here.
We are coming from Dekjung District and going down to Songgang.
I'm Searching the central square
I think I found him crossing  Dohwa Motel
Gather our People  and also search the vehicles
Someone saw him at  Dohwa Motel
Don't just search for motels, check out nearby bars and karaoke rooms.
Excuse me.... I am police
His room is No. 304
What are you doing?
Tell me where is he?
He just left
I found him
Be vigilant, we must find him
Stay in the car and see whether he comes back
Don't act rashly
We must let him in
Just do your job, asshole!
Cancel the search, send three people here
don’t move
Down
Nice to meet you bastard
Son of a Bitch
He drove like a fool
Hey
Pull Over bastard
Pull Over
Move
Damn
Son of a Bitch
what are you doing ??
Trying to catch him Bastard
over there
Son of a Bitch
Damn
Oh-Sung Bastard
Get a hold of yourself Bastard
over there
Fast
Shit
Where are you
This bastard is mine
Where are you Bastard ??
Find the location of Jang Dong-Soo
He's got the murderer...FAst   Fast
Fasten your seat belt Bastard
Before I kill you Live a good life
Park at the rest stop
what ??
I am starving
really interesting
Is there any difference between us?
you asshole you don't see what you've done
How dare you stab me
Aint it interesting ??
Playing with the lives of others
He drove to Cheonam
The monitoring of the toll booth captured him.
Bastard
when you kill someone..
Do You know what the best feeling is...??
shut up....you asshole..
Do you like Meat ?
I want  to cut you into pieces
Then thrown it everywhere.
son of a bitch
This is the best moment
When life and death are in your hands
Give it a try and kill me
Go on kill me
I said kill me
Do you know what you are talking about?
After killing so many people, do you think you can continue to  live ??
That's why you should kill me.
Asshole Die quietly
If you talk blood will spurt out
Sorry Dude
I'm still a cop.
Nice to meet you Bastard
Kang Kyung-Ho, I am arresting you on charge of murder
Even a devil like you
Has the right to hire a lawyer
and Right to remain silent
Anything you say
can and will be used in the court of law.
And If you can't afford a lawyer
We will use taxpayers' money to appoint a Lawyer for you
what is this ??
Isn't that obvious??
He is the serial killer
what are you doing ??
Come here
Salute
Come here  Bastard
Wait a moment
Let us through! Step back!
When investigating the September kidnapping
Cheonan City police obtained a key piece of evidence that led them to Kang Kyung-Ho
He is currently in cheonan Dist. hospital receiving treatment for minor injuries
after that He will  be further investigate by the police
and then will be handed over to the prosecutor's office for trial
Next News
The slot machine game hall has recently become a social issue
The prosecution has tracked that these game Machine were operated by gangs.
The one who is running the game machine is the wanted gang leader Jang Dong-Soo
Jang Dong-Soo book operates dozens of  machine game room
By illegal modifications to the machine
And made a lot of money with the Street machine
At present, the where about of Jang Dong-Soo is unknown.
Is this all done by you?
No
You convince the world that he was the murderer but now..
There is no evidence ?
Our evidence is circumstantial evidence
There is no concrete evidence that he killed these people
Even if I am a judge
I Won't be able to sentence him to death
what is this ??
This is a knife
The knife that you kill the people with ?
killer's knife
What is your outlook on life?
No matter what I think, I can't understand you
Do you know why ??
Because you are not a person
What is your outlook on life ??
A good cop, or a model citizen?
You can't answer me right ?
Who will abide by aoutlook on life?
We are alive because we have done So..
I wore gloves when I first murder
But they have been slipping and not moving as I thought.
You have to stab him in one go
The feeling of piercing
You can feel it from your fingertips
like this don't you think ??
And these photos
what ??
The order is completely wrong
Is there any evidence to proof that I did it?
Even if I received the death penalty
you know I won't die.
Go to hell
I'm going to kill you
I'm gonna kill him..leave me alone
If you get the death penalty without proof
That is murder
The real devils are the ones
who commit crimes with a kind face.
Think about it as the creator and executor of  law
Do you really have this right?
If you're innocent
Then I'm innocent too
You said you don't know this knife right ?
Yes I don't know
This knife killed 5 victims between July and September 2005.
Objection Your Honor
The prosecution did not provide any evidence in this trial.
and there is no specific connection between the knife and my client.
So we cannot assume that the knife belonged to him.
Yes, you are right
This knife has nothing to do with the defendant
At least until now.
Your Honor, we would like to summon a witness
who is the only survivor under Kang Kyung-Ho sinful knife.
who defended himself and survive the attack of  Kang Kyung-Ho
Witness, please step forward.
You still have the courage to appear in front of me asshole
Damn you look terrible.
We  are paying  taxes to let you arrest and kill those shit
This is the law
Arrests Bad people and punishes them
It also protects us because of that.
Shut the fuck up you should have let me kill him!
You're my last resort.
Let us kill him with the law
what did you say ??
Surrender yourself
Are you crazy ??
You killed Heo Sang-Do right ??
Yes I killed him
Asshole
If it gets out we're both dead.
Don't make me use this..
Give up and come forward as a witness.
You're the only witness
With you on the witness stand
I'll link him with all the murders.
Let's just die together
I swear to the Almighty God, to speak  the truth.
The truth and the only truth
Your Honor
The witness of the prosecution is a wanted gang leader.
Charged with several serious crimes
He is a suspect in other cases
It Does not affect his testimony in court
I agree
witness
How do you prove that the person who stabbed you is the defendant??
People like me who are often stabbed
will not forget the face of the person who stabbed him
until he ends up in the underground.
That is the  bastard who  stabbed me
After I was stabbed
I immediately found someone to draw this sketch.
Your Honor, the portrait is just a simple drawing of Kang Kyung-Ho
It has no substantive and scientific value as evidence..
Your Honor
This is the witness's ward record
Just after the attack
Witness is a gang boss
who always stabbed while fighting during his Normal Business
we don't know whether He is being treated
for being stabbed by someone else
He violated the rights of the defendant and slandered the authority of the law.
Asshole you talk too much..
Hey, lawyer.
witness
If your family is killed in the same way
would you speak the same?
Rights of the accused?
How can he deserve to have rights?
The asshole killed people for pleasure
I am also a bad person, but he shouldn't be alive..
Evidence ??
I will show you
That night, he bumped into my car and forced me to get off the car
Suddenly He stabbed me twice in the side,
After a struggle he stabbed me in the chest
I tried to grab this bastard knife by hand
and got my hand cut..see...
If I am an ordinary person, I would have died on the spot.
And Take off his clothes
I stabbed him in the left chest
He should have a wound there
And look at his hands,
you will find lots of scars.
Those who use the knife,
they have small cuts from stabbing
And damage fingernails
And lastly
That bastard wrote this
Analyze his handwriting
and you will find that it's a match
Heo Sang-Do is my friend
Heo Sang-Do and his assistant died
Although I feel sorry for Killing him
But if Kang Kyung-Ho shakes everything..
We can accused everything to him
The Defendant has an extreme tendency to violence
deliberate disrespect for human life
and  for the pain
that the victims had to endure
All these Factor will be Taken into account while giving the  judgment
Therefore, the defendant Kang Kyung-Ho
Is Sentenced to death
Thank you sir
Turn back
Salute
Boss is coming, let's greet him
Good afternoon Boss
I have one condition
Say it
Promise that you'll put me in the same prison with him
We played this game with the lives of people.
We have to end it
The Gangster
The cop
The Devil