(Barry) My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
(Barry) My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
(Barry)
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
(Caitlin)
Previously on The Flash...
A man in yellow,
he took Eddie.
(Iris)
Hi, Barry.
Or should I say
The Flash?
Observe. Barry marries Iris,
and not you.
- I've been having these dreams.
- What happens in the dreams?
(Cisco) Dr. Wells is
the Reverse-Flash,
and he kills me.
(Caitlin)
If this is Dr. Wells,
then who have we been
working for this whole time?
(Barry)
A completely different person.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to kill you, Barry.
I need you.
We will face each other again
very soon.
(Wells)
I want you to take a moment,
and think about all the things
that define your life.
All the people you love.
Your job.
Your coworkers.
Your home.
And now imagine if one day,
in a flash,
all of that vanished.
Would you simply
accept your new life
and continue on?
Or would you do
whatever it takes...
to get back
what was taken from you?
Because...
I can assure you.
I will get everything
that was taken...
from me.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Every age ♪
♪ Has its turn ♪
♪ Every branch of the tree ♪
♪ Has to learn ♪
♪ Learn to grow ♪
Hey.
What's all this?
Return labels
for Eddie and me.
I ordered 200 to start,
but this afternoon,
2,000 arrived.
I guess I ordered wrong.
I have so many now.
Iris, we're gonna
find Eddie.
How?
You searched everywhere.
More than once.
And you haven't
found anything.
I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at you.
- It's just...
- You miss him.
Yeah, I do.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
Wells took my mom
from me.
I won't let him take someone
from you, too.
♪ ♪
[phone vibrating]
Cisco.
I gotta go.
Yeah, go.
♪ ♪
I kept asking myself,
why would Wells pretend
to need a wheelchair?
Sympathy, I suppose.
That's what I thought
at first,
but he's the man in yellow.
He's the Reverse-Flash.
He's much smarter than that.
Sympathy can't be
the only reason.
Yeah, it was a misdirect.
Just like everything else
Wells has done.
I mean, the last person we'd
suspect to be the man in yellow
is someone who lost
the use of their legs.
That's exactly right, Joe.
Which is why I started messing
around with the wheelchair.
And that's when
I found this.
Damn. You can't get that
at Radio Shack.
(Barry) Looks like the tech
inside Gideon.
I measured the output,
and this thing is kicking off
serious juice.
I mean, we're talking
enough to power
all of Central City.
- Seriously?
- Oh, yeah.
What do you think
Wells was using it for?
I think this thing
is some kind of battery.
- Battery?
- As in, Wells was using it
to power himself.
To gain more speed.
And that's why
he's so much faster than you.
[computer beeping]
The accelerator,
it's been reactivated.
- It can't be.
- How is that possible?
It blew up.
It had to have
been rebuilt.
- Wells.
- Even if he did rebuild it,
how did Dr. Wells turn
the Particle Accelerator on?
He's here.
That's why we couldn't find him.
He's been inside S.T.A.R. Labs
the whole time.
Stay here.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Cisco, what did you bring in
that orange soda for?
Whenever something happens
with the Reverse-Flash,
liquid floats in the air.
You know, Barry's fish tank,
Wells's champagne,
Lance's coffee,
remember that?
If this does
the same thing,
we'll know that Wells
is in there.
Do it.
[exhales]
[computer beeping]
♪ ♪
Man... this... is... big.
Oh, God.
Guys...
[suspenseful music]
Barry!
Wha-what do we do now?
(female computer voice) Prisoner release.
Protocol initiated.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
[grunting]
[gunfire]
[electricity sparking]
No!
♪ ♪
Peek-a-boo.
[gasps]
[grunts]
Do you have any idea
what it's like
to be stuck in that box?
[grunting]
Now you're the one
who's gonna go into a box.
In the ground.
Aah!
[heavy breathing]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
Aah!
[panting]
[siren wailing in the distance]
[dramatic music]
[computer beeping]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I will be.
Thanks to Iris.
I'm glad you showed up.
How do you think
she got out of there?
Wells must have
released her.
- Help.
- Wait a sec.
Did you hear that?
I checked all
the containment cells.
Everyone's accounted for.
No, no. Listen.
(Thawne)
Help! Down here!
Help!
- [coughs]
- Eddie?
Oh, partner.
Oh, my God.
I got you.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Eddie.
Are you okay?
Let's get him
out of here.
Come on.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
There you go.
Go slow.
♪ ♪
Your vitals are normal,
but you're just
a little dehydrated.
The IV should help with that,
but drink some fluids
and stay off your feet,
Okay, Eddie?
Thanks, Caitlin.
Wells got away.
Oh, he was too fast.
He always too fast.
Eddie.
We found him under that hatch
in the pipeline.
I'm so sorry.
I thought I looked
everywhere for you.
Hey, it's not your fault.
Sometimes you just can't
see the clues.
Even if they're right
in front of you.
Um, well, you know,
all that's important
is that we're all safe,
and back together,
right?
Eddie, why did he take you?
[exhales]
I don't know.
He said that
we're... family.
Said his real name
was Eobard Thawne.
Eobard Thawne?
Just like in my dream.
Did he say anything else?
I mean, anything
that could help us
figure out what
he's really after?
I... he didn't say much.
He just kept working
on some tube.
A tube?
What did it look like?
Metallic,
futuristic.
He said it was
the key to him
getting back everything
that was taken from him.
The key?
I don't understand. Wha...
Yeah, I don't know.
Look, I just want to go home.
- Is that okay?
- Yes, of course.
(Iris) I'll make sure
he gets some rest.
Okay.
[grunts]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
What do you think
Wells was talking about?
[computer beeping]
Oh, no, no, no.
What?
What now?
Um, are you seeing this?
That's the tube
Eddie was talking about.
It's some sort of
future power source.
That's what's charging up
the accelerator.
Can you shut it down?
Do you see
a power button
anywhere on this thing?
Dude, this thing
is from the future.
It's beyond me.
I press,
or touch, or cut
the wrong thing,
I could bring
the whole building down.
Okay. How long until
it's fully functional?
Best I can tell,
36 hours.
That's when Wells
will be back.
Why would Wells want
the Particle Accelerator
to work again?
I don't know.
It's not like it was
such a big success
the first time.
It made me The Flash.
That's not all it did.
(Caitlin) So what happens if the
Particle Accelerator turns on
while the meta-humans are in
their containment cells?
They're toast.
We put them down there
and now their lives
are in danger because of us.
Look, I think
you all know
I've never been a fan
of this arrangement here.
I thought the whole plan
was to rehabilitate them
and set them free.
It was.
We've been a little busy.
Well, if they stay in there,
the die.
And if we let them go,
they destroy the city.
We're gonna have to
move them.
Move them where?
Iron Heights can't
handle meta-humans.
You're right,
but Lian Yu can.
What the hell's a “Lian Yu?”
Lian Yu is the island
where Oliver
was stranded
for five years.
A.R.G.U.S built
a covert military prison on it.
It's where we sent
Captain Boomerang.
Oliver keeps
his worst criminals there.
They won't be able to escape,
and more importantly,
they won't be able
to hurt anybody.
Great. So we ship them
from one illegal black site
to another?
Yeah, I guess so.
Yes.
And how do we move them to
Oliver's own private Alcatraz?
I'll call him. Maybe he can help
with transport.
And Cisco...
if we do this,
nobody can get loose.
I might have a way of
getting them out of here safely.
All right, get on it.
Barr, this is insane.
Joe, we have to do this.
You don't think that
if we start
bussing super-villains
through downtown,
nobody's gonna notice?
Oh, they'll notice.
That's where
you'll come in.
Oh.
Cecile.
Aww.
How's my favorite D.A.?
Thanks for stopping by.
Hey, anything for
my favorite detective.
Hey.
So what can I do for you?
You sounded a little cryptic
on the phone.
Yeah, I wanted your opinion
on something.
These people with powers,
the meta-humans.
Is that what
they're calling them?
People love their labels.
Yes.
Let's say, hypothetically,
I know a prison
of sorts,
a place that can do
what Iron Heights can't.
Where these meta-humans,
the bad ones,
are being locked up.
I would be
very concerned.
Especially if,
hypothetically,
you had anything
to do with it.
Why are you asking me
about this?
Well, because Singh's
on his honeymoon,
and you're the only other person
I can trust to know this.
Okay, what are you
asking me to do?
I need to clear a route
through the city.
Barricades, police cars,
the works.
What am I
supposed to tell people?
The President's in town?
I don't know.
You think they'll believe you?
No, Joe, no.
They wouldn't.
What you're doing,
it's called
unlawful imprisonment
and human smuggling.
Joe, those are
very bad things.
These are some
bad people, Cecile.
But their lives
are in danger.
I can't... I can't
get involved in this, Joe.
I can't.
And as your friend,
and quite possibly the attorney
who will one day
be prosecuting you,
I'm telling you, get as far
away from this as possible.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Okay, so A.R.G.U.S. has
a transport plane
that can take the meta-humans
to Lian Yu.
We just need to get them
to Ferris Airfield.
So Oliver Queen
came through then?
Uh, no.
Actually, it was not him.
Apparently he's in
Nanda Parbat...
- What?
- Wherever that is.
I don't know.
I called Lyla, Diggle's wife.
She's gonna hook us up.
So, what about CCPD
giving us an escort?
- Man, it ain't happening.
- What?
You saw me talking
to the D.A.
She was very clear.
I could lose my badge.
I could go to jail.
- We could go to jail.
- We... we are protecting people.
We are, Barry,
but... I'm a cop.
There's a certain set
of rules I need to follow,
and this year,
I broke all of them.
- Lying to my boss...
- I know.
Ignoring the law.
I mean, at what point
do we become no different
than the people
we're fighting?
- We are way different.
- How?
We only break the rules
to help people.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Give me another one.
Ice cold.
♪ ♪
Well, well, well.
If it isn't
the scarlet speedster.
We need to talk.
♪ ♪
You want anything?
Beer, food?
(Snart) Pickled eggs here
are fantastic.
[Foreigner's Cold As Ice plays]
No, I'm good.
I need your help with a problem.
Must be pretty desperate to come
asking for my assistance,
but I'll bite.
What do you need?
Help transporting
some people out of the city.
- How many?
- Five.
Five very bad,
very angry people
who have powers.
Powers, hmm?
So you want me to what?
Freeze the problem?
Protect you from them
if anything goes wrong?
First rule of business:
always protect yourself.
I'm not gonna help
usher your enemies out of town.
Hey, they're not just
my enemies.
They're your
enemies, too.
I doubt it.
♪ ♪
They will destroy
Central City.
It's not my problem.
You said that you love it here.
That this is your home.
I do and it is.
Well, guess what?
These people get loose,
there won't be a city
to love anymore.
You won't be able to
rob anyone
if everybody's dead.
♪ ♪
It's a compelling argument.
But if I'm gonna
help you out...
♪ ♪
I'll need something
in return.
- Like what?
- This.
[chuckles]
No.
This is impossible.
- I can't do that.
- Then I can't help you.
There has to...
Snart, there has to be
something you want
that I can get.
♪ ♪
Let me think about it.
♪ Cold as ice I know ♪
♪ As cold as ice ♪
Eddie.
- Hey.
- Where have you been?
Here.
Work.
You were kidnapped
for nearly two weeks
and your first thought
is to go back to work?
I just needed something
constant in my life.
I thought that was us.
Eddie, I miss you.
I love you.
Hey.
I saw this
when we found you.
This was for me,
wasn't it?
When you took me
to the waterfront
and Dr. Wells abducted you,
you were going to propose.
I was.
But now you're not?
What did he do to you?
He didn't do
anything to me, Iris.
It's what he showed me.
What could he possibly
have shown you
that would make you
change your mind about us?
The future.
He showed me
the future, Iris.
We don't get married.
You and Barry do.
[dramatic music]
Look, I gotta go.
♪ ♪
Are you out of your mind?
What do you mean
you talked to Leonard Snart?
I asked him for help.
Barry, why would you do
something so stupid?
Because, Joe, we have already
tried everyone else.
Look, you tried the CCPD.
I tried Oliver.
I even tried Ronnie
and Dr. Stein.
And the Particle Accelerator
goes online in...
16 hours.
16 hours, Joe.
I'm not willing
to let the metas die,
and we can't let them
escape, either.
So, like it or not,
Snart, with his cold gun,
is the only one
that can stop them
if Cisco's transportation
does not hold.
Then lucky for you I figured out
what it is you can get me.
Hello, Detective.
Nice to see you again.
Caitlin, Cisco.
I thought about
your proposal.
You want my help,
this is what I want.
My fingerprints,
dental records,
DNA, criminal records,
family tree,
everything there is
in this world
concerning Leonard Snart.
I want it destroyed.
All of it.
At CCPD, online,
everywhere.
The brass on this dude.
You really think
we'd do that for you?
I'll do it.
If it's the only way,
fine.
You and me need to talk
right now.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
What is wrong
with you?
You can't just erase
Snart's criminal record.
Yeah, I can. And I'll do
whatever I have to do.
Barry, there's gotta be
a different way to do this.
Okay, well, what is it, Joe?
Tell me what it is,
and we'll do it.
We're running out of time!
What is going on
with you?
You working with
that killer.
This isn't
who you are.
Who I am is the guy who's not
fast enough to stop Wells.
He... he hasn't been
one step ahead of us, Joe.
He's been 1,000.
I can't catch him.
I can't beat him.
What I can do is save
those people down there.
Wells turned them into
what they are,
and I'm pretty sure
he does not care
if they live or die.
I do.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Oh.
[computer beeping]
♪ ♪
Bye-bye, Leonard Snart.
[beeping]
[zooms off]
♪ ♪
I've deleted everything
the CCPD,
A.R.G.U.S., and the FBI
had on you,
and sent a virus to erase every
digital record of you online.
And this is
every single piece
of physical evidence
the police had.
Good.
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
I hear we're all
going to be working together.
That's right, Sis.
Partners.
♪ ♪
Please tell me
this is a joke.
Oh, you were right, Lenny.
She is very uptight.
I am not uptight.
[tense music]
You can't call me uptight.
Look, guys,
we need their help
if we're gonna pull this off.
Why are you wearing
your mask?
Snart already knows
who you are.
And I promised
I wouldn't tell anyone.
That includes my sister.
Jerk.
Trainwreck.
Don't look so surprised,
Detective.
I am a man of my word.
Yeah, you better be.
Or I'm gonna make sure
you're on that damn plane, too.
♪ ♪
Hey, Cisco.
Oh, hey,
Captain Cold's evil sister.
Aww.
You're not still
mad at me, are you?
I really did enjoy
kissing you.
You kissed her?
Under duress.
Calm down.
I've... I've thought a lot
about you.
Have you really?
♪ ♪
Well, stop.
Because this right here,
it ain't gonna happen.
A girl can hope.
[inhales deeply]
Really not enjoying
being one of the good guys
this week.
Really not.
(Flash)
Hey, dude.
Have you figured
out a way to get
the meta-humans
to the airport?
I have, actually.
And it's pretty dope.
This is cool.
Where'd you get this?
My uncle owns it.
His company hauls
frozen food cross country.
Okay, so I retrofitted
the cooling system
with the wheelchair's
power source
to create
an energy damper.
Which means what, exactly?
Basically, the back of this rig
is being flooded
with so much power
that it's effectively creating
a transient pulse
strong enough to disrupt
the meta-humans' powers,
so we can get them
to the airport and get them
on a plane
without them getting
fresh on us.
Technically, we need somebody
with a Class A commercial
driver's license
to drive this, though.
I can drive it.
What?
I have a Class A CDL.
- You do?
- We can't all be doctors.
(Flash) All right, well,
let's do this.
Plane's gonna be here
in two hours.
Hey, hey!
What the hell?
Hey!
[groaning]
[dramatic music]
[groans]
♪ ♪
(Caitlin) It's done.
They're all unconscious.
♪ ♪
Dampeners are
fully functional.
All right.
I'll make sure
the roads are clear.
Do not stop for anything.
Let's move out.
After you.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[truck engine starting]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
(West)
Hey, we got traffic up ahead.
I'm on it.
♪ ♪
(Wells)
How's our cargo doing?
(Cisco)
All quiet so far.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[heavy breathing]
Don't bother.
Your powers don't work in here.
None of ours do.
What the hell's
going on?
- They're moving us.
- Where?
Funny,
I didn't get an itinerary.
- [grunts]
- Hey!
Tall, dark, and handsome,
I said your powers are offline.
All brawn, no brains.
I know you,
don't I?
Kyle Nimbus.
Used to be a member
of the Darbinyan crime family.
That's right.
Weren't you executed
about a year ago?
It didn't take.
No.
The Darbinyans weren't known
for hiring
the best and brightest.
You couldn't even
die right.
So you're so stupid mad
right now, Mardon,
you're just going to
pick a fight with anyone?
Guess so.
(Nimbus)
If I had my powers right now,
I would gas you all
out of existence.
And then you'd be standing
in a container
with four corpses.
What would that get you?
Peace and quiet.
[suspenseful music]
Well, I don't know
about you guys,
but I don't need
my powers
to fill this rig
full of bodies.
Come on.
♪ ♪
[tires screeching]
What was that?
Wherever they're
taking us,
we're here.
♪ ♪
Ferris Air?
I thought this place
got shut down.
It did.
One of their test pilots
disappeared.
So what's the plan?
I want to get this over with.
It should be here
any minute.
Look, Joe, I know
you don't agree with this...
Save it, Barr.
I just want to get it done.
How come you haven't
given me a code name?
I heard you came up
with Captain Cold.
What do you think
I should be called?
Female inmate.
Oh, come on.
You made my gun.
Least you can do
is give me
a badass alias.
[playful music]
Please?
Fine.
Golden Glider.
Smart is sexy, Cisco.
♪ ♪
Your A.R.G.U.S. friends
aren't very prompt.
Maybe that's why they've never
been able to catch me.
Look, there it is.
[aircraft approaching]
Turning on each other
won't solve anything.
[grunts]
Don't ever touch me.
Wait.
Look.
[chuckles]
[sparking]
Oops.
[computer beeping]
- Uh-oh.
- What's wrong?
That's not good.
[suspenseful music]
Guys, guys, we have a problem.
The damper's fluctuating.
The rig's losing power.
I don't know why.
- Wait, can you do something?
- I'm trying.
[beeping]
[lightning cracking]
Oh, God.
Mardon.
[crashing]
[exploding]
[dramatic music]
Trip's canceled!
♪ ♪
Take your last breath!
[gunfire]
[sparking]
♪ ♪
I'm outta here.
Aah!
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[gunfire]
(West)
Caitlin, get down!
♪ ♪
[gunfire]
You locked Ronnie
in the pipeline
and you killed Ronnie!
- Caitlin, Caitlin, stop!
- He killed Ronnie!
- What are you doing?
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[gasping]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
(Mardon)
Finish him, Simmons.
[moans]
♪ ♪
[whirring]
How about we call tonight
a tie?
I'd power down if you don't want
me to melt your face.
Let's all go
our separate ways.
My name is Leonard Snart.
I know who you are.
Always pleased
to meet a fan.
Just remember who it was
made sure
you didn't get thrown
on that plane
bound for nowhere.
You're just letting us go?
Why'd you shoot that guy?
He owed me money.
Mmm.
What?
You want a “thank you?”
Who doesn't like
a “thank you?”
Thank you.
You are so
very welcome.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
You sabotaged the truck,
didn't you?
[breathing heavily]
Why did you let them escape?
Because now they all
owe me.
And something tells me
they'll be a lot more use to me
as part of my rogues
than rotting away
in the North China sea.
You gave me your word.
[chuckles]
It's true, I did.
But here's the thing.
I'm a criminal
and a liar,
and I hurt people,
and I rob them.
What did you expect me to do?
Not be what I am?
I saw an opportunity
to turn things to my advantage,
and I did.
Who you're really mad at
is yourself.
This is on you, Barry.
Then why don't you
just kill me?
Well, I guess you owe
me one now, too.
Good luck with...
all of this.
I'm actually really excited
to see how it all turns out.
[Flash groaning]
Hey, hey, hey.
[motorcycle engine revving]
Bye, Cisco.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[poignant music]
Hey, Cisco told me
you were in here.
How's Caitlin doing?
He used that
light thingie on her.
She's fine.
Mostly embarrassed.
Yeah.
Thanks for not saying,
“I told you so.”
But I did
tell you so.
(West)
Repeatedly.
I just...
Man, I've seen the way
that Oliver does things,
and he's not afraid to just
do whatever it takes
to get what he needs,
and I thought that I could
do that too.
I thought I could just
use Snart,
but instead he used me.
You're not the Arrow,
Barry.
No.
That's not the kind of hero
you are.
♪ ♪
What kind am I?
The kind that cares about
whether or not
those criminals
lived or died.
I mean, whatever Mardon
and Nimbus and Shawna did,
they're human beings.
And you knew letting Wells
use them as pawns was wrong.
You know the difference
between right and wrong.
And you weren't willing
to blur the lines
between the two.
That's the kind of man
you are.
And that's what makes you
different than the Arrow.
♪ ♪
So, please...
no more walks
on the dark side.
Agreed?
[laughs softly]
Yeah.
[alarm blaring]
- What the hell is that?
- Guys...
The Particle Accelerator
is fully charged and online.
Whatever Wells needs it for,
it's ready.
[suspenseful music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Iris, there really isn't
anything else to say.
Are you kidding me?
You're going to end
this relationship
because some lunatic
from the future
told you that I am destined
to marry Barry?
Well, I don't believe that,
okay?
I believe that we choose
our own destiny.
I decide who I love,
and I love you.
Whatever future
Wells showed you,
it is not my future.
It's not our future.
Please let me
prove it.
This isn't about
the future, Iris.
It's about here.
Now.
Today.
Ever since
the very beginning,
there's been three people
in this relationship.
You, me, and Barry.
That is not true.
You can deny it
all you want.
But Barry knows it.
Joe knows it.
And if I'm gonna be
completely honest with myself,
I knew.
I always knew.
I guess I just...
thought I could love you enough
to change things.
[poignant music]
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
But if you really do
love me,
you'll let this end.
Fine.
♪ ♪
Then it ends.
[computer beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Barry, don't even
think about it.
Barr, no.
You can't go out there
by yourself.
Yeah, I can.
♪ ♪
Well, I heard your prison
transfer didn't go so well.
I'm so sorry.
All a part of your plan,
I assume?
Actually, that didn't factor
into my plan at all,
but I'm impressed
you went to such great lengths
to keep those people
from harm.
Ever the hero,
huh, Barry?
You've hurt enough people.
I know.
You see me as the villain,
but, Barry,
if you were to look back,
look back carefully
at everything I've done,
every wheel
I have set in motion,
you would realize
I have only done
what I had to do.
Nothing more.
Nothing less.
And the Particle Accelerator?
(Barry) How does that fit into
your grand plan?
Well, why don't you
go on inside,
and let me show you.
You know,
I just learned the hard way
not to trust the bad guy.
And yet...
I've shown you
time and time again
you can't beat me,
Barry.
[boom]
♪ ♪
- Ronnie.
- Firestorm.
♪ ♪
Wow. You brought yourself
a friend.
♪ ♪
Welcome, Mr. Queen.
Hope we're not too late.
You're just in time.
I don't care how fast
you are.
You can't fight all three of us
at the same time.
Oh, I can't?
Trust me.
This...
This is gonna be fun.
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
Move, Barry.
[grunts]
Barry, move!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[exploding]
Come on!
♪ ♪
Ronnie.
Nanites, courtesy of
Ray Palmer.
(Arrow) They're delivering
a high frequency pulse
that's disabling your speed.
You're not gonna be running
around for quite a while.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
Aah!
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
The history books say
you live to be
86 years old, Mr. Queen.
Well, I guess
the history books
are wrong.
♪ ♪
That's the spirit.
You can't stop me, Flash.
And you never will.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Now!
[glass shattering]
[chuckles]
[thrusting]
[grunts]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing]
Thanks, fellas.
No problem.
Nice haircut.
And I see we've abandoned
our traditional green.
Trying something different.
Look...
I might need
a favor from you.
Wherever, whenever.
♪ ♪
I got you.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com