Hey, you hungry?
I was thinking blueberry pancakes
for breakfast this morning.
Or I could get us something fun
from that Brooklyn's Best Bagels place.
They just opened a
new location downtown.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC]
Iris?
♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[TOUCH TONES DIALING]
[LINE TRILLS]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Iris.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[CHUCKLES] Thanks for
the company, Cecile.
Any time.
You know, I figured you'd
be working this time of day.
Oh, I was.
Yeah, I'm actually
avoiding a new meta-client.
So I figured I'd get out of the office,
come over, see what Team Flash is up to.
Ah, well, we're all good here.
Yeah, the town is quiet, no alerts,
no crisis, just sweet, sweet,
- silen...
- Okay.
Barry, what's wrong?
Yeah, should we be worried?
It's Iris.
She's missing.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
Satellites aren't picking
Iris up anywhere in the city.
I'm gonna expand the
physical search radius.
Cecile, anything?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Nothing.
I can't sense her either,
and I've reached out
across a five-state radius.
It's like Iris's mind has just vanished.
Same here, only worse.
Barry, Iris isn't registering
anywhere on the planet.
How's that even possible?
It's just like last time,
she's not here anymore,
at least not in this plane of existence.
She must have had another attack.
Now she's lost in time.
Okay, well, then we
need Deon to find her.
No one's seen Deon since he disappeared,
and I can't access the
Still Force without him.
Okay, so...
so what do... what do we do?
Okay, okay, it's a long shot, but...
look, when Iris was in
Coast City, it wasn't just
her time sickness that
caused her to vanish.
Tinya Wazzo's powers did too.
♪
I can't believe you're serious.
You really want to try
and bring Frost back?
And I already have a
plan... I'm gonna repurpose
Eva McCulloch's R-CEM chip to replicate
Frost's cryogene so I can
create a new body for her.
Caitlin, I know you're hurting,
and so am I, but listen to yourself.
It worked before. It will work again.
And what about the thing
that makes Frost, Frost?
I have already identified
her latent empathic genes on my DNA.
I'm talking about a soul
and you give me brainwaves?
I'm also going to extract her
active imprints from her own DNA.
Look, I've already got the sample.
Unfortunately, the keratin in the cells
is decaying a little too quickly, so...
I'm gonna need a better sample.
You talking about grave robbing?
It's called an exhumation,
and I am a doctor as
well as the next of kin,
so getting approval won't
be a problem, we just...
we need to do it quickly.
[TENSE MUSIC]
I-I know how this sounds.
Oh, like that old horror movie,
"Frankenstein Created Woman?"
Does Team Flash know
what you're planning?
Didn't think so.
- They wouldn't understand.
- Neither do I!
Caitlin, have you forgotten
that you literally just tried
to resurrect your dead husband,
and it was a complete disaster?
No, I haven't, but that
thing was never Ronnie, okay?
Deathstorm used a physical form
that I loved to try and trick us.
Look, this is different.
The science is solid, trust me.
No.
Mad science.
Mark... Mark, Frost was supposed
to live a full and complete life.
You both were, together,
and now that's been taken from you.
Don't you want that back?
What do you think?
You can process losing Frost
in whatever way you need to,
but as far as all of
this is concerned...
Count me out.
♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
♪
Tinya, um, can... can we talk?
Why? I don't know you.
I'm Barry Allen.
You know my wife, Iris West-Allen.
I'm really sorry, but she's
missing again, and I don't...
Again?
Whatever, I don't care.
Your other half ruined my life.
You have every right to be angry.
I need your help.
The first time Iris disappeared,
she was with you.
You mean when I wiped
her out of existence,
like she did to my mom?
Are you okay?
What the hell?
Mom!
What did you do to my mom?
Tinya, she never meant to hurt anyone.
Well, I did,
which is why you should back off.
Do you even understand
how your powers work?
Examining how they work
could help us answer
what's really happening to Iris.
I don't care about Iris.
God, what is wrong with you?
You know, I was fine until Iris found me
and started spewing all
that crap about family
and having faith in people.
She made me believe that I could
have the life that I always wanted.
And now that's gone,
and it's never coming back.
So welcome to the club.
♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[AUDIO DISTORTING]
[DISTANT SCREAMING APPROACHING]
Deon, thank God. Iris is missing.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, she's in the Still Force.
I've been trying to
track her down, but...
- [GROANING]
- Hey...
No, don't... don't... don't.
Don't.
I've been infected by
Iris' time sickness too.
I need you to find the isotopic sensor.
It's the only way we can track down
that particle that I placed inside Iris.
We?
Barry, I can't find her alone.
I-I'm going to need your help.
Okay.
Okay... the sensor's damaged.
We're gonna need to repair it first.
Okay.
Okay, do it fast.
I'll come back for you after.
[CHAOTIC MUSIC]
♪
This is how we get Iris back.
So you're saying that
Deon wants to do that
by bringing you into the Still Force?
Well, both of us, together.
I thought he said it was
too dangerous for anyone
to go in there who
wasn't, you know, a god?
It's risky, but I trust Deon,
and he wouldn't suggest this
if there was any other way.
Well, Deon's right about one thing.
Our satellites can't
trace isotopic particles
across other planes of existence.
That's why we need you
to repair the sensor.
It's the only thing
that can locate Iris'
temporal particle
inside the Still Force.
But once we find her, we bring her home.
Amen to that.
Not to question a god,
but why would Deon need help
tracking a particle
that he created himself?
Deon's not at full strength.
Iris' time sickness
has affected him too.
Uh, Chester, how long will it
take to get the sensor running?
Uh, an hour, maybe less,
but Barr, how are you gonna get inside
the Still Force in the first place?
Deon's gonna come back
for me as soon as he can,
and we need to be ready when he does.
And you ran this plan
past the other forces?
Nora, Bashir, Alexa,
they're all on board too?
Uh, no, I haven't been
able to contact them...
any of them.
And Iris' sickness,
it could have spread to them already.
Which would explain why
they've been radio silent.
If that is the case,
then maybe we should all slow down
and figure it out before we launch you
into a place where we
know nothing about, Barry.
There's no time.
Look, Joe, Deon is our
only chance at finding Iris.
If he says going into the Still Force
is the answer, then I believe him.
I-I'm gonna get the
sensor from the Starchives.
I'll meet you in your workshop.
I should get back to CCC.
Got to keep the lights
on until Iris is safe.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Barr, hold up!
- What?
- Look, I'm willing to do
whatever it takes to bring Iris home,
but something don't
feel right about this.
Look, it's dangerous, but
we've taken greater risks...
Yes, we have, but are you sure
about the facts, because
you seem to be putting
a whole lot of faith in Deon's plan.
Because I know it'll work.
That's what Deon thinks you should do.
What do you think you should do?
- That's just it, I don't know.
- And Deon does?
Look, Joe,
I owe Deon this.
As soon as I learned
about Iris' time sickness,
I should have spent
every waking moment trying
to find a cure, even when
she told me to stop pushing.
But I didn't. Now it's worse,
plus Deon's affected too.
If there's a chance I can find Iris
and make up for all
this, I have to take it.
♪
[PHONE BUZZING]
- Parliament Runkadelic...
- It's Captain Kramer.
Uh, yes... yes, ma'am.
[CLEARS THROAT] How can I help?
Chester, I need a full analysis
on an unknown device we
found at a crime scene.
You're not busy, uh,
saving the world, are you?
No... no, Captain,
your timing is perfect.
Barry's gone to where
no man's been before,
so I'm free to fly solo.
Great, thanks, I'll see you soon.
Oh, you heard it, Chester P,
the crime-fighting
world needs your mojo!
Mojo.
[WHISPERING] Mojo.
Seven out of ten.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[DISTANT SCREAMING APPROACHING]
Oh, damn, moving through
dimensions is getting harder.
Is that it?
Are... are you sure we can find her?
There's just one thing.
Where we're going,
there's only one way in and out,
and it's a bumpy ride, so hang on.
'Cause things are
about to get real weird.
♪
[PANTING]
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
I've been here before.
- When Iris...
- First got sick, yeah.
Place is like a doorway.
I call it my front porch.
I can see everything from here.
[RUMBLING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
This place is different than before.
Yeah, that's 'cause
it's more dangerous now.
Welcome to the Still Force...
What's left of it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Sorry about the mess.
How bad is it?
Ever since Iris got lost here,
things have been mad disorganized.
I mean, night becomes day
in the blink of an eye,
and just as fast, it's night again.
And now it's getting worse.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
You see, past, present, and future
all exist here simultaneously,
but now the balance is all out of whack.
See what I mean?
All right, now, stay close to me,
'cause if we get separated...
- I could get lost too.
- Or worse.
You could get trapped in the dead zone
where time just repeats
itself indefinitely.
That happens?
I'd never get you out.
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Sensor's picking up Iris' signature.
All right. Let's ease
on down the road, man.
[BIRDS CAWING]
[DISTANT CONVERSATION]
Don't... don't.
- We're getting close.
- Yeah.
My decision...
Oh, one thing, once we find Iris,
let me try and stabilize her first,
before we do anything else.
They need to know what
you've been hiding.
- All right.
- Taylor, don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
- I know those voices.
- They need to know...
they... they need to know
what you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't... don't... don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
They need to know what you've
been... you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't. Taylor, don't.
Ugh! This is my life.
- What is this?
- My decision.
They need to know... been hiding.
Future moment, stuck on repeat.
Hiding... they need to
know... they need to know...
They can't move onward and
become part of the past.
- My... my decision.
It's not what you think.
They need to know what
you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't... my...
my life. My d-d-decision.
Taylor, don't. This
is... this is my life.
How do we stop it?
We can't.
Not till we find Iris
and fix this whole place.
Help me. Someone, please help me.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Help me.
Please, I don't know
what's happening to me.
I have to get back to my daughter.
Renee.
Renee Wazzo. You're Tinya's mom.
Yes. Do you know where she is?
I have to find before... be-be-before...
She's trapped in here
too, just like Iris.
- Mm.
- We have to find her again.
Tinya thought she'd lost
her, but if her mom's alive...
Uh-uh, she's fracturing just
like me and Iris, all right?
We need to stick to why we're here.
Deon, we have to help her.
Renee's been lost in all this for weeks.
Hey, what we need to do is keep moving,
or else Iris is history.
She's the key to everything, man.
[SENSOR BEEPING]
Iris is close.
I can feel it.
Hey, thanks for coming in.
Oh, always happy to tech consult
for Central City's finest.
Also, I am in love with
the artwork in here.
- Is it, uh...
- Indigenous, yes.
Reminds me of home.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
♪
Nice.
So I'm guessing this
is our mystery machine?
There was an explosion
at a halfway house
downtown this morning.
Fire department secured
this from the rubble.
Apparently, it was attached
to the water heater.
Was anyone hurt?
Well, that's the strange part.
CCFD got a call about
an imminent explosion.
By the time they arrived on scene,
everyone had already been evacuated.
Then this released an energy wave
that took out the entire building.
Damn. Folks could have died.
How many people were living there?
37 at the time.
We got lucky.
Halfway house staff have no
idea who led the evacuation,
so this device is our only lead.
I need to know what it is,
what it does, and who built it.
Oh, I'm picking up traces
of radioactive particles.
This thing was packing
serious kinetic energy
before it went kaboom.
Maybe it's some kind of...
Some kind of like, EMP.
Whoa.
That's quantum coiling.
Captain, whoever built
this got mad skills.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
♪
Everything all right, Chester?
Huh?
Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm as good as a hydrogen-phat
sunrise over Jupiter.
Yeah, um, I'm just...
I'm gonna take this
back to my workshop and
do a full diagnostic,
you know, just to make
sure that everything's
totally cool, if that's fine.
Of course. I'll authorize it.
Okay.
Runk, are you okay?
Yeah, yep... definitely.
I'm five-by-five by the wayside.
Just gonna pack up my things.
♪
[SENSOR BEEPING]
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪
Vanya's the editor-in-chief?
[SENSOR BEEPING]
This can't be right. Where is she?
- Stop.
- What?
Tracing that particle should
have led us right to her.
Yeah, I know, I know,
just... just hold on.
What are you...
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Deon!
We needed that to find Iris!
Sorry, Barr.
Gotta bounce.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
What the hell?
I'm back home again...
With no way out.
♪
Shark Stadium erupted in
cheers after XS' heroic save.
Even without Impulse,
her partner in crime-fighting,
who was too busy partying
to answer his alerts.
[BELCHING LOUDLY]
Ugh. You are so disgusting!
It is clear that XS is the most
daring speedster to appear in years.
Good afternoon, Nora West-Allen.
How can I assist you?
Gideon, I need another word for
daring that isn't too flowery.
Of course. I have found
twenty-sev... twenty...
Gideon?
Gideon.
Where'd you go?
[DISEMBODIED GASP]
Nora!
Nor...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Nora!
Deon?
I-is that you?
Barry's trapped.
I can't help him, but you can.
[SPLUTTERING] Where? How am I...
[GROANS]
Uh...
Oh, schrap.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Iris, come on!
This brunch reservation
ain't gonna get any later.
Joe, don't worry. I'll
make sure we're on time.
You guys got any resolutions for 2022?
I know mine.
More family time.
[BUILDING SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Holy schrap, thank
goodness I found you, Dad.
Nora?
This place is messing with me.
Dad!
- Nora?
- Hi.
You're really here.
Oh, my God, I'm a super villain.
Seriously?
That's what you're worried about?
Okay, then where's
your meta hunting dagger
or your purple head fan?
No, no, I'm... I'm serious, okay?
I'm the bad guy in all of this.
- No, you're not.
- Oh, yeah?
Allegra, the microchip that
I found inside that thing
was hardwired with a one-of-a-kind
energy converter that I created.
But you didn't build this one.
So... so what?
I still went live with the designs
on my blog last month.
What is this anyway?
It's a quantum coil transformer,
which means it's extremely powerful
and dangerous if used
for the wrong application.
You know what, you were right.
You're ri... I should have
never put my designs online.
I never will again.
Chuck, you're overreacting.
I should have vetted my online posse.
Your posse could be anyone, but,
Chuck, you inspire people.
You don't send them to the dark side.
Think about it. You said there were no
casualties because the
person that built this
evacuated the place before it detonated.
Does that sound like a supervillain?
Or his accomplice?
No, Allegra, but I...
Then believe me when I tell you,
we're missing the real story.
And you're one of the good ones.
So have a little faith in yourself.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC]
♪
Dad, how are we supposed
to get out of here?
I don't know.
You shouldn't have followed me here.
You were safer in 2049.
But Deon told me you needed my help.
Deon?
Deon's the reason I'm stuck here.
I never should have trusted him.
I mean, you and Mom created Deon.
Of course you're gonna trust him.
I know.
Joe tried telling me
something was off and...
I didn't listen.
I was so focused on...
trying to find your mom,
I ignored the signs.
She's counting on me, and I...
I keep letting her down.
I want to tell you something.
I mean, you're gonna find out
in a few decades anyways, but...
you know how the other Nora was a CSI
and was following in your footsteps?
Well, I kind of did the opposite.
I'm a reporter.
And even though I love it,
I-I'm just starting out.
And sometimes I'm, like,
how does Mom even do this?
I'm proud of you.
So you're not mad I didn't
join CCPD like you and Grandpa Joe?
No, of course not.
I'm just... I'm glad you found
a path that's right for you.
Phew.
So, um, the thing is, is that
I'm having a really hard time
finding my voice as a reporter.
But Mom is teaching me
to have faith in myself
and listen to my instincts.
And if she were here right now,
she'd tell you to do the same.
And that everyone loses
faith in themselves sometimes,
even heroes.
But learning how to keep
believing in yourself
when the whole world is
telling you the opposite,
that's what makes a hero.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
You really are your mom's daughter.
Well, I'm yours too.
Maybe it's our belief in
each other that keeps us
connected just as much
as the other stuff.
You're right.
We are connected.
But not just our family.
Me and Iris, to the Still Force.
It's like you said, we created it.
Nora, I heard your voice
before you got here.
I think somehow, just for a moment,
I connected to the future
before it became a part of the present.
Or the past.
You must already have a piece
of the Still Force inside you.
If I can figure out how
to connect to it again
and control it this time,
I can get us out of here.
[SABER-TOOTHED CAT GROWLS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Okay. I'm ready.
Okay, remember, whatever
remnant of stillness
is inside me won't be there for long.
You look like Uncle
Wally when he taught Bart
how to create lightning constructs.
This is also how Wally taught me
how to make contact
with the other forces.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Nothing's happening.
[BUILDING HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
Focus on Mom's brush.
She still has it in the future.
You can use it as an anchor.
♪
[HEARTBEAT THUMPING]
[CHAOTIC MUSIC]
♪
What in the world...
in the world... in the world?
Barry, Nora, what are you
two doing in my living room?
[ECHOING] Grandpa Joe, you can see us?
Plain as day,
only you're glowing with
some kind of green light.
Barry, I thought you were
in the Still Force with Deon?
Dad, whatever you're
doing, it must be working,
because if Grandpa Joe can see us too,
the present must be stabilizing.
Barry, can you hear me?
Barry!
[VOICE ECHOING]
♪
Grandpa Joe's gone.
And so is the brush.
Dad, are you okay?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
Nora, the temporal stream...
I can feel
the pure Still Force
energy moving through me.
I can see the past, present,
and future all at once.
I can see Jesse and Harry.
Cisco and Frost too.
I can see Bart's children,
your wife.
Nora, you're all so happy.
I see...
Max?
I'm getting married?
Who's the lucky lady?
Actually, don't tell me.
I can already feel the
spark inside me fading.
Take my hand.
Oh, this feels seriously weird.
Let's get the hell out of here.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
Where's the exit in this place?
Memorial Park.
It's the only way in and
out of the Still Force.
♪
[BOTH YELP]
Schrap! What the hell happened?
It's a temporal barrier.
We have to hit it with
everything we've got
while trying to phase through it.
♪
[BOTH YELP]
[BOTH GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
We're caught in a temporal loop.
Dad, we're never gonna get out of here.
You see, the past, present, and future
all exist here simultaneously.
Yes, we are.
This isn't a time loop.
It's the Still Force pulling us back
into the past every time
we're about to escape.
Why would it do that?
Deon said the past, present,
and future all coexist here,
so if we've already escaped,
the only way to stop us...
Is to keep us stuck in the past.
Nora, use the spark I gave
you to focus on the moment
that's already on the
other side of that barrier.
The moment you and I get back home.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪
Focus on the moment
you and I get back home.
We get back home.
I get back home.
Home.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪
Wait, so you're telling me that you were
able to get out of there
'cause you already knew you had?
I know, it's totally surreal, right?
Barry, is there still
a spark of the Still
Force inside of you,
because if that's the case,
then maybe we can use
that to help find Iris.
Not anymore.
I tried to tap into it again
as soon as we got back,
and I must have used every bit
I had to get us out of there.
We'll have to find Iris another way.
And we will.
You know, guys, there's one thing
that I still don't quite get.
Barry, why would Deon want
to trap you in the past?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm really worried about him.
I'd better get back to 2049,
make sure Mom's still
there and that she's okay.
I'm gonna miss you guys so much.
- We're gonna miss you too.
- Sweet one.
But you're right, we need you there
to keep our family's future safe.
Bye.
[SIGHS]
I miss her and Bart
more and more every day.
Yeah.
And my baby girl.
Joe, about earlier, I
should have listened to you.
You know, you were
right about everything.
It's okay, we all stumble.
I'm just glad you picked yourself up.
Look, there's... there's something else.
When I was in the Still Force
and I tapped into a tiny bit of it...
I could feel Iris, almost see her.
It was like a spark of stillness
was inside her too, that I could sense.
What do you think it means?
I'm not sure, but somehow I know,
wherever she is right now,
she's okay.
[PEACEFUL MUSIC]
♪
No problem, just remember,
you can message me anytime
you need help with a
project, day or night.
You're feeling better.
Yeah, yeah... hey, you were right.
Yeah, there was more to the story,
and once I started digging, I remembered
where I'd seen this circuitry before.
Wookielover77 posted this
in the comments of
one of my live streams.
He was asking the Chester Posse
for tips on renewable energy.
It was all an accident, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Wookielover77 volunteers
at that halfway house.
He was just trying to
provide the residents
with unlimited hot water
from a clean source.
Someone's a believer again.
Thanks to you.
You're welcome.
So I was thinking, you know,
Marco's birthday drinks are in ten.
How about I buy you a root beer?
You know, to say thanks,
and I could use one myself, actually.
I would love that.
Yeah? Okay.
[CHEERFUL MUSIC]
♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
It's me, open up.
Go away.
Sorry about that.
I think you're gonna want
to hear what I have to say.
What is wrong with you?
First, you blow me off,
and now you break into my home.
What, I should... I
should call the Flash?
Well, that's your choice,
just like this one's mine.
I'm gonna help you.
And don't worry, I'll
pay for a new lock.
Now, you wanna know
why I changed my mind?
Because you were right.
Frost and I were just starting
to build a life together,
and thanks to her, I was
finally becoming the man
that I didn't even know
I'd always wanted to be.
Losing her broke me,
but losing her twice?
That'd kill me.
That's...
that's why I was so afraid to help you.
So...
if we do this,
I need you to promise me one thing...
that we won't fail.
We won't, I promise.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Then let's get to work.
♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Greg, move your head.