[light music]
♪
Dad?
Nora?
How... how are you...
Don't worry, Dad.
I know we've been through a lot,
but everything's gonna work
out like it's supposed to.
I promise.
It's really you.
I love you.
I love you too.
We've missed you so much.
♪
[music heightens]
Iris, hey.
This is gonna sound crazy, but...
I think we're pregnant.
[exciting music]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This must be why you're
feelin' so sick, you know?
And since meta-DNA signatures
can misrepresent HCG levels,
I gotta...
Hey, do you know where my keys are?
I gotta drive these
samples to S.T.A.R. Labs
otherwise the chemical
integrity could be compromised.
Of course, right here.
I'll call you as soon as
I know the test results.
- Cecile!
- Oh, hey!
Hey. What are you doing here?
Oh, uh, I have a file that Iris needed
for the Kord case. Is she in?
No... um, she is...
at work already.
Isn't that her work
computer right there?
Yes, it is.
But she's been more of a...
pen and paper kind of
reporter lately, you know?
Old school.
You're feeling very nervous.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
You're feeling nervous and excited...
Ecstatic, even.
Barry, what's going on?
I'm just... running late for work.
It makes me kinda nervous...
And ecstatic, 'cause
I love my job, so...
And I'll make sure she gets this,
and I'll see you later!
Hey, I thought we were
having lunch today.
- Us?
- Yeah.
Th... oh, uh, y...
No, our monthly Tuesday lunch date!
- Yeah.
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
No, I'm really looking forward to that.
As always. This is just a...
bag of... protein bars.
It speeds your metabolism.
I'm always hungry, so, um,
see you later.
Bye.
- Uh, okay, I...
[exhales]
[Okenyo's "Women's World"]
♪ Clink your glasses,
melt the eyes like ice ♪
♪ Raise your glasses,
melt the thighs like ice ♪
♪ Clink your glasses, hot flashes ♪
♪ You weren't ready for
it to feel this nice ♪
Girl, you gettin' your art mojo on.
I can dig it! [laughs]
Ooh. Okay, well, my bad.
I did not mean to disturb
the artist at work.
But a friend of yours is out and about.
- Who, Mark?
- Yeah.
And I just figured it was
something you should see.
Why?
What do you know?
Caity told you everything, didn't she?
Nothing, I just
remembered you two fought
at that bar the night you got arrested?
Yeah, and again the
night of the Force Storm.
Well, says here that
he handed in state's
evidence and got parole, so,
maybe he's turned over a new leaf.
[gasps] Like Captain Cold!
Uh-uh, I don't buy it. Not for a second.
I'm just waiting till
he shows his true colors,
and then I'm gonna kick his butt
right back to Iron Heights.
Sounds kinda like you're
gonna stalk him or something.
[laughs] You know, like,
watch his every step.
That would be crazy.
Great idea, Chester.
Wait, what? No.
I said that sounds like it's crazy.
I said "crazy," right?
Now, you're a damn good detective.
You dug up more on Operation Griffin
in one week than I did in years.
And hit the same dead end.
So the last we saw your perp,
Warrant Officer Adam Creyke,
was on a security camera
stealing five M18 Claymore Mines
from the barracks armory.
Which he used to eliminate my unit.
One thing I don't get:
the explosive output in close proximity
of five Claymores?
That would have been lethal.
Creyke would have known that.
How did you survive?
Honestly, I have asked
myself that same question
over and over.
Well, what exactly do you remember
about the attack?
Fragments.
Just...
[explosion and shouting echoing]
Screams, mostly.
[screams and explosions continue]
The heat of the explosion.
[fire crackles]
Adam's eyes.
[mysterious tone]
Somehow, I could tell
he knew he'd survive,
thanks to whatever his
damn meta ability is.
Creyke was like a brother to you.
What...
What drove him?
Adam and I are both
Wet'suwet'en First Nations.
Adam loved open waters.
He wanted to join the navy
and followed me into the army.
Said he didn't trust anyone
else to look out for me.
I had an uncle who used to
take me fishing every summer
on a schooner.
Sailors take naming their vessels
as seriously as they
name their firstborn.
Did Adam have a call sign?
- Yeah, "Rasputin."
- "Rasputin."
Yo, a schooner named "Rasputin"
is registered in Midway City
six weeks after Operation Griffin.
He's been a few hours
away this whole time.
There's no way in hell I'm
letting him get away again.
Kramer.
What are you gonna do when you find him?
This has to be about justice.
If this is gonna be about vengeance,
you can do this by yourself.
[tense music]
♪
Lead the way.
[intriguing music]
♪
[exciting music]
[buzzing in modem-speak ]
[replying in modem-speak]
[speaking in modem-speak]
[exhales]
[gasps]
Did you drive here?
What's up, party person?
Yo! [laughs]
So, why is the Flash driving a car?
Oh, wait.
Do you have a Flashmobile?
No, i-it just isn't safe
to zoop these samples.
Samples for what?
Blood and urine
for my annual physical with Caitlin,
who is my GP.
Right...
isn't it kinda weird to have
a teammate as your doctor?
[laughing] Yeah, yeah, no.
I mean, it was at
first, but it's cool now.
I should get to the med lab.
Hey, good luck.
'Cause Caitlin's in there
running a medical consult
with... Ultraviolet.
- Oh.
- I guess she accidentally
double-booked your appointments.
Yeah.
- Catch you later.
- Not if I catch you first!
[laughs]
- I get it, 'cause you're fast.
- Right, yeah.
- Yes, yeah.
[phone line trilling]
Iris, Caitlin's in the med lab
and we don't want anyone to
know yet until we're sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
My lab at CCPD has everything I need
to create a neutralizing
meta-gene variant
that'll track your HCG levels.
All right, thanks. Love you too, bye.
What did they do to me?
Black Hole introduced a
deliberate irregularity
into your vascular system,
one that creates a 40% decrease
in your body's ability
to maintain oxygen intake.
He made it so the mask keeps her alive
to ensure her loyalty.
Actually, the mask is
hiding the real damage:
implantation circuitry
grafted to your vocal cords.
Okay, how do we help my cousin?
So the software in the chip
requires regular software updates
just like your smartphone.
But no Black Hole means
no more software updates.
So pretty soon, it'll stop working
and I won't be able to repair it.
[speaking Spanish] _
No. [speaking Spanish] _
Caitlin thinks she
has a way to fix this.
- Permanently.
- Right.
It's risky, but I think
I can repair the damage.
It doesn't matter. I won't do it.
I'll leave you two alone.
Esperanza...
why won't you let Caitlin operate?
_
But you trust me. And I know this team.
I fought with them.
Suffered losses alongside them.
They're good people.
So if Caitlin thinks she
can help you, let her.
I don't need help.
Unlike you, I don't fear dying.
_
Maybe so.
Look, I get it.
Surgery is how this
nightmare started for you.
But Caitlin isn't Black Hole.
It's my life, not yours.
Then why am I the only one
who gives a damn about it?
Don't you get it?
This isn't about saving Ultraviolet.
It's about saving Esperanza Garcia.
Mi familia.
[slam]
Oh!
[grunts]
[intense electronic music]
[breathing heavily]
You boys really know how to
throw a "welcome home" party.
Yeah, well, the only rats welcome here
are the ones in the kitchen.
[laughs]
Yeah, that's funny
coming from you, punk.
Leave!
Now.
[exhales sharply]
[groans]
Snowflake.
As always.
Perfect timing.
So what happened?
Came to ask your old
boss for your job back?
- Didn't go so well?
- [pained laugh]
That... [inhales sharply]
Plus something about
"snitches get stitches."
Oh, no one's buying this whole
"turned over a new leaf" crap.
Look...
[grunts]
You ready for that dinner date yet?
I mean...
I should probably be a gentleman
and change first.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No.
Come on, I'm taking
you to Danville General.
No. No, no, no.
They're probably still pretty upset
about the CAT scan machine
that I sabotaged a few years back.
Okay, fine. Leawood Med, then.
Kinda blew up their bio-chem lab.
Okay, um...
fine, there is a shady
vet down on Fairview.
- He won't ask...
- [laughs] Hey.
Dr. Haley.
Yeah, I love that guy.
He's wanted to kill me
ever since Tijuana, though.
That's actually a really funny
story for some other time.
I can't believe I'm about to say this.
I will take you to S.T.A.R. Labs
and have Caity fix you.
But if you step out of line...
I will let you bleed out.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
[light music]
♪
Is that urine?
Hey! Um...
Is it lunch already, or...
Yes, and I'm starving.
Please tell me you're not still
in the middle of something.
No. Um...
Yeah, I'm just waiting to see if this
chemical compound reacts and turns blue.
Oh, cool.
What does blue mean?
[mysterious tone]
[squeals excitedly]
Barry.
Cecile.
- Are you and Iris...
- No.
N-n-n... oh, no, no, no.
We... we're not... [low rumble outside]
[boom]
[exciting music]
♪
[car alarm blaring outside]
Are you all right?
It was Godspeed?
He must have broken out of Iron Heights.
Either that or there's
another clone in Central City.
Great.
Why would they attack downtown?
I thought they wanted
to steal your speed?
The last one did.
When Rathaway and I took him down,
he said whoever sent him
wants infinite velocity.
Well, now it looks like
he wants infinite chaos.
- [monitor beeps]
- Oh, man.
I just picked up two
different reports in progress.
One has Godspeed causing
a multi-car collision
near City Hall.
And the other one has
him at a gas station,
like, three miles away.
Man, he's fast.
Even you can't be in two places at once.
Neither can he.
There's two of them.
Frost, if I run you downtown...
- I'm already ahead of you.
- All right,
- I'm gonna take the gas station.
- Wait.
Where'd they go?
Satellites aren't picking up anything,
They're just... gone.
Okay, maybe Iris can rally Team Citizen.
They can canvas the sites,
find out what they were looking for?
No.
Uh, what I mean is...
There's two of them, so,
that means they have the advantage now.
So anybody that's not a speedster
should stay put where it's safe.
And Iris is already home sick anyway,
so she's already in the
safest place possible.
Okay, what are we supposed to do?
I've been thinking about that.
A cryptographic algorithm
might help us decode their modem-speak
and figure out why they're back.
All right, do it, yeah.
I'm gonna search the city.
So here's a question.
Confidentially speaking, I mean,
what is your sister into?
Is it horror movies, Westerns,
single malt, blended?
"Cardigan" or "Blinding Lights"?
Go.
- Confidentially speaking?
- Uh-huh.
You can't handle her.
[grunts]
Rest up.
Hey, what's with our sonic booms?
Don't mind me.
Let's play... [grunts]
a guessing game.
Shall we?
Let's see.
A sonic boom at ground level.
And with this being Central
City, AKA meta heaven,
I am guessing a speedster's behind it.
And since there have been
one, two... that's math.
Five Godspeeds running
around Central City
in the last year and a half alone,
I am also guessing another one
just showed up to the party.
I hate you.
There's two more.
Yup, you heroic types
have quite the dilemma.
How are we gonna stop both
of them at the same time?
[yawns] That's a good question.
"We" aren't doing anything.
You need to focus on
Ultraviolet's surgery.
Who's Ultraviolet? Is sh...
- Will you just be quiet?
- Shut up.
Stay here. I've got a job to do.
Do you need any help?
I could stay, you know.
C'mon, put me in coach?
You just got patched up.
You're benched.
Right.
You, Caitlin,
and whoever else is part
of your S.T.A.R. Labs posse
think you get to just sit
up here in your ivory tower
judging who's good and who's bad.
Well, guess what?
Life. Isn't. Binary.
It's everything in between.
Now, you don't trust me? That's fine.
But you cannot decide who
someone's gonna be today
based on what they did yesterday.
And you should know that
better than anybody else...
Killer Frost.
I'm sorry I-I just wanna help you.
- No.
- [door pad beeps]
Okay.
Is this really necessary?
Great. [sighs]
[monitors beeping]
She's gonna be okay, right?
Of course. Hey.
She's in good hands.
[tense music]
♪
[alarm sounding]
- [whooshes]
- They're back, aren't they?
One of the Godspeed clones is attacking
the Central City power plant,
and if he takes it out like
he did with the gas station,
the blast radius will
be over 40 square miles.
- All right.
- You should take Allegra
- and Frost with you.
- No,
if the other Godspeed attacks,
they're our last line of defense.
[whooshes]
[alarm blaring]
[intense music]
♪
[whooshes]
Look, I know you're
not the real Godspeed,
but I won't let you
harm this city anymore.
So why don't you just
tell me who sent you.
[roars in modem-speak]
Barry, my algorithm is
translating what Godspeed said.
What is it?
[modem-speak]
"I have him."
Oh, frak, it's a trap!
Get out of there!
[whooshes]
[intense music]
Barry, get out of there!
[whooshes]
Chester, initiate Babel Protocols!
But Barry, if I drop the force field,
you'll be locked out.
Do it now!
♪
[shouting in modem-speak]
[tense music]
♪
[distant bangs]
So what? They couldn't phase through,
so now they're trying to punch through?
How long will the force field hold?
At the rate they're
going, an hour maybe?
[exhales sharply]
Wait, what are you gonna do?
Get reinforcements.
Maybe.
[breathing heavily]
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm just...
just thinking I'm glad
Iris is home and not here.
At least she's safe there.
But I still put the
rest of you in danger.
Hey, man.
Look, we're Team Flash.
Hey, we can handle this.
Plus, look at it this way:
With all the clones
here, the city's safe.
Wait, Chester, is
there a way to evacuate
without raising the force field?
Even if there was,
Caitlin's mid-surgery
with Ultraviolet right now.
So if she stops...
- Allegra's cousin might die.
- [distant booms]
All right, we need a new plan.
- Fast.
- Yeah, on it.
I'm gonna check in with Iris.
Hey, Iris.
You must still be resting, that's good.
Um...
I'd come check on you in
person, only it's kinda
turned into a hell of a
day here at the ole office.
Anyway, um...
I know it's supposed to
be one of the happiest days
of our lives, and I
don't want you to worry.
Just rest.
But know that whatever happens,
I'm gonna do everything I can
to keep you and the baby safe.
[gasps] A-ha!
[laughs] I knew it!
You're having a baby!
I'll check in with you later, love you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Chester,
but we haven't told anybody yet.
So if you could please
help me keep it that way...
Oh, no, no, I got you, I got you.
- Consider it locked and zipped.
- Okay.
But whoa...
a little baby speedster! [chuckles]
Maybe his first steps
will be a "fathwoom."
It's a girl, not a boy.
Wait, have... have you
already met this kid?
- Um...
- Is this like a
"Back to the Future" type thing?
Yeah, well, not exactly.
Then how do you know the gender?
'Cause relatively speaking,
you just knowing you have a kid
introduces a whole new
set of temporal variables,
all of which can have
an effect on present
and future timelines...
and change what was once
predetermined outcomes.
I guess I don't know for sure.
[distant boom]
I mean, I have seen so many
different versions of our future.
[rumbles]
Just like the Godspeeds.
If it looks like those clones
are gonna break through,
I want you to hide in the Time Vault.
Cisco turned it into a
panic room before he left,
just in case I ever
went Dark Flash again.
Nothing can get inside.
Oh, snap, I completely
forgot why I came here!
I have a plan.
- So, remember that trap from earlier?
- Yeah?
That was the Godspeed clones
creating a set of variables
designed to predict a fixed outcome...
That you would come to
save the power plant.
But they didn't predict
that you'd get away.
Which means that our best
defense against them would be...
The unpredictable.
[rumbling]
H-how much longer?
Allegra, honey, she's gonna be fine.
- [rumbles]
- Okay, but...
how can you do that
with all hell breaking loose out there?
I don't have a choice.
[rumbles]
[door whooshes]
Oh, like you're really surprised.
[distant booms]
Well, that's getting worse.
Guess those two Godspeeds
need a place to crash, huh?
Can't be good.
There's six of them now.
And if they get in here,
they could kill us all.
You brought Derek and Nancy.
It's worse than I thought.
First,
I need you to promise me
that if I give these to you,
you won't stab me in the
back the first chance you get.
- [sighs]
- I'm serious, Mark.
Today, you need to be a good guy.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because I'm not a good guy.
Don't you know that?
It's why you're attracted to me.
Please, can we not do that right now?
- Fair enough.
- [distant boom]
If you really want my help,
then you need to at
least try to speak to me
in a way that someone
like me can understand.
'Cause I'm no hero.
I'm never gonna be.
Fair enough.
If those six speedsters
get in here, we're screwed.
So I need all the backup I can get.
'Cause I don't wanna die,
and I'm pretty sure you don't either.
[distant booming]
I'm in.
It takes a lot to gain my trust.
Break it, you won't get it back.
♪
[sighs] So what's the plan?
So here's the plan.
You know how those
Godspeed clones use that
- modem-speak to communicate?
- Yeah, yeah.
Well...
I can take audio of it,
and then I can transmit
that sound through CCPD's
emergency alert system.
- Like this.
- [modem-static blaring]
Yeah, okay, now,
imagine one of these
staticky clone voices
coming through every
speaker, every radio,
and every cell phone in Central City.
It would be like trying to
talk to a friend over
a loud dance floor.
Impossible, right? And...
They wouldn't be able to
predict where to go first.
And in the confusion, Frost, Mark, and I
would have a chance to take
them down one at a time.
And I can boost the signal loud enough
to scramble their brains
like eggs for good measure.
But first, I gotta prep the CCPD server
by uploading the signal.
How long will that take?
- Five minutes?
- [rumbles]
Make it four.
- Got it.
- [keys clacking]
[monitors beeping]
Is... is that supposed to be happening?
No.
Whatever Black Hole did,
removing the chip has
caused some sort of
systemic neural trauma.
I-I don't understand.
The anesthesia should be working.
W... she's hurting, you
have to do something.
What I have to do is finish
this and close the wound.
Okay, hey,
Caitlin...
can I try something?
[music builds]
♪
[exhales]
[monitors beeping]
[music softening]
♪
Her reaction's stabilizing.
What did you do?
The only thing I could.
I can share my feelings with others now.
So I gave Esperanza
the peace that I feel
knowing that you and Caitlin
and the rest of Team Flash are out there
saving the world,
one day at a time.
[intense music]
♪
[alarm beeping]
Barry, we have a big problem.
Brute force and phasing
didn't work, so now...
They figured out something better.
Draining energy from
the forcefield itself,
like they would with my speed.
[power shutting down]
[intense music]
[monitor beeps]
[alarm blaring]
We have a perimeter breach.
[whooshes]
[triumphant modem-speak]
He's calling the others.
Chester, get out of here.
[intense music]
♪
[panting]
Gideon.
Gideon, secure the room!
Tachyon nullifiers activated,
Chester P. Runk.
Time Vault secured.
[whooshes]
Can I change my mind about helping?
Too late.
[modem-speak]
Chester P. Runk, multiple Godspeeds
are assaulting S.T.A.R. Labs.
Do you need assistance
formulating a plan?
I already had one, Gideon.
I was gonna pipe their
clone-speak into CCPD systems
and confuse the hell out of them,
but, you know, I'm stuck in a room.
Would you like to
play the signal through
S.T.A.R. Labs' intercom system instead?
Yes, Gideon! [laughs excitedly]
Yes, I would!
And hopefully, this will
give Barry and the others
the distraction that they need.
Okay, Gideon,
pipe audio file number 2808
into every room in this facility.
And crank it... I mean, "P. Funk" loud.
Of course.
[modem-static blaring]
[modem-static continues]
[The Prodigy's "Diesel Power"]
♪
♪ Yo, I used to check out
lyrics upon the format ♪
♪ Built with skill, with technique ♪
♪ Computer ADAT ♪
♪ My lyrical form is
clouds on your brainstorm ♪
♪ I get hyped think, thought, flow ♪
♪ Acrobat, sink the
track, pump the track ♪
♪ Dance missions, clubs
like spores react ♪
♪ By strobe visions ♪
♪ And hurrying more reflects ♪
♪ On the dance floor ♪
♪ Blowing up and having
mad people showing up ♪
♪ Packing crowds, jam packed venues ♪
♪ Needles collapse while
atmosphere continues ♪
♪ Sprinkle that, Win it like that ♪
♪ Move it like that, hitting like that ♪
♪ The melody is phat ♪
♪ Yo, I'm on the energy source ♪
♪ The cosmic boss with Prodigy ♪
♪ Flipping astrology ♪
♪ My intellects devour ♪
♪
♪ With diesel power ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[modem-static blaring]
♪ Mono 7-0-6 ♪
♪ 8-0-7-3, 4-21 ♪
♪ Robot-sonic ♪
[driving hip-hop beats]
♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[grunts]
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[modem-speak]
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[music stops abruptly]
Oh, crap.
Oh.
[dark music]
♪
[whooshes]
Come on!
[modem-speak]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[exciting music]
♪
[grunting]
[whoosh]
[all shouting in modem-speak]
[yells, winces]
[pained grunting]
[sonic boom]
[pants]
[energy booms]
What the hell?
Ultraviolet's recovering,
but she's gonna be okay.
Good.
Thanks, both of you.
Without that chip, she's free.
Now I just have to help
her adjust back to...
you know, normal.
Yeah, well, with you in her corner,
that'll be easy-peasy.
Thanks, Chuck.
'Cause with everything that's going on,
we're gonna need all
the help we can get.
Allegra's right.
How do we stop a dozen Godspeeds?
Oh, yeah, Barry, how much of
your speed did they steal?
Barely any.
The other clones attacked the first ones
before they could do any real damage.
But why fight each other?
Yeah, and why would any Godspeed
wanna protect the Flash?
I don't think they wanted to help me.
I think they were trying
to kill the other six.
Speedsters fighting speedsters?
Yeah, that ain't no
regular bad guy battle.
Whatever it is, we're
stuck in the middle of it.
All this time,
we assumed the Godspeeds were aligned.
But if they're not...
It's a civil war.
[suspenseful music]
You know, technically...
we didn't win.
But we are alive.
Something I didn't think
would be the case an hour ago.
That...
is cause for celebration.
Now I guess that you're done with me,
you're not gonna let
me spend the night, huh?
[coughs]
Uh...
No one's kicking you out.
Not yet.
Wow.
One little near-death experience.
Are we becoming friends?
You tell me.
Well, you gotta admit,
we do have explosive chemistry.
It's kinda like sucrose and
potassium chlorate with heat.
[laughs]
What a nerd.
[chuckles]
You know, when those two
Godspeeds had us pinned,
I really thought that was it.
But somehow,
I was okay with it.
Can I tell you why?
It was because you were with me.
And somehow,
knowing that you would be
the last face that I would see
or the last voice
that I'd hear...
just made everything okay.
Everything.
I didn't think we were
gonna make it, either.
But we did.
What are you thinking about now, Mark?
You, Snowflake.
[bang, clatter]
What the hell was that?
Sucrose and potassium chlorate my ass.
Mark!
- Barry?
- Mm.
Stop worrying.
You're gonna be a great dad.
- [chuckles]
- We all know it.
Thanks, Cecile.
I just...
wish Iris was feeling
better and could be here.
I know, I know.
But you're gonna call
her as soon as we're done.
Yeah.
Okay, what is it?
Oh, I was just thinking. I'm...
I hope our child has
Iris's heart.
And her fearlessness.
Oh, she will.
It's... it's negative.
I don't...
I...
I mean, my dream.
Nora said everything was gonna work out.
It will, honey.
- I know it will.
- How?
If... if this isn't the
future for me and Iris...
What is?
[crickets chirping]
Creyke hasn't shown up all day.
Maybe he moved on?
No, he'll be here.
I can feel it.
It's strange,
being so close to
almost closing this case.
Are you worried about
arresting an old friend?
After we joined the service,
I went into intelligence.
Adam ended up in special forces.
Turns out he had a knack for killing.
Oh.
One the army used to great effect.
Something changed in him, West.
And I didn't see it.
And since you two grew
up so much alike...
Now you're worried
that whatever broke him
might break you too?
All our lives, we had
each other's backs.
'Till he stabbed me in mine.
Left me for dead.
What could change a
person enough to do that?
What the hell is that?
Get out of the car!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --