Barry, we're in position
to attack. Where are you?
Sorry! I... I still have a few things
to take care of on the way.
- [GRUNTS]
- Ah!
[EXCITING MUSIC]
[WHOOSHING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[WHOOSHING]
So just the banana?
♪ ♪
["GRANDMA GOT RUN OVER
BY A REINDEER" PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
[SCREAMING]
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[CONTINUES SCREAMING]
You okay? Don't worry about that guy.
I just dropped him off at CCPD.
Saved by Mr. Flashy himself!
Oh, I've gotta give you
a nice, big reward.
Oh, no, that's not necessary.
I can't accept your money, I...
But it's butterscotch.
- Oh.
- [LAUGHS]
Thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
Flash, we're getting hit hard!
- We're not gonna make it!
- [WHOOSH]
Hold on, Chester. I'm on my way.
♪ ♪
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
- 19! Critical hit!
- Oh!
Uvarkk the Cleric attacks
with the Sacred Flame.
Way stronger than my glaive.
Uvarkk vanquishes The Lich,
saving our merry band of adventurers.
Radiant damage, am I right?
♪ ♪
What the hell's going on?
[THRILLING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[LAUGHTER, CHATTER]
The Dungeon Kraken is awoken
by Thodris' fear
and pounces, pinning
the warrior to the ground.
There's no escape for him now.
Save him! Somebody... somebody save him!
Help me, Karash the Orc!
You're my last hope.
- You...
- It's my turn?
- Yeah.
- Use your vorpal sword,
- use your vorpal sword.
- Wh... my what?
What do you do, Karash?
I... I tell the thing
to raise its little claws,
and read it its Miranda Rights.
- [ALL GROAN]
- Oh, come on.
Guys, this game is not for me.
- I'm sorry.
- All right, Joe.
- Come on.
- All right, no, look, look...
Let's take a break. Let's just...
Let's take a break. Refill our goblets.
- Okay.
- [LAUGHTER]
Yeah, you were acting, bro.
- Sorry.
- No, I get it, I get it.
This is a little different
for family game night.
[LAUGHS] A little.
It's got a 600-page instruction booklet.
Well, I... I read the whole
thing in, like, two seconds.
[MOCKING] Oh, I read that in,
like, two seconds.
I don't sound like that. But, look, I...
I was a little intimidated, too.
But Iris made me give it a try,
and we wound up having...
a great time that night.
That sounds like my baby girl.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Any sign of her?
Nora says that Iris
is still in the future,
which means she's okay.
The path we're on now
should lead us to her.
Well, the timeline has split
you and Iris up before,
and it never holds, so...
I have to have faith in that
just like you do.
[PHONE BUZZING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hey, um, I gotta go to CCPD.
Kramer needs you?
No, not Kramer.
♪ ♪
You trying to make me
feel like I ran back in time?
[DRAMATIC CHORD]
What can I say, Allen?
This'll always be home.
[CHUCKLING]
And, don't worry, I covered for you.
While The Flash was stopping
robberies in Central City,
Barry Allen has been in his lab
all day with me.
Captain Kramer'll never suspect a thing.
Thanks, Chief, but it's fine.
She already knows I'm The Flash.
What? You told her already?
- She just got here.
- Actually,
she figured it out on her own.
Well, I figured it out first.
- You did.
- I mean, good for her.
Uh, so, you said you had a case for me?
Uh, yes.
A high profile theft at a Mercury Labs
came across my desk.
- Uh, what is it?
- We thought it was
a simple smash-and-grab job by a thief
who wiped the security cameras
clean before they left.
But the inventory report says
they made off
with a Gamma Absorption Array.
The Mercury tech unit says
a device like that
in the wrong hands
can cause all kinds of damage.
Yeah, they're right, I mean,
arrays like this use bursts
of gamma radiation to interact
with cellular structures.
It could be used for almost anything,
from growing super crops
to taking out an entire army.
So the only way to solve our
mystery is to catch our thief.
[THRILLING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I will never get used to that.
[CHUCKLES] So, uh, tire
prints from the crime scene
have traces of residual calcium plates,
most commonly found in the barnacles,
which grow directly
onto a hard substrate,
like a boat or a dock.
So the perp is probably hiding out
somewhere near the shipyard.
Okay, I will get Captain
Kramer up to speed.
Great work, as usual.
Thank you.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
So you know what happens now.
[SIGHS]
Oh, I bring in our mystery thief.
[SNAPS]
[WHOOSHING]
That, I'm used to.
Chester, bring up the plans
to the shipyard warehouses.
Our perp is hiding somewhere out here.
Might as well list the whole area
on villainhideouts.com.
These warehouses haven't been
in use in seven years.
- [WHOOSHING]
- [PANTING]
I think I found something.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Tire treads match those
from the crime report.
♪ ♪
Great gamma gadget!
Barry, that van must have been shielded,
'cause as soon as you opened it up,
the radiation readings
spiked through the roof.
[SIGHS] It's the gamma array.
Whoever stole this made
some seriously advanced mods.
I'm gonna run it back
for a full analysis.
[MENACING LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
Oh, you won't be running
anywhere much longer.
Hey.
♪ ♪
You're the bad guy, aren't ya?
You wanna save us both
some time and tell me
what these mods do, before I
take you to prison, or after?
♪ ♪
Why don't I show you?
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[EXPLOSION BOOMS]
♪ ♪
Flash, are you okay?
Flash?
[LAUGHS]
Enjoy what time you have left, Flash.
Ow, what hit me?
Gideon, run a full diagnostic.
Commencing full-body diagnostic scan.
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTS]
Multiple biological
abnormalities detected.
What? What...
What kind of abnormalities?
Moderate signs
of arthritis, hearing loss,
osteoporosis, high
cholesterol, and heartburn.
That's what that is?
Holy Benjamin Button, Barry.
Every cell in your body
has deteriorated suddenly.
It says here you've
aged 30 years overnight.
How's that possible?
He looks exactly the same.
It looks like the blast that hit Barry
was mostly absorbed
by his internal biology.
Organs, cardiovascular
system, bones, joints.
He may look young on the outside,
but on the inside,
things are very different.
- Can we reverse it?
- Maybe, but I'd need
the device that whammied you
to even try.
- Oh.
- All right, let's find
Dr. Creep Face and get it.
But, why build an "old gun" anyway?
I don't know, but whatever the reason,
it's probably dangerous.
I'm gonna go back to his
warehouse and search for clues.
Hang on, hang on. Do you really think
it's a good idea for you to go
in the field like this?
Do we even know... has this
affected your powers?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Uh, Gideon, run a meta efficiency test.
Test initiated.
We'll start with phasing.
♪ ♪
[WHIRRING]
[LIGHT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
[GROANING]
- Oh!
- [WHIMPERS]
Phasing unsuccessful.
Phasing's pretty advanced.
- Um, yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
Let's, uh, try something easier.
Wind arms.
[SNAPS] Wind arms are easier.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my...
- [GRUNTING]
Come on! Ah!
- Test complete.
- I almost had it.
Meta ability has decreased by 29%.
Okay, Barry, honey, why
don't you come sit down?
I'm fine.
I can, uh... I can feel
the Speed Force inside me.
I just need to stretch my legs.
Get 'em moving. [PANTING]
Figure out what I can still handle.
[GRUNTS]
- [CRASHING]
- Oh!
Ah!
[BARRY GROANING]
[WEAKLY] I'm okay.
♪ ♪
I already updated the software.
Now I gotta give the damn thing a name.
How about, Vacuum?
- There's the Joe West I know.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Good to see you, man.
- Hey, David.
Hey, hey, hey. Oh!
Barry told me you'd be around.
Sorry, I've just been screaming
at electronic equipment
for the last couple hours.
I wanted to see how
retirement was treating you.
I was expecting all-day football,
or a wine and jazz room,
not a... an appliance minefield.
Yeah, ever since Jenna's
been in pre-school,
I've had more time
on my hands... a lot more.
You know, you can just use
some of this time
to find ways to relax.
When Rob's mom retired,
she took up meditation.
Well, that sounds like a lot of
sitting around doing nothing.
Plus, all these little
projects keep me busy.
The problem is, each one of them comes
with a novel-long instruction booklet.
I mean, you have to learn to program
a computer to just use a mop.
You know what?
Rob and I got his mother
one of these last Christmas.
♪ ♪
Let's see what you're working with.
[WHOOSHING]
[FEET SLIDING]
- Hey!
- Hey.
You look better. How you feel?
Um, just a little tired.
But as long as I keep it under Mach 10,
I can maintain control of my speed.
And that's more than fast
enough to catch this guy.
Right, but we know that
Allegra can handle herself
out in the field, so when
crazy scientist guy comes back,
then she and Chester can handle it,
- and I can even help out with...
- Cecile,
I can't risk any of you
getting hit with that machine.
And you heard Chester.
The only way to cure me
is to get that gamma array back,
and the fastest way
to do that is with my speed.
But, are you sure
that this is the right way to do it?
It just feels like you're racing past
some red flags here.
I mean... is everything okay?
♪ ♪
Guys, we've got a
break in at Magnus Labs.
Another tech facility.
Guess we found our guy.
Uh, Chester, get ready to adjust
that gamma array when I get back.
I won't be long.
[SIGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- [SIRENS WAILING]
- [BEEPING]
High velocity object incoming.
♪ ♪
I assumed correctly you would recognize
a thermal detonator, Flash.
Barry, that's no ordinary grenade.
It's got major bad energy
emanating from it.
He modified it to pack a serious punch.
♪ ♪
This isn't the answer
to getting what you want.
There is only one way
to get what I want,
and it's in here.
I'm going to obtain a
power more precious
than any ever wielded by a superhero.
♪ ♪
How's this for power?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[THRILLING MUSIC FADES]
Cute.
My turn.
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
♪ ♪
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
His heart rate's spiking.
Barry.
Barry!
♪ ♪
Well, there's no permanent damage,
but you're near-sighted now.
Why did your vision go bad?
You didn't have this problem earlier.
That's not the only new thing.
It's just, like...
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I thought he was only supposed
to be old on the inside.
Hey, Chester.
Run my scan results
through Gideon's bio-algorithm,
and let's just... let's
take a detailed look.
Done, and if I'm reading this right,
um, you aged another ten years.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What? How?
Was it the grenade blast?
I don't think so.
It looks like the... the gamma radiation
inside Barry's cells is activated by
- his Speed Force energy.
- Wait, Chuck,
are you seriously saying that
the more The Flash runs...
The more he ages.
Barry, you gotta stop using your speed.
Cecile, I have to find this guy.
What... [SIGHS]
Hold on. Maybe Cecile's right.
You almost had a heart attack
back at Magnus Labs.
Plus, if your aging's
showing on the outside,
I can't even imagine what's
going on inside your body.
Guys, I won't let this guy get away.
We still don't even
know what he's planning.
What if he uses this
device on someone else?
And what if you die of old age
- before you can stop him?
- But I won't.
Look, we just need
to track this guy down
as soon as possible and end this.
And I think I know how to start.
[BEEPING]
- You found out who he is?
- Yeah, he wiped
the security cameras
at his first crime scene,
but I showed up before he
had a chance to do it again.
Pulled this photo from the footage
and ran a background check.
Dr. Pytor Orloff.
Former technician at a small R&D lab,
Corbin Taft Industries.
Says here he was fired for using
company resources
on unsanctioned research.
I'm gonna check his old lab at Taft,
see if Dr. Olsen left any clues.
Barry, it's Dr. Orloff.
- Remember?
- That's what I meant.
And I'm gonna need
those contacts, Chester.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Okay, I'm gonna go with you.
- Cecile, I...
- Look, this guy
has surprised us
a couple of times already,
and my powers will feel him coming
if he decides to show up
while we're at his lab.
- Okay.
- Great.
Oh, uh, real quick.
This time, we're gonna take my car.
♪ ♪
[SOCKET WRENCH CRANKING]
Use the provided
triangular hex-bracket tool
to fasten the side brushes.
Yeah, I couldn't find
whatever the hell that is,
so I'm using my trusty,
dusty socket wrench.
Okay, are you sure
that's gonna fit the...
- [SQUEAKING]
- Uhh...
Just a little elbow grease.
All right, let's see
if this thing works.
[LIGHT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BEEPS]
- [ELECTRICITY ZAPPING]
- [BOTH EXCLAIM]
Damn it!
[VACUUM POWERS DOWN]
Why do we need robots
for a man's job anyway?
Jenna's gonna have to learn
what chores are.
Is it... [SIGHS]
Joe, I love ya, man,
but I have not seen you
this frustrated since...
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Do you remember the Steve Palmer case?
Look man, I would
spend months and months
and months on a case
if that's what it took, right?
I mean, obviously it wasn't
easy, but I loved it,
like, I... I loved it.
♪ ♪
Now, I...
Uh, okay, that's enough of that.
I'm calling in a 10-85.
Delay due to coffee break.
You, my friend, need to get
out of this house badly.
Man, let me just clean
up this vacuum mess.
Oh, no, Joe, I'm not asking.
This is an order from
the Chief of Police.
Let's roll!
♪ ♪
All right, you're buying.
- Don't I always?
- True.
Look for Orloff's old work files.
Maybe they can tell us where he's hiding
or what he could be planning.
Usually, these facilities
have strict record keeping.
[DRAMATIC CHORD]
I got it.
♪ ♪
Okay.
[BEEPING]
♪ ♪
What was that?
I think it was a facial ID scan,
like how your phone unlocks.
♪ ♪
That's a countdown
to wipe the hard drive.
If we don't hack past this now,
all the data is gonna be erased.
I need to run this to Chester.
- Wait, no, Barry, you can't...
- I don't have a choice.
We need to find out
what's on this hard drive!
Well then, there's
got to be another way,
- let's take a second and think...
- I don't have time.
- We need to run this to CCPD.
- CCPD?
You mean S.T.A.R.?
Barry, that's the second time
you forgot something.
I didn't forget it, I misspoke.
Okay, we need to go, right now.
[SIGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[WIND HOWLING]
Where did you take us?
♪ ♪
[GASPING]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
Barry, we are a long way from home.
Barry?
♪ ♪
[PANTING]
How did we get here?
♪ ♪
Connections of the hippocampus
are showing gradual decay.
While cognitive functions have
returned to normal levels,
Barry Allen's memory loss
will likely be a recurring event.
[SIGHS]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Barry...
how you feelin'?
I feel like we don't have time for this.
I'm fine now.
Barry, I don't think
you get how serious this is.
According to your latest
bioscan results from Gideon,
if you use that much speed again,
it could kill you.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Then we need to find Orloff
more than ever.
All right, getting his gamma array
is still the only way to cure me
and stop whatever he's planning.
Chester, were you able
to save his laptop?
[SIGHS] I managed to stop the countdown.
But it's gonna take some more
time for me to hack inside.
Okay, well let me know when you do.
In the meantime,
everyone watch satellites
for gamma ray spikes in the city.
Right now, that's our only
other means to find Orloff.
I'm gonna visit the Starchives,
see if I can find anything
to safely hold the gamma emitter
when I bring it back.
♪ ♪
Sometimes, I feel like
time's chasing me.
I spend half my day trying to keep up
with the changes all around me.
Like, I had to set a reminder
on my phone to pick up Jenna
from her playdate, an hour from now.
It's like I don't recognize my life.
But maybe that's what happens
when you have more years
behind you than you have ahead of you.
You spend so much time looking back
that it's really hard to move forward.
♪ ♪
Hmm.
Joe, um,
your life isn't the problem.
Retirement isn't the problem.
It's you.
You don't wanna move forward.
You've always been like this.
Stuck in your ways.
Not really willing to embrace
anything new.
My ways put hundreds
of criminals behind bars.
♪ ♪
Mm-hmm.
Do you know why it took us so long
to close the Steve Palmer case?
It wasn't just 'cause of the dead ends.
It was because you refused
to learn the new CCPD computer system.
[SIGHS] Listen, now...
my file folders worked just fine.
Maybe.
And maybe you spent a lot of
extra time filling out forms.
Time you could've spent doing
the job you love instead.
Joe, your life has always been changing.
Think about it.
You were a single father who took in
a traumatized boy who just
lost both of his parents.
And you raised that boy
to be one of the most
extraordinary humans
to ever walk the Earth.
♪ ♪
Joe, you raised The Flash.
And he didn't get his
greatest superpowers
from a bolt of lightning.
He got them from a man who embraced
an unexpected time in his life.
He got them from you,
Joe West.
♪ ♪
Now imagine all the amazing new things
Joe West can still do with his life.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey.
I've been looking for you.
I thought you were going
to the Starchives.
♪ ♪
Barry?
I...
forgot where it was.
Okay.
All right, come on, talk to me.
♪ ♪
Barry, what's going on with you?
You're not normally this stubborn.
What are you trying to prove, honey?
You know you're scaring all of us.
♪ ♪
I'm scared too, Cecile.
Orloff's still out there, and I can't...
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
I feel myself withering.
♪ ♪
When I run, my bones ache.
Like they're made of glass, and...
my hands won't stop shaking.
I'm always out of breath,
and it's getting harder...
♪ ♪
It's getting harder to...
remember the people I love.
♪ ♪
My friends.
Nora, Bart, Joe.
♪ ♪
Even Iris.
What if I forget who she is...
before she comes back?
♪ ♪
I thought I had plenty
of time to get Iris back...
♪ ♪
And live my life with her.
Now it's all fading away,
like my body.
And now, with my mind going, too...
it's like losing everyone you love...
♪ ♪
All at once.
[SNIFFLES]
♪ ♪
You know, you're not the first superhero
that I've seen go through this.
♪ ♪
No, oh, I knew one badass fighter,
through and through...
my grandmother.
♪ ♪
And just like you, she was always
running from one adventure to the next.
♪ ♪
[CHUCKLES]
Not just when she was
young and spry, either.
Oh, no, no.
I mean, I'm talking well
into her golden years.
♪ ♪
She never lost her love for life, and...
that inspired me to do more with my own.
♪ ♪
She sounds like an amazing woman.
Here's the thing, though.
[SOFT UPLIFTING MUSIC]
She never feared getting old.
Mm-mm.
She made a choice.
She knew if she was
gonna run out of time,
then, damn it, she was
gonna use the time
that she had to live exactly
the life that she wanted.
♪ ♪
See, she knew...
she knew that no one could outrun time.
♪ ♪
But you can embrace it.
Barry, nobody's saying
that you can't go get the bad guy,
but don't let your fear
of running out of time
cloud your ability to see
the right way to do it.
- [COMPUTER CHIMES]
- Guys.
I finally broke the encryption code
on Orloff's laptop.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
So I took a look through Orloff's notes
on the gamma array.
He is a next-level genius, no doubt,
but unfortunately,
he's planning something
seriously dangerous.
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
This is what he stole from his
second lab raid.
It's an energy amplifier
that could boost
his machine's output a hundred fold.
So he wants to make everyone old? Why?
His research is obsessed with finding
the scientific equivalent
of a fountain of youth.
He just wants to be young again,
and I think he's figured out how.
By taking it from other people.
Can you pull up the
security footage I used
to run his background?
[TYPING]
Look at his hair.
He's not gray anymore...
His machine works,
only it needs to absorb a lot
of energy to make him
even just a few years younger,
which is why he stole the amplifier.
Chester, what happens when he finishes
connecting the amplifier
to the gamma array?
♪ ♪
He becomes immortal.
And the city, everyone in it,
all age hundreds of years in an instant.
We'll all be dust.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[BREATHING EXCITEDLY]
[WHIRRING INTENSIFYING]
♪ ♪
[LAUGHS]
[ALARM BLARING]
We've got a massive radiation spike.
I'm reading 2,000 millisieverts...
wait, no, 3,000.
Orloff just activated his machine.
Okay, we know where he is.
Let's take him down. Pull the plug.
No, it's not gonna be that easy.
I mean, look at these readings.
If we shut it down too suddenly,
there would be a cascading
degradation cycle
in the gamma isotopes.
Meaning we can't just turn it off.
It's already built up
too much of a charge.
Shutting it off now would cause
the gamma rays to explode out,
affecting hundreds of people.
We better think of something quick.
In a few minutes,
it'll be charged enough
to affect the whole city.
Is there any way we can slow it down?
No.
We have to speed it up.
Guys, the gamma radiation siphons energy
from human cells, speeding up
the biological aging process.
Like what's been
happening to me all day.
But if we fed it more energy
than it can handle...
The amplifier would
have to kick into overdrive
to match the high energy
consumption rate.
It would burn out the machine.
Okay, what do we got that
can put out that much energy?
Me.
No.
Barry, you remember what Chester said.
If you use your speed again,
it could kill you this time.
I have to try.
If I die or it ages me to 100,
I'm not afraid anymore.
You're right, Cecile,
I can't outrun time,
but I can embrace it,
and I can choose to spend
every moment I have left
trying to save innocent lives.
♪ ♪
Then run, Barry.
Run.
[THRILLING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[WHOOSHING]
[BARRY PANTING]
You don't... you can't...
Yes, I can, and I am.
[BEEPING]
Orloff's machine just
hit 100,000 millisieverts
of radiation... that's
fully charged, Barry.
Whatever you're gonna do,
you gotta do it now.
You're out of time, Flash,
and slower than ever.
It looks like everyone in Central City
is running out of time, except me.
[WHIRRING INTENSIFIES]
♪ ♪
[EXPLOSION BOOMS]
[FLASH WHIRRING]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
I don't understand. What's Barry doing?
He just matched the gamma
machine's energy output,
stopping it from expanding,
but if he's gonna overcharge it,
he's gonna have to hit
some savage velocity.
[BEEPING]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's having a heart attack.
How much longer can he hold out?
Biologically, he's over 100 years old.
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
♪ ♪
No. Ah...
No!
♪ ♪
- [LAUGHS]
- He did it!
[LAUGHTER AND RELIEVED SIGHS]
♪ ♪
Wait, what... what's... what's wrong?
Wait.
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
♪ ♪
Barry... Barry, what happened?
My readings are saying that you're...
Better than ever.
♪ ♪
My years, my time!
It's all gone!
♪ ♪
What do I do now?
My advice:
embrace the time
you have left in prison.
[LIGHT MUSIC]
He looks good.
- Is he good?
- Oh, yeah.
No, that boy's doing better than good.
Barry forcing the gamma array's
field backwards
completely inverted its energy charge.
So young man Orloff became old,
but not only did old man Barry
become young again,
you completely regenerated
and then some.
Hold on, are you saying I'm...
Sorry to break it to you, kid,
you're not in your 30s anymore.
How old am I?
29.
But y'all know what that
means, though, right?
♪ 30th birthday party next year ♪
[TOGETHER] ♪ 30th birthday
party next year ♪
- [LAUGHTER]
- Yeah!
I gotta tell you, a party is the least
we can do for the man
who saved us all today.
I just stopped being stubborn,
found the best way to use
the time I had left.
Well, you'll be happy to know Dr. Orloff
is gonna spend the rest
of his time in Iron Heights.
That's thanks to you guys.
You watched out for me,
even when I wasn't
watching out for myself.
Don't sweat it, boss.
Why don't you keep getting some rest,
- and we'll see you later?
- Yeah.
Hey, Cecile.
I owe the most to you today.
I'm sorry I didn't listen sooner.
I know your grandma
would be proud of you.
♪ ♪
I hope so.
I would consider myself lucky
if one day I could
be half of the role model that she was.
You already are.
[LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
So you're a Meta, too?
Yeah, I used to be, like,
a human light bulb,
- but now...
- She's a hell of a lot more.
Oh. So what's your code name?
Uh...
You know, Barry used to be The Streak,
and then he became The Flash.
What do people call you?
I don't know.
I... I've never really
thought about it before.
But I like to keep a low profile, so...
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Uh... okay, Joe, I'm thinking
we tweak the quest.
We can set it in CCPD.
Maybe we solve a homicide?
We could do that, or...
[SWELLING DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ALL GASPING]
- [ALL EXCLAIM]
- Yes!
What if Karash the Orc
used Vorion root-induced
barbarian rage...
Uh-huh?
- And his vorpal sword...
- [LAUGHTER]
To kick some Dungeon Kraken ass?
ALL: Yes!
I've been doing a little light reading
in that handbook, there, children,
and once I show y'all how
to play this game,
I'm gonna teach y'all Spades,
and y'all gonna need a manual for that.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [PHONE BUZZING]
That was not bad!
I'm sorry, I gotta take this, hold on.
You guys keep...
- You shall not pass!
- [LAUGHTER]
Carla, hey. What's up?
[EERIE MUSIC]
No, I thought Caitlin was with you.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
[KNOCKING]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT NOISES]
Caitlin?
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[LIQUID BUBBLING]
♪ ♪
Barry?
Caitlin, are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Your mom called trying to find you.
You said you were staying with her,
but she says she hasn't
seen you since the funeral,
that you haven't returned her calls.
I changed my mind.
Okay, well, what's... what is going on?
♪ ♪
I've been working on some stuff.
What is it?
♪ ♪
You know you can ask
for my help with anything.
♪ ♪
I know I can, but...
But what?
Caitlin, talk to me. I mean...
♪ ♪
- Okay, I...
- What's this doing here?
I know how this looks.
Caitlin, what's this doing here?
Barry, just listen to me.
The mirror gun split Frost and me
into two people once before.
It took her from my subconscious
and gave her a body,
so I've been running tests
over and over again,
and there must still be
a piece of Frost inside of me.
So, if I can access those latent pieces
in my subconsciousness,
then I can bring her back.
♪ ♪
Okay, I... I know what
you're thinking, and frankly,
if I was in your shoes,
I'd probably be thinking
the same thing, but just for one second,
imagine this isn't Frost
that we're talking about.
What if we could bring your mom back?
Or your dad?
What would you do to make
that possibility a reality?
♪ ♪
We don't have to say goodbye to Frost.
Caitlin, losing someone you love
can make it really hard to move on,
but as difficult as it is,
you have to accept that Frost is gone
and that she's not coming back.
♪ ♪
But I don't want to.
I know, but it's the only
way to start living again.
♪ ♪
I can do this.
I have to.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
Barry... Barry, please.
♪ ♪
Barry, don't!
[EXPLOSION BOOMS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
♪ ♪
[BARRY SIGHS SOFTLY]
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
Greg, move your head.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -