I know you.
You have been talking to the
Tattaglia family.. right?
I think you and I can do business.
I need someone strong like you.
I heard you are not happy...
with the Corleone family.
Want to join me?
What's in it for me?
$50,000 to start with.
Not bad!
Agreed?
I kiss your hand, Don Tommasino.
Why are you so far
from the house?
You know I'm responsible to your
father for your life.
The bodyguards are here.
It's still dangerous...
We've heard from Santino
in New York...
Your enemies know you're here.
Did Santino say when
I can go back?
Not yet.
It's out of the question.
Where are you going now?
Take my car.
I want to walk.
Be careful.
Where have all the men gone?
They're all dead from vendettas.
There are the names of the dead.
Mamma Mia what a beauty.
I think you got hit
by the thunderbolt.
In Sicily women are more
dangerous than shotguns.
Did you have a good hunt?
You know all the girls
around here?
We saw some real beauties.
One of them struck our friend
like a thunderbolt.
She would tempt the devil himself.
Really put together.
Such hair, such mouth!
The girls around here are
beautiful... but virtuous.
This one had a purple dress...
And a purple ribbon in her hair.
A type more Greek than Italian.
Do you know her?
There's no girl like that
in this town.
My God, I understand!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
It's his daughter.
Tell him to come here.
Call him.
Fabrizio, you translate.
Come to my house Sunday morning.
My name is Vita“.
What's her name?
It's safer to teach you English!
I know English...
How are things in Palermo?
Michael is teaching me to
drive.. watch, I'll show you.
How are things in Palermo?
Young people don't respect
anything any more...
times are changing for the worse.
This place has become
too dangerous for you.
I want you to move to a villa
near Siracusa.. right now.
What's wrong?
Bad news from America.
Your brother, Santino,
they killed him.
Let's go... you promised.
Get the car.
Calo, where is Apollonia?
She's going to surprise you.
She wants to drive.
She'll make a good American wife.
Wait, I'll get the baggage.
Where are you going?
Wait there! I'll drive to you.