You're in, lover.
You are too talented.
This beautiful little battery...
...will power suburban homes
for 10 years, for next to nothing.
And by the time Star Labs
realizes it's missing...
...their competition will have it
in production already.
- You're a genius.
- I know. Let's go.
Oh, Stasia. I'm very disappointed.
But frankly, not totally surprised.
You see, I expected it.
So did I.
No hard feelings. Right, Sam?
Red Line express,
door-to-door delivery.
Hurry up and change.
We're running late.
Me? We could've taken the car
like normal people...
...if you hadn't changed
so many times.
What's the matter?
Nothing's the matter. It's only
the end of the world as I know it.
- Don't you think you're overreacting?
- You don't know my mother.
Tina, slow down.
- Barry, did you have to wear this jacket?
- She's not my mother.
Know how your father drives you nuts?
That's me and my mother.
My friends thought she was so cool,
dropping in from Paris with the latest trend.
She sounds interesting.
Hipper than my dad anyway.
I could never keep up with her.
I think I really disappointed her.
- There you are, Tina.
- Hello, Mother.
Hello, darling.
Why don't you call me Jocelyn.
After all, we're both adults.
My mother, Jocelyn Weller.
This is Barry Allen.
- I think I mentioned him in...
- Oh, the Boy Scout.
My mistake.
Jerk.
- And what do you do, Barry?
- I don't believe it. Barry Allen?
Barry!
I see that you do rather well.
Don't tell me
you don't remember me.
- Stasia Masters.
- It's been a long time, huh, Barry?
- I haven't seen you since...
- High school.
I just got back in to town
for a few days...
...and I guess I was just overwhelmed
to see a friendly face.
Barry, do you mind?
It's been terrific seeing you, Barry.
Bye.
Barry, who was that?
Oh, I did her homework
in high school.
You did her homework,
or you were her homework?
Now, help us with the luggage.
I'll bet you have
an interesting secret life.
Maybe this trip
won't be so dull after all.
Thank you, darling. I'm here for the new
postmodern reconstructivist show.
- I thought you had a car.
- Oh, it's at the lab. We'll have to stop.
That's funny, my wallet's gone.
This crystal is on loan from
the government.
I had to pull a lot of strings
to get it here.
As you can see, it focuses the laser
onto an even tighter beam...
...allowing more accurate nucleic
manipulation of the sample tissue.
Yes, well, I'm sure that's very nice,
darling.
But how can you stand working
in a place that's so sterile?
It's a laboratory, Mother.
Star Labs has been very good to me.
They encourage me to work on my own.
Any daughter of mine
could lock herself away in such...
...an antiseptic environment... But then,
you are your father's daughter as well.
- No cracks about Daddy.
- Sorry.
There are research firms in
more civilized cities. Like New York.
- Central City has a lot to offer. It...
- That's true.
Did you know the corn dog
was invented here?
Yeah. Okay. Wow, look at the time.
I've got morning duty at my lab.
I'll just be...
So you play this game too?
Police sciences, forensic criminology.
- Really?
- Scout's honor.
From Tina's description, I expected
something rather more heroic.
Really?
Heroic. Yeah.
I don't care.
Look, we have a deal,
and you better live up to it.
No.
Listen, Fletcher, the only reason
I came back to this town...
...was to hook up with you.
What do you mean, two days?
Look, I think one of Sam's goons
is on to me.
How? I don't know how.
But if I can't unload this battery...
I'd like a romantic table for two,
next to that lovely blond.
I gotta go.
- Well, what looks good, Marceau?
- I don't know.
How about the poached shark?
Or the eel?
Or the rat?
Buy you lunch, Stasia?
Talent. How's it going?
Doll face, Sam said you'd
be passing through town.
Yeah? Well, give him my best.
He also said you had something of his.
Maybe it's in here, huh?
I can't believe you junk-food junkies
never had a Lucky Dog.
These are the best,
and I should know. Go ahead.
I want two chili dogs with everything,
especially that orange, shiny sauce.
- Oh, Murph, that is pure grease.
- To you, Bellows.
- To me, it's secret sauce. Join me?
- No, thanks.
Corn dog, please.
See, I support our city's heritage.
- Hey, those guys are packing.
- Stay low, Barry. We'll handle this.
Freeze and drop them!
Cover me!
Hey, get out of the street.
Go. Go!
Murph, I lost the other guy.
Things really got nuts after
that cowboy showed up.
- Cowboy?
- Yeah.
- Right before the Flash saved my neck.
- Oh, now it's the Flash and Pecos Bill.
Partner, your brain
is a-jingle-jangle-jingling.
Fletcher. I was right,
Tom's got a line on me.
Now look, if I'm gonna wait for you,
I'm gonna need some help.
What do you mean,
that's my problem?
Okay. Okay, I'll handle it, Fletcher.
But you've got exactly 48 hours
to show up...
...or I'm gonna throw this damn battery
in the river.
Yeah, I love you too.
I'm dead. I'm dead.
I gotta find someplace to hide. L...
I've gotta find someone to help me.
Out of nowhere, this woman
plants a lip-lock on me, right?
It's Stasia. Haven't seen her in 15 years,
since she streaked high school graduation.
- You two were an item?
- No, she ran with a different crowd.
Bikers, outlaws.
I tutored her in chemistry.
- When you guys getting together?
- What?
Come on, dinner, dancing,
skydiving, whatever.
- This isn't high school.
- That's the thing.
It was so fast,
I didn't get her number.
Who says you don't get
a second chance in this life?
Stasia.
You know, I never would've
figured you for a cop, Barry.
I thought you'd be teaching
somewhere.
Helping all those eager young coeds
with their homework.
What are you doing here?
Must have fallen into my purse.
You know, when we were kissing.
Every penny's there. You can count it.
Stasia Masters, this is Julio Mendez.
Hi. I heard a lot about you.
It's hard to believe you and Barry
were in the same class.
Yeah. Well, I better go. There's
a science crime I have to prevent.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Likewise.
So who would have thought,
after all these years, huh?
Well, a lot of things have changed
around here. The city, me.
Tell me about it.
- Well...
- What about this Flash?
I mean, where'd this guy come from?
Your guess is as good as mine, really.
Unclassifiable urban phenomena,
you know.
- Real mystery man, huh?
- Yeah.
What made you come back
to Central City?
Rendezvous with an old boyfriend.
I thought something was still there...
...but things went bad real fast.
He became very abusive.
Story of my life, huh?
Maybe I wouldn't be so screwed up if
I'd dated someone like you in high school.
Anyway, now that my plans
have been shot to hell...
...I gotta figure out
what I'm gonna do next.
I tried calling a couple of my old friends,
but I didn't have much luck.
I guess I should try
and find a hotel...
...but hotels are so cold. Lonely.
Well, I...
You could stay at my...
You could stay with me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh, Barry, you are a lifesaver.
Thank you.
Hey, you.
I didn't hear you, Sam.
You scared the pants off...
You.
- Keep your pants on, Talent.
- How the hell do you do that?
It's all done with mirrors...
...and stolen technology.
- Where's Stasia?
- Well, I had her, but I lost her.
A little interference from
a local creep. The Flash.
The guy gives me the willies.
Comes out of nowhere, then, zip...
...he's gone. Can't be human.
Ectoplasm, that's what I think.
Well, Flash or no Flash, I want you
to find Stasia and bring her to me.
Sure. But I'm telling you, as a friend,
that girl is no-good.
Just find Stasia. And make sure
she has the battery, okay?
- Okay.
- The Central City Star Labs...
...has something of interest.
I think I'll put in an appearance.
Better check that guy
for ectoplasm too.
Mother... Jocelyn.
I'm on my way home.
Where are you going?
But I was cooking dinner tonight.
Okay.
You have the spare keys?
Right. Fine.
McGee, you forget your keys again,
you're fired.
Oh, my God!
Damn it. Wrong one.
I tried the extinguisher,
but it didn't work.
What is this damn mime doing here?
He just popped out of nowhere.
Hey, where are you going?
Put the fire out.
Wait!
I'm losing my mind.
- Dinner was sensational. Thank you.
- Yeah, what I could see of it.
- Was that place dark enough?
- Oh, it wasn't that bad.
Listen, I want to thank you
for letting me stay here.
I really do feel safe with you.
So bottom line on this Flash,
did somebody build him?
- Build him?
- Yeah.
What do you mean?
Like some kind of...
...mad scientist? Some Professor Zoom...?
- Sure. Some eccentric professor...
...in some top-secret lab somewhere. Think
of the fortune to be made on that research.
You know, all we did through dinner
was talk about the Flash.
- I'm feeling left out.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Are you jealous?
- A little.
- Good.
Hello?
Yeah, this is his place. Who's this?
Hold on a second.
- Tina.
- Tina? Tina, hi.
Slow down.
What?
All right, yeah. I'll be right over. Yeah.
Yeah, sure. Bye. Bye.
- I gotta go.
- What, are you and Tina...?
Just friends. We're intimate,
yet platonic.
You know something,
you really are a nice guy.
Yeah, well...
- Make yourself at home.
- Okay.
- I might be a while.
- All right.
- Hurry back.
- Yeah.
Bye.
Yes.
Don't even think about using this
as a chew toy, Fido...
...or you're not gonna have a tail
to wag.
You see what I mean? No burns, nothing.
- Mimes, vanishing firemen.
- You're not the only one hallucinating.
I saw a cowboy, complete with rope tricks,
evaporate in front of me.
I don't know your excuse is,
but I think my mother...
...is pushing me over the edge.
- What? Come on. She just got here.
Yes, and we quarreled all afternoon.
- You need some tea.
- The heating coils are broken.
Not a problem.
It's as if she resents me for not going
with her when she left my father.
Why didn't you?
I was 13 years old. He was crushed.
All of a sudden, I had to play grownup
and take care of him.
I didn't think Mother wanted
to be burdened with a daughter...
...while she was finding herself.
Here, have some tea.
Tina, what's this?
I guess you're not so crazy
as you thought.
That's the most sophisticated
image projection I've ever seen.
- But why? Some practical joke?
- Maybe, it's a distraction for a theft.
That crystal in the laser sight.
- But it's still in its housing.
- Is it?
Tina, you've been robbed.
That crystal's irreplaceable.
It cost a fortune.
- Between this and the California robbery...
- California?
A prototype long-term generator was
taken from our Silicon Valley branch.
My God, Barry,
what am I gonna do?
- It's not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
The Research Bureau didn't want the crystal
to leave Washington, but I insisted.
If we don't get this crystal back,
I'm gonna lose my job.
Then we'll get it back.
Now, a stone that unique would probably
have to be cut before it was sold, right?
A high-density crystal, if it could be
cut at all, would need a powerful laser.
All right, then if the thief
is attempting to cut it...
...we can track abnormal power surges
through the city.
I can break into Water and Power.
Fox and Broom.
The hotel on Fantino.
Damn it. It's useless. I can't cut it.
- It's gonna be hard to sell at that size.
- Yeah, but not impossible.
It's just gonna take a little more time
to find the right buyer. But when I do...
Seven figures?
Maybe eight.
Now, what about the girl?
- She dropped out of circulation.
- Find her, Talent. You owe me.
You know, maybe if I try splitting
the crystal on a different axis.
Sam...
...I don't think you should slice
the rock at all.
I'd rather sell it for one big score.
Be smart, Talent.
You haven't the faintest idea how
to move that stone into the market.
I'll learn.
Hey. Where do you
think you're going?
Well, since you're obviously
not working for me anymore...
...I guess I'll have to find Stasia myself.
- It's not gonna work that way, Sam.
Oh, really? What are you gonna do,
kill me right here? I don't think so.
In here, gentlemen. He's the one
who stole the Star Labs crystal.
Hold on. You got the wrong guy.
What's the deal here?
You're bought, aren't you?
Scudder, you lousy...
Thank you, officers.
I hope you didn't disturb
the other guests.
Well, the Flash.
Did you know that
three East Coast crime families...
...have commissioned studies on you?
- I want the Star Labs' crystal.
- Who put you on to me? Was it the girl?
- What girl?
Look...
...how much for you to forget
you ever saw me, take a walk?
I'm not for sale.
Everybody has his price.
- I've seen this picture.
- I don't think I'm there anymore.
Come on, Fletcher.
It's me.
Yeah, I still got the battery.
But the longer I have to squat in
this burg, the higher the price.
You don't show by tomorrow night,
the deal is off.
You know, some things
I'll put up with.
But getting double-crossed
by the woman I love...
...is definitely not one of them, babe.
- Sam, you don't know how good...
- What?
"How good it is to see you"?
You left me for the wolves, Stasia.
If I'd have been out 10 seconds longer,
they would've caught me.
But you...
...you were too confident.
You left a trail like a tracer bullet.
All I had to do was...
...check your credit cards,
call your travel agent.
Sam, you gotta believe me, baby.
I didn't wanna do it. I was in trouble.
I owed some people money.
Save it. Save it for a new sucker.
I want the battery. Now.
- I sold it.
- Yeah, you sold it?
- I got a line on something...
- You always got a line.
I do, baby. I got a line on
the mother lode this time.
Make me believe.
I can get you the Flash.
You're lying.
- No. I'm not.
- Yeah, you're lying.
I swear to you. I sold the battery
to this eccentric scientist.
- Guy calls himself Professor Zoom.
- Professor Zoom?
Yeah. Turns out he's the guy
who created the Flash.
Some sort of bioengineering process,
something like that.
And he's willing to give you
the formula, huh?
Well, come on, baby,
I can convince him. You know?
Don't be too persuasive, love. Okay?
Come on, he's the paranoid type.
You know how these geniuses are.
- Yeah?
- I'll probably have to be alone...
...to arrange a meet.
- Yeah?
But just think of it. Think of the price
the Flash will bring on the market.
Think of the money.
You can play with my heart...
...but messing with my business
is gonna get you hurt.
I have a reputation to uphold.
You have 24 hours.
But the next few, they belong to me.
You must have had a great time
last night to look this wasted.
- I got no sleep at all last night, all right?
- You dog.
- Come on, give me details.
- No details, no story.
I left the apartment for a couple of hours.
And when I got back, she was gone.
- That's not a good sign.
- No.
Stasia's playing some kind of a game.
I'm being used.
I'd be willing to bet the farm
that you'd stand in line for more abuse.
Barry.
Barry, look.
Every guy has a woman in his life that
will pop up out of nowhere and just...
...turn his whole world upside down.
In my case, it was Elena Tobias.
I don't have any idea what
she's been up to for the last 15 years.
Well, if it's bad, we're definitely
in the position to find out.
No.
Oh, no. No, Julio, come on,
that wouldn't be right.
Come on. No one would know
that you're checking.
How bad could it be?
- Anastasia Masters.
- All right.
Hey, look, you have no choice, pal.
You're a cop, all right?
Take a look. Just petty larceny.
Six months served when she was 20.
Until you get to her last arrest
four years ago.
Industrial sabotage. Hooked up
with a guy named Scudder.
Used high-tech holograms.
Nicknamed Mirror Master.
The file on him is very thin.
So your dream date and Scudder
are connected.
Her dance cards and our mug books
have a lot in common.
I don't wanna believe Stasia's involved
with the crystal theft...
...but anything new on those mirror disks?
- Stolen from a government laboratory...
...along with a holographic camera
small enough to wear on your wrist.
Oh, I'm so depressed about this robbery,
I can barely talk about it.
I didn't actually see the crystal in
the hotel room, but I believe it was there.
And I'm sure the man
was Samuel Scudder.
I'll get that crystal back for you.
And the first step is to find Stasia.
- Meanwhile, how do I deal with this?
- Oh, this. Well...
...the way to get through these things is,
you never talk much about the work. Okay?
And when you do, try to use "duality"
and "juxtaposition" in the same sentence.
It is without a doubt
a skillful juxtaposition of duality.
This is one of the most
beautiful paintings I've ever seen.
A perfect marriage of line and color.
I will take it, sir. It's magnificent.
I'm glad you both could make it.
The work's going over awfully well.
- This city's starved for culture.
- I'm just starved. See you in a minute.
I must say, Barry's quite a surprise.
- He's not like the men you used to date.
- How would you know?
You were never around to see the men
I went out with.
Well, they were so straight
and academic. Like your husband.
You never knew David. He was
a sweet, funny, passionate man.
You never even made it to the funeral.
- I meant to. I was just in the middle of...
- Damned right.
- Always in the middle of something.
- Tina!
You ran out on my father and you ran
out on me. If you want a daughter...
...start acting like a mother.
You going after her?
- I have a show to deal with.
- Jocelyn, wait.
Tina's going through a hard time
right now.
She might lose her job
over the crystal robbery.
I think it would help
if you would just talk to her.
Let her know you're concerned.
Yes, I suppose I should.
Perhaps when I'm through
with all of this.
Oh, it looks like they're selling
another picture.
Excuse me.
You probably hate me, huh?
I'm sorry I disappeared on you
last night.
- I guess you think I'm pretty terrible.
- According to your rap sheet.
- My rap sheet?
- Yeah, when you didn't come back...
...I guess my cop instincts took over,
what can I say?
All right, Barry. I admit it. I'm no angel.
But I've gone straight.
- I have. Honestly.
- What about your boyfriend, Scudder?
- I can explain that.
- Explain it to the feds.
No, wait a second, Barry.
You can't do that.
Okay. Okay, Scudder and I
were involved.
But I wanted to get out of that life.
But he's tracked me here.
That's why I left last night. I only just
got away from him, and now he's back.
Please, Barry. You gotta protect me
from him. Please?
I don't trust you, Stasia.
But Scudder stole something
from a friend of mine at Star Labs...
...and I want it back.
So helping me is gonna help you too.
Right?
He's really a cool dude.
I think he'll lend you the money.
- What? You want me to do what?
- Be Professor Zoom.
You'll pretend to be the guy
who invented the Flash.
Oh, come on. Why would
Scudder ever buy that?
Because the Flash has a big secret,
which means he's a valuable commodity.
Scudder can't afford to pass it up.
So, what we're gonna do is get him to
trade the crystal for the Flash's formula.
- It will never work.
- Trust me. Come on.
All right, how are we gonna convince
Scudder that I'm Professor Zoom?
Attitude, baby. Attitude. Now, wait.
Now let's lose these immediately.
Put these on.
Very nice. Where did you get these,
a trash can?
Don't be such a baby. Now remember,
you are Professor Zoom.
- I am Professor Zoom.
- Brilliant and unstable.
I want you to stay here.
I'm gonna go find Scudder.
Keep an eye on him, please.
Give him a drink.
A kamikaze.
You meet me at Central Rail Station tonight.
I'm not gonna last another day here.
Now, you don't show,
you can forget about the battery.
Oh, and if I play my cards right, I might
just have something else to sell you.
Something that sparkles. Be there.
- Barry? You see what I mean?
- It is you.
- That's a nice 'do, man.
- Act like you don't know me.
- That won't be tough.
- Wait, wait. Wait a minute.
Are you undercover,
or is this your secret life?
No! If you don't want Garfield to find out
who used the lab for a stag party...
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
What? You told me Roger
wasn't having a stag party.
He didn't. I wouldn't lie to you.
- Come on. We'll meet him in the back.
- Okay.
Back here.
- Now remember, be Zoom.
- I am Zoom.
- No, thanks.
- Nothing.
Sometimes it's hard to believe
anything you see.
Anything.
These you can believe.
So you're Zoom.
- How come I've never heard of you?
- I try to keep a low profile.
A man of my talent would be
swamped...
...with requests and offers.
I do not like the attention.
- And you created the Flash?
- Among other things.
You may not know, but I
also invented the video game...
...the LaserDisc, the microwave oven,
the digital watch.
- Of course, others take credit for...
- Shall we get down to business, please?
I think the three of us
should work together.
And just what am I supposed
to bring to this deal?
I understand that you have...
...the laser crystal that disappeared
from Star Labs.
The secrets of the Flash
for the crystal?
Exactly.
May I see the crystal?
A show of good faith is gonna
require a little more than that.
- The battery she sold you.
- Battery?
The battery she sold...
- She's played us both for suckers.
- Stop! Central City Police.
You're under arrest for dealing
in stolen goods.
Snakes! Snakes!
Interesting look, Barry. But aren't you
a few years ahead of yourself on the hair?
- Where have you been?
- I went over to Tina's apartment...
...but she wasn't there.
She hasn't been back, has she?
No.
What an evening. I did well tonight.
These kids are gonna be
very successful.
- It doesn't really matter, though.
- It doesn't matter?
What difference does it make
if I've ruined my relationship with Tina?
Why don't you just talk to her?
Oh, excuse me, Father,
the gallery's closed.
Barry!
An art gallery is a great front.
And you must be their dealer.
Yes, I'm a dealer.
- What's this all about?
- English, huh?
It's an international operation. Okay,
Your Highness, you're coming with me.
Zoom. Or should I say...
...Barry Allen?
Now, tell me, what's a cop doing
trafficking in stolen technology?
Let her go. She has nothing
to do with this.
Answer a few questions then.
The Flash at my hotel room?
- Cooperating with the police.
- And the tricks at the bar?
- Sleight of hand rigged for the sting.
- I think I missed something.
- What happened at what bar?
- Let her go, Scudder.
Don't be silly. She's Stasia's
European connection.
I heard her tell you on the phone the other
night to meet her at Central Station.
You think I'm a black marketeer?
- Oh, that's funny.
- The battery at Star Labs West...
...Stasia stole it from you.
- And now she's played you for a sap too.
She thought she could get her hands
on the battery and the crystal.
I think I'll head her off at the station.
Imagine her surprise when she sees me
instead of you.
Oh, by the way, if you look in the mirror,
you'll see I've left something for you.
The laser couldn't cut through
the crystal...
...but it's more than able to cut a nice
clean hole through the two of you.
Reflecting the beam is just a flourish.
They don't call me the Mirror Master
for nothing.
You've got about
three and a half minutes.
Enjoy them.
- Where's Barry? And where's my mother?
- I don't know. Maybe they eloped.
With your boyfriend? I'm fed up
with your games. I'm calling the police.
Put it down.
Now!
Now, I want you to sit down
and shut up.
I don't want you to make a move
until I'm out that door. You hear me?
- Thanks, doll.
- Wait a second. Wait a second.
You turn me into the cops, you are never
gonna find your mother and Barry.
Think about it.
Start talking.
I'm supposed to meet my fence
at Central Station to sell him the battery.
Scudder's been second-guessing me
ever since I got to this place.
- So maybe he knows about the meet.
- Maybe he doesn't.
I'm the only shot you've got, McGee.
So I suggest we get going.
What do you say?
- What's happening?
- I don't know...
...but I think I'm getting loose.
- Does this happen to you a lot?
- Yeah.
But usually Tina's around
to help me out.
Tina?
Yeah.
There's more to your daughter
than you realize.
- Yes, I suppose there is.
- Right now, you call the police.
I'm headed to Central Station.
- Stasia.
- Oh, Fletch, baby.
You don't know how good it is to
see you. Did you bring the money?
- Who's your friend?
- This is Tina.
She's gonna be working with us.
- Show me the battery.
- It belongs to Star Labs.
Now put the briefcase down
and hands up.
Oh, nice move, McGee. Now what?
Now I take the cash and the battery.
I love double jeopardy.
Come on, the battery.
Wrong, Scudder.
This is the lightning round.
Yeah? Let's see how well you do
in a crowd.
I've had enough of you. All 12 of you.
Here's your crystal. Where's Stasia?
I don't know,
but she's got the money.
Baby, I am rid of Scudder at last.
What do you say we just take
this money and run away to...?
Oh, I don't know.
How about Istanbul?
No, I've been there.
How about Mexico?
I hear Leavenworth's lovely
this time of year.
Come on, buddy, let's go.
You're coming with us.
Oh, Barry.
How come I always fall
for the right guy at the wrong time?
Bad study habits maybe?
All right, lady, you too.
Out of the cab.
- Thanks for the lift to the train station.
- Don't be silly.
It's the least I could do.
And really, best of luck
with this group of artists.
You too. Best of luck
with your research.
This is idiotic. You're my mother,
for God's sakes.
I don't want to do this anymore.
And don't you run out on me again.
Please.
Oh, sweetie.
I had to leave your father.
But leaving you hurt the most.
I never felt part of your life.
And when David died, l...
I just didn't know what to say.
Look, we've got so much to talk about.
I need a vacation soon.
We could meet in New York.
I have to go to London...
I'll cancel it.
New York would be fabulous.
You know, Mother, you can be
a real pain sometimes. But I love you.
I've had it with both of you.
I'm only gonna say this once.
I am freezing in here! So just...
Just stop it with
the cool British reserve, all right?
- You're family, for God's sake.
- He's so American.
Barry, relax. It's all under control.
- It is?
- Don't make me use this.
Oh, not the mime.
Anything but the mime.
[ENGLISH]
www.tvsubtitles.net