[DRONING MUSIC]
The universe is on fire.
Heat. Burning.
A perfect inferno set
against cold, endless nothing.
But within some dimensions,
there exists an aberration.
Life.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I owe you a real ring.
I love you, Ronnie.
♪
I have come to end that life.
I am Deathstorm.
♪
What are you?
Complete, thanks to you.
Now I'll return the favor.
[SNARLS]
[SCREAMS]
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[GROWLS]
[SNARLS]
Get away from her!
[GROANS]
It's still not enough.
But I'll be back.
And this life of yours will end.
Caity?
- [GROANS]
- What the hell was that thing?
I don't know.
Whatever it was, my
lightning didn't affect it.
What's wrong with her?
[WHEEZING]
How do you feel?
Lucky to be alive, so... fine, I guess.
Hold on, it burned her,
but she looks okay
and there aren't any marks or anything.
Let's just call it a win.
What was that thing anyway?
It calls itself Deathstorm.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Hmm. Like Firestorm, only...
It wasn't Ronnie.
It never was.
How do you know that?
Because it told me.
Then what exactly is it?
- And where did it come from?
- I don't know.
But whatever we brought
back from Piedmont Park,
that thing, it isn't human.
It said Ronnie's death gave him life.
And when Ronnie was gone,
it became something more,
something incomplete.
And that I helped make it whole again.
That's why it wanted you to
modify the Firestorm Matrix.
So that I could bring it back
from whatever hell it's been hiding in.
Barry, I'm so sorry.
You were right this whole
time, and I wouldn't listen.
Hey, that's okay.
You just did what any
one of us would have done.
No, Ronnie's been dead for seven years.
And now this thing is back in his place,
all because of me.
You're okay now, and
that's all that matters.
Barry, if Caitlin's right,
if Deathstorm wanted Caitlin
for some creepy resurrection,
why is he trying to kill her now?
I mean, he got what he wanted.
That's what we need to find out.
Well, Chuck is using satellites
to try and figure out
where this thing went.
But if Frost is right and
it's coming back for Caity,
we need to keep her safe.
We will, and we're gonna send this thing
back to whatever hell it came from.
How?
The Cold Fusion Sphere
has been destroyed.
We'll find another way.
- Until then, Frost...
- I'm way ahead of you.
If this matchhead thinks he's getting
anywhere near my sister,
he's gotta go through me first.
Hey, I heard what
happened. How can I help?
Thank you, but we're not even sure
what we're dealing with yet.
Barry.
Look, from the second I
walked into S.T.A.R. Labs,
I could feel how worried you are.
But what I'm sensing,
it's way more than just concern.
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
You're hurting, badly.
Hey, what's going on?
It's Iris.
- Is she okay?
- That's just it. I don't know.
What's even worse is, I don't even know
where she is right now.
What are you talking about?
I thought she was in
Coast City with Sue.
Yeah, she was. Only now...
[PHONE CHIMES, BUZZES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Oh, thank... Cecile, Iris is back.
I gotta go.
[WHOOSHES]
Iris, thank God you're back.
- Sue said you'd vanished...
- No, Barry.
What's wrong?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Renee Wazzo, Tinya's mom.
I'm the last person that she touched,
and she's... gone because of me,
because of my time sickness.
Okay.
But then Sue said that
Tinya attacked you,
that she made you disappear on purpose.
So how did you survive?
Your time sickness.
It must have pulled
you into the Still Force
at that exact moment.
So whatever is making her sick
might have also saved her life.
Okay, that's... that's freaky.
I'm gonna give you guys some space.
I'll be back, okay?
♪
Barry, what happened to Tinya's mom,
I didn't mean to...
I know that.
Look, it's gonna be okay.
[GASPS]
I'm not afraid.
♪
What is it?
Barry, the Still Force,
it's supposed to be a place
where... all time exists,
past, present, and future
but when I was there,
I saw moments from before,
even when I was a
little girl, up to now.
But I didn't see my future.
What if I don't have one anymore?
You do.
With me.
♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[CRYING SOFTLY]
[HISSING]
[WIND HOWLING]
♪
Hello?
[HISSING]
Who's there?
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
So how does one summon a Force god?
Well, I mean,
they've had appointments before,
but usually all Iris
has to do is concentrate,
and Deon knows to appear.
[PHONE BEEPING, BUZZING]
A few weeks ago, I gave Captain Kramer
an emergency alert to summon the Flash,
and this is the first
time she's used it,
- which means...
- It's serious.
As in 'gotta go" serious.
Yeah, but, Iris, I can't
leave you here alone.
Hey, she won't be.
Yeah, no, it's okay.
- Okay, but...
- Barry,
with everything that's happening
and now with Deathstorm,
people need you more than ever.
Go.
Yeah, I get it.
Waiting sucks.
You know what might make it suck less?
A five-course meal from Angelino's
delivered straight to your door.
We could eat our problems away.
Food as a distraction?
- You're a bad influence.
- I'll take that as a yes.
[LINE TRILLING]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[PHONES RINGING]
A skull-faced thing
flew down from the sky
and took your wife?
Ma'am, please, try to remain calm.
And nothing else was
burnt, just the body?
Can you describe the figure?
A living skeleton.
♪
This is the tenth burn
victim in half as many months,
and now you're saying
it's gonna get even worse?
It already has.
Sorry to interrupt, Captain.
Joe, Flash.
But we've got three more
confirmed burn vics downtown,
another two uptown, and at least four
reported on the lower east side.
And the phones are ringing off the hook
about a skull-faced demon.
He calls himself Deathstorm.
Have Matlin call in
every unit for backup.
We need all hands on deck for this.
Copy.
Glad to have you with us, Flash.
So why is this thing
burning people alive?
We're not sure, but
the current theory ism
to feed off their grief.
How do we fight him?
We don't know yet.
One thing I do know about Team Flash is,
they'll find a way.
I don't know what's more terrifying,
that this Deathstorm
can turn up anywhere,
or that not even the Flash is
powerful enough to stop him.
Well, Kristen, I know
this seems hopeless...
No, it's not just that.
Joe, how the hell did you
used to deal with this?
For the past 17 years,
I've been either a soldier or a cop,
and nothing I've done
prepared me for this.
Look, I hear you... when I was captain,
I fought evils in this
town I didn't know existed,
so I know exactly where you are.
Looking out into the unknown
at something that you cannot stop.
But I always had a
friend to watch my back,
just like you do now.
Joe's right. Everyone has a weakness.
Deathstorm does too.
We just have to find it.
Until then, what's the plan?
I'll use my speed to
keep searching the city.
I can help you coordinate protocols
so all of our officers are safe
and they can actually do their job.
What are you, my advisor now, Joe?
That would be up to you, Captain.
Remember, if you or any of your officers
- see this thing...
- Don't worry.
You'll be the first to know.
I'll let you know what I find on my end.
[SIGHS] Have faith.
He'll find a way.
Until he does,
you and I have to lock down this city.
Let's get to work.
Listen up, everyone.
Our city is under attack.
Captain, is it true?
Some kind of fire ghost?
Yes, and I suppose that's
as good a description as any.
To be honest, we don't
know much about our enemy,
but I can confirm that
the streets aren't safe
for anyone who is currently grieving.
So if you've had any
upsetting news recently
about a family member,
friend, or loved one,
please see myself or Joe immediately.
You're not safe on the streets.
The rest of us will be working
with the Flash and his team
to take this threat down together.
So your orders are as follows:
do not engage this monster.
We need to protect this city
by keeping civilians out of harm's way.
The Flash and his team
will do the heavy lifting.
Now, Martinez, Howe, send out
a city-wide lockdown alert.
We need everyone off the streets.
Korber, Matlin, gather teams
to set up a perimeter grid.
I want eyes and ears
on every street corner we can manage.
Anyone sees this thing, call it in,
then get yourselves to safety.
I have looked through all the evidence
on Deathstorm's past attacks,
and still no clues as to where he went.
So far, every grid
has turned up nothing.
And satellites are still a dead end.
Hey, what about the CCC Media tip line?
Nothing yet, and I have
the bullpen on alert.
It's like he shows up just to feed
and then disappears into thin air.
Just like a ghost.
He's not a ghost,
so he's gotta be hiding somewhere.
Hey. How are you guys doing?
Never mind. I already know.
I can feel your frustration
from the Med Lab.
Chester, I thought that we had a way
to track these black fires.
We did, but ever since our new Big Bad
turned from black flames
into a fiery, walking
and talking corpse,
he's become untraceable.
How's Caitlin?
She and Frost are moving
into the Speed Lab.
Physically, Caitlin is fine,
but she's still pretty shaken up.
Yeah, 'cause even though
you can hide emotions,
you can't get rid of them.
Guys, we don't need the satellites
to search for Deathstorm.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC]
♪
Cecile, you're gonna help us find him.
So wait, you want to use Cecile
as, like, a Deathstorm compass?
Yeah, think about it.
Deathstorm absorbs grief.
Grief is an emotion.
My powers.
My powers feel other people's emotions,
even from a distance.
If we can figure out a way
to interface Cecile's empath powers
with S.T.A.R.'s search systems,
it would be like using a
wireless neurogenic array
synced with the Med Lab's
synaptic monitoring relay.
Holy Paschal Beverly Randolph.
Barry, this could work.
Yeah, but syncing Cecile's mind up
with that thing, it
sounds pretty dangerous.
Allegra's right.
Okay, tapping into a pool
of emotion that large,
it could overload your neural synapses.
You sure you're okay with this?
This murderous bastard
has already killed
more than a dozen people.
So yeah, try and stop me.
I can't believe I was so blind.
Frost, this is all my fault.
I let that thing out.
No, I'm not gonna let you go there.
I mean, come on, we're on lockdown
because I went rogue.
All because I was so obsessed
with reconnecting with the past.
Ronnie wasn't just your
past. He was your husband.
And Deathstorm knew that,
which was why he knew
he could use it to manipulate
you into bringing him back
from whatever hellscape he comes from.
This isn't your fault, okay?
Isn't it? I mean, the whole
city is paying for my mistakes.
And as stupid as it sounds...
I just feel like I lost
Ronnie all over again.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
Why does this hurt so much?
Because you loved him.
[CHUCKLES]
And even though it's been a long time,
he'll always be a part of you.
And that's okay.
♪
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[THUNDERCLAP]
Oh, thank God.
Oh, let me guess. The Still Force.
Call me Deon.
My headaches, they're getting worse.
Okay. I'll see what I can do.
You also said to tell
you if something happened.
Well, it did.
Tinya's mom. I already know.
Oh, right.
'Cause you can see past,
present, and future.
Not in this case.
I actually only saw what
happened to Tinya's mom
once it became part of the past,
which ain't how things
are supposed to work.
My time sickness,
it's spreading into the Still Force.
That's why it took me
so long to get to you.
I've infected you too, haven't I?
That's probably why I
didn't see this coming.
Somehow... somehow,
I'm getting sick too.
What about Tinya's mom?
Once I get my strength
back, I'll look for her,
but, Iris,
I can see everyone's
future except for yours.
We've got to slow down
whatever's happening,
because if we don't...
Iris is gonna disappear again.
Maybe for good this time.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
We just... we gotta find
a way to bring her back,
'cause if she gets lost in space,
we need a way to find her.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
You remember that tracking
app that you guys used
- to find Tinya?
- Yeah.
Maybe I could do the same.
It's pretty far out, but if it works...
Do it.
♪
I should be able to
track your movements now.
In the meantime,
fight as hard as you can to stay here.
And do whatever you can
to just anchor yourself to the present.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪
Yo, something's wrong.
[SCREAMS]
♪
Okay, so I've linked up
a wireless neurogenic monitoring system
to your cerebral cortex.
You can do that?
Pretty sure, given enough time,
Chester can do anything.
Aww. Thanks, Barr.
So yeah, all you need
to do is concentrate
on any large pockets of grief.
If we're right, that'll lead us
right to where Deathstorm's been hiding.
Once you get a hit, I'll triangulate
real-time coordinates, find a location...
Then the Flash will take over.
Works for me.
You ready?
Uh... [INHALES SHARPLY]
Yeah.
Okay.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[HISSING]
[LAUGHS]
Oh, it's working. Keep going, Cecile.
[BEEPING STEADILY]
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
Wait, there must be
a glitch or something.
It says that...
It's coming from S.T.A.R. Labs.
[ALARM BEEPING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[INHALES RASPINGLY]
[DISTORTED WHISPERING]
[AS DEATHSTORM] You're wasting your time.
You won't find me until I'm ready.
Shut it down.
- Now. Shut it down.
- It won't work.
The empath and I are one.
Deathstorm,
if you hurt her...
[LAUGHING]
Don't bother with hollow threats.
You can't stop me.
The truth is, there's only one way
all of you survive.
We're never gonna give you Caitlin.
Then I'll take her from you!
[LAUGHS]
I can taste the tiniest bits of sorrow
coming from you both.
Mmm. They are so delicious.
And exactly what I need.
You don't scare us.
And you can't control us anymore.
We've already faced our grief.
And yet there's always
the smallest morsel left behind,
long after a loved one has passed.
[DISTORTED WHISPERING]
Which is why you can't stop me.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[GASPING AS HERSELF]
Cecile.
Deathstorm.
He overwhelmed my emotions.
It was...
It was horrible.
All that matters right now
is, you're back with us.
Okay?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Barry, I could feel
his determination.
His sheer force of will.
Barry, he's never, ever gonna give up
on trying to get Caitlin.
♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Esperanza.
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
Which would make you his bitch.
Be careful, prima.
The juvie in you is starting to show.
Yeah, we're done.
[RUMBLING]
What was that?
A localized explosion of some kind.
Oh, if Pyro Pazuzu is back,
we could be under attack.
Guys, I'm picking up a category-three
spectral discharge,
four levels beneath us.
What could cause that?
A light-based detonation on
the electromagnetic spectrum.
Allegra.
- What happened?
- Barry, watch out.
That thing, it looks like my cousin,
but it isn't.
It...
It was right there.
One of those grief
freaks like Chuck's dad,
but this time, it looked like Esperanza.
[TENSE MUSIC]
I knew it wasn't my
cousin as soon as I saw it,
but when I fired, it fired back.
The blast knocked both of us out.
Now it's gone.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
Only why is Deathstorm trying
to haunt me all of a sudden?
♪
We have no idea what happened to Deon.
Whatever's going on with me,
it's not just my problem anymore.
It's time fracturing itself.
Okay.
There's not much we can
do about that right now.
But obsessing over it,
it's only gonna make things worse.
Say, did I ever tell you about the time
that I crashed a royal wedding?
SPOILER ALERT: they don't arrest you
if you buy the castle.
Right. Not the time.
More like not enough time.
Did you know that being
married to a speedster
affords you the ability to
live an entire day in a second?
Makes you think that you have
all the time in the world.
[SOFT MUSIC]
We don't.
Every moment is precious.
Agreed.
You know, I used to
think that Barry and I
and our children,
that we had so much ahead of us, but...
Now it feels like I have no future.
Look, you are Iris West-Allen.
You are your own force of nature.
I promise,
whatever time this world has left,
it's not done with you yet.
Not by a long shot.
[HIGH-PITCHED WHINING]
Okay, Iris, stay with me.
The time stream, it's too strong.
Just remember what Deon said.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Concentrate on being right here,
right now, with me.
I can't... I can't fight it.
Hell yes, you can. You know why?
Because you have way
too much to live for.
[SCREAMS]
Barry. Nora and Bart.
They need you, Iris.
You're their future and they're yours.
Are you gonna give up on that?
- No.
- No. So fight this.
You say that you can't see a future?
Fine, anchor yourself to them.
Write yourself a new
future starting right now.
You got that?
[GASPING]
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
Better?
I'm still here.
Yeah.
I know that look.
Kramer had it earlier.
You're wondering what
to do now too, huh?
Using grief to track
Deathstorm was our best shot.
A long time ago,
I met someone who was
as unprepared as it gets.
Young, inexperienced,
thrust into this whole new world
that was sink or swim.
You know what happened
that he didn't see coming next?
DeVoe.
Zoom.
Cicada.
Bloodwork.
But you're still standing, ain't you?
What's happening now,
the way Deathstorm's
going after Caitlin.
I mean, how do we stop this thing
if we don't even know
why she's the target?
Barr, all the resources, weapons,
and planning in the world
ain't gonna help you prepare
for a monster like this.
All that you can do is
be who you already are,
somebody willing to fight,
no matter what the odds are.
So believe me when I say, don't worry.
In due time, you will find a way
to get the advantage over Deathstorm.
- And until that happens?
- You do what you do best.
Run...
into the unknown and trust yourself.
Believe me,
you're better prepared than you think.
♪
[PENCIL SCRIBBLING]
[WIND HOWLING, HISSING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪
[WHISPERING] Caity.
[HISSING AND HOWLING BUILDING]
[CACKLING]
[SNARLS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Now your life ends.
[SCREAMS]
What happened?
Deathstorm, he got in somehow.
- Caitlin?
- He took her.
- What about Frost?
- Well, I scanned her vitals.
She's still in the Speed Lab.
Alive, but not responding.
Barry, I'm tracking the
GPS on Caitlin's phone.
Deathstorm's moving with her fast,
headed to who knows where.
If we don't catch him
before he disappears...
Check on Frost. I'm
gonna go after Caitlin.
Chester, stay on comms.
Yeah.
[EPIC MUSIC]
♪
Found them!
He's too high. I can't reach them.
Chester, my boots can
redirect most energy sources.
Does that include currents equal
to the kinetic output
created when I run?
Uh, it should, and
the force of those two
equal energies would probably
cancel each other out.
It'd be like running into a brick wall.
I'm counting on it.
Hold up. Hold up.
Are you about to do what
I think you're about to do?
Yeah. Time to ride the lightning.
[METALLICA'S "RIDE THE LIGHTNING"]
♪ Flash before my eyes ♪
♪ Now is time to die ♪
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC]
♪ Burning in my brain ♪
♪ I can feel the flame ♪
♪
Chester, I've lost Caitlin.
- Where'd they go?
- I don't know.
One second, you almost had them,
then they completely disappeared.
We have to find them!
[BRIGHT ORGAN MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
[EERIE MUSIC]
[SNARLING]
♪
[ROARS]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
♪
[SNARLING]
[ROARS]
If you're gonna kill me,
just get it over with.
Why would I do that?
I traveled across the
stars to transform you,
so you could end my loneliness.
Because tonight, you become my bride.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
Oh, Flash, Caitlin just popped back up.
She's at the Ripley's Wild World,
just outside the city.
♪
Caitlin, what happened?
Where's Deathstorm?
Caitlin?
[SNARLING]
He said I'm not ready yet.
♪
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
It's incredible.
All my vitals are elevated,
my blood pressure is lower,
and so is my body temperature,
but that's not the strangest thing.
My cells are in a constant
state of regenesis.
It's like I'm not aging at all,
at least not the way I'm supposed to be.
Why?
Why would Deathstorm
try to make you stronger?
Ah.
Uh, Caitlin?
I'm sensing a massive amount
of grief inside of you.
It's... it's enough
for an entire family.
When I found you at the park,
there were four more charred bodies.
Deathstorm's calling card.
Okay, here's what I don't get.
The black flames that he emits,
how come they don't hurt you?
I don't think that they're supposed to.
I think that that's what's changing me.
When Deathstorm attacked
me again, he said,
"I traveled across the
stars to be with you."
But that my transformation
wasn't complete,
that I wasn't ready yet.
Ready for what?
To be his bride.
♪
I think he wants us to be together
in wherever it is that he's from.
And that what's happening
to me now is something
that he has to do to
make sure I'm prepared.
He was never trying to kill you.
Barry, I know it sounds crazy,
but if Deathstorm is
using the grief he
consumes to change me,
and he's saying he needs more...
He's gonna feed again.
And as soon as he's full,
he's gonna come back for you.
Okay, that's it.
I am done waiting around
for the bachelor from hell
to come give Caity a rose.
We need to find this sicko and end him,
before he does anything
worse to my sister.
[GROANING]
Hey, you okay?
It's fine. I'm gonna be okay.
I just... I gotta rest.
Frost, Cecile, stay with her.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find a way to end this.
We're more than just Team
Flash... we're a family.
And if anyone tries to hurt
a member of this family,
we do whatever we can to stop them.
[HEROIC MUSIC]
♪
Okay, Barr, so what now?
Yeah, we might not have a plan,
but now we know something
we didn't before,
something I'm hoping can help us.
What's that?
Where Deathstorm goes
when he disappears.
So when I was chasing Deathstorm,
he opened a portal,
and even though I
couldn't get to Caitlyn,
I saw inside of it, just for a moment.
And guys, I've seen
space like that before.
Inside your singularity,
right before you joined the team.
Whoa, now.
So what this means is,
when Deathstorm disappears,
he's not just teleporting around town.
No, he's jumping back and forth
between points in dimensional space.
I think I know what happened now.
When Ronnie's grief
traveled through that singularity,
it created Deathstorm.
Only he's been trapped
there, trying to get back
across the stars to Caitlyn ever since.
And now that he's complete,
he can move back and forth
between that hell
dimension and here at will.
All this time, we've been wondering
why Deathstorm would come after Caitlin,
seven years after Ronnie died.
He's been searching for his
plus one this whole time.
It took him this long because
of how far he had to travel.
So a death monster
from another dimension
traveling through outer
space to find his death bride.
Yeah, it's official. I
have heard everything now.
Great Benjamin Banneker.
Trans-dimensional particles.
Okay, now you're just making stuff up.
No, no, no, no, look.
Now that I know that his powers are
literally from out of this world,
it makes me think that
we need something cosmic.
And folks, I know just the
gadget that we can augment
and use to defend ourselves
against this thing.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
The Mental Augmentation Chamber.
The M.A.C. saved my ass
by absorbing the entire
mass of black hole energy
that I accidentally
unleashed a couple years ago.
I'm sorry about that again.
And black holes are composed
of trans-dimensional particles.
Exactly. Now, this is
gonna sound a little nuts.
But what if we adjust the M.A.C.
so that instead of absorbing
trans-dimensional energy,
it emits cosmic craziness instead?
We'd finally be able
to fight fire with fire.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's not like
we can just turn the M.A.C.
into a portable cannon or shield.
What we would really need is...
A person to contain all the energy.
Done and doner.
Look, I don't speak geek,
but I understand enough
to realize that you guys
need an anti-Deathstorm
in order to take down the real thing.
Frost and Deathstorm's powers
are both based on cold fusion.
That could be the key to
pull this whole thing off.
Yeah, but Frost, this is right up there
with some of the most dangerous stuff
we've ever attempted as a team.
We can't ask you to do this.
You don't have to.
It's like I told Mom. Dad
created me for one reason.
To keep Caity safe.
I was literally born for this.
♪
So...
let's extinguish the son of a bitch.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪
[HISSING]
[SNARLING]
♪
Iris.
Thank God.
It's so good to see you.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --