BARRY: My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
...but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
NARRATOR:
Previously on The Flash:
You killed my mother. Why?
MAN: If you wanna know that,
you're gonna have to catch me.
Not fast enough, Flash.
I love you, Iris.
I couldn't lie to you anymore. I'm sorry.
BARRY:
My name is Barry Allen.
I am not the fastest man alive.
That title belongs
to the man who killed my mother.
But not for long.
That was too close.
[DRONE WHOOSHES]
-He told me to make it hard.
-He didn't tell you to make him dead.
Remember this is just supposed to be
a training exercise to improve Barry's speed.
FLASH [OVER COMM]:
Cisco, you gonna bring it or what?
Bring it.
[GRUNTING]
Why isn't he running away?
Barry, run away.
[CISCO SIGHS]
Very impressive, Mr. Allen. Your reaction to
stimuli at super speed continues to improve.
-It's still not enough.
-It will be.
Keep working like you are.
Stay focused.
You will be ready next time
your man in the yellow suit comes.
I think you mean the Reverse-Flash.
What? He said it, not me.
And he's right. Yellow suit,
red lightning, and evil. The reverse of Barry.
-Meh.
-Actually, I kind of like it.
I'm so ready for another round.
How many drones do you have?
Two, and they've got lasers.
BOTH:
No.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Told you it would break.
And the shrink says I'm crazy.
-What is this place?
-Customs warehouse.
Imported cars from Europe.
All worth a fortune.
Question. How do you suggest
you and I drive all these cars out of here?
We're not. We're not stealing anything.
What are you talking about?
Our entrance set off the silent alarms.
The cops will be arriving
in two minutes and 14 seconds.
Bring them.
[RORY GRUNTING]
That's not for the cops...
...as we discussed.
He'll be here.
[SIRENS WAILING]
You do hear that, right?
He's not coming.
We're leaving.
-This better make sense real fast, buddy.
-It will. Let's go.
-You promised I'd get to do my thing.
-I always keep my promises.
Seatbelt.
[RORY GRUNTS]
-Are you sure nothing's missing?
-That's what the supervisor said.
I can check again.
JOE: Barr.
-Hey.
Uh, well...
...the breakage indicates
that the door somehow...
...had zero viscoelasticity
when it hit the ground.
What does that mean
to normal people?
Sorry. Uh, the steel shattered like glass.
It was frozen, Joe.
-Snart.
-He's back.
I thought Snart was some world-class thief.
All these expensive cars, he didn't take
any of them? Doesn't make sense.
-Eddie, put out an APB on Snart.
-Got it.
BARRY:
Snart wasn't here to steal anything.
-He was setting a trap.
-For me.
-And by me, I mean--
-I know what you meant.
God, you're beautiful.
Mick.
This is a joke. How do you know
this Flash didn't skip town, hm?
Maybe that's why he didn't show up.
Or maybe he's dead.
Or maybe someone
smarter than you iced him.
He's not dead and he didn't leave town.
You will tell me what we're stealing this time?
We are partners, after all.
This is what we came for.
That's worth money?
SNART: It's called Fire & Ice.
An abstract modern-day masterpiece...
...said to represent
the dichotomy of being.
It represents to me that people
with lots of money buy dumb stuff.
Osgood and Rachel Rathaway,
one of the richest couples in Central City...
...paid 25 million for it in Paris.
They're flying home with it today.
Mm.
CISCO:
Captain Cold is back.
For a non-metahuman,
Leonard Snart is quite the nemesis.
He still has the cold gun,
the one he stole from us. The one I built.
What does he want this time?
[SIGHS]
The Flash.
If Snart wants a fight,
then I'll give him one.
-Well....
-You don't think I should?
I didn't say that. But, Barry, as fast as you are,
you cannot be everywhere at once.
And it becomes then a question of priorities.
In the last month, you have made...
...a commitment to increasing your speed,
enhancing your reflexes.
It's working. You're getting faster.
Okay, but what am I supposed to do?
Just ignore Snart?
The last time you had a fight with Snart,
a train derailed.
You were lucky to get
all those people to safety.
-Now, if you don't give him that fight--
-He may just back off.
And there'll be no casualties.
Look, Barry, Cisco and I
will work with Joe and the police...
...and devise a way to catch Cold.
Yes, I said it.
Soon as it came out of my mouth, I heard it.
We can come up with ways
to neutralize Snart.
WELLS: Listen, Barry,
whether or not you go after Snart...
...that's your choice. We here,
we will do whatever we can to support you.
But after this past Christmas...
...after the events with the Reverse-Flash...
...I just think he poses
a greater threat to all of us.
Okay.
IRIS:
T-minus three days and counting.
Until the big move-in.
You know, I've never had a roommate.
But it did occur to me
if we ever get in a fight...
...I can't just storm away and go home
because home will be with you.
-Are you predicting many arguments?
-Have you met me?
[CHUCKLES]
I remember the night we met.
I stopped a mugger who stole your bag.
My hero.
Hey.
Eddie, you know where Joe is?
-Uh, I think he's upstairs in your lab.
-Okay. Thanks.
No second thoughts
about moving in together?
None.
-Joe, hey.
-Hey, I'm glad you're back.
-I've been going over Snart's file.
-Yeah. I need to talk to you.
Um, as CSI, my work on this case is done.
And as...
...the Flash, I don't think
I can focus on Snart right now.
Mind telling me
what brought about this change?
This man in yellow,
the man that killed my mom...
...he's still out there. I have to be ready
to face him, which means amping up my speed.
It's a question of priorities.
Your mom's killer isn't the only reason
you've been doing this.
You told me if you could use your powers
to save someone, you would.
Look, Dr. Wells and S.T.A.R. Labs
are gonna work with you.
Cisco thinks he has a way to protect
the police against Snart's cold gun.
I understand if you're scared.
We talked about this.
Of course I'm scared, Joe.
This guy could run into the precinct and kill
everyone in seconds. He threatened Iris.
I won't let him hurt
the most important people in my life again.
If that means devoting every second
I have outside this place to getting faster...
...and stopping him, that's what I'm gonna do.
I've made up my mind.
JOE:
Aw.
McSnurtle the turtle. How you been?
When did you stop sleeping with this?
He was your favorite.
He was. But if I remember correctly,
you took him away from me...
...after I broke your
Duke Ellington Live at the Blue Note vinyl.
-Oh, yeah.
-Mm.
-You can have him back.
-Oh, gee, thanks.
Heh.
Oh, Dad.
I'm gonna miss you, baby.
-Dad, I'm only 10 minutes away.
-I know.
Ah, don't you worry about me.
I'll be fine. Just like always.
[DOOR OPENS]
-Hey.
Came to help her pack?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Iris said that she had something for me?
IRIS:
Oh. Ahem.
I found this in my closet. Heh.
[JOE LAUGHING]
BARRY:
I haven't seen this in years.
Well, the nerd survival kit is still intact.
Wow.
IRIS: Heh. I thought those
might be worth something.
Uh, I am so late for work.
I promise I'll clean this up when I get back.
-Bye.
-Bye. Yeah. Heh.
Okay.
You mind telling me
what's going on with you and Iris?
-Nothing.
JOE: Hm.
That's funny because I have
these two things called eyes...
...and it doesn't look like you two are fine.
I told Iris.
You told Iris you're the Flash?
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
[CHUCKLES]
I told her how I felt about her.
-Oh, God.
-Mm-hm.
What'd she say?
Well, I mean,
she's still moving in with Eddie, isn't she?
I just wanna pretend like it never even
happened. That's what we're both doing, so....
Well, not saying how you feel
is what got you in this mess in the first place.
Speaking of which, we both know she's
not gonna clean this mess up anytime soon.
No.
Sure.
[SIGHS]
Uh, excuse me.
If I could have everybody's attention, please.
You have our attention, Mr. Ramon.
Okay, check it.
So Dr. Wells and I,
we took your ballistic shields and--
And we lined them with a pretty sweet
compacted heating ribbon...
...designed to repel temperature attacks...
...especially those reaching absolute zero,
like Captain Cold's gun.
That's supposed to keep us
from getting turned into popsicles?
Um, yeah. Yeah, they will.
How are we supposed to trust anything
from S.T.A.R. Labs after you nuked the city?
You're right.
You shouldn't trust us.
What happened a year ago,
that was our fault.
And we can't change the past,
as much as we wish we could.
But tomorrow is a different story.
Tomorrow's a different thing.
We just want the chance
to make things better.
Observe.
[CHATTERING]
Dummies are one thing...
...my officers are another.
You seem pleased with yourself, doctor.
Well, I'm just happy
to help the police catch Snart, Joe.
-Barry might be able to help too.
-I think Cisco's heat shields are up to the task.
Joe, if Barry feels he's gonna
endanger lives by taking on Snart...
...and feels he's gonna save lives
by training to take on the man in yellow...
...that's his call.
You know what makes Barry so special?
He wants to help everyone he can,
however he can.
Always has. Until now.
I guess it's just a question
of priorities, then.
You know,
Barry said the exact same thing to me.
I thought, "Doesn't sound like him."
I guess because it sounds like you.
BARRY: Hey.
CAITLIN: Aah!
BARRY:
Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you.
-It's okay. I was just kind of focused.
-Gotcha.
What's Firestorm?
One of the last things Ronnie
said to me before he flew away.
My dead fiancé can fly.
Haven't broke that to my parents yet.
-You doing okay?
-Yeah, yeah. I just....
I told Iris how I felt about her.
-Bold choice.
-I knew where we stood before.
We're best friends and, I don't know, now I
just don't know what's normal for us anymore.
Before I met Ronnie, I knew exactly
what was going to happen every day of my life.
It was predictable. I like predictable.
But when Ronnie and I started dating,
everything started to change.
He made me try Indian food
and scuba diving.
At first it was scary, but then it was better.
Things weren't really normal with you
pining after Iris and her being totally unaware.
Whatever happens next, it will be better.
Wait, Caitlin.
-Scuba.
-What about it?
"Self-contained underwater
breathing apparatus." It's an acronym.
What if Firestorm isn't a word?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
"Fusion ignition research
experiment and science...
...of transmutation originating
RNA and molecular structures."
It's 800 pages.
[BARRY CLEARS THROAT]
There's a lot of stuff in there, but it mostly
focuses on transmutation, which is...
...the process of altering the structure
of an element by unzipping atoms--
And rebuilding it to create
an entirely new element.
Yeah. Well, the article
was co-written by Jason Rusch...
...a grad student here at Hudson University.
If anybody knows what happened to Ronnie--
Maybe he does.
-Maybe.
-Thanks.
MAN: Pleasant flight, Mrs. Rathaway?
-Yes, quite. Thank you.
Careful, please. It's worth a fortune.
-Welcome home, Mr. Rathaway.
-Thank you, Ethan.
Sir, your son, Hartley, he called again.
OSGOOD:
We don't have a son anymore.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Someone better call 911.
[SIRENS WAILING]
COP:
Move! Move!
Snart, freeze.
SNART:
Mick.
RORY: Aah!
-What the hell?
Why do they call you people "the heat"?
I'm the heat.
SNART:
Forget them, Mick.
-Get ready for him.
-It's beautiful.
Mick.
We go. Now.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
JOE:
Is he all right?
Okay.
-Hey. Hey, are you okay?
JOE: I'll call you back.
I'm fine.
Snart's new partner,
he's got this handheld flamethrower.
Almost everyone was treated on the scene,
but we got two in the Burn Unit though.
-I'm sorry. I should've listened to you.
-It's all good.
Next time Snart and his pyro pal show up, you
make them sorry they ever messed with you.
I gotta call the hospital.
The cop's bullet ruptured
the secondary internal fuel chamber.
Could have been worse. You were right to get
me to learn every part and circuit of this thing.
Repairing it was a snap.
Give me one reason
I don't kill you right now.
It's gonna be hard to find someone else
to listen to your speeches.
You lost it out there just like the last job.
You lost focus, became obsessed.
I'm obsessed? What about you?
You're usually counting the seconds.
Got the whole thing planned out.
Dotting T's, crossing I's.
But all you care about now is the Flash.
-We have to put him down.
-Why?
We got the finger painting. It's worth millions.
It's ours. We're rich. Job done.
What about the next job, Mick?
And the job after that?
With weapons like these, no one can
stand against us. No one except the Flash.
[SIGHS]
If you want out, take the painting and go.
But if you want Central City to be our home,
where we can do and take whatever we want...
...this is our chance.
Your chance.
Mm.
Very motivational. How do we get him?
The Flash isn't so different from us.
-He's got partners too.
-Hm.
-Jason Rusch?
-Yes. Uh, Dr. Snow?
Please, call me Caitlin.
Uh, thank you for meeting me.
Happy to. Although to be totally upfront,
if this is about the résumé...
...I mailed to S.T.A.R. Labs,
I've accepted a position at Mercury Labs.
Uh, no, actually.
I wanted to talk to you about FIRESTORM.
I'm sorry. Uh, this was a mistake.
I have to go.
No. Look, someone I care about is in trouble,
and you're the only clue I have to help him.
Please.
JASON: What's the line? I never got paranoid
until they started plotting against me?
Why would they be plotting against you?
Because of our work.
Because of FIRESTORM.
Transmutation.
The ability to alter matter on a molecular level.
We had rudimentary success
with our stage one testing...
...working with sand grains.
But Professor Stein said--
Sorry. Professor Martin Stein?
He was the co-author of the paper?
Yeah, he was our team leader. He didn't believe
in baby steps, so we skipped to stage three.
Which was?
We melted a concrete wall.
But the university
threatened to shut us down...
...so Professor Stein published his paper
without permission. They went nuts.
He talked to a friend of his
to secure private backing.
-And who was that?
-He didn't say. He just said he'd call me later.
And no one has seen or heard
from Professor Stein since.
What do you think happened to him?
All I know is that the Army showed up
the next day and confiscated all of our research.
So tell me, Dr. Snow,
do you think I'm being too paranoid...
...or not paranoid enough?
[CAITLIN GASPS]
Car trouble?
[SCREAMING]
[SIGHS]
WELLS:
I hope we're not enemies.
What? No, of course not.
I thought you might blame me.
For pushing you to pursue your training
rather than help the police.
Look, I'm an adult.
I make my own choices, my own mistakes.
And I'm glad you push me to be better.
It's so weird.
There was a time in my life that...
...I would have paid money
for your autograph. And now we're--
Partners.
I was gonna say friends.
In case you doubt it,
you push me to be better too.
Guys, you have to come look at this.
When the heat gun was fired,
it increased the surrounding temperature...
...of the air dramatically.
Sort of like an extreme heat wave.
-Heat Wave.
-Stop doing that.
Okay. I measured the temperature output
of both the cold and heat guns, right?
And while the cold gun
achieves absolute zero...
...the heat gun reaches absolute hot,
or the hottest temperature an object can reach.
Planck temperature.
So potentially, these two guns
could cancel each other out.
Yeah, but to do that,
you'd have to make them cross streams.
You mean like Ghostbusters?
That film is surprisingly
scientifically accurate.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
And really quite funny.
Hey, Joe. What's up?
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
-Joe. Anything?
JOE: There's no sign of Caitlin.
BARRY:
Oh, my God.
-We're getting her back. We have to find Snart.
-Damn right we do.
Come on, let's go.
Joe. Joe. We got a hit.
Second pair of prints.
They belong to a Mick Rory.
-Who is he?
-Big-time arsonist.
He and Snart worked a job last year
that went bad.
Half of Rory's body was burned
in a fire that got out of control.
He escaped from an ambulance.
Hasn't been seen since.
Why would they kidnap
someone like Caitlin?
Joe. Thawne. It's on every station.
[CAITLIN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
SNART [ON TV]:
Greetings, citizens of Central City.
I am Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Cold.
I'm gonna make this
very simple for everyone.
That red streak
you've been hearing whispers about.
The one mysteriously saving people
these past few months?
Well, surprise, he's real.
He calls himself the Flash.
Porter and Maine. Tonight. Sundown.
Come out, come out, wherever you are, Flash.
Show the whole world you're real.
Or this woman dies.
No, don't come for me. Stay away.
He'll hurt--
[CAITLIN GRUNTS]
You're a friend of his, huh? He's fast.
Like fire.
Fire, it's undefinable.
Heat, light, energy.
It's an evolution when things burn.
CAITLIN:
You're sick.
Maybe you're the sick ones.
You ever think about that?
-Not really.
-Mm.
You've got third-degree burns.
Why didn't you get skin grafts?
The fire revealed my true self.
It showed me who I really am.
I wonder what your Flash will reveal
when I burn his suit and skin off?
Do whatever you want to me,
but leave him alone.
Ooh.
Okay.
You and this Flash must be really close
if you're willing to die for him, hm?
You want me to show you who you really are?
That'd be fun. Hm?
Show you who you really are.
SNART:
Mick.
Time to go.
You better pray the next people
that come through this door is us.
[CAITLIN GASPS THEN GRUNTS]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-Hey.
-Okay. You're on.
-Good luck, son.
-Thanks.
Barry, after tonight, everyone's
gonna know that the Flash exists.
Are you ready for that?
[SIGHS]
I'll see you soon.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Did you see that? That was him.
-That was the Flash.
-I don't believe it.
[PANTING]
Believe it.
SNART:
The scarlet speedster.
Any preference on how you'd like to die?
The flame? Or the frost?
Not in the mood for chitchat.
Gotcha. Ready when you are.
SNART:
Cover me.
Run on this.
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
Barry? Barry, are you okay?
You know what you have to do.
Yeah. Get them to cross beams
and cancel their guns out. I know.
SNART:
Mick.
Ah! Gotcha.
Yeah, not as easy as it sounds.
-Eddie. Eddie.
EDDIE: Iris, what are you doing here?
-They evacuated Jitters. I saw your car.
-You can't be here. It's not safe.
JOE:
Are you sure Caitlin's here, Cisco?
From Caitlin's car, I pieced together
surveillance footage that lead us to this area.
But there's over a dozen warehouses.
But only one of them has had
the heat on the last three nights.
And I'm betting Mick Rory likes it hot.
Okay.
Stay behind me.
-Caitlin.
CAITLIN: Mm?
CISCO: Caitlin, is that you?
CAITLIN: Mm-mm.
[MUFFLED YELLING]
Caitlin, we're gonna get you out of here.
JOE:
Cisco. Cisco, down!
SINGH: The fight is spreading beyond the evac
area. We need to expand the perimeter.
We can't. We can't let this spread.
Oh, my God.
SINGH: Thawne, where you going?
-Eddie.
[CAITLIN GASPS]
I thought I was gonna die.
Not while I'm around. Or him.
[GROANING]
EDDIE:
Hold on!
I got this. Go, go, go!
I can't get them to cross streams.
Speed isn't getting it done.
You're right.
Maybe the way to do this
is not by going faster.
-It's going slower.
-Yes.
Okay.
Thanks for playing, kid.
[RORY LAUGHING]
[YELLING]
[FLASH GRUNTING OVER MONITOR]
[RORY LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
[SNART LAUGHS]
I didn't see that coming.
Mm, I guess you win this time.
There won't be a next time.
[IN DISTORTED VOICE]
Thank you, detective.
[RORY YELLING]
We'll burn every last one of you pigs!
Get your hands off me!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
[RORY GROWLS]
Yeah!
-Your partner's a real hot head.
-That's funny.
You know what's hilarious, Snart?
We got you.
-Congratulations.
-Get him out of here.
-Nice work, Eddie.
-It wasn't me.
It was the Flash.
We're not gonna be needing these for trial.
You'll make sure--
They'll never hurt anyone ever again.
[SIGHS]
Mr. Ramon.
Thank you.
He was like a lightning bolt through the streets.
He took them both out singlehandedly.
-That's amazing.
-Wonder who he is?
OFFICER:
You ask me, he's a hero.
Okay. All right.
IRIS:
I think that's it.
This better be it.
Well, like you said, I'll be 10 minutes away,
so if you forget something....
Okay.
IRIS:
Dad.... Heh.
JOE:
I can't say it enough. I'll miss you.
You know you can come around any time, Joe.
-Just give us a heads-up.
IRIS: Heh.
Or not.
Come around whenever. You want a key?
[EDDIE CHUCKLES]
I'm gonna go...
...wait in the truck.
Why don't I give you two a minute?
[SIGHS]
Well....
I know things have been
really weird between us recently.
Yeah, they have.
[SIGHS]
Did you know I can see into the future?
-Really?
-Oh, yeah. Did I forget to tell you that?
You did not mention it, no.
-Wow.
-Ha-ha.
So, what do you see?
I see you and Eddie
being really happy together.
And things aren't weird
between us anymore.
Took a little time,
but everything's back to normal...
...and we're still best friends.
The future doesn't sound so bad.
No. And it'll be here faster than you think.
[TV CLICKS ON]
MAN [ON TV]:
The Patriots continue their....
Dad, um, is it okay if I...?
JOE:
Oh. Yeah.
My baby girl.
-Bye.
-See you.
[EXHALES]
Well....
[BARRY SIGHS]
You okay?
Mm-hm.
-How about you?
-It was bound to happen sometime, right?
Mm-hm.
Want to order pizza
and watch the ball game?
Make it pizzas, and you're on.
[JOE CHUCKLING]
If you ever need somebody
to come and eat your food, I'm there.
Besides, the laundry machines
in my building have been broken for a month.
I don't know why you moved
into that death trap in the first place.
You've got a perfectly good room here.
-You said you were turning it into a gym.
-We both know I'm not turning it into a gym.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Besides, you've got me
running around enough as it is.
It is getting hard to hide the blasting
in and out of my apartment from my neighbors.
I suppose it would make sense
for me to move back in.
I am a millennial. That is what we do.
[LAUGHING]
Don't do it on my account.
I'll be fine on my own.
Oh, yeah. Me too. For sure.
All right, roomie.
You order the pizzas, I'll unpack.
Heh-heh. No way.
I wanna help you. I wanna enjoy this.
All right.
You know this does nothing to me.
-Just drink it.
-Mm-hm.
I should have burned the entire city block down,
but instead, I listened to you.
We had the painting. We had the guns.
We could have had everything.
But you had your stupid plan.
How's that stupid plan
working out for us now?
Everyone's seen the Flash now.
This changes things, again.
[TIRES SQUEALING THEN GUNFIRE]
What the--?
-Snart.
-Relax, Mick.
What's going on?
[YELLING]
The plan.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, sis.
Nice.