Help!
-Mom.
-Barry, no!
-I can't--
-Mom!
GUSTIN:
Well, Barry isn't really sure what he saw.
It was just a bunch of lightning
Circling his mom.
And as a kid, he had no idea what it was...
...other than his mom was in danger...
...she was screaming,
she was in a lot of trouble.
All of a sudden he was transported
from his house.
There was no way of explaining it.
Mom?
GUSTIN:
And then he comes back to his home...
...and his mother's been murdered
and his father's getting put into a police car.
So he doesn't know what happened
other than it wasn't his father that did this.
And he's determined to...
...find out who did.
Mom.
JOE: Barry.
-Mom.
MARTIN:
Well, initially when it first happened...
...we weren't aware at all
what Barry saw.
He just kept saying, "I saw yellow...
...and red lightning."
And honestly, there's a Reverse-Flash,
the yellow piece of lightning...
...and a red Flash, our Flash, Barry.
But that red Flash is actually Barry
from the future.
Which I guess could be kind of confusing,
but we're trying to figure it out.
KREISBERG: One of the things
I always loved about the Flash was that...
...you know, he was just a guy
who got hit by lightning.
And when you look at the DC Comics
characters, they all tend to be gods.
Superman's an alien,
and Diana's an Amazon.
Aquaman is from Atlantis.
Barry was always like if it had happened to us
and we got to be part of the Justice League.
He was funny, but he was a hero sort of
of the people and for the people.
I think that combination of, you know,
the fun of his powers...
...combined with his innate vulnerability,
both physically and emotionally...
...always made him one of the most
appealing characters for me.
The Flash is the fastest man alive.
And you just--
As a kid, and as an adult,
you dream of that ability and that capacity.
You know, and it's our job as storytellers
to come up with...
...what are the pros and the cons
of having that ability.
Even though he was really fast, he could
be shot, you know, and he could be killed.
And he was, in fact, killed, you know,
famously.
BERLANTI: The Flash was the first comic book
that I cried when I read it as a kid.
He died in a series of books
called Crisis on Infinite Earths.
And he died sacrificing his life.
We deal with that in the show a lot
in terms of sacrifice.
I mean, I think as kids, it was really one of the
first sort of deaths that we had dealt with.
If you were reading the comics,
you know, in the '80s...
...you know,
things started to get much tougher.
Certainly with Crisis and, you know,
we actually borrow a little bit...
...of the iconography
of Barry's face melting...
...in episode 123, "Fast Enough," because...
...you know, again that--
Those images meant so much to us.
And usually you're used to like,
"They'll figure out a way to do it in the end."
And at the end of the day,
Barry realized:
"I'm willing to give my life to save the world
and to save my friends."
Barry's guilt drives him.
He knows that his father's innocent.
The fact that he can't prove it is killing him
and driving him at the same time.
He thinks he needs to take care
of the whole city now.
Even though we haven't had
Barry Allen die on our show...
...that level of courage
and that level of sacrifice...
...and that level of love that he has,
you know, not just for his friends...
...but for everybody,
certainly permeates our version of the show.
BERLANTI: It was always
my sort of secret dream, I think...
...to be a part of launching
a Flash anything, really.
To me, what was so exiting about
sort of doing...
...a Flash television show
at this particular moment...
...was really sort of, I think, we're kind of all
in this era of everything moves so quickly.
You know, we can be in touch with people
and our friends all throughout the day...
...and I think people can really kind of
finally identify emotionally with the Flash.
FLASH:
Whoo-hoo!
JOHNS: Speed can be a bit addictive, right?
It's kind of the modern day vice, right?
We're all trying to go faster.
We want things faster.
We want downloads faster.
We want information faster.
We want everything faster,
and life is designed to speed up everything.
The heart and soul of the show
really kind of gets at that...
...which is fast isn't always enough,
you know.
Sometimes it's about
all the other elements too.
Even the fastest man alive
could be late.
Sorry I'm late, Captain Singh.
What was it this time, Mr. Allen?
Did you forget to set your alarm clock?
KREISBERG: I think the biggest thing
that we had to do was really settle on...
...who our version of Barry Allen was.
And, you know, in some ways
we kind of cherry-picked...
...from a lot of different versions.
There's certainly the Barry Allen
that we all know from the Silver Age...
...but he's got a little bit
of Wally West in him.
What we really wanted
the audience to invest in...
...as far as Barry was concerned
was his vulnerability.
So that was sort of the biggest decision
we had to make and our biggest challenge.
And as soon as we saw Grant...
...we knew that we had found
our Barry Allen or our Flash.
You're gonna have to revise your definition
of lightning fast.
KREISBERG: And what we were looking for
in our Barry Allen, in our Flash...
...was somebody who didn't necessarily
look like the standard superhero.
And certainly didn't look like the, you know,
6-foot tall, blond-haired muscular guy...
...that Flash is in the comic books.
And once people saw his screen test,
and definitively...
...when people saw those two episodes
of Arrow that Grant guested on...
...you know, I think we'd, you know--
We'd introduced Flash
for a new generation of people.
You're also gonna have to revise
your definition of possible.
KREISBERG: We worked with David Nutter
on the Arrow pilot...
...and he did such an amazing job there.
There really was no question
of who we would get.
Are you ready?
BERLANTI:
I've worked with David Nutter many times...
...over many years.
And I think what's so exciting is...
...he doesn't just get a story in terms
of a filmic level, he gets it emotionally.
And I thought what would be exciting
about this in contrast to something like Arrow...
...it had this real emotional underpinning...
...that I knew would--
I hoped that David would respond to...
...and then be able to sort of translate
to the actors.
KREISBERG: You know, David was there
every step of the way...
...helping us to mold this,
helping us to find this character...
...helping us to, you know,
realize the visual effects.
But also finding the heart of the character.
BARRY:
I’m so proud...
...to be your son.
BERLANTI: We use the words
"heart," "humor," and "spectacle"...
...whenever we're talking about the show...
...that the best episodes
have all of those things.
And I think that's where--
One of the great things about the show...
...is it actually hopefully feels like
you're actually reading a comic book.
When I watch a great episode of the show,
it makes me feel the way...
...the books used to make me feel
when I was a kid.
Which is it's sort of larger than life,
anything's possible...
...but a totally emotional, relatable
sort of story.
That at the end of the day
is the most important thing for us.
Um, Barry Allen is a character.
What Barry's going through...
...what the audience is going to feel
as they're watching it.
And David is one of those directors...
...who is equally as adept at staging
an amazing car chase...
...or the tornado sequence...
...as he is having a scene between,
you know...
...Barry and Iris in Jitters
or, you know...
...Barry and his dad at the end,
you know, and I think it's--
You know, the skill that David has
in elevating all of those things...
...is what makes The Flash so special and
makes it feel like more than just a comic book.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV]
WOMAN [ON TV]: --enthusiasm here
as no one seems ready to leave.
Those outside are finding cover....
MARTIN:
It seems that every hero...
...is born out of some tragedy.
And, of course,
the same is true with Barry.
His father ends up in jail
for, seemingly, life...
...and his mom, of course, dies.
Um, and much later...
...you know, does the hero emerge.
JOHNS: Having him experience tragedy
in his life, like his mother dying...
...but having him not go dark about it--
Like there's a darkness within him...
...and he's haunted by it...
...but he's still moving forward, he's still smiling,
he's still trying to help people.
Geoff Johns said it to me best
early on...
...that I think this is the way
Barry handled his past:
"Your past is like an anchor.
And you don't cut off an anchor
and leave it at the bottom of the ocean.
You pull it up with you and you carry on."
And I think...
...better than most superheroes,
Barry does a good job of...
...you know, this is what happened to me.
I'm gonna find out why this happened...
...and how, but I'm gonna
move toward with my life...
...and I'm not gonna let this
define me or ruin me.
I don't know if I can be some vigilante.
-You can be better.
KREISBERG: We talk a lot about Barry...
...obviously, in contrast to Oliver.
Oliver's getting hit by lightning
was being marooned on the island.
And he was not a hero before that.
He was actually, you know, very selfish
and manipulative and not a good guy.
When you have, like,
Bruce Wayne or any of these characters...
...when they've had a dark tragedy happen
in the past, it's made them very cold adults.
It almost would have been better
if both his parents had died.
But losing one parent and then have the other
one be accused of murdering them...
...um, you know, it's the stuff of nightmares...
...and yet Barry still found a way to dream.
He had the heart of a hero,
but now he finally had the feet to match.
The power itself of the Flash...
...you know, has a great deal of appeal.
There's something much more grounded
about enjoying the Flash's powers...
...because who wouldn't wanna
get to where you're going faster?
Who wouldn't want to move faster? You know,
there's never enough time in the day.
Barry can get seduced by that speed,
we all could.
And he can get over-confident
and think he has time to do everything.
You know, but it's still time.
It's still gonna take time to do anything.
There's a great scene in a comic book...
...where the Flash is running...
...he's trying to save people, as many people
as he can, he gets to a car wreck...
...he's like, "I'm gonna save everybody,"
and he opens the door...
...and the person inside is already dead.
It's too late. And I think the most frustrating
thing that Barry has to deal with now is that...
...as a forensic scientist, he's always
at a crime scene that's already happened.
Mommy.
Everybody's out.
What else you got for me, Cisco?
Barry, it's Caitlin.
Hey, Caitlin.
-How's your day?
KREISBERG: One of the other things that...
...we wanted to imbue this show with
was joy.
And the joy of being the Flash.
And, you know, sometimes that joy
leads Barry to, you know, um....
You know, be a little full of himself.
FLASH:
Cisco, are you gonna bring it or what?
Bring it.
BERLANTI: I think Barry can get a little cocky
sometimes because he's...
...you know, got this new ability
and it feels good.
And it feels good to be great at something.
And it feels good to save people.
GUSTIN: I'm the one with these powers
at the end of the day...
...so you can't really tell me how to use them,
they're mine. Um....
But yeah, and I think that stems
from he's a 25-year-old...
...that now has these
just unbelievable powers.
And no one can really stop him
from doing what he wants to do.
Money, now.
I just-- You're really gonna be kicking
yourself, man.
If there was an Olympics for bad luck, you
didn't just medal, pal, you Michael Phelps'ed.
I'm gonna count to three,
then I'm gonna shoot you.
-One.
-Yeah.
[COCKS GUN]
Two.
I don't see Barry being seduced by power,
I don't see Barry giving into...
...that power and doing bad things with it,
I think...
...if anything, Barry's gonna
over-extend himself...
...and he's gonna try too hard,
and he's going to...
...maybe even believe he can do it,
which might hurt him.
And, uh.... And that's it.
But I just don't, you know--
As far as, like, enhancing flaws...
...I think it only really enhances goodness
in him and his intentions are good...
...but ultimately,
it might lead to something bad.
You know, as far as his bravado's concerned...
...that's something we're certainly talking
a lot about for season two.
You know, season one was about
Barry becoming a hero.
Season two is really going to be about:
Now that you're a hero, what does that mean?
And the responsibilities of being a hero.
You were the one at my house that night.
You killed my mother!
Why?
REVERSE-FLASH:
If you wanna know that...
...you're gonna have to catch me.
BERLANTI: I think with all these shows,
you know, the hero's only as good as the villain.
We spend a lot of time thinking about
what are the match-ups that week.
Who's the Flash going up against?
The Flash comic books always had a little bit
of that great sci-fi, science element.
So you were kind of getting a science lesson
along with the fun.
CAlTLIN [OVER COMM]:
You can't fight him, Barry.
Gas is the least stable form of matter.
This metahuman will not be able to stay
in his mist form for long.
His particles will need to reform.
[SNARLS]
KREISBERG: So for us, the villains
are just as important as the hero.
And it's not just a question
of the visual effects, you know...
...what's a compelling, you know...
...visceral opponent for the Flash
to go up against...
...you know, special effects-wise.
But also what are they going through
that Barry's going through?
BARRY:
The thing that happened to you, Tony...
...it happened to me too.
But it didn't just give us abilities...
...it made us more of who we are.
You got strong.
I got fast.
Allen. Allen, don't walk away.
KREISBERG:
Barry, if he hadn't been....
If he'd been struck by lightning and had been
a different kind of damaged soul...
...you know, the terror and havoc
he could wreak with these powers....
And in some ways, Barry has had it worse
than some of these other villains.
Um, and how can, you know, Barry's journey
be mirrored in their journey?
And how can we see how Barry's heroism
is not just in defeating the villain physically...
...but also in a way...
...overcoming the emotional damage
that the villain has experienced...
...that the villain wasn't able
to overcome, but Barry has.
BERLANTI: The cavalcade of villains
that we've been really lucky to have this year...
...and then some of the talent that we've
attracted for that has also made the show...
...I think, you know, just a lot of fun to watch.
-What's this?
-It might not look like much.
But never judge a book by its cover,
you know.
Fires highly concentrated,
combustible liquid fuel...
...that ignites on contact with the air.
I don't need to heat things up.
I need to slow them down.
[WEAPON POWERING UP]
KREISBERG: Obviously, Captain Cold
is really the Joker, you know.
You know, he's his arch nemesis.
JOHNS:
Captain Cold is my all-time favorite villain.
I don't know why. I think it's because...
...one of the very first Flash comics
I ever read, he was on the cover.
And he had these goggles that were so cool
and, like--
He kind of looked almost like a gangster
and he had this cold gun.
He said, "Wait till you see what I did
to the Flash," and it's, like--
It says "censored" over the Flash's body,
and I was like, "Oh, my God, what did he do?"
BERLANTI: Yeah, I mean, we wanted Cold
because in the history of the Flash...
...he's the archrival.
He's got a cold gun,
which obviously is working...
...in direct opposite
to what the Flash can do. Um--
But he had his own moral code.
And we really wanted Leonard Snart
to be the first human villain...
...that the Flash went up against.
So it was a match of real wits.
[CRASH]
I didn't see it before.
Your mom know you're out
past your bedtime?
KREISBERG: Barry really believes
in the inherent goodness of people.
Snart had just as sort of tragic
a back-story as Barry did.
You know, he grew up with a very
abusive father, who abused him...
...who is an even worse criminal
than Snart.
You seem like a good brother.
-You too.
-Debatable.
KREISBERG: One of the interesting things
that Wentworth said to us...
...when we were talking about the character,
that he feels that what separates Snart...
...and what makes him, like,
not quite fully evil is that...
...Snart always says to himself...
...that no matter how bad he is,
his dad was worse.
Don't look so surprised, detective.
I am a man of my word.
Yeah, you better be...
...or I'll make sure
you're on that damn plane too.
KREISBERG:
This show is Flash begins.
That goes true for the villains as well.
In the comic books, Captain Cold...
...has a very serious set of rules
and a code and a sense of honor...
...that doesn't just apply
to his fellow Rogues...
...but also to the Flash
and the people of Central City...
...and we're not quite there yet.
You're starting to see glimpses of it.
And, you know,
the fact that he's kept Barry's secret...
...that he discovered Barry was the Flash...
...midway through the season and hasn't told
anybody, even his sister and his partners...
...speaks to that, you know, burgeoning code.
And I think it's what makes him
such a fascinating villain.
I guess your secret's safe...
...Flash.
Oh, I don't suppose you'd give me
a ride back to town, would you?
The Rogues.
Cute.
I've been going over unsolved cases
from the past nine months...
...and there's been a sharp increase
in unexplained deaths and missing people.
Your metahumans have been busy.
I'm not blaming you. I know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
I know you all lost something.
But I need your help to catch Mardon
and anyone else out there like him.
But I can't do it without you.
MARTIN:
I think it's kind of important to surround...
...your lead character, your superhero...
...with people who might actually
be super humans.
And what I mean by that is people who are just
really, really concerned about the humanity...
...that this person should have
and should seek out.
I mean, because when you become
a superhero, a lot of things become physical.
You know, were you can physically
save the world.
But emotionally, you might not be there.
So he needs some really "super" humans...
...around him in order for him to have, like...
...a stable, emotional life.
BERLANTI:
What's great about Team Flash is that...
...they're all really discovering the hero
within themselves this year.
Everybody really was affected by that
particle accelerator's explosion that night.
And so much of their journey
for the year is discovering...
...the best that's in each of themselves
and how they work well...
...independently and together as a team.
And there's all sorts of challenging things
about working with a group of people.
You know, there's times
you work smartly together...
...and there's times that you're in conflict.
But there's a real familial sense.
You can tell they all really like
and admire each other.
This isn't even
remotely anatomically correct.
That's not the point, Dr. Snow.
Then what is the point?
To have fun.
GUSTIN:
Barry has a huge support system...
...for somebody that is kind of a loner.
I mean, he's got multiple father figures
in his life now.
Joe, who essentially is Barry's father
since he was 11...
...he's been there for him every day.
Joe is probably...
...Barry's biggest go-to support system.
And Iris obviously, but he can't be
fully honest with Iris right now...
...about multiple things and that
kind of eats at Barry so it's--
Their relationship
is kind of a roller coaster...
...throughout this first season. Um....
But Caitlin and Cisco as well...
...I think are Barry's
first true, like, friends.
We've been trying to track Snart...
...but he must have disconnected
the signal somehow.
[BARRY SIGHS]
We'll find him, Cisco.
Together.
VALDES: I think Cisco as a character
has a lot of optimism.
He sees Barry and he sees what he can do.
And it's not just his comic-book
fanboy fervor that allows him...
...to train him and push him...
...and fervently develop this technology
for him.
It's also something that he sees in Barry.
He sees a lot of potential in him.
And so I think when he sees that potential...
...he goes and he commits
to being a part of this team.
PANABAKER: I think each character
has a different reason...
...for showing up to work every day
and fighting the universe...
...and making it a better world, you know.
Caitlin does wanna change the world.
She's a doctor...
...she does wanna change
the world for the better.
Everybody has their own take
on how the loss has affected them...
...and how it propels them forward.
I think, again, that's Barry Allen's
great strength is that he--
Not only is he a hero himself, but he's able
to make other people heroes around him.
When we put our minds to it, dude,
nothing can stop us.
GUSTIN:
He doesn't take that for granted, Barry....
It's really important to Barry
that he has this team.
And then Harrison Wells who is...
...this new father figure in Barry's life.
CAVANAGH: In many ways,
Barry Allen and Harrison Wells...
...are joined at the hip, you know, they....
There's no television show The Flash
without the Flash.
There's no Flash without Harrison Wells
and Harrison Wells' ability...
...to find someone worthy.
Um....
And Barry Allen is that guy.
Barry does not pick up on the fact that
some shady things are going on with Wells...
...as the audience finds out pretty early on.
But Barry's a little late...
...to pick up on all of those clues.
What's important is you!
Not me.
I lost everything. I lost my company.
I lost my reputation. I lost my freedom.
And then you broke your arm...
...and it healed in three hours.
We always had a notion that, uh....
That Wells...
...you know, was ultimately Barry's...
...you know, big bad rival.
Uh, and would be in his midst the whole time,
and we would develop that dynamic.
We certainly didn't know or didn't think
that it would be executed...
...to the level that it was
in the sense that Tom Cavanagh...
...was just so brilliant in the part.
The dynamic between Barry and Wells...
...knowing, and then as we let
the audience know...
...who Wells really was
and where he came from.
You know, and the irony
that he would be the one...
...to give Barry back his faith
so many times...
...because at the end of the day...
...he needed Barry to go fast enough
so that he could go home.
And so you had the villain, you know...
...teaching the good guy...
...how to be a better good guy.
And that dynamic, I think, was really fresh
and original for a show like this.
And certainly, again, with Grant and Tom
in those scenes...
...was just terrific to see.
MARTIN:
Initially with Joe West...
...I think part of Joe was really...
...jealous of the fact that Barry...
...idolized and seemingly loved
Wells so much.
I'm waiting on you, Dr. Wells.
KREISBERG: One of our favorite films
is Searching for Bobby Fischer.
And we talk a lot about how that film,
you know, the main character had sort of a--
He had three father figures...
...and it was about a boy looking for fathers...
...and, in a way,
finding this sort of ultimate father...
...by taking the best of the three fathers
that he was presented with.
It doesn't matter
that you didn't believe in me...
...because you always believed in my son.
KREISBERG: If Joe and Henry sort of represent
the heart and the soul of him...
...you know, Wells represents
everything he can be.
You keep working like you are,
you stay focused like you are...
...you will be ready the next time
your man in the yellow suit comes around.
I think you mean the Reverse-Flash.
KREISBERG:
It's like you don't want him to be--
You don't want him to be the villain.
It's not that you can look past it...
...but you wish that the awful part
wasn't true.
What if the man who killed my mom
was like me?
I think I can say unequivocally,
you are one of a kind.
That fact that he was able to still be
a father figure to this man that he hated...
...and that Barry was able
to sort of see him as a father...
...even though, you know, not knowing
his true identity, but the audience did...
...it just made all of the scenes work
on a whole other level.
KREISBERG: When you have a show like this,
you have a big bad...
...but the big bad is part of the team,
and the big bad is in some ways...
...the most likable character
on the show.
Um, we just thought it was such
an interesting way to go.
That's gonna have an impact on him.
And I think as the years go on
and we see future seasons...
...you know, the events of this year
are in some ways as...
...you know, um...
...seismic and permanent
as the events of his childhood.
And this is a very personal opponent
and it's--
That's gonna get in the way for Barry, I think...
...and he just-- He needs to focus...
...and psych himself up
and believe that he can handle this...
...and kind of put all
the personal stuff aside...
...or harness it in the right way
and let them drive him...
...but he also needs to study everything
that happened that night...
...and make sure it doesn't happen
the same way.
CAITLIN: You can't be running around the city
like some supersonic fireman.
Why not?
This is what we talked about.
Me using my speed to do good.
BERLANTI: It's not an easy answer to
sort of say kind of what makes Flash a hero...
...because it's so many great qualities,
I think...
...and he has to sort of--
Certainly in the show...
...has to rediscover that
about himself many times.
I think like most of us...
...he has his good days and his bad days...
...and they're just more extreme
because of his abilities and his capacities.
But his heart's in the right place...
...and he's always trying to do
the right thing.
Barry's attachment to people...
...people he cares about...
...is actually the key
to getting him up to speed.
He's overcome, even in childhood,
this great tragedy.
And it's-- It hasn't darkened him or made him
someone you don't wanna be around.
In fact, it's just the opposite.
And I think that reminds us all
about what's the best in all of us.
That really is his superpower,
is that ability to, you know...
...despite everything that's happened to him,
to keep marching forward...
...and not just for himself, but be able
to share that with other people.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
PANABAKER: I think seeing a real human
helps us all empathize and say:
"I could be that person,"
and believe that, "I could be the Flash.
I could get struck by lightning
and my world could be changed."
And, yes, he has the power to do
great and incredible things...
...but, you know, he isn't perfect...
...he is flawed and he's figuring it out
as he goes along.
He makes some mistakes and that also
makes him really human and relatable.
COSNETT:
Everyone else around him realizes...
...that anything's possible after this...
...and I think that's a wonderful thing
about the show, is that we all....
Um, we can all believe in the impossible,
we all believe that...
...something we thought
was not possible is possible.
Barry?
MARTIN:
I-- That's why I'm not so sure where Barry's--
What Barry's destiny could possibly be.
Hopefully, it doesn't....
It doesn't actually occur till many,
many, many years from now.
So we can still keep telling this story.
Because, I mean...
...as you know, the Flash universe is vast.
He's gonna be staying with us for a while.
GUSTIN: It's amazing. It's--
I really have, I think, slowly but surely...
...slipped more into the skin and I--
It's been a nice parallel actually with--
I can't believe this--
I have this opportunity
and this is happening to me...
...just as Barry can't believe
this happened to him...
...and he's now this superhero
and he has this responsibility.
He's growing with the character.
And I feel like I'm-- You know, I was
super awkward Barry Allen at the beginning...
...and as Barry's become the Flash...
...I've become more confident with Barry
and with being the Flash...
...and it's been kind of a nice journey
for Barry and myself...
...to kind of have a little parallel journey.
It's been fun.
FLASH:
Every kid dreams of being a superhero.
Having powers, saving people.
Truth is, not much else changes.
You still hurt, you still love...
you still wish and hope and fear things...
...and you still need people
to help you with all of it.
In some ways, that's the best part.
Supersonic punch, baby! Whoo!
FLASH:
Actually, the best part is this: