Go.
ARMEN: It's a special breed
that I think could work...
...on a show at the scale
in television. It's not easy.
We can have 150 to 200 visual-effects
shots in an episode.
And so suddenly that's spread out
over six episodes...
...it truly is as many visual-effects shots
as would be in...
...a summer blockbuster, the biggest one.
KREISBERG: At any given moment,
there's a superhero movie on TV.
I mean, there's a channel right now that is
showing something with a superhero on it.
And these are movies that have cost
hundreds of millions of dollars to make.
If you don't put on something
that's gonna compete with that...
...or certainly stand alongside of it,
people are gonna check out.
That's why it was important
from the beginning...
...to be able to make sure
that we were able to...
...pull off the level of visual effects
that we were.
ARMEN: When we hire people,
we let them know that it's a TV schedule.
There's some amazing feature guys out there,
but the pace that they're used to...
...is a little bit of a different pace
than what our TV guys are used to...
...but the quality has to be similar.
BREDERECK: We learned a lot
from feature films...
...and we use a lot
of feature-film technology.
But we kind of have to find, then,
always like the most efficient solution...
...to then make the deadline
and, you know, like...
...have those shows on air, on time.
Everybody is excited about that show
and wants it to look as good as possible.
And it's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
And we have a lot of people
that have that spirit...
...and just push every day to,
you know, like, create the impossible.
KREISBERG:
A lot of it is the technology...
...but a lot of it is also just
the will, and the desire, and the creativity.
You know, I mean, our show
obviously costs a lot of money to make...
...but there are other shows
that cost a lot more money.
And I think it really is a question of
the desire to sort of make these things work.
ARMEN: I try to do something
that hasn't been done before.
And it's just going up to my guys
and saying:
"I know this is hard.
I know we don't do this regularly.
But this is what we're gonna need."
And just moving forward with them.
We have a really good reference,
the comic book.
Obviously a lot of things don't translate over
from the comic book over to live-action...
...but we've been able to
do it as closely as possible.
BREDERECK: There's, like, a huge phase
of research and development...
...where we kind of, like, come up
with looks and solutions...
...um, to just come up with
all those crazy effects required to...
...you know, bring those comic book
events to real television.
And it's also, um, very important
to do, like, a lot of pre-visualization...
...to show the show creators very early on
what we're planning to do...
...and what will be CG, what will be
practical, and all that kind of stuff.
It really is a combination of things...
...that usually take people
sometimes a year to work on.
And we're doing it in a few months.
It's definitely a lot of planning...
...and a lot of putting heads together...
...and coming up with
the best and fastest solution.
We'd heard horror stories
about the '90s Flash series.
That they'd been taken off
and put back on several times...
...in part because they couldn't make their
air dates with the visual effects.
So the second we had a story idea
and what a character could be...
...we would get that
to our Visual Effects Department...
...months before
they would typically get a script...
...so that they could start the R & D
on those characters...
...so we could be ahead of the curve.
What the hell?
We always do get a good heads-up
from our producers of:
"This is coming up.
This is a very important episode."
Early after the pilot, Greg called me and said
there was gonna be a train crash...
...where Flash goes in
and saves a bunch of people.
I mean, if I knew that two weeks before
I was gonna work on it...
...I would never make the air date.
But again it's knowing in advance
and putting a special team on that...
...saying, "This is what we have to do."
And we started propping early as far as,
like, building the asset of the train...
...and thinking about
the kind of shots we wanted.
Got in touch with a local
storyboard artist here...
...and kind of worked out
what the shots would be.
And after everybody approved it,
what we did, you know...
...which is what you see behind me,
is the animatic...
...to show the moving version of the beats...
...that we thought would tell
the story that they wanted to be told.
The animatic is basically an extension
of the storyboards. It's a moving storyboard.
And after the storyboards are complete,
once you have the animatic...
...you kind of know
what the blocking of the scene is...
...and you know exactly what it should
look like when it's complete.
Obviously the elements are really raw...
...and it's all gray-shaded, and it's--
Nothing looks believable.
But the animatic, it plays a big role...
...in the planning of the shots
and planning of the scenes.
You know, it was just basically
Snart's on the train.
Uh, he causes the train to freeze
on the bottom.
So we kind of embellished it,
added some cool shots...
...you know, extended
the whole train crash...
After the animatic stage, uh,
you know, we sent that to Production...
...so the DP, director, everybody
could take a look at it...
...so they knew
the kind of plates that we needed.
TARANYAN:
Sometimes you'll cut to shots where...
...you're having to put them
into a live-action plate.
So was our job to kind of
be able to match the look...
...to the surrounding shots that were shot
with an actual camera on a location.
A good plate is a very good starting point.
You know, so it's amazing
to have plates like we have.
So they did a really good job
shooting those plates.
ARMEN: We work very closely
with our directors of photography...
...as far as, uh, sequences.
They come up with suggestions, too,
to make--
You know, again,
to add more dynamic to the shots.
And, you know, ask us,
you know, respectfully, like:
"Is this possible to do? It might be hard."
And again, we're all for,
"If it makes the shot great, let's do it."
You know, there's very few instances
that we've said no to them.
MAN: Cut.
ARMEN: We do work very closely with them.
You know, I do have a data wrangler
in Vancouver...
...who's able to get
all the lens data, measurements...
...we do HDR photography
for light and reflections.
I mean, we have a pretty tight department
to be able to get everything we need...
...so we could,
you know, finish the shots here.
TARANYAN: We do have visual-effects
supervisor that's there to actually tell them...
...if something is working
versus something that's not.
And, uh, that's kind of like the bridge
that we have...
...with, uh, the Camera Department,
is through the visual effects supervisor.
Three, two, one, go.
MAN:
Action.
[GRUNTS]
ARMEN:
This was an actual plate...
...that we shot pulling back
with a stunt girl kind of hanging.
And it was all-digital Flash going through...
...and saving her.
So she was kind of--
I mean, we shot her in slow motion...
...but she was kind of on a rig.
So it looked like she was suspended
in time.
And we had the Hair Department
actually hairspray her hair...
...so it felt like it was
kind of floating in the air.
And it was, yeah, a stunt girl that was
kind of just hanging there the whole time.
She was harnessed. There was, I believe,
a rig underneath her and also on top...
...just to kind of put her in the position
that she's in mid-air.
And then, you know, we paint that out.
And he was completely digital in this shot.
The digital version of the Flash is...
...pretty much outfit with any kind of joints
or bones you find in a real human being.
Basically it's a model of the actor
with all of his features...
...like the skin, the pores of the skin...
...or the gold of his costume,
the leather of his costume...
...all that re-created in the computer.
And it's basically enabling us
to, um, let him do things...
...that he could never do as an actor,
or even as a stunt guy.
Like for example, running up a building...
...or beating somebody up really quickly...
...all those things are possible...
...because we have
a computer-animated version of him.
Instead of just using
photographs, um, of the actor...
...we are going through
a complex scanning process...
...where we basically get not just
a two-dimensional image of the actor...
...but actually a three-dimensional
scan of the actor.
So-- And it's so detailed that
we get skin pores...
...we get little hairs and other things...
...we get, like, all the costume details
and all that.
All that process gives us tons of data.
We get, like, a 3D scalp
that is basically our base...
...for creating the digital double.
It's a multiple-step process,
you know, like, we have to go from--
Light stage, you know,
they do all the scanning...
...and then it goes through
a rigging process.
When we get a scan,
we get a full body, okay?
So we get a full body and there's--
Like, basically the same bones
that we have in our body...
...are put into that digital double.
And, uh, that's called the rigging process.
When it goes through the rigging process...
...then the rig is given to the animators...
...and the animators would then take it
and put it into a scene.
You put the CG model in there
and you basically animate him...
...to do whatever it is
he needs to do in the shot.
There was no motion-capture used on this.
Uh, everything is hand-animated.
After that, uh, it gets sent
to Lighting and Rendering.
They put that light in there, they give it
the highlight, they give the sheen.
If the lip is wet, they'll put a little bit
of a wet area right there.
And we did that for that shot, actually.
So those are things,
like, elements that are necessary...
...in order to make something believable.
Every muscle in his body
can be basically, like, flexed...
...or, like, moved in certain ways.
We can give him facial expressions.
You know, you see if he is, like--
I don't know, if he has fear...
...if he is, like, kind of like stressed...
...or if he's happy,
when he's running really fast.
We have all those controls built in there
on top of that...
...and then we have, like, layers and layers
of great textures and materials...
...that are basically based on
the real-world materials...
...to match him as good as possible.
And, um, in some shots, we're using
the fully, like, digitally created Barry...
...and people will probably not notice that.
For example when he grabs,
like, a missile...
...and swings it back to the drone
that was firing, and that kind of stuff.
You can get a photo of Grant, and you can
put the digital one right next to each other...
...and they're pretty much almost identical.
It's really fun to see those effects then,
like, coming together.
To understand Flash's world,
we have to basically live in his time...
...and that's why the rest of the world
has to slow down really dramatically.
And usually, like, we're getting footage...
...that got shot in
120 frames per second, or even more.
We had to come up with custom solutions
for more and more slow-motion shots.
When he moves really slowly
and you wanna see the lightning develop.
And then so we had to make it
a little bit more detailed.
[GRUNTING]
So this is our digital city.
And then this kind of shows you
the different layers that make it up.
And the reason we chose to do
a digital city with him is because...
...if you get any kind of real footage
and speed it up...
...everything in the footage speeds up,
so the cars, the people would speed up.
But this way we would have
total control...
...where the camera
is just the only thing that's sped up.
And everything would remain at the speed
that it's gonna be, you know, at.
And that was the only way
to kind of sell Flash...
...running fast through the city.
It also gave us an opportunity
to create shots...
...where we had total control over
the camera to follow him through the city.
BREDERECK: And we put
the digital version of Flash in there...
...and the animators put, like, a lot
of detail in whatever he's doing...
...also adding all the debris and the particles
that fly around, that kind of stuff.
ARMEN: There's the effects dust
and everything we added.
Sparks, debris, lens flares.
We love our lens flares here.
We have effects guys who actually then
deform the train parts that it's gonna crash...
...and, you know, give the little cracks
and, you know, whatever else is necessary.
Then our Lighting and Rendering team
gives us our beauty pass...
...which is pretty much just a raw render
of the 3D elements.
And then we have the reflection pass
and the specular pass...
...which is a separate pass
that then our compers could dial in...
...to see how much reflection
and spec that you wanna see.
The effects and dirt is generated and
simmed based on the train's movement.
So there's holdouts of the train, so the dust
could actually go around the train...
...not just the layer that's put over it.
And then, you know, we added sparks
and other, you know, bits and debris...
...you know, just to add to the chaos
of the shot, basically.
There's sparks, there's, uh, dust,
there's debris.
There's a lot of elements
that we have to throw together...
...to be able to make a shot that's believable.
As much as elements that you get from 3D,
there's still things that you need to do...
in order to get it to look, uh, real.
I'm not going out without a fight.
Good.
Because you just found one.
TARANYAN: This scene, episode six,
was something where Flash runs in...
...and he blows the doors off its hinges...
...and he just flies in
and he tries to punch out Girder.
So as far as-- From the start, you know,
all we got was just an empty plate.
Basically, what was given to us,
it was just a shot of an open room.
What we're able to do is
we track the shot, we got a camera...
...and the animators went through
and they animated Flash...
...the way he was supposed to be animated.
Then they went through
the lighting process and it came to me.
We had to paint out a flag
that was in there. The American flag...
...that's right behind him,
we had to actually paint the flag out...
...in order to be able
to replace it with a CG flag...
...because as Flash is flying by,
his force is making the flag move.
He's flying over the trophy showcase
that is made of all glass...
...so we have to be able to put reflections
of him and his lightning...
...we have to composite all that together.
Supersonic punch, baby! Whoo!
[GRUNTS]
The Flash is a character who is
in essence, in some ways, a visual effect.
And so those have to be rendered as well,
and as cleanly, and as smartly, and as real...
...to take people away, or else
all the work we're doing on the story...
...you know, or all the work they're doing
in the acting...
-...isn't gonna make a difference.
-What's happening to me?
The Flash look starting from the pilot...
...up until, like, the very end of the season
has evolved.
Now run, Barry, run.
TARANYAN: The same way his speed has
evolved from starting in the pilot...
...as he's learning to use his superpower...
...you know, the same way we were learning
how to get him to run faster...
...and push it more.
The look has developed,
the lightning has developed...
...you know, the streak,
the whole blur aspect of Flash...
...has evolved along the season.
ARMEN:
The blur is done in, you know, two ways.
You know, for the really, really wide shots...
...or shots that you really wanna
get a sense...
of him coming towards camera,
going away from camera.
Again, his digital double is animated.
You don't see him as much
because he is a blur...
...but it's still animated to generate
the lightning that comes from him.
There's different layers that we add on
to give him the signature look...
...that we're gonna give him.
The flares that we put on from the lightning,
generated from the lightning...
...those, I hope, kind of sell it again,
and give the shot depth.
ARMEN: Then you have the really, really
wide shots, which were actually Greg's idea.
We had never, you know,
discussed that during the pilot.
Where you're just a wide on a city...
...and you just see this lightning bolt
kind of going through the city.
And he thought that was really
a fun way to bridge shots.
And it's in every episode now.
And it works really well.
A lot of the blur is the lightning.
To the naked eye, you don't necessarily
see the blur part of the elements...
...but what you are seeing
is a lot of the lightning elements.
And what the lightning does
to the environment around it.
You know, it's passing cars,
it's passing people.
You know, a lot of times, the stuff
that they shoot practically.
You know, wind getting blown
when Flash comes into a scene.
Those are all things that help sell the look.
BREDERECK: What effect does he have
on the environment?
So if he runs over dry ground,
there should be a little bit dust kicking up.
If he runs through, like, let's say, an alley...
...with a lot of, like, you know,
garbage lying around...
...that needs to fly and shoot around.
And if he runs through water...
...we have to have a little bit spray.
Can I run on water?
We haven't really seen anybody
run on water before.
So basically everything
is pretty much made up.
BREDERECK: You study, like, Jet Skis
and boats and other things...
...that are going, like,
over water surface really, really quickly...
...but then you also have to
have that extra level of imagination.
So how would it look like
if somebody could run that fast over water?
What exactly will happen?
Is it a stream that just gets emitted
from behind him?
Or is it like every step is a little puddle?
BREDERECK:
We're taking our running Flash model...
...um, and then basically, like, use that...
...on top of a very, very complex
water simulation.
So we're trying to, like, simulate
what would it look like...
...and then tune it to something
that looks really, really cool...
...and looks also close
to what the comic books...
...actually, you know, like,
showed over years.
And it's basically a combination
of all those things.
TARANYAN: We have people,
like water specialists...
...that try to simulate all these elements...
...and go through a whole shading process
to make it look like water.
And all that basically gives the illusion...
...like there's somebody, like, actually
running over water...
...so fast that he's not, like, sinking in.
We've gotten pretty good with
how long it takes to do Flash...
...running through a city
and, you know, different things like that.
Those aren't as challenging anymore.
What's challenging is the big fights.
More and more, we've kind of tried
to take those to a next level.
I knew about Reverse-Flash
very early in the season.
I knew that episode nine was a big episode.
And that episode, it was in a stadium.
I think that was accidental
that it would be in a stadium...
...that our DP came up
with this cool lighting thing that happened.
Then the director said,
"It'd be cool if we did this."
And we have an amazing stunt crew
that said, "We could do this practically."
And then it's us chiming, said, "Well,
we could do this if you get us these plates."
So it becomes everyone's baby
at that point.
It's like a bunch of kids, you know, deciding
how they're gonna build their sandcastle...
...you know, just on a bigger scale.
TARANYAN: The Flash-and-Reverse-Flash,
uh, fight sequence...
...it was the first time
we're seeing Reverse-Flash...
...so the look for his lightning
hadn't been developed yet...
...and we're trying to figure out,
obviously it's gotta be a different color...
...so we figured red,
so we went with the whole red--
It was like the inverse of--
It is the reverse, you know.
So he's red with yellow lightning.
The other guy's yellow with the red lightning.
So it totally made sense.
We did a big fight
in one of the episodes where...
...you flash back to the,
you know, time that his mom died...
...and we did a slow-motion fight, uh,
inside the house.
And we did that all CG,
we scanned the set...
...we texture-mapped the set,
so we could control the camera move.
BREDERECK:
There was, like, a lot of work put in...
...to get the animation, and the staging,
and the action, and the whole story right...
...down to the wine spilling out of
Nora Allen's glass, and that kind of stuff.
And it's definitely, like,
a really cool creative process...
...where you work with the production
together to achieve the best result.
Because sometimes
they wanna do something...
...but they're not sure, can we do that?
And then we show them,
"Yes, we can. And how about this?"
I could talk a little bit about this
beginning of what we did. It's kind of cool.
So to sell that he
was jumping out of the train...
...we just set up a platform,
and kind of timed as we were driving back...
...for, you know, the stunt guy
to jump out...
...you know, to mimic that he just
jumped out of a moving train.
Good luck with that.
So many of these amazing
visual-effects shots...
...only work because of the stunt people.
You know, and our stunt team,
led by J.J. Makaro...
...who also works on Arrow...
...you know, it really is this
amazing collaborate process.
Towards the end, Flash
takes the stunt girl off camera...
...and then we had
basically stunt doubles...
...on the outside,
you know, portion of the shot...
...just kind of fall into place,
like they're being dropped off by him...
...and again, his digital double
mimic them being dropped into place...
...you know, which was the exterior shots
that came after this.
There's little we kept
from the original plate...
...except the ground
and a little bit of the background.
Kind of stepping up our game,
episode per episode.
We introduced Firestorm and featured him.
Again it was a very iconic character
that, you know, you brought to life.
I mean, it's a guy with his
head on fire, and hands on fire.
You always have the danger
of making something like that look cheesy.
So that was great to finally get a look
that I think everybody was pleased with.
When I watch a great episode of the show,
it makes me feel...
...the way the books used to make me feel
when I was a kid.
One gratifying thing about the show is
so many times when we sit back in editing...
...it really does feel like a comic book
come to life.
BERLANTI: There's a great learning curve
that happens...
...of how early you have to break stories
and figure things out...
...so you can start visual effects
and prevising those events kind of early.
BREDERECK: I'm sure the writers,
after, like, this first season...
...know that we can do pretty much,
like, anything that they imagine.
And so they will probably come up with
bigger things that will challenge us again.
Story comes first.
And we hope that with the visual effects
that we're doing...
...that we're taking lots of
those boundaries, of those limits off...
...so the writers can be creative
and can really go crazy...
...and give the fans
what they want and what they need.
It's a great feeling, the best feeling
working on this show is...
...that my 11-year-old gets to go to school...
...and tell his friends that his dad
works on The Flash.
That's the best experience, you know,
part of it, but again it's playing.
I mean, it's being able to, as an adult,
be able to take something...
...and create something out of it.
TARANYAN: The effects that
we're doing, we're trying to push--
We're pretty much pushing the limit
of what's possible...
...to do on TV, on a TV schedule.
And it's awesome and it's great, you know?
Like, we-- I have fun
working here every day, you know.
When I go home, I think about the stuff
that I'm gonna do the next day.
And it's really rewarding, you know.
And then seeing all the fans...
...and all the feedback
that we're getting from everybody...
...you know, it'sjust phenomenal.
You know, it's great.
KREISBERG:
It's just a whole new level of storytelling.
All anybody wants is to entertain people.
And all anybody wants is for it to all work.
And all anybody cares about
is making the best possible show.
And there really isn't a lot of ego.
And when you watch everybody
collaborating like that...
...and everybody coming together
to make the show look as good as it does...
...I think that, you know, is pretty special.