[THE GODFATHER THEME PLAYING]
BONASERA: I believe in America.
America has made my fortune.
And I raised my daughter
in the American fashion.
I gave her freedom, but I taught
her never to dishonor her family.
She found a boyfriend,
not an Italian.
She went to the movies
with him.
She stayed out late.
I didn't protest.
Two months ago he took her for
a drive with another boyfriend.
They made her drink whiskey
and then they tried to
take advantage of her.
She resisted,
she kept her honor.
So they beat her
like an animal.
When I went to the hospital,
her nose was broken,
her jaw was shattered,
held together by wire.
She couldn't even weep
because of the pain.
But I wept.
Why did I weep?
She was the light
of my life.
Beautiful girl.
Now she will never be
beautiful again.
[COUGHS]
Sorry.
I went to the police,
like a good American.
These two boys
were brought to trial.
The judge sentenced them
to three years in prison,
but suspended
the sentence.
Suspended the sentence!
They went free
that very day!
I stood in the courtroom
like a fool.
And those two bastards,
they smiled at me.
Then I said to my wife,
"For justice,
we must go to Don Corleone."
VITO: Why did you
go to the police?
Why didn't you
come to me first?
What do you want of me?
Tell me anything,
but do what I beg you to do.
What is that?
[WHISPERING]
I want them dead.
That I cannot do.
I'll give you
anything you ask.
We've known each
other many years,
but this is the first time you ever
came to me for counsel, for help.
I can't remember
the last time that
you invited me to your house
for a cup of coffee.
Even though my wife is
godmother to your only child.
But let's be frank here.
You never wanted
my friendship.
And you were afraid
to be in my debt.
BONASERA: I didn't want
to get into trouble.
I understand.
You found Paradise
in America.
You had a good trade,
made a good living,
Police protected you
and there were courts of law.
You didn't need
a friend like me.
But now you come
to me and you say,
"Don Corleone,
give me justice."
But you don't ask
with respect.
You don't offer friendship. You
don't even think to call me Godfather.
You said you'd come into my house on
the day my daughter is to be married
and ask me to do
murder for money.
BONASERA:
I ask you for justice.
That is not justice.
Your daughter is still alive.
Let them suffer, then,
as she suffers.
How much shall I pay you?
[CAT MEOWS]
Bonasera, Bonasera.
What have I ever done to make
you treat me so disrespectfully?
If you'd come to me
in friendship,
then the scum that ruined your daughter
would be suffering this very day.
And if by chance,
an honest man like yourself
should make enemies,
then they would become my enemies.
And then they
would fear you.
Be my friend?
Godfather?
Good.
Some day, and that day
may never come,
I'll call upon you
to do a service for me.
But, uh... until that day
accept this justice as a gift
on my daughter's wedding day.
Grazie, Godfather.
Prego.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING OUTSIDE]
Give this to Clemenza.
I want reliable people that
aren't going to be carried away.
We were not murderers,
in spite of what this undertaker says.
[BAND PLAYING
TRADITIONAL ITALIAN MUSIC]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Where's Michael?
Don't worry,
it's early
We're not taking the picture
without Michael.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
What's the matter?
It's Michael.
[ALL CHEERING]
VITO: Don Barzini.
[VITO SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Hey, Paulie!
Let me have some wine.
Paulie! More wine.
Music plays.
Ah, you look terrific
on the floor.
What, you a dance
judge or something?
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Go take a walk around
the neighborhood.
Do your job.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Hey Sandra, come on, do me a favor.
Watch the kids.
Don't let them run wild,
all right?
Well, you watch
yourself, all right?
[BAND PLAYING MAZURKA]
20, 30 grand.
In small bills, cash.
In that little silk purse.
If this were somebody else's wedding...
Sfortunato!
Hey, Paulie!
I got two gabagool,
capocol, and a prosciut.
PAULIE: Stupid jerk!
Hey, what's the matter?
Have to go back to work.
Oh, Tom.
It's part of the wedding.
No Sicilian can refuse any request
on his daughter's wedding day.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Don Corleone, I am honored and grateful
that you have invited me to your home.
Hey!
Partire. Get out of here!
It's a private party.
Go on!
What is it?
Hey, it's my sister's wedding.
SONNY: Goddamn FBI
don't respect nothing!
Hey! Come here, come here,
come here, come here!
...but towards the end, he was paroled
to help with the American war effort,
so for the last six months he's
been working in my pastry shop.
Nazorine, my friend,
What can I do for you?
Now that
the war is over,
this boy, Enzo, they want to
repatriate him back to Italy.
Godfather, I have a daughter.
You see, she and Enzo...
You want Enzo to stay in this country,
and your daughter to be married.
NAZORINE: You understand
everything.
Mr. Hagen. Thank you.
Wait till you see the beautiful
wedding cake I made for your daughter!
Oof, like this! [CHUCKLES]
The bride and the groom
with the angel...
Who should I give
this job to?
Not to our paisan.
Give it to a Jew Congressman in another
district. Who else is on the list?
Hey, Michael!
[ALL GREETING]
TOM: He's not on the list,
but Luca Brasi wants to see you.
Is this...
Is this necessary?
He didn't expect to be invited to the
wedding, so he wanted to thank you.
All right.
Don Corleone, I'm honored and grateful
that you have invited me to your home
on the wedding day
of your daughter.
May their first child
be a masculine child.
Michael...
That man over there
is talking to himself.
See that scary guy
over there?
He's a very scary guy.
Well, who is he?
What's his name?
His name is Luca Brasi.
He helps my father out sometimes.
Oh Michael, wait...
He's coming over here!
Michael!
[EXCLAIMS]
Hey!
You look terrific!
My brother Tom Hagen,
Miss Kay Adams.
How do you do?
Nice to meet you. How do you do, Tom?
Your father's been
asking for you.
Very nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
If he's your brother,
why does he have a different name?
Oh, back when my brother,
Sonny, was a kid,
he found Tom Hagen
on the street.
And he had no home, and so
my father took him in.
And he's been with us
ever since.
He's a good lawyer.
Not a Sicilian.
I think he's going
to be consigliere.
What's that?
That's a,
like a counselor, an advisor.
Very important to the family.
You like your lasagna?
Don Corleone.
I am honored and grateful
that you have invited me
to your daughter's wedding.
[PAPER RUSTLING]
On the day of
your daughter's wedding.
And I hope that their first
child will be a masculine child.
I pledge my
ever-ending loyalty.
For your daughter's
bridal purse.
Thank you, Luca.
My most valued friend.
Don Corleone, I'm going to leave
you now, because I know you're busy.
Thank you.
[ALL SINGING]
SignoraCorleone!
No! No! No!
[CHATTERING]
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[SINGING CHE LA LUNA]
[ALL SINGING]
Senator Cauley apologized for not coming
personally, but said you'd understand.
Also some of the judges.
They've all sent gifts.
[TOASTING IN ITALIAN]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
What is that outside?
Johnny! Johnny! Johnny!
I love you!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
He came all the way from
California to come to the wedding.
I told you he was
going to come!
Been two years.
He's probably in trouble again.
He's a good godson.
Johnny, Johnny!
Sing a song!
[ALL CHEERING]
You never said
you knew Johnny Fontane!
Sure.
You want to meet him?
Huh? Oh...
Great! Sure.
My father helped him
with his career.
He did?
How?
[JOHNNY SINGING
I HAVE BUT ONE HEART]
Let's listen to this song.
No, Michael...
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
♪ This heart I bring you
♪ I have but one heart
♪ To share with you
♪ I have but one dream
♪ That I can cling to
♪ You are the one dream
♪ I pray comes true
Please, Michael. Tell me.
♪ My, darling,
until I saw you ♪
Well, when Johnny
was first starting out,
he was signed to this
personal service contract
with a big bandleader.
And as his career
got better and better,
he wanted to get out of it.
Now, Johnny
is my father's godson.
And my father went
to see this bandleader.
And he offered him $10,000
to let Johnny go,
but the bandleader
said no.
So the next day
my father went to see him,
only this time with Luca Brasi.
And within an hour,
he signed a release for a
certified check of $1,000.
Well, how did he do that?
My father made him an
offer he couldn't refuse.
What was that?
Luca Brasi held a gun
to his head,
and my father assured him
that either his brain
or his signature
would be on the contract.
That's a true story.
[SINGING IN ITALIAN]
That's my family, Kay.
It's not me.
[ALL APPLAUDING]
MAMA CORLEONE: Beautiful!
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
I'll take care of it.
Tom...
I want you to find Santino.
Tell him to come
to the office.
How are you, Fredo?
Fredo. My brother Fredo,
this is Kay Adams.
Hi.
How are you doing?
This is my brother Mike.
Are you having
a good time? Huh?
Yeah. This is your friend, huh?
JOHNNY: I don't
know what to do.
My voice is weak.
It's weak.
Anyway, if I had this part
in the picture, you know,
it puts me right back
up on top again.
But this...
This man out there. He won't give
it to me, the head of the studio.
What's his name?
Woltz. Woltz, he...
He won't give it to me,
and he says there's no chance.
No chance.
TOM: Sonny?
Sonny?
[BOTH MOANING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
TOM: Sonny?
Sonny, are you in there?
What?
The old man wants you.
All right, One minute.
[BOTH MOANING]
WOMAN: Oh, Sonny!
[SINGING IN ITALIAN]
JOHNNY: A month ago he bought the movie
rights to this book, a best-seller.
And the main character
is a guy just like me.
Why, you know, I wouldn't
even have to act.
Just be myself.
Godfather, I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
[SNIFFLES]
You can act like a man!
What's the matter with you?
Is this how you turned out? A Hollywood
finocchio that cries like a woman?
[MIMICKING JOHNNY] "What can I do?
What can I do?"
What is that nonsense?
Ridiculous.
You spend time
with your family?
Sure I do.
Good.
Because a man who doesn't spend time
with his family can never be a real man.
You look terrible.
I want you to eat.
Want you to rest well,
and in a month from now
this Hollywood big shot's
gonna give you what you want.
It's too late,
they start shooting in a week.
I'm going to make him
an offer he can't refuse.
Now, just go outside, enjoy yourself,
and forget about all this nonsense.
I want you to
leave it all to me.
All right.
[BAND PLAYING]
What time does my daughter
leave with the bridegroom?
In a few minutes,
right after they cut the cake.
Now your new son-in-law,
do we give him something important?
Never. Give him a living,
but never discuss the family
business with him.
What else?
Virgil Sollozzo called.
Now, we're gonna have to give
him a day sometime next week.
We'll discuss it when you
come back from California.
When am I going
to California?
I want you to go tonight.
I want you to talk to this movie big shot
and settle this business for Johnny.
Now if there's nothing else,
I'd like to go to
my daughter's wedding.
Carlo, we're going to
take the picture.
MICHAEL: Wait a minute.
KAY: No, Michael. Not me.
Okay, that's it.
Just like that now. Hold it!
[BAND PLAYING WALTZ]
[BELL RINGING]
[ALL CHATTERING]
MAN: You need a little
more heat on that arc.
All right, start talking.
I was sent by a friend
of Johnny Fontane.
This friend is my client. He would give
his undying friendship to Mr. Woltz,
if Mr. Woltz would
grant us a small favor.
Woltz is listening.
Give Johnny the part in that new
war film you're starting next week.
[CHUCKLES]
And, uh... What favor would
your friend grant Mr. Woltz?
You're gonna have some union problems,
my client could make them disappear.
Also one of your top stars has just
moved from marijuana to heroin.
Are you trying to muscle me?
Absolutely not...
Now, listen to me,
you smooth talking son-of-a-bitch!
Let me lay it on the line for
you and your boss, whoever he is.
Johnny Fontane will
never get that movie!
I don't care how many
Dago Guinea wop greaseball
goombahs come out of the woodwork!
I'm German-Irish.
Well, let me tell you
something, my Kraut-Mick friend.
I'm going to make so much trouble
for you! You won't know what hit ya.
Mr. Woltz. I'm a lawyer.
I have not threatened...
I know almost every big lawyer in
New York. Who the hell are you?
I have a special practice.
I handle one client.
Now you have my number,
I'll wait for your call.
By the way, I admire
your pictures very much.
Check him out.
It's really beautiful.
Look at this.
It used to decorate
a king's palace.
Yeah. Very nice.
WOLTZ: Why didn't you say
you work for Corleone, Tom?
I thought you were some
cheap two-bit hustler
Johnny was running in,
trying to bluff me.
I don't like to use his name
until it's really necessary.
WOLTZ:
How's your drink, Tom? Fine.
Hey come on over here with me. I wanna
show you something really beautiful.
You do appreciate
beauty, don't you?
There you are.
$600,000 on four hoofs.
I'll bet Russian czars never paid
that kinda dough for a single horse.
Khartoum.
I'm not going
to race him, though.
I'm going to put
him out to stud.
Thanks, Tony.
Welcome.
Let's get something
to eat, huh?
TOM: Corleone is
Johnny's godfather.
To the Italian people that's a very
religious, sacred, close relationship.
WOLTZ: And I respect that.
Just tell him, he should
ask me anything else.
But this is one favor
I can't give him.
Well, he never asks a second favor
when he's been refused the first.
Understood?
You don't understand.
Johnny Fontane never
gets that movie.
That part is perfect for him.
It'll make him a big star.
I'm going to run him out of the
business, and let me tell you why.
Johnny Fontane ruined one of Woltz
International's most valuable proteges.
For five years,
we had her under training.
Singing lessons, acting
lessons, dancing lessons.
I spent hundreds of thousands
of dollars on her,
I was gonna make
her a big star.
And let me be
even more frank.
Just to show you that
I'm not a hardhearted man.
That it's not all
dollars and cents.
She was beautiful.
She was young, she was innocent!
She's the greatest
piece of ass I've had
and I've had them
all over the world.
And then Johnny Fontane comes along with
his olive oil voice and Guinea charm.
And she runs off.
She threw it all away just
to make me look ridiculous!
And a man in my position can't
afford to be made to look ridiculous!
Now you get
the hell out of here!
If that goombah
tries any rough stuff,
you tell him
I ain't no bandleader.
Yeah, I heard that story.
Thank you for the dinner
and a very pleasant evening.
Maybe your car can
take me to the airport.
Mr. Corleone is a man who insists
on hearing bad news immediately.
[WOLTZ SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
You're not too tired,
are you, Tom?
Oh, no, I slept
on the plane.
I have the
Sollozzo notes here.
Now...
Sollozzo is known
as The Turk.
He's supposed to be
very good with a knife,
but only in matters of business with
some sort of reasonable complaint.
Uh, his business is narcotics.
He has fields in Turkey,
where they grow poppy.
In Sicily he has plants
to process them into heroin.
Now, he needs cash,
he needs protection from the police.
For which, he gives
a piece of the action.
I couldn't find out how much.
The Tattaglia family is
behind him here in New York.
Now, they have to be
in it for something.
What about his
prison record?
Two terms.
One in Italy, one here.
He's known as
a top narcotics man.
Santino,
what do you think?
A lot of money
in that white powder.
Tom?
TOM: Well I say, Yes.
There's more money potential in narcotics than anything else we're looking at.
Now, if we don't get into it, somebody else will,
Maybe the five families,
maybe all of them
Now with the money they earn,
they can buy more Police
and political power.
Then they come after us.
Now we have the unions,
we have the gambling,
and they're the best
things to have,
but narcotics is the thing
of the future.
If we don't get a piece
of that action,
we risk everything we have.
I mean, not now,
but in 10 years from now.
So? What's your answer
gonna be, Pop?
Don Corleone.
I need a man who
has powerful friends.
I need a million
dollars in cash.
I need, Don Corleone,
those politicians
you carry in your pocket,
like so many nickels and dimes.
What is the interest
for my family?
30%.
In the first year your end should
be three, four million dollars.
And then it would go up.
And what is the interest
for the Tattaglia family?
My compliments.
I'll take care of the
Tattaglias, out of my share.
So I receive 30%
for finance,
political influence and legal protection,
that's what your telling me?
That's right.
Why do you come to me?
Why do I deserve this generosity?
If you consider a million
dollars in cash just finance,
te salud, Don Corleone.
I said that I would see you, because
I heard that you were a serious man,
to be treated
with respect.
But, I must say no to you.
And I'll give you
my reasons.
It's true,
I have a lot of friends in politics.
But they wouldn't be
friendly very long
if they knew my business was
drugs instead of gambling,
which they regard
as a harmless vice,
but drugs
is a dirty business. Oh, Don Corleone...
It doesn't make any difference to me
what a man does for a living, understand.
But your business is...
A little dangerous.
If you're worried about
security for your million,
the Tattaglias
will guarantee it.
Are you telling me the Tattaglias
would guarantee our investment...
Wait a minute.
I have a sentimental weakness for my children,
and I spoil them, as you can see...
They talk when
they should listen.
But anyway...
SignorSollozzo,
my no is final.
And I wish to congratulate
you on your new business.
I know you'll do very well,
and good luck to you.
Especially since your interests
don't conflict with mine. Thank you.
Santino.
Come here.
What's the matter with you?
I think your brain is going soft from all that
comedy you're playing with that young girl.
Never tell anybody outside the
family what you're thinking again.
Go on.
Tom, what...
What is this nonsense?
It's from Johnny.
He's starring in that new film.
Huh.
Take it away.
Take it over there.
And, uh...
tell Luca Brasi
to come in.
I'm a little worried
about this Sollozzo fellow.
I want you to find out what he's
got under his fingernails, you know.
Go to the Tattaglias.
Make them think that you're
not too happy with our family
and find out
what you can.
[HAVE YOURSELF A MERRY LITTLE
CHRISTMAS PLAYING ON RADIO]
♪ Let your heart be light
I got something for your
mother and for Sonny
and a tie for Freddy,
and Tom Hagen got the Reynolds pen.
What do you want
for Christmas?
Me? Oh... Just you.
[ON RADIO]
♪ Make the Yule-tide gay
♪ From now on our troubles
will be miles away
♪ Here we are
as in olden days
♪ Happy golden days of yore
♪ Faithful friends... ♪
VITO: Andiamo, Fredo.
Tell Paulie to get the car.
We're going.
FREDO: Okay, Pop.
I'll have to get it
myself, Pa.
Paulie called in
sick this morning.
Paulie's a good kid.
I don't mind getting the car.
Buon natale, Caro.
Grazie.
Luca!
I'm Bruno Tattaglia.
I know.
[BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN]
You know who I am?
I know you.
You have been talking to the
Tattaglia family... right?
I think you and I
can do business.
I need someone strong like you.
I heard you are not happy...
...with the Corleone family.
Want to join me?
What's in it for me?
$50,000 to start with.
Not bad.
Agreed?
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
[GASPING]
Tom! Tom Hagen.
Merry Christmas.
Hey! I'm glad I ran into you.
I want to talk to you.
Well, I haven't got time.
Make time, Consigliere.
Get in the car.
What are you worried about? If I wanted
to kill you, you'd be dead already.
Get in.
[CAROLS PLAYING ON RADIO]
Fredo, I'm going to
buy some fruit.
Okay, Pop.
Merry Christmas.
I want some fruit.
[WHIMPERING]
[SOBBING]
[SHOUTING]
[BELL TOLLING]
Mike, Would you like me
better if I were a nun?
Like in the story.
No.
Well then, would you like me
better if I were Ingrid Bergman?
Now, that's a thought.
Michael.
No, I wouldn't like you better
if you were Ingrid Bergman.
Mike.
What's the matter?
They don't say
if he's dead or alive.
[HORN BLARING]
Sonny, Michael.
Michael, where you been?
Is he all right?
We don't know yet.
There are all
kinds of stories.
He was hit bad, Mikey.
Are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Where have you been?
I was worried.
Didn't Tom tell you
I called?
No. Look, come home, kid.
You should be with Mama,
you hear? All right.
SANDRA: Oh, my God.
[CLATTERING]
[GASPING]
Sonny!
[BABY CRYING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Stay back there.
Who is it?
Open up, it's Clemenza.
There's more news
about your old man.
Word is out that
he's already dead.
What's the matter...
What's the matter with you?
Take it easy!
Where was Paulie?
Paulie was out sick.
He's been sick all winter.
How many times
he been sick?
Only maybe three, four times.
I mean, I asked Freddy if he wants
me to get a different bodyguard
He said no. Pick him up now.
Do me a favour, pick him up right now.
I don't care how sick he is.
If he's breathing,
I want you to bring him to my father's
house now, you understand? Now.
Yeah, You want me to
send any people over here?
No, no, no. Just you and him.
Go ahead.
[BABY CRYING]
Okay, I'm...
I'm going to have a couple of our people
come over to the house. Couple of our people.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello?
SOLLOZZO:
Santino Corleone?
Yeah.
We have Tom Hagen.
You got three hours he'll be
released with our proposition.
Listen to everything he has
to say before you do anything.
What's done is done.
And don't lose that famous
temper of yours, eh, Sonny?
I'll wait.
[HANGS UP]
SOLLOZZO:
Your boss is dead.
I know you're not in the
muscle end of the family, Tom,
so I don't want
you to be scared.
I want you to help the Corleones
and I want you to help me.
Yeah, we got him outside his office just
about an hour after we picked you up.
Drink it.
So now, It's up to you to make
the peace between me and Sonny.
Sonny was hot for my deal,
wasn't he?
And you knew it was
the right thing to do.
Sonny will come after you
with everything he's got.
That will be his
first reaction, sure.
So you gotta talk
some sense into him.
The Tattaglia family is behind
me with all their people.
The other New York families will go along with
anything that will prevent the full-scale war.
Let's face it, Tom
and all due respect,
the Don, rest in peace,
was slipping.
Ten years ago,
could I have gotten to him?
Well, now he's dead.
He's dead, Tom,
and nothing can bring him back.
So you gotta talk to Sonny,
You gotta talk to the Caporegimes,
Tessio, and that fat Clemenza.
It's good business, Tom.
I'll try. But even Sonny won't
be able to call off Luca Brasi.
Yeah, well...
Let me worry about Luca.
You just talk to Sonny.
And the other two kids.
I'll do my best.
Good.
Now you can go.
I don't like violence, Tom.
I'm a businessman.
Blood is a big expense.
[HORN HONKING]
He's still alive.
They hit him with five
shots, and he's still alive!
That's bad luck for me, and bad luck
for you if you don't make that deal.
Your mother is over in the
hospital with your father.
Looks like he's gonna
pull through. Thank God.
It's a lot of
bad blood.
Sollozzo, Philip Tattaglia,
Bruno Tattaglia, Ramon...
MICHAEL: You gonna
kill all those guys?
Hey, stay out of it, Mickey.
Do me a favour.
TOM: Sollozzo's the key, you get rid
of him, everything falls into line.
What about Luca?
Sollozzo thinks he can control him.
I don't know if Luca sold out, we're in a
lot of trouble. Believe me, lot of trouble.
Has anyone been
in touch with Luca?
Yeah, we've been trying all night.
He might be shacked up.
Hey, Mickey, do me a favor...
TOM: Luca never
sleeps over with a broad.
Well, Tom,
you're consigliere.
What do we do if the old man dies?
God forbid.
If we lose the old man,
we lose the political contacts
and half our strength.
The other New York families
might wind up supporting Sollozzo
just to avoid a long,
destructive war.
This is almost 1946.
Nobody wants bloodshed anymore.
If your father dies,
you make the deal, Sonny.
You know, that's easy for you to
say, Tom. He's not your father.
I was as much a son
to him, as you or Mike.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
What is it?
Paulie, I told you
to stay put.
Well, the guy
at the gates. They...
They said they
got a package. Yeah?
Tessio, go see
what it is.
You want me
to hang around?
SONNY: Yeah, hang around.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah?
There's some food in the house.
Are you hungry or anything?
No, it's all right.
How about a drink? How about a little
brandy? It's good to sweat it out.
All right, sure.
Go ahead.
That might be
a good idea. Yeah, right.
I want you to take care of that
son-of-a-bitch, right away.
Paulie sold out
the old man. That stronz...
I don't wanna
see him again.
Make that the first thing on your list.
Understand?
Understood.
Hey, Mickey, tomorrow,
You get a couple of guys,
you go over to Luca's apartment.
Hang around,
wait for him to show up.
Uh, maybe we shouldn't get Mike
mixed up in this too directly.
Listen, uh... Hanging around the house
on the phone would be a big help, huh.
Try Luca again.
What's the hell is this?
TESSIO: That's
a Sicilian message.
It means Luca Brasi
sleeps with the fishes.
[CHILDREN YELLING]
I'm going now. What time are
you gonna be home tonight?
I don't know.
Probably late.
WOMAN: Don't
forget the cannoli!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rocco, sit on the other side.
You block the
rear-view mirror.
That Sonny's running wild.
He thinking of going
to the mattresses already.
We gotta find a spot
on the West Side.
Try 309 West 43rd Street.
You know any good spots
on the West Side?
Yeah, I'll think about it.
Well, think about it while
you're driving, will ya?
I want to hit New York
sometime this month.
And watch out for the kids
when you're backing out.
CLEMENZA: Hey, Paulie, I want you to
go down 39th Street, Carlo Santos,
pick up 18 mattresses for the guys
to sleep with, you bring me the bill.
PAULIE: Yeah, all right.
CLEMENZA: Make sure
they're clean,
because those guys are gonna be stuck up in there for a long time, you know.
PAULIE: They're clean and they told
me, they exterminate them.
CLEMENZA: [CHUCKLING] That's a bad word to use.
Exterminate! Look at this guy. Watch out, so we don't exterminate you!
[CLEMENZA CHATTERING IN ITALIAN]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
CLEMENZA: Pull over.
I've got to take a leak.
[SHIP HORN BLOWING]
[SEAGULLS CAWING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR DOOR OPENING]
Leave the gun.
Take the cannoli.
CLEMENZA: Hey, Mike!
Hey, Mikey!
Yeah. You're wanted
on the telephone.
Who is it?
Some girl.
Hello. Kay?
KAY: How's your father?
He's good.
He's going to make it.
I love you.
Huh?
I love you!
Michael?
Yeah, I know.
Tell me you love me.
I can't talk.
Can't you say it?
Yeah, I'll see
you tonight.
Hey Mikey, why don't you tell
that nice girl you love her?
I love you with all my heart. If I don't
see you again soon, I'm going to die!
[CLEMENZA CHUCKLING]
Come over here kid,
learn something.
You never know, you might have
to cook for 20 guys some day.
You see, you start out with a little
bit of oil, then you fry some garlic.
Then you throw in some tomatoes, tomato paste,
you fry it and make sure it doesn't stick.
You get it to a boil, you shove in
all your sausage and your meatballs.
Add a little bit
of wine.
And a little bit of sugar.
And that's my trick.
Why don't you cut the crap.
I have more important things
for you to do. How's Paulie?
Oh, Paulie.
Won't see him no more.
Where are you going?
To the city.
Send some bodyguards
with him, all right?
No, I'm just going
to the hospital...
Nevermind, send
somebody with him.
CLEMENZA: He'll be all right.
Sollozzo knows he's a civilian.
Be careful, huh?
Yes, sir.
Send somebody
with him anyway.
[ALL OF MY LIFE
PLAYING ON RADIO]
I have to go.
Can I go with you?
No, Kay. There's gonna be detectives
there, people from the press.
Well, I'll wait
in the cab.
I don't want you
to get involved.
When will
I see you again?
Go back to New Hampshire,
and I'll call you
at your parents' house.
When will I see you
again, Michael?
I don't know.
[DOOR CLOSES]
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed
to be here now.
I'm Michael Corleone.
This is my father.
There's nobody here.
What happened to the guards?
Your father just had
too many visitors.
They interfered
with hospital service.
The police made them leave
about 10 minutes ago.
Get me Long Beach
45620, please.
Nurse. Wait a minute.
Stay here.
Sonny, Michael.
I'm at the hospital.
Listen, I got here late,
there's nobody here. SONNY: What? Nobody?
Nobody. No Tessio's men, no
detectives, nobody. Papa's all alone.
Don't panic.
I won't panic.
I'm sorry,
but you will have to leave.
Uh...
You and I are going to move
my father to another room.
Now, can you disconnect those
tubes so we can move the bed out?
That's out of
the question!
Do you know my father?
Men are coming
here to kill him.
Do you understand?
Now, help me, please.
[DOOR CLOSING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Who are you?
I am Enzo, the baker.
Do you remember me?
Enzo.
Yes, Enzo.
You'd better go,
there's going to be trouble.
If there is trouble,
I'll stay here to help you.
For your father.
All right. Listen.
Wait for me outside,
in front of the hospital,
all right?
I'll be out in a minute.
Go ahead.Okay.
Just lie here, Pop.
I'll take care of you now.
I'm with you now.
I'm with you.
Get rid of these.
Come here.
Put your hand in your pocket, like
you have a gun. You'll be all right.
[MICHAEL SIGHS]
[WHISPERING]
You'll be okay.
[CAR APPROACHING]
You did good.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I thought I got all you
Guinea hoods locked up!
What the hell
are you doing here?
What happened to the men
who were guarding my father?
Why, you little punk!
What the hell are you doing
telling me my business!
I pulled them
guys offa here, eh.
Now you get outta here and
stay away from this hospital!
I'm not moving until you put some
guys around my father's room.
Phil, take him in!
The kid's clean, Captain.
He's a war hero.
He's never been...
God damn it.
I said take him in!
What's The Turk paying you
to set up my father, Captain?
Take a hold of him.
Stand him up.
Stand him up straight.
[GRUNTS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I'm the attorney for
the Corleone family.
These men are private detectives
hired to protect Vito Corleone.
They're licensed
to carry firearms.
If you interfere, you'll have
to appear before the judge
in the morning
and show cause.
All right.
Let him go.
Come on.
What's with
all the new faces?
We'll need
them now.
After the hospital thing,
Sonny got mad.
We hit Bruno Tattaglia
four o'clock this morning.
Jesus Christ.
Looks like
a fortress around here.
Tamaduch! Hey...
A 100 buttonmen on the
street 24 hours a day.
That Turk shows one hair
on his ass, he's dead.
Hey, Mike, come here.
Let me look at you.
You're beautiful, beautiful.
You're gorgeous.
Hey, listen to this.
The Turk, he wants to talk!
Imagine the nerve
of the son-of-a-bitch, eh?
Craps all last night.
He wants a meeting today.
What did he say?
What did he say...
[BABBLING]
He wants us to send Michael
to hear the proposition.
And he promises that the deal
is too good to refuse.
Eh?
What about Bruno Tattaglia?
That's part
of the deal.
Bruno cancels out what
they did to my Father.
Sonny, we ought to hear
what they have to say.
No. No. No more!
Not this time, Consigliere.
No more meetings, no more discussions,
no more or Sollozzo tricks.
You give them one message.
I want Sollozzo,
or then it's all out war,
we go to ...
The other families
won't sit still...
They hand me
Sollozzo!
I don't want to hear this!
This is business, not personal!
They shot my father...
Even the issue with your father
was business, not personal, Sonny.
Well, then business will have to
suffer, all right?
And listen,
do me a favor, Tom.
No more advice
on how to patch things up.
Just help me win,
please, all right?
[SIGHS]
I found out about this Captain
McCluskey, who broke Mike's jaw.
What about him?
He's definitely on Sollozzo's
payroll, and for big money.
See?
McCluskey has agreed
to be The Turk's bodyguard.
What you have
to understand, Sonny,
is that while Sollozzo is being
guarded like this, he's invulnerable.
Nobody has ever gunned down a
New York police captain. Never.
It would be disastrous. All the five
families would come after you, Sonny.
The Corleone family
would be outcasts!
Even the old man's political
protection would run for cover.
So, do me a favor.
Take this into consideration.
[SIGHS]
All right, we'll wait.
We can't wait.
I don't care what Sollozzo
says, about a deal,
he's going to kill Pop.
That's it.
That's the key for him.
We've got to get Sollozzo.
Mike is right.
SONNY: Let me ask you something.
I mean...
What about
this McCluskey, eh?
What do we do
with this cop here?
They want to have a meeting with
me, right?
It will be me,
McCluskey and Sollozzo.
Let's set the meeting.
Get our informers to find out
where it's going to be held.
Now we insist it's a public place.
A bar, a restaurant.
Some place where there's
people, so I feel safe.
They're gonna search me
when I meet them, right?
So I can't have
a weapon on me then.
But if Clemenza can figure way to
have a weapon planted there for me
then I'll kill them both.
[CLEMENZA CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
SONNY: Hey.
What are you gonna do?
Nice college boy, huh? Didn't want to
get mixed up in the family business.
Now you want to gun down
a police captain,
why, because he slapped you
in the face a little bit, huh?
What do you think, this is the army
where you shoot them a mile away?
You got to get close like
this, bada bing!
You blow their brains all over
your nice Ivy League suit.
Come here.
You're taking this very personal.
Tom, this is business, and this man
is taking it very, very personal.
Where does it say
you can't kill a cop?
Come on, Mikey...
Tom, wait a minute.
I'm talking about a cop
that's mixed up in drugs.
I'm talking about
a dishonest cop.
A crooked cop who got mixed up in the
rackets and got what was coming to him.
That's a terrific story. We have
newspaper people on the payroll,
don't we, Tom?
They might like
a story like that.
They might.
They just might.
It's not personal, Sonny.
It's strictly business.
CLEMENZA: It's as cold
as they come.
Impossible to trace,
so you don't worry about prints, Mike.
I put a special tape on
the trigger and the butt.
Here. Try it.
What's the matter?
Is the trigger too tight?
[CHUCKLING] I don't know.
My ears!
Yeah, I left it noisy.
That way it scares away any
pain-in-the-ass innocent bystanders away.
All right. You've shot them both.
Now what do you do?
Sit down,
finish my dinner.
Come on, kid.
Don't fool around.
Just let your hand drop to your
side and let the gun slip out.
Everybody will still think
you've got it.
They're gonna be staring
at your face, Mike,
so walk out of the place
real fast, but you don't run.
Don't look nobody
directly in the eye,
but don't look away either.
Hey, they're gonna be scared
stiff of you, believe me,
so don't worry
about nothing.
You know, you're gonna
turn out all right.
You'll take a vacation,
nobody knows where,
and we're gonna
catch the hell.
How bad do you think
it's gonna be?
Pretty goddamn bad.
Probably all the other families
will line up against us.
But it's all right. These things
have to happen every five years or so.
Ten years...
How else do you get rid
of the bad blood.
Been 10 years
since the last one.
You know, you got to stop
them at the beginning.
Like they should have
stopped Hitler in Munich.
They should've never let him
get away with that.
They were just asking
for big trouble.
You know, Mike, we was all proud of you.
Being a hero and all.
Your father too.
[CLICKS]
[SIGHS]
Nothing. Not a hint.
Absolutely nothing.
Even Sollozzo's people don't know
where the meeting's gonna be held.
How much time
do we have?
They're going to pick you up in front of
Jack Dempsey's joint in an hour and a half.
Exactly an hour and a half.
CLEMENZA: We could put a tail on them.
See how that turns out.
Sollozzo would lose our
ass going around the block.
What about
the negotiator?
He's over at my place playing
pinochle with a couple of my men.
He's happy.
They're letting him win.
It's too much of a risk for Mike.
Maybe we ought to call if off, Sonny.
The negotiator keeps on playing cards
until Mike comes back safe and sound.
So why doesn't he just blast
whoever is in the goddamn car.
CLEMENZA: It's dangerous.
They'll be looking for that.
Sollozzo might not even
be in the car, Sonny!
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
I'll get it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Louis' restaurant
in the Bronx.
Is it reliable?
That's my man in
McCluskey's precinct.
A police captain has got to
be on call 24 hours a day.
He signed out at that number
between eight and ten.
Anybody know this joint?
Yeah, sure, I do.
It's perfect for us.
A small family place,
good food.
Everyone minds
his business. It's perfect.
They've got
an old-fashioned toilet.
You know, the box
and the chain thing.
We might be able to
tape the gun behind it.
All right. Mike,
you go to the restaurant,
you eat, you talk for a while,
you relax. You make them relax.
Then you get up
and you go to take a leak.
No, better still,
you ask for permission to go.
Then you come back,
you come out blasting.
And don't take any chances.
Two shots in the head apiece.
Now listen.
I want somebody good,
and I mean very good to plant that gun.
I don't want my brother
coming out of the toilet
with just his dick
in his hands, all right?
The gun will be there.
All right, listen. You drive him and
you pick him up after the job is done.
Come on.
Let's move.
Did he tell you to drop
the gun right away?
Yeah, a million times.
You don't forget.
Two shots apiece in the head as soon
as you come out the door, all right?
Let's go.
How long do you think it will
be before I can come back?
At least a year, Mike.
Listen, I'll square it with Mom, that you're
not seeing her before you leave and...
I'll get a message
to that girlfriend
when I think
the time is right.
Take care, huh?
Take care, Mike.
I'm glad you came, Mike.
I hope we can
straighten everything out.
I mean, this is terrible. It's not
the way I wanted things to go at all.
It should never
have happened.
I want to straighten
everything out.
I don't want my father
bothered anymore.
He won't be, Mike. I swear on
my children that he won't be.
But you got to keep an
open mind when we talk.
I mean, I hope you're not a
hothead like your brother Sonny.
You can't talk
business with him.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
McCLUSKEY:
Nah, he's a good kid.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry about
the other night, Mike.
I've got to frisk you, so turn
around, huh? On your knees, facing me.
[SIGHS] I guess I'm getting
too old for my job.
Too grouchy. [CHUCKLES]
Can't stand the aggravation.
You know how it is.
[SIGHS]
He's clean.
Going to Jersey?
Maybe.
[TIRES SCREECHES]
[HORNS BLARING]
Nice work, Lou.
How's the Italian food
in this restaurant?
Good. Try the veal.
It's the best in the city.
McCLUSKEY: I'll have it.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[CORK POPS]
[SIGHS]
I'm going to speak
Italian to Mike.
Go ahead.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
What I want...
What's most
important to me,
is that I have a guarantee.
No more attempts
on my father's life.
What guarantees
can I give you, Mike?
I'm the hunted one!
I missed my chance.
You think too much of me, kid.
I'm not that clever.
All I want is a truce.
I have to go
to the bathroom.
Is it all right?
When you got to go,
you got to go.
I frisked him.
He's clean.
Don't take too long.
I've frisked
a thousand young punks.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
[SOLLOZZO SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[TRAIN SCREECHING]
[CHOKING]
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIREN WAILING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[SIREN WAILING]
[BABY CRYING]
Okay, you take over.
[ALL CHATTERING]
I love you, Grandpa.
[BABY CRYING]
CONNIE: I'm sorry, Pa.
He doesn't know you yet.
All right.
Hey, big guy.
Give it to Grandpa.
Okay.
"I hope you get well, Grandpa, and wish I would
see you soon. Love, your grandson Frank."
Go with your mother.
Go on. Take them
downstairs. Go on.
Go on, Carlo,
you too.
Go on.
[ALL CHATTERING]
What's the matter
with you, Carlo?
Shut up
and set the table.
[SIGHS]
Since McCluskey's killing,
the police have been cracking
down on most our operations.
And also the other families.
There's been
a lot of bad blood.
They hit us,
so we hit them back.
Through our contacts
in the newspapers
we've been able to put out
a lot of material
about McCluskey being linked with
Sollozzo in the drug rackets.
So things are loosening up.
And I'm sending Fredo
to Las Vegas,
under the protection
of Don Francesco of L.A.
I want him to rest.
I'm going to learn
the casino business. Yeah.
[SOFTLY] Where's Michael?
It was Michael
who killed Sollozzo.
But he's safe. We're starting
to work to bring him back.
I want you to find out where that
old pimp Tattaglia is hiding.
I want his ass now.
Right now!
Hey, Sonny, things are starting
to loosen up a little bit.
If you go after Tattaglia,
all hell's gonna break loose.
Let the smoke clear.
Pop can negotiate.
No. Pop can't so nothing until
he's better. I'm gonna decide...
All right. But your war's
costing us a lot of money.
Nohting's coming in.
We can't do business.
Well, neither can they.
Don't worry about it!
We can't afford
a stalemate.
Well, there ain't
no more stalemate.
I'm gonna end it
by killing that old bastard!
You're getting a great reputation!
I hope you're enjoying it!
You just do
what I tell you to do!
God damn it! If I had a
wartime consigliere, Sicilian,
I wouldn't be in this shape!
Pop had Genco.
Look what I got.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Ma made a little dinner.
It's Sunday.
You know, niggers
are having a good time
with our policy banks
up there in Harlem.
Driving them new Cadillacs,
paying 50% on a bet.
I knew this was going to happen
when they started making big money.
Papa never talked business at
the table in front of the kids.
CARLO: Hey,
shut up, Connie...
Don't you ever tell her to shut up.
You got that?
Don't interfere.
You know, Sonny, Tom, I'd like
to talk to you maybe after dinner.
I could doing a lot more
for the family...
We don't discuss
business at the table.
[WHISTLES]
[HORN HONKS]
[IN ITALIAN]
I kiss your hand, Don Tommasino.
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
Why are you so far
from the house?
You know I'm responsible to your
father for your life.
The bodyguards are here.
It's still dangerous...
We've heard from Santino
in New York...
Your enemies know you're here.
Did Santino say when
I can go back?
Not yet.
It's out of the question.
Grazie.
Where are you going now?
[IN ENGLISH]
To Corleone.
Take my car.
[IN ITALIAN]
I want to walk.
Be careful.
[BELL TOLLING]
Michael. Corleone.
[BOTH SPEAK ITALIAN]
Where have all the men gone?
They're all dead from vendettas.
There are the names of the dead.
[IN ENGLISH] Hey, hey,
take me to the America, G.I.!
Hey, hey, take me to the America, G.I.!
Clark Gable! Hey!
America! America! Take me
to the America, G.I.!
Clark Gable, Rita Hayworth!
[GRUMBLING IN ITALIAN]
[WOMEN SINGING]
[MEN SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Mamma mia what a beauty.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
I think you got hit
by the thunderbolt.
In Sicily women are more
dangerous than shotguns.
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Did you have a good hunt?
You know all the girls
around here?
We saw some real beauties.
One of them struck our friend
like a thunderbolt.
She would tempt
the devil himself.
[REPEATING IN ITALIAN]
Really put together.
Eh, Calo?
[REPEATING IN ITALIAN]
Such hair, such mouth!
The girls around here are
beautiful... but virtuous.
This one had a purple dress...
And a purple ribbon in her hair.
A type more Greek than Italian.
[REPEATING]
Do you know her?
There's no girl like that
in this town.
My God. I understand!
[OWNER SHOUTING IN ITALIAN]
What's wrong?
Let's go.
It's his daughter.
Tell him to come here.
Call him.
[MEN CHATTERING IN ITALIAN]
Fabrizio, you translate.
[IN ENGLISH] I apologize
if I offended you.
[TRANSLATING IN ITALIAN]
I'm a stranger
in this country.
I meant no disrespect
to you or your daughter.
I'm an American,
hiding in Sicily.
My name is
Michael Corleone.
There are people who'd pay a lot
of money for that information.
But then your daughter
would lose a father...
Instead of
gaining a husband.
I want to
meet your daughter.
With your permission, and under
the supervision of your family.
With all respect.
Come to my house Sunday morning.
My name is Vitelli.
[IN ITALIAN]
What's her name?
Apollonia.
[VITELLI SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[BELL TOLLING]
[CHATTERING IN ITALIAN]
[WOMEN CHATTERING]
[COIN CLINKING]
SONNY: I'm gonna
knock you dizzy.
Save it for the library.
Come on. We've got to go
pick up my sister. Let's go.
What's the matter?
Huh?
It was my fault!
Where is he?
Sonny, please.
It was my fault.
Sonny, it was my fault.
I hit him.
I started a fight with him.
Please, Sonny.
I hit him, so he hit me...
[SHUSHING]
Okay. I'm just going to get a
doctor to come take a look at you.
Sonny, please don't do anything.
Please don't do anything.
What's the matter with you?
What am I going to do?
Make that baby an orphan
before he's born?
Huh? Hmm?
All right?
You spic slobs
still betting Yankees?
Tell them to stop
taking in action, all right?
[COMMENTATOR NARRATING
BASEBALL GAME ON RADIO]
We lost enough money
last week.
Oh. Come here,
come here, come here!
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
If you touch my sister
again, I'll kill you.
[BELL TOLLING]
[RECITING IN LATIN]
[BAND PLAYING
TRADITIONAL MUSIC]
[ALL APPLAUDING]
Hey! We weren't expecting you, Kay.
You should call.
Yes, well, I have. I mean,
I've tried writing and calling.
Now I want
to reach Michael.
Nobody knows
where he is.
We know that he's all
right, but that's all.
Uh, what was that?
Well that's an accident,
but nobody was hurt.
Tom, will you give this letter
to Michael. Please? Please.
Well, if I accepted that,
in a court could prove I have
knowledge of his whereabouts.
Now you just be patient, Kay.
He'll get in touch with you, all right?
I let my cab go, so can I come
in to call another one, please?
Come on. I'm sorry. Come on.
[KAY CLEARS THROAT]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello?
WOMAN: [ON TELEPHONE]
Is Carlo there?
Who is this?
This is a friend of Carlo's.
Would you tell him that I can't
make it tonight until later?
Bitch!
Dinner's on the table.
I'm not hungry yet.
The food is on the table.
It's getting cold.
I'll eat out later.
You just told me
to make you dinner!
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
Vafangool!
I'll vafangoolyou!
[DISHES CLATTERING]
She has a filthy mouth,
this little Guinea brat.
That's it, break it all,
you spoiled Guinea brat. Break it all!
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Why don't you bring
your whore home for dinner?
Maybe I will.
[SOBBING]
Now clean it up!
Like hell I will!
You skinny, spoiled brat.
Clean it up! Clean it up!
Clean it up! I said, clean it up!
Clean it up!
Clean it up. Clean it up!
Clean that up, you...
[SCREAMING]
Clean it!
Clean it up! Yeah, yeah.
Come on now, kill me.
Be a murderer,
like your father!
Come on! All you Corleones
are murderers anyway!
Come on!
I hate you!
Come on, kill me!
Get out of here!
I hate you!
Now I'll kill you.
You Guinea brat.
Get out of here!
[CONNIE SCREAMING]
[BABY CRYING]
Connie, what's the matter?
I can't hear you.
What is it?
Connie, talk louder.
The baby's crying.
Santino, I can't understand.
I don't know. I don't understand.
[SHUSHING]
Yeah, Connie.
[CRYING CONTINUES]
Listen to me.
You wait there.
No, you just wait there.
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch!
What's the matter?
Open the goddamn gate!
Get off your ass.
Sonny!
Sonny.
Get out of here!
Go after him, go on!
[HORN HONKING]
[TOLL BELL DINGS]
[MAN CHATTERING ON RADIO]
Son of a bitch.
Come on!
[HORN BLARING]
[COIN CLINKING]
[SCREAMING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CARS DRIVING OFF]
[GLASS CLINKING]
Give me a drop.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[GULPS]
My wife is crying upstairs.
I hear cars
coming to the house.
Consigliere of mine,
I think you should tell your
Don what everyone seems to know.
I didn't
tell Mama anything.
I was about to come up and
wake you just now and tell you.
But you needed
a drink first.
Yeah.
Well, now
you've had your drink.
They shot Sonny on the causeway.
He's dead.
[SIGHS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
I want no inquiries made.
I want no acts of vengeance.
I want you
to arrange a meeting
with the heads
of the five families.
This war stops now.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Call Bonasera.
I need him now.
[CONTINUES DIALING]
This is Tom Hagen. I'm calling
for Vito Corleone, at his request.
Oh, you owe
your Don a service.
He has no doubt
that you will repay it.
He will be at your funeral parlor
in one hour. Be there to greet him.
Well, my friend,
are you ready to do me this service?
Yes. What do you want
me to do?
I want you to use all your
powers and all your skills.
I don't want his mother
to see him this way.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Look how
they massacred my boy.
[LAUGHING]
[BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN]
[APOLLONIA LAUGHING]
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
It's safer to teach you English!
I know English...
Monday, Tuesday, Thursday,
Wednesday, Friday, Sunday, Saturday.
[HORN HONKING]
Greetings, Don Tommasino.
How are things in Palermo?
Michael is teaching me to
drive. Watch, I'll show you.
How are things in Palermo?
Young people don't respect
anything any more...
Times are changing
for the worse.
This place has become
too dangerous for you.
I want you to move to a villa
near Siracusa, right now.
What's wrong?
Bad news from America.
Your brother, Santino,
they killed him.
[CAR HONKING]
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Let's go... you promised.
Fabrizio! [SPEAKS ITALIAN]
Get the car.
Are you driving
yourself, boss? Yes.
Is your wife
coming with you?
No, I want you to take her to her father's
house until I know things are safe.
Okay, anything
you say, boss.
[BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN]
Calo, where is Apollonia?
She's going to surprise you.
She wants to drive.
She'll make a good
American wife.
Wait. I'll get the baggage.
Fabrizio!
Where are you going?
[CAR HONKING]
[APOLLONIA SPEAKS ITALAIN]
I'll drive you.
Wait there
No! No, Apollonia!
VITO: Don Barzini,
I want to thank you
for helping me organize
this meeting in a day,
and the other heads of the five
families from New York and New Jersey.
Carmine Cuneo
from the Bronx,
and from Brooklyn
Philip Tattaglia.
And from Staten Island
we have with us
Victor Strachi.
And the other associates that came as
far as from California and Kansas City
and all the other territories
of the country. Thank you.
How did things
ever get so far?
I don't know.
It was so unfortunate,
so unnecessary.
Tattaglia lost a son,
and I lost a son.
We're quits.
And if Tattaglia agrees,
then I'm willing to let things
go on the way they were before.
We're all grateful to Don
Corleone for calling this meeting.
We all know him
as a man of his word.
A modest man who
always listens to reason.
Yes, Don Barzini.
He's too modest.
He had all the judges and
politicians in his pocket.
He refused to share them.
When did I ever refuse
an accommodation?
All of you know me here.
When did I ever refuse,
except one time? And why?
Because I believe
this drug business is gonna
destroy us in the years to come.
I mean, it's not like gambling
or liquor or even women,
which is something that
most people want nowadays,
but is forbidden to them by
the pezzonovante of the Church.
Even the police departments
that have helped us in the past
with gambling and other things
are going to refuse to help us
when it comes to narcotics.
And I believed that then
and I believe that now.
Times have changed.
It's not like the old days,
when we can do anything we want.
A refusal is not
the act of a friend.
If Don Corleone had all the judges
and politicians in New York,
then he must share them
or let others use them. He must let
us draw the water from the well.
Certainly he can present
a bill for such services.
After all,
we're not communists.
[ALL LAUGH]
I also don't believe
in drugs.
For years I paid
my people extra,
so they wouldn't
do that kind of business.
Somebody says to them
and says, "I have powders.
"If you put up
3-4,000 dollar investment,
"we can make
50,000 distributing."
So they can't resist.
I want to control it as a
business, to keep it respectable.
I don't want it
near schools,
sold to children.
That's an infamia.
In my city we would keep the traffic
and the dark people, the colored.
They're animals anyway,
so let them lose their souls.
I hoped that we could come
here and reason together.
And as a reasonable man,
I'm willing to do
whatever is necessary
to find a peaceful solution
to this problem.
Then we are agreed.
The traffic in drugs will be
permitted, but controlled.
And Don Corleone will give us protection
in the east, and there will be the peace.
But I must have strict
assurance from Corleone.
As time goes by and his
position becomes stronger,
will he attempt
any individual vendetta?
BARZINI: Look, we are all
reasonable men here.
We don't have to give
assurances as if we were lawyers.
You talk about
vengeance.
Is vengeance gonna
bring your son back to you?
Or my boy to me?
I forgo the vengeance
of my son.
But I have
selfish reasons.
My youngest son was forced
to leave this country
because of this
Sollozzo business.
All right.
And I have to make arrangements
to bring him back here safely.
Cleared of all these
false charges.
But I'm
a superstitious man.
And if some unlucky accident
should befall him,
if he should get shot in the
head by a police officer,
or if he should hang himself
in his jail cell,
or if he's struck
by a bolt of lightning,
then I'm going to blame some
of the people in this room.
And that I do not forgive.
But, that aside
let me say that I swear
on the souls
of my grandchildren,
that I will not be the one to break
the peace we've made here today.
When I meet
with the Tattaglia people,
Should I insist that all his drug
middlemen have clean records?
Mention it.
Don't insist.
Barzini is a man who will
know that without being told.
You mean Tattaglia.
Tattaglia's a pimp.
He could never
have outfought Santino.
But I didn't know
until this day
that it was Barzini
all along..
Come on, Nancy.
Keep together,
everyone. Brian.
Okay, all right.
How long
have you been back?
I've been back a year.
Longer than that, I think.
It's good to see you, Kay.
Hi, Ms. Adams.
[CYCLE BELL TRILLS]
[DOG BARKING]
I'm working for
my father now, Kay.
He's been sick.
Very sick.
But you're not
like him, Michael.
I thought you weren't going to
become a man like your father.
That's what you told me.
My father is no different
than any other powerful man.
[SCOFFS]
Any man who's responsible
for other people.
Like a senator
or president.
You know
how naive you sound.
Why?
Senators and presidents
don't have men killed.
Oh.
Who's being naive, Kay?
Kay, my father's way of doing
things is over. It's finished.
Even he knows that.
I mean, in five years
the Corleone family is going
to be completely legitimate.
Trust me. That's all I can tell
you about my business. Kay...
Michael, why did
you come here? Why?
[SOBS]
What do you want with me after all this
time? I've been calling and writing.
I came because I need you.
Because I care for you.
Please stop it, Michael.
Because...
I want you to marry me.
It's too late.
Please, Kay...
I'll do anything you ask. Anything
to make up for what's happened to us.
Because
that's important, Kay.
Because what's
important is that
we have each other.
That we have a life together.
That we have children.
Our children.
Kay, I need you.
And I love you.
TESSIO: Barzini's people chisel my
territory and we do nothing about it!
Pretty soon I there won't be one
place in Brooklyn I can hang my hat!
MICHAEL: Just be patient.
TESSIO: I'm not asking you for help,
Mike Just take off the handcuffs.
MICHAEL: Be patient.
CARLO: We got to
protect ourselves.
Give me a chance
to recruit some new men.
MICHAEL: No.
I don't want to give Barzini
an excuse to start fighting.
TESSIO: Mike, you're wrong.
CLEMENZA: Don Corleone...
You once said that
the day would come
when Tessio and me
could form our own family.
Till today
I would never think of it.
I must ask
your permission.
Michael is now
head of the family
and if he gives his permission,
then you have my blessing.
After we make
the move to Nevada
you can break off from the
Corleone family and go on your own.
After we make
the move to Nevada.
TESSIO:
How long will that be?
Six months.
Forgive me, Godfather,
but with you gone,
me and Pete will come under
Barzini's thumb sooner or later.
And I hate that
goddamn Barzini.
In six months' time there will
be nothing left to build on.
Do you have faith
in my judgment?
Yes.
Do I have your loyalty?
Yes, always, Godfather.
Then be a friend to Michael.
Do as he says.
There are things
being negotiated now
that are gonna solve all your problems
and answer all your questions.
That's all
I can tell you now.
Carlo, you grew up
in Nevada.
When we make our move there,
you'll be my right-hand man.
Tom Hagen
is no longer consigliere.
He'll be our lawyer in Vegas.
That's no reflection on Tom,
just how I want it.
Besides, if I ever need help,
who's a better consigliere
than my father?
Well, that's it.
Thank you, Papa.
I'm happy
for you, Carlo.
Mike... Why am I out?
You're not
a wartime consigliere, Tom.
Things may get rough
with the move we're trying.
Tom.
I advised Michael.
I never thought
you were a bad consigliere.
I thought Santino was a bad
Don, rest in peace.
Michael has all my
confidence, just as you do.
But there are reasons why you must have
no part in what is going to happen.
Maybe I could help.
You're out, Tom.
[DOOR CLOSING]
I can't get over the way
your face looks.
It really looks good!
This doctor did some job.
Who talked you into it?
Kay? Hey, hey, hey!
Wait. Hey, hey.
Leave them out here.
We'll deal with them later.
He's tired and wants
to clean up. All right now.
Let me open the door,
all right?
[PLAYING FOR HE'S A JOLLY GOOD FELLOW]
Hello, Mike!
Welcome to Las Vegas!
All for you, kid! Huh?
It's all his idea, right?
JOHNNY: Your brother Freddy.
FREDO: Girls?
[BOTH LAUGH]
I'll be right back.
You keep them occupied.
Atta boy, huh?
Anything you want, kid,
anything. Huh?
Who are the girls?
That's for you
to find out.
Get rid of them, Fredo.
Hey, Mike...
Fredo, I'm here on business.
I leave tomorrow. Now get rid of them.
I'm tired.
Get rid of the band too.
Hey, just take off.
Come on. Take off. Let's go.
Come on. Hey, that's it.
Hey, Angelo.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, come on! Scram!
Come on, honey. Let's go.
I don't know, Johnny.
What the hell's
the matter with him?
I'm sorry.
Sorry... Sorry.
I don't know.
He's tired.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSING]
What happened
to Moe Greene?
He said he had
some business.
He said to give him a call
when the party started.
Well, give him a call.
[PATS ON BACK]
Johnny, how are you?
Hello, Mike.
Nice to see you again.
MICHAEL:
We're proud of you.
JOHNNY: Thanks, Mike.
Sit down, Johnny,
I want to talk to you.
The Don is proud
too, Johnny.
Well, I owe it
all to him.
Well, he knows
how grateful you are.
That's why he'd like
to ask a favor of you.
Mike, what can I do?
The Corleone family is thinking
of giving up all its interests
in the olive oil business
and settling out here.
Now Moe Greene will sell
us his share of the casino
and the hotel, so it could
completely be owned by the family.
Tom! Hey, Mike,
are you sure about that?
Moe loves the business. He never
said nothing to me about selling.
Yeah, I'll make him an offer
he can't refuse.
See, Johnny...
See, we figure
that entertainment
will be a big factor in
drawing gamblers to the casino.
And we hope
you'll sign a contract
to appear
five times a year.
Perhaps convince some of your
friends in the movies to do the same.
We're counting on you.
Sure, Mike.
I'll do anything for my godfather.
You know that.
Good.
Hey, Mike! Hello, fellows.
Everybody's here. Freddy, Tom.
Good to see you, Mike.
How are you, Moe?
All right.
Did you get
everything you want?
The chef cooked
for you special,
the dancers will kick your tongue
out and you credit is good!
Draw chips for everybody in the
room so they can play on the house.
My credit good enough
to buy you out?
[LAUGHING]
Buy me out?
The casino, the hotel.
The Corleone family
wants to buy you out.
wants to buy me out?
No, I buy you out.
You don't buy me out.
Your casino loses money.
Maybe we can do better.
You think I'm skimming
off the top, Mike?
You're unlucky.
[CHUCKLING]
You goddamn Guineas
really make me laugh.
I do you a favor
and take Freddy in
when you're having
a bad time,
and now you try
to push me out! Wait a minute.
You took Freddy in because the
Corleone family bankrolled your Casino,
because the Molinari family on
the coast guaranteed his safety.
Now we're talking business.
Let's talk business.
Yeah, let's talk
business, Mike.
First of all,
you're all done.
The Corleone family don't have
that kind of muscle anymore.
The Godfather is sick, right?
You're getting chased out of New York
by Barzini and the other families.
What do you think is going on?
You think you can come to
my hotel and take over?
I talked to Barzini. I can make a
deal with him and still keep my hotel!
Is that why you slapped my
brother around in public?
Ah, that was nothing, Mike.
Now, Moe didn't mean nothing by that.
Sure he flies off the handle
once in a while,
but Moe and me we're good
friends, right Moe, huh?
I've got a business to run.
I've got to kick asses
sometimes to make it run right.
We had a little argument,
Freddy and I,
so I had
to straighten him out.
You straightened
my brother out?
He was banging cocktail
waitresses two at a time!
Players couldn't get a drink at
the table. What's wrong with you?
I leave for New York tomorrow.
Think about a price.
[DRINK SPILLING]
MOE: Son of a bitch!
Do you know who I am?
I'm Moe Greene!
I made my bones when you were
going out with cheerleaders.
Wait a minute, Moe.
I got an idea.
Tom, Tom,
you're the consigliere.
You can talk to the Don...
You can explain...
Just a minute now.
Don is semi-retired and Mike is in
charge of the family business now.
If you have anything to
say, say it to Michael.
[DOOR SLAMMING]
Mike, you don't come to Las Vegas and
talk to a man like Moe Greene like that!
Fredo...
You're my older brother,
and I love you.
But don't ever take sides with
anyone against the family again.
Ever.
I have to see my father and his
people, so have dinner without me.
Oh, Michael.
This weekend we'll go out.
Mmm.
We'll go to the city, we'll see a
show and we'll have dinner. I promise.
Mmm.
Oh, Michael., Michael,
your sister wants to ask you something.
Let her ask.
No, she's afraid to.
Connie and Carlo want you to
be godfather to their boy.
We'll see.
Will you?
Let me think about it.
We'll see. Come on.
So...
Barzini will move
against you first.
He'll set up a meeting with
someone that you absolutely trust.
Guaranteeing your safety.
And at that meeting
you'll be assassinated.
I like to drink wine
more than I used to.
Anyway,
I'm drinking more.
It's good for you, Pop.
I don't know.
Your wife and children,
are you happy with them?
Very happy.
That's good.
I hope you don't mind the way I keep
going over this Barzini business.
No, not at all.
It's an old habit.
I spend my life trying
not to be careless.
Women and children can be
careless, but not men.
How's your boy?
He's good.
You know, he looks
more like you every day.
He's smarter than I am.
Three years old and he can
read the funny papers.
Read the funny papers.
Uh...
I want you to arrange
to have a telephone man
check all the calls that go
in and out of here...
I did it already, Pop.
I took care of that. It could be anyone.
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
What's the matter?
What's bothering you?
I'll handle it.
I told you I can handle it,
I knew that Santino was gonna
have to go through all this.
And Fredo...
Well...
Fredo was, well...
But I never...
I never wanted this for you.
I worked my whole life.
I don't apologize
for take care of my family.
And I refused
to be a fool,
dancing on a string held
by all those big shots.
I don't apologize.
That's my life, but I thought that...
That when it was
your time,
that you would be
the one to hold the strings.
Senator Corleone.
Governor Corleone. Something.
Another pezzonovante.
Well...
[SIGHS]
Just wasn't enough time, Michael.
Wasn't enough time.
We'll get there, Pop.
We'll get there.
Hmm.
Now listen, whoever comes to
you with this Barzini meeting,
he's the traitor.
Don't forget that.
Can I hold it, please?
Can I water these?
Yes, go ahead.
Over here, over here.
Be careful.
You're spilling it.
[ANTHONY LAUGHING]
Anthony.
Come here, come here.
Come here.
That's it.
We'll put it right there.
[SIGHING]
I'll show you something.
Come here. Come here.
Stand there.
Give me an orange!
[GROWLING]
[ANTHONY CRYING]
[VITO LAUGHING]
That's a new trick.
You run in there.
Run in there.
[VITO LAUGHING]
ANTHONY: Where are you?
[COUGHING]
[ANTHONY LAUGHING]
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
[ANTHONY EXCLAIMING]
[ANTHONY CHATTERING]
[BELL TOLLING]
Mike, can I
have a minute?
Barzini wants to
arrange a meeting.
He says we can straighten
out any of our problems.
You talked to him?
Yeah.
I can arrange security.
On my territory.
All right?
All right.
Do you know how they're
going to come at you?
They're arranging a meeting
in Brooklyn. Tessio's ground.
Where I'll be safe.
I always thought it would have
been Clemenza, not Tessio.
It's the smart move.
Tessio was always smarter.
But I'm going to wait.
After the baptism.
I've decided to be
godfather to Connie's baby.
And then I'll meet with
Don Barzini and Tattaglia.
All the heads
of the five families.
[ORGAN PLAYING]
[BABY CRYING]
[RECITING IN LATIN]
[RECITING CONTINUES]
PRIEST: Michael, do you believe
in God, the Father almighty,
Creator of Heaven and Earth?
I do.
PRIEST: Do you believe in Jesus Christ, His only Son, our Lord?
MICHAEL: I do.
Do you believe in the Holy Ghost,
the Holy Catholic Church?
I do.
[RECITING CONTINUES
IN LATIN]
[BABY CRYING]
[RECITING CONTINUES]
PRIEST: Michael Francis Rizzi,
do you renounce Satan?
I do renounce him.
And all his works?
[MUFFLED SHOUTING]
I do renounce them.
WOMAN: Oh, God!
PRIEST:
And all his pomps?
I do renounce them.
Michael Rizzi,
will you be baptized?
I will.
[RECITING IN LATIN]
Michael Rizzi,
go in peace,
and may the Lord
be with you. Amen.
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
[ALL CHATTERING]
Kay!
Kiss your godfather.
[INAUDIBLE]
Carlo, can't go to Vegas.
Something's come up.
Everybody has to
leave without us.
CONNIE: Mike,
it's our first vacation!
Connie, please.
Go back to the house, wait for my call.
It's important.
All right.
I'll only be
a couple of days.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
We're on our way
to Brooklyn.
I hope Mike can get us
a good deal tonight.
I'm sure he will.
Sal, Tom, the boss says he'll come in
a separate car, so you two go on ahead.
Hell, he can't do that.
It screws up all my arrangements.
Oh, that's what he said.
I can't go either, Sal.
Tell Mike it was only business.
I always liked him.
He understands that.
Excuse me, Sal.
Tom, can you get me
off the hook?
For old times' sake?
Can't do it, Sally.
[TELEPHONE BEING DIALED]
You have to answer
for Santino, Carlo.
Mike, you got it
all wrong.
You fingered Sonny
for Barzini.
That little farce you
played with my sister.
You think that could fool
a Corleone?
Mike, I'm innocent.
I swear on the kids, Mike.
Please, Mike, don't do this.
Sit down.
Don't do this
to me, please.
Barzini is dead.
So is Philip Tattaglia.
Moe Greene.
Strachi. Cuneo.
Today I settle
all family business,
so don't tell me
you're innocent, Carlo.
Admit what you did.
Get him a drink.
Come on.
Don't be afraid, Carlo.
Come on. Do you think I'd
make my sister a widow?
I'm godfather
to your son, Carlo.
Go ahead, drink, drink.
No, Carlo, you're out of the family
business. That's your punishment.
You're finished.
I'm putting you on a plane to Vegas.
Tom.
I want you to stay there.
Understand?
Mmm-hmm.
Only don't tell me
you're innocent.
Because it insults my intelligence.
Makes me very angry.
Who approached you?
Tattaglia or Barzini?
It was Barzini.
Good.
There's a car waiting outside
to take you to the airport.
I'll call your wife and tell
her what flight you're on.
Mike...
Come on, get out of my sight.
Hello, Carlo.
[GRUNTING]
[CONNIE SCREAMING]
I'm trying
to tell you...
CONNIE: Oh, Mama, please!
[SOBBING]
Michael! Michael!
KAY: What is it?
CONNIE: Where is he?
Michael, you lousy bastard!
You killed my husband.
You waited until Papa died, so nobody
could stop you and then you killed him.
You blamed him for Sonny.
You always did. Everybody did.
But you never thought about me!
You never gave a damn about me!
Now what are we gonna do?
KAY: Connie.
CONNIE: Why do you think
he kept Carlo at the Mall?
All the time he knew
he was going to kill him.
And you stood godfather
to our baby.
You lousy
cold-hearted bastard!
Want to know how many men
he had killed with Carlo?
Read the papers,
read the papers!
That's your husband,
that's your husband!
[CONNIE SPITTING]
[CONNIE SOBBING]
No! No, no...
Take her upstairs.
Get her a doctor.
[MICHAEL SIGHS]
She's hysterical.
Hysterical.
Michael, is it true?
Don't ask me
about my business, Kay.
Is it true?
Don't ask me
about my business.
No.
Enough!
All right.
This one time.
This one time I'll let you
ask me about my affairs.
Is it true?
Is it?
No.
I guess we both need a drink.
Come on.
[GLASS CLINKING]
Don Corleone.