[alarms ringing]
What do we got, Chester?
Multiple fire alarms
at Ivo Labs.
You know, hopefully it's not
an overcooked chicken tenders
in the microwave situation.
I said I was sorry for that.
Roger that, yeah, yeah.
It's just, you know, man,
that smell took us forever
to get out of the lounge--
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
The fire's
already been put out.
Flash, you're back!
- I just got here.
- No, you didn't.
You sped us out of the way,
and then put out the fire
with a wind tunnel,
like you did with the Hotness!
- I did?
If it wasn't
for your super speed,
seven years of research
would have gone up in smoke
literally.
- You're welcome.
Wait, Flash,
what's--what's going on?
What are they talking about?
- I don't know.
[dramatic music]
I think there may be
a new speedster in town.
[heroic music]
♪
[electricity crackling]
A new speedster?
You sure?
Those Ivo employees said
someone ran them to safety
and then used a wind funnel
to put the fire out
just like I would.
That sure sounds
like a speedster.
You have any leads
on to who it might be?
Not yet.
August Heart's still
locked up at Iron Heights.
Thawne doesn't have his speed.
He's under heavy guard
at A.R.G.U.S.,
and all the Velocity-X vials
are secure at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and I still can't reach
Speed Force Nora
or any of the other Forces.
[somber music]
Is there more?
♪
I just--Caitlin still
hasn't returned my calls
since I stopped her experiment
to resurrect Frost.
You did more than stop it.
[electricity crackling]
[glass shattering]
I'm not saying it was wrong,
but Caitlin lost
the most important person
in the world to her,
and she could lose something
just as important,
hope.
We are gonna be late!
Oh, hey.
- Hey.
We've got
kindergarten interviews
for Jenna
at every school all day.
The competition
is crazy fierce.
Um, oh, great!
You've got Jenna's backpack.
I have the paperwork.
I have the interview questions.
You and I, we are gonna
go over that in the car.
[quirky music]
What am I missing?
- Jenna?
[gasps]
♪
Hey, I need your notes
on the profile feature
for Judge Hankerson's
retirement.
Already in your inbox.
And here's the briefing
I wrote up
for your next field piece.
They're closing Fort Delany?
That's right up my alley.
Allegra,
did you sign off on my--
Expense reports?
Yep, they're with accounting.
- Okay, then.
- Allegra!
I want to run an expose
on the light meta
who works with The Flash.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
Okay, I'll leave you to it.
[chuckles]
I've been pulling pictures.
Whoever this is, her face
is always hidden by light,
but I think I could ID her
with enough resources.
Maybe she doesn't
want to be ID'd.
[chuckles]
Well, we don't know that.
And a new hero in town
is big news.
That's why we should run this.
- No.
I--I mean,
it's not right for CCC Media.
Says the temporary
editor-in-chief.
I already ran this story
by Iris before she left.
What did she say?
That it was
an interesting angle
and she would
strongly consider it.
Well,
maybe we hold off
on moving forward with it
until she's back.
♪
[phone chimes]
I don't get it.
I thought you left the Arañas
after you were paroled
from Iron Heights?
I did, but our old gang's
trying to pull me back in.
The Arañas are expanding.
They've taken over every
square inch of Keystone,
and now they want Central City.
The gang's
been dropping bodies.
What?
The Arañas aren't killers.
We used to just steal cars.
Not anymore.
Thanks to new leadership,
there's no line
they won't cross.
Who are these people?
The kind you
don't wanna mess with.
Look...
you did me a huge favor
when you wrote
that article about me,
and because of you,
I was able to make
a new, better life
in this city,
and I don't want
to give that up,
but I have to leave.
♪
Because the same reason
they want me to run things
is the reason I won't survive
if I turn them down.
Lydia,
if what you're saying is true,
we have to stop them
before anyone else gets killed.
We can't.
What if you help
CCC Media break this story?
Like you said,
you know everything about them.
Where they keep their money,
their contacts,
their stash houses.
Lydia.
You're the only one that can
help me take them down.
No way.
You know what
they'd do to me for snitching?
CCC Media will treat you
as an anonymous source.
We'll protect you.
- How?
I know someone who can
run you out of town quick
if something goes south.
♪
Look, I know you're scared,
but the Arañas,
they operate in the shadows.
The only way
to take away their power
is bring them into the light.
Thank about all the other girls
in the gangs,
the ones who are trying
to get out, but they can't.
Telling your story
could help them
get their lives back too.
♪
Okay.
But not here.
And after our interview,
I'm on the first bus
out of here.
We'll keep you safe.
I promise.
[ominous music]
♪
I found Lydia.
Looks like she's skipping town.
That's not all she's doing.
Rawlins, Lydia's talking
to Esperanza's cousin,
the reporter.
We can't let them expose us.
♪
They won't.
No one defies the Arañas
and survives.
♪
So I've been
checking S.T.A.R. Labs'
satellite readings all day.
Not a stray tachyon
to be found.
Our new speedster
isn't using the Speed Force.
And now they're in the wind.
[soft dramatic music]
What's wrong?
The fire's origin is here,
but the only thing that
could've started it
is this acetone.
Even with an incredibly
low flash point,
it would still need
an ignition source.
Chester, what if the speedster
was the combustion force?
Oh, snap--yeah, no,
the friction
from their super-speed
would totally be
enough to kick start
a reaction
and it would explain how they
arrived on scene before you.
Because they started it.
But why?
♪
Look at this biometric lock.
It's broken.
And whatever was inside
is MIA,
just like our speedster,
but, man,
the only reason you would need
a temperature-controlled
polymer case like this would be
to hold a very strong
electrochemical cell.
Like Ivo Labs'
Newton Battery.
It's experimental,
but it's incredibly powerful.
What if the fire
was a distraction
so they could steal this?
- Damn.
Yeah, okay, I guess we can
scratch them off
the nice speedster list.
What do we do now?
We get answers from
the one person who knows
villainous speedsters
better than I do,
which means
I'm gonna be off the grid,
so Team Flash
is on its own for a while.
You're going to go see him?
You sure that's a good
I have to know if it's him.
Okay, yeah, you do you.
We'll be fine here.
♪
[phone chimes]
[exhales]
This is the Arañas gang.
For years,
their MO was stealing cars.
It was founded by
a teenager in Keystone,
who later became known
as the meta-human Ultraviolet.
Now, more recently,
UV has worked alongside
Millie Rawlins
and Dr. Kimiyo Hoshi,
AKA Sunshine and Dr. Light.
Collectively known
as the Assassins Three,
they've worked for Black Hole
and Eva McCulloch.
Only according to rumors,
Ultraviolet died last year.
And why should we care?
Because I just found out
Sunshine and Dr. Light
are now running the Arañas.
We're talking extortion,
million dollar thefts
that should be impossible,
and they're leaving
a trail of bodies
made from everyone
who gets in their way.
And you got all this
from one source?
Is there anyone else
who can corroborate her story?
She is all we need.
Which is why we're doing
a live interview with her
tonight.
- [scoffs]
- [chuckles]
I mean,
you can't be serious.
We'd have no time
to fact check her story.
And this "source,"
how do you even know
if she's reliable?
- I just do.
I don't get it.
Why are you so passionate
about this story?
♪
Look, I know this
all sounds crazy,
but I am telling you,
it's the right move.
You just have to trust
I know what I'm doing.
[scoffs]
I'll--I'll go
call my babysitter.
I'll DVR the Sharks game.
♪
Okay, let's do this.
- Chester, meet Lydia.
- Hi.
We've got
a skeletal staff tonight
to protect her identity,
and Lydia, don't worry,
I trust Chuck with my life.
- What do you do around
Tonight, I'll be running
an AI-generated filter
to conceal your voice
and face during the interview.
So no worries.
Not even your mom
will recognize you.
[chuckles]
- I need some water.
♪
- Is she gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
- What about you?
'Cause
reporting on the Arañas,
I know that's
a big deal for you.
How'd your staff react
when you told them
about your connection?
I--I didn't tell them.
Like, are you sure
that's the right move?
I need them to trust me,
and if I tell them
I was in the Arañas,
it--no, I--I can't risk them
losing faith in me.
This story is too important.
I'm gonna go check on Lydia.
♪
[sighs]
My stomach is doing flip-flops.
You're scared.
I get it.
But the risk we're taking,
it's worth it.
Think about your life
before you joined the Arañas.
[speaking Spanish]
♪
It was rough.
[somber music]
I was on my own,
struggling to get by,
always wishing to be
a part of something,
a family,
and what I didn't know
is that it could get
even worse.
[speaking Spanish]
Yeah, but somehow,
you got out
without getting killed.
I might not get so lucky.
[suspenseful music]
What's happening?
- Get down!
[glass shatters]
[device humming]
♪
[phone beeping]
The Arañas.
I knew they'd find me.
Okay, we have
to get out of here now.
[weapon blast hums]
Hello, Lydia.
♪
- [gasps]
- Come on!
♪
Sorry, ladies.
It's the end of the road.
♪
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
♪
Quick, in here!
[keypad beeps]
[high-pitched humming]
♪
[dramatic music]
You can't
keep me out forever.
Who the hell was that?
The Arañas are here.
We're all under attack!
- [whimpering]
- She's hurt!
I'm on it.
Oh, this can't be happening!
We need to get
to a secure location.
We're in one.
I just activated
a photo-kinetic energy shield
around the whole building.
It's--it's bulletproof,
teleport-proof,
basically everything-proof.
How'd you know to do that?
You're just an IT guy.
Well, I--
I--back when we
were "The Citizen,"
Dr. Light attacked us.
That's why Sue Dearbon hired
him to secure the building.
Why isn't my phone working?
They must be using
a signal jammer
to block communications.
Frick.
- What is it?
My force field
was only meant to be
a temporary shield
until we could call for help.
- And now we can't.
- Guys, she's back!
[tense music]
I've been in combat.
Knowing where your enemy is
is a good thing.
Now we need a plan.
Chuck, can you
MacGyver something together
to bust through their
cell jammers and call for help?
I can build
an oscillating transmitter
to bypass their signals.
♪
Sunshine just
flipping disappeared!
Yeah, okay,
we need to just remain calm.
Until this force field
goes critical,
Hoshi can't fire
her photon bullets,
and Sunshine can't teleport in.
How do you know
so much about them?
Yeah, Allegra, how do you?
♪
[energy sizzling]
Oh, my God.
♪
We need to talk, Thawne.
[eerie music]
You took my speed.
What more do you want?
My body is broken.
I can barely think.
I can't sleep.
I used to be able to run around
the world in five seconds.
Now it takes me
at least that long
to cross this stupid cell because...
♪
You took my speed.
You did this to yourself, Thawne.
Armageddon was your plan.
And it should've worked.
♪
But it didn't, and now...
I'm gonna have to find
a new way to kill you.
Oh, you can try.
I've gotten what I need.
Wait, you're out?
Wait, you're leaving me
just like that?
No parting gift?
No 411 on your precious
Team Flash?
And by the way...
♪
It's just too bad
what happened to Frost,
isn't it?
♪
Then again...
She was in over her head
from the beginning, wasn't she?
Yeah,
this was a waste of time.
Wait, Allen, don't go.
Come on.
That's no way
to treat an old friend.
What do you want?
Huh?
To see
if you were responsible
for something impossible,
and now I know.
You couldn't be.
Responsible for what?
♪
What is it?
What scared you so bad
that you had to run
all this way just to be sure
I was still here?
♪
I found a new speedster.
[soft dramatic music]
Huh.
They can't have Lydia,
so we stick to the plan.
Chuck's working
on the transmitter.
And what if they get in here
before he's done?
They threatened to kill us!
- She's right.
They're an invading force.
We need a Plan B.
♪
What, you're already
working on page one?
[soft dramatic music]
I'm writing a letter
to my kids
in case I die in here, okay?
♪
[panicked breathing]
I give up!
You hear me?
I surrender!
Lydia, stop!
You can't give yourself up.
You.
Open the doors.
- What? No.
Lydia, they'll kill you.
- They're gonna anyways!
Now open the door
so no one else has to die!
Good call.
[suspenseful music]
Lydia, look,
I get what you're trying to do,
and it is damn selfless,
but there's
got to be another way.
Don't forget why you came here.
You came here to stop them.
I came here so no one else
would get killed.
Now let me out!
Hey, if she wants to go,
let her.
No way!
We can't send someone
out to die, Taylor.
So what, we're just gonna
sit here instead
and wait for them
to fry us or shoot us...
- I don't--
Or whatever
the hell it is they do?
Open the damn doors.
Lydia, I am the only one
with the code to that shield,
and there's no way in hell
I'm giving it to you,
which means we're gonna
help you survive this, okay?
[soft dramatic music]
And you ain't never getting in.
Now I'm mad.
[tense music]
♪
Let me take this.
You people are
just as crazy as Arañas.
- We promised to keep her safe.
- You did.
I didn't!
- Okay.
we all just need
to take a step back
and figure out
a new way out of this
'cause that woman's life
depends on our next move.
And what about our lives?
The Arañas want Lydia, not us.
We turn her over,
they'll let us go.
I like that plan!
No, it doesn't matter
what we do.
They will not let us go.
Not now.
You don't know that.
Look, I saw the code
Chester typed in earlier.
♪
And this is what Lydia wants.
Hey, Lydia is our source.
It is our duty as journalists
to protect her no matter what
even from herself.
An ethics lesson
from you, really?
Your whole past is unethical.
♪
What's she talking about?
The reason Allegra knows
so much about the Arañas.
They need to know
what you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't.
This is my life, my decision.
Too late!
♪
Right before we were attacked,
I had a contact
take a look at some of
Allegra's sealed juvie records.
And guess what they found?
Our ex-con co-worker
was in a gang
with her cousin, Ultraviolet,
the same gang that's been
killing people in Keystone.
Allegra used to be one of them,
one of the Arañas.
- Is this for real?
I am so sorry that I
didn't tell you the truth,
but we have to stick together.
We have to protect Lydia!
Stick together?
You lied to us!
And now
it's gonna get us killed!
She's right.
We can't trust you.
♪
Okay, once I finish
this transmitter,
we can get out of here, okay?
Why couldn't you just
let me go out there?
Because you came here
to do something important.
You and Allegra are trying
to drag a bunch of killers
out of the darkness and expose
everything they're doing,
and you still can.
Why do you think
Hoshi and Rawlins
are still out there?
Because they're scared
of you, Lydia.
We need to get that emergency
signal out now, Chuck.
Yeah, look, I just--I just
need a little more time.
Well, we don't have it!
Taylor just told everyone
that I was in the Arañas
and now no one trusts me.
Plus she memorized
your shield code.
They are this close
to opening those doors.
[speaking Spanish]
I--I never should've
taken over after Iris left.
No, no,
this isn't your fault.
Yes, it is!
I--I am not a leader.
I never have been.
[somber music]
You know how Esperanza
and I ended up in juvie?
I had an idea for a job.
We were gonna hit a bunch
of semis at a rest stop.
It was my idea,
so Esperanza put me in charge
of the whole thing,
and I checked the trucks,
and when it came time,
I told the girls it was clear,
but I--I missed a driver,
and he had a shotgun,
and one of my girls
got hit with a round.
You know
what was in that truck?
Lawn furniture.
Chuck, a girl almost died
because of me.
I'm not cut out
to lead anyone.
All I'll do is--is get
people hurt or worse.
♪
[speaking Spanish]
That's not true.
Look,
I was lost when you found me.
I wanted out
of the Arañas so bad,
but I couldn't actually do it,
and then you wrote
that article about me.
[tender music]
And seeing how you saw me
as someone with a future,
it helped me reclaim my life.
And today, I was terrified,
but you inspired me
to come here
because when you said
we could take down the Arañas,
I believed you.
I still do.
She's right.
You are a leader.
And not in spite of your past,
but because of it.
[chuckles]
You're Allegra freakin' Garcia.
You always know who you are,
what you wanna do,
but you can't lead if you're
trying to stay in the dark.
So, Allegra,
what do you want to do?
[heroic music]
♪
They didn't leave behind
any tachyons after the fire.
Could you tell
if they were tapping into
the Negative Speed Force?
- How could I tell?
You severed my connection,
remember?
But you time travelled
before that a lot.
Did you ever sense
another speedster in 2022,
someone trying
to hide their abilities?
Can you really not see
how obvious this answer is?
Are you stupid?
So enlighten me.
[tense music]
No.
♪
Okay.
I get it.
You don't want to help me
because even after all this...
♪
You're still jealous.
I'm not jealous of you.
I pity you.
I meant jealous of them.
- Who?
- This new speedster
out there living a life
you lost
while you can barely move.
Their journey
is just beginning.
Yours is already over.
♪
What's it like knowing
you've been replaced?
♪
I won't be replaced.
I will never be replaced
because no speedster is ever
gonna feel for you what I do!
Hate.
Hate!
Pure and infinite hate.
I hid in plain sight for years
to be next to you,
to be close to you
so I could hurt you.
I devoted my life
so I could destroy yours!
No speedster
will ever replace me!
♪
No speedster would ever feel
what I felt,
and because they don't,
this new speedster...
♪
Doesn't care about you at all,
and so there's another reason
they don't want to be found.
So what is it?
You really don't see it?
♪
[chuckles]
I guess I am faster
than you after all.
Think about it, Allen.
♪
A new speedster running
through the city streets...
With frightening new speed
just like you eight years ago.
They're hiding because they
can't control their abilities.
[soft dramatic music]
The fire was an accident.
♪
Look, I--I wish
there was another way,
but if we want to survive,
we have to give Lydia over now.
No.
Lydia's not going anywhere
because I have a plan
to get us all out,
but for it to work,
I need you to trust me.
Yeah,
that's not gonna happen.
Okay, we don't want
to turn Lydia over,
but Taylor's right.
- I know.
And the truth is, I was ashamed
of being in the Arañas,
and I was afraid if I told you
the truth about my past
that you would
stop trusting me.
I thought there was
too much at stake
for me to be honest
about who I really am.
♪
[exhales sharply]
But it was lying about my past
and keeping you in the dark
that lost your trust.
♪
So I'm done hiding.
[energy humming]
[dramatic music]
I am the light meta
in those photos,
and I've never really
told anyone that before.
You were the one who's
always helping the Flash?
The one saving people?
[energy whirring]
[suspenseful music]
♪
And right now,
I'm going to save us.
All you have to do is trust me.
Look,
Allegra's the real deal.
If she says she has a plan,
then I'm in.
All in.
Me too.
[heroic music]
So...
who's with me?
♪
[ominous music]
[energy humming]
This is
a photo-kinetic energy shield.
It'll take time
to split the bonds.
Not if we have
the right weapon.
Give me your ammo.
♪
[energy hissing]
And now we do.
♪
[pulse hums and hisses]
This is gonna be fun.
[energy whooshes]
Where are they?
Easy, ladies.
We can all still walk out
of here without a sunburn.
We made you
a real nice offer, Garcia.
Give up the girl and live.
Yeah, and then when you
slink back into the shadows,
every other body you drop
makes CCC Media responsible.
Not happening.
[energy hums]
[weapon hums]
Hurry, she's buying us time!
Camera and sound are up.
How's the transmitter coming?
I just need
to reset the encoder.
Well, reset faster!
If this crazy plan
of hers doesn't work--
It will.
We just need to trust Allegra.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[groans]
[grunts]
[whimpers]
♪
[flesh sizzling]
[energy humming]
[heroic music]
♪
[grunts]
Nice trick,
but I can feel how hard it is
for you
to maintain so much power.
[suspenseful music]
Because you can't beat me, Garcia.
I'm not trying to.
This is a Central City
Citizen Media Special Report.
We're here today with
a very brave young woman
who's ready to come forward
and talk about
the gang activity
in Keystone City.
Lydia Sanchez,
can you tell us about
a group called the Arañas?
I've been living in fear
of the Arañas for a long time,
and even when I agreed
to do this interview,
I--I didn't want to show
my face at first,
but now I realize,
they're the ones
who should be afraid
because we're the ones
dragging them into the light,
so to all the girls
out there struggling
to break free
of their control,
look at me.
I did it.
So can you.
And who's running this gang?
Their names are
Millie Rawlins
and Kimiyo Hoshi.
[dramatic music]
That interview
is going out live
to millions of people
across the city.
If either of you
try to go after Lydia again
or anyone on my staff,
the whole world
will know it was you.
♪
You can go now.
- This isn't over.
- Bring it on, bitch.
♪
[triumphant music]
[soft dramatic music]
A Mr. Runk showed me
the damage outside,
and it looks like you two
had a rough night.
How are the both of you
still alive?
♪
I guess we're just lucky.
Well, Hoshi and Rawlins' luck
is about to run out.
I've got APBs out for both
of them across the whole state,
and the information
you provided helped us
freeze their accounts
and seize their assets,
which means the Arañas
are out of business.
Do you mind if I ask you a few
more questions at the station?
Lydia, I think,
was trying to catch a bus.
Not anymore.
[warm orchestral music]
♪
20 million views
and counting.
[laughs]
This is our biggest story yet.
Wow.
Guys...
thank you.
I owe you,
which is why--
look, if you need to expose
the truth about me, I get it.
Allegra,
you reminded us today
of the oldest rule in the book.
Always protect your sources
and each other.
♪
We're gonna
keep your secret, too,
for as long as you want us to.
- Thank you.
Hey, did you put a call in
to the Keystone PD commissioner
to get a comment on the Arañas?
Already did.
Let's hit our old contacts
at McCulloch Tech.
Guys, it's, like, 4:00 A.M.
Yeah, that's what
the coffee's for.
Plus, we need
to get a follow-up out.
Right after
I call my babysitter.
Probably gonna charge me
a fortune for this.
[chuckles]
- You're not gonna join them?
- Seriously?
You're not firing me
for, you know, everything?
You were trying to save
the lives of your co-workers,
so no.
Plus, you're a great
investigative reporter.
[tender music]
Thanks for keeping us
safe today, boss.
♪
Hey, those photos
of me and Flash,
where did you find them?
Chirper.
It's not that hard, really.
♪
Allegra, I know you're
not hiding from us anymore,
but how long can you hide
from the rest of the world?
♪
Man, you should've
seen her last night.
She totally crushed
the leadership game.
I'm talking--I'm talking
Janeway meets--meets AOC
meets--meets Angela Davis-type
leadership, like.
Well, I don't know
about Janeway, but--
no, it was really nice
to just be myself,
feel like
I didn't have to hide.
Nice work.
You really stepped up,
both of you.
And if Hoshi or Rawlins
make any more moves,
obviously, I've got your back.
- Thanks.
So how'd it go on Lian Yu?
Did you find any answers
on the speedster?
Not exactly.
I--I did find some perspective.
[computer beeping]
Incoming video message.
[soft dramatic music]
Hey, guys.
I wish I could've come back
to S.T.A.R. Labs
to tell you all this
in person,
but I can't go back there.
Not yet.
Barry, when you
left my apartment,
I wasn't sure how to feel,
and the truth is,
I'm still not.
I just know it hurts.
[somber music]
So I'm gonna go away
for a little while.
I'm gonna stay with Carla
for real this time.
I just need
some space to think,
and I don't know when
I'll be ready to come back,
so, until then,
just know that I love you all.
♪
[sighs]
Is she gonna be okay?
Yeah, I think she is.
♪
[mysterious music]
That's something
you don't see every day,
someone returning
the tech they stole.
[soft dramatic music]
Listen, hey,
I just want to talk to you.
♪
Listen, I--
I just have some questions.
♪
[electricity crackling]
[dramatic music]
♪
I can run at
the speed of sound, but you--
Can run
a lot faster than that.
Look, the point is,
you can't outrun me.
So why don't you just
tell me who you are
and what's really going on?
Look,
I'm not a super villain.
That fire was an accident.
- I know.
But you risked people's lives
to steal a battery.
And I'm so sorry about that.
I'm not a natural speedster
like you.
[sighs]
That's why you've been
so hard to trace.
Your speed's temporary.
- Exactly.
You see, my...
associate and I
found a way to generate
my own speed source.
I'm still trying
to work out the kinks,
so the effects
only last a few minutes.
I thought maybe the battery
could help extend the window,
and I figured
why spend another four years
calibrating
sodium nitrate cells
when I could just borrow
the one I'd already made?
♪
I designed the original
Newton Battery
when I was a young engineer
working here at IVO.
The Newton Battery
was invented by Meena Dhawan.
♪
It's Dr. Meena Dhawan, actually.
You--you're
the CEO of Fast Track Labs.
Your book, "Quantum Gravity
and the Universe,"
I've--I've read it
three times.
You're a genius.
[chuckles]
That's surprising
and very flattering.
Unfortunately,
this genius intellect
hasn't been any help in
mastering these new abilities.
That's why I've been
trying to take a low profile,
running trials with my team.
The truth is...
I just want to use my gifts
to help people.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
[sighs]
I--when I first got my speed, I...
I had a mentor,
someone to coach me
on how to use my powers,
so if you're interested.
[heroic music]
You'd really do that for me?
♪
[laughs]
Thank you.
I promise
you won't regret this.
♪
Greg, move your head.
[thunder rumbling]
[electricity crackling]