You're gonna run over there,
you're gonna come back at me...
...and get hit with an arrow.
-No, I'm not.
-Heh, heh.
Ready?
I think I may be the fastest man alive.
BERLANTI: The purpose of the screen test
was to see if somebody could come in...
...to a moving train that was Arrow
and be the Flash.
It was a real burden
for someone like Grant to bear.
Because you have to come on...
...and you have 75 years of history
of this character that everybody knows.
You have to feel like there's a whole show
behind you that could happen...
...and we'd be interested.
I broke the sound barrier.
I mean, air couldn't get out of my way
fast enough.
My clothes caught fire.
From the second Grant came in on his own,
we kind of knew he was Barry.
And not because he looked obviously
like Barry from the comic book...
...because he kind of didn't.
And not because he felt old enough
as the part we were imagining in our head...
...because he kind of wasn't,
but he had the heart.
And Grant had the acting chops
to carry this role.
All my life I've wanted to just do more.
What if I'm not a hero?
When you're making a pilot,
every milestone means the world.
Like, it's-- When you pitch it,
when you finish the script....
Every step along the way feels so huge.
And we felt strongly
that if Felicity loved Barry Allen...
...the audience would love Barry Allen too.
Because the audience trusts and knows
and loves Felicity.
-Who are you?
-Do your parents know that you're here?
I'm Barry Allen.
I'm from the Central City Police Department.
I'm with the Crime Scene Investigation Unit.
-What did you say your name was again?
-Barry. Allen.
Felicity. Smoak.
You can't predict or count on chemistry.
And there was just magic between them.
I was serious about not being able to dance.
But I'll hold your hands and sway.
Sold.
KREISBERG: Emily Bett Rickards
was generous enough to let us fly her down...
...and do the screen test, and you could
just see it between the two of them.
They just had chemistry.
It's hard to talk about, because it's--
If it was quantifiable,
everybody would be doing it.
The vigilante. I read that he saved you.
What is he like?
-He's green.
-He's green. It's interesting. Right?
Why green?
Black would be better for stealth
and urban camouflage.
Me personally, I think that he trained in
some sort of forest or jungle environment...
...and the green is a nod to that.
I don't give the vigilante much thought.
-Why are you so interested in the vigilante?
-When I was 11, my mom was murdered.
They arrested my dad. Put him on trial.
And I told the cops
that my dad was not the man...
...that I saw running away from my house.
But the court-appointed shrink
said I was too traumatized...
...to be a reliable witness.
He was sentenced to life in prison.
The killer ended my mother's life...
...but it was the law that ended my father's.
You could see in the words
and see in the actors...
...and see in the chemistry
and see in the world...
...that were even created
in that little bit of screen test...
...that there really was a show there.
I'm not your stereotypical superhero.
I'm not one of the Hemsworth brothers.
So, yeah, I....
And the, you know--
The breakdown said:
"Late 20s to early 30s, blond hair."
I knew what Barry's build was
in the comics...
...and it wasn't something I was like,
"I'm gonna book this."
But it went my way.
I can't believe I have this opportunity...
...and this is happening to me, just as Barry
can't believe that this has happened to him...
...and he's now this superhero,
and he has this responsibility...
...and as Barry has become the Flash...
...I've become more confident with Barry
and with being the Flash.
And it's been kind of a nice journey
for Barry and myself...
...to kind of have a little parallel journey.
It's been fun.
He really did feel like the kind of actor
you could build a show around.