My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
If you ever need anything,
I will race over in a heartbeat.
Same. Well, as fast as I can run.
(Ray) Advanced Technology
Operating Mechanism... A.T.O.M.
What are you gonna use it for?
To protect the people of this city.
You think Dr. Wells killed Barry's mom?
(West) I don't know yet.
But I do know that Wells keeps secrets.
(Barry) The way that he described running...
feeling the wind and the power...
it's like he was talking from experience.
Harrison Wells is The Reverse-Flash.
[dramatic music]
Eddie, we need your help.
[siren wailing]
[dramatic music]
Pedal to the metal.
(female dispatcher)
We've got a 10-31 in progress.
Shiny Diamond, 18th and Olive.
That's only a few blocks from here.
Has every crook in Central City gone crazy?
This is the third attempted
robbery tonight.
Barry. We got another one.
Hello.
18th and Olive.
Got it.
Who's this?
Oh. Indecent exposure. Powell Park.
That ain't something
you should be showing people.
They're getting away, guys.
They're not getting away, Eddie.
Let's get these bozos up ahead of us first,
and then we'll worry about
the idiots at the Shiny Diamond.
All right.
We're gonna run out of room, though.
I'll take care of that.
What do you think he meant by that?
Oh. That's what he meant.
I think we lost them.
Oh, no, you didn't.
And by the way, you're under arrest.
[chuckles]
We need to go. Now. Come on!
[alarm wailing]
Uh-uh. Freeze.
You guys missing these?
(Thawne) On the ground. On the ground.
So, uh, I'm just curious, but...
have you guys not heard of me, or what?
[laughs]
Nice work, detective.
- Good night, Dr. Kang.
- Good night.
[lock beeps]
[bee buzzing]
[engine turns over]
[bees buzzing]
[dramatic music]
[yelps] Oh... ow!
[screaming]
Victim's name is Lindsay Kang,
engineering professor at Hudson University.
- Just got tenure.
- Hey.
So, her whole body's covered in
these puncture wounds
you see on her face.
Bite marks maybe.
Whatever it was, she must have
gone into anaphylaxis.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
The blood sample should tell us
everything we need to know.
I'll run tests back at my lab.
They can do it faster at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well, yeah, but, I mean, it's just...
It's just what?
It's kind of weird being there right now.
Barry, you know we have to
play it cool with Wells.
If he finds out we suspect him...
I know. I get it.
I just think that we should tell
Cisco and Caitlin.
They could help us.
The more people who know, the more chance
Wells is gonna find out we're on to him.
I mean, what if one of them slips up?
Or panics?
- Or what if...
- What?
What if they're not on our side?
No. Absolutely not.
They're not involved in
whatever he's planning.
I mean, Wells is their boss, their mentor.
They've been with him for a long time.
I've seen plenty of people make
the wrong choice for loyalty.
Please do not include them
until we can be sure.
All right.
[dramatic music]
Death by apitoxin.
Honeybee venom.
Bees. Why did it have to be bees?
Y'all, I don't do bees.
Ain't nobody got time for bees.
But when a honeybee stings,
the stingers are literally
torn from their abdomen,
and they die.
But there were no stingers in the body
and no dead bees in the car.
A honeybee can only deposit
.1 milligrams of apitoxin
when it releases its stinger.
(Wells) And yet, Ms. Kang was found
with enough venom in her system
to kill a herd of elephants.
It appears not only is a meta-human
controlling these bees but also
increasing their toxicity.
Bees communicate by releasing pheromones.
Maybe this meta's controlling
them through secretion?
Anyone want to join me
in getting a beekeeper suit?
I'm pretty sure I can outrun a bee.
Just don't run into a lake.
Bees will wait for you to come up for air
and then they'll sting you.
Discovery Channel.
Turns out there's a lot to discover.
Felicity, what are you doing here?
Can you guys come outside for a sec?
[gentle sweeping music]
What exactly are we waiting for, Ms. Smoak?
Up there.
Is that a bird?
It's a plane.
It's my boyfriend.
[sighs] Hi.
I'm Ray.
So he seems a little tall for you.
Barry Allen, are you jealous?
Je... no. No, I'm not jealous.
I just... I really wish you would've called
before flying in.
Oh no, he flew. I drove.
I'm serious, all right?
Now is not the best time.
Why? What's going on?
Ah, well, my ears popped,
so that's something.
You're lucky you didn't break your neck.
What is it with billionaires
being superheroes?
So have you... picked a name yet?
I'm kind of partial to The Atom.
Shoo.
You married to that, or...?
Your A.T.O.M. suit...
it's quite the technological
achievement, Mr. Palmer.
(Wells) I'm impressed.
And he is never impressed.
Well, thank you, but I can't
quite seem to keep it up.
(Felicity) He means the suit.
- Yeah, I mean the suit.
- Yeah.
I can attest that
everything else works just fine.
There's nothing we need to fix in...
[clicks tongue] That area.
No, no, no. The sex is great.
God, there's two of them.
I know from Felicity that you have been
very helpful with Barry and the Flash suit,
and I was hoping to get
another set of eyes on my...
- Problem.
Any friend of The Arrow's is a friend...
- Hell, yes.
- Uh, guys.
We kind of have a lot going on already.
There's the meta-human killer
that can control a whole swarm of bees?
Cool. [chuckles]
I mean, awful.
I'm sure Caitlin and I will
provide ample support, Barry.
And I will be happy to sit this one out.
You...
Ray, why don't you stay here
and work on your suit
while Barry and I run to
Jitters for some java?
Sounds like a plan.
- Coffee?
- Sure.
[tense music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey, Detective.
- Iris.
What are you doing here?
I am following up on my story
about crime in Central City.
Or lack thereof.
Could someone be working with The Flash?
No. Of course not.
You caught a flasher,
armed robbers in a getaway car,
and two jewelry thieves last night.
I'm just that good.
What is going on with you lately?
You've been acting
really weird and withdrawn.
If I didn't know any better, I'd think that
you were hiding something from me.
Iris, I'm... I'm not hiding
anything from you.
[solemn music]
Do you ever go to work?
Oh, you're funny.
[laughs]
Okay, I can't keep lying to Iris
about The Flash.
You have to.
It's really starting
to affect our relationship.
We haven't had sex in two weeks.
Which you didn't want to know about.
Keeping her in the dark keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
Well, I'm her father.
And I'm her boyfriend.
When does my vote outweigh yours?
When you become her husband.
You know I left Starling City
to get away from the mood and brood,
but it looks like it followed me here.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's like I said before,
now is not the best time.
Barry, I have been through enough with you
to know when you're holding something back.
Is this because I told Ray your secret?
Because he is trustworthy, Barry.
He wants to help people, just like you.
I know, that's not what I'm worried about.
It's...
I really don't want to
put anyone else in danger.
In danger of what?
Barry, hey.
Eddie, hey.
- You remember Felicity.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Great to see you.
Yeah.
What is wrong with you?
Is everyone in Central City in a bad mood?
I thought Central City was
supposed to be the fun one.
It's, um...
- It's not...
- Felicity knows.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
So everyone but Iris.
It feels that way.
How do you lie to everyone you care about?
(Felicity) For starters,
don't think of it as lying.
Think of it as protecting her
from getting hurt...
with a fib.
But Iris can tell I'm hiding something,
and it's putting this distance between us.
(Felicity) I have an idea.
Why don't we all go to dinner tonight?
A little wine and dine
is sure to bridge the gap.
Come on, we all had fun last time.
Sure. Why not?
Barry Allen, fifth wheel.
(man) Well, I can't make my
3:00 meeting this afternoon.
Also, confirm my dinner
reservation for tonight.
Last time, they couldn't find it,
and that was unacceptable. Thanks.
[tense music]
You see that bad man over there?
[bee buzzing]
Tell your sisters it's time.
(Cisco) So you put solid oxide
fuel cells into the belt?
Yeah, it's the only place
to hide the hardware.
Hmm, well, they should be
generating enough energy
to power the suit.
It could be the operating temperature.
I mean, you're essentially...
Overheating the system, yeah. I figured.
But if we insulate them
with a ceramic compound...
We may improve the operating efficiency.
[chuckles]
You really are quite clever, Cisco.
(Reverse-Flash voice-over)
Some would say I'm the reverse.
[dramatic music]
You're incredibly clever, Cisco.
How do you turn this thing on?
Cisco? You okay?
Yeah.
I haven't been getting enough sleep, so...
[alarm blaring]
(Caitlin) Cisco, we need you up here.
[energetic music]
Killer bees are at it again.
Get a hold of Barry.
[phone vibrates]
Another bee attack. Folston Tech.
I'll see where Joe is.
- Bee careful.
- For real?
Bad pun. Sorry. Just don't die.
[dramatic music]
[people screaming]
I'm too late.
Where are the bees?
I don't know. There's no sign of them.
[bees buzzing]
Found them.
(Flash) How do I get out of here?
Take the northeast crossway.
It's the quickest way out of the building.
Guys, they're everywhere. I'm surrounded.
[siren wailing]
Barry!
Barry.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
[computer beeps]
Barry, stay with me.
Cisco! Barry doesn't have a pulse.
- Step away from him.
- What? Why?
We need to jumpstart his heart.
There's a defibrillator in the suit.
[dramatic music]
(Caitlin) Charge it to 360 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
[electricity sparks]
Hit him again. 400 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
[gasps]
[coughing]
- Barry.
- [gasping]
Joe.
That is it for the defibrillator.
It is completely fried.
You're lucky to be alive, Mr. Allen.
I was very specific that you not die.
Yeah, that's a pretty big thing for her.
Cisco, what happened out there?
I followed your directions exactly.
I'm sorry. I led you the wrong way.
The schematics that we had,
they... they weren't up to date.
(Barry) What, they weren't up to date?
What do you mean?
That's never happened before.
What, you think Cisco
was trying to get you killed?
No. Why would he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know. That's why I was joking.
Barry, it's our job
to protect you, and today,
we failed, but that'll just
serve as a warning
for all of us to be
more vigilant in the future.
(Caitlin) Good news... the
apitoxin is out of your body.
Your levels are back to normal.
Terrific.
Ray, Felicity.
We're gonna be late for dinner.
Are you sure that's wise, Barry?
You just died.
Maybe you should order in tonight.
Yeah, we could totally cancel.
I'm fine. Alive. Hungry.
All right? Let's go.
- That was weird.
- Yeah.
Why didn't we get invited to dinner?
[tense music]
[bee buzzing]
[upbeat music]
Oh. Thank you.
Hey, guys.
Wow, Iris. Check you out.
[chuckles] Hi, Felicity.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hey. Guys, this is Ray Palmer.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Barry.
Bienvenue chez Massimo Restaurant.
(maitre d') Mr. Palmer,
your table is ready.
Great. Shall we?
Yes.
Hey, how did he get a reservation here?
We've been trying for months.
- I don't know.
- [laughs]
Here's your table, sir.
I thought it'd be nice if it was quiet,
so I bought out the entire restaurant.
- Too much?
- Just a tad, sweetie.
Joe.
Oh, Cisco. Hey.
You just saved me a trip to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I got some info on our second victim.
Name's Bill Carlisle.
(West) He was recently
hired at Folston Tech
to beef up their robotics division.
Robotics?
That's just like the first victim.
Wow. That is weird.
That's not why you stopped by.
No, I wanted to talk to you about Barry.
Okay.
[tense music]
Is there something going on with him?
Something he's not telling us?
What do you mean?
He hasn't really been himself lately.
Not that I'm aware of.
It's like something is just
really bothering him.
Well, I think he's got his mind trained on
catching the bad guys, Cisco.
And he's probably worried about
when The Reverse-Flash is gonna
show his face again.
(Reverse-Flash voice-over) Oh,
I'm not like The Flash at all.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, no, I'm fine.
It's just... I've got this crazy headache.
Thank you for the file and the talk.
[solemn music]
- So how did you two meet?
- Work.
Well, actually, I bought the company
where Felicity was employed,
and so she was forced
to join me at Palmer Tech.
It's not as creepy as it sounds.
So you two work closely together?
- Mm-hmm.
- Interesting.
I guess you guys share all of your thoughts
and feelings and...
Yeah...I share everything with Felicity.
It's nice that you guys have
that level of communication.
[lounge music playing]
Oh, well, no, not every-everything.
I mean, sometimes it's good
to just shut up.
[chuckles]
I get that.
Some things are better left unspoken.
Really?
I... I don't find that to be true.
Oh, thank God. It's the food.
(Barry) Food's here.
Our first course on the tasting menu
is a quail egg frittata.
Bon appétit.
(Ray) Barry. [chuckles]
I got to admit, I envy you
spending so much time at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Harrison Wells is, like,
a personal hero of mine.
I mean, it's amazing just to actually
be in the same room with him.
[voices and music echoing]
I'll be right back. Just excuse me.
Okay.
[tense music]
Well, I, um...
have to pee.
Okay, you've been acting super strange
ever since Ray and I got to Central City.
What is going on with you?
And don't say it's a bad time.
Oliver might be joining
the League of Assassins,
Laurel's the Black Canary, and
Thea's training with Malcolm,
so I know about bad times.
Okay.
Joe and I found out that
Wells isn't who he says he is.
He... [sighs]
He is the man that killed my mother.
Oh, my God. But he's been helping you.
Get faster, stronger. I know.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can and can't trust.
So you think Cisco and Caitlin
are helping him?
That's impossible.
- Is it?
- Yes.
They were trying to save you today, Barry.
- They did save you.
- Wells has also saved me.
Many times.
I thought that Wells was a great man,
and I was so wrong about him.
What if I'm wrong
about everything else too?
[door clicks]
Hey, guys.
Uh, things are getting
a little intense in here.
[both chuckle]
Please can't we just have a nice evening?
Okay, so it's my fault that
we're not having a nice evening?
I am your girlfriend. Who you live with.
I shouldn't have to beg you to talk to me.
If I could talk to you
about this, I would, believe me.
But I can't.
You know what? I am not hungry anymore.
- Iris.
- You know what?
When you are ready to act like
we are two people who love each other,
call me.
I'll be at my dad's.
[somber music]
Thank you for dinner. I've got to go.
[phone vibrating]
Uh, emergency at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Go.
- Sorry.
[chuckles]
Well, only 17 more courses to go.
(male voice) Containment breach.
Foreign object detected.
[shouts]
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Where is he?
[buzzing]
[buzzing silences]
Thank you.
Let's see what makes this bee so poisonous.
[groans]
You saved my life.
That is one odd-looking bee.
(Cisco) That's 'cause
it isn't a bee at all.
It's a robot.
No way.
Unbelievable.
This bot's got a 360-degree vision system.
I mean, we're talking
multiple micro-cameras
all coming from various angles
at the same time.
Which means...
It can see all around the room at once.
That is...
(both) Amazing.
Disturbing.
It's also next-gen hardware
that nowhere near the market.
So we're not dealing with a meta-human?
It's just a mad scientist.
Cisco, you said the second victim,
Bill Carlisle, was a robotics engineer.
Let's cross-reference
his previous employers
with those of Lindsay Kang.
Allow me.
Mama's been away from
a keyboard for far too long.
Okay.
[solemn music]
They both worked at Mercury Labs.
Let's call Joe.
I think it's time we paid
a visit to an old friend.
(McGee) Twice in one year, Harrison.
You really are vying for
comeback scientist of the year.
Always a pleasure, Christina.
To what do I owe this visit?
Did you finally find my tachyon prototype,
or are you here to
blackmail me for another one?
Do you have another one?
(West) We came here for information.
Bill Carlisle and Lindsay Kang.
Former employees who were
recently murdered.
My God. I wasn't aware.
Stung to death by robotic bees.
You're looking for Brie Larvan.
Brie Larvan?
A quite brilliant roboticist
who once developed
miniature mechanical bees
for agricultural use.
Kang and Carlisle warned me
that Brie was weaponizing
the bees for military use,
so I terminated her.
Well, it seems that you would be
on her hit list too, Doctor.
You've got to let us keep you safe.
[chuckles]
I'm all too familiar
with your inability
to protect things, Harrison.
I can take care of myself.
Good day, gentlemen.
Thank you.
[soft pop music playing]
Hey.
Okay, so we found our queen bee.
Brie Larvan. She's a roboticist.
Joe is running a trace
on her current location,
but so far nothing.
[clears throat] Good.
Where is Ray?
Oh, he's working on his suit with Cisco.
I like Ray.
He seems like he's a really good guy.
He is a good guy.
Just like Cisco.
And Caitlin. Girl.
Is that why you called me here?
I know that you're in a tricky situation,
but that's when you need
your friends to have your back.
And how can they if you won't let them?
It's not that simple.
What if Joe is right, and
I tell them, and it backfires?
Wells isn't just their boss, Felicity.
He is their mentor, their hero.
[sighs] My hero.
Look, it's...
I don't know what to do.
[sighs]
When I first met Oliver,
before I knew he was The Arrow,
he would... he would ask me
to do weird things for him
like decrypt a bullet-ridden computer
or hack some company.
And when I would ask him why,
he would come up these ridiculous excuses.
And I always knew he was lying,
but I would help him anyway.
- You know why?
- Hmm?
Because I knew Oliver was
a good person with a good heart.
And Cisco and Caitlin?
They're no different.
- Hey.
So you're really staying here tonight?
Tonight. Tomorrow night.
The night after that.
Do you think that Eddie is cheating on me?
No. Eddie's not that kind of guy.
Well, then I don't know what else
he could be hiding from me.
Iris...
Remember when we were kids,
and Joe would come home from work
with that blank expression on his face?
[chuckles] Yeah.
The "Earth to Joe" look.
How could I forget?
(Barry) I never understood that look
until I started working for the CCPD.
Showing up at crime scenes and
seeing someone murdered...
it can be ugly work.
(Barry) And I'm lucky.
I get to hide behind the science of it
and just stay in my lab,
but Eddie,
he's out there every day in the darkness.
I just... I think that maybe
if he doesn't want to talk
to you about his work,
it's probably because he wants
to keep you in the light.
What?
I'm just surprised.
You going out of your way like this
to help me see Eddie's point of view.
I mean...
Eddie makes you happy.
All I ever want is
for you to be happy, Iris.
Welcome home.
[chuckles]
It is so fun to watch
grown men play with their toys.
(Caitlin) You're so lucky.
Ray is so nice and smart and hot.
Yeah, it's kind of like I'm dating Barry
but in Oliver's body.
A sentence you will never repeat to anyone.
Your secret's safe with me.
[bee buzzing]
It must have re-activated.
And if it's being controlled wirelessly...
I can trace its signal and figure out
where it's trying to go.
[tense music]
- Oh, no.
- Oh, boy.
What?
The swarm is headed for Mercury Labs.
Brie Larvan's going after Tina.
[tense music]
[swarm buzzing]
Hello, Dr. McGee.
You gonna open the window,
or should I buzz myself in?
How do we stop them?
(Wells) She's got to be remotely piloting
those bees from somewhere.
We need to stop this bug-eyed
glasses woman.
And her mini bandits.
- Bug-Eyed Bandit.
(Felicity) Got her. She's
in an abandoned greenhouse.
Barry, you have to take out Brie.
It's the only way to stop these nanodrones.
What about Dr. McGee?
The defibrillator in your suit is broken.
You cannot risk going near Mercury Labs.
Bees can't penetrate my suit.
- I'll go.
- Whoa.
We haven't tested out
the new power system yet.
We'll do it now.
- I'm following you.
- I'm driving.
(Felicity) And I'm kissing you.
[heroic music]
Dr. Wells...
Mr. Palmer will protect Tina. Go.
[dramatic music]
You fired me,
destroyed years of my research.
You took everything from me.
What you were doing was wrong.
You wanted to harm people, not help them.
I did what I had to do.
You mean ruin my life?
Sure.
Now I'm doing what I have to do.
[buzzing]
[electronics beeping]
Found her.
Felicity, can you jam their frequency?
I already tried, but I might
be able to redirect them
onto a new target.
(Felicity) Ray, get ready for incoming.
We have the technology.
It's over, Brie.
(Flash) I know you're
trying to kill Dr. McGee.
You think that she betrayed you.
I can imagine how that feels.
You think you understand
the sting of betrayal?
I'll show you what it means to be stung.
[swarm buzzing]
[dramatic music]
Barry.
Barry, I hacked into the bees' frequency.
I'm controlling them.
I'm the queen of this hive.
Oh, she's good.
She's like my nemesis.
I've never had a nemesis before.
I kind of like it.
[swarm buzzing]
Okay, Cisco. Now what?
(Cisco) Ray, get to the ocean.
If the bots follow you into the water,
their electronics will fry.
Got it.
Wait. But so will my suit.
[swarm buzzing]
[heroic music]
[electricity crackling]
Cisco, I'm fried.
I'm losing propulsion control.
[dramatic music]
Can you see the van?
[electronics beeping]
Yeah.
We'll catch you.
- You will?
- We will?
We will.
All right.
Keep it steady!
[groans]
- Whoo!
- The Atom lives.
[chuckling]
- [groans]
- Oh.
Let's work on some softer gloves
for next time, okay?
Sorry.
Oh, you want to bring it?
It's been brought.
[yelps]
Rude.
Felicity, right now
would be a good time to do something.
Stay away from Barry Allen.
[dramatic music]
- Felicity!
- Got it.
Boom. Drop the mic.
It's metaphorical, of course,
because I don't have a real mic.
Brie's restrained.
Call CCPD.
Ah. Some kind of team you have here.
Helps to have friends in your corner.
[buzzing]
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music]
[bee buzzing]
[gasping]
Are you okay?
Cisco!
Come on. Please.
Wake up.
Cisco's been stung. He's going into shock.
(Flash) I'm on my way.
Come on, stay with me.
Hold on. Back up.
I'm gonna try something.
[electricity crackling]
- Cisco.
- [gasps]
Either my fear of bees is over
or it just got a lot worse.
Thank God you're okay.
I've never had anybody take a bee for me.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, bro.
Cisco, you're a hero, man.
- Dr. McGee.
- May I come in?
Yeah, of course. What can I do for you?
I wanted to apologize.
(McGee) I should have listened to
you when you warned me about Brie.
Perhaps next time I will take
the CCPD's offer of protection.
After we lost your tachyon prototype,
I can understand why
you were hesitant to trust us.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
I couldn't help but notice some tension
between you and Dr. Wells.
That's all in the past.
Do you mind if I ask
what happened between you two?
I ask myself that same question
all the time.
15 years ago, Harrison and I
were thick as thieves.
We were promising young scientists
in Starling City.
He was such a kind man.
Then everything changed after Tess died.
They were gonna get married?
I understand how grief can affect someone,
but this was more than that.
It was like, after that day,
Harrison Wells became
a completely different person.
Good day.
Bye.
Doctor.
How's Cisco?
Happy to be alive.
And sad that Ray is leaving.
It was a really brave thing
he did, risking his life.
(Barry) Selfless.
Yeah. It definitely was.
[upbeat music]
And another end to
another exciting adventure
in Central City.
Ah, yes, thank you.
Ray, thank you for all your help.
- Oh.
- And I hope you
figure out the problem with your suit.
- I already have, actually.
- Oh.
All this time, I've been looking at
the power source the wrong way.
I kept thinking we needed to go bigger.
But the solution, as always,
is simply to go smaller.
Oh. Great.
[chuckles]
You okay?
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna be.
Thank you for your advice.
I won't even charge you the 5¢.
[sighs] Bye, Felicity.
Bye, Barry.
Hey.
What's up?
I, um...
I spoke to Barry last night.
Oh, yeah?
He was trying to help me understand
why you've been so off lately,
why you might be having trouble
connecting with me.
Really?
What did he say?
It was a good explanation.
Valid.
But the truth is, it doesn't matter,
because when you love someone,
you tell them everything.
So if you love me, Eddie,
you'll tell me what is going on
with you, or...
Or what?
You know what.
[solemn music]
All right, all right,
who's ready for some...
♪ Karaoke ♪
We are not going to karaoke, are we?
No.
This is everything we know
about my mother's murder
and The Reverse-Flash.
I've been gathering information
on him for a long time.
And this is everything we know
about Dr. Wells.
[tense music]
I don't understand.
What do Dr. Wells and The Reverse-Flash
have to do with each other?
Um...
They're the same person.
That's impossible.
Look, Caitlin,
it took me a long time to believe it too,
but it's him.
Dr. Wells is a speedster?
He's paralyzed.
Is he, though?
And why would he kill Barry's mother?
It doesn't make any sense.
Cisco. Say something.
I've been having these dreams.
Mostly at night,
but sometimes during the day.
But they don't really feel like dreams.
They... They feel real.
What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is The Reverse-Flash.
And...
he kills me.