[soft music]
- Your tea's ready, babe.
- Aww!
I can't thank your aunt enough
for taking care of Jenna.
I now am left with some free time
to look after my lady.
Aww, loving that.
But are you sure I'm
not distracting you?
You look like you got a lot going on.
Well, I thought that
when I left the force
that I would dig into
Kristen Kramer's background.
You know, see what she
wants with this city's metas
since she's replaced me as captain.
And look, everything I've
dug up so far looks like this.
Hmm, I actually have something for you.
So one of my pro bono clients
is a meta who's also an army vet.
I was prepping for his deposition,
and I came across a name
I think you might find interesting.
- Kristen Kramer?
- Yep.
[suspenseful music]
This says they served
together at Fort Dakota,
but her DOD doesn't say that.
Maybe it's an oversight?
Or it could be
that she doesn't want anybody to know
that she served there.
If these files are still
around, they're here.
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
Good luck.
[chuckles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
Somebody help me!
Let me out! Let me out! Please!
[sobbing]
Somebody help me!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Wow! This is new.
Uh, frak.
Was I supposed to ask
before I changed everything?
'Cause, look, I kept
the pinball machine.
Oh, and Frost is gonna love that.
It's just I've never seen this room
without all of Cisco's stuff in it.
Which I totally understand.
I'll tell you what.
It ain't no thang.
I can take all my
junk back to my garage.
- I can bring everything...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down, Chester, okay?
I just said it's different.
That's not necessarily a bad thing.
And look, S.T.A.R. Labs is your lab,
and we want you to
feel at home here too.
[sighs]
Thank you for saying that...
'cause it took a very long time
to set up these stealth audio speakers.
[claps]
[Parliament's "The Big
Bang Theory" playing]
♪ ♪
Wow!
Whoo!
♪ ♪
Come on, girl, get your groove on.
Oh no, I have two left feet.
No worries, I will teach you the basics,
which, I might add, I
learned from building robots.
Amazing.
You know what I think we need?
I think we need some
more bass up in here!
[claps]
[machinery sizzling]
♪ ♪
I said I think we...
just one sec, just...
♪ ♪
I said I think we need
some more bass up in here.
[claps]
- [sizzling]
- Oh!
[clears throat]
[quirky music]
Uh... not to worry.
We have a replacement
cable just like this one
in the Starchives.
Aisle B, Shelf 52.
Wow, you're inventorying
the Starchives as well.
Cisco really did leave us in good hands.
Well, I learned from the best.
Now, don't go anywhere,
'cause when I get back,
our dance lesson shall commence.
♪ Our dance lesson shall commence ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
[light music]
[beatboxing quietly]
♪ ♪
Oh, who put you down here, little fella?
Oh, you're supposed to be...
[crashing]
Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Anybody there?
Hey, Chester.
- Hey, man.
- How you doing?
I'm... I'm... I'm fine.
Yeah. What are you...
What are you doing down...
[clattering]
[playful music]
Hey, Chester.
- Iris?
- Iris.
It's me. [laughs]
What are you... what are you...
Wait if you're down here,
and he's down here,
then that would mean...
- No, man. No, no.
- Oh, my.
No. We were just...
- Cataloging.
- Yeah.
- See? Yeah.
- Cataloging.
Your hair. And your shirt's inside out.
Um, I have that call.
I was telling you about the work call...
- You were.
- I was telling you about?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- So I'm gonna go do that, okay?
You boys have fun.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Kay, bye.
- Yeah, go...
[exhales slowly, pops lips]
- Hey.
- Hey. [laughs]
Sorry about this.
You know, after everything
that happened with the Forces,
Iris and I, we've
decided to start trying...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, no. Cool. Cool.
- Nice, bro. No, it's cool. Cool.
- Yeah. Well...
- I don't need to know.
- Okay.
- All right. Cool.
We good, man. Yeah. I
don't need to know. I'm good.
Yeah. Actually, that's the Cecile.
She needs help with the case...
- Cool. Cool, cool.
- So I should go. Bye.
♪ ♪
Cisco, you did not warn me about this.
So what do you think?
Does my client have a case?
I mean, as you know, the State says
your meta client Erik Frye
used his pyrokinetic
powers to burn the building,
but CSIs found butane at the scene.
So obviously, seems
more like human arson.
Mm, sounds like reasonable doubt to me.
Great work, Barr.
Yeah, and this case,
does it feel familiar to you?
Didn't you defend someone
like this a few years ago?
[tense music]
- Whoa.
- Hey, are you okay?
I don't know. I feel
numb all of a sudden.
♪ ♪
What's the matter, Barry?
[in sinister voice] Getting ill?
I can't see.
Cecile, what are you doing to me?
Getting you out of the way.
I have a plan, Barry Allen,
and you need to be gone for it to work.
Oh, one more thing. Ugh, I'm not Cecile.
Your mind belongs to
me now, so just let go.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
Barry?
Is it really you?
♪ ♪
I don't know what happened.
One second he was
helping me with a case,
and the next, he just passed out.
Barry's brainwaves are oscillating
at 0.5 hertz, which is
typical of a coma patient.
Look what the EEG picked up.
It appears to be some sort of
psychic neurofeedback signal.
I think that's what's
causing this brain activity.
But I've never seen anything like it.
If Barry's brain
activity stays like this,
he could be comatose
for the rest of his life.
[tense music]
We need to figure out
who did this and fast.
Okay. And how do we do that?
Well, this may be a long shot, but...
What? Me?
♪ ♪
Oh.
Yeah, I would love to try,
but guys, I'm just an empath.
Cecile, if you use your powers
on Barry's brain,
you'll be able to sense
if there's someone else's emotions
that are active within his mind.
Chester's right. It could work.
♪ ♪
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
[sighs]
Barry's emotions, I can't sense them.
But I can feel something else.
Something... cold.
Like madness.
I can see something
now. I can see something.
It's... it's like a light in the middle
of all of that darkness.
It's shining.
Glowing gold?
Like a golden mask?
Sweet Ira Cooper.
Folks, I think I know who did this.
♪ ♪
So, Cecile, the mask that you saw,
did it look like this?
♪ ♪
Mm-hmm.
Psycho Pirate. I knew it.
Roger Hayden?
He was a patient at Arkham
Asylum who we fought.
He claimed that he got psychic powers
from a mask he stole
from the Khandaqi Embassy.
But no one believed him because
he was certifiably insane.
But I-I don't get it.
Why would Hayden go after the Flash?
He didn't.
He's at Arkham, but the mask isn't.
It says here that after the breakout,
Arkham returned the mask to the embassy
but then they donated it
to the Central City Museum.
It's going on display tomorrow
as a part of an exhibition.
Okay, they have no idea
just how dangerous this thing really is.
♪ ♪
According to legends,
the warrior Gilgamesh used a gold mask
to imprison a powerful demon,
or what we might consider today
as an ancient psychic meta-human.
But with the centuries,
the mask has popped up
all over the world: the
Yoruba Tribe in Africa,
17th-century pirates,
all the way up to Hayden.
Now, the story goes,
if you wear the mask,
it doesn't just give you powers.
It feeds off of your mind,
leaving you insane and leaving the mask
in search of a new wearer.
A psychic parasite
moving from host to host,
and now it found a brain that's
capable of speed thinking.
So it's the mask that's attacking Barry.
But Barry's not wearing the mask.
No. The neurofeedback
signal must be the mask
trying to start feeding.
And now that it's touched something,
it'll just keep feeding and feeding
until it gets rid of all the brainwaves.
What about the cerebral inhibitor
- that you guys used on DeVoe?
- That would stop the signal
and get Barry's brain functioning again.
But we need the mask here to do that.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
It's too bad you can't
just grab the mask
from the museum, huh?
♪ ♪
Why can't we?
- Cecile?
- [crying]
Are you okay?
I don't know. I don't know.
I'm so happy to see you.
It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of
here, wherever here is.
Do you have any idea where we are?
♪ ♪
The last thing I remember, I
was... I was at home with Joe
and there was a storm.
[dramatic music]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
And then I woke up...
[gasping]
And I was locked in this room.
♪ ♪
Cecile, the Force
Storm was two weeks ago.
What?
Have you've been in here
this whole time all alone?
Barry, I don't think there's
any way out of this place.
Then we have to make one.
♪ ♪
Before I got here, I
thought I was talking to you.
I think whoever trapped us
here took over your body.
Who could do something like that?
I'm not sure. I don't know.
Bashir, maybe.
But Bashir is on our side now.
So I don't think this was him.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I don't have my powers.
When I was in Grodd's
mind, he trapped me
in one of his old cages.
If this... if this is a
mindscape, like that was,
maybe this asylum is a memory.
But whose memory is it?
And why trap is here now?
- [gasps]
- [door creaks]
[uneasy music]
Has that ever happened?
♪ ♪
No.
Okay. All right.
We have to see if there's
a way out of this place.
Wait. Barry, wait. Your
powers aren't working.
What if it's not safe out there?
What if... what if...
what if it's not safe
and... what happens if
we die in a mindscape?
Then we die in real life too.
But we're not the only
ones in danger here.
Whoever took over your body
could hurt Joe or Iris. All right. Look.
If there's any chance we can
escape, we have to take it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Barry's still losing brain activity.
How long till we get
our hands on that mask?
Okay. So heists aren't
really my expertise,
but Cisco did leave me
a number to call in
case of an emergency.
It's a good thing too.
[dramatic music]
'Cause this one sounds like a doozy.
♪ ♪
So the mask goes on display tomorrow.
But for tonight, it's on lockdown
in Central City Museums'
state-of-the-art restoration lab.
Hermetically sealed and protected
by a laser security grid system
that's sensitive enough
to detect a dust mite.
Which is nothing I can't handle.
There is one snag, though.
The museum just installed
a bleeding-edge Montgomery 5000 vault.
It has a passcode
that changes every day.
The only person that knows
that code is the security guard.
Hold up.
- Cecile.
- Huh?
You could put some kind
of empathic whammy on him.
You know, like getting
to the guard's noggin' with your powers?
I'm not a mind reader, Chester.
Okay.
But... but maybe
if I get close enough to the guard,
I could try transferring
my emotions into him,
making him anxious enough
to want to open the vault door for us?
But no. No, it's way too risky.
Look, I am a lawyer.
I am not a cat burglar.
There's no way I can pull that off.
Uh, yes, you can. I know you, Cecile.
You're just as brave and as
capable as the rest of us.
Look, all you need
to do is follow Sue in
after you disable the lasers, right?
Mm-hmm.
[whimpers]
Joe is never gonna believe this.
[laughs]
Okay, then.
I am definitely gonna
need a better outfit
for breaking and entering.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Feeling pretty confident, huh?
Oh, I am now. You
planned that heist so fast,
you made Dom Toretto in "Fast Five"
look like Dom Toretto in "Fast One."
- [both laughing]
- About that.
Is there anything about
this whole situation
that seems kind of, I
don't know, odd to you?
I mean, we ID'd our target an hour ago,
and we've done zero recon.
It's heist 101.
You think it's almost too easy.
Okay. Look.
Ever since I got here, I've
been training my butt off
for craziness exactly like this.
So I-I've done my homework,
I've checked the math.
Heck, this isn't even the first time
I've helped save Barry's brain.
Team Flash just makes it look easy.
We got this.
If you say so.
♪ ♪
Yeah, no, we... we got this.
Yeah. Yeah, we got this.
♪ ♪
Okay, it looks like security
just switched shifts.
Ilsa Faust, you are good to go.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[light music]
I'm in.
How's it looking?
Well, I'll know in a second.
♪ ♪
Whoa, those are some serious lasers.
Oh, this is nothing.
You should see what Ralph
and I faced in Tunisia.
[grand music]
♪ ♪
Lasers are clear.
You learned that in Tunisia?
No. DeMatteis Academy of Dance.
She's good to go.
Ahh. Ah! Okay. Oh.
[grunts]
[panting]
I remember why I hate rock climbing.
You're doing great.
Let's find that security
guard and get in there.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[uneasy music]
All these doors are locked.
I think we should try another floor.
No. It's a one-story building.
I think that we should just double back.
♪ ♪
- What was that?
- Barry, don't.
It's okay. Come on.
♪ ♪
What is that?
That's our way out.
I've seen portals like this before.
We go through there, we're home free.
[eerie laughter]
What the hell?
Barry, we gotta go.
Hold on a sec.
Hello?
Are you okay?
Please, forget her.
We gotta get out of here.
Somethings not right. Who are you?
Are you trapped here too?
Barry, let's go!
Hey, we can help you.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[laughing]
Have a nice day, Barry.
Cecile...
[laughing]
♪ ♪
[laughing maniacally]
[machinery beeping rapidly]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
[warbling]
No.
I gotta make sure
everything's still there.
♪ ♪
[keypad beeping]
[dramatic music]
Vault secured.
Okay. Be very careful.
Until we get that mask
secure in S.T.A.R. Labs,
consider it dangerous.
♪ ♪
Guys, we've got a serious problem.
I was reading two brain signals,
Barry and the mask,
but now there's a third.
But how's that possible?
The mask is already
feeding off of Barry.
Must be targeting someone else.
There's something I've
been trying to dig up.
For a case.
It's too bad you can't just
grab the mask from the museum, huh?
Oh my God.
♪ ♪
Sue, that's not Cecile.
You need to get out of there now.
♪ ♪
A mortal weapon against the likes of me?
Pathetic.
Stop it! No!
Okay, this is gonna suck.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
Since time began, many
have tried to stop me.
- All have failed.
- Cecile, this isn't you.
Let our friends go, or we'll make you.
Such hubris.
And from the boy who
delivered everything I needed.
How amusing. Now my host shall serve me.
For eternity.
I'm up. I feel great. I feel amazing.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're not going anywhere.
Not for a little while.
Okay, fine.
Since when does Cecile
have that kind of power?
She doesn't. It was the mask.
That was the voice inside of our heads.
She was possessed just like Hayden
and all the others before him.
Okay. When did all this happen?
During the Force Storm,
we thought Cecile was hit
by the Sage Force lightning.
But it must have been the
psychic spirit of the mask
that used that as a cover
to take over her mind.
Now they're both missing. We
have no idea where they are.
- Or what they're up to.
- We have to find her.
That mask is the only
link to helping Barry
and figuring out what
happened to the real Cecile.
The legend says that the mask
gives the wielder
enhanced psychic powers.
So maybe if we track
her neurological signals?
And how about we let someone else
come up with a plan for a change?
Sue, Chester was just trying to help.
Yeah, so was I when I told him
that this job seemed too easy.
But he brushed me off,
and I shot a tranq into my own neck.
She's right. This is on me.
Chester, that thing tricked all of us.
But you heard what it said.
It put Barry in that
coma, just like Grodd did,
to play me and zing my
insecurities as the new guy.
It knew I'd pick Psycho
Pirate out of that binder
and call Sue to help us
break into that museum.
All to make me think I
had this all figured out.
[somber music]
Really, I didn't know jack.
♪ ♪
[uneasy music]
Oh, thank God.
You're okay.
That thing that attacked
me, that was you.
How is that possible?
I don't know.
Cecile, you said there
wasn't a second story.
♪ ♪
There's no way you could know that
unless you've been here before.
You know exactly where
we are, don't you?
♪ ♪
We're at St. Carmine's
Psychiatric Hospital,
just outside of Houston, Texas...
where I was a patient.
♪ ♪
My first year in law
school, I... I got a job
interning at the DA's office.
It was so fulfilling.
I was working around the
clock even when Mom got sick.
[somber music]
And when we found out that
it was cancer, she said,
"Cece, don't worry about me.
"You keep working.
I can feel myself
getting better already."
I was in court when I got the call.
♪ ♪
She died all alone, Barry.
She died alone because of me.
Cecile.
After that, I couldn't
eat, I couldn't sleep.
♪ ♪
Couldn't stop hating myself.
And I just spiraled into
anxiety and depression.
♪ ♪
And then I had a breakdown
and I ended up in here.
Most days I'd just wander those halls.
I'd spend all night lying awake
staring at that ceiling
thinking about my mom.
♪ ♪
When I finally checked
out, I was so ashamed
and afraid that all of that darkness
was gonna catch up to me again,
and so I...
I told myself, "Toughen up.
Toughen... toughen
up. That's it. Smile."
♪ ♪
"And you pretend like
this never happened."
And that is exactly what I did.
And you hid all that pain,
but it never went away.
I carry it with me every day.
Cecile...
I'm never gonna know
what it was like for you
to go through all this.
But I know what it's like to lose a mom.
And to blame yourself for it,
even when it's not your fault.
It makes you want to take that
pain and bury it under a mask.
Away from the people you love.
But masks don't heal wounds.
They only hide them.
Facing those wounds
can be scary as hell,
but it's the only way to start healing.
What if I can't do it?
You can. I know it.
♪ ♪
Maybe that's our way out of here.
This is your memory.
That thing is just
amplifying your fears.
When the door opened before,
what were you thinking about?
The truth about my time here.
But, Barry, I'm thinking
about it right now.
Nothing's changing.
[electricity zapping]
You sure about that?
♪ ♪
If you face this, if you
can confront your past,
I believe you can get us home.
[dramatic music]
Okay.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah.
I need more neuro-fiber
to fix the memory machine,
so we can use it like
we did against Grodd,
but we don't have enough supplies here.
So I gotta go back to my garage.
Shouldn't be here anyway.
Wait, Chester. Yes, you should, Chester.
I mean, this is... it's your lab.
No, Iris. It's not.
What?
Look, I didn't come to S.T.A.R. Labs
to replace Cisco.
I came here to work with him.
And I want to do a good
job more than anything.
But when I saw Barry in trouble today,
Iris, I didn't even know where to start.
I thought to myself, you
know, what would Cisco do?
[somber music]
Decided I'm gonna act
confident and brave.
♪ ♪
Act like I had it all figured out.
[scoffs]
Chester, confidence isn't
what made Cisco Cisco.
I know.
What made Cisco Cisco
was the connections
and the love that he had for you all.
Don't you get it?
I don't have those bonds,
Iris. I barely know you guys.
And I can't help with thinking
that if I just knew Team Flash
a little bit better, that
I would have been able
to figure out that that
wasn't the real Cecile.
And then this entire thing just would...
Okay. Okay.
Chester, Cisco didn't
form these bonds overnight.
It took time. It took patience.
And we all have your back.
Just like we know that you've got ours.
Thanks.
And look, Iris, I promise, okay?
From today on, I'm
really gonna up my game,
and I'm gonna, like...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I think I know where
Psycho-Cecile is going.
♪ ♪
Back at the museum, the mask said
it wanted Cecile to be
its host for eternity.
But the legend says
that once the mask
feeds on the host's mind,
it moves on to another.
So if Cecilia is an empath,
then maybe that makes
her a stronger host.
But not strong enough.
She would need something
to amplify her mental abilities.
To create a permanent food source.
Okay. So where do we
find a device like that?
♪ ♪
In our basement.
[music building]
♪ ♪
At last. The key to permanence.
Barry's about to experience
complete brain death.
Please tell me we have a plan.
We think the mask is trying
to use the Thinker's chair
to create a permanent bond with Cecile.
Oh, frak! She's already there.
How the hell are we
gonna stop this thing?
Okay, this is gonna sound crazy...
Crazy works sometimes.
It's just... I don't know
if it's the best idea.
Look, Chester,
if you believe that it will work,
then I do too.
Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
This is where the portal was before.
That's our only way out.
[uneasy music]
♪ ♪
What's happening to this place?
[laughing]
You can't leave here.
You belong here. Forever.
♪ ♪
Barry!
And this time, you're
never checking out.
♪ ♪
Who dares avoid my gaze?
I do.
♪ ♪
You can't trap me in here.
This is my mind, not yours.
Ooh, so brave.
But you weren't so brave
for Mommy, were you, Cecile?
[gasps]
♪ ♪
Don't you remember her?
Your mommy dying alone in a hospital bed
calling out for her only daughter,
"Where is she? Where is my sweet Cece?"
[whimpering]
♪ ♪
I can sense the faith
you have in yourself.
It's the faith of a fool!
Oh you cracked once,
and you will crack again.
And then you'll be a
psycho just like me.
I used to think that.
I used to think that too.
I was so afraid of losing myself
that I hid a piece of me away,
but I am not ashamed of it anymore.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So go ahead. Try and scare me.
But I know exactly who I am,
and I am done wearing a mask.
♪ ♪
[screaming]
Ahh!
[electricity sizzling]
♪ ♪
Barry, Barry, the portal.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Barry! You're okay.
Cecile.
♪ ♪
[gasps] No, don't shoot. Don't shoot.
It's me, it's me, it's me.
♪ ♪
So what happens
with that crazy mask now?
Yeah. Caitlin's taking it to A.R.G.U.S.
with an armored escort as we speak.
She's gonna help Cisco
retrofit a vault there
with medical dampeners
that'll keep the mask
from finding more victims.
So, Sue, I'm sure you can't
wait to get out of here, huh?
All right. Relax, Chester.
Iris explained everything to me.
And I'm sorry that I was so harsh.
[soft music]
I guess getting
whammied makes me grumpy.
♪ ♪
As for my next move,
Ralph is still busy,
and I did miss Central City.
So I think I'm gonna
stick around for a while.
I'm staying at the penthouse
suite of the Lily Hotel.
Nightcaps and a late
dinner on my terrace?
- My treat.
- Both: Yes.
- Yes.
- Yeah? All right.
See you there.
♪ ♪
Um, hey, Barry...
You know, if it weren't for you,
I probably never would've
gotten out of that place.
No. It was all you. And
I knew you could do it.
But I'm not the only
one that believes in you.
I know.
I should probably go
home and talk to Joe.
Few things I should tell him.
Tell Sue rain check.
- Yeah.
Chester, are you coming?
I mean, I know you're more
of a root beer kind of guy,
but you've earned a victory meal too.
Really?
Even after falling for the wrath
of some omnipotent,
psychotropic, immortal mask?
You know, after saying it
out loud and hearing it back,
I'm kind of like, you know... [laughs]
Yeah, count me in.
Chester, you are a full-fledged member
of Team Flash now.
Your voice will always matter here.
Just make sure you use it.
Yeah. Okay.
With that being said, there
is a... just this tiny thing
that I wanted to talk to you both about.
- Yeah, what's up?
- Okay.
So you know, the next time
you guys wanna, you know...
- Oh
- Yeah.
Please just, you know,
take a day off, maybe?
Or go on vacation.
- A vacation. Yeah.
- Totally. We hear you. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Cool. Yeah.
- Cool.
- Kay, bye.
- All right.
- Yeah. Bye.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Babe, I had no idea.
Why didn't you tell me this before?
I didn't want you to see me differently.
Or think that I was weak.
Oh, Cecile,
I know what it's like in our community.
There's sometimes a
shame in asking for help
when it comes to mental health.
With what our families go through,
on top of everything
else in this world...
It could crush us.
But we need to start taking
good care of ourselves.
And that's just what you
did, so don't apologize.
Just know that I will always
be here for you.
And we will get through
this or anything together.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Love you.
I love you.
♪ ♪
Hey, whatever happened with Fort Dakota?
Yeah.
You weren't the only one wearing a mask.
There's a reason that Kristen Kramer
wants this part of her
past to stay buried.
[suspenseful music]
Kramer's last army mission,
she was in command of a squad
sent in to take out several
strategic facilities.
She never completed the mission.
She led them into an ambush.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, there's more.
♪ ♪
She was the only one that survived.
Cecile, I think Kristen Kramer
was working with the enemy.
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --