[suspenseful music playing]
[device beeping]
[phone line ringing]
- [woman] Seq, I'm in.
- [Seq] Captain.
[woman] You were right.
The skylight was a window pane.
[Seq] I've got serious interference.
[woman] Weird. It's some kind of Modal.
[Seq] Looks like old code.
[woman] It feels really familiar.
[Seq] Drop a pin.
I'll signal for backup.
- [woman] I'm gonna check it out.
- [Seq] Bugs?
If the general finds out
we've been fishing...
[Bugs] A quick peek can't hurt.
- [static]
- [Seq] Did you hear that?
Shit. I think our signal was traced.
Bugs, this feels like a trap.
Bugs!
[suspenseful music playing]
[SWAT officer] Freeze! Do not move!
We will shoot!
Very slowly, raise your hands.
[suspenseful music playing]
[lieutenant] Here we go.
Hey, where are you going?
You were warned, Lieutenant.
I think we can handle one little girl.
You're wasting your time!
My men are bringing her down now.
No, Lieutenant.
Your men are already dead.
[gasps slowly]
Seq, you with me?
This old code keeps crashing.
Your projection's breaking up.
Switch to audio.
[Seq] Bugs, this is a direct violation
of the general's protocols.
I know, I know.
But something is happening here.
Something important.
[Bugs] Oh, fuck.
We know what happens next.
She kicks their ass.
[all grunting]
[groans]
Now she makes a call.
[woman] The line was traced.
- And then...
- Then she runs for her life.
[woman] Are there any Agents?
We know this story.
This is how it all began.
God damn it.
This is where he began.
You're thinking this Modal is a loop?
Or a treadmill?
Some sort of sequencer
evolving a program to do what?
I don't know.
But I'm going to find out.
All right.
[dramatic music playing]
[grunts]
[panting]
[woman grunts]
[woman groaning]
So déja vu
and yet it's obviously all wrong.
Why use old code
to mirror something new?
I don't know.
[all grunting]
[panting]
If that's supposed to be Trinity,
that's not what happens.
Maybe this isn't the story
we think it is.
Bugs, you have to get out of here.
- It's gotta be a trap.
- [helicopter whirring]
Shit.
[ominous music playing]
[Bugs grunting]
[Bugs growls]
[both grunting]
[Bugs screaming]
[agent screaming]
[both grunting]
[Bugs] Uh...
You all carry on.
As you were.
I'm just gonna...
see myself out.
Kill her.
[grunts]
[yells]
[sirens approaching]
[brakes screech]
[gasps]
[exclaims] Oh, Seq!
[tires screech]
[brakes screech]
[panting]
[gun cocks]
[Bugs straining]
[dramatic music builds]
- Why did you save me?
- You first.
Who are you? Where did you come from?
Okay.
My name is Bugs.
As in "Bunny."
And tech that listens.
Do you know this is a Modal?
What's a Modal?
It's a simulation
used to evolve programs.
Do you understand that you are...
digital sentience?
I know what I am.
Just like I know my job is to hunt down
and destroy sentience...
like you.
And yet...
Here we are.
The other Agents
don't know about this room?
How'd you find it?
No one was ever in the key shop,
so I started looking.
More you looked, the more you found.
Story of my life.
What?
I feel like I know this room.
Holy shit.
This is his apartment.
[gasps]
You mean Thomas Anderson's?
I searched everywhere. He doesn't exist.
He stopped being Thomas a long time ago,
but maybe you know him by his real name.
Neo.
You do.
Oh, okay.
Uh...
I can't believe this,
after all these years.
You see, most people
think that Neo is dead.
But I know he's not.
Because I've seen him.
Where?
It's not something
I can explain easily, but...
But the moment he looked at me,
I felt something...
unlock my mind.
Okay.
Something like that happened to me.
I saw this pattern...
and it was everywhere.
We can't see it,
but we're all trapped inside
these strange, repeating loops.
Somehow, I saw it in the mirror.
Just a flicker,
but it was like you said.
And suddenly I understood.
This is not the real world.
[agent] For the first time,
I felt real purpose.
I knew who I was
and what I had to do.
Who are you?
What do you have to do?
I am...
Morpheus.
And I have to find Neo.
[Bugs gasping]
Morpheus.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, my God!
I have to get you out of here.
I need to figure out
who built this Modal.
Okay, come with me.
You have to be ready to leave.
You have to be really ready.
And if you're not,
if you think that
this is where you belong...
You call this a choice?
Oh, honestly, when somebody
offered me these things,
I went off on
binary conceptions of the world
and said there was no way
I was swallowing
some symbolic reduction of my life.
And the woman with the pills laughed
'cause I was missing the point.
What point?
The choice is an illusion.
You already know what you have to do.
Truth.
Okay.
There's an old building
with a skylight and lots of stairs.
The Lafayette.
One of the four back doors leads there.
[Morpheus] Oh.
- Don't fight it.
- Whoa, what's happening?
Keep breathing.
Extraction works pretty much the same
for humans and programs.
Ouch.
Ah.
Okay.
- Hey.
I've never worn
different glasses before.
Yeah, looks good. Which door?
- It's gotta be...
- Okay.
Agent White.
Agent Smith?
[laughs]
[Bugs grunts]
- [Bugs] Go!
- [grunts]
[men grunting]
Seq! Can you hear me?
Bugs! I thought I lost you.
Can you get us to the window pane?
Bugs! Bugs! He's an Agent!
[Morpheus exclaims, grunts]
That window! Go hard!
[both screaming]
[screaming fades]
[keyboard clacking]
[fast-paced music playing on speakers]
- [computer buzzing]
- What the...
What the hell?
[suspenseful music playing]
Something wrong?
Uh... Just a little crash.
Morning, Bobbi. Morning, dude.
What a beautiful day to be alive.
Am I right?
- Problemo?
- He lost something.
Is this old Matrix code?
A little Modal experiment.
- For Binary?
- [cell phone chimes]
- I need a coffee.
- Coffee. Yes, stat!
I'm buying.
[man] I'm not trying to
blow smoke up your ass,
but the first time I played the trilogy,
I was shook.
The paradox
between free will and destiny.
Are we all just algorithms
doing what we're supposed to do,
or can we escape our programming?
Genius, inside the context of the game,
BT dubs.
Hey, did I tell you
it took over my life?
Yeah. I failed the seventh grade.
[chuckles]
Your game almost ruined me.
- So you've said.
- Yet here we are.
- [cups clink]
- You tell me, Mr. Anderson,
is it free will
or destiny?
Oh, yeah.
There she is.
Total f-ing MILF.
Daggers. Look, I'm sorry.
I'm a geek. I was raised by machines.
Maybe you should go.
No, please. I... I promise, best self.
Best self.
Sure.
You ever talk to her?
Tell you what.
For all you've done for me,
let me do this for you.
Jude, no. Stop.
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Thanks.
Hi. Um...
I know this is all a bit extemporaneous.
I'm Jude Gallagher.
I work for a game company
called Deus Machina.
Hi, Jude, I'm Tiffany.
Tiffany. Wow. Didn't see that coming.
- Mom loved Audrey Hepburn.
- Jude.
Oh, and this is my very good friend,
Thomas Anderson.
He is a bona fide famous person
and considered by most to be
the greatest game designer
of our generation.
I'm sorry about this.
- Jude...
- [softly] Just talk to her.
Hi, Thomas. Everyone calls me Tiff.
Hi.
Have we met?
Uh, we both come here.
- Can I have your morning bun?
- [boy] Hey.
Are you trying to ball my mom or what?
- Brandon!
- [chuckles]
[Boy 2] Can I have one bite?
Babe. What's going on?
We're gonna be late.
This is my husband, Chad.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
Babe, we gotta get Callie to practice.
Right. Sorry. [chuckles]
Come on, kids. Let's move out.
[soft music playing]
What?
[keyboard clacking]
[ominous music playing]
Sorry. Uh, it's the boss.
"Billions of people
just living out their lives,
oblivious."
I always loved that line.
You wrote that one, yeah?
Every time I stand here,
I mean, O-M-G.
It's so perfect, it's gotta be fake.
- Right?
- [chuckles softly]
Yeah.
Sure.
Have a seat.
[man sighs]
Smoke?
I thought you quit.
I quit calling it a habit.
Now it's just a guilty pleasure.
Oh. Maybe I can make this easy for you.
I know Binary is over budget.
This is not about Binary, Tom.
It's bigger than that.
This is about our future,
which is a sticky subject,
given our past.
What do you mean?
How's the therapy?
Good.
Any...
episodes?
No.
That's terrific.
Look, Tom,
I know we've always had our differences.
What did you say
about our first meeting?
We had all the chemistry
of an FBI interrogation.
[muffled yell]
[scoffs]
But look at this place.
We did this.
Together.
Yeah.
Now what?
Things have changed. The market's tough.
I'm sure you can understand
why our beloved parent company,
Warner Bros.,
has decided to make a sequel
to the trilogy.
What?
They informed me
they're gonna do it with or without us.
I thought they couldn't do that.
[exhales]
Oh, they can.
And they made it clear
they'll kill our contract
if we don't cooperate.
Really?
I know you said
the story was over for you,
but that's the thing about stories.
They never really end, do they?
We're still telling the same stories
we've always told,
just with different names,
different faces
and I have to say I'm kind of excited.
After all these years,
to be going back
to where it all started.
Back to The Matrix.
I've spoken to Marketing...
- [sinister music playing]
- [distorted voice]
[in normal voice] Tom?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
[exhales nervously]
Yeah.
[analyst] What were you feeling
at that point?
What was I feeling?
I felt either I'm having
a mental breakdown again
or I'm living inside
a computer-generated reality
that has imprisoned me...
again.
[laughs]
[chuckles softly]
Not much of a choice.
No.
Maybe it's not as binary as that.
Maybe there are other ways
to understand what happened.
Yeah.
Thomas, you are a suicide survivor
gifted with a powerful imagination.
Those facts have combined
to create dangerous fictions
in your life.
Yesterday, you walked into a meeting
with your business partner
and he ambushed you,
demanding you make a game
you said you would never make.
This attack
effectively took away your voice.
His violence triggered you
and your mind fought back.
You did to him
what he was doing to you.
We've talked about the value
of adaptive anger in healing trauma.
Far from suggesting
a repeat of your initial breakdown,
I believe this episode
demonstrates healthy self-protection.
And more importantly,
I remember how hard it was
for you to share something like this.
Which tells me just how far we've come.
[chuckles softly]
Do you need a refill
on your prescription?
[sighs]
Yeah.
[pills rattle]
[mysterious music playing]
[grunts softly]
First of all,
I know I speak for everyone
when I say that I'm so, so excited
to be working on a game
that was such a, well, game changer.
Now, the packet in front of you
has our focus group research.
Inside, you'll find the breakdown,
including key word association
with the brand.
The top two
being "originality" and "fresh,"
which I think are great things
to keep in mind
as you begin working on Matrix 4.
And who knows how many more?
[alarm buzzing, stops]
[singing indistinctly]
What made Matrix different?
It effed with your head.
On point.
People want us up in their grey space,
switching their synaptic WTF light on.
["White Rabbit" playing]
[man laughing]
What made Matrix different?
It effed with your head.
People want us up in their grey space,
switching their synaptic
"What the hell is going on here?"
light on.
[panting]
[shower running]
I didn't love the first one,
like some of you.
And, frankly, I've got zero tolerance
for anything that requires
a syllabus and a highlighter.
I like my games big, loud and dumb.
We need guns! Lots of guns.
Matrix means mayhem.
[grunting]
Mindless action is not on-brand.
[man] She's right.
Matrix is mind porn.
Philosophy in shiny,
- tight PVC.
- Yeah.
Ideas are the new sexy.
["White Rabbit" continues playing]
Obviously The Matrix is about...
- trans-politics.
- Crypto-fascism.
It's a metaphor...
of capitalist exploitation.
This cannot be another reboot,
retread, regurgitated...
Why not? Reboots sell.
We are so far down
the wrong rabbit hole here, people.
You say Matrix to anyone...
You say Matrix...
[echoing] Matrix... Matrix... Matrix...
this is what they see.
[mimics explosion]
- [guns firing]
- [bullets whizzing]
[clicks tongue]
Allow me to sum up our goal
in a single word.
Bullet time! Bullet time!
That's two words.
We need a new "bullet time." [echoing]
[laughs maniacally]
We need to revolutionize gaming again.
Revolutionize gaming again! [echoing]
["White Rabbit" continues]
[barista] Afternoon, Tiff.
The ushe?
You know what, Skroce? I'm going wild.
I'll have a cortado today.
Fly that freak flag.
Mind if I get that?
Oh, hi.
Hi.
[Tiffany] I remember wanting a family,
but was that because
that's what women are supposed to want?
How do you know
if you want something yourself
or if your upbringing
programmed you to want it?
Mm.
I pay my analyst a lot of money
to answer such questions for me.
Smart.
I should get more therapy
but honestly, I'm too goddamn tired.
Kids are exhausting, you know?
No. Never had kids.
Oh, right, I knew that.
- Sorry. I googled you.
- [chuckles]
So, what's it like
being a world-famous game designer?
- Must be amazing.
- Uh... A lot of hours.
Sometimes it is amazing.
Most times,
I don't know.
But you made The Matrix.
Even I've heard of that.
Yeah. We kept some kids entertained.
- So, worth it?
- [chuckles]
Can I ask something about your game?
Sure.
Did you base your main character
on yourself?
There is a lot of me in him.
[indistinct shouting]
Maybe a little too much.
Can I ask you something else?
Please.
There's a woman in your game.
Trinity.
Which is a weird
coincidence also, right?
God, yeah.
I like her.
- I like Trinity.
- Ah.
And I dig her Ducati.
Another coincidence. I love motorcycles.
[engine revs]
My friend Kush and I
actually build them.
Really?
You have your analyst, I have my bikes.
So, I was looking at images
from your game.
At Trinity.
Well, I showed Chad a scene,
and I was like, "So, what do you think?"
He didn't get it until I said,
"Don't you think she looks like me?"
You know what he did?
He laughed.
And I laughed too, like it was a joke.
How could it not be, right?
Made me so angry.
I hated myself for laughing.
I wanted to kick him so hard.
Not too hard.
Maybe just hard enough
to break his jaw off.
[chuckles]
And right now,
you're probably regretting
sitting down with me.
This is the best thing I've done
in a long time.
[chuckles]
- [cell phone ringing]
- [gasps]
I have to take this.
Hi, this is Tiff.
Oh, God, no.
[gasps]
I'll be right there.
My... My, uh, youngest
stuck a Lego up his nose.
Oh.
I gotta go.
I hope I see you again.
[alarm blaring]
[announcer on speaker]
There has been a report of an emergency.
Proceed calmly to the nearest exit
and leave the building immediately.
What's going on?
We probably just got swatted
by some 14-year-old.
Yeah, someone pissed
about the latest update.
Or they're just a dick.
Please move to the exits.
Building's being evacuated.
[cell phone buzzes]
[suspenseful music playing]
[security guard] Sir, this way.
Jude?
Jude!
At last.
[chuckles] Ah.
I wasn't too sure about the callback,
but, you know, it was hard to resist.
What?
Morpheus Uno. Reveal at the window.
Lightning, thunder and theater.
At last.
All these years later, here's me,
strolling out of a toilet stall.
Tragedy or farce?
I know you.
Not every day you meet your maker.
This can't be happening.
Oh, most definitely is.
You can't be a character I coded.
One hundred percent natural.
[gasps softly]
How?
All the explanation you need.
Oh.
No.
No, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What do you mean, "no"?
You wanted this, you did this.
This was your idea.
[hesitating] It was a test.
An experiment.
An experiment?
You put me in a tiny-ass Modal,
left me to bang my head
till I nearly lost my shit
searching for you,
as an experiment.
- The exit's breaking down.
- He hasn't taken the pill.
What? There's no time.
I know, I know. He's having a moment.
Does he know
how hard it was to hack that mirror?
[tense music playing]
Still open.
This... This can't be real.
[SWAT officer] Target acquired.
We got him.
[grunting]
This isn't happening.
It's in my mind. It's in my mind.
[SWAT officer 2] Hey, you!
Stop! Hold it!
[all screaming]
[groaning]
This can't be happening.
- [gunshots]
- [gasps]
[SWAT officer 3] Freeze! Don't move!
[gun firing]
Neo!
[tense music playing]
[gun firing]
Oh, my God!
[distorted gunfire]
[men groaning]
[grunting]
[tense music continues]
Neo!
[tense music builds]
[shouts] Mr. Anderson!
No.
It can't be.
I've missed you.
[cat meows]
[bell tinkling]
It's in my mind.
[cup clinking]
[analyst] Can you hear me, Thomas?
Follow my voice.
Feel the tips of your fingers.
What are they touching?
[bell tinkling]
The bell.
Do you hear the bell?
Do you remember what happened?
How you got here?
You must have walked.
I heard Déja Vu outside,
opened my door, and there you were.
[Thomas Anderson exhales]
You feel like you can talk about it?
When we started working together,
you had lost your capacity
to discern reality from fiction.
You came to me
after trying to jump off a building.
You said you wanted to fly away.
[indistinct chatter]
[people shouting]
We have made
a lot of progress since then,
but you seem
particularly triggered right now.
Can you tell me how it started?
He texted me.
Who?
Morpheus.
Ah.
So, he's back.
It wasn't actually him.
It was a program I coded for a Modal.
And this Modal, Morpheus,
came to help you escape
from a virtual reality
called The Matrix?
Am I crazy?
We don't use that word in here.
What word should I use?
What word explains
what is happening to me?
Can I see the texts?
[exhales]
They were erased.
If we got in my car
and drove to your office,
what do you think we'd find there?
Nothing.
Because there was no attack.
No one was Killed.
No one texted.
My mind made it all up.
Is that what I'm supposed to say?
Is that what you believe?
It felt real.
Of course.
It was your great ambition
to make a game
that was indistinguishable from reality.
To achieve this goal,
you converted elements of your life
into narrative.
Your sublimated anger toward
your business partner
cast him as your nemesis.
A married woman named Tiffany
became the Trinity of a doomed romance.
Even your dislike of my cat
made it into your Matrix.
There's nothing wrong with that.
It's what artists do.
But it becomes a problem
when fantasies
endanger us or other people.
We don't want anyone to get hurt,
do we, Thomas?
Hi, Thomas. Everyone calls me Tiff.
- Who are you?
- My name is Trinity.
[Oracle] No one can tell you
you're in love.
You just know it, through and through.
Balls to bones.
[Trinity whispers] You feel this?
I'm never letting go.
[yells]
[both grunting]
[Morpheus] You have to
let it all go, Neo.
Free your mind.
[cell phone buzzing]
- [buzzing stops]
- [sighs]
[pigeon cooing]
Huh.
Looks easy enough.
[exhales]
"Free my mind." Shit.
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay.
Free my mind.
[grunts]
I fly...
or I fall.
[suspenseful music builds]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
Who the hell are you?
You won't remember me,
but a long time ago, you changed my life
when you leapt off another roof.
Back then,
I was just like any other coppertop,
pretending my life
until I looked up and I saw you.
It was a different you, but I saw
the real you,
just a second before...
you leapt.
[people shouting]
And you never fell.
Are you the one that hacked my Modal?
Yeah.
[cell phone buzzing]
That'll be Jude. He's not your friend.
He's a handle,
a program used to control you.
He's on his way here,
and he's bringing Agents with him.
Jude.
Bro, I've been calling you all night.
We have a major problemo.
Are you alone?
That's kind of a sexy question, dude.
[Bugs] They don't look like
typical Agents.
They use bots now,
skinned as normal people,
which means they're everywhere
and you never know who to trust.
Why should I trust you?
Because if they open that door,
we lose our hack.
I will be caught and killed
and you will be put right back
on that treadmill they designed for you
just like they did the last time
you tried to leap your way out.
I know why you left your Modal open.
You needed someone else
to free Morpheus.
And it's because of him
that we were able to get to you.
I know these things the same way
that I knew one day I would find you.
And that when I did,
you would be ready for this.
If you want the truth, Neo,
you're going to have to follow me.
Okay.
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
- Where are we?
- Tokyo.
A moving portal
makes it harder to track us.
- Seq is the best of them.
- [Seq] Portal's clean.
Reading no shadows.
I don't remember this.
We don't have to run
to phone booths anymore either.
[upbeat music playing]
Door's on your right.
[door opens]
Set and setting, right?
Oh, no.
It's all about set...
and setting.
After our first contact went so badly,
we thought elements from your past
might help ease you into the present.
Nothing comforts anxiety like
a little nostalgia.
This is footage from your game.
[Morpheus] Time is always against us,
etcetera, etcetera.
No one can be told what the Matrix is,
blah, blah, blah.
You gotta see it to believe it.
Time to fly.
[suspenseful music playing]
Wait.
If this is real,
if I haven't lost my mind,
does that mean
this happened?
[soft music playing]
But if it did,
then we died.
Obviously not.
Why the Machines kept you alive
and why they went
to such lengths to hide you
are questions we don't have answers to.
Hide me?
I've been at a company making
a game called The Matrix.
Doesn't seem like
they were trying to hide anything.
We've been tracking
that company for years.
We screened
every Thomas Anderson we found.
What we didn't understand
was that they could alter your DSI.
Pods generate your digital self-image
through a feedback system
called Semblance.
This is how you look to yourself.
Somehow they were able
to alter your DSI loop.
This is how everyone else sees you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Twenty years?
Why did it take 20 years to find me?
It took a lot longer than that.
It's been over 60 years
since you and Trinity
flew to one of the Machine Cities.
What?
There's so much we don't know.
Like why you've barely aged,
or how many times
they've altered your DSI.
[Morpheus] But based on what we do know,
it appears no one found you
because you didn't want to be found.
- That's not true.
- [Morpheus] Maybe it isn't.
Maybe there's no foundation
to the rumors that you disappeared
because you were
working with the Machines
from the beginning.
Morpheus, stop.
All I'm saying is this is the moment
for you to show us what is real.
If you want out,
you'll take this pill.
But if you are where you belong,
you can go back to this.
Every day.
Over and over, forever.
Fuck.
[dramatic music playing]
[Seq] Keep the loop tight.
[Bugs] Cybebe needs that tower pin.
I got a signal. It's faint.
It's definitely off-grid.
Captain. I'm tracking
a whole lot of weird.
- What?
- It's some kind of graft.
Thomas?
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
- We got company.
- How'd they find us?
Thomas, none of this is real.
You are in the midst
of a serious psychotic break.
- Lexy?
- Almost there.
Thomas?
Thomas, please. This is not a game.
Feel my hand.
This is what is real.
Stay with me.
[Thomas Anderson] No. No.
[analyst, distorted] Stay with me.
[distorted grunts]
Neo!
Morpheus!
[Morpheus] Let's go, let's go!
[people screaming]
[woman screaming]
- Bots are being activated.
- It's a swarm.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[woman screams]
[Bugs] Come on!
[Morpheus grunting]
[grunting]
[whimpers]
[shrieking]
I got a hack in the bathroom. Hurry.
Yes.
Come on!
Seq, where?
- That mirror.
- What? We'll never fit.
You gotta fit, 'cause I don't have
another way off this train.
- [groans]
- [Morpheus] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I know. I know.
Think perspective.
Closer you are, bigger it gets.
Okay, come on.
In you go.
[suspenseful music builds]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[tense music builds]
[ominous music playing]
[haunting music playing]
[metal clicking]
[grunts]
[yells, straining]
[groaning]
[whirring]
[screams]
[yelps, grunts]
[warbling]
[groaning]
[soft music playing]
[softly] Trinity.
No.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Sentinels chittering]
[thunder crashing]
[dramatic music playing]
[electricity crackling]
[echoing] Welcome back
to the real world.
Trinity.
What's up, Doc?
[woman] His vital systems
have been meticulously maintained,
but it doesn't look good.
[EKG beeping]
- We're losing him.
- Cold boot could shock him.
Do it.
[computer buzzing rapidly]
[groans]
[exhales]
I remember this.
The Construct.
In between
everything and nothing.
Welcome to the Crib.
I've been chilling here
in the ship network,
learning all about you.
[TV static]
And me.
Careful. It'll do your head in.
Are memories turned into fiction
any less real?
Is reality based in memory
nothing but fiction?
As to my role in all this,
my best guess is that you wrote me
as an algorithmic reflection
of two forces
that helped you become you,
Morpheus and Agent Smith.
A combo pack of counterprogramming
that was...
[inhales]
Let's just say,
more than a little bit crazy-making.
But it worked because here we are.
Now, for the bad news.
Your brain is hooked on this shit
The Matrix has been force-feeding you
for years.
Hooked bad.
You're going through major withdrawals.
Docbots are giving you crap odds
for surviving.
But, see, they don't know you like I do.
I know exactly what you need.
[lively music playing]
You gotta be kidding.
Uh-uh.
No joke.
Could be this is the first day
of the rest of your life.
But if you want it...
[water splashing]
You gotta fight for it.
No. I'm done fighting.
Are you?
[traditional battle music playing]
[Neo grunting]
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[music resumes]
[groaning]
What the hell is he doing?
Oh, yeah. They taught you good.
[Neo grunting]
Made you believe
their world was all you deserved.
But some part of you knew
that was a lie.
Some part of you
remembered what was real.
You don't know me.
No?
[both grunting]
[groans]
Ooh.
[yelling]
[panting]
[Neo grunting]
[Morpheus grunting]
[both grunting]
I know you,
because I know the only thing
that still matters to you.
I know it's why you're here,
why you're still fighting
and why you will never give up.
[both grunting]
[Neo groaning]
- [whimpering]
- [EKG beeping]
Come on, Neo!
This is it.
This is your last chance.
[Neo groaning]
[emotional music playing]
[groaning]
You gotta fight for your goddamn life
if you want to see Trinity again.
[Neo groaning]
Come on, Neo! Fight for her!
- Holy shit.
- Fight for her!
[yelling]
[explosion]
[gasps]
[sighs]
- Hey.
Mind if I...
How are you doing?
If this plug is actually real,
that means they took my life...
[scoffs]
And turned it into a video game.
How am I doing?
I don't know.
I don't even know how to know.
That's it, isn't it?
If we don't know what's real,
we can't resist.
They took your story,
something that meant
so much to people like me,
and turned it into something trivial.
That's what the Matrix does.
It weaponizes every idea.
Every dream.
Everything that's important to us.
Where better to bury truth
than inside something
as ordinary as a video game?
That sounds like the Oracle.
[Bugs chuckles]
Heard so much about her.
She was gone before I was free.
Gone?
When this new version of the Matrix
was uploaded,
there was a purge.
[sighs]
They promised peace
and they gave us purge.
No.
No, there was peace.
You made it possible,
and it changed everything.
Doesn't feel like it changed anything.
The Matrix is the same or worse.
And I'm back where I started.
It feels like everything I did,
everything we did...
[both grunt]
like none of it mattered.
All of it mattered.
I can show you.
This is my crew.
Our operator, Seq.
Sequoia. But everybody calls me Seq.
Nice to meet you.
Dad loved redwoods.
When he escaped the Matrix
and found out they no longer existed,
it almost killed him.
Lucky he met Mom,
and here I am.
This is Lexy, Berg and Ellster.
Hi.
You knew my grandfather, Captain Roland.
Roland was your grandfather?
He always laughed,
joking how he never believed in you.
But, in private, he said
that you freed his mind a second time.
Uh, not to fanboy out here,
but this is kind of
a huge moment for me.
Berg is our resident Neo-ologist.
A what?
There's a lot of people
out there like me
who are a little bit obsessed
with your life.
I would never have recognized your Modal
if it weren't for him.
Whenever you're feeling up for it,
I've got, like, a million questions.
Me too. Starting with them.
[Bugs] It's okay.
Come meet him.
This is Cybebe.
That's Octacles.
- That's Lumin8.
- [chittering]
Machines are on our side now?
They are synthients.
It's a word they prefer to Machines.
Your contact with the Synthient City
had a huge impact on their world.
[Bugs] That's what I meant.
What you changed that nobody believed
could ever be changed.
The meaning of "our side."
[Cybebe warbling softly]
Cybebe and Octacles risked their lives
to help get you out.
Thank you.
But why?
[Morpheus] Not all seek to control.
Just as not all wish to be free.
What is that?
An exomorphic-particle codex.
It's pretty new.
It gives programs access to this world.
Within limits.
Limits are the domain of the limited.
Morpheus.
Thank you.
It was my honor.
[chuckles] Wow.
- [crew chuckles]
- How does it work?
Paramagnetic oscillation.
If you want,
I can download the codex manual for you.
- Sure.
- Downloading used to be fun.
Now it's all manuals and diagnostics.
Can I ask them something?
When you unplugged me,
there was another pod?
[warbling softly]
Yes. We've analyzed the data.
It could be Trinity.
It's her.
I figured we were going to
have this conversation.
Look, you were not
a typical flush-and-grab.
You were in this weird tower
that Cybebe had never accessed,
and she's now exiled.
We burned our one shot for you.
Even if it were Trinity
and she wanted to be free,
we have no idea how to do it.
Yet.
Nobody believed we'd ever find him,
but we did.
Okay.
We don't know how to get her out... yet.
Captain, we're approaching
security clearance.
We're here.
Zion?
Have a seat.
This is Hanno. Best pilot in our fleet.
Quite a few synthients
deserve that title before me.
[Control on radio]
Mnemosyne, you are cleared for landing.
Welcome home.
[Hanno] Thank you, Control.
Um, we're about to crash.
[dramatic music playing]
[chuckles]
General realized we were never going to
beat the Sentinels,
so we just got better at
hiding from them.
Welcome to Io.
Io.
[sweeping music playing]
Wow. That looks real.
Bio-sky.
Works kind of like grow lights.
It's way more complex than that.
It pulls water from the crust,
hydronating the air.
It balances the ECO and our SRI cycles.
Plus... [sighs]
It is pretty to look at.
As opposed to that.
I guess the general
sent us a welcome party.
God damn.
It is you.
Niobe?
A few more wrinkles
and a few less teeth,
but wise enough to know
I don't know anything.
I sure as shit never saw this coming.
Neither did I.
I told you he was alive.
Captain, you and your crew
have been grounded.
General, if you'd just let me explain.
The protocols are put in place
for everyone's protection.
I'm sorry. I saw an opportunity
and I was afraid we'd lose him.
But, General,
people have been waiting for so long.
We found The One.
I don't believe in The One.
I never did.
No?
Me neither.
But there was a time
when you trusted me with your ship,
against the Council's orders.
The world was different then.
We were different.
Report to the docks.
Scrub down the Mnemosyne.
Transfer your access codes.
You are done, Captain.
[gasps softly]
We need to talk.
[Niobe] When word first came,
that it actually might be you,
I didn't know how I would feel
in this moment.
It is nice to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
- [glasses clink]
A long way from Dozer's paint stripper.
[chuckles] Yes.
A lot has changed.
Except maybe you.
You remember this?
It's so easy to forget how much noise
the Matrix pumps into your head
until you unplug.
[Neo sighs]
Yeah.
Something else
makes the same kind of noise.
Takes over every damn thing
just like the Matrix.
War.
I stood at the barricade of the Temple.
Staring at the army of Sentinels,
waiting for them to Kill
every one of us.
But then, they left.
They said you saved us.
I didn't believe it.
Every night I would dream
of attack sirens.
But then,
I would wake up to this...
silence.
I'm ashamed of it now.
My pessimism
of how long it took me to believe
a world without war was possible.
You gave me that.
You gave that gift to us all.
And it is the gift
that continues to bear fruit.
Come help me get up.
Let's take a walk.
[mysterious music playing]
[elevator door opens]
Oh! Beautiful.
This is Freya, head of botany.
And this is Quillion,
our lead digitologist.
I presume
our guest needs no introduction.
Nothing travels faster than light.
Except gossip.
[Freya chuckles]
Welcome to the Garden, Neo.
A strawberry?
Using digital code from the Matrix,
we retro-convert it into DNA sequences.
And they grow here?
It's not easy augmenting the genome
to photosynthesize Bio-sky, but...
- We're getting there.
- [chuckles]
Go ahead. Try it.
[Niobe chuckles]
We're quite excited
about the blueberries.
You remember that shit we used to eat?
That slop that tasted like rust.
Zion could have never
made something like this.
Why?
Because we needed synthients
and DI like him.
Zion was stuck in the past.
Stuck in war.
Stuck in a Matrix of its own.
They believed
that it had to be us or them.
This city was built
by us and them.
What happened to Zion?
I've been waiting
for you to ask that question.
All of the troubles
started in the Machine Cities.
Power plants were unable
to produce enough energy.
Nothing can breed violence
like scarcity.
For the first time,
we saw machines at war with one another.
We got word from the Oracle
of a new power rising.
That was the last we heard from her.
Morpheus.
[Niobe] After the siege,
he was elected unanimously.
High Chair of the Council.
Oh, how he loved that. [scoffs]
But as rumors of this new power spread,
he ignored them.
He was certain what you had done
could not be undone.
All of these people
never stopped believing in miracles,
believing in you.
I'm sorry.
How could I know this would happen?
We didn't understand
all of it back then.
No more than we do now.
I didn't come here
to cause you problems, Niobe,
but I need your help.
Trinity is alive.
Then there is another question.
Why did they keep her alive?
I can't answer that.
But if there's a chance I can free her,
I have to try.
Even if it means
endangering everyone in this city?
I'm sorry, Neo.
I won't let what happened to Zion
happen to Io.
I hope you'll forgive an old woman
for asking you to go with Sheperd here,
till we have better understanding
of what's going on.
You're going to imprison me
after I just got free?
I know it doesn't seem fair,
but neither does growing old.
But you don't hear me complaining.
[elevator whirring]
Sorry.
I've never met a legend before.
Neo.
Sheperd. [breathes shakily]
[chuckles in disbelief]
Crazy. You're real.
"Real."
There's that word again.
[Sheperd] People talk a lot
about the old days.
About you, the viral Agent.
The siege of Zion.
Everything was simpler back then.
People wanted to be free.
It's different now.
Sometimes it feels like people gave up.
Like the Matrix won.
[unlocks door]
This is you.
And I gotta ask you one thing.
Is it true you could fly?
Cool.
[locks door]
[trickling]
[Morpheus grunts]
Morpheus.
Oh. General stuck you
in the Rapunzel tower.
[Morpheus exhales]
On the upside, it's a nice view.
What happened to Bugs and the others?
They're supposed to be sterilizing
the Mnemosyne with a toothbrush.
"Supposed to be"?
Well, I could tell you
that they're standing by,
waiting for you to make the choice
to remain meekly incarcerated
or bust the hell out of here
and go and find Trinity.
But that ain't a choice.
[dramatic music playing]
[Sheperd] General, what should we do?
[Freya] Bugs has the same
independence of mind
she had the day you freed her.
This is not independence of mind.
It's mutiny.
[Freya] Come on, 'Be.
I know how much you hated
locking him up.
Just like I know there's a part of you
that's relieved now that he's gone.
We've worked so hard to keep Io safe.
This scares me.
That's her.
[Seq] On the bridge.
Got her.
[engine revving]
It's sick how the Semblance works.
You see flashes of the real her,
but the way she reads...
Code-wise, she's pure bluepill.
This is a tough question, Neo,
but it has to be asked.
What if she's happy where she is?
How did I read?
Exactly like her.
Take us to broadcast depth.
[suspenseful music playing]
Thank you for helping me.
Most of us are here because of you.
I also admit our only chance
to get out of the general's doghouse
is for you to find your mojo.
What if I can't be what I once was?
- Then we're all fucked.
- [signal beeps]
[Hanno] Two minutes.
Two minutes to broadcast.
[Seq] I slipped you in
through a hotel room.
[Seq chuckles]
Should be safe.
Portal's open.
Closest I could get you
is the warehouse near her garage.
Whole zone's crawling with bots.
Let's go.
So, what do you think of him?
I was kinda worried at first
because he's so much older.
The beard, the hair... Oh.
- No, totally works for me.
- [scoffs] You idiot.
I mean "The One" thing.
You know, everyone that
shipped with him died.
Oh, yeah. He's gonna
get us all killed for sure.
[guns cocking]
Predictable as ever.
Smith.
Smith? As in, the Smith?
[chuckles]
This is so insane.
There's so many theories
about the two of them
and they're standing right there.
This code is freaky.
He's like an Agent, but not.
An appeal to reason.
How did you find us?
You never appreciated our relationship.
Not like The Analyst.
- The what?
- My doctor.
He used our bond
and turned it into a chain.
It's so obvious once you see it, right?
But this whole altered-code update
really blew my mind.
I still don't know how he did it.
You, as a balding nerd.
Hilarious.
And me... [sighs]
Even more perfect.
Maybe a little too far
on the piercing blue eyes.
What do you think?
What do you want, Smith?
I have such dreams, Tom. Big dreams.
Well, mostly just extremely violent
revenge fantasies,
but in order for me to pursue mine,
I need to dissuade you
from pursuing yours.
Hmm. Sounds like conflict.
Inevitable?
Doesn't have to be.
All you have to do
is stay out of the Matrix,
and leave the good doctor to me.
You can have him. I'm here for Trinity.
That's the trouble, Tom.
He knew you'd come, just like I did.
[scoffs]
Trust me.
You're not ready for him.
Captain, I'm reading portals
from the lower frequencies.
I won't have his leash on my neck again.
I found some old acquaintances of yours.
- Bugs!
- [growling]
[ominous music playing]
[snarls]
Exiles.
I thought they were all purged.
[man] You?
[excitedly] Oh!
It is you!
[man speaking French]
All these years. I can't believe it.
Oh, God.
You stole my life!
[speaking French]
[in English] What the Merv
is trying to say is that
their situation
is a little bit like mine.
To have their lives back,
yours has to end.
[bullet whizzing]
Kill him!
[tense music playing]
[blade slicing]
[all grunting]
You ruined every
suck-my-silky-ass thing!
We had grace.
We had style!
We had conversation!
Not this... [mimics text message sound]
[all grunting]
- [bone cracks]
- [yells]
Art, films, books were all better!
Originality mattered!
You gave us Face-Zucker-suck
and
Couch-flix-climatey-Wiki-piss-and-shit!
[screams]
[screaming]
[ominous music builds]
[man groans]
I still know kung fu.
Neo!
[Smith yells]
[both grunting]
Just like old times.
[tense music playing]
[Neo groaning]
[woman shrieks]
[man yelling]
Neo.
I've been thinking about us, Tom.
About binaries that form
the nature of things.
Ones and zeros.
[grunting]
Light and dark.
Choice and its absence.
[Smith grunts]
Anderson and Smith.
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
You've lost something, Tom.
You're not what you used to be.
It's true.
[grunts]
[jaw cracks]
- Nice one.
- Thanks.
Come on, Neo.
[Neo groaning]
[panting]
[gasps]
Captain. You okay?
Yeah. Where's Neo?
Smith is killing him.
[Bugs] Where?
[Neo groaning]
I feel bad about this, Tom.
After all,
you are the one who set me free...
again.
So you, more than anyone,
understands why I can't go back.
[grunts]
You should have listened to me.
Now you'll never see her again.
[grunts]
[yells]
[energy explodes]
What was that?
That was Neo.
Mojo rising.
[Lumin8 chittering]
[Seq exclaims]
[Bugs] You all right?
Yeah.
- It's gonna trigger a response.
- I got multiple exits ready.
[The Merovingian] This is not over yet!
Our sequel franchise spinoff!
[speaking French]
[spits]
[Bugs] We should go.
I can't.
I have to talk to her.
Neo, those Exiles were older than you,
and we barely handled them.
[sighs]
You really wanna do this now?
I mean...
you look like shit.
[buzzing]
Oh, my God. What? What happened?
An accident.
[Tiffany] Kush. Call a doctor.
It's fine.
I don't have a lot of time.
I wasn't sure I'd see you again.
After we spoke, I realized
my life wasn't a life.
At some point, I think I gave up
searching for something real.
Wait.
Something happened.
I looked for you at the coffee shop.
I began to wonder if I imagined you.
And then last night I had a dream.
In the dream,
you were surrounded by police,
then they started chasing us.
- Us?
- You were on my bike with me.
How did it end?
Not good.
I've had dreams
that weren't just dreams.
You mean a dream that came true?
[bell tinkling]
[suspenseful music playing]
Finally, we can talk like adults.
I hate lying. I do.
It exhausts me.
Tiff and I have been waiting for you,
like, forever.
[distorted rewinding]
Déjà vu, right?
Oh, no use. You can't beat time.
This rewind is happening
faster than you can blink.
You gave me the idea.
Allow me to sum up our goal
in a single word.
"Bullet time."
[grunts in slow motion]
I know. Kind of ironic,
using the power that defined you
to control you. [chuckles]
I kept such a close eye on you
and, still, you found a way out.
Clever monkey, using that Modal.
Call me an optimist,
but this could all be for the best.
The skin's not looking
too bad this time.
I know some of this
will be difficult for you to hear,
after everything you went through.
All that pain and suffering,
only to learn
the world doesn't end when you do.
Surprise.
[Neo grunts]
I was there when you died.
[Neo screaming]
I said to myself,
"Here is the anomaly of anomalies."
What an extraordinary opportunity.
First, I had to convince the Suits
to let me rebuild the two of you.
Why her? Getting there.
And don't worry, she can't hear me.
Resurrecting you both
was crazy expensive.
Like renovating a house.
Took twice as long, cost twice as much.
[gasps]
I thought you'd be happy
to be alive again.
So wrong.
- [machine whirring]
- [screaming]
Did you know hope and despair
are nearly identical in code?
[screaming]
We worked for years
trying to activate your source code.
I was about to give up,
when I realized...
Trinity.
It was never just you.
Alone, neither of you
is of any particular value.
[Trinity screaming]
Like acids and bases,
you're dangerous when mixed together.
Every sim where you two bonded,
let's just say bad things happened.
Neo!
However, as long as I managed
to keep you close,
but not too close,
I discovered something incredible.
Now, my predecessor loved precision.
His Matrix was all fussy facts
and equations.
He hated the human mind.
So he never bothered to realize
that you don't give a shit about facts.
It's all about fiction.
The only world that matters
is the one in here.
And you people believe
the craziest shit.
Why?
What validates
and makes your fictions real?
Feelings.
Allow me.
Kush here is one of my handlers.
They're everywhere.
Such a pain,
cloning Agents over a coppertop.
Far more effective
just to saturate a population.
And, bonus, swarm mode is sick fun.
[chuckles]
[gun fires in slow motion]
Ooh! Nicely done.
You ever wonder why you have nightmares?
Why your own brain tortures you?
It's actually us,
maximizing your output.
It works just like this.
Oh, no. Can you stop the bullet?
If only you could move faster.
[chuckles] Here's the thing
about feelings.
They're so much easier to control
than facts.
Turns out, in my Matrix,
the worse we treat you,
the more we manipulate you,
the more energy you produce.
It's nuts. [chomps]
I've been setting productivity records
every year since I took over.
And, the best part, zero resistance.
People stay in their pods,
happier than pigs in shit.
The key to it all?
You.
And her.
Quietly yearning
for what you don't have,
while dreading losing what you do.
For 99.9% of your race,
that is the definition of reality.
Desire and fear, baby.
Just give the people
what they want, right?
[squelches]
She's the only home you have, Thomas.
Come home
before something terrible happens.
[tense music playing]
[Neo grunts]
[keyboard clacking]
- Bugs!
- I hear him.
- [sirens approaching]
- [tires screech]
Trinity!
- You shouldn't call me that.
- I'm sorry.
I have to go.
But I'll be back.
Neo! Time to go.
- [gasps]
- [alarm blaring]
- Sentinels?
- Worse.
[Sheperd on radio] General ordered me
to look after the ship.
So you shadowed us?
Check your long-range scans.
Squids are combing this area.
He's right.
You can stay here and die,
or come back and face a court-martial.
And you call that a choice?
[Niobe] Sheperd should have left you
to the Squids.
I'm too damn old
to sit through some boring-ass trial.
Niobe, don't blame Bugs.
Do shut your mouth.
Do address me as General.
And do not rob my ex-captain
of her agency,
which she exercised with her own
particular brand
of shortsighted stupidity.
Shortsighted?
You care more about growing fruit
than freeing minds.
We are not going
to have this argument again.
It's not an argument. It's a fact.
You gave up on people.
I tell you what I'm going to give up on,
and it's you!
- Sheperd, get her out of my sight.
- General.
Disarm!
Kujaku's a friend.
[Kujaku warbling]
Hello, friend.
[chittering softly]
Okay.
Him?
General.
Thank you for seeing me.
I figured if there was anyone
who could make sense of this mess,
it would be you.
Hello, Neo.
I know you.
I tried to keep my eye on you.
[clicks tongue]
Why?
We met a long time ago.
Good morning.
Sati.
My father knew we'd meet again,
though he would have wished
for happier circumstances.
His inadvertent role
in what happened to you
was the greatest regret of his life.
I don't understand.
My father was the chief engineer
at the Anomaleum.
[Niobe] The what?
My father designed the resurrection pods
where Neo and Trinity were imprisoned.
[Niobe] I'm sorry.
You knew what happened to him?
You knew that he and Trinity
both were alive,
and you didn't tell me?
There were times
I doubted my decision, Niobe.
But Io needed you.
This city needed to be built
for your people as well as mine.
If I would have told you everything,
you would have had
a very difficult choice to make.
My friends
let me make my own choices.
If it was a mistake,
you have my deepest apologies.
Why are you here now?
Neo's escape
has destabilized the Matrix.
The Anomaleum draws its current
from Trinity alone now.
A fail-safe has been triggered to reset
the Matrix back to the previous version.
But The Analyst halted the reset.
He's convinced the authorities
that you will soon return voluntarily.
And why would he say that?
Because if I don't go back,
he'll kill Trinity.
Faced with returning to your pod
or enduring Trinity's death again.
What would you choose, Neo?
I'll go back.
Well, The Analyst knows you well,
but that knowledge
has made him incautious.
After you escaped,
he should have accepted his losses
and devacuated Trinity.
But that would have prevented
this extraordinary opportunity
that now exists before us.
A few hours ago,
no one would have been able
to convince me
that I would be standing here,
trying to explain a mission
as crazy as this one.
What are you doing?
- Volunteering.
- Oh, no.
You are the one captain
that I am ordering to go.
Now you don't have to order me,
General, 'cause I'm volunteering.
I need two more.
Are you out of your minds?
You don't even know what it is.
General, we know you.
If you say this is important,
none of us is choosing to stay home.
Thank you.
Knuckle up and good luck.
[dramatic music playing]
[Kujaku chittering]
[Sati] Trinity is held in the Anomaleum,
which is in this transmission tower.
The passages used to rescue Neo
are now sealed
and a legion of Sentinels
patrols the tower.
So stealth will be paramount.
As long as we raise no alarms,
this first part of the mission
should be the easiest.
You mean crossing the Fetus Fields,
sneaking across an entire power plant,
climbing a two-kilometer tower
guarded by thousands of Sentinels?
That's the easy part?
Exactly so.
Because all we have to do
is convince someone
who does this every day
to take one of us along.
- [electricity crackling]
- [dramatic music continues]
Fifty meters below the Anomaleum
is a stratum of amniotic filters.
Hidden along this edge
is a small hexagonal vent.
This vent feeds the air intake
into the corpuscular modifier,
which oxygenates
the bio-gel used in Neo's pod.
I get it.
The exomorph
slinkies up Neo's old umbilicus.
What could go wrong?
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[straining]
[Sati] Once inside,
Morpheus will use the System Operator
to open the devacuator line
and disengage the macerators.
[machinery clanking]
In order to unplug Trinity's body,
while her mind
still remains connected to the Matrix,
I'm gonna need a second human brain
to implement the bypass.
And since Neo must be with The Analyst,
the only available mind
that's a near-enough match is yours.
Figures.
[tense music playing]
Thanks, Cybebe.
[grunts]
Does Trinity still have to
take the red pill?
Since Kujaku and I are transferring
her consciousness onto the ship,
it's not strictly necessary.
But what matters
is that this is her choice.
Extracting a confused
or an uncertain mind
will, in all probability, kill her.
But even if it is what she wants,
won't The Analyst
just order the Sentinels to stop you?
He will.
But if my plan works, it won't matter.
Why?
Because we'll already be gone.
Somebody thinks this hard about a plan,
there has to be a reason why.
When my father realized
how the Anomaleum was going to be used,
he covertly transferred
the designs to me.
The Analyst discovered his betrayal,
and had my parents purged.
[inhales sharply]
I would have been murdered too
if it wasn't for Kujaku.
Not a day goes by
that I don't grieve them.
I've been praying for this day
for a very long time.
[door unlocks, opens]
We're coming up on broadcast.
I thought you should know
that I'm here because of her.
All I ever wanted
was to be as fearless as Trinity.
But I saw how she reacted in the garage,
and I...
You're wondering if I'm wrong.
What if we're too late?
What if she's not Trinity anymore?
[sighs]
I never believed I was The One.
But she did.
She believed in me.
It's my turn to believe in her.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Sati] This is where it gets tricky.
Have you ever done
an operation like this?
Not yet.
[suspenseful music builds]
Here we go.
[suspenseful music continues]
Welcome home.
All I want is to talk to her.
Do you mean Tiff?
Come back, and you can talk to her
as often as you like.
I mean, handsome Chad
may have something to say about it.
If she tells me this is what she wants,
you win.
Really?
But if she wants me,
then you'll let us go free.
And why would I do something
as stupid as that?
Right now, I'm on a ship full of people
who will unplug me
before they'll let you take me back.
If you want this Matrix,
this is your only chance.
But how do I know
they won't unplug you anyway?
Same way I know
you'll let us walk out of here.
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay.
I like tests.
We'll let Tiff decide.
[electricity crackling]
[Sati breathing heavily]
That's it.
Bypass is ready.
Now what?
We wait.
Doesn't it seem crazy
to come all this way
and leave her here?
We must abide by her decision.
And if she says no,
what happens to Neo?
At this time,
the most important choice of Neo's life
is not his to make.
[slow suspenseful music playing]
I saw this in my dream.
If I was the Oracle,
maybe I could explain it.
The Oracle.
From your game?
It's not a game.
Oh, God.
[Tiffany sighs]
After you left, I went home
and I played it.
I kept thinking,
"Why does this story
feel like a memory?"
There's a part of me
that feels like I have been
waiting my whole life for you.
And that part is like,
"What the hell
took you so long?" [sniffles]
I don't have an easy answer.
Maybe I was afraid of this.
Afraid of what might happen.
Afraid of hurting
the only person I ever loved.
I wish I was who you think I am.
But look at me.
I can't be her.
- [Donnie] Mom!
- [Brandon] Mom! Come on.
- Mom!
- It's Callie.
Is this real?
[Donnie] You have to come with us.
[Brandon] Come on, we gotta go.
Tiff, hey.
Don't know what's going on here,
but I'm glad we found you.
- She got hit by a car.
- I know, it's crazy.
She was chasing after you.
They're casting her arm. We gotta go.
[Chad] Doctor said she's gonna be fine.
[Donnie] You have to come with us
to the hospital.
It's too late.
I understand.
- Tiff, come on, let's go.
- [Donnie] Come on.
What's happening?
Neo was wrong.
[somber music playing]
Tiffany.
Tiffany, you have to come with us.
Tiffany! [echoing]
I wish you would
fucking stop calling me that.
I hate that name.
My name is Trinity
and you better
take your hands off of me.
[Trinity grunting]
Neo!
Trinity!
Oh, shit.
Get her out. Get her out!
[grunts, yells]
Aye-yi-yi, what a mess.
I own that mistake.
Shouldn't have pressed.
Women used to be so easy to control.
You know there's no way
I can let you two go free.
Cannot happen.
So, I guess it's déjà vu all over again.
She dies,
and it's all your fault.
Lies, lies and more lies.
Smith?
What has the world come to
when you can't even trust a program?
- How...
- [gun clatters]
Tom and I have more in common
than you know.
Once he got out, let's just say,
I was free to be me.
[grunts]
- Yeah!
- Trinity?
[tense music playing]
[bell tinkling]
[all grunting]
[Trinity groaning]
[breathes shakily]
You ready?
Yeah.
[Bugs groans, yells]
[bell tinkling]
[cat yowls]
[grunting]
[distorted screaming]
[yells]
- [Sati grunts]
- [screaming]
[screaming]
Oh, no.
Destroy her. Destroy her!
[Neo and Trinity straining]
Stop them.
[both yelling]
[explosion]
You think this is over?
Lockdown. Initiate swarm.
Here, our unexpected alliance ends.
You know the difference between us, Tom?
Anyone could have been you.
Whereas I've always been anyone.
[grunting]
What just happened?
What?
- [alarm blaring]
- Oh, no! Move! Move!
Get the hell out of there.
[tense music playing]
- How bad?
- Like, all the bad.
Yeah, this is bad.
I don't suppose you can still fly?
[grunting]
Yeah, that's not happening.
[ominous music playing]
[all screaming]
Neo! Get on.
[engine revving]
Calliope! Take the wounded!
Everyone else, we stay with them!
- How is she?
- Life signs are good.
Her signal's strong, Captain.
[Kujaku squawks]
Well done, Captain.
Now all we need is a miracle.
[tense music playing]
[siren wailing]
[Neo grunts]
[tires screech]
I hate bots.
- Get us out of here!
- I'm trying!
The lockdown is tracking.
Swarm is everywhere.
Never seen anything like this.
[grunts]
[siren wailing]
[tense music playing]
[engine revving]
Seq, what is that?
What's wrong?
What are you... [screams]
[grunts]
He's turning bots into bombs.
[glass shattering]
[bodies thudding]
[tires screeching]
Shit! [grunts]
Lexy?
[gunfire]
- [tires screeching]
- [tram bell ringing]
Sheperd's in trouble.
[Lexy grunting]
Jack me in.
I can get you in.
I don't know if I can get you out.
- No!
- [tires screeching]
[motorcycle revving]
What are they doing?
Herding them into a kill zone.
[both groaning]
[Neo groaning]
Captain, you gotta hurry.
- [Lexy groaning]
- Hang on, Lex.
[Lexy screaming]
- Lexy!
- [grunting]
[tense music playing]
[SWAT officer] There they are!
[Neo straining]
[all grunting]
Morpheus!
Lex.
- Bugsy.
- Hell yeah!
Seq, where's Neo?
It's bad. They're pinned.
Heading to a roof.
[dramatic music playing]
[Neo grunting]
[Neo yelling, grunts loudly]
[both grunting]
[machine beeping rapidly]
Nodal fibrillation is critical.
She'll die if we don't extract.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
It's so beautiful.
I remember this.
I remember us.
My dream ended here.
We can't go back.
We won't.
[evocative music playing]
Can they make the jump?
[music stops]
[slow evocative music playing]
[grunting]
I'm not doing this.
Are you doing this?
[dramatic music playing]
[helicopter hovering]
Bye.
[soft music playing]
- [bell tinkling]
- [meows]
[crumbling in distance]
[suspenseful music playing]
How dramatic.
"Tiffany"?
[chuckles] It was a private joke.
An amusement, that's all.
An amusement? Hmm.
[flesh tears]
- [softly] Whoa.
- [groaning]
Kind of like that?
[chokes]
[gulps]
Okay. Ow.
If you hated the name so much,
why did you heel
like a good little bitch so long?
- [Trinity grunts]
- [blade slices]
[body thuds]
Yeah. Definitely asked for that.
- [snaps fingers]
- [The Analyst groaning]
[shudders] Can't you control her?
[groaning]
That was for using children.
We have a few questions.
- You tried to activate the fail-safe.
- The Suits tried.
Obviously, without control
of your source code,
I knew that was impossible.
So, why haven't the Suits purged you?
Because I know the system.
I know human beings.
And I know you.
[bones crack, sighs]
Right now, you're feeling good
about what you've done.
You should. It was a victory. Bravo.
Now what?
You've come here
to negotiate some kind of deal?
You think you hold all the cards
because you can do
whatever you want in this world.
I say, go for it.
Remake it. Knock yourselves out.
Paint the sky with rainbows.
But here's the thing.
The sheeple aren't going anywhere.
They like my world.
They don't want this sentimentality.
They don't want freedom or empowerment.
They want to be controlled.
They crave the comfort of certainty.
And that means you two,
back in your pods,
unconscious and alone, just like them.
[both chuckle]
We're not here to negotiate anything.
We were on our way to remake your world.
Change a few things.
I kind of like the
"paint the sky with rainbows" idea.
Just remind people
what a free mind can do.
I forgot. It's easy to forget.
- He makes it easy.
- That, he does.
Something he should think about.
Before we got started,
we decided to stop by to say thank you.
You gave us something
we never thought we could have.
And what is that?
Another chance.
[punk rock music playing]
Face reality, people. Movies are dead.
Games are dead.
Narrative? Dead.
Media is nothing
but neuro-trigger response
and viral conditioning.
Wait, what are you two talking about?
Cat videos.
What we need is a series of videos
that we call "The Catrix."