Barry got into a fight
Guess I wasn't fast enough
It's better to have a good heart
than fast legs
When I was eleven my mom was murdered
I saw what looked like a ball of lightning
Inside the lighting there was a man
He killed my mom
Mom? Dad?
- Sorry...sorry
- You can't keep docking work so you can go off
chasing down these urban legends Barry
- Everyone you work with thinks you're a wierdo
- You gotta get yourself a girlfriend
I spent my whole life searching for the impossible,
never imagining that I would...become The Impossible
- He's hit by lightning
- How is he still alive?
- he's codeing
- Charge it 200, Clear!
- Oh my God
- Where am I?
- We're at S.T.A.R. Labs
- I need you to urinate in this
Why? What is happening?
What is going on?
you're struck by lightning, dude
Lightning gave me abbs?
- You were in a coma
- for how long?
Nine months
Welcome back Mr. Alan
We have a lot to discuss
I watched you die Barry
You kept dying, your heart kept stoping
- It's still beating
- It feels really fast
So you thought the world was slowing down. You were going so fast,
it only looked like everyone else was standing still
- There is so much that we don't understand
- What's happening to me?
You had a distilled radiaous fracture.
It's healed in three hours
- How is that even possible
- We don't know
How does it fit?
It's a little snug
You don't really beleave you can run that fast, do you?
We've been searching for other meta-humans like yourself
The sky went black and then, boom!
Outside was inside
Clint Mardon, he's a Bank robber
I think he can control the weather
- What really happened that night?
- Dimentional barrier raptured unleashing unknown energies into our world
- Anti-matter dark energy, X elements...
- Those are all theoretical
And how theoretical are you?
I've been thinking too small
they're still out there
We have to stop them
You're not a hero
You're just a young man who was struck by lightning
Mardon!
This just keeps getting cooler
The Meta-humans have been busy, but I need your help
to catch Mardon and anyone else out there like him
- But I can't do it without you
- I have something that might help
It's made of a reinforced tri-polimer
It's heat and abrasive resistant
What if I'm not a hero?
What if I'm just some guy who was struck by lightning?
I don't think that bolt of lightning struck you Barry
I think It chose you
Because you can inspire people
watching over your city like a guardian angel
Making a difference
Saving people in a flash
It's time to think big
- I'll run around him in the opposite direction
- You'll die
- You're not faster than a bullet
- Run Barry, Run
What happened here?
Just like everyday kinda badguy shootout
My name is Barry Alan
And I'm the fastest man alive
A friend recently gave me the idea for a new name
And something tells me it's gonna catch on
Take your own advice
Wear a mask
Cool
"Subtitle created by sunnyrocks786"