Charlie.
Sam.
Come here.
- Where you been?
- Where I been? I've been getting dinner.
Buddy, got any change?
Thanks.
- It sounded like it came from here.
- Yeah, but I don't see anything.
Sure sounded like a scream.
Look out!
Move, Sam! Sam, move.
Charlie!
Jack?
Charlie.
Charlie, what are you doing?
Don't touch him.
Oh, my God. It's Jack.
It's up here!
Right here! Right here.
- Right over here.
- Yeah, come on.
Come on.
- What...?
- He was right here.
He was right here five minutes ago.
Sure he was, pal.
- Hey, buddy.
- Forget about it, man.
Forget about it.
- Sam, he was right here five minutes ago.
- I know.
Good night, guys.
Barry.
Barry Allen.
Father Michael.
- A little far from your parish, aren't you?
- There's been trouble on the street.
I've been waiting to speak to your
Lieutenant Garfield for two hours.
Garfield.
You'd have an easier time with the pope.
Look, if you're on your way out,
I won't keep you.
No, it's all right. What's the problem?
Several homeless people in my
parish have been disappearing.
It's very strange,
and folks are starting to get scared.
Let's talk to the lieutenant.
Father, I wanna help, okay?
But you know what these people are like:
No IDs, phony names.
They come, they go.
That's not exactly disappearing.
If you could just assign a couple
extra patrolmen to the area who could...
I can't put more patrolmen
on the skid-row detail unless...
...and forgive me for being blunt,
some bodies turn up.
If you'll excuse me, Father,
I need to speak with Officer Allen.
Thank you for your time.
Allen, look, so the preacher
was a friend of your brother's, fine.
I'm a church-going man myself.
But you can't start an investigation
based on rumor.
- So you're not gonna do anything.
- It's a question of manpower.
I've got budgetorial problems.
I know you mean well,
but stick to your test tubes.
Sure.
Garfield...
...you haven't been in church
since you were baptized.
The human race stands at the doorway
of a brave new world.
Through genetic engineering...
...humanity will soon be able...
...to redesign itself...
...of altering its own evolution.
We can remove the causes
of birth defects...
...reduce or eliminate the aging process.
Expand our minds and senses.
- Sorry. Sorry. Excuse me.
- Our only limits...
...are our own fears and misconceptions.
- Sorry.
Hey, easy.
- Hey, come on.
- For 2 million years...
...we have lived at the whim of nature.
- Sorry.
- I got here as fast as I could.
- So I see.
You look great.
What? Oh, sorry.
Today, we hold that future
in our own hands.
Tina.
Hello.
Carl, meet a very good friend of mine,
Barry Allen.
- Barry, Carl Tanner.
- How do you do?
Hi, how are you?
Well, how long has it been?
When was the last time I saw you?
The UN science conference
in New York, two years ago.
Carl and my husband and I
were all friends in college.
Rivals, you mean. David and I
were both in love with Tina.
- Oh, Carl.
- Oh, we were. It's true.
- I'm really glad you could make it tonight.
- So am I.
So, Carl,
you're here on a lecture tour, huh?
On a research grant at the university...
...which will put me in town
for about a year.
How's the work going?
Fine. It's pretty technical, and usually
most people wouldn't understand it.
Well, I'm up on my recombinant DNA
and gene splicing.
I'm afraid it goes a bit beyond that, Barry.
Try me.
Are you familiar with the work of Rosenblat
and Viskovich on genetic reorganization?
Or Petrolo's research
on radical mutation?
Well, of course the real groundbreaking's
going on in Amsterdam.
Van Deckrett and Sheinberg.
Van Deckrett?
Aren't they those TV lawyers?
Try any case for $49.95.
Sorry.
And I also apologize
for getting carried away.
It's just that I never get a chance to talk
with someone who shares my work.
Really, Carl, your lecture
was very interesting.
The end of disease, birth defects,
reversal of the aging process...
...does raise some very interesting
moral questions, though, don't you think?
Well, it's not my responsibility to be
the conscience of the human race.
- I'm only a scientist.
- I disagree.
I think we're all responsible.
I'm afraid I do have a very early
appointment tomorrow morning.
- Well, let me take you home then.
- Oh, all right.
- Is that okay, Barry?
- Yeah.
Good night.
Carl, I think you should be
careful with your work.
Why?
Well, David was working on genetic
research too, and it killed him.
I know about David.
Believe me, that will not happen to me.
Spare change?
I ain't had nothing to eat
since yesterday.
- Twenty dollars? Thank you. Thank you.
- That's fine.
That was nice.
He was hungry.
Whenever I see a wasted human life,
it makes me angry somehow.
How can you know that his life
is wasted?
You can't make that judgment.
You're right.
Well, here we are.
May I ask you something?
- Of course.
- Lf I hadn't gone to Tokyo that summer...
...leaving you alone with David,
you think we would've had a chance?
Oh, Carl, I don't know.
That was a long time ago.
Doesn't seem like it.
You still have the same effect on me.
Tina.
It's mail call, soldier.
And may I divert your attention
to this item in particular.
It's from Iris.
Yep, she says Paris is amazing.
Her canvasses are selling,
and she just found an apartment.
Anything else you'd like to tell me
about my life?
Look, somebody ought to.
Look, man, she's not coming back.
Yeah, I know.
Then you should forget about Iris...
...and move on.
Last night you and Tina went out, right?
What was it, a lecture or something?
Well, that's a little dry for my taste,
but it's a start.
- So?
- So...
...the guy giving the speech was intelligent,
good-looking, charismatic...
- Wait. You're losing me here.
- An old romance of Tina's.
Well, that's okay. Just ask her out again.
This time, just try something a little more...
You know, like a foreign film,
or maybe a picnic...
Julio, Tina and I are friends,
all right?
- Just friends.
- Okay. I'm just trying to help, okay?
What's going on down there?
Hey, yo!
We want some justice here!
Hey, listen. If people were dying
in your neighborhood, okay...
...you would have stopped it by now.
- Look, everybody, be cool.
We just came to talk.
We don't want any trouble. Please!
Please!
This isn't a town meeting.
- You people disperse now.
- We want justice!
- Let me talk to them.
- What are you, king of the hobos?
Push them back, boys!
- Drop that weapon!
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Don't be foolish, Mickey.
- Put the gun down.
- But they don't listen, Father.
- I gotta make them listen!
- This is not the way.
But what about Jack
and Bill and Wesley?
They're gone. They're dead!
- Get him!
- Grab him!
Get him down on the floor!
Get these people out of here.
- Get them out of here!
- Lieutenant Garfield, please.
Let him go. I beg you, don't hurt him.
He didn't know what he was doing.
Hey, let him go!
- Let him go!
- All right, I'll release him...
...but you get these people out of here,
or I'll slap their butts in jail.
Let him go!
A jail cell's about the only place
these folks would be safe.
Lieutenant. You mind if I take the priest,
maybe a couple of the men up to the lab...
...see if I can help them out?
Suit yourself, Barry.
Nice work, Chaney.
This may be the only opportunity we get.
Sam, Charlie, I want you to tell Julio
and Barry what you told me.
Yeah, okay.
It's like this:
Somebody's killing street people,
and making them disappear.
Are you sure they're dead?
We seen it. We found a dead body
a couple of nights ago.
- This was a guy we knew.
- Yeah.
Only he was all messed up.
It was like...
Like his face had turned to putty
or something.
- You mean he was beaten?
- No, man.
No, he wasn't human.
We called the cops, but by the time
they showed up, there wasn't any body.
Tell them the other stuff.
There's talk about...
...somebody prowling around at night,
offering people money...
...and sticking them with needles.
- Needles. You mean drugs?
I don't know.
Maybe I better come down
to the neighborhood, check it out myself.
Come down to 4th and Willow.
You'll find us. We should be going.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Charlie.
You know, I keep getting this feeling
that we've met before.
We don't hang around
with the same crowd.
Oh, you.
Yeah.
I brought you some groceries.
Follow me.
Why don't you pass those around, Sid.
- You live here?
- Yeah. The Ritz was all booked up.
Hey, listen, if you think
I'm gonna lie down and kiss your feet...
...just because you came down here,
you can forget it.
Hey, I'm just trying to help out.
Hey, look around, pal.
We need a lot more than help around here.
We need an act of God.
Charlie...
...where you from?
Different places.
Are you sure we haven't met before?
I don't know, maybe we have.
Maybe we haven't.
I'm kind of dwelling on where
to locate breakfast, you know?
Just stay away from me!
I don't want nothing to do with you.
Stay away!
No!
Hey, I know you.
No! No.
No! Please, no!
It hurts!
It hurts...
No!
- Did you hear that?
- No, not again.
It hurts!
Help me...
Moore, his face was all twisted and
distorted. I've never seen anything like it.
Are you sure we're talking
about the same guy?
Yeah, he was found in an alley
on skid row last night, right?
Well, that's the guy, all right.
Only...
...he looks okay to me.
For a corpse.
I swear,
he did not look like this last night.
What did he die of?
Heart failure, pure and simple.
I need a blood sample.
- I'll send it up to your lab.
- Thanks.
- Father Michael.
- Barry.
The police asked us
to identify Sam's body.
Thanks for all your help.
I thought we were going
out to lunch.
Your disappearance left me
at the mercy of the vending machine.
Sorry. I went home to get this.
- What is that?
- It's a micro-rito.
You put that in your mouth, man?
Here, look at this.
- All right, man.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Allen.
No, that's not why I brought this.
That's a bad helmet, man.
You're talking about hair?
Give me that.
- Look at that shot of you.
- Yeah, yeah. Look at this picture.
Charles Wright.
- That's our guy. Charlie.
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
I wanted a second opinion.
- Did you know him?
- Yeah.
He just looks a lot older.
- Guess it's that life on the streets.
- I guess.
I got that blood sample from the coroner.
Run every test you can think of.
I need the results ASAP.
- What am I supposed to look for?
- I don't know.
Something weird. I gotta go downtown.
I'll see you later.
I just don't understand
how he could end up like this.
I don't know Charlie that well,
but the stories aren't all that different.
You get caught in a downward spiral.
You lose your job, can't make your rent,
and suddenly, you're on the street.
I feel like I should do something.
What Charlie needs is a job
and a place to live.
What are you? Are you nuts? I don't know
anything about science and computers.
No, you don't need to.
It's a night watchman's job.
Charlie, I spoke to a friend of mine.
She works there. It's already set up.
- I don't know, man...
- There's a room with a bed and a hot plate.
Yeah, right.
What?
All I did was offer you a job.
I'm not a charity case.
I've got my pride.
Well, maybe too much pride.
Look, I know you know who I am.
Just quit trying to ease your conscience.
Look, we were friends in school.
That's all.
No, we weren't friends.
We hardly knew each other.
- We know each other now.
- So what?
So what? So...
...give it a try.
- Look, I haven't had a job in years, okay?
- What if I screw up?
- They'll fire you.
Come on, Charlie...
...you made it on the street.
You'll make it there.
I like it. Very chic.
Well, I guess I better get those
employment papers signed.
Hey, Barry.
Thanks.
I hope it works out.
Yeah.
Now, let's you and me go
get something to eat.
There's a great Japanese place
right around the corner, just opened up.
I'd love to,
but I've asked Carl to dinner.
Really.
That's terrific.
Yes, it is.
Since I came to town, I've been hearing
a lot of rumors about this Flash.
I suppose it's sort of our version
of the Loch Ness Monster.
Well, some of the things
they're saying are pretty wild.
A man so fast, he's nearly invisible.
- You think that's possible?
- Of course not.
It's probably the invention
of a clever newsman out to make copy.
You're probably right.
This really is a wonderful house.
It was a complete wreck
when we found it.
David and I rebuilt it bit by bit.
You know,
sometimes when I come home at night...
...I expect to find him pounding nails into
the banister or cursing about split varnish.
I looked up one of David's old papers
in a science journal yesterday.
It's funny how close
our lines of research were.
Whatever happened to his notes
on genetic reorganization?
Well, I have them at the lab.
- Why?
- Well, I'd love to see them.
I'd prefer if you didn't, Carl.
I am so close right now.
So close to something important
with my work.
There may be something in David's papers
that would help isolate the flaw in my data.
I can't.
David's research killed him.
Look, I'd rather not talk
about this anymore.
Fine, then we won't.
And I apologize if I've upset you.
It's okay.
It's getting rather chilly.
Let's go inside for dessert.
Tina, you forgot your wine.
Every time I ran the DNA tests
on those blood samples you gave me...
...they came out different.
- That's not possible.
Take a look yourself.
- We have to run them again, that's all.
- I ran the test four times.
There's something funny
with that sample.
The problem is we don't have the kind
of equipment to find out what's going on.
Star Labs does.
Tina.
Carl?
I think you've been working way too hard
in that lab of yours.
Did I fall asleep?
I'm so sorry.
I only had one glass of wine.
Tina, you know you never could drink.
Listen, I'm afraid I have to go.
Yeah?
Charlie, it's Barry.
Listen, don't worry, I haven't quit yet.
That's not why I'm calling.
Listen, is Tina there by any chance?
- Tried her at home, there's no answer.
- No. Afraid not.
She blew out of here hours ago.
Hold it.
The security panel just lit up.
Looks like something's going on in Lab 7.
I better call you back.
Charlie?
He'll be all right, Barry. But another moment
in that vacuum chamber...
- Anything missing here?
- Nothing obvious.
I can't imagine what anyone
would want in here.
All I was trying to do was help him out,
and I nearly get him killed.
It's not your fault, Barry.
Barry. Barry, wait.
It's so simple.
How could I have missed it?
I think whoever broke into the lab was
looking for David's research notebooks...
...on genetic engineering.
- You know who it is.
- I'm not sure.
Come on, Tina.
- It's Carl Tanner.
- I can't believe that.
Well, look at the evidence.
His arrival in town coincides
with the skid-row disappearances.
Julio tested one of the bodies. The blood
stream was spiked with mutating cells.
What do you think?
You can't protect him
just because you're in love with him.
I am not protecting him. And since when
did you become an expert on my love life?
He's using you.
You sound almost glad
that Carl might be the killer.
- That's ridiculous.
- Is it?
- Aren't you just a little bit jealous?
- No.
- Let's just forget this, okay?
- Oh, forget it, huh?
Aren't you being a little childish?
Childish? I'm not the one running around
trying to save the world.
You know, if that's how you feel,
maybe we should just...
...dissolve this little partnership.
- Yeah, maybe we should.
This thing could be spreading rabies
all over town, Murph.
We just gotta hold it
until the animal control gets here.
I don't know about you,
but I smell a big promotion here.
You think we can handle this ourselves?
Maybe we should call the SWAT team.
Rabid dog.
Well, here we are. Where is it?
- Here, poochie. Here, boy.
- Here, poochie.
- Here, poochie, poochie.
Oh, my God. Did you see that?
Did I see it? That ain't no mutt.
That's... That's Dogzilla.
Get the shotgun. I'm gonna follow it.
- Follow it? What for?
- Just get the shotgun, and call for backup.
Bellows, be careful, man.
Unit 24. Unit 24.
We got a beast the size of Guam out here.
Some kind of wild animal.
Corner of Gardner and Fox.
We need a backup.
Bellows!
- You all right?
- Yes.
The Flash just saved my neck.
The Flash?
- The Flash?
- Murph! I got your call on the radio.
- Are you guys all right?
- Hey, look at this.
I just got one question, guys.
- What's that, Murph?
- Who's gonna write up this report?
- There. You see?
- You're right.
I can see the cells mutating.
I've never seen anything like it.
- I have.
- Where?
Right here.
My husband created them.
It was the research he was working on
before he died.
I'm sorry, Barry. You were right.
Carl used me.
It's worse than that, Tina.
He's been experimenting
on homeless people.
I'm sorry, I've got to stop him.
I'll be waiting here.
It's all over, Tanner.
What are you?
Some kind of government experiment?
- Where do you come from?
- It's time to turn yourself in to the police.
No! No.
I'm so close. No! No!
Hydrazine.
It's extremely unstable.
Now, you grab me...
...and they'll peel us both off the ceiling.
Let's see how fast you really are.
There's no way out, Tanner.
- No!
- Hang on!
Murph.
Murph, are you all right?
I'm upside down.
Carl.
I can't go back to the university.
I need your lab.
They don't understand
how important my work is.
If they catch me,
then it's all for nothing.
You understand. I know you do.
You murdered people. Innocent people.
It had to be done, Tina.
But how could you use
human beings as guinea pigs?
Their lives are worthless, I know.
My... My parents were just like them.
My real parents.
They lived in a tenement in filth.
- But I thought you...
- Oh, the privileged childhood? The...
The big house on the coast?
A lie.
An invention to cover my shame.
They should all be cleaned off the streets.
Washed away like dirt.
The formula has to be ionized.
I learned that in David's notes.
Carl, don't. I can't let you do this.
What do you think?
Carl.
Carl, for God's sake, listen to me. Please.
You don't know what you're doing.
And if you care about me...
...which I believe you did once...
...and if you were ever a friend of David's,
please, I'm begging you, stop.
Because this killed him.
And it will kill you too.
You don't understand.
But you will.
No!
You're really grossing me out, Tanner.
Barry.
- Where are you going?
- I've got to stop him.
But you're hurt. He'll kill you.
- Don't go near. Don't go near.
- Don't touch him.
Stand back.
Carl?
Leave me alone.
Don't come near me.
[ENGLISH]
www.tvsubtitles.net