Hasta mañana, Stan.
Have a good one.
[faint crackling]
Donna?
[screaming]
[suspenseful music]
If you're trying to scare me,
it won't work.
I told you I ain't paying you
a damn cent more.
♪
[Loosely Tight's
"Through Thick N' Thin" plays]
♪ Whoa!
♪
Come on, man.
That's enough.
♪
♪ Well, I go where I want,
and I go where I need ♪
[growls]
[screaming]
[heroic music]
[electricity crackling]
♪
[sighs]
Ooh!
Iced java...thank you, baby.
Hey, I was thinking
that we could get
an early dinner
reservation tonight.
Sure.
[pensive music]
Actually, um, you know what?
Why don't we, um, stay in,
have a quiet night,
just the two of us?
That feels better.
Thank you. I'm okay.
You know, I gotta get
used to it eventually.
It's just another day.
I can clear my schedule.
I'm fine, really.
Besides, things are--
things are busy at CCC.
You need to be there.
[phone dings]
And I need to get to work.
I'm just a phone call away.
I know.
[electricity crackles]
[sighs]
Is it that bad?
Huh? Sorry.
That fire just kind of
weirds me out is all.
[clears throat] The vic's
name is Stanley Mullen.
Uh, he's the manager
of this local watering hole.
It's weird.
The body's burnt through,
but the ground
underneath isn't even charred.
Yeah, this was
definitely a meta attack.
Dark matter levels
are off the charts.
Well, whoever that is,
they produce fire
that ignores the laws
of physics.
Oh man, you know,
this is giving me, like,
"Goodbye, Armageddon,
but hello, Dante's Inferno"
type of a vibe.
- Morning, Allen.
- Morning.
Runk.
Find anything that can
help us piece this together?
Uh, no. Not yet.
Were there any witnesses?
Uh, the bartender, Donna
Winters, didn't see the crime.
But she said our victim got
into a pretty
nasty argument last night
with a recently
paroled ex-convict.
Apparently,
the guy had a bad temper.
Oh, and he was wearing
a L.I.P.S. concert T-shirt.
You know, as in the rock band.
I was gonna ask him some
follow-up questions.
Would it be okay if I showed
her a picture of someone
who could be our suspect?
- Sure.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Donna,
this is CSI Barry Allen
and CCPD consultant
Chester Runk.
Ms. Winters, the person you
saw arguing with the victim,
was this him?
That's him. That's the guy.
Jaco Birch.
I'll put out an APB.
This way, ma'am.
The Hotness did this?
I thought
it was all about the moolah,
not cold-blooded murder.
Plus, how did he kill someone
without burning
half the place down?
Looks like we're not the only
ones who leveled up this year.
♪
[distant police sirens]
Here you go, boss lady.
This is every suggestion
the bullpen brainstormed
for who should be our
first CC Citizen of the Week.
Nice work.
Only,
this is every suggestion...
except the winning one.
[apprehensive music]
- Rosie Levin.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, boss,
I don't think launching
our first
profile section on some
shallow social media influencer
is the way to go.
I just thought we were supposed
to be the voice of the people.
I hear you.
But Rosie Levin is who
the people are interested in.
500,000 of them, to be exact,
and if we could bring
those eyeballs to CCC,
then, hopefully, people will
read the stories that matter.
♪
Is there something
that you wanna tell me?
Yeah. Okay, fine.
Taylor brought this to me
earlier, and I told her
it wasn't right for us,
and she went behind my back.
She believed in the story,
and she followed protocol
and made an appeal
to the editor-in-chief,
and I approved it.
Is that a problem?
Yes!
I mean, no.
I just mean if the bullpen
knows they can come to you
when I say no...
my word means nothing.
[sighs]
Look, you're still their boss.
But I'm also yours,
and that means that sometimes
we are going to disagree
on the stories that we tell.
It's part of the process.
Yeah, you're right.
Of course, I--
Actually, you know what?
Why don't you both
interview Rosie?
You want Taylor and me
to work together?
You're my supervising editor.
Go supervise.
Plus, opposing perspectives
make for better stories.
And keep an open mind.
I mean, you might be surprised
at what the two of you
can do together.
Yeah. You got it.
[sighs]
♪
Whoa, whoa.
Easy with the guitars, roadies.
You're unloading the gilded
weapons of true rock gods.
Come on!
You gotta trust your old man,
Harold!
Watching a L.I.P.S. concert's
gonna blow your freakin' mind.
Yeah. Whatever, dude.
Hey, you know I'm sorry
I couldn't land
the backstage passes
I promised, all right?
I kind of ran into a little
bit of a cash flow issue.
You bribed me here with stuff
you couldn't even get, Jaco?
You're even more
lame than usual.
[chuckling] I know, right?
But, uh, hey, look,
maybe after the show,
we could grab some food, huh?
I could tell you some stories
about these crazy things
these bands
I'm working with get into.
You aren't with the bands, Jaco.
You're arena security.
Anyone could do that.
I'm gonna go for a walk.
♪
But--but Harold...
[sirens wailing]
[tires squeal]
Whoa.
[tense music]
♪
Jaco Birch.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Stanley Mullen.
Nah,
I think you got the wrong guy.
What's going on?
Take him somewhere safe.
Hey.
Let go of me, jerk.
Hey, hey, hey!
Get your hands off my son!
Calm down, and put
your hands behind your back.
Nobody's taking
my kid away from me.
Never again!
[steam hissing]
Thanks, Flash.
We got it from here.
Harold, I'm innocent.
I swear.
I'm innocent!
Please believe me.
Flash! You gotta help me.
Please, I didn't do anything.
Please, I can't lose my son!
Please!
I didn't do it.
I swear to God
I didn't do this.
- [yelling] Where's mom?
- What's gonna happen
to my son?
- Dad!
- Barry!
Harold, I didn't do anything.
I swear!
I swear. Please.
Please believe me, please!
♪
[dramatic music]
Okay, I gotta be honest.
Uh, based on this
police report,
I'd advise Mr. Birch here
to start thinking
about a plea bargain.
[sighs]
I'm guessing
you feel differently.
I just want to make sure
they got the right guy.
Well, it seems like they do.
He had an argument
with the victim
hours before he was killed.
He's got no alibi.
The crime matches his powers,
and the guy is an ex-con.
Who was released early
for good behavior.
You know, Korber and those
other officers could've been
killed, too,
if you hadn't intervened.
I know--I--
I know how it looks for Birch,
but there isn't any hard
evidence that he's guilty.
And last night,
he supposedly killed a man
and then instead of laying low,
he went back
to work this morning?
As a security guard
of all things?
It's just--it doesn't add up.
Yeah.
Stranger things have happened.
I know, look, I-I've...
I've worked
hundreds of cases like this,
and I'm telling you,
something about this just--
it doesn't feel right to me.
Okay, okay, but you know that
Birch had motive
and opportunity
to commit this murder.
You didn't see the look
on his face
when they took him
from his son.
He was...
he was begging for me
to believe that he's innocent.
And you do?
I'm not sure yet.
Look, would you--would you be
willing to meet with him
to get a read on his emotions?
[sighs]
Yes, of course,
I'll meet with him.
Guilty or not, everyone
deserves proper representation.
But Barry...
using my powers
to read a client...
[stammers] It's an ethical line
that I can't cross.
Yeah, of course.
I'm sorry. I--
I just don't wanna see
someone go to prison
for a murder
they might not have committed.
♪
So Rosie, dropping out
of Cornell to become
a social media influencer
took guts.
What inspired you
to make such a bold decision?
Let's just say
institutionalized learning
felt like a total prison.
Ugh. Mm-hmm.
Trust me. It's not.
[chuckles]
What my supervisor
means is that our readers
are just so eager to get
to know the real Rosie Levin.
So sorry.
Will you excuse me?
Uh--
[scoffs]
So sorry, I don't know
what her problem is.
Uh, now why don't you take me
through a typical day?
Lydia.
Garcia.
Oh, my God.
It's so good to see you.
How are you?
Look who decided
to come say hi.
I haven't seen you
since Iron Heights.
At least, not in person.
Then again,
your face is plastered
all over that news website.
CCC Media, yeah.
I work there now.
These days,
I'm writing the headlines,
not starring in them.
Must be nice.
So you've been working here
since you got out?
No, um, my first gig was
cleaning out porta potties.
That was fun.
I guess this is kind of
like a promotion for me.
Not that you care.
What's that supposed to mean?
I get it, you're too busy
to help out old friends.
You're mad
because I'm a reporter now?
Look, you got out,
walked into a legit career.
Good for you.
Meanwhile, I busted my butt
to get my GED in prison,
and look where it got me.
This is just temporary.
I mean,
I'm sure you can do better.
Gee, thanks.
I didn't mean it like that.
I know what you meant.
The truth is cleaning floors
is the best job I can get
with a record like mine.
People like you don't see
who I'm trying to be--
only who I was.
It makes it really hard,
you know?
No.
I don't know.
Not yet.
But...
I'd like to try and help you.
How could you
possibly help me?
Let me share
your story with the world.
Trust me.
♪
Before we get into this,
I need to know my son's okay.
The cops won't
tell me anything.
Yeah, Harold is fine.
He's with Social Services,
just until
they can track down his mom.
Good luck with that.
She's been in and out of his
life since he was born.
No telling when
she'll turn up again.
Harold's mother--
she took care of him
while you were
in Iron Heights, right?
Barely.
That's why
I got my act together
and got the hell
out of that place.
Harold, he never forgave me
for abandoning him,
and I don't blame him.
Every second of the four years
I spent in that prison,
it's like
he was serving time too.
And the thing is,
Harold's a good kid.
I don't know what he did
to deserve a father like me.
Okay, why don't you tell me
what happened last night.
Stan and I
got into it at the bar.
I sold him a guitar so I could
buy Harold backstage passes
to the L.I.P.S. concert,
and at the last minute,
Stan decided to only pay me
half of what we agreed on.
Then what happened?
Sure, we argued.
And yeah,
I told him this wasn't over.
But then I went home.
That's the last I saw of Stan.
Is there anybody
that can confirm that?
Anybody--was your son home
with you last night?
No! He was out with friends.
So unless
my vinyl collection can talk...
I got nothin'.
♪
All right.
Listen, I've been around
long enough to know
you're about to tell me
I'm screwed.
But I'm telling you,
I'm innocent.
Jaco, the bartender
places you at the scene
moments before the crime.
Any jury is gonna see that
as more than enough evidence
to convict.
- [yells]
I won't leave my son
without a dad again!
Okay?
You got that?
I wish I had something
better to tell you, Barry.
But Birch just doesn't have
the pieces that you need
to build a strong defense.
And all of the evidence,
it's still pointing
to him as the killer.
I know you didn't use
your abilities in there,
but what does
your gut tell you?
It's telling me that whether
he is actually innocent
or not, he definitely
believes that he is.
But it's not nearly enough.
Yeah, but look,
if there's any chance
he is innocent,
we have to help him.
[door opens]
[suspenseful music]
What's going on?
Jaco Birch just escaped
custody en route to holding.
Was anybody hurt?
Thankfully, no,
but so much for his
"I'm innocent" sob story, huh?
♪
[gasps]
You told the cops
I killed Stan?
Come on, man.
I only told them what I saw.
And when you think about it,
I really didn't see anything.
Hey, you and me are good,
right?
I'm gonna lose my son
because of you--
because of what you said!
Hey man, relax, I--
maybe I didn't see anything!
[whooshing]
- Damn straight,
'cause you're gonna
take it back.
You're gonna
take it all back...
right now!
Wait, man! Please!
[screams]
[computer whirring and beeping]
Nothing
on the satellites yet.
Keep trying.
We have to figure out
where Birch is going
before CCPD does.
That's the only way
we'll have a chance
to prove he's innocent.
I'm sorry,
are we talking about the guy
who just burned his way
through a CCPD
transport convoy?
The fact that Birch ran away
doesn't change the evidence.
There's still nothing directly
tying him to Mullen's death.
Sure, Barry, sure,
but fleeing custody
is not exactly exculpatory,
and I am saying that
as his lawyer.
She's right, Barr.
If Jaco Birch is innocent,
why run?
Why did Frost run
when Chillblaine framed her?
Because unfortunately,
sometimes people don't get
a fair shot
from the justice system.
Yeah, and as a former DA,
I know.
I know that sometimes,
it's true.
They don't.
- Okay, but how do we know
Birch isn't the same hothead
he's always been?
I mean, he'd be halfway
across the country by now.
No, he didn't skip town--
not without his son.
- And you know this how?
- I just do.
Okay.
[computer whirring and beeping]
Uh, guys.
Emergency dispatch is getting
calls about a fire...
right outside O'Shaughnessy's.
What?
Why would Birch go back
to the scene of the crime?
If it's really Birch.
Yeah, I'll find out.
[suspenseful music]
I'll come with you
for backup.
♪
Holy crap.
What kind of fire is this?
I think I know who this is.
Is that the witness
who pinned it on Birch--
the bartender?
You know,
your innocent man, Barr,
is not looking
so innocent anymore.
♪
I thought we were supposed
to be working together on this.
Next time.
Right now, I am in the zone.
Thought I saw
you two were back.
How's the interview go?
Great.
I feel like this story
is exploding out of me.
So everything went well?
[sighs]
Yeah.
Peachy.
Seriously, you're gonna love
what I'm doing here, I promise.
Excuse me.
I just need to get some air.
[chuckles]
All right, well,
I'll let you get back to it.
I'm looking forward to reading
the finished product.
Roger that.
I got back the tomography
reports from the crime lab.
Donna Winters,
the bartender who died?
The thermal lesions on her body
match the marks
on Stan Mullen's body exactly.
Too exactly.
I mean, there's no
pyrokinetic meta
who could replicate burns
like that even if they tried.
I--I--I told you something
about Birch's case
just wasn't adding up.
Barr, we're the ones
who told Birch
that Donna blamed him
for the first murder,
and now Donna is dead.
She's dead!
You have got to see
how that looks, right?
Yeah, but the facts
are still on Birch's side.
Neither crime scene has any
direct evidence
tying him to it.
No DNA,
no fingerprints, no witnesses--
That are still alive.
Barry, you gotta admit
Birch has motive...
and the more emotional he gets,
the stronger his powers are.
Like, you know,
earth-shattering.
Thank goodness
he wasn't in a bad mood today.
That doesn't
make him a killer.
[sighs]
Okay, look, we know that
you're just trying
to do the right thing here.
We do, but Barry, we can't help
but wonder if just maybe
you're not thinking clearly
about this case.
Oh, so that's it.
You've already decided
you're giving up on him.
[stammers] We're just
looking at the facts, man.
So am I.
The two exact fire signatures
makes me think
Birch is not our guy.
Chester, could you please
at least take a look at this,
and see what you can find?
[inquisitive music]
♪
Yeah, okay.
Look, I know you all thought
Birch was guilty
from the start.
No, we haven't.
That's not true.
Each of us have been trying
to help him from the beginning.
But then Birch ran off.
He was just trying
to protect his son.
I mean,
what about other suspects?
There are none.
Both victims worked
at O'Shaughnessy's.
Maybe they owed somebody money
or pissed off the wrong person.
I get Birch is a known
fire meta and an ex-con.
That also makes him
the perfect fall guy.
Okay, now you think
he's being framed?
I'm saying it's possible!
Look,
Birch is the freaking Hotness
and a bad guy.
It feels like he's changed!
Not to us,
and honestly it feels like
you're asking us to believe
in something impossible.
Yeah, I am!
'Cause if anyone had
when I was a kid,
my dad wouldn't
have gone to jail.
♪
Barry...
Barry, honey.
Look, we're sorry.
We--we--we weren't thinking.
Look, here's the deal.
I believe Birch is innocent.
So with or without your help,
I'm gonna do everything
within my power
to clear his name.
[sighs]
[apprehensive music]
That looks familiar.
♪
Been what, seven, eight years
since I've seen this board?
Except the last time,
it was covered with photos
of a different man.
Cecile told me what happened.
The team is worried about you.
No, they don't have to be.
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
They don't know what today is.
I do.
February 1st--Henry's birthday.
♪
I remember
when he was turning 45,
and your mom threw
that surprise party.
The whole block showed up,
and you were
baking cupcakes for weeks,
and when the big night came,
before he could
even take off his coat,
the pager went off.
They actually needed him.
He had to miss his own party.
- And you were disappointed.
Of course.
But you understood.
He was helping save
people's lives, right?
Yeah.
But Henry, he was crushed.
He was worried that
he was missing all these
moments with you and your mom.
But I told him, "Those cupcakes
might be stale now.
But you'll have more birthdays
for both of them."
Oh, there were.
That was the last one
before it happened.
- Barry!
- Dad!
Stay out of the house!
Barry!
Joe, the look in my dad's
eyes that night...
It was the same look in Birch's
eyes when they arrested him.
Look of an innocent man...
desperate
not to lose his son...
Begging someone to believe him.
And you do.
Yeah, I do.
I just keep thinking about
all the time my dad lost.
[sighs]
All the birthdays we spent,
separated by plexiglass.
I can't let Birch
and his son go through that
if he's innocent.
[inhales deeply]
I don't know.
Maybe the team's right.
Maybe I'm making something
out of nothing.
You think maybe I've had
blinders up this whole time?
Maybe.
Or...
You can see
something they can't.
Look, what you went through,
I wouldn't wish on anyone.
But what it did,
was it gave you
the ability to believe
in the underdog
when no one else is willing to.
So...
If your gut tells you...
To not give up on Birch...
Then for Henry's sake, don't.
Not yet.
[cell phone chimes]
[suspenseful music]
♪
So what do you think?
I think the lede is in the
second graph, not the first.
But besides that,
it is a very engaging
and beautifully
written article.
I think it's going to open
a lot of eyes.
Seriously? You like it?
Yes, I do.
But Allegra,
as strong as that article is,
that's not what I assigned you.
I know,
but I have a unique insight
into Lydia, and me
connecting with this story
so much is what's gonna make
it connect with our audience.
Agreed, but I wanted you
to make this special, and
to help support a colleague.
There's some decent writing
in Taylor's article,
but it's all surface.
There's no context.
There's no examination
of Rosie's influence
on young women.
Allegra, you could've
made this story so much better
if you had helped her
like I asked you to do.
Yeah.
Iris, I'm so sorry.
The interview with Rosie
wasn't going anywhere.
So you abandoned it?
I followed my instinct.
I thought that's
what you'd want me to do.
What I want is for you to
learn how to be a supervisor.
That's why I'm trying
to teach you how to mentor her.
Instead,
you did just the opposite.
But...
I have an obligation
to our readers
to publish
the best articles that I can,
and your profile on Lydia...
is amazing.
I think it's gonna start
an important conversation.
So... [sighs]
We're gonna go with it.
But next time, please run any
changes this big by me first.
And another thing:
I want you to talk to Taylor.
You're her immediate boss,
so it's up to you to fix this,
not the other way around.
♪
Chester, what'd you find?
You were right.
Yeah, check this out.
So I cross-referenced
the heat signature
from O'Shaughnessy's
to the one in the alleyway
from the second victim
like you asked.
Guess what I found.
Both signatures produced
an anomalous heat effect
created by non-composites
reacting to hydrogen isotopes--
nuclear fusion.
What you're describing
is cold fusion.
But Birch's powers
come from absorbing heat,
not nuclear fusion.
Meaning...
He's innocent.
Yeah, we get this data to CCPD,
you can clear his name.
Okay, Chester, put everything
you have on a drive.
I need to get this
to Captain Kramer fast.
I need to find Birch.
[suspenseful music]
Let's hope he doesn't do
anything else stupid
before we can clear his name.
♪
Harold, I know this is tough.
But we're gonna find you
a place to stay.
I'm here to make sure
your transition
is as easy as possible, okay?
Whatever.
I'm used to Jaco
being a screwup,
especially
since he got his powers.
♪
I want my son!
Now!
Harold, get out of the car.
[tense music]
Get down on your knees with
your hands above your head.
I'm not letting you
cart my son off
to a bunch of strangers.
Harold!
Birch, I said get down.
[yelling]
Why won't you leave me alone?
CCPD scanners have Birch
at Hastings Avenue
and Nicola Lane.
Oh, man.
Satellites just picked up
a city vehicle
at the exact same spot.
It's a social services SUV.
He's trying to get his son.
Barry, CCPD still doesn't
know that Birch is innocent.
If he tries to take his kid
by force--
We have to stop him.
Before he does something
he'll regret.
Birch, listen to me.
No, you listen.
I just want my son.
Now get out of my way.
♪
[whispering] Wait, wait.
No, wait. Wait.
Harold, stay back.
She's right, son.
It's too dangerous.
I'm not scared of him.
[rumbling]
Look, Harold.
I know how bad this looks.
But I swear,
I'd never hurt anyone.
What's wrong with you?
You get that
you're a total loser, right?
I am.
A total loser.
Have been
since the day I was born.
Thought having powers
would change all that,
but all that did
was make things worse.
And now they turn the only good
thing in my life against me?
My own kid...
[rumbling]
All I wanted
when I got out of Iron Heights
was a clean start,
to get my life together
so we could be a family!
[hard rock music]
♪
- This is your final warning.
- Who cares?
No matter what I do, you'll
always think I'm a killer,
and now you wanna
take my son away forever?
Well, I won't let you!
[heroic music]
[panting]
You can't keep me
from my family, Flash!
No one's taking Harold away.
I know you didn't kill anyone, Birch.
Your lawyer found evidence
to prove you're innocent.
But you have to stop
what you're doing
before anyone gets hurt.
Okay.
All right?
[tense music]
♪
[rumbling]
[car alarms wailing]
Oh, come on.
I'm not doing anything.
It's not what you're doing.
It's what you already did.
[rumbling]
[car alarms wailing]
Officer, get them to safety!
♪
Thanks for the save!
Birch, your heat abilities,
they're connected
to the earth beneath
wherever you're standing.
Uh, yeah, science
is not my strong suit.
But yeah, okay.
I'll buy that for a dollar.
He means emotionally.
Ooh...right.
Chester, can you scan
for thermal activity below us?
Yeah, yeah.
Merry Mack Gibson Jr.
Kay, there's a volcano's
worth of magma
erupting beneath the city's
lower crust.
When Birch was upset, he
must've absorbed so much heat
from the planet's core that
he opened up a lava channel.
Flash, if you can't stop this
in the next 30 seconds,
Central City's
gonna turn into Mount Doom.
♪
Officer, get them back!
Flash,
you gotta do something.
I know this is all my fault.
You and everyone in this city,
my son,
he can't die because of me.
You gotta save him.
No, you have to save him.
Look, I've got an idea.
If it works, there's gonna be
a huge release
of pressure forming beneath us.
When that happens, I need you
to absorb the remaining heat.
I've never done
anything like that before.
You can do this.
I know you can.
Hey, ten seconds.
Time to ride or die, people.
[rumbling]
♪
Let's rock.
[Loosely Tight's
"Through Thick N' Thin" plays]
♪ Whoa!
Where'd he go?
I--I don't know,
but I'm detecting new activity
right under the surface.
50 meters down.
No, no, wait. 90 meters down.
♪ Let me rock
110 meters. 120 meters.
Whoa, hey, Flash is doing
his thing underground, y'all.
So get ready.
♪
Yeah!
♪ Let me rock
♪
Yes!
Yes. Yes!
You don't see that every day.
[heroic music]
Not that I'm complaining,
but how'd you do that?
I phased into the water
table under the city
then released it
directly into the lava channel.
That stopped a meltdown, but
not the massive heat exchange
that was being released--
one I couldn't stop,
but I knew Birch could.
Otherwise, everybody within
a ten block radius--
Would've been fried
like a bananas foster
in the French Quarter.
Mark and I are goin'
to Mardi Gras next year.
Okay.
Wait,
so saving hundreds of lives--
Try thousands.
Saving that many lives
is what I just did?
Yeah.
Looks like you're the father
Harold deserves after all.
You okay?
You used your powers again.
I know.
I know, I--
- To save us.
♪
Thanks, Dad.
I love you.
♪
[sentimental music]
Okay. Okay!
Social Services is
on their way with Harold.
They should be here any minute.
[sighs]
I can't believe
they're actually letting me
have custody of my son.
That evidence
you found saved my ass.
Plus, Harold is almost 18,
and Judge Hankerson let him
decide where he wanted to be.
And you know
with his mom being--
MIA as always?
You and Harold
are getting another chance--
a real one, this time.
It's all because of you two.
And The Flash.
Yeah, but you're the one
who told him
not to give up on me.
I'm just really grateful.
- Oh, yeah.
Thanks. Thank you.
If there's ever anything
I can do for you,
just let me know.
Just be there for Harold.
♪
You okay?
I will be.
Hey there, kiddo.
Hey.
Come on.
Dinner is on me.
We got a lot to catch up on.
♪
Barry,
they are gonna be all right.
I guess the real question is...
are you?
♪
Come to gloat?
No.
Kind of the opposite.
I guess you saw
the first article
for our new profile section.
You mean yours?
Taylor,
I know how this looks,
and... I wanna apologize.
Yes,
Iris loves the Sanchez story,
but we are running your piece
on Rosie Levin next week.
And our audience
deserves to read it.
Thanks.
So tell me--
what did I do to deserve
getting stabbed in the back
by my own supervisor?
Iris assigned you to help me,
not run me over,
which is exactly what you did.
I didn't mean to,
and you're right.
I shouldn't have done that.
I just--I got excited,
and I guess I felt like
Lydia's story was something
our readers needed right now.
And that's how I felt
about my story.
Iris did too, until you called
in a favor with the boss.
Guess you learned that
in prison.
[chuckles]
You're right.
I got lost in a great story--
You stole my byline!
Taylor, we are still
publishing your article.
Because Iris
is a journalist with ethics.
Something you are
clearly lacking.
Fine.
Good to know.
Look.
I messed up.
I said I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
But I am still your supervisor.
So I'm hoping
we can get past this.
Okay?
[tense music]
I'm gonna destroy you.
Yeah?
♪
Shouldn't we be toasting
with champagne?
Mm-mm.
Plain, old light beer.
That was Henry's favorite.
I used to give him hell
about it.
I'd say, "You're a doctor.
You should have better taste,"
and he'd laugh, and he'd say,
"Oh, I'll drink something more
expensive when you buy it."
[laughter]
Do you guys remember
when Henry filled in
on Dad's softball team?
Oh, my gosh.
What a disaster.
What? What happened?
Well, even as a kid,
I knew that
you're not
supposed catch a ball
with your face.
- [laughs]
Oh, no!
No, really?
Yeah, right in the nose.
Good thing, as a doctor,
he was able
to reset it himself.
[laughs]
[sentimental music]
Hey, baby, you okay?
Yeah, no, it's--
it's just nice
to hear everybody
remember him this way.
What do you
remember the most?
Oh, little things mostly.
[laughs]
Um, he never made me
clean my plate at dinner,
even when all
I'd eat were carbs,
like mac and cheese
or those Hawaiian dinner rolls.
Mmm...
I kept asking him to read me
the same bedtime story
over and over.
It was the one about the hippo
who went to school
and made cookies for everyone
and then became their friends.
I can see how ridiculous
that must have been now.
Well, I'm sure he enjoyed it.
Mostly,
I just remembered being loved.
I still miss him.
Every day.
And that is okay.
Yeah.
Well, um, happy birthday, Dad.
♪
So if Birch didn't kill
those two, then who did?
I've checked every
fire-based meta-human in here.
Everyone's either still
at Iron Heights or alibi'd up.
So what do we do now?
I know what Joe would say.
No suspects?
Then shift your focus
to where it matters--
the victims.
But Stan and Donna
were different ages,
races, and genders.
But they both worked
at O'Shaughnessy's.
So the killer's
a disgruntled employee?
Or they were
chosen at random,
and we're still
missing something.
[suspenseful music]
What are you thinkin'?
Chester, the cold fusion data
we pulled off the bodies--
could your program those
variables into the satellites?
Sure.
What am I looking for?
More victims.
If there's a meta
serial killer out there,
we need to find them...
Before somebody else gets hurt.
♪
[heroic music]
Greg, move your head.