'Cause the way you drive is wrong! See?
You really a badass, cowboy, or you just talk like one?
You call that drifting?
That's for selling me a broken iPod!
Not bad.
Hey Han...
Take a look at this.
You have a visitor.
Uncle.
Uncle Kamata, I was just about to go see you.
Have you been well?
Yes.
Here's last week's take.
Business good?
Yes.
Please.
To tell you the truth...
I look over these printouts of yours...
and I don't understand half of what l'm looking at.
lt looks more complicated than it is.
Then how is it even I am able to figure out...
that your partner is stealing from us?
Even if that were true...
lt couldn't have been much, uncle. I would've caught it.
There's an old saying:
For want of a nail...
the horseshoe was lost.
For want of a horseshoe, the steed was lost.
For want of a steed...
the message was not delivered.
For want of an undelivered message...
the war was lost.
I miss your father.
Get in.
l'd like to see Mr. Kamata, please.
Who's your friend?
Nobody.
I can handle this.
I have something which belongs to you, sir.
Don't listen to this gaijin.
Takashi...
after everything you've done, you're giving me orders?
I apologize.
You're free to go.