[TENSE MUSIC]
Almost at the goal line.
[SIGHS]
Look, I know I've been
stable for a few months,
and I'm not due for
another treatment quite yet,
but I appreciate you checking.
Hey, gotta check yourself
before you wreck yourself.
All right.
Well, you're all good now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, it's... it's just that...
um...
lately, I've been forgetting things.
For instance, there was this
dinner at my dad's and I...
Dad? Weren't you just upstairs?
Yeah, and then I went to the
garage because you asked me
to get the files from
the old Scarpulla case.
Remember?
Um.
Yeah, I-I I must've just...
Checked out or something
for a couple of minutes,
and then I have this hazy memory of...
Of a train station.
And for some reason, I
feel like you were there.
You forget we had an
appointment in the books?
You're gonna start moving in
and out of timelines again.
It's news to me 'cause I'd remember
something like that. [LAUGHS]
Yeah, yeah, I know. Of course.
Hey, how does someone catch
a time sickness, anyway?
No idea, but I intend to find out.
Whoa, hold up now.
What is it?
I'm picking up mutations
like ones I've never seen before.
Well, that sounds bad.
Actually, it could mean a lot of things,
might even be a side
effect of my treatments.
Tell you what, I'm gonna
go hit up my Force sibs
to see if they can
help me figure this out.
- What do I tell Barry?
- Nothing.
I don't know what this is
yet, so for now, just chill.
Trust me, all right?
As soon as I find out what's up,
I'll come find you wherever you are.
♪
- [HEROIC MUSIC]
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This case gives dead ends a bad name.
At least no one else has been hurt.
Yet.
Barr, what's wrong?
I just can't shake the feeling
that there's something we missed.
Well, look, I'm gonna
dig into the evidence
you gave me from last
week's crime scene.
All right, thanks. Hey, where's Caitlin?
We need all the help we can get.
Ever since she decided
to go all in with Marcus,
it's open season on
spontaneous getaways.
So one minute, they're
listening to showtunes,
getting all weepy on
the couch, and then next,
they got last minute tickets
to "Dear Evan Hansen" in Metropolis.
Well, good for her, but
where does that leave us?
One step closer to the truth, y'all.
Okay, so I stayed up all night
building this cold fusion
alarm module for our satellites.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
Chester?
- I...
- You all right?
Yeah. Sorry, sorry.
This all-nighter's got me zoning out.
Here's the deal. So we
know that this meta's
fire powers are cryokinetic,
meaning that their power output
would read as extreme cold pockets.
This alarm I just finished building,
it's gonna alert us as soon
as there's any rapid drops
in barometric anomalies
anywhere in the city.
Only downside is, we won't know
where our baddie actually
is until "flame's on."
Or someone else gets burned up.
No, the moment we get a
hit, I'll be fast enough
to get there in time,
and we can end this
before anyone else gets hurt.
♪
Sue Dearbon, loving
the non-catsuit look.
Why the change?
I got restless, so here I am.
Iris?
Hi, you good?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm great.
Yeah, so what brings
you back to Central City?
Oh, well, now that Black Hole's gone
and my parents are in
white collar prison,
I am in charge of revitalizing
the family business.
So I'm just here showing face
at all the business holdings
and reassure everyone personally
that things are gonna be different.
And added bonus, I get to
pop in on my favorite tenants.
Well, we are eternally grateful
for your help in expanding our office.
Hey, you guys are the
ones doing all the work.
All right, I have got
to jet to Coast City.
We own a string of luxury
hotels I have to go inspect.
- Sounds fun.
- No, no. It's boring as hell.
Yeah, but if I'm lucky,
maybe I'll catch a glimpse
of the CCP while I'm there.
Oh, you guys haven't heard.
Apparently there's
been multiple sightings
of someone walking through walls.
It's popping up on socials
as #CoastCityPhantom.
It sounds like a new meta.
I wonder how they got their
powers on the West Coast.
Actually, I have run into
quite a few metas around the world.
Turns out there's
folks all over the place
with latent meta genes.
All it takes is the
right set of circumstances
for their powers to manifest.
Maybe that's what
happened in Coast City?
Yeah, giving them their first meta.
Iris, this could be a great story.
Yeah, you should come with me.
I would love the company.
You don't mind staying in posh,
five-star hotel suites, do you?
I'll go.
- You will?
- Yeah.
Allegra can cover things while I'm gone.
I can?
Yeah, don't you have a
blossoming media empire to run?
Well, I can run things remotely,
and besides, Allegra's right,
I mean, this is a huge scoop,
and if this story pops,
it could lay the groundwork
to a West Coast expansion.
I am sold.
Great. That's that.
- Road trip.
- Oh.
Let's go.
Okay.
[ALARM BLARING]
Is that a cold spot?
Our fire meta just turned
up at 138 South Devon Road.
♪
What the hell?
Flash, did you find them?
Barry, what's happening?
I'm too late.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- Black fire?
- Yeah.
It was like nothing
I've ever encountered.
And it put itself out.
How is that even possible?
I don't know, but I'm telling you, man,
I mean, it was there one
second, the next nothing.
So what else do we know?
The vic's name, Parker DeStefano.
She teaches classes here at the studio.
♪
Hey, are you seeing this?
Holy "Fahrenheit 451."
Okay, we need a way to preserve it.
Maybe we can try using
the micro-catalyzed containment unit?
The what?
Ray Palmer and I designed it together
in collaboration with the foundation
that he named after my dad.
The MCCU preserves the
vaporized integrity of gases,
but it's back at my workshop.
- What's it look like?
- It's like an 8-inch
vacuum-sealed borosilicate canister
with an ionic-fused base and cap.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
That's gonna take some
time to get used to.
Is this it?
Yeah, yeah, that's... yeah. [CHUCKLES]
Okay.
♪
Okay, try to determine
its molecular properties
then reprogram our satellite module.
To detect whatever meta-data I find.
Yeah, then match it
to a city-wide search.
That way, if we're lucky...
We can catch this murderer
before they kill again.
I triangulated the last few
Coast City Phantom sightings
posted to social media,
and all of them occurred downtown.
Wow, you're really
pulling out all the stops.
So how's tricks?
Everything okay at work?
Yeah, better than ever. I
mean, CCC Media is evolving.
How about you and Barry?
You guys still the
couple of the century?
[CHUCKLES]
You say that like it's a bad thing.
- Lady, it is the best thing.
- Agreed.
Uh, yeah, no, Barry is leveling up
and firing on all
cylinders with Team Flash.
And... hold on.
What's with all the prying?
It's nothing. I mean, I get it.
Life's grand, and you're
busy as all get out.
But with all that going on,
you're still really eager
to help this new meta
become the Streak part two.
And Allegra could've handled this story
and taken some of this off your plate.
Is there anything you want to share?
[PHONE CHIRPING]
Oh.
Oh, look at that. We got a hit.
Let's go.
Okay, not them.
♪
Hmm, could be either one.
- We should probably get closer.
- Uh, uh.
Give it a minute.
♪
Yahtzee.
Hi, I'm Iris West-Allen
with "The Central City Citizen" Media.
Never heard of it.
- Fair enough, and this is...
- Her landlord.
Yeah, still not caring.
So if you don't mind.
Okay, well we were hoping
that you could help us
with a story that we're researching.
Not interested.
It's about the Coast City Phantom.
You ever heard of him? Or her.
Look, we don't want to
cause you any trouble, okay?
We really just want to talk to you
and see if there's any
way that we can help you.
- What's your name?
- I'm not telling you that.
- Order for Tinya.
- Oh, Tinya.
Triple espresso,
that's a lot of caffeine for a teen.
Okay, I'm gonna be honest.
When we heard that
there was a possibility
of a meta in Coast City...
- What's a meta?
- People like you with powers.
And what?
You think I'm your next headline?
No, no, it's not like that.
It's just in Central City,
we have experience working with metas.
To do what?
Well, to help others.
Have you heard of the Flash?
Okay, well eight years
ago, I was the reporter
that who helped break his
story and if you let me,
I can help do the same for you.
How'd you guys find me anyway?
Well, metas like you are
made up of dark matter,
and this app helps us find just that.
Really?
♪
Well, good luck finding me now.
[GROANS]
[CHUCKLES] Yeah, that went well.
I've triple checked
the who's who binder.
Nothing on a "Tales From The Crypt" meta
who can conjure up black fire.
With no chemical signatures
to program into our satellites,
we're still flying pretty blind.
All right, keep working the science.
I'm gonna pay Kramer a visit.
Now that she's part of the team,
she needs to know what
we're really dealing with.
Plus, maybe she can
help us find a connection
between all three victims.
Just call me if you find anything.
Yeah...
No problem-o.
Just me and the scary black flame.
Nothing weird about that.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
[SIGHS]
Okay, relax, Chester P. Relax.
You got this.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SCREAMS]
Hey, hey.
There's a fire!
There's a fire. Help!
Help me!
Someone help!
Chuck, Chuck.
[GROANS]
It's okay, it's okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
It's just us.
You were shouting in your sleep.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I just... just a bad dream.
Must've been a doozy.
Are you sure that's it?
I can feel how frightened you still are.
Yeah, no, no, no, I'm...
[CHUCKLES] I'm good, I'm good.
Really, I've just been
working way too much lately.
Maybe I just need
some coffee to power up
the old mental hard drive. [CHUCKLES]
[CLEARS THROAT] Sorry.
♪
Okay, I can feel him struggling.
Anybody else notice
that he's been having
- a hard time lately?
- Yeah, I definitely have.
If something's bothering
him, why wouldn't he say so?
I mean, he's the most
touchy-feely person I know.
It must be super personal then.
To keep us out, Team Flash?
I mean, that's just wrong.
He'll talk to me.
Since your phone's toast,
I'm downloading
Chester's dark matter app.
Only seven hours and nine minutes to go.
Okay, I really need
to upgrade my service.
I can afford it.
No, Sue, we don't
have that kind of time.
I mean, Tinya can walk through walls.
I mean, she could be anywhere.
Well, until this downloads,
we have the rest of the day
to come up with a better idea,
and this looks like the
perfect place to strategize.
Okay, well, we need to
narrow down all the places
that we think that she
might be and search them.
Great, and we can talk about
the real problem while we're doing it.
Come on, Iris, what are
you really doing here?
[SCOFFS]
It's... it's far out, so...
Try me.
Last year, I started feeling...
weird, and so the Still
Force took a look at me
and discovered that I had
contracted a time sickness.
Now, what that means and how
I got it is still a mystery,
but I don't know.
Recently, I feel like
I'm starting to lose time.
Okay, okay. I see why you're freaking.
Yeah, and then this morning,
I checked in with Deon,
and he found something that
he had never seen before.
And even though he told me to
relax while he looks into it,
I mean, I can't help but feeling that
something is really wrong.
And that's why you threw
yourself into this story?
Yeah, I needed a distraction.
Believe me, I understand.
I did the same thing when
I found out that my parents
volunteered to work for Black Hole.
At first, I was so mad I
just looked the other way.
I mean, seriously, I
did everything to avoid
facing the consequences
of their actions.
But I had to stop running
away and face my parents.
And Iris, you have to do the same thing
about this fear around
this time sickness thing.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
[SIGHS] Yeah, but I mean,
what if Deon shows up
tomorrow with bad news?
Yeah, that could happen.
You could also be fine.
Either way, you have to stop running
from the fear of the unknown.
It's... it's a race you can't win.
- What?
- Tinya.
What if I'm not the only one running?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
I think I know where to find her.
Got enough for a second cup?
Yeah, yeah, definitely. [CHUCKLES]
I'm not gonna lie, you
look more stressed now
than you did during the
"Trials of Gyntarri" campaign.
Yeah.
That was a tough one.
Wow.
Even D&D talk isn't gonna perk you up?
I'm sorry. [CHUCKLES]
I'm a little out of it.
I know this new fire meta
case is pretty intense,
and as our resident science guru,
you're in it pretty deep.
I mean, you have to examine victims
and run tests on bodies.
That's a lot of pressure.
I guess what I'm saying
is, you're not alone.
I mean, we're all in this together.
Right?
So if you need to talk
about something, anything...
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪
- It's happening again.
- How'd it get out?
It didn't trust me.
I know you're not really here.
This is just another dream.
No, it's not.
Doesn't S.T.A.R. Labs have
a fire suppression system or something?
The fire's cold fusion.
It doesn't produce carbon dioxide.
Our sensors wouldn't
pick it up as real fire.
Please, please, not like this.
It's here.
♪
I can't put out these flames.
All right, just stay behind me.
♪
I don't get it.
First, Chuck has a dream
about this weird fire,
and then the meta who
created it attacks us?
And why would anyone
want to hurt Chuck anyway?
I don't know, but we're
gonna keep you safe.
- I promise.
- Thanks.
Chester, what about your
barometric detection thingy?
Why didn't it go off?
When I programmed the search parameters,
I used the default
setting that establishes
a tracking grid outside
of S.T.A.R. Labs.
Right. Maybe you should fix that.
Yeah, I just did. I also doubled checked
to make sure that S.T.A.R.
Labs was clear too.
It's like this black fire meta
can appear and disappear at random.
Plus, their fire leaves no trace.
Like a ghost.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪
I gotta get some air.
He's hurting really bad inside.
Can you blame him?
First, two bodies show
up at O'Shaughnessy's...
Then the yoga instructor,
DeStefano, this morning.
Yeah, and now the same
person is hunting Chuck,
a guy who would never hurt anyone.
It doesn't make any sense.
If this meta can get inside
S.T.A.R. Labs undetected,
they could be anywhere.
What if they're controlling
the flames remotely?
I mean, the shape that
we saw in the fire,
it had no face, no identifying marks.
Maybe it was some kind of projection?
I mean, it could explain why you haven't
been able to catch them.
The killer's never actually been
at any of the crime scenes.
But that doesn't explain why
our black fire meta
is going after Chester.
Put S.T.A.R. Labs on lockdown.
Nobody except for me gets in or out
until we figure out what's going on.
Where you going?
If somebody is controlling
the fire remotely,
I'm gonna search the
city until I find them.
Stay on comms.
On it.
♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
She's not here.
How did you get...
I don't know how you found
me, but I'm out of here.
How about you stay?
All right, you do know that
I can walk through walls, right?
Well, we have friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and when I told them that
we had a ghost meta on our
hands, they gave me this.
It's called a molecular
destabilizing matrix.
Apparently all I have to do is
turn it on, and it destabilizes
any folks like you within
a three-block radius.
What do you say we give it a try?
Yeah, I thought you two helped people?
Oh, she does. Me,
it depends on my mood.
So why don't you relax?
Let's hear Iris out.
Why do you even care?
We know that you're
looking for your mother.
It was your backpack.
At Jitters, it looked like
your whole life was jammed inside of it.
I started looking through Coast City's
missing persons database,
and that's when I found out
that you had run away from foster care.
And that your birth mother
worked at that Jitters,
and that this apartment
was her last known address.
Yeah, she's a damn good reporter.
Okay, well then you also know
that my real mom abandoned
me when I was born
and hasn't tried to contact me since.
Not once.
Not to see how I'm doing
or if I even survived, but I did.
And it's been hell recently,
but now that I suddenly
have these new powers,
I have a chance to be somebody.
So you wanted to show
your mom who you've become.
Yeah, because maybe she'll think
that I'm something special.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
And take me back.
Latent meta powers manifested
by intense emotion, check.
Let us help you find her.
♪
It's just a paperweight.
Like I said, Iris is a great reporter
and if there's anyone that
can help you find your mom,
- it's her.
- If you'll trust me.
♪
We're gonna find out
what's behind all this...
And you're gonna be fine.
I'm starting to wonder
if that's still possible.
We've got your back.
Trust me, you're more than
just a part of this team,
you are a part of my life,
and I'm not letting you go anytime soon.
Got it?
Allegra, I...
Never mind.
It's just...
You just a really good friend.
So are you. The best.
Which is why I gotta tell you this.
Okay, that person in the fire.
I know who it was.
And it wasn't some new fire meta.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
It was a ghost.
You seriously think
you're being haunted?
For real?
By my father.
That's who's in the fire.
And I know that because
that's how he died,
but for some reason,
he's... he's come back.
But I was there,
and whatever it was,
it didn't have a face.
It was just a shape.
No, no, no, it was more than that.
I wasn't with my dad when he died.
Okay, but when that fire appeared,
that thing inside of it
made me feel like I was.
Right there on the road where
it happened 24 years ago.
It's was like I could see the wreckage
and feel the heat from
the engine burning.
And I could hear my
dad shouting for help.
But no one came.
Allegra, no one came.
He just... no one came.
He just... he died alone.
I don't know what you saw,
but that wasn't your father.
It couldn't have been.
Yes, it was! It was.
Chuck, you told me what happened
last year when you met.
How much he loved you,
what a great dad he turned
out to be all this time.
Chester,
a good father would not
do something like this.
It had to be. Look, I get...
Allegra, I can feel
it. Okay, I can feel it.
Like I was right there at
the crash site, I can...
You said,
"Quincy P. Runk loved his
son more than anything else."
Which means whatever you
felt or thought you saw,
it was a lie.
Allegra...
I hated him my whole life.
Okay, what if this is
some kind of, like...
Some kind of messed
up afterlife payback?
No.
I don't believe in
ghosts, and neither do you,
which is why we have to figure out
what's really going on.
♪
[ALARM BLARING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
He's... he's back, isn't he?
If so, he's gonna have
to go through me first.
Let's go.
- What's going on?
- We're not sure yet.
We got cold fires on multiple levels,
and it's spreading.
And they're all headed our way.
[ALARM BLARING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
If it's cold fire,
how come it's getting hotter in here?
These flames form in a subzero state,
but they still give off high
levels of kinetic energy.
Which means they can still
burn the hell out of us.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
That was a router junction.
They're in the walls too.
He's after me. This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
Chuck, you need to concentrate.
Okay, we're gonna need
your help to survive this.
Oh, no, no, I can't. I can't.
The fire's already burning through
our structural supports.
Once they're done...
Every volatile resource in
S.T.A.R. Labs will meltdown
and contaminate Central City.
So what do we do?
Chester, look, I know
this is hard right now,
but we need your help to stop this.
That means we need you to
initiate a search protocol.
Look for anything that could
create cold catalyzed reactions.
We'll buy you as much time as we can.
Okay. Okay, I'm on it.
Tracking muon-catalyzed heat signatures.
Barry, the flames are
converging on the speed lab.
I don't know why, but
maybe there's some sort
of epicenter forming there or something?
Let's do this.
♪
- Frost.
- I'm on it.
[GROANS]
Our heat index is off the charts.
Chester, I just felt a
massive wave of despair.
I told you I can't do this.
He thinks he's being haunted by his dad,
and that's the reason
all of this is happening.
[GASPS]
That's not the reason.
Chester... [GASPS]
The despair that I'm sensing,
it's not just from you.
It's like I can feel the
pain of thousands of people,
maybe more.
[SCREAMS] What the hell is this?
- Cecile?
- All right, listen to me.
You guys need to evacuate
while you still can.
No, we're not leaving you behind.
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
- [BOTH YELP]
It's here.
All that pain and sadness.
All that grief.
♪
Dad?
Take my hand.
It's time to come home, Chester.
I'm so sorry I couldn't save you.
Chuck, that's not your dad.
It's true.
Chester, all of the
sadness that I'm feeling,
it's...
it's coming from that thing.
Allegra's right. That's not your father.
Chester, we belong together.
No, no.
Chester, everything
that's inside of you,
it's moving from you into it.
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
Becoming a part of it.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
it's feeding on your grief.
Chester, you have to let it go.
I love you, son.
It's lying.
No, no, that thing is lying.
It's lying to you, honey,
it wants you to stay trapped
inside of your sadness because it's...
[GROWLS]
Hungry.
Chester, honey, you have to let it go.
I cant. I can't.
Chuck, listen to me.
Think about the last
time you saw your dad
and what you remember most about him.
That's what you have to hold on to.
Okay?
Yeah 'cause if your real dad was here,
he would be the first to say,
"Remember how much I love you."
Hold on to that, Chuck.
That's what matters.
♪
Take my hand.
My dad...
[GROWLS]
He never asked me to turn
my back on my life here.
♪
Oh, no, he would love the
life that I've built here.
He'd freak...
If he saw my workshop.
And he'd love that I'm working
with an actual superhero.
Helping him save the world every day.
No, my dad...
He'd be proud of his son.
[GROWLS]
And the man that I've become.
I said take my hand.
No.
No, I'm gonna stay here
with my friends because they...
They're my real family,
and you're not my dad.
So why don't you just go to hell!
[SCREAMING]
♪
[CHUCKLES]
Chester, the cold flames are gone.
What happened?
I sent them packing.
With a little help from my friends.
[CHUCKLES]
Chester, seems like you had
a pretty close call, huh?
You too, Barr.
Yeah, well thankfully, I
was able to phase myself
and Frost long enough for
Chester to do the rest.
Oh, it wasn't all me.
If it wasn't for Allegra and Cecile,
I'd be just another burnt
corpse right about now.
Hey, what about the other three victims?
Joe, did you find anything?
I did some digging, and
I called in a few favors.
Turns out our first victim, Stan Mullen,
recently lost all his
belongings to foreclosure.
Then Donna Winters, her
sister died last week.
Let me guess, our yoga vic
was suffering some loss too?
Fiancé and childhood
sweetheart to cancer.
That's a grief pattern.
Which fits with where
I've been at lately.
So this new meta, whoever he is,
eats grief and sorrow to survive.
Yeah, that's not terrifying.
It gets scarier.
We thought we were looking
for a meta serial killer,
someone that was
controlling the black flames
like the figure I saw in the fire.
But the fire created that.
And when I spoke to it, it heard me
like it could understand or something.
Chester's right.
With all of that sorrow
that I felt coming out
of that thing, I also
felt other emotions:
determination, passion, desire.
It's almost like whatever that thing is,
it's got a mind of its own.
So we're not looking
for a separate fire meta?
No.
The will to seek out victims to kill,
need to satisfy its
hunger at all costs...
The flames have a survival instinct.
Which means the flames aren't
being used by the killer.
They are the killer.
Because they're alive.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
We're not interrupting, are we?
No, no, no, it's good.
Just trying wrap my
head around all this.
You know, every member of
this team has dealt with grief.
Me with my own mom back in Houston.
Nash and Esperanza.
And Barry, all that he's dealt with,
and with both of his parents.
It's weird, but I
guess dealing with loss
is just another thing
that makes us human.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC]
When we help each other deal with it...
It's what makes us family.
Yeah.
♪
So I have some filing I
need to do back at my office.
- Right now?
- Yup.
You guys stay. I'll see you tomorrow.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, I know we have, like,
D&D plans for tonight,
but honestly, I just I... I can't.
Yeah, I'll text Marco and the gang.
Maybe we can pull an
all-nighter this Saturday?
I'd like that a lot. [LAUGHS]
Me too.
And Chuck...
You know I'll always be there for you.
Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
And for the record,
you're a very big part of my life too.
♪
- How's Sue?
- A life saver as always,
and it turns out that
the Dearbon Corporation
owns an entire city block
in downtown Coast City.
Oh, she rich-rich.
Yeah, you forget about it
until she puts all three of us
in a place like this and
you're like, yeah, billionaire.
- So Tinya's there too.
- Uh, yeah.
She's sleeping in the suite next door.
She has no place else to go, Barry.
I... I really want to help her.
That's what I love about you.
You make a real difference
in people's lives
with everything you do.
Yeah, you too.
Speaking of,
I was thinking that
with powers like hers...
She could be a hero too.
Like the Streak?
I mean, why not? That worked out.
Yeah.
Babe, what is it?
No, I'm...
I'm just... I'm glad you decided to stay
in Coast City a little longer.
The black fires?
Yeah, it's just not safe here right now.
Um... okay.
I mean, is there
anything that we can do?
No, it's okay.
I mean, we don't even
know how to locate it,
let alone stop it.
If anything happened to you...
Yeah, no, I get it.
- Okay, well, I love you.
- I love you too.
- Get some rest, okay?
- Yeah, you too.
♪
[WHOOSHING]
You found out what's wrong with me.
And it ain't good news.
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --