[dramatic music]
Bart's gonna be okay. He has to be.
♪ ♪
He will be, Nora.
You don't know that.
Nobody does.
Caitlin, we can't get back home.
Central City's being torn apart.
My dad's out there doing something
that'll probably get him killed.
Just feels like
everything's falling apart.
♪ ♪
[intense dramatic music]
- West.
- Go, go, go, go.
[electricity crackling]
[tires squealing]
[indistinct clamoring]
Heaven have mercy.
[epic dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[soft suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Fine.
You got what you wanted.
I'm here.
Now tell me what you were doing
at the Flash Museum.
[tense music]
What do you really want, Heart?
My, oh, my.
You're really direct.
Then again, you're meeting me
for the first time.
We're bound to learn new things
about each other.
Tell me what the hell's going on.
Or what?
You'll force me too?
Oh, Flash.
I'm the living God of Speed.
The one...
unlike you and your infernal spawn.
You're gonna leave them alone
or I swear...
Are you threatening me, Flash?
Here? [voice echoing]
Seriously?
♪ ♪
You still can't comprehend
what you're dealing with.
So let me enlighten you.
Once upon a time, there was
a young physicist named August
who dreamed of moving faster than light,
so he developed a way
to achieve his goal
and created the velocity formula.
But it wasn't enough
because no matter how fast he ran,
he soon came to realize
one salient fact...
♪ ♪
That he'd never be fast enough.
Heart, tell me how to stop this war.
Both sides are looking for you,
including one that wants to kill you.
And what?
You're gonna turn me over to them?
♪ ♪
Mm-mm.
You're too much of a hero
to sell me out.
♪ ♪
Now Impulse, that's a different story.
I said leave my son out of this.
Oh, but I can't.
He's the one who helped me
realize the truth.
That artificial speed would
always be a pale imitation
of the real deal.
♪ ♪
Spoiled, little brat.
He's not just reckless, he's unworthy.
All the times we fought.
He was so cavalier with his gift...
a gift that should have been mine!
♪ ♪
Now it will be...
thanks to you.
[laughs]
That's what this is all about.
You want organic speed.
[claps]
Keep going.
Everything that's happened...
us finding you, your clones, this war.
It's all a part of my plan
to force your hand.
So why the act if your
memories are still intact?
That's the one thing I didn't foresee.
Memory loss is a side effect
of fracturing myself in time.
♪ ♪
Who knew, right?
Then again, I knew you'd
come looking for answers,
which eventually would bring you to me.
♪ ♪
Give me the gift I deserve,
and I'll save your precious city
by reabsorbing my other selves.
Or refuse my request...
♪ ♪
And watch your city burn.
There's no way that's happening.
Besides, what you're asking me to do?
It's impossible.
The impossible is your thing.
You can figure it out.
Or watch more cities fall
as my army spreads
and this entire world is torn apart.
[chuckles]
Ooh!
I can see those little wheels
turning in your head.
You're trying desperately
to think of a way out of this.
Well, guess what?
There isn't.
♪ ♪
So what's your answer?
[tense musical crescendo]
♪ ♪
Answer me, damn it!
I already did.
I said no.
Oh, you'll change your mind.
♪ ♪
You have no choice.
[shouts]
[gasps]
[panting]
- [electricity sizzles]
- [panting]
Kid! You all right?
[soft dramatic music]
- Yeah. Yeah, no. Oh, yeah.
- Oh, thank God.
What happened? Did you find the real me?
Yeah.
[stutters] What did I say?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So what are we gonna do
about Godspeed's ultimatum?
We have to give him
what he wants: organic speed.
[soft dramatic music]
Nora, I'm never gonna do that.
Dad, everything will be destroyed.
Not just Bart, but whole families.
We have to protect them.
What about our family?
If Heart is Bart's Thawne, that
means he's already caused Bart
a lifetime of pain and suffering.
But we can stop this, here,
in this time, by finding another way.
But we've tried everything,
Dad, and nothing's worked.
And now Bart's dying,
and we're still no closer
to ending this damn war!
Nora, honey, if his clones
could do this to your brother,
then what do you think would happen
if the real August Heart
got organic speed?
It just all feels so hopeless.
It never is. Promise you that.
He's right.
As long as we're still standing,
we can still win this.
Let's go check on your brother.
[soft downbeat music]
♪ ♪
Kid?
I know giving August Heart
his powers back is crazy.
but if we don't, we'd better
come up with another idea.
A big one.
Not a big one.
A fast one.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
What am I supposed to do now?
August...
[soft dramatic music]
I know that things seem
really hopeless right now.
But believe me when I tell you
that this team of ours,
if there's anyone who can find
a way out of this thing,
it is Team Flash.
[sighs] I believe you.
I do, but I saw Barry's face
when we both came back.
It's true, isn't it?
I'm a monster, aren't I?
You don't have to be.
What if I don't have a choice?
You all think I'm someone
from the future,
a future where I'm supposed
to be a killer
obsessed with taking speed
and ruling the world.
You know how that feels?
Now imagine getting back
the thing you want most,
your memories, your whole life...
and then learning you're the bad guy.
If that's true, how am I
supposed to live with that?
I'm no fortune teller,
but I can tell you
that the sorrow I feel coming
from you, August,
bad guys, they don't
feel remorse like that.
♪ ♪
Maybe the future is not so set
in stone after all.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Chuck, I'm done with pep talks, okay?
I can't charge your dad's gizmo.
Not now, not ever.
Allegra,
I don't give a crap
about the S.E.E. right now.
Right now, all I care about
is my friend.
[soft dramatic music]
Now look,
Esperanza chose to go on that mission.
That's not on you.
Hey, but you know what is?
The Flash being alive today
because you didn't go with her.
♪ ♪
- That doesn't make any sense.
- That makes all the sense.
That Godspeed clone in the pipeline,
he was gonna kill Barry.
- [snarls]
- [grunts]
And you stopped that.
Which means the Flash
can get back to the business
of ending this war.
But Esperanza, she left to start one.
She let the city down. You didn't.
You helped lift it up.
You really think so?
Girl, I know so.
Now, I don't know about you,
but I'm ready to get back
to the business
of keeping Central City safe.
So what do you say, you with me?
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I... I guess that means a yes. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles] Cool.
Hey, don't forget your Java this time.
[chuckles]
[soft tense music]
Ever since this war began,
we've been outfought and outnumbered.
That ends now.
For all their speed,
our opponents,
no matter how fast they are,
they can't outrun a force of nature.
- [thunder cracks and echoes]
- [chuckles]
Big Nora! It's so good to see you.
Yeah, we've already met.
Remember when I first saw you?
I was like, "Oh, my gosh,
the freaking Speed Force".
And I was just so amazed
and... and nervous
and I just kept rambling
on and on and on
and totally embarrassing
myself because she...
It's good to see you too, Little Nora.
[chuckles]
This is a rare pleasure, ma'am.
And if I may,
you look a whole lot
like someone very close to me.
I get that a lot.
Barry, Iris, it's good to see you again.
Are the other forces coming, too?
No.
With me here,
they're all working overtime
to keep the universe in balance.
I've seen what you've all been facing.
I've been fighting it myself
within the Speed Force.
Now, you all need to be at full strength
in order to defeat this threat,
which is why whether you're
already a full speedster
or have just a spark
of Speed Force inside of you,
I'm going to give you all a boost.
That is if everyone's okay with that.
[chuckling] Oh, yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Schway.
- Yup.
That works.
- Barry, Bart's still...
- I know.
Oh, my impulsive boy.
- [exhales deeply]
- [ethereal whooshing]
[computer chiming rapidly]
♪ ♪
What in the world?
[laughing] Whoo!
- Oh! I'm back.
- Bart!
[laughing] Hi, did you miss me?
- Did you miss me?
- [chuckles]
Oh, thank you for the reboot, S.F.N.
I appreciate it.
[sighing grunt]
Speed Force Nana. Uh, it's...
it's our little thing.
Oh, somebody redid my nails.
It must have been Caitlin.
[swelling orchestral music]
Uncle Jay. You're... you're here.
Uncle?
That's new. Um...
- yeah, I kinda like it.
- [both chuckle]
It's good to finally meet you, Bart.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
All right. What's next, Pops?
[dramatic music]
We end this civil war.
Once and for all.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You guys get out of here!
Come on!
You gotta get up! Run, run!
We gotta get in contact with CCPD!
♪ ♪
West!
[panting]
♪ ♪
How did I... what just happened?
You just ran as fast as the Flash.
♪ ♪
Kramer, Kramer! Can you hear me?
Hey, looking for me?
♪ ♪
together: Kill the adversary.
Kill the adversary.
♪ ♪
Kill the adversary and his allies.
Kill them. Kill them all.
Kill them.
Now, remember...
hit 'em hard.
Wear 'em down and drain their energy.
together: Kill the adversary
and his allies.
Kill them. Kill them all.
♪ ♪
[triumphant epic music]
[menacing resonances]
♪ ♪
[slow dramatic music]
[upbeat dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[helmet clinks]
Frost, Mecha-Vibe, how are you doing?
We're holding our own!
Wouldn't say no to backup, though.
All right. We'll be there in a minute.
Dad, something's wrong.
[dissonant resonance]
[panting]
- What's happening to us?
- Flash, we have a problem.
[dissonant resonance]
[tense dramatic music]
But we knocked them all out!
- They're being recharged.
- How?
♪ ♪
They're feeding off me.
It's what happened
inside the Speed Force.
And now that energy drain
is affecting all of us.
♪ ♪
- Nora, you have to go.
- I can't let you fight alone.
You'll still be with us,
but you have to leave.
Right now!
♪ ♪
We're not going down without a fight.
Hang on to your buns!
♪ ♪
[upbeat dramatic music]
Whoa!
The S.E.E. readings are five
times their maximum strength.
Oh, yeah, watch out world!
This wavelength's off the charts!
♪ ♪
[S.E.E. powering down]
- Nice timing.
- Yeah.
Flash, more Godspeeds just arrived
and they're heading your way.
Continuous waves.
Wherever we run, they'll follow.
That's gonna put more
people in danger, Flash.
I know.
Thank God you guys are okay.
We managed to save the reactor,
but it looks like round two
is about to begin.
And this time there's no
Speed Force Nora or the S.E.E.
We threw everything we had at them.
[energetic suspenseful music]
What are we gonna do?
Dad?
♪ ♪
We need to get back out there.
Frost and Mecha-Vibe need our help.
Yeah, we will as soon as...
They're gone again.
Wow, Frost and Mecha-Vibe
make a hell of a team.
Chester, how long would
it take to rebuild the S.E.E.?
Four or five weeks, maybe?
How come your tech thingy
affected the clones and not us?
Well, we're all organic speedsters,
so I tweaked my Pop's design
to only target
artificial cell membranes.
Making it ineffective against us.
- [snaps fingers]
- Well done.
Dad, Mom,
I know you both wanna
keep the future safe,
but if we don't stop this right now,
there won't be a future to save.
Please can you just consider
giving Heart organic speed?
[sighs]
Nora, I know that
seems like the answer...
but we are your parents.
It's our job to protect you.
Maybe so.
But Central City doesn't need
parents right now.
[dramatic music]
Dad, it needs heroes.
♪ ♪
I know we said we'd protect the city
while the team figured
out a way to end this,
but can a man get a timeout?
Not happening.
♪ ♪
Hey, how long can you hold your breath?
What does that matter?
♪ ♪
When I say now,
we're gonna suck in as much air
as we can and hold it in.
What's that gonna do?
Wait, you're not actually gonna...
- Oh, I'm gonna.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Now!
- [both inhale deeply]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Yeah!
Thank God those bubbles are temporary.
- Oh!
- That's right.
Your boy put an auto timer
on the entropy bubble
and in the process,
answered his own question.
A man can get a timeout!
Am I a genius?
Never do that again.
[upbeat dramatic music]
I'll take that as a yes. [chuckles]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Whoa, you guys are stellar.
Thank you. What did we just do?
Oh, you saved me at least three weeks
in the proverbial salt mines of science.
At this rate, the modified
version of my Pop's S.E.E.
could be up and running in a day or two.
A day or two?
Isn't there some way
we can speed that up a little?
There is, but mom and dad
won't change their minds.
We already did.
♪ ♪
We're gonna give August organic speed.
[chuckles] Okay.
Oh, you're not kidding.
Where's Mom?
She's still with the Speed Force.
They're both helping, too.
What changed your mind?
My kids...
when I realized that
their future starts right now.
♪ ♪
[soft suspenseful music]
How exactly will this give
me my memories back?
The theory is your artificial
speed cells have gone dormant.
But we believe that
a speed boost from Barry
can jumpstart them and
give you organic speed.
And the harness should trigger the rest.
Hey, don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
Yeah, if this does work,
I'll try to come back.
Differently.
Good luck.
♪ ♪
Are you okay?
[sighs] If Dad is right,
and we're actually creating
the future by doing this...
everything from now on
will be different.
♪ ♪
I know you don't have to do this.
So whatever your reasons are,
I know they're pretty important.
I just hope this works out
for both of us.
♪ ♪
Me, too.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[electricity buzzing]
[straining]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
[electricity surging]
August, no.
Sorry, Cecile.
Turns out I like being the bad guy.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
No matter what happens, stay here.
- What?
- Absolutely not.
Your mother and I have a plan.
♪ ♪
[thunder booming and echoing]
[speaking Punjabi] _
♪ ♪
[screams]
[ominous dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[distorted] At last!
True speed for a true god!
♪ ♪
You got what you wanted, Heart.
Now what?
Now you die, Flash. By my hand!
♪ ♪
_
Oh, no one is dying tonight, Heart.
[laughs]
But you are going to Iron Heights.
You'll have to catch me first!
Dad, be careful!
You don't know what he's capable of!
I will.
What do you need me to do?
You be my anchor while I concentrate.
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Heart's got organic speed.
He just reabsorbed all his clones.
Jay is right.
Until the excess speed burns off,
Heart could be faster than you.
There can only be one
God of Speed, Flash!
- [grunting]
- [screaming]
[groans]
This didn't work out
like you planned, Flash.
- Now guess what comes next?
- [groans]
Tag, you're dead.
Dad!
Bart!
I know what I said, I know what I said.
But this is different.
This is different.
I'm not gonna let Heart kill
anyone that I care for.
Not now. Not ever.
I believe you, son.
Now, we just met.
You got no reason to listen to me.
But we both know Barry, right?
And if he says to stand down no
matter what, he has a reason.
But it's...
[soft dramatic music]
It's time to take our hats off, okay?
♪ ♪
_
Now that you've leveled up,
what better time to feast?
[electricity thrumming]
♪ ♪
Wait, is that Thawne?
It sure as hell is.
Miss me?
Save it, Thawne.
You're back because of us, right?
And in exchange,
I've agreed to help you
take down a psychopath.
Flash, that was nuts!
You do like to party.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Joining forces with your worst
enemy just to take me down.
That's very flattering, Flash,
but it won't do you any good.
Don't you two to get it?
You can't kill a god!
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful dramatic music]
[epic dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[lightning swords crackling]
[lightning sword crackling]
♪ ♪
Heart!
[sparse tense music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
You could have killed him.
Wasn't that the plan?
Didn't you say you needed help
dealing with a threat?
Well, I dealt with it.
And now...
[chuckling] and now...
it's just you and me, Flash.
I've been waiting for this moment
for a long, long time.
I'm only gonna say this once.
Walk away while you still can.
Allen.
You are too weak to stop me.
[distorted]
And I'm just getting started.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What did you do?
I created you.
I taught you everything you know!
Everything you are is because of me!
What did you do?
I got faster.
Didn't you?
♪ ♪
No.
But I will, Flash.
Mark my words.
I will.
♪ ♪
How did you bring Thawne back?
Well, the Speed Force did it
by connecting with the Negative Side,
which is pretty dangerous.
So with Barry occupied,
I was the perfect choice
to anchor the Speed Force.
Wait.
Tapping into the Negative Speed Force...
do I even know who you guys are?
Okay, but why Thawne?
Like, why not just let us
come help instead?
Sometimes,
what makes the speedster
dangerous isn't just speed.
It's having no limits
on how they use it.
Right. Godspeed has no limits.
But Thawne, his one limit is he
can't let anyone else kill me.
That's why I knew he'd turn
on me the first chance he got.
But Dad, Thawne's still out there.
Yeah, and he'll be back someday,
but that's future us's problem.
What about August Heart?
He's in Iron Heights now.
But Barry, he knows your real identity.
- What if he talks?
- Luckily, he's a speedster.
So Speed Force Nora was able
to remove that from his memory.
- It's finally over.
- Great.
Can we eat now? I'm starving.
Family dinner tonight on Dad.
- Yeah, I would love that.
- That sounds perfect.
I'll get us a reservation.
♪ ♪
Iris, hang on.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Okay. [chuckles]
Now, ever since you came into my life,
I've been more than just
the fastest man alive.
I've been the luckiest.
Marrying you was
the best decision I ever made.
Well, I agree.
And even though we're husband and wife,
you never really got
the wedding you deserved.
These past few days,
when it looked like
I might never see you again,
I swore if I ever did,
I would make it up to you.
So...
- Iris West Allen...
- [chuckles]
Will you renew your vows and remarry me?
[soft dramatic music]
Yes.
[chuckles] Yes, I will.
♪ ♪
Oh, I'm obviously interrupting.
No, it's okay. It's good to see you.
- I should go.
- Kramer.
We haven't talked in a week.
How are you?
I don't really know how to answer that.
I just wanted to let you know
that my Meta test came back positive.
So you are a speedster?
Well, yes and no. Adam was right.
I should've died
in that bombing, but I didn't.
And neither did he because
he has immortal healing powers.
And so did I when
I absolutely needed them.
Just like when I needed
super speed to save your life,
I had it for just a moment.
That's incredible.
Turns out I can mimic
the abilities of any Meta
in close proximity, which sounds insane,
but it's real.
Well, it's given me new perspective
on the path I took as a member
of law enforcement.
Um...
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry, West, for all of it.
Hey, you lost your way a little,
but I always knew that your
heart was in the right place.
- You just needed to find it.
- [chuckles]
Agreed.
That's why I'm taking
an indefinite leave of absence
from CCPD.
♪ ♪
- Take care of yourself, West.
- Kristen.
Call me Joe.
♪ ♪
[birds singing]
Are you sure you're okay with me
being your plus one because...
Do not say his name.
Frost, I know...
He lied to me and then totally bailed.
- I hate weddings.
- Technically, this is...
Okay, fine. Renewal ceremony.
♪ ♪
Maybe we should renew our vows.
Oh, I'd marry you again in a heartbeat.
Aw. I love renewal ceremonies.
And weddings.
- Good to know.
- Mm.
Everyone,
if I may direct your attention
to the stairs.
♪ ♪
Hi, Daddy. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
- Nice entrance.
- Thank you.
Now, before we get to the main event,
I know you two have asked us all
to keep it simple for this occasion.
- [all chuckling]
- But one of us couldn't resist
adding a little something extra
special to the festivities,
so without further ado, my man.
Thank you, Cisco. Appreciate it.
Mom, Dad, this is for you.
♪ Could you be that fine love? ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ That 1949 love ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ That quiver in your spine love ♪
♪ That summer wine love ♪
♪ Just grab a warm body
and pick up the key ♪
♪ If you need somebody ♪
♪ Somebody to be ♪
♪ You can't count on timing
or just wait and see ♪
♪ I'll be that somebody,
so settle for me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'll give you all the affection ♪
♪ You've been craving ♪
♪ When you're ready ♪
♪ I'll be waiting ♪
♪ Waiting, baby ♪
♪ And I've got ♪
♪ I'll give you all the affection ♪
♪ Just grab a warm body
and pick up the key ♪
♪ If you need somebody,
somebody like me ♪
♪ You can't count on timing
or just wait and see ♪
♪ Be that somebody ♪
♪ So darling ♪
♪ If you're ready ♪
♪ To settle ♪
[chuckles]
[applause]
- Bart.
- Yeah?
That was crash.
- What?
- No, no. Just no.
That's how you say it.
That's not how I say it.
You say it weird.
Let's just do the thing again.
My fellow Earthlings, today,
we are here to witness
the greatest sequel since
"Empire Strikes Back..."
Mm.
As Barry and Iris renew their vows
and lend new meaning
to the term relationship goals.
Now, I understand you both
wrote a little something
- for each other.
- Mm-hmm.
If you'd like to share,
this is the time.
- Iris?
- [clears throat]
Barry...
they say that love is a friendship
that has caught on fire,
but ours is a friendship
that was struck by lightning.
You and I are our own force of nature.
And I promise today...
to continue loving you
with my whole heart.
That was beautiful.
- Good luck following that.
- Yeah.
Iris...
Thank you.
Ever since we met,
you've been my lightning rod.
But now that you're my wife,
you are my past,
my present, and my only future.
That's why today,
I promise to continue
loving you now and forever.
[mouths words]
Okay, that was... that was decent.
Ten points for Gryffindor.
Now, then...
- Oh, yes.
- [chuckles]
Do you Iris, Bartholomew,
take each other to cherish and to love
in good times and bad
for all the days of your life?
I do.
- Again.
[chuckles]
Then by the power vested in me
by a last-minute Internet web search...
[laughter]
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
- Again.
- [applause]
Am I... am I forgetting something?
- Yes. The kiss.
- Oh, yes.
[stutters] The kiss. Yes, do the thing.
[laughs]
[swelling orchestral music]
♪ ♪
Flashtime, huh?
Do you blame me?
I want this moment to last forever.
♪ ♪
Greg, move your head!
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -