My name is Barry Allen and I
am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
(West) That's Barry's old house.
Maybe it's been too long.
Everything's different.
Except that mirror.
(Cisco) This mirror might contain
photographs of what happened that night.
That blood belongs to one
of the two speedsters
that was here that night.
It's Barry's... As an adult.
Mrs. Stein, have you seen this person?
- Yes.
- He's not even Ronnie anymore.
He's Martin Stein walking around
in Ronnie's body.
Any attempt we make
to separate the two of them
could be catastrophic...
a nuclear explosion.
Barry?
Barry, what happened out there?
Are you guys okay?
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
I think so.
Oh, God. The nuclear explosion.
There's no telling how much
radiation we were exposed to.
Wait... wait, wait,
wait, wait, this can't be.
The Geiger counter in the suit...
it's reading less than one millirad.
But that's normal.
(Wells) There's no radiation.
Let's go.
(Cisco) Did it work?
Did you separate them?
I don't know.
Ronnie?
Tell me your name.
Ronnie Raymond.
Cait.
It's me.
Uh, pardon me.
Obviously, I need a change of clothes.
Nice to see you in the flesh
again, Professor Stein.
We're coming home.
All of us.
- Ronnie Raymond.
- Cisco.
Man. Ohh.
I missed you so much, man.
I shouldn't have locked you in there.
Hey... don't.
Welcome back, Mr. Raymond.
Dr. Wells.
Caitlin told me what happened to you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm responsible for putting
myself in this chair.
You are responsible for my
still being alive... thank you.
You said you'd bring him back, and you did.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me?
Are we all planning to sing Kumbaya next?
Professor Stein, I presume.
Harrison Wells.
Do you have somewhere I can freshen up
and get a change of clothes?
Of course.
Right this way, Professor.
(Bates) General, are you getting this?
Roger that, Sergeant.
Sir, look at this.
Two imprints of impact.
Two imprints.
(Eiling) Two different people.
It's Firestorm. He's separated.
Your vitals appear to be normal,
except you have a slight fever of 100.6.
Cait, I'm fine, I promise.
I know, but we just need to be...
Shh.
Yep... just when I forgot how awkward it was
to walk in on you two.
Well, you can get used to it again.
So I did a full medical
workup on the professor.
It turns out that now that he
and Ronnie are separated,
they no longer possess the ability
to harness nuclear energy.
Professor Stein, you seem to be running
a little hot as well.
Same as Ronnie... 100.6.
Hardly a sweat, Dr. Snow.
And hopefully now the only thing
Ronald and I have in common...
- It's Ronnie.
- Mm.
Hey?
You gonna miss being able to fly?
Yeah, maybe if I was the one
holding the controller.
Meaning?
Meaning, you weren't the most
conscientious body-mate.
So you do not consider keeping you alive
to be conscientious?
Alive?
We were living under
a bridge, eating garbage.
I did not determine that it would be
my mind that would dominate our existence,
but thank God it was.
I could feel your fear and panic,
emotions that likely
would have gotten us killed
in that state.
You kept me buried down.
You kept me from her.
Which is likely why she's still alive.
Now I believe you and I have spent
quite enough time together.
Yeah.
I would like to go home to see my wife.
- Mr. Allen will take you.
- Thank you.
- I need some pizza.
- You got it.
I can't believe it.
Oh... wait.
Uh... what should I say?
I don't think you're gonna
have to say anything.
Oh, Clarissa.
I'm so sorry I put you through this.
[mouthing] Thank you.
Mister, uh... Barry.
Yeah?
Barry, I... I know I can be
difficult, but thank you
for bringing me home.
I'll see you soon, Professor.
Hey.
I left you three messages.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
About the lack of communication,
or that new hole
out in the badlands?
Uh, we're all fine, thanks.
I wasn't calling about the explosion.
I have to show you something.
What?
It's smaller than I remember.
Yeah.
It's because you're bigger.
Have you been in here?
- I mean, recently.
- No.
I haven't been in this house
since that night.
Bar? This mirror... you remember it?
Yeah. It belonged to my grandma.
How is it still here?
Just be glad it is.
Look... I don't fully know
how Cisco did it, but...
Did what? Joe, what are we doing here?
Mom.
You can definitely see two very fast people
fighting around your mother.
Two speedsters.
You see that?
The blood?
Cisco and I had the DNA tested.
It's yours.
No, it's not. That's impossible.
I wasn't even downstairs yet.
No, Barry. Not that you.
This you.
Cisco had the samples
analyzed and the proteins
in the blood were that
of an adult, not a child.
But that means...
The second speedster,
the one trying to stop
the man in yellow...
Is the Flash.
That's me.
Time travel.
If the last five months
have proven anything,
it's that anything can exist,
but to actually travel through time?
Well, the greatest minds in human history
put their collective genius
towards solving that puzzle.
So. Is it possible?
Yes, it's possible.
But problematic.
Assuming you could create
the conditions necessary
to take that journey...
well, that journey would then
befraught with potential pitfalls.
The Novikov principle of
self-consistency, for example.
Wait, the what, now?
If you travel back in time
to change something,
then you end up being
the causal factor of that event.
Like Terminator.
Ah.
Or is time plastic?
Is it mutable whereby
any changes to the continuum
could create an alternate timeline.
Back To The Future.
Oh... saw that one too.
Doc Brown. Tremendous picture.
Right. So what's the answer?
I might be a clever guy, Joe,
but if you're asking me
to give you a working theory on
how to travel through time,
I'm afraid I just can't do that.
There is someone else
you can talk to about this.
Danish?
Why do you have a blueprint
of the S.T.A.R. Labs
Particle Accelerator?
Do you actually know anything
about physics?
Not a thing. Might as well be in Dothraki.
So what more is there
with the S.T.A.R. Labs story?
The only new piece of information
is the fact that Harrison Wells admitted
that he was warned of a potential disaster.
Yeah. Why do you think he did that?
Because he's a good person?
- Is he?
- Yes.
He saved my friend's life.
He was struck by lightning
that night and Dr. Wells
and his team kept him alive.
So?
Your friend wouldn't have needed saving
if Wells hadn't zapped him
in the first place.
It was an accident.
What if it wasn't?
So you think Harrison Wells
wanted the Particle Accelerator to explode?
Why would he do that?
I don't know what goes on
inside that building.
But I think you know some people who do.
So you think I would investigate my friends
because you got me a danish?
I think that you'll do it
because you really want
to know what goes on inside that building.
[doorbell rings]
Barry?
Mrs. Stein, I'm sorry to bother you here,
but is Professor Stein here right now?
Well, after a year apart,
I'm not letting him out of my sight.
S.T.A.R. Labs did quite a few
tests on Martin,
didn't they... and they said he was fine?
Yeah. Why, is something wrong?
He just seems a little different, is all.
Different how?
He's been asking for pizza.
Martin despises pizza.
Is that the delivery man? Oh, Mr. Allen.
I suppose it's too much
to hope you moonlight
as a pizza boy. I am famished.
Okay.
Oh, bravo! Please, come in.
Mr. Allen.
Oh, mmm. What can I do for you?
I... I needed to talk to you about a paper
that you wrote 25 years ago
for the Oxford University Press.
I've written many papers
for that publication.
Could you be more specific
about the subject matter?
Time travel.
These are just a few of the random thoughts
I've had on the subject.
Few?
See, I believe that space-time
is a free-flowing highway
that intersects the physical world.
We live in... in the moments
between the on and off ramps.
Theoretically, to travel through time,
one merely needs to find
a way onto the highway.
Okay, so... so you're saying
that this is actually possible
to... to travel into the future?
Undoubtedly.
What about the past?
Yes.
My own personal choice would be
the Chicago World's Fair, 1893.
I... I think Nikola Tesla and I would have
some wonderful arguments.
What about you?
Would you be interested
in taking a trip into history?
I think that I already have.
Professor, um...
15 years ago, my mom was murdered
and we recently discovered
some evidence that...
I was there that night,
and not just as a kid,
but as an adult.
That must be a side effect
of your incredible speed.
In some... future date,
you actually move so fast
that the resulting kinetic energy buildup
smashes a hole in the space-time continuum!
You seem disappointed by the prospect.
I mean, if I do somehow make it back there
to that night, then...
it means that I didn't save her.
My destiny is to fail.
And the boomerang goes flying
through the cortex,
smashing everything and Cisco's all,
"My bad. This one's on me."
Sounds like you had some crazy times.
Yeah, we have.
Are you ready for life
to get back to normal?
What do you mean?
I was thinking we could leave town.
Start fresh somewhere.
Our lives are here. My job is here.
Yeah, hunting meta-humans.
There's more to it than that.
- And it's dangerous.
- It can be.
Look, I stayed at S.T.A.R. Labs
because I believed in Dr. Wells.
But ever since Barry became
The Flash and we've been working
to keep this city safe,
I found a new way to help people.
Look, Cait, I'm not mad at anyone.
Okay, I know the accelerator
explosion was an accident.
But that building took a year of our lives.
I don't want it to take anymore.
Do you guys need anything else?
We're about to close up.
I'm good. Babe?
Ronnie, get down.
- Get out of here.
- No, not without you.
I'm right behind you... go!
- Professor?
- Martin?
What's wrong?
I don't know, I... I feel terrified.
My... my heart is racing.
(Man) Hands in the air!
I think... I think Ronald is in trouble.
How could you know that?
Jitters. He needs help.
Go!
Ronald Raymond.
Burning Man himself.
Half of him, anyway.
Who are you?
General Wade Eiling, United States Army.
What do you want?
Firestorm.
[screams in pain]
Stings, doesn't it?
Had that one developed especially for you.
Micro fragments
attracted to kinetic energy.
Firestorm was tonight's main objective,
but getting you... that's just gravy.
Get in!
Gentlemen, we are at war.
You need to hurry, Barry's wounds
are starting to heal with the fragments
still under his skin.
This is just like that time
I stepped on a sea urchin.
Only much worse.
Just don't pee on me.
Uh, you know that's a myth, right?
[yells]
I'm so stupid.
Jason Rush, the grad student
who was helping Professor Stein
with his Firestorm research,
he said that the Army
took all of Professor Stein's
material when he disappeared.
I should have known it was General Eiling.
Not your fault.
He still thinks you hold
the keys to the ultimate
human weapon... both of you.
Okay, let's just finish this.
I gotta get to Stein's house.
Eiling's gonna be after him too.
Stein's fine.
- How do you know?
- He's right there.
I don't think Mr. Raymond
and I are as distinctive
as we had hoped.
I'm still inside Ronald.
There has to be a better way
to phrase that.
Beta, Alpha, Theta, Delta...
all your brain waves
are perfectly in sync.
The chances of that happening
are next to impossible.
Impossible's just another
Tuesday for us, remember?
Yeah, but this is like
some Twilight Zone level stuff,
and I say that knowing
full well that we have
a guy locked up in our basement
who can turn himself into poison gas.
Wait, really?
Dude, that was, like, week three.
Look, if this Eiling is as
dangerous as you say,
then I need to warn Clarissa.
I promise, I can get Clarissa
out of the city in time,
but we need you to stay here.
Professor, I need you to trust us.
Very well.
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just not
the S.T.A.R. Labs I knew.
Ronnie, this isn't the world that you knew.
Tell me about it.
All right, here we are.
Uh, all right.
You guys can stay down in Iris' old room.
- It's kind of small, but...
- Hey.
- We have guests.
- Yeah, we do.
I hope that's okay.
- Mi casa.
- This is Ronnie.
Nice to meet you.
- Ronnie, the...
- Dead fiance.
Right.
- Beer?
- Thanks.
Dad? Barry?
- Iris, hi.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Uh, it's Tuesday.
I was gonna make us dinner, remember?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
Here, I'll help. Got it.
I knew you'd forget.
Well, there's plenty for everyone.
Caitlin, what brings you by?
There's a gas leak in my apartment,
so Barry said that we could stay here.
Oh, that's sweet of him.
And, uh, who's this?
- This is, uh...
- Her cousin.
- Sam.
- Visiting from Coast City.
You look really familiar, Sam.
Yeah, I... I have... one of those faces.
So what's for dinner?
- Harrison.
- Wade.
I had a feeling you would be wheeling by.
Tell me.
They still pulling needles
out of Barry Allen's hide?
I guess your sweet little Flash didn't want
Sergeant Sans Soucie to die
looking into a mask.
I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
I don't know how Firestorm works.
Well, you may not know
the how, but you know the who.
Both of them.
Thanks to you, it's the dawn
of a new age, Harrison.
Cold War, the war on terror.
We'll seem like cave men
fighting with sticks
once those two freaks bind together.
Well, you know where to find me
when you've come to the right decision.
And I know you will.
After all, you're the smartest guy I know.
Bar?
Should I have not shown you?
No, I had to know.
We have been through so much.
You have... all your life.
And you've been so strong.
But I am still your guardian,
and it's my job to guard you,
not just physically, but from heartache.
I can't help but feeling
like I just handed you
a brand new burden.
Yeah. But it's our burden, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Mm hmm.
How did you know that the blood
in the house belonged to me?
You would have had to have
tested it specifically.
Cisco tested it against everyone who worked
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You wanted to know if it belonged to Wells?
Joe.
Dr. Wells had nothing to do
with my mom's murder.
You believe that now?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah... I do.
Cheers.
Delicious.
This is quite an impressive facility.
Well, it was.
Now it's just a shell, I'm afraid.
Must have been devastating,
seeing your life's work
fall to pieces before your eyes.
It was and yet,
it was the exact same moment
your life's work came to fruition.
My life's work?
If living the last 14 months
as a conjoined meta-human
has taught me anything,
it's that my life's work
should have been being the best
husband I could to my wife.
Are you all right, Martin?
I apologize, it's just...
I feel a little light-headed.
[glass shattering]
Are you okay?
Uh...yeah.
Yeah, I'm... I'm fine.
Just got a little dizzy for a second.
You want the secret to Firestorm.
He has it.
See, Harrison? We do work well together.
Oh, hey... hey.
You said you knew some of
the leftover scientists
at the S.T.A.R. Lab.
What about a Caitlin Snow, M.D.
You know her?
Yeah, I know her, why?
There was an incident
at a local coffee shop.
She was there.
That's Jitters. I used to work there.
Is there anything you can't do?
Gimme this.
Witnesses swear they saw soldiers
shooting the place up,
so I contacted the Army's
media relations division and asked,
"Are soldiers permitted
to operate like that
on U.S. soil?"
You know what they told me?
Hooah.
That's weird, Caitlin didn't
mention anything
the last time I saw her.
Really?
When and where was that?
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure there's
an explanation for all of this.
He didn't hurt you?
Barry, I told you... only my pride is hurt.
Unfortunately, I'm not
in the position to take on
armed soldiers.
Where do you think
Eiling took Professor Stein?
I imagine some off-the-books
military research facility.
We have to get him back.
Easy... Eiling has already
demonstrated he has the weaponry
to disable The Flash, or worse.
Well, we can't let him
turn Stein into a weapon.
How do we find him?
What?
No abnormal brain activity.
All vitals steady.
You really think Ronnie can somehow feel
where they're keeping Stein?
Ronnie got dizzy when
the soldiers grabbed Stein,
and Stein developed
Ronnie's obsession with pizza.
I don't feel anything right now.
Just keep trying.
Whatever this is, it doesn't have
an on and off switch.
It's possible it's just some
kind of residual connection.
A temporary link to your time together.
Wait. I feel something.
I'm... I'm cold.
It's freezing in here!
My apologies.
It should warm up pretty quick.
I know what you want.
But my research was never
intended to be used as a weapon.
I joined the military
when I was 20 years old,
Professor.
My father had me convinced
that our greatest threat
was the Soviets.
Our greatest fear... nuclear war.
Then came terrorism
and Ebola.
And now, it's the age of Firestorm.
Soldiers enhanced
by your project, Professor.
Soldiers who can generate energy blasts
with their bare hands.
Soldiers who can fly.
I would gladly die
before I see my life's work
perverted in this way.
Good. Because you will die, Professor.
How soon I let that happen,
though, is entirely up to you.
What's going on?
Last time I did this was to a gorilla.
[screams]
You're okay, man, we got you.
What's happening to him?
Nothing's happening to him.
It's happening to Stein,
and Ronnie is feeling his pain.
I was wrong.
The connection's not temporary.
It's only getting stronger.
Just try and hold on.
Water. Water.
My, my, my, my, my, my.
You show remarkable grit for a teacher.
I am impressed.
Why don't we let you catch your breath?
Think about how much more
of this you want to endure.
Hmm?
Ronnie, no!
Wait, Cait, wait.
He's cutting himself.
I know. Let him.
Ronald.
[taps]
Anything?
Nothing. Nothing, just...just cold.
Like a metal surface.
Pressure on and on and off.
Tap, tap. Tap.
Tap. Tap.
Tap, tap, tap.
Morse code.
I got this.
Same thing again. Tap, tap.
Tap.
Tap, tap, tap.
- 27.
- What does it mean?
Army bases... they sometimes
go by numbers, like Area 51.
Facility 27, about 300 miles away.
It was shut down in 1961.
Well, that's where they're keeping Stein.
Bet you that's where
they're keeping aliens too.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
You can't.
I'm connected to Stein. I have to go.
But did you ever stop
to think why your connection
to him is growing stronger by the minute?
Maybe you're being drawn back together.
Maybe your proximity will cause
you to re-merge into one.
And what happens to me if he gets killed?
Cait, Barry was right.
The world is different now.
Look, I... I thought we could get away,
start a new life, a normal life, together.
But there is no normal life for us.
You will always risk your life
to try and help people,
and I will always be the guy that runs
into that pipeline for you.
The quantum splicer.
It was used to separate you once.
Maybe it could be of use to keep you you.
Thanks.
- Okay, let's go.
- Wait.
Come back. All three of you.
Let's go.
Oh.
This place definitely
doesn't look too shady.
Stein's inside.
I can feel our connection growing stronger,
like he's pulling me.
It's as I feared... the Firestorm matrix
is building toward a proximity reemergence.
Like all matter, it yearns to be whole.
If you do merge...
we might not be able to separate you again.
We've been able to isolate
the Firestorm matrix
inside the subject's cellular structure.
Excellent.
Professor Stein,
I'm afraid you have
made a terrible assumption...
That I need you alive.
Eiling has a gun to Stein's head.
He's about to pull the trigger.
He's here.
Ho!
Whoa... I never thought
I'd be happy to see you.
- Yeah, likewise.
- Let's get out of here.
[screams]
Run!
Okay... come on, come on.
Barry, I'm picking up some
serious pH numbers on your suit.
They hit me with some kind of chemical.
(Cisco) It's a weaponized phosphorous.
Water or foam won't extinguish it.
But you can't burn in a vacuum,
so you need to create one.
Run, Barry. Run!
- We need to merge again.
- Ronnie, no!
Cait, we're dead if we don't.
Listen to me.
The last time you two combined,
you both fought it.
This time, don't.
Accept the change, accept the balance.
Accept each other.
Once more unto the breach, dear friend.
Cait... whatever happens, just
remember I'll always love you.
(Stein) Can you hear me, Ronald?
Professor?
(Stein) It appears we merged
properly on this attempt.
Wells was right about
balance and accepting.
Behind you!
(Stein) Ronald, there's more of them.
Eiling, this ends now.
Yes, it does...
For both of you.
An ion grenade.
Just bombarded your cellular
structure with enough ions
to destabilize your matrix.
Mr. Raymond, Professor Stein,
you're both fine Americans.
Your country thanks you for your sacrifice.
That was a lot of running.
Ronnie?
- Home?
- Yeah.
I think it looks worse than it is.
Ronnie or Stein?
It's me, Cait.
[Stein clearing throat] Excuse me.
It's both of us. Somehow.
(Stein) She's quite lovely.
Acceptance is a powerful thing.
Powerful enough to reverse it?
(Stein) I'm game if you are, Mr. Raymond.
We could try.
I think we're getting
the hang of this quite nicely.
It's okay.
I understand. You have to go.
How'd you know?
I'm connected to you too.
Where will you go?
Pittsburgh, maybe.
Professor Stein has a colleague he thinks
can help us learn more about our abilities.
We can help you here too.
Eiling has already breached S.T.A.R. Labs.
We need to stay one step ahead of him...
for all of us.
- I'm coming back.
- We'll have pizza.
Godspeed, Mr. Allen.
You too.
As to our earlier conversation,
I believe in second chances.
You'll get yours.
Give it time.
- Ready, Ronald?
- Please stop calling me that.
I'll see you soon.
We love you.
I had Ronnie, then I lost him.
Then I found him again,
but he wasn't actually Ronnie.
Then I got him back but just for
a day until I lost him again.
You guys are like 10 seasons
of Ross and Rachel,
but just, like, smushed into one year.
I am not heartbroken this time.
I love Ronnie. I always will,
but there's not this
devastating hole inside me.
I have a life, and it's a good one.
Hey, guys.
- Iris, hi.
- Hi.
Where is your cousin?
Uh, he went home.
Oh. Uh, where was that again?
Uh, Midway.
Oh, I thought you said Coast City.
Uh, Midway via Coast City.
He moved around a lot.
That's always really hard.
All right, well. Enjoy.
- Bye.
- See you.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
It means that I'm gonna help you figure out
what's going on at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I think our Burning Man used to work there.
[door bell rings]
- Yo.
- Hey.
So why'd you bring me here?
I don't know how and I don't know when,
but one day soon, I'm gonna be
in this house again,
15 years ago.
And I'm gonna fail...
Unless this time, I don't.
What are you saying?
Knowing that I'm supposed
to lose gives me the advantage.
Those images are a lesson
in what not to do.
When I face off against the man in yellow,
I won't make the same mistake twice.
You're gonna... change the past?
Joe... I'm gonna save my mom.
[electric buzzing]
What... what the hell was that?
(distorted voice) It's good
to see you again, General.
Who are you?
(distorted voice) Who am I?
Harrison... You're one of them.
A meta-human.
Yes, I am.
And I protect my own.
[growls]
Who was that?
Now, that...
is an old friend of ours.
(Grodd) General...
That... voice...
It's in my head.
Dear God.
Not God. Grodd.
[snarling]
[Eiling screaming]
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com