You little brats, beat it!
Hey...!
It should have been me!
You'll miss the train
Hurry
PART ONE
'Kouzuki Noriaki
Go back to sleep
We're still far from the house
Pleased to meet you
I am Okju.
A Western-style wing
by an English architect
Not even in Japan is there
a building combining two styles
It reflects lVlaster's
admiration for Japan and England
Next is the annex
which lVlaster
had furnished as a library
Last, the ser\/ants' quarters
As the Lady's handmaiden
you won't sleep there.
You may eat her leftover food
but tea leaves go
to the kitchen girls
Used soap
is for the steward
l'm sure you wouldn't dare
Tamako.
Among the richest men,
lVlaster is the greatest book lover
And among book lovers
he is the richest.
His ties to the colonial government
even let us use electricity.
ln such a home
you know what's expected
of a maid like you?
Don't be alarmed at the blackouts
I sleep in here?
lVliss Hideko wakes easily
on account of her ner\/es.
She's behind this door?
IVlother!
lVliss!
lVliss, are you alright?
Junko! ls that you?
Junko was kicked out, lVliss
l'm the new girl.
Seems you had a bad dream
You see that big cherry tree?
I\/ly aunt went mad
and hanged herself there
Sometimes on moonless nights
my aunt's ghost
dangles from that branch
Here, drink up
When babies cry, my auntie
feeds them a spoonful of sake
Sweet bird, sweet bird
You think l'm Tamako,
a poor Korean handmaiden
But my rea/ name 's
Nam Sookee.
I was able at age 5 to tel/
a rea/ coin from a fake.
Then /earned to forge stamps
from Gugai,
and studied pickpocketing
from Kutan,
but these babies will never
/earn such useful skills.
Abandoned as newborns
we 'll wash and feed them,
then sell them to Japan.
Such meaningful work
Instead of starving, they grow up
gentlemen and ladies.
Kutan only breastfeeds her own kid
I wou/dn 't be so miser/y.
I wish my breasts gave milk
I 'd breastfeed all of them.
l'll tell you the story
of an interpreter,
who bribed his way into
translating for high officials
After helping Japan annex Korea
he got rights to a gold mine.
Now he wants to turn
fully Japanese.
So he gets naturalized
marries the daughter
of a fallen Japanese noble
and adopts his wife's
family name Kouzuki.
BaH.Bas
Bastard builds a mansion,
fills it with books and antiques
He invites Japanese collectors
to his library,
He loves books and paintings
like his own flesh,
but he can't help
parting with a few
What to do, when he must sell
but can't bear to?
He sells a fake
He seeks out a specialist
to create intricate forgeries
Unlike him this specialist
is a real Japanese
of noble birth!
Count Fujiwara from Nagoya
So, who is this?
You'll seduce her
- ls she pretty?
The Jap wife died ages ago
with no children.
But the dead wife's
dead sister's living daughter
But is she pretty?
An orphan.
Her father was rich
Soon she'll fall in love with me
and we'll elope to Japan.
After marrying her there
and inheriting her fortune
l'll declare her insane
and lock her up in a madhouse
Right!
Love?
What does a crook
know about love?
What of her fortune?
She's rich?
Each night in bed I think
of her assets.
1.5 million in cash
300,000 in bonds.
The uncle is just a guardian
lt's Hideko's fortune.
That's why Kouzuki
schemes to marry the girl
To his w...wife's niece?
What a s...sick f...f
Right, a sick fuck
So what's our share?
l'll share 50,000
Sookee gets the
dresses and jewellery
l'll do it! Take me!
I\/ly Japanese is better,
and I worked as a maid!
On top of the fifty
I get dresses, jewellery
and my own 100,000.
She must be crazy
Crazy? Not a bit.
I 'll take my fortune
and flee this country.
Endure these country yoke/s
a bit longer.
Those fuckers
This is Tamako
I am at your service
lVliss...
Bloody hell
He should 've told me
she was so pretty.
I 'm completely flummoxed
A reference letter
from Lady lVlinami
my last mistress.
Here's the letter
Pay attention.
Dear lVliss Izumi Hideko
A maid is like
a pair of chopsticks
Her presence is little noted, but
her absence causes much distress
The sun scarcely ever shines here
Uncle won't permit it
One could never grow fond
of such a dreary place.
Not a good liar, are you?
l'll take my leave
I\lly head aches before
every reading practice.
Would you read it to me?
Pardon?
Lady lVlinami said such
nice things about me!
Is that so?
You're a Japanese lady,
why don't you speak Japanese?
The books he makes me read
are all Japanese.
So read that for me
Dear lVliss Izumi Hideko
Count Fujiwara said
you're looking for a maid
lVlaids are like
a spoon... no
are like chopsticks
Is it a spoon?
I don't know how to read, lVliss
Not at all?
What about Korean?
This is your name
Can't you read it?
Reading can be learned
and I don't care if you
curse or steal.
But don't ever lie to me
Understood?
Yes, lVliss
IVly mum
She's beautiful,
quite the charmer!
And me?
Am I "quite the charmer?
Everyone says I can't
compare to my mother
Count Fujiwara said
So you've met the Count?
I\lly aunt!
I heard it from my aunt
She was his nanny
What did the Count
say about me?
He said your face
Every night in bed he thinks
of your assets... your face.
I've nowhere to go
I've just stayed in this house
since coming to Korea at age 5
But in new shoes, even
well-trodden paths feel fresh
The ones from here
up to here
should fit you
Time for reading practice
l'll go alone
lVliss?
But rain is falling
At noon, come knock
on the door. Promise?
See you at
See you later
Why would the lady
of such a big house... ?
Did the big house
make her go mad?
I\lly new handmaiden
The snake, the snake!
You mustn't pass that point
Be warned!
The snake marks the
bounds of knowledge'
A snake!
The Count?
Today?
That's why you insisted
on a bath.
I\lly aunt, when she heard
a guest was coming,
dropped eveiything and
bathed her Baby lVliss.
Nothing made her happier than when
guests praised her baby's scent.
You are my Baby lVliss
Auntie gave the babies
candy during baths.
To teach them that
bath time is sweet.
What's wrong?
One of my teeth is sharp
It keeps cutting me.
So this was the scent.
Welcome, sir!
You are too kind to greet me
this way upon my arrival,
when the journey has
left me so unkempt.
Now your tedium is over
l'll ensure your painting
lessons are stimulating.
This must be Okju
At your ser\/ice, milord
You know if you fail, it'll put
me in an awkward position?
A decent bone structure
for a Korean...
So, are you carrying out
your duties faithfully?
Count Fujiwara asks lVliss Hideko
to kindly allow her maid Tamako
to be sent to his Lordship
for a brief errand.
Did you call for me, milord?
You may enter
How you'll be an even
greater thief than your mum
Who believes the talk
of a swindler?
When I give the signal
"fully ripe",
Then l'll gobble her up
to the pit.
She's so naive,
even if a man pulls on her nipples
she won't know what he wants
So it's yourjob to tell her
that everything
is because of me
"Oh my,
since the Count arrived
your toenails
are growing much faster!
That sort of thing, all right?
Here, a gift
Oh, he's so thoughtful!
That'// be mine when
she goes to the madhouse
It pains my heart
to see this poor girl
Have you ever seen
sapphires so blue?
Let's take a look
This isn't a sapphire
it's blue spinel.
lt's all right, lVliss.
Spinels are expensive too
Oh, my Auntie... I mean
Lady lVlinami taught me
But it's fine!
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart
Is that so?
has anything been this pretty?
I 'd like to show her to
the people at home.
Probably this?
lVlesmerising!
S...Spellbindingly beautiful!
He 's shameless
B...b...beautiful!
I...I...I'm flummoxed
in your presence!
If you stutter like that
and make your face go red
those uppity bitches
will feel superior,
You try it
One, two, three!
The Count kept pushing
wine on me.
lt's suffocating.
How do ladies wear such things?
lVliss, you're killing me!
Dressed up,
you look like a lady, too
I think I know
what the Count meant
Your face
Each night in bed
I think of your face
Don't be silly, lVliss
Ladies truly are
the dolls of maids
All these buttons
are for my amusement.
lfl undo the buttons
and pull out the cords
then, the sweet things within
those sweet and soft things
lf/ were stil/ a pickpocket
l'd slip my hand inside...
lVliss, are you truly
going to marry your uncle?
That's what he raised me for,
knowing he'd need my fortune
There's a famous collector
in France.
He’ll be putting his entire
library up for auction.
The gold mine's proceeds
won't cover the cost.
If it were me, l'd sell books
to buy gold, not the opposite
For now,
the Lady needn 't go read
to the sick fuck
who wants to marry
his wife 's niece.
Instead the fake Count goes to
the Library to make fake books.
The Lady waits for her
2 o'c/ock art class,
and waits
Poor girl,
losing her heart to a fake
Please, Count!
Sorry to be late
lt's no matter
lVlaybe I need more practice
to give it dimensionality?
Dimensionality... perhaps
Nonetheless, you have a vision
that transcends mere skill.
As if you see directly
into an object's essence
I hesitate to stand before you
for fear that you might
read my thoughts.
That's enough for today
Almost fully ripe
A/ready?
Damn
Do you know what?
Since the Count arrived,
your cheeks have grown flushed
Have they?
When I was a baby, at a
big house, she was hanged
Well, pretty much
Still, while alive
she hugged you a lot?
I\lly mother died
giving birth to me
So it's as if
I strangled her myself
I wish l'd never been born
No baby is ever guilty
of being born.
If your mother thought you
could understand
this is what she'd have said
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying
That she had no regrets
Your mother stole
a thousand times,
Did she cry?
She laughed
Said she was lucky
to have you before dying
That she had no regrets
Wait here a moment, lVliss
l'll go pick mushrooms
We'll have mushroom stew
tonight, you like that.
l'll go with you
l'll be quick
Before it rains
Good girl
What a coincidence
Indeed
IVlay I sit by you?
The lady sits, shy and trembling
The gentleman is persistent.
The perceptive maid
has stepped out for a moment.
All is well, Sookee
Everyone's performing
their roles so damned wel/
Fucking hell
You know S€I"\/HDTS
can't use this entrance!
Hey!
I wish I 'd never come here
It was wrong to come
Tamako, you brought
watercolours, right?
Of course, milord!
Watercolour paints and brushes
Go and get the oils
A day like this demands oils, yes!
A blackout!
Bring a lantern
Yes, ma 'am
I need to think
I need to become rich
sail off to a distant harbouh
eat food I scarcely recognise
buy my HI/ of
glittering baub/es, and
not think of Hideko
Never think of Hideko
I returned and you didn't
even come to me?
You know how hard it is
to do those readings?
IVlust I remove makeup and
change clothes all by myself?
I feel a nightmare coming
Sleep here.
He proposed to me
Next full moon
when my uncle visits his mine
he wants to elope to Japan.
What did you say?
I said I wasn't sure
l'm scared
Of your uncle's anger?
Of the Count
What's to be scared of?
He's so kind.
I don't know, Ijust feel it
Like the reflex of pulling
your hand from a flame.
Tell me
Pardon?
I mean after getting married
at night...
How would I know?
l'm practically a child
With no mother
No one hereto..
Firs
I guess we'd kiss?
What the hell
I 'll show her one thing then
put her to bed.
Poor thing
alone in a strange country,
reading those useless books
without /earning
a single useful skill
Why does the candy
taste different?
The bitter turned souh
the sour turned sweet,
the sweet turned savoury.
How do you know all this?
You must have experience?
I\lly friend Kutan taught me
Taught you?
In words?
Yes, only in words
So this is how it feels
That's what you will
feel for the Count.
The Count, truly
He won't think
he's making love to a corpse?
You know about my
cold hands and feet.
Really?
Here
Feels just fine
You like it?
l'm sure he'll want
to do this too.
And then
lt's so cute
If the Count sees this
Will he really be
so tender as this?
Of course
And he'll touch you like this
And like this
Keep doing it
like the Count would
And this is what he'll say
lt's so soft, warm
wet, and
s...s...spellbindingly beautiful!
Okju
Hideko
Mummy.
Daddy.
Now, the model must stay still
Okju
Hideko
- Wait.
_ _ .doesn 't like it,
you damned scoundre/I
Stop it!
I can't do this
Come here, Tamako
Find some otherjob to do
You catch my meaning?
I've no otherjob to do
Myjob is to
look after the Lady
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's fully ripe! Fully ripe!
If I miss this fortnight
l'm finished!
Can you feel it?
How much I want it?
you think l'll let you
fuck it up, you bitch?
Shall I tell the Lady you're
nothing but a lowly pickpocket?
Fine, l'll have something
to tell her too.
That you’re nothing but the son of
a lowly Korean farmhand and shaman
Boksun raising babies with her
bad back, and those two halfvvits
How will they feel if
you go home empty-handed?
Want to shit
on your mother's legend?
You should go home in glory
So don't push Hideko too hard
She's got no one
on this earth.
If you frighten her,
she'll close up hard as a clam
And please
Don't ever again put my hand
on your tinyjoke of a cock.
Oh my
Your toenails have grown faster since
the Count arrived.
How curious
Miss, doesn't it bother you
not to know?
How many ships sail
on the wide sea...
People leaving,
people returning
those saying farewell
or welcome back.
The hill beyond the manor?
I could be content here
if you were with me.
You're fortunate, Miss
The man who loves you
has the power to protect you
That's rare
But l'm not sure
if I love him.
You do love him
How do you know?
Turn in your sleep and sigh
Even if I say I don't love him
if I say that
I love someone else
Do you still want me
to marry him?
You will love him
Miss!
In the end,
Hideko accepted the proposal,
provided that I come to Japan too
nodded his head
On the day her Uncle left
to visit his mine,
the Count pretended to go back
to Japan, and hid nearby.
You'll have a week of freedom
but always remember
the basement.
Miss!
Thank you for travelling
on our ferry today.
Finally we're going home
lt's been three years
To not steal
To not commit adultery
To not lie
Spider thread pulled
into strings
Strumming makes
a zither sing
Thousand woes
Under the blue sky
Only the crows cry
Excuse me
Sorry
The Count paid the innkeeper to spy
on us, afraid we might run off
Why get dressed?
I've nothing to do any\/vay
Things are moving too slowly.
I fear Hideko might
truly go mad.
Shall we play 'maid
like before?
From morning to night
we see no sign of the Count.
Certifying the marriage and
converting the inheritance to cash
You plucked the flower
now re-plant it.
What do you want?
Hurry up and throw her
into the madhouse!
A week here
Then Hnally.
This way
Who is that person?
The Countess Lady Fujiwara
Her maiden name was
Izumi Hideko.
And who might you be?
I am the Lady's handmaiden
Then, what kind of treatment
do you believe
your Lady requires?
where no one can harm her,
and where she can do no harm
Just a few tests, then let's have
lamb chops at the Peace Hotel.
Almost there
Good work.
Don't be frightened
Good day, Countess
Do you remember me?
Countess?
What is this?
We mean you no harm, Countess
We're going to look after you
You've got the wrong person
She is the Countess.
Tell them, Your Lordship!
She still believes
she's a Korean handmaiden
lt's because
her nanny was Korean
Let go of me,
you filthy bitches!
We do not use such language here
your Ladyship.
Miss!
If it's any help
this is from her mammy,
and she used to cherish it
Such a considerate maid
I tel/ you, right from
the start Miss Izumi Hideko
had always been
Miss!
l'm not a rotten bitch!
No! No!
Put it in your mouth, Hideko
Hold out your hand
Next time you feel
like talking back,
remember the taste
of this metal bead.
You'll sleep alone from tonight
All right?
Please give me a light
We've been ordered to save oil
You little brat
Speak Japanese!
In there is a man
the size of an ogre
who can't stand the sound
of girls screaming.
And then?
He'll smother you
with his giant body
So you can't make a sound
Aunt
|V|y, my
Scaring a little girl like that
Am I pretty too?
Look closely
to my big sister
DHV
Night
Man
Woman
Eye
Nose
Mouth
HI'
Shoulder
Nipple
Navel
Eye
Nose
Mouth
HI'
Shoulder
Nipple
Navel
Penis
P...penis
You think if you speak Korean
I won't understand?
I was going a bit crazy,
so I made them crazy too
When Mrs. Sasaki
looked as crazy as me
life was more bearable
I know you are a bit insane
It runs in your mother's family
That's why l'm training you
To set your mind right
Established by
the rational Germans
it's very effective
in treating lunacy
They dig holes in the dirt
put a patient in each one
and put lids on top
If patients improve
they get a leash,
so they can crawl
around like dogs.
The cherry tree that came
with me on the ship from Japan
bloomed twice
"When Jinlian finally
took off her clothes,
Ximen-Qing-examined
her-Jade-Gate...
to-find-it-hairless-white-as-snow
and-smooth-as-jade..."
You must pause between words
Don't read like a dog
lapping at his plate!
Listen to your aunt read
"When Jinlian finally
took off her clothes,
Ximen Qing examined
her Jade Gate,
Discovering the Secret Well
to find it hairless
white as snow,
and smooth as jade
and soft as silk
Once he drew apart
the curtains of flesh,
and on fold upon fold
of the red velvet interior
beads of dew were forming
Its centre was dark and void
yet as if it had its own life
it twitched and twitched
Everyone wanted to cut it down
but my uncle refused.
He said this tree from Mt. Fuji
had absorbed my aunt's soul.
The servants whispered it was
due to the tree's high cost,
You can tel/
from the cherry blossoms
which turned brighter
and bloomed longer.
Tell me, Juliette
Do you wish this impetuous
young knight to save you?
Now
my brave knight
Oh, it's a new face!
Now
my brave knight
what do you feel?
I pity the poor woman
I wish to lick her and lick her
caress her and caress her.
If you pity her so
why not take her place
and let her whip you?
The duchess raised the whip
high in the air, and then...
And again
If she could be yours
for ten minutes,
what would you give
in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires
Anything in this whole wide world
Once the duke untied me
I sat on the chair
pulled her to me,
and slid my cock
into her cunt.
Oh, Juliette, Juliette
As I felt the duke approach
from behind,
a rope slithered
around my neck
The duke slowly
tightened the rope
I pulled the swirling
currents of her hair.
Then the duke spoke
The ten minutes are almost up
Slowly, my dear
said the Duchess
I haven't yet
fully savoured his pain
No, the knight cried
don't stop!
in the midst of this pain
Is it Sade?
lt's Sade-esque
Believed to be the same Japanese
man who wrote 'The Lizard Skin'.
Acquired from a Japanese sailor
on a ship from Hamburg.
Can you imagine myjoy when
after such a journey, it sat
on my shelf with its brothers?
These are the babes
to whom I feel the most affection
It used to contain an elaborate
monochrome woodcut illustration
but as you can see
So unfortunate
If that were intact,
you could've named your price
The author felt words alone could
not fully describe the positions,
and so included an illustration
In that regard,
before we start the bidding
Hideko!
'Pain is a Garment
Beautiful!
See you again
Yes, thank you
Today's reading was outstanding
Especially the puppet!
There was a time when
Imagine the torment
of having so many women
make advances on me
when I couldn't afford to
buy them a glass of Burgundy
Do the women here
advance on you?
I look at women's eyes
Only the eyes
They turn their gaze away
but then they always look back
If I were to slide under
someone's covers tonight
only one woman here
would refuse me.
Does that include Mrs. Sasaki?
You left her to marry
a Japanese woman.
But the S€I"\/HDTS tell me
you still share a bed with her
You went so far as to
abandon your wife,
why this urge
to become Japanese?
Because Korea is ugly
Some Japanese say
Japan is ugly,
and Korea is beautiful
Beauty is cruel by nature
Korea is soft, slow, dull
and therefore hopeless
Does it include Mrs. Sasaki?
If I gave her the right signal
she'd knock on my door
without her unden/vear.
My thoughts exactly
Then who is it?
The one who would deny you?
I heard you own
the highest quality
antique bookmaking tools
of East and West,
but I don't see them here?
Who would deny you?
I met Hideko's eyes by chance
but she didn't look away.
Indeed it was I
who shifted my gaze
Will she make an appearance
in your lewd dreams tonight?
Even if honoured
with such a visit,
I don't think I could consummate
Because her body
would be as cold as waterfowl
The result of long training
I heard you are engaged to her
If l'm not mistaken,
you are yet to have intercourse?
Her eyes have no desire
It means her soul
is dead inside.
You should go easy
on her training,
unless you enjoy
making love to a corpse
My particular way
of possessing beauty
Hideko too must have
received painting lessons?
I was too occupied teaching
her to read with correct diction
Dear me!
In England, where I studied
all ladies were expected to produce
vibrant colour and graceful lines,
even in the less noble families
A phone call, sir
At this hour?
lt's the Iwamura Bookstore
Is that so?
Excuse me a moment
You are mesmerising
when they wish to touch
a lady's breasts.
l'm familiar with
Western conversational etiquette
I do a bit of reading
you know.
There was no calculation
in what I said.
It was a reflex, like pulling
one's hand from a flame.
l'm no flame
l'm cold as waterfowl
your Lordship.
He will return soon
Mr. Iwamura only called
with a frivolous inquiry,
at my request
There's an issue regarding
your future you should know
l'll wait by the stone lamp
at midnight.
That Iwamura is a real fool
My maid is asleep
in the room next door
I don't fancy being in
scandalous rumours with you
I saw Junko go to the
ser\/ants' quarters with her pillow
Consider your reputation
as a nobleman.
l'm no nobleman
l'm not even Japanese
Think it was easy for a Korean
farmhand's son to reach here?
Fifteen hard years in Japan
before hearing about you.
Another three years to prepare
I studied bookmaking
and learned to paint forgeries
All so that I could meet you
To seduce and marry you
to possess your
father's inheritance
and then probably
to get rid of you.
But I knew as soon as I met you
For a man to seduce you
would be...
impossible
So in place of seduction,
I decided to propose a deal
Most marriages are prison
but this one will free you.
l'll rescue you from here
take you far away,
and give you freedom
Of course,
we'll split the money
Nonsense
Marrying an old man with a black
tongue at your tender age makes sense?
I won't marry anyone
What have you in mind?
That's not proper
There's no beauty in that
If you kill yourself,
what of your fortune?
So he can buy 10 little girls
and teach them to read books?
My uncle will find us somehow
Uncle
The basement?
It says here
when people are hanged
and her bottom was clean
Want to go somewhere nice?
l'll tell you in detail
what I did to your aunt
after I caught her
running away.
So don't you ever think
of running, understood?
But if I ever
end up there again
Highly concentrated opium
Three drops will make you
sleep all day.
Five drops will
knock down a horse
If you crave death
within five minutes
drink it all
If you carry this, he can never
take you to the basement.
At least not alive
It'll be my wedding gift to you
lt's more expensive than jewels
Bring a girl to be my maid. One who
could disappear and not be missed.
If a bit dense, all the better
We'll send her to a madhouse
under my name.
I can find you a new maid
but what do we do
aboutJunko?
You really think l'm prettier
than Miss Hideko?
Sure, Hideko's pretty
and you're pretty.
What?
You speak Korean?
You know
I learned it
You are just mesmerising
Oh my gosh!
You little tart!
I can't!
Forget this wretched place
Come live with me!
Oh, fucking hell!
Fucking hell?
Fucking hell
Naive and a bit foolish
Mother!
Show Sookee your clothes and
jewellery at every opportunity.
The material greed she got from her
mother will make her more gullible.
P.S. Don 't worry if she reads this
/etteh she's totally illiterate.
Countess Fujiwara Hideko
What's with your foot?
Who took Tamako's shoe?
If she ever runs away
because of one of you
l'll strip you all naked
and throw you out!
Fucking hell
All smooth
You like the scent?
Want to come in?
Pardon?
No need to be
ashamed at all
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart
Is that so?
Returning the earrings
you loaned me.
A woman might wager her fate
on such an exquisite pair.
I 'm sure that Sookee
will try her very best
in order to see herself
wearing these in the mirror.
l'll tel/ you how to keep her
from getting suspicious.
Keep her busy until
the day of the wedding
on making you
fall in love with me
In other words, don 't fall
in love with me so easily.
How did your mum die?
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying
That she had no regrets
ls this the companionship
they write about in books?
Men are disgusting
What's on my mind?
You don't really believe
that I crave your body?
You do!
You read too many
of those books.
If there's one thing
l'm after, Miss...
lt's not your eyes,
your hands or ass
it's your money, only that
Of all that you have
money is the best.
Feels great being so rude
to a noble lady.
What's with her?
Why does she stomp her feet,
expressing her angeh
sit up in the middle
of the night and sigh?
Every time she sees the Count,
her eyes seem to say...
I despise you
Try to bear it. Only if she sees this
will she believe the proposal.
Think of me as that puppet,
and l'll imagine another woman
What woman?
The duchess Juliette
Lady!
Milord!
Lady
Jinlian could not fathom
their depths.
Knowing this, Lady Sun
gave Jinlian four
small silver balls.
These are 'minling
or 'bells of passion
Place two in
the lady's Jade Gate
and the other two in yours
Spread your legs apart
and like two scissors
When the lips below
rub against each another
youWlhear
a clear ringing sound
A blackout!
Bring a lantern!
Yes, sir!
'The Sound of Bells
on a Wind/ess Night
When do I put this in?
asked Jinlian.
Does the lady breathe deeply
and swallow hard?
Does she whisper sweetly
in your ear,
and kiss you?
and caress your nipples?
Does her secret part
become slippery
as she gently bites
your shoulder?
Then, put in the bells
Amazing!
- Indeed!
lt's so cute
If the Count sees this
Will he really be
so tender as this?
Of course
And he'll touch you like this
And like this
Tamako, keep doing it
Like the Count would
The Count
He'll go crazy over this
And this is what he'll say
lt's so soft, warm
wet, and...
s...s...spellbindingly beautiful!
Shall I teach you more, Miss?
Yes
Teach me everything
I wish that I had breast milk
so I could feed you.
Do you like it when I do this?
Can you promise
that you won't betray me?
Iilnever
FIGVSI'
SVSI'
Miss, how could such an innocent
You must be a natural
Stop!
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's got no one
on this earth.
You see?
If you don't give the impression
you want this marriage,
she may throw another fit
and refuse to go fon/vard.
I can't do it
What?
I want to quit
What's with you all today?
You feel sorry for her?
What is it with women?
You know what that poor
Sookee said about your Ladyship?
That you're too dense to get it
if someone pulls on your nipples
That she was nice out of pity
but you ate it up.
That you were so gullible!
That naive ser\/ant's face
If I say that
I love someone else
Me, who has no one
on this earth...
Do you still want me
to marry him?
Yes
Miss!
I wish l'd never been born
Let go
Miss, l'm sorry!
Let go!
l'm sorry, Miss!
Don't die
l'm sorry
What are you sorry about?
I tried to trick you into
marrying that bastard.
I was going to put you
in a madhouse and run off
Don't die.
Don't get married, Miss!
Sookee,
are you worried about me?
l'm worried about you
How do you know my name?
You think you're tricking me?
You're the one being tricked
You're the one
bound for the madhouse
I was going to lock you up
in there under my name,
then l'd become you
and run far away, with him
I won't say sorry,
since you tried to trick me too
That fucking son of a bitch!
Oh, sorry Miss!
'I hope this letter Hnds you wel/
This is Sookee.
I 'm writing to inform you
of a change in plans.
I decided to team up
with the Lady Hideko
As such, l'm now in need
of all your help.
Always remember
the basement.
Want to go somewhere nice?
You didn't teach me
to read Japanese.
Did that bastard draw this?
Is this what you've been reading
to that dirty old man
and those gentlemen?
The daughter of
a legendary thief
who sewed winter coats
out of sto/en purses.
Herself a thief
pickpocket, swind/er.
The saviour who came to
tear my life apart.
My Tamako
My Sookee
You scoundrel!
Let go of me,
you filthy bitches!
Miss!
Let go!
l'm hungry
The first month, I ordered
a slim herringbone suit.
PART THREE
The next month, I wore it to
dine at the Imperial Hotel.
Some Englishmen who frequented
the brothel recognised me.
I thought they'd call the
maitre d' and kick me out
but what do you know?
They were amused
l'd spend a month's pay
on one dignified meal
They started calling me 'Count
Frankly, l'm not that
interested in money itself
What I desire is
how shall I put it.
Something like that
Fourteen hours by train
from Vladivostok
is the summer home of a
genuine Russian noble family
Shall we marry there?
That my wife Fujiwara Hideko
has died.
I doubt Sookee would want
to live there very long.
Fuck!
I arranged it with
a photography studio
We'll replace this with
your photograph.
From tomorrow,
we'll give Sookee a new life
l'm glad
Marry me once again
This time as Nam Sookee
You want another wedding night?
I think I like you... slightly
Poor Sookee,
in a place like that
all by herself
Did such a thought
ever cross your mind?
Not at all.
Why should I pity her?
Where I come from,
it's illegal to be naive
Where you come from, it's not naive
to fall in love with a business partner?
Of course. lt's illegal
So even if my love for you
leads me to ruin,
don't pity me
Love?
What does a crook
know about love?
Fire!
C...c...come this way!
This way!
Because you desired me
and overcame
all obstacles to reach me
I have been born anew
it's true.
l'm grateful for that
l'll allow a kiss
Why hot?
ldon%Hke
kisses with conditions
I never learned
how to stop half\/vay
After this l'll thrust in deep
to your navel.
Please do that
Those aren't the eyes
of one who wants it.
You know you can't
deceive me in such matters
If I could be yours
for ten minutes,
what would you give
in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires
Anything in this whole wide world
You'll become a
completely new woman
It won't hurt.
You know from those books?
In truth, women feel
the greatest pleasure
when taken by force
Now l'm going to
rip your unden/vear
Would you fetch those for me?
Respected Uncle
it always pained me
to see you straining
to speak flawless Japanese
before the Count from Nagoya
and even to quiver your voice
like a nobleman.
So I 'm happy to inform you
that you no longer need do so
That man is the son
of a Korean farmhand
Oh, did my gift arrive safely?
I 'm afraid that in rea/ life
no woman feels pleasure
at being taken by force.
I fee/ "s/ight/y" grateful
You wished to see
my bookmaking tools?
Don't just look,
experience them for yourself
l'll choose five books
that I cherish...
Let's see
Firs
Confessions of a Whip
The Lizard Skin
'Decadent Girls
Who Sell Lingerie
May I please
smoke a cigarette, sir?
'Bells and Balls
The Mortician's Bedroom
How could you let
a little girl fool you?
But don 't worry.
I 'll catch them for you soon
I arranged so that no two girls
travelling together can leave Kobe
Please change the destination
to Shanghai.
Changing two tickets,
from Vladivostok to Shanghai
Yes, that's correct
Show me your passports
Miss Nam Sookee?
Mr. Go Pan-dol?
You need to pay
an additional 3 yen
Aii right
l'm just an old man
who likes dirty stories
Even listening to the same story
people imagine different things.
Peering into each of
those fantasies
was this old man's
humble recreation.
What to do,
now that it's all over?
You should at least
tell me your story.
How did that bitch Hideko taste?
Right, right
You have that silly
penchant for cigarettes?
So how was Hideko?
You have no windows here?
Sookee could be listening in
Let's do our best.
What's this?
So, where did you touch first?
Her face ?
Her breasts?
Was it soft?
Did it tighten up?
Did it have many wrinkles?
Was it sufficiently wet?
The viscosity and transparency
of her vaginal secretion?
Please, one more cigarette, sir
Spider thread pulled
into strings...
I dare say no book
has ever described
such a ferocious wedding night.
I thought I heard
a nightingale sing
And... the clean
bright crimson blood!
Thus the Lady
became my wife
Coy one moment,
bold the next...
But how was she coy
how was she bold,
tell it to me in detail!
A story is all about the journey
You should know
Did she resist?
So did you pinch her ass
as punishment?
Or did she spit at you
in contempt?
Or else
Did she beg you to do it?
Like the lady in
The Widow's Lapdog?
How dare you!
Hideko is my wife
What kind of scoundrel rattles on
about his wedding night!
lt's odd
Your smoke
lt's cold, blue
and strangely beautiful
You too have become
soft, slow and dull.
Mercury is most deadly
in its gaseous state.
At least I will die
with my cock intact
I hear a sound
in the distance
that sounds like
the steps of my love
An echo that
makes my heart
skip a beat
But I wait
all through the night
and my love never
comes to me
There is no end
to the heartache
that grips me
in this hour
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love
Waiting for
the footsteps of
But then in
my waiting heart
suddenly
happiness overflows
There you are
in the distance
coming to me
Filled with dreams
of a new life
H//ed with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
flowers start to bloom
Come my /oven
come to me
Let's dream of
happy times
like long ago
H//ed with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
flowers start to bloom
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love
Waiting for
the footsteps of