So much torque,
the chassis twisted coming off the line.
Barely kept her on the track.
-So, what's your best time?
-I've never driven her.
Why not?
It scares the shit out of me.
That's my dad.
He was coming up
in the pro stock-car circuit.
Last race of the season.
A guy named Kenny Linder
came up from inside, in the final turn.
He clipped his bumper
and put him into the wall at 120.
I watched my dad burn to death.
I remembered hearing him scream.
But the people that were there
said he had died before the tanks blew.
They said it was me who was screaming.
I saw Linder about a week later.
I had a wrench, and I hit him.
And I didn't intend to keep hitting him,
but when I finished, I couldn't lift my arm.
He's a janitor at a high school.
He has to take the bus to work every day.
And they banned me
from the tracks for life.
I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters.
Not the mortgage, not the store...
...not my team and all their bullshit.
For those 10 seconds or less...
...I'm free.
So, how is it, anyways,
that the gang came to be?
-What?
-The gang.
The gang?
No, they don't call themselves a gang.
-What do they call themselves?
-They're a team.
-They call themselves a team.
-All right. How did the team come to be?
Well, that's a whole lot of history.
-I've got time.
-Okay. Vince grew up with my brother.
Actually, he didn't ever actually grow up,
as you can tell.
But they were friends as kids.
And Letty, she just lived down the street.
Always into cars, though.
Ever since she was, like, 10 years old.
So, naturally, you know,
my brother always had her attention.
-And then she turned 16--
-And then she had Dom's attention.
Yeah. It's funny how that works, isn't it?
Yeah.
How does Jesse fit into the whole thing?
Jesse. Well, Jesse and Leon just sort of
showed up one night and never, ever left.
It's just the way my brother is, you know.
Dom's like....
He's like gravity.
Everything just gets pulled to him.
Even you.
No.
The only thing that pulled me in was you.
Being friends with your brother
is just a bonus.
That's good.
That's good. It's nice to come first
every once in a while.
Want to go for a drive?
-Yeah?
-The hijackers have hit again.
Bi/kins has decided that we're gonna move
on Johnny Tran and his guys at 17:00.
Un/ess you say otherwise.
/f you agree, just say yes.
-Yeah.
-Who is that?
It's just a wrong number.
Yes, sir. Yeah, I know, but--
Yeah. Yes, sir.
Yeah. I got it.
The DVD players were purchased legally.
All we've got are a couple
of low-rent weapons charges...
...and some outstanding speeding tickets.
-So, they're out.
-Yeah.
Father bailed them out.
Is this the kind of intelligence
I can expect from you, O'Conner?
-You're gonna put this on me?
-I can put it on whoever I want to.
-Perks of the job.
-No, you can't put this on me--
No, wait a minute. Let me tell you.
I don't care if you have to aim at someone
and blow your cover to smithereens.
You've got 36 hours to crack this bastard...
...or you might want to think
about another career.
It's Toretto, Brian.
It always has been Toretto.
Tran and Hector are....
They're just fumes.
I know you've been lying to me.
My question is this:
Have you been lying to yourself
because you can't see past Mia?
He won't go back to prison.
Well, that's a choice
he's going to have to make.
There's all kinds of family, Brian.
And that's a choice
you're gonna have to make.
You ready for this?
Nice car.
What's the retail on one of those?
More than you can afford, pal. Ferrari.
Smoke him.
So, what's wrong, Brian?
Nothing, man, I'm fine.
Come on. Obviously something's off.
Look, I have my good days and bad days
just like anybody else.
Brian, don't lose that cool of yours.
That's your meal ticket.
My meal ticket?
I can't pay for my own shrimp?
I got the shrimp.
No, that's one thing about me
you don't understand.
I don't take handouts.
I earn my way, every step.
I need something extra on the side,
like you.
What do you mean, like me?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-That's what I mean.
-What does that mean, like me?
-Don't try--
I'm not stupid, all right?
I know that there's no way you paid
for all that shit you got under the hood--
There's no way you paid for
what's under the hood of those cars...
...by doing tune-ups and selling groceries.
Whatever it is you're in on,
I want in on it, too.
-Well, what is this?
-Read it.
-What is this for?
-It's directions.
To Race Wars.
We'll see how you go.
Then we'll talk.
-How's it going?
-What's up?
-Welcome to Race Wars.
-Great. Thanks a lot.
Baby. Hey, baby.
You should watch from the side.
I wouldn't want to get exhaust
on that pretty face.
-Put your money where your mouth is.
-I'll race you for that sweet little ass.
You want ass,
why don't you hit Hollywood Boulevard?
You want an adrenaline rush,
it'll be two large.
Right here. Right now.
What's it gonna be?
You got it.
"Another one bites the dust"
Come on. What you got?
See ya.
-What's up?
-Hey, what's up, Jesse?
What's in your hand?
Throwing down the pink slip, just like you.
-The pink slip to what? The Jetta?
-Yeah.
-You can't bet your dad's car.
-It's all right.
I ain't losing.
This fool is running a Honda 2000.
I'll win.
That way, me and my dad can roll
when he gets out of prison. It's all good.
They're gonna throw him right back
in prison after he kills you.
You visualize the win.
Visualize the win, Jesse. I'm serious.
You got to listen to me, man.
Who are you racing?
Jesse, don't do it.
I bet you he's got more than $100,000
under the hood of that car.
Too soon, junior.
No!
Shit!
Oh, God!
Yo! Heads up, bro. We got problems.
-What?
-Jesse.
Where's Jesse going?
-He just raced Tran for slips.
-Oh, shit.
-Where's he going?
-He went to the car wash.
Whatever. Go fetch my car.
Go fetch your car?
We're not on your block.
You better watch who you talk to like that.
Toretto!
SWAT came into my house...
...disrespected my whole family,
because somebody narked me out.
And you know what? It was you!
Get off of him, man.
Dom, chill out, man. Come on!
I never narked on nobody!
Mia.
I have respected you
and I haven't said shit.
Now I am asking you not to go.
-I'm doing this for both of us.
-Don't give me that crap.
You're doing this for you.
Why are you insisting on doing this?
Dom, please, just don't.
-Mia, what's going on?
-What?
-You know what I'm talking about.
-No, I don't.
You always have tears in your eyes
when Dom drives away?
What's the matter with you?
What's he racing off
in the middle of the night for?
-You know about the trucks?
-No, Brian! What trucks?
-Jesus Christ. What?
-Listen to me.
Mia, I'm a cop.
What are you talking about, Brian?
What is this?
Ever since the first time I met you,
I've been undercover.
I'm a cop.
Oh, you bastard.
You bastard.
-Mia.
-Get off of me, Brian!
Mia! Listen to me!
Everything I ever said
I felt about you was real.
I swear to God.
You have to believe me, Mia.
But this isn't about you and me.
Your brother's out there to pull a job.
We're running out of time. Those truckers
aren't laying down anymore.
Maybe they'll make it through tonight,
but every law enforcement agency...
...is coming down on them.
If you don't want anything to happen
to them...
...you have to get in that car
with me right now and help me.
Mia, you are the only person
that can help me right now.
Please, Mia. Please help me.
Civics are stashed somewhere
outside of Thermal.
They wouldn't double back,
and Highway 10 is too well patrolled.
-So, what does that leave us with?
-All this.
-Nexte/.
-This is Officer Brian O'Conner.
Serial number 34762.
I need a cell phone trace.
-Okay. What's the ce// number?
-Mia, what is it?
Come on, Mia.
She needs Dom's cell phone number now.
323-555-6439.
Thank you. Yeah, you get that?
All right, we're one man short.
Letty, I need you on the left side.
Your sister's right about this one.
This don't feel good.
-Don't do that.
-Something's wrong.
-Stop.
-We shouldn't be doing this without Jesse.
This is the mother Iode.
We've been on this for three months.
After this, it's a long vacation for everyone.
-Let's go.
-I hope so.
Listen, the other night I had a dream...
...that you and I were
on the beach in Mexico.
-Really?
-Really.
Come on. Let's make this happen.
-Leon, keep on those scanners.
-Copy that.
All right, let's go.
Okay, we traced the number
to the northbound 86.
Mi/e 114, outside Coache//a.
We'// keep the trace open, Officer.
Let me see this.
I think we're about 40 miles away.
What are you gonna do?
Okay! Go time!
We're all good.
I got nothing on the scanners.
Keep going.
Vince!
Vince, don't! Get back in!
He's got a damn shotgun! Leon!
Back off! Get him off of there!
Oh, shit!
Get me off this thing! Pull up!
Unhook yourself. Do it!
-Do it!
-I can't get--
You can do it!
Come on, Vince!
Dom! I'm pulling up to distract him!
Come on, boy!
Shot doesn't get better than this.
Son of a bitch!
Take me off here,
or I'll have to unhook the wire!
Try it again. One, two, three!
Unhook yourself!
I can't get my arm free!
-Vince, grab my hand!
-My arm!
Listen, give me your hand.
I'm gonna pull you off the rig!
Vince!
Hold on!
Give me your hand! Listen to me!
Dominic!
Shit!
-Dominic!
-Hang on!
Dom! Move out of the way.
I'm coming to get him.
Letty!
Leon!
Pull back for Letty.
Get her out of there/
I'm on it! Go!
I've got her! You get Vince off that truck.
Letty! Come on, baby.
You okay?
Oh, shit. Come on, girl, you all right?
Come on, let me look at you.
Come on. We got to go. Let's go.
Vince!
Take the wheel.
-What do you mean?
-Put your foot on the gas!
I'm gonna get him.
Put your foot on the gas!
Okay!
-Come on. Keep it steady.
-I got it!
All right, hold on, Vince.
He's having a hard time holding on.
Get me a little closer.
All right.
-Closer.
-I'm moving in.
Hold it right there!
Go!
You got to hang in here with me now!
We'll get you off. Give me your arm!
Vince, look at me! Don't let go!
Come on, Vince!
Throw this arm around me!
Vince, don't let go!
Come on, Mia. Get closer!
Mia, get closer! Come on.
Come on, Vince. Here we go!
Shit.
It's gonna be okay, Letty. I love you.
-Watch her.
-I got her.
Come on, Vince! Hang in there! Come on!
If he doesn't get to an ambulance
in 10 minutes, he's dead.
-Hold the pressure. Hold his arm up.
-I got it.
Yeah. Yeah, this is Officer Brian O'Conner.
I'm off-duty MAPD.
I need a life flight roll out right away.
My 20 is Highway 86, mile marker 147.
I got one trauma victim,
about 24 years of age.
Six-foot, maybe 200 pounds.
He's got a deep laceration to his right arm
with arterial bleeding.
And he's got a shotgun wound
close range to his left flank.
Yeah, he's going into shock!
Dom, put the gun down now!
-Move your car.
-No bullshit!
Put it down now! No more running!
I'm not running!
-Where's Leon and Letty?
-They're long gone!
Then it's over.
I didn't call the police, but don't push me!
-Put the gun down. I swear to God!
-You are the cop!
You're a cop!
Brian, I got to find Jesse before they do.
-I'm all the kid's got.
-I'll call in the plates.
PD will pick him up way before
Johnny even gets near him.
-Move your car.
-Dom, stop it! It's over. Please.
Mia, stay out of it!
Dominic, I am so sorry.
I don't know what I'm doing, Dom.
I'm so scared right now.
I don't know what's going on.
What were you thinking, man?
I don't know! I panicked! I'm sorry.
I'm scared!
I don't know what I'm doing!
Will you please help me?
Dom!
Jesse!
No, Jesse!
No, Dom, no!
Call 911. You call 911!
I used to drag here back in high school.
That railroad crossing up there
is exactly a quarter mile away from here.
On green, I'm going for it.
That's not what I had in mind.
You know what you're doing?
I owe you a 10-second car.
I live my life a quarter mile at a time.
Nothing else matters.
For those 10 seconds or less...
...i'm free.