Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
There's only one here.
They were forged as a pair.
We'll keep looking for it.
It must be buried elsewhere.
Elsewhere?
Like where?
Kamala! Are you doing
your homework, beta?
Yeah! Science!
Boom!
Enter, Kamala Khan.
Ready for...
Captain Marvel.
She needs my help.
Shine on, baby.
Why are hands so hard to draw?
Okay, Ms. Marvel arrives,
and just in time...
...'cause even the Avengers need backup,
ya know?
Wham! Kapow!
This is my chance!
Pow!
Boom!
Not bad, kid.
What's your name?
Ms. Marvel.
Dude.
Twinsies!
Hey, you wanna go party with the Avengers?
Uh... Yeah!
Can you fly?
No, but I can do this!
Kamala! Don't make me come up there!
-That does not sound like science to me.
-Okay.
You don't remember anything?
I see...
flashes.
Little moments.
If I could just piece together
what happened that morning...
maybe it'll all make sense.
You stole me from my home,
my family, my friends.
Lieutenant Trouble.
-Higher, further, faster, baby.
-That's right.
Tell the Supreme Intelligence
that I'm coming to end it.
The war, the lies.
All of it.
You can't do this.
I'll be back before you know it.
I could fly up and meet you halfway.
Only if you learn to glow
like your Auntie Carol.
Come here, Goosey.
Incoming call from Nick Fury.
You expecting a call?
Maybe we just send it to voice mail.
Nick Fury...
my favorite one-eyed man of intrigue.
Carol Danvers.
Prodigal child of the Milky Way.
How goes it out there?
Thriving.
What the hell was that?
-Goose?
-Yeah.
What about you?
How are you doing?
What do you know about the surge
in the jump point system a few hours ago?
I didn't notice anything unusual.
I'll take a look now.
It rattled the whole system.
We're trying to get a handle on
what happened.
The entire network was affected?
Yeah. End to end.
Thankfully, our neural network team...
was able to trace the origin back to
MB-418.
-You're in the neighborhood, right?
-Yeah.
Can you check it out?
-I'm on it.
-Appreciate you.
Monica and her team
will send more intel as they acquire it.
Monica?
What's she doing there?
I thought that she was on Earth.
-Is she okay?
-Yeah.
And she's not that
little kid you remember.
So, do we think that
we can finish this before dinner?
Yeah. I don't think we're gonna fix it
in time to get a reading
on the jump point.
But I do know someone with superpowers
who could.
Oh.
Fine. I'll go.
You guys head in
and check the status of the network.
We've gotta find this damage
and see if we can reverse it.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Fury...
I think I found something.
Communications override.
Captain Rambeau. Spacewalk.
Connected.
Rambeau...
what the hell are you doin'?
Seems the surge has had
some residual effect on the jump point.
I'm gonna get you some readings, Fury.
Mon...
-Hello?
-Monica.
Hello?
Was that Monica?
-Aunt Carol?
-Fury...
-was that Monica?
-Why, you wanna talk to her?
I don't think I'm in the best...
position to... I... I don't...
I don't wanna...
Look...
I don't wanna talk to her like this.
-Not after all this time.
-You know...
-eventually you're gonna have to talk to her.
-I know.
I know, but...
let's save the family reunions
till I'm back inside.
I think I found the source of the surge.
What are you seeing?
It's a jump point,
but it's not closing. Like...
it's stuck.
Danvers.
Danvers!
The jump point's still leaking energy.
-Captain Rambeau?
-Hello?
-Monica.
Beautiful.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
Stop spinning, stop spinning, stop spinning,
please!
It's Nick Fury! Hey!
How did you... Oh, wow.
I'm Kamala Khan.
No, sorry, I'm Ms. Marvel, actually.
But I'm from Jersey City and I...
Oh, no, I don't have my mask on.
Is this an Avengers test?
Who the hell are you?
Hi.
Really good living room.
-Kamala?
What did you do to me?
-What is Dar-Benn doing?
-It's too late.
The Supremor's already on Tarnax.
You can't stop this.
Watch me.
Fury. It's the Kree.
They're going after the Skrulls on Tarnax.
Now, hold on.
Do not go in swinging.
-This is a peace and reconciliation tour.
-Fury.
-I got this.
-Carol...
So, I switched with someone
named Kamala Khan?
Yeah.
She seemed to be as confused as you are.
Well, there's nothing in her power-set
about teleportation.
Enough about her.
I wanna know what happened
to you on MB-418.
Yes, sir.
Let me preface this by saying
I'm not really sure. But...
I did not break my closet door, okay?
I was in space.
-Oh, so it broke itself?
-No, no, no. See, I disappeared.
So maybe Captain Marvel broke it.
-What?
-Yes, your friend, Captain Marvel.
She was walking up and down
our living room...
and now you come back...
-waltzing in with no apologies.
-I'm sorry, Captain Marvel was in our house?
Is Captain Marvel pressuring you in any way?
Look, I understand that she's
an important figure and all that...
but you don't have to do as she says.
No, no, they're clearly working together.
-Look at her face. Look at her smile.
-Aamir, stop it.
-She's being super secretive as always.
-Aamir, stop picking on your sister.
-Look at her.
-Muneeba.
Kamala, are you lying again?
-Just tell me if you're involved or...
-My daughter has said she's not lying.
-Kamala.
-Looks like she's having...
-so much fun.
-Muneeba...
-She's bad at keeping secrets.
-Oh, my God! It's happening!
Approaching Tarnax.
Warning.
Kree ship detected.
This is not what we agreed, Dar-Benn.
Supremor Dar-Benn.
The Skrull...
have been scattered
to every corner of the universe.
Made refugees wherever we go, and still...
we came into these negotiations
in good faith.
I hear you, Dro'ge.
I, perhaps more than anyone, understand what
you and your people have been through.
After my predecessor was destroyed...
heretics rose up to fill the void.
The Civil War has polluted our skies.
My people cannot breathe.
Our sun is dying.
Hala is out of time.
I hope we can rebuild together.
So much so that I'm willing
to put our ancient animosities behind us.
And give you a chance to protect your people.
To stop running.
The Skrull will take their rightful place
in the Kree Empire.
And I will aid in their relocation.
-Relocation?
-What?
-What is the meaning of this?
I would hate for your people to suffocate
when I strip the atmosphere.
It's the Annihilator!
Oh, my God!
-What the hell is going on?
-Yes, what the hell is going on?
I was on some freaky spaceship
and then I teleported here.
I don't know if that's my new power.
-And then this freaking cat ate a man.
-How can a cat eat a man, Kamala?
I don't know. It has tentacles...
-and it ate a man.
-What tentacles, Kamala?
-I don't know.
-Where are the tentacles?
It comes out of his mouth,
and they're...
-Oh, my God!
-Oh!
Oh, my God,
it's happening again!
-Oh, no, no, no.
-Kamala, who are they?
Please run.
How did you get here,
and how're you involved in this?
-The Kree jury-rigged a wormhole on MB-418.
-You mean like a jump point?
-I don't know. But I touched it and then I...
-Why'd you do that?
Because it was glowing and mysterious.
Okay, new rule, no more touching shit.
Especially glowing, mysterious shit.
Okay, I'm feeling a lot of
negative energy from you...
and I don't like it. That's not the point.
The point is...
is that it was siphoning off
the atmosphere. And it did this!
Scissors beat paper.
Fury! There was, like,
energy that went around my hand. Focus.
Okay, maybe if I do this.
Annihilator.
I don't like that name.
-Friends of yours?
-Hi.
Annihilator!
Aamir, get him!
Get him! Hit him!
Yusuf!
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Kamala, are you okay?
Fury!
I think I'm getting teleported whenever I
channel any kind of radiant...
I think I switch when I use my powers.
Strong theory.
Our tests keep generating the same result.
With each new jump point,
this band becomes more unstable.
I strongly suggest we wait
for the second band.
Oi.
Hi, again.
So sorry about earlier.
We're looking for Kamala Khan.
Did I get in?
-Is this the new iPad? I haven't seen it yet.
-They wish!
-All right. Come on, let's go.
-I know. Wait...
if this is all top secret information,
why is it on a clear case?
Well...
just... swipe it a little bit... Hi.
-Okay.
-Can you believe it? They have intel on me.
On me!
I am intel.
Look at you!
Hey, what does S.A.B.E.R. stand for?
Strategic Aerospace Biophysics...
-and Exolinguistic Response.
-That's classified.
Sorry.
"Hard Light powers,"
yes.
-"Noor..."
-Okay, but why do you have intel on her?
Is there some sort of surveillance on us?
-"Surveillance" is a strong word.
-Well, ma'am...
your daughter is the hero
that saved Jersey City.
So, of course we would have intel
on someone like her. And you're also...
-electromagnetically altered.
-What does that mean?
Oh, it just means that we both have...
light-based powers.
What's your code name?
Oh, I don't have a code name.
-We'll workshop it.
-No, thank you.
Aunt Carol...
Captain Marvel also has light-based powers.
It's probably not a coincidence.
Not to mention the two of you
came into direct contact...
with some malfunctioning jump points.
I still cannot believe that Captain Marvel
was here and I didn't even get to meet her.
You know, we're supposed to be
all, like "twinsies!" you know.
We have the same name.
I would obviously, then...
I don't know, I would just give her
the letter I wrote for her...
and we would go out for lunch,
and then it would just...
Did you say "Aunt Carol?"
I said that Captain Marvel...
can absorb light energy.
I can see it.
And you, you can turn light...
into physical matter.
Which I have never heard of.
-But my working theory...
-I could totally show you.
No!
What the...
Hi.
Nah, they don't seem related.
Whatever, Yusuf. Families are complicated.
Monica, you wanna fill Carol in
on your working theory?
Yeah.
Hi, Captain Marvel.
It is so good to see you,
Lieutenant Trouble.
You too.
And it's Captain Rambeau now.
Right. Sorry.
So, what's new?
-Where's my sister?
-Yeah.
I'm thinking that our joint exposure
to these unsteady jump points...
and our susceptibility to
electromagnetic energy...
-has temporarily entangled our world-lines.
-Yeah, that, right there.
Entanglement.
Our light powers are entangled.
So, we switch places
whenever we use them at the same time.
-Which would mean Kamala...
-When did you get powers?
I walked through
a radiation shielding barrier...
of a witch hex
and now I can manipulate and see...
all wavelengths
of the electromagnetic spectrum.
I'm very happy for you. Yeah.
-Where's our daughter?
-Yes, please. Where is Kamala?
Wherever you were.
-Where were you?
-Who's Kamala?
The third person we're switching with.
-Light powers. Teenage girl. Where were you?
-What are you doing?
-I'm trying to switch.
-Why isn't it working when I need it to work?
-Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
-Danvers, Danvers!
-Hey!
-So confused.
-Tell Kamala that her Abu is very upset.
Where are we going
and why are we going there?
-Carol!
-Carol, where you going?
-Oh, my God!
-Uh-oh!
Monica, you gotta fly.
No, no, no. I...
I mean, I know.
But technically, I haven't done that yet!
Yeah, well, you got to now...
or Kamala's not gonna graduate
from high school.
Come on! Use your core!
Oh, jeez.
Hey. Black Girl Magic.
I got you! I got you!
I got you!
Oops!
Hold on!
What is happening?
I can't hold on to you while I'm flying.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-We're gonna die!
-Hold on!
Hold on! I'm thinking, I'm thinking!
Wait, I have an idea.
Grab on to me!
This had better work!
Oh, it's cool. It's Carol.
Okay, no powers, no powers. Just...
Who are they?
They are associates of Captain Marvel.
The Annihilator is here?
Yeah, well, she was.
And then these two just sort of appeared.
What about the band?
If she's meddling, I need to strike now.
Yeah. I still can't account for the
instabilities exhibited on MB-418.
-This thing does much more than just...
-But it works?
Yes. Yes. But if you give me more time...
-I can make it safer.
-No.
No. We do it now.
Before the Annihilator appears.
What should we do about... these two?
You.
Hold that thought.
We gotta get that band off of her.
It looks like mine.
Guys!
I can't fly.
Do you guys have
a spaceship I could borrow or...
Kamala, don't talk to them.
You know my name!
The Kree came here hopeful...
-that we could build a covenant of peace.
-What have you done?
But then you sic the Annihilator on us.
Like we're vermin.
Once again,
the Skrull have betrayed the Kree.
And for that...
Carol, we gotta get these people out of here.
Emperor Dro'ge...
you need to evacuate your people now.
We have nowhere to go.
Carol, the ships...
they're not gonna make it.
Get back to the ship
and don't use your powers.
-But I can help.
-Now.
-Let's go.
-Where's Kamala?
Kamala!
No!
Let's go, let's go!
-Come on!
-Keep moving...
please, please.
-All these people, they're gonna...
-Come on, sweetie.
-No! How can you just leave them here?
-Kamala, now!
We need to save who we can.
Transmission sent.
Hey.
This peace treaty...
it was a good thing.
-It was a ruse.
-If it were...
your intervention failed.
We don't need your help anymore.
I called a friend.
She can find a safe place for you.
Is that okay?
We have no choice.
Incoming.
Are you all right?
Thank you again.
Always.
I see that you've finally
found yourself a team.
It is unintentional.
Oh, I've been
on some unintentional teams myself.
-I know, but...
-You can stand tall without standing alone.
Take it from me, Marv.
Hey.
Captain Marvel will fix this.
I promise.
Thank you.
May our next meeting be joyful.
Breathe.
Do you remember?
When the sun used to shine on Hala?
How beautiful our home was?
Before her?
Before the Annihilator.
I was there.
I heard her lies...
claiming she was there to set us free.
But when she destroyed
the Supreme Intelligence...
she destroyed the Kree.
For 30 years I have been fighting
alongside you.
Not only have I brought you peace...
but I have found a way
to return Hala to glory.
Supremor!
We need more power than that band
can provide if we're to reignite our sun.
That amount of energy...
Well, it would kill you.
If my life is the cost, so be it.
We will find the other in time, Suprem...
There is no more time.
Hala is out of time.
Need a hand?
Yeah.
Will you hand me that laser?
Three micrometres.
Wow.
So you can do that
because you walked through a witch hex?
Yep.
When I got blipped back,
they weren't sending us to space anymore.
Grounded us to investigate
earthbound anomalies.
That must have been hard.
Your mom told me that you
always dreamed of going to space.
That you had something to prove.
You said you'd be back before I knew it.
What?
When you left...
you said you'd be back before I knew it.
I meant what I said. I just,
I didn't know...
what I was getting myself into.
I didn't know how to explain
to a little girl that...
A little girl that hung on your every word.
If you knew...
I was going to come back.
I just...
There was people that needed me.
We needed you, Carol.
Hey.
I hope you don't mind.
I didn't have any other clothes.
It's totally fine.
Looks good on you.
I...
I'm really sorry...
for the way I spoke to you.
Thank you.
I know that this situation isn't ideal...
but it is actually nice...
having people on board again.
It gets pretty lonely out here.
Anytime you need company, I will be there.
I will drop everything. I will...
I will drop high school.
Don't do that.
But can we start again?
Hi, I'm Carol Danvers.
I am Kamala Khan.
But when I'm fighting crime
on the streets of Jersey City...
I go by Ms. Marvel, and I hope
that's okay, like, copyright-wise.
Because, honestly,
I never thought I'd ever get to meet you.
But now that it's happening and we're,
like, touching each other...
I've realized I should have
asked permission.
So, twinsies.
Okay. All right.
Here's what we're gonna do.
-Captain Marvel.
-You need to stop calling me that.
-I used to change your diapers.
-Oh, that was once.
And then I was told
you proceeded to vomit everywhere.
First of all...
it's my ship, so I make the game plan.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When's the last time you led a team?
As early as last week.
Goose doesn't count.
Please. You try giving Goose orders.
Oh, my God, we're a team?
-We're not... We're not a team.
-No, no, no, we're not a team.
I, Kamala Khan of Jersey City...
am on a team with Captain Marvel
and Captain Monica Rambeau...
who from this point onwards
will now be known as...
-Professor Marvel.
-Oh!
-No.
-No, no, she, she will not. But thank you.
-The Marvels.
Now that we've got that out of the way,
team, I've been trying to tell you...
I think I know how she's making
the weird jump points.
She has one of these.
It's my nani's bangle.
It started glowing really weirdly...
when Dar-Benn opened
that first jump point. Also...
it once traveled me through space and time...
so that's probably related.
What you're describing is a Quantum Band.
I mean, I knew there were two of these.
I just did not expect the other one
to be in space.
They're a pair?
How do you have a Quantum Band?
Okay. What is a Quantum Band?
A myth. Or I thought it was a myth.
It's an ancient artifact.
So this is what Dar-Benn found on
MB-418.
And then her and Kamala just happened
to stumble into each other?
I mean, what are the chances?
"What you seek is seeking you."
It's inscribed on the bangle.
If the Kree legends are true...
the Quantum Bands were used
to create every jump point in the universe.
Teleportation network.
Two Quantum Bands working in unison
to connect the galaxy.
So that would explain
our switch-y entanglement situation.
Yeah, yeah, but Dar-Benn only has one.
She must be overloading it with the
energy from her space hammer thingy.
It's called the Universal Weapon.
Oh, really? I was gonna call it Cosmi-Rod.
Either way, she's using it to force
unstable jump points into the grid.
We have got to get to her
before she makes another one.
She had star charts and maps
on the screens on her ship.
Okay. To where?
-To the stars?
-Okay.
It's fine. Got a plan.
We will use this.
-Is that...?
-A Skrull torture device.
And, wait, we put it on our heads?
Yes, it's fine.
You use it to access memories.
I've been using it...
to regain the memories
that the Kree took from me.
Still?
Yeah.
But, you know, it has a lot of other uses.
It's safe.
You might wanna get comfortable.
This is weird.
Wait. Go back.
Her band absorbs your energy
and redirects it.
It's like you gave her power
to use against you.
Kamala?
What about this?
There! Those coordinates.
Can you read that?
Yes. The Magellanic Galaxy.
All right, the pilot seat's all you.
Is that you, Monica? You're so cute!
No, wait.
Carol, what are you doing?
Why'd you ask me to come, Maria?
Mom.
The cancer's back.
So I need you to take care of Goose.
-No.
-What do you mean "no?"
No, I mean, you beat it once.
You'll beat it again.
Carol...
-I'm not taking the cat.
-It's not a cat.
It should've been you that day.
That stupid race to the hangar.
I never wanted to be Captain Marvel.
Captain Rambeau suits me just fine.
And it's just until Monica gets back.
She blipped.
Carol, I don't wanna relive this.
I'm sorry.
Stop now, please, Carol!
Remember why you're out there.
-I'm looking for a patient in room 104.
-I don't know. I don't know what to tell you.
And remember to come home.
Your mom, she died, honey.
No. No, no, no!
Never do that again.
I'm sorry. It wasn't on purpose.
Wait, so your mom...
Passed away while I was blipped.
And when I came back...
no one was there.
Okay.
Thank you.
She seemed really cool. I'm sorry.
She was.
She was the best.
Well, we have to make do
with what we know right now.
Here is what we do know.
The Universal Neural Teleportation Network...
is a system of wormholes through
the space-time continuum aka, jump points...
which allows us to hop
between different planetary systems.
Basically, it stretches and reconfigures
space without rupturing the continuum.
Like fracking, the more holes you drill...
the more destabilized the shale becomes
and then... earthquake.
Bottom line, if she keeps creating
these jump points...
it's gonna get really bad, really fast.
Question is, what does she want?
Tarnax used to be occupied by the Kree, so...
maybe the attack was a warning?
So, she could be after another former colony?
Is there a former Kree colony
in the Magellanic?
At one point the Kree colonized 25%
of the galaxy, so...
If all she wanted was to destroy Tarnax...
why not bring in an army
or use a bomb or something?
Why a jump point?
You're right. Jump points aren't weapons,
they're means of transportation.
Every jump point has two sides...
so if Tarnax's atmosphere
was siphoned away...
-it had to go somewhere, or...
-Hala.
The Kree Civil War...
basically bankrupted Hala
of its natural resources.
The air is barely breathable...
-they're suffering from a drought.
-A drought?
So, she could be after water next.
-Okay. Where in the Magellanic can we find...
-Aladna.
Oceans cover 99.63% of the planet.
That is a very specific stat.
You've been there.
Yeah.
She said that really weird.
-Yeah. Why are you being weird?
-Okay.
Consensus on Aladna.
-Aye.
-Yeah, I say we do it.
Get to Aladna
and separate Dar-Benn from that bangle.
We have our heading.
Kamala, you are not going
on any space adventures.
Nicholas has told me
how dangerous they can be.
It's just "Fury." God.
Wait. Where are you guys? Where is Abu?
Hell. This man has taken us to Hell.
Hell? So that means I'm the devil?
-Really, Fury?
-They insisted,
and your dad is not adjusting very well
to space travel.
Hey, babe, so I'm in this crazy
space elevator and we're going up.
Or maybe we're going down.
-Are there directions in space?
-Yes, there are.
But no filming.
Oh. Okay.
Help me.
Whoa.
Fury, everything okay?
We've had another surge.
Reports are coming in across the network.
It seems everyone's been affected.
Well, we need to stop her
from making another one...
and we can't risk intergalactic body swapping
in the meantime.
Mrs. Khan, I'm sorry, but your daughter
will have to stay aboard my ship...
-until we can get to the bottom of this.
-Oh, no, no, no.
Yes!
You will let her go.
Mrs. Khan, it is not that simple.
We need Kamala.
Ammi, we found Nani's other bangle...
and there's this weirdly beautiful
but kind of terrifying woman...
using the other one to hurt people.
And we have to stop her.
You're telling me there's another bangle.
And they're going to use that bangle
to hurt you?
Monica will take care of her.
We will. And we will make sure
she gets back home in one piece.
I promise.
Stay the course.
We'll figure out
how to close those jump points.
Kamala, you listen to me.
If anything happens to you...
I will kill her.
You tell her that.
I love you, beta.
I love you more.
-Wait, what did she just say?
-Nothing.
Nobody cares more than Captain Marvel...
and nobody gets more grief for it.
Trust me. Kamala is in good hands with Carol.
What's wrong with that cat?
It's acting very weird.
Also, Mr. Fury, she's looking little pudgy.
I think you're overfeeding her.
Goose.
Goose!
Firefly? Night Light.
Countess Marvel. Mistress Marvel?
-Doctor Marvel?
-That's too much.
Doctor Bright.
Professor Marvel.
Nova, Supernova Girl...
-Spectrum, Spectrum-Vision.
-You're doing too much.
Vision! Oh, wait.
No. Sorry.
How many times do I have to tell you guys
I do not want...
-or need a code name?
-Why?
Besides, none of it matters
if we're not coordinated out there.
Wanna figure out the switching thing?
Powers stay activated after a switch.
Good to know.
Okay, everyone together on three.
Ready? One, two, three, go.
Now, why would you say "go"
if we're going on three?
I'm aware.
Now.
One, two, three!
She gave me eyes.
Now. Now.
Can you hold on for one second?
Walk. And switch!
Switch!
Hey, I got this!
Yes!
And switch!
That's why you wanna invest in index funds
rather than in individual stocks.
Of course, both a Roth IRA and 401k
are important for tax purposes.
You know, I never even thought
about planning for retirement.
Hey, it's never too late.
And it's never too early, like I say.
-How old are you?
-306.
Wow. Same age.
What was that?
-I'm gonna find out.
-Please.
Foreign object in sector K.
-Sweet Svartalfheim.
-Don't touch it.
What is it?
I haven't the foggiest idea.
-How did it get in there?
-I don't know.
Should we tell Fury?
Twenty seconds to the jump point.
Do you guys realize
how crazy this is right now?
Like, I'm in a spaceship
with two superheroes.
Also, is it too late to go
to the bathroom?
Because I feel like
it's gonna hit really soon.
No one would believe me. Like my...
Nakia, she would never...
Okay. Here we go. Comms.
Wow!
-I've always wanted one of these.
-Thank you.
-Testing. Testing, one, two, three.
-Kamala. Kamala.
We hear you, baby. Thank you.
So, real quick before we get sucked in...
What the hell is that?
I should warn you that
I'm kind of famous here.
Well, you do know
you're famous everywhere, right?
This one's kinda different.
I helped the prince with a legal issue.
Okay.
Mm-hmm. Let's go.
No matter what...
follow my lead.
Aladnean culture is very specific.
So, there's gonna be a bit of a
ceremony we have to do...
but just... stay cool.
Fair Aladna...
it's a peaceful crossroads
Diamond of the quadrant...
Aladna, our home
Hi, small child, could you tell...
Fair Aladna...
as if no time has passed
So excited that you're home
Our princess is home
Princess?
It's a technicality.
Carol. What is happening?
Their language is Song.
Most of them won't understand you
unless you sing. Come on.
Going to the banquet
Prince Yan's at the banquet
Hi. Oh, hi, hello.
Going to the banquet
Where's the prince? Where's the prince?
Hey, hey, hey
Going, going, going, going
Going to the banquet
Why aren't you guys dancing?
I am dancing.
Dancing is life
Oh, we're almost there.
How angelic.
Hi... Okay. All right.
Wow.
Oh, my gosh,
give me some of what they're having.
-If you tell anyone about...
-What?
That you're a pretty, pretty princess?
So, that's what you meant
when you said "legal issue."
It is a marriage of convenience.
It's more of a diplomatic act, you know?
It's like, there was a power struggle.
Matriarchal society.
We are friends. It's a long story.
Maybe you could sing it.
Maybe not.
We're here.
Damn.
-You saw them arrive
-Oh, hello
Well, okay, I see why you like
to come here.
-Attention
-Yes
A pleasure to announce
To this lovely roomful
Two new faces
One could be more cheerful
Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha-Ha
But nonetheless, we ring the bells
To usher in, who, pray tell?
None other than
One, two, three
The Marvels!
The Marvels
The Marvels?
Yes!
How is that even a thing already?
-Okay, let's be cool.
-Where's the prince?
That's...
What the hell?
-What is she doing?
-She's respecting the flow.
How long
do I have with my dance partner this time?
Yan...
we are all in danger
What is happening?
What?
-The Captain needs our help
-Help!
Dar-Benn is coming
I'm feeling so many feelings right now.
Oh, Aladna's not afraid of her
Invite her down
put her feet on the ground
Give me a chance here...
-before it gets too messy
-So lead the wolf inside our walls
And trust that you alone...
-can stop an army?
-Have I ever let you down?
How many chapters of your Captain Marvel
fan fiction is this giving you?
I'm not about to start...
So many.
and don't forget...
Don't forget
I'm not alone
Monica.
My Princess from the star...
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Stop. Please stop.
We need to talk.
-Okay, let's talk.
-Okay.
Oh, wait. He doesn't have to sing?
Yeah, he's bilingual.
We are severely underdressed.
But could you get us
something a little more battle-ready?
Of course.
Thank you.
Theories so far?
At best, a one-off pest problem.
At worst, an enemy plant.
Some kinda infestation bioweapon.
Or it could be from a traitor from within.
Well, let's not go there yet.
This... egg you say...
let's just continue to study it,
and if anything...
Warning. Twenty-nine new objects detected.
Oh, my God.
What about Lady of Light?
-Frequency. Pulsar.
-No. No.
Pulsar Light Lady.
Absolutely not. These...
These are too much, right?
-Definitely.
-No.
We make this quick. Nothing grandiose.
You three need to disappear. But stay close.
My specialty.
This will work, Yan.
Remember, we wanna keep
unintentional switching to a minimum.
Entertain her as long as you possibly can.
Monica and I will get the jump on her.
And we'll get the bangle.
It's time.
Supremor, why have you come?
I've come here to pardon you
for your crimes against the Kree Empire.
Kneel.
To you?
-I will never kneel.
-Okay.
Damn it!
Use your scarf.
Go!
I found her.
Monica, where are you?
Monica, tag me in.
One, two...
Don't do this.
You're too late.
Where did you get that?
My grandma, she sent it to me in the mail.
-Give it to me.
-Kamala, run.
Get to the ship.
With this, your powers
only make me stronger.
The surges are frying our systems.
Are we doing something about these?
The space elevator's offline.
You ever come in here with good news?
Half the evacuation pods just went down.
That's not good news.
Are you guys in?
In.
Redirect all fighters.
Disengaging autopilot.
Oh, my God.
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Monica?
Monica, we're going down, Monica!
I thought you could drive this thing!
Carol! Get down here.
Hold that thought.
Can you believe this woman?
O, Captain! My Captain!
-No, no, no!
-Move over.
I'm activating a jump point.
-No, I can lose her.
-And what about the other 20 ships?
I can do this.
-Missile lock.
-Guys?
Missile lock.
Incoming missiles.
-Impact in five...
-We need to leave now.
-I can't let this happen again.
-four...
-It already has.
-three, two...
-I can do this.
-And you'll kill us trying.
Jump point activated.
We left Aladna to fend for themselves.
Dar-Benn was gonna get my bangle.
So I made a tough call
like you did on Tarnax.
Don't try to be like me.
I messed this whole thing up.
If we weren't entangled...
if we weren't here,
then you could have beat Dar-Benn.
And I'm sorry.
No, you don't understand.
The Kree had been ruled by an AI
for a millennia...
that led them into a war.
And I thought the only way to stop it
was to destroy it.
But I just...
made it worse.
I'm the reason why the civil war
started in the first place...
I'm the reason why they
couldn't breathe the air.
That's how I got the name Annihilator.
And I never wanted you to see
that version of me.
Is that why you never came back?
I thought if I fixed it...
then I could come home.
Carol.
That's not how family works.
I never expected you to be
the mighty Captain Marvel.
I just wanted you.
My aunt.
I'm really glad that you're here now.
And you, too.
I'm glad to be here.
I hope that goes without saying.
And I am sorry...
for coming on too strong at the beginning.
I did not give you a lot of space
to be a real person.
We have to find her.
I mean, but she could be anywhere.
No, not anywhere.
She's targeting the people
that I care about...
and stealing resources
from every place I call home.
We have to warn Fury.
This is an emergency.
All S.A.B.E.R. personnel must report
to an evacuation pod immediately. Walk.
-Do not run.
-We only have one evacuation bay online.
Which means that all we have left...
to evacuate 350 personnel
are 15 escape pods...
which seat five, 10, if we squeeze.
It's nowhere near enough.
Well, fill the remaining ones
with as many people as you can...
-then come up with a Plan B.
-This is an emergency. All S.A.B.E.R...
No, no, no.
Aamir. Go help them.
Okay, okay. Okay.
I got this.
My living room.
Goose?
Goose, how'd you...
Come here. Come. Come on.
Yes. Yes. Come here. Look at you.
Look!
Oh, no, not my good eye!
We only have one escape pod left.
We're doomed.
In the end...
none of us choose how we transition
from this life...
to the next.
What? No!
Get everyone to the evacuation deck.
Now!
Here, kitty. Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
What are we doing?
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
-I can't. Can you?
-I got it.
What is going on, fam?
Kamala?
Kamala! Yusuf, Kamala!
Kamala! Kamala!
You're back safely, beta.
You're not dead.
I've lost contact with Earth.
We're officially at abandon-ship phase.
Spit him out.
-Spit him out.
-No, no, no.
No. That's the plan.
-That's the plan?
-It's much easier...
to transport a family of cats
than hundreds of crew members.
So, we're literally herding cats?
Come here, kitty.
Attention, S.A.B.E.R. crew.
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
You will be fine.
S.A.B.E.R. crew.
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
Stop running.
I'm sorry.
Stop running and let the Flerkens eat you.
Stop running.
Guys, I found her.
-Come on. Come on, move.
-Hey! Come on.
Come on, come here.
-Go, go, go.
-Come on, come on.
-Go to the spacecraft bay.
-Okay. Come on.
Come on.
Yusuf, stop with your belt.
Nope. No. No, no, no. Thank you. No.
Come, come, come.
Don't you worry, little one.
Here, go to Kamala. Go to Kamala.
-There you go, come, come.
-I found Dar-Benn.
What?
She wants our sun.
You leavin' again?
Yeah.
Ammi, the universe isn't safe.
And if the universe isn't safe,
that means you guys aren't safe.
And if you guys aren't...
Listen to me.
You are chosen for a greater purpose, okay?
So, of course you must go now.
But I will never let you go.
You understand that, right?
-Yeah.
-Come back safely, beta.
You better.
I don't wanna be an only child.
Not again. Not with these two.
You think it's wise taking that bangle
to the bad guy?
Yes. Mr. Fury's right. Give it to me.
I will take it home.
Dar-Benn's opened another jump point...
and we're gonna need both bangles
to close it.
Then I guess you'd better make damn sure
she doesn't get her hands on it.
Understood.
Oh, God, Mr. Fury...
-you are going in the wrong direction!
-Mrs. Khan, I know!
-You did it, Mr. Fury!
-I didn't do anything.
Are you praying?
Don't stop! We need all the help we can get!
Amen!
Holy cow!
Mr. Fury!
There she is...
the Annihilator herself.
It's over, Dar-Benn.
No, not yet.
I know that you would do anything
to protect Hala.
This will be the end of the Kree.
It will be the end of everything.
You took from me.
I'm simply repaying the favor.
Now, give me the band.
You're forgetting something.
-What?
-Me.
This could have been so much easier.
I don't know. I like our odds.
You're living up to your name again.
I didn't want this.
Death seems to follow you.
It doesn't have to end like this, Dar-Benn.
Please, just give us the bangle.
I won't!
Hala's sun died because of you.
Why shouldn't you repay us?
Maybe she should.
The reaction in your sun's core has slowed.
It needs an incredible amount of energy
to jump-start it...
and that's what you have, Carol.
You can use your powers to save Hala.
But I've never done anything
like that before.
In the last couple of days I have done
a lot of things I have never done before.
You got this.
For Hala.
Try anything
and I'll kill her faster than you can move.
Carol!
No!
You won't survive this.
Dar-Benn, listen to me.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I didn't switch.
One, two, three.
I'm so glad you're okay.
You got the bangles.
We are gonna need those.
Okay, come on, Princess.
So, what are we looking at?
A self-propagating singularity
with negative mass...
and non-Newtonian topology.
She tore a hole in space-time.
That is a different reality
bleeding into ours.
Can we even fix that?
In theory, you and Carol can reproduce
the same amount of energy...
that was used to open it.
I will absorb it and then release it,
but from inside the tear.
But what about the switching?
Our powers aren't entangled anymore.
Well, that's a good thing, I guess.
But, wait. You want us to blast you
with the same amount of power...
that punched a hole in the fabric
of space-time?
If we wanna un-punch it, yeah.
Monica...
You're gonna need this.
How are you feeling, Ms. Marvel?
These bangles traveled
through space and time.
To find me.
I was born for this.
It has to be now.
Your mom would be proud.
Higher, further, faster.
It's closing, Monica.
You've got to get out of there.
I can't leave, Carol.
What? What do you mean?
I can't leave.
I have to finish the job.
No! Monica, it's closing.
You'll be trapped!
It's okay.
Come on.
Always knew I would have to stay.
Kamala.
Kamala, you saved
the world.
Why are you crying?
What happened?
We lost Monica.
She got stuck on the other side.
And Carol?
She went to fulfill a promise.
How are things?
The planets are expected
to make a full recovery.
And a team of scientists are being sent
to Hala to try and help their people.
That's not what I meant.
This says "Kitchen," but there are
all these hot sauce packets...
And then there's
this very bizarre-looking tray...
which I will say is
a very good quality, though.
You can keep it.
-Oh, no, no, Carol, I just...
-Where else would they go?
Oh, yeah, yeah, it was for me.
The vastness of it just gives you
a whole new perspective on life.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
And it was surprisingly cool.
This place is amazing.
Yeah, it is.
Hey, do you still fly that thing?
-You wanna check it out?
-I do.
All right.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
-I'm so happy that you're home safe, beta.
-Okay.
Aamir...
this would be a lovely house
to raise a family in, you know?
Aamir.
This is so cool.
Pilot seat's all you.
Let's fly this thing.
I actually don't have the key.
I'm just looking after it.
Just until Monica gets back?
Yeah.
Just until Monica gets back.
I really miss her.
We were good together.
Which got me thinking...
Pizza delivery.
Okay.
Can I help you?
Kate Bishop.
Did you think you're
the only kid superhero in the world?
-Well, I'm 23.
-Oh, I know.
I've been reading up on you.
Where did you get that?
I found it in my couch.
Okay.
You've just become
part of a much larger universe.
Which, at the moment, is just me, mostly.
I do have feelers out, though.
-Did you know Ant-Man had a daughter?
-What do you want?
I'm putting together a team.
And I want you on it.
Please?
Mom?
"Mom"?
-Mom!
-"Mom?"
I've missed you so much!
You missed me?
-I'm so sorry. I'm... I'm...
-Okay. Okay. Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, look at me.
It's okay. You're okay. Hey.
How's our mysterious visitor?
She seems a little disoriented.
Where... Where are we? What happened?
We were hoping you could tell us.
All we know is that Binary found you.
My theory? You somehow crossed
through a tear in space-time.
You are now in a reality parallel
to your own.
Which is, of course, impossible.
I think there might be
a little confusion happening.
Confusion is but the first step
on the journey to knowledge.
Okay. I'll take it from here.
Charles asked for an update.
I'll come by and check on you later.
Who are you?
Oh, shit.