[droning music]
The universe is on fire.
Heat. Burning.
A perfect inferno set against
cold, endless nothing.
But within some dimensions,
there exists an aberration.
Life.
[dramatic music]
I owe you a real ring.
I love you, Ronnie.
♪
I have come
to end that life.
I am Deathstorm.
♪
What are you?
Complete, thanks to you.
Now I'll return the favor.
[snarls]
[screams]
[heroic music]
♪
[growls]
[snarls]
Get away from her!
[groans]
It's still not enough.
But I'll be back.
And this life of yours
will end.
Caity?
- [groans]
- What the hell was that thing?
I don't know.
Whatever it was,
my lightning didn't affect it.
What's wrong with her?
[wheezing]
How do you feel?
Lucky to be alive,
so...fine, I guess.
Hold on, it burned her,
but she looks okay
and there aren't
any marks or anything.
Let's just call it a win.
What was that thing anyway?
It calls itself Deathstorm.
[tense music]
Hmm. Like Firestorm, only...
It wasn't Ronnie.
It never was.
How do you know that?
Because it told me.
Then what exactly is it?
And where did it come from?
- I don't know.
But whatever we brought back
from Piedmont Park,
that thing, it isn't human.
It said Ronnie's death
gave him life.
And when Ronnie was gone,
it became something more,
something incomplete.
And that I helped
make it whole again.
That's why it wanted you
to modify the Firestorm Matrix.
So that I could bring it back
from whatever hell
it's been hiding in.
Barry, I'm so sorry.
You were right this whole time,
and I wouldn't listen.
Hey, that's okay.
You just did what any one of us
would have done.
No, Ronnie's been dead
for seven years.
And now this thing is back
in his place,
all because of me.
You're okay now,
and that's all that matters.
Barry, if Caitlin's right,
if Deathstorm wanted Caitlin
for some creepy resurrection,
why is he trying
to kill her now?
I mean, he got what he wanted.
That's what we need
to find out.
Well, Chuck is
using satellites
to try and figure out
where this thing went.
But if Frost is right
and it's coming back for Caity,
we need to keep her safe.
We will,
and we're gonna send this thing
back to whatever hell
it came from.
How?
The Cold Fusion Sphere
has been destroyed.
We'll find another way.
Until then, Frost--
- I'm way ahead of you.
If this matchhead thinks
he's getting
anywhere near my sister,
he's gotta go through me first.
Hey, I heard what happened.
How can I help?
Thank you,
but we're not even sure
what we're dealing with yet.
Barry.
Look, from the second I walked
into S.T.A.R. Labs,
I could feel
how worried you are.
But what I'm sensing,
it's way more
than just concern.
[high-pitched ringing]
You're hurting, badly.
Hey, what's going on?
It's Iris.
- Is she okay?
- That's just it. I don't know.
What's even worse is,
I don't even know
where she is right now.
What are you talking about?
I thought she was
in Coast City with Sue.
Yeah, she was.
Only now...
[phone chimes, buzzes]
[dramatic music]
Oh, thank--
Cecile, Iris is back.
I gotta go.
[whooshes]
Iris, thank God you're back.
Sue said you'd vanished--
- No, Barry.
What's wrong?
[somber music]
Renee Wazzo, Tinya's mom.
I'm the last person
that she touched,
and she's...gone because of me,
because of my time sickness.
Okay.
But then Sue said
that Tinya attacked you,
that she made you disappear
on purpose.
So how did you survive?
Your time sickness.
It must have pulled you
into the Still Force
at that exact moment.
So whatever is
making her sick
might have also saved her life.
Okay, that's--that's freaky.
I'm gonna give you guys
some space.
I'll be back, okay?
♪
Barry,
what happened to Tinya's mom,
I didn't mean to--
I know that.
Look, it's gonna be okay.
[gasps]
I'm not afraid.
♪
What is it?
Barry, the Still Force,
it's supposed to be a place
where...all time exists,
past, present, and future
but when I was there,
I saw moments from before,
even when I was a little girl,
up to now.
But I didn't see my future.
What if I don't
have one anymore?
You do.
With me.
♪
[ominous music]
[crying softly]
[hissing]
[wind howling]
♪
Hello?
[hissing]
Who's there?
[growling]
[screams]
[clock ticking]
[tense music]
So how does one summon
a Force god?
Well, I mean,
they've had appointments before,
but usually all Iris has to do
is concentrate,
and Deon knows to appear.
[phone beeping, buzzing]
A few weeks ago,
I gave Captain Kramer
an emergency alert
to summon the Flash,
and this is the first time
she's used it,
which means--
- It's serious.
As in 'gotta go" serious.
Yeah, but, Iris,
I can't leave you here alone.
Hey, she won't be.
Yeah, no, it's okay.
- Okay, but--
- Barry,
with everything
that's happening
and now with Deathstorm,
people need you more than ever.
Go.
Yeah, I get it.
Waiting sucks.
You know what might make it
suck less?
A five-course meal
from Angelino's
delivered
straight to your door.
We could eat our problems away.
Food as a distraction?
You're a bad influence.
- I'll take that as a yes.
[line trilling]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[phones ringing]
A skull-faced thing
flew down from the sky
and took your wife?
Ma'am, please,
try to remain calm.
And nothing else was burnt,
just the body?
Can you describe the figure?
A living skeleton.
♪
This is the tenth burn victim
in half as many months,
and now you're saying
it's gonna get even worse?
It already has.
Sorry to interrupt, Captain.
Joe, Flash.
But we've got three more
confirmed burn vics downtown,
another two uptown,
and at least four
reported
on the lower east side.
And the phones are
ringing off the hook
about a skull-faced demon.
He calls himself Deathstorm.
Have Matlin call in
every unit for backup.
We need all hands on deck
for this.
Copy.
Glad to have you
with us, Flash.
So why is this thing
burning people alive?
We're not sure,
but the current theory ism
to feed off their grief.
How do we fight him?
We don't know yet.
One thing I do know
about Team Flash is,
they'll find a way.
I don't know
what's more terrifying,
that this Deathstorm can
turn up anywhere,
or that not even the Flash is
powerful enough to stop him.
Well, Kristen,
I know this seems hopeless--
No, it's not just that.
Joe, how the hell did you
used to deal with this?
For the past 17 years,
I've been either a soldier
or a cop,
and nothing I've done
prepared me for this.
Look, I hear you--
when I was captain,
I fought evils in this town
I didn't know existed,
so I know
exactly where you are.
Looking out into the unknown
at something
that you cannot stop.
But I always had
a friend to watch my back,
just like you do now.
Joe's right.
Everyone has a weakness.
Deathstorm does too.
We just have to find it.
Until then, what's the plan?
I'll use my speed
to keep searching the city.
I can help you
coordinate protocols
so all of our officers are safe
and they can actually
do their job.
What are you,
my advisor now, Joe?
That would be up to you, Captain.
Remember,
if you or any of your officers
see this thing--
- Don't worry.
You'll be the first to know.
I'll let you know
what I find on my end.
[sighs]
Have faith.
He'll find a way.
Until he does,
you and I have to lock down
this city.
Let's get to work.
Listen up, everyone.
Our city is under attack.
Captain, is it true?
Some kind of fire ghost?
Yes, and I suppose that's
as good a description as any.
To be honest, we don't know
much about our enemy,
but I can confirm
that the streets aren't safe
for anyone who is
currently grieving.
So if you've had
any upsetting news recently
about a family member,
friend, or loved one,
please see myself
or Joe immediately.
You're not safe on the streets.
The rest of us will be working
with the Flash and his team
to take this threat down together.
So your orders are as follows:
do not engage this monster.
We need to protect this city
by keeping civilians
out of harm's way.
The Flash and his team
will do the heavy lifting.
Now, Martinez, Howe, send out
a city-wide lockdown alert.
We need everyone
off the streets.
Korber, Matlin, gather teams
to set up a perimeter grid.
I want eyes and ears
on every street corner
we can manage.
Anyone sees this thing,
call it in,
then get yourselves to safety.
I have looked through
all the evidence
on Deathstorm's past attacks,
and still no clues
as to where he went.
So far, every grid has
turned up nothing.
And satellites are
still a dead end.
Hey, what about
the CCC Media tip line?
Nothing yet, and I have
the bullpen on alert.
It's like he shows up
just to feed
and then disappears
into thin air.
Just like a ghost.
He's not a ghost,
so he's gotta be
hiding somewhere.
Hey. How are you guys doing?
Never mind. I already know.
I can feel your frustration
from the Med Lab.
Chester,
I thought that we had a way
to track these black fires.
We did, but ever since
our new Big Bad
turned from black flames
into a fiery,
walking and talking corpse,
he's become untraceable.
How's Caitlin?
She and Frost are moving
into the Speed Lab.
Physically, Caitlin is fine,
but she's still
pretty shaken up.
Yeah, 'cause even though
you can hide emotions,
you can't get rid of them.
Guys, we don't need
the satellites
to search for Deathstorm.
[intriguing music]
♪
Cecile, you're gonna
help us find him.
♪
So wait,
you want to use Cecile
as, like, a Deathstorm compass?
Yeah, think about it.
Deathstorm absorbs grief.
Grief is an emotion.
My powers.
My powers feel
other people's emotions,
even from a distance.
If we can figure out a way
to interface
Cecile's empath powers
with S.T.A.R.'s search systems,
it would be like using
a wireless neurogenic array
synced with the Med Lab's
synaptic monitoring relay.
Holy Paschal Beverly Randolph.
Barry, this could work.
Yeah,
but syncing Cecile's mind up
with that thing,
it sounds pretty dangerous.
Allegra's right.
Okay, tapping into a pool
of emotion that large,
it could overload
your neural synapses.
You sure
you're okay with this?
This murderous bastard
has already killed
more than a dozen people.
So yeah, try and stop me.
I can't believe
I was so blind.
Frost, this is all my fault.
I let that thing out.
No, I'm not gonna
let you go there.
I mean, come on,
we're on lockdown
because I went rogue.
All because I was so obsessed
with reconnecting
with the past.
Ronnie wasn't just your past.
He was your husband.
And Deathstorm knew that,
which was why he knew
he could use it to manipulate
you into bringing him back
from whatever hellscape
he comes from.
This isn't your fault, okay?
Isn't it? I mean, the whole
city is paying for my mistakes.
And as stupid as it sounds...
I just feel like I lost Ronnie
all over again.
[somber music]
Why does this hurt so much?
Because you loved him.
[chuckles]
And even though
it's been a long time,
he'll always be a part of you.
And that's okay.
♪
[soft dramatic music]
[thunderclap]
Oh, thank God.
Oh, let me guess.
The Still Force.
Call me Deon.
My headaches,
they're getting worse.
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
You also said to tell you
if something happened.
Well, it did.
Tinya's mom. I already know.
Oh, right.
'Cause you can see
past, present, and future.
Not in this case.
I actually only saw
what happened to Tinya's mom
once it became
part of the past,
which ain't how things are
supposed to work.
My time sickness,
it's spreading
into the Still Force.
That's why it took me so long
to get to you.
I've infected you too,
haven't I?
That's probably why
I didn't see this coming.
Somehow...somehow,
I'm getting sick too.
What about Tinya's mom?
Once I get my strength back,
I'll look for her,
but, Iris,
I can see everyone's future
except for yours.
We've got to slow down
whatever's happening,
because if we don't--
Iris is gonna
disappear again.
Maybe for good this time.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
We just--we gotta find a way
to bring her back,
'cause if she gets lost
in space,
we need a way to find her.
[indistinct whispering]
You remember that tracking app
that you guys used
to find Tinya?
- Yeah.
Maybe I could do the same.
It's pretty far out,
but if it works...
Do it.
♪
I should be able to track
your movements now.
In the meantime,
fight as hard as you can
to stay here.
And do whatever you can
to just anchor yourself
to the present.
[foreboding music]
♪
Yo, something's wrong.
[screams]
♪
Okay, so I've linked up
a wireless neurogenic
monitoring system
to your cerebral cortex.
You can do that?
Pretty sure,
given enough time,
Chester can do anything.
Aww. Thanks, Barr.
So yeah, all you need to do
is concentrate
on any large pockets of grief.
If we're right, that'll lead us
right to where
Deathstorm's been hiding.
Once you get a hit,
I'll triangulate
real-time coordinates,
find a location--
Then the Flash
will take over.
Works for me.
You ready?
Uh...
[inhales sharply]
Yeah.
Okay.
[computer beeping]
[hissing]
[laughs]
Oh, it's working.
Keep going, Cecile.
[beeping steadily]
[beeping rapidly]
Wait, there must be
a glitch or something.
It says that--
It's coming
from S.T.A.R. Labs.
[alarm beeping]
[tense music]
♪
[inhales raspingly]
[distorted whispering]
[as Deathstorm]
You're wasting your time.
You won't find me
until I'm ready.
Shut it down.
Now. Shut it down.
- It won't work.
The empath and I are one.
Deathstorm,
if you hurt her--
[laughing]
Don't bother
with hollow threats.
You can't stop me.
The truth is,
there's only one way
all of you survive.
We're never gonna
give you Caitlin.
Then I'll take her from you!
[laughs]
I can taste
the tiniest bits of sorrow
coming from you both.
Mmm. They are so delicious.
And exactly what I need.
You don't scare us.
And you can't
control us anymore.
We've already faced our grief.
And yet there's always
the smallest morsel
left behind,
long after
a loved one has passed.
[distorted whispering]
Which is why you can't stop me.
[electricity crackling]
[gasping as herself]
Cecile.
Deathstorm.
He overwhelmed my emotions.
It was--
it was horrible.
All that matters right now
is, you're back with us.
Okay?
[breathing heavily]
Barry, I could feel
his determination.
His sheer force of will.
Barry, he's never,
ever gonna give up
on trying to get Caitlin.
♪
[dramatic music]
Esperanza.
[speaking Spanish]
♪
[suspenseful music]
[speaking Spanish]
Which would make you his bitch.
Be careful, prima.
The juvie in you
is starting to show.
Yeah, we're done.
[rumbling]
What was that?
A localized explosion
of some kind.
Oh, if Pyro Pazuzu is back,
we could be under attack.
Guys, I'm picking up
a category-three
spectral discharge,
four levels beneath us.
What could cause that?
A light-based detonation on
the electromagnetic spectrum.
Allegra.
- What happened?
- Barry, watch out.
That thing,
it looks like my cousin,
but it isn't.
It--
it was right there.
One of those grief freaks
like Chuck's dad,
but this time,
it looked like Esperanza.
[tense music]
I knew it wasn't my cousin
as soon as I saw it,
but when I fired,
it fired back.
The blast knocked
both of us out.
Now it's gone.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
Only why is Deathstorm trying
to haunt me all of a sudden?
♪
We have no idea
what happened to Deon.
Whatever's going on with me,
it's not just
my problem anymore.
It's time fracturing itself.
Okay.
There's not much we can do
about that right now.
But obsessing over it,
it's only gonna
make things worse.
Say, did I ever tell you
about the time
that I crashed a royal wedding?
Spoiler alert:
they don't arrest you
if you buy the castle.
Right. Not the time.
More like not enough time.
Did you know that being married
to a speedster
affords you the ability to live
an entire day in a second?
Makes you think that you have
all the time in the world.
[soft music]
We don't.
Every moment is precious.
Agreed.
You know, I used to think
that Barry and I
and our children,
that we had so much
ahead of us, but....
Now it feels like
I have no future.
Look,
you are Iris West-Allen.
You are
your own force of nature.
I promise,
whatever time
this world has left,
it's not done with you yet.
Not by a long shot.
[high-pitched whining]
Okay, Iris, stay with me.
The time stream,
it's too strong.
Just remember what Deon said.
[breathing heavily]
Concentrate
on being right here,
right now, with me.
I can't--I can't fight it.
Hell yes, you can.
You know why?
Because you have
way too much to live for.
[screams]
Barry. Nora and Bart.
They need you, Iris.
You're their future
and they're yours.
Are you gonna give up on that?
- No.
- No. So fight this.
You say that you can't
see a future?
Fine, anchor yourself to them.
Write yourself a new future
starting right now.
You got that?
[gasping]
[soft music]
♪
Better?
I'm still here.
Yeah.
I know that look.
Kramer had it earlier.
You're wondering
what to do now too, huh?
Using grief to track
Deathstorm was our best shot.
A long time ago,
I met someone who was
as unprepared as it gets.
Young, inexperienced,
thrust into this
whole new world
that was sink or swim.
You know what happened
that he didn't see coming next?
DeVoe.
Zoom.
Cicada.
Bloodwork.
But you're still standing,
ain't you?
What's happening now,
the way Deathstorm's
going after Caitlin.
I mean,
how do we stop this thing
if we don't even know
why she's the target?
Barr,
all the resources, weapons,
and planning in the world
ain't gonna help you prepare
for a monster like this.
All that you can do
is be who you already are,
somebody willing to fight,
no matter what the odds are.
So believe me when I say,
don't worry.
In due time,
you will find a way
to get the advantage
over Deathstorm.
- And until that happens?
- You do what you do best.
Run...
into the unknown
and trust yourself.
Believe me,
you're better prepared
than you think.
♪
[pencil scribbling]
[wind howling, hissing]
[foreboding music]
♪
[whispering]
Caity.
♪
[hissing and howling building]
[cackling]
[snarls]
[suspenseful music]
♪
Now your life ends.
[screams]
What happened?
Deathstorm,
he got in somehow.
- Caitlin?
- He took her.
- What about Frost?
- Well, I scanned her vitals.
She's still in the Speed Lab.
Alive, but not responding.
Barry, I'm tracking the GPS
on Caitlin's phone.
Deathstorm's moving
with her fast,
headed to who knows where.
If we don't catch him
before he disappears...
Check on Frost.
I'm gonna go after Caitlin.
Chester, stay on comms.
Yeah.
[epic music]
♪
Found them!
He's too high.
I can't reach them.
Chester, my boots can
redirect most energy sources.
Does that include
currents equal
to the kinetic output
created when I run?
Uh, it should,
and the force of those two
equal energies would
probably cancel each other out.
It'd be like
running into a brick wall.
I'm counting on it.
Hold up. Hold up.
Are you about to do what
I think you're about to do?
Yeah.
Time to ride the lightning.
[Metallica's
"Ride the Lightning"]
♪ Flash before my eyes
♪ Now is time to die
[intense rock music]
♪ Burning in my brain
♪ I can feel the flame
♪
Chester, I've lost Caitlin.
Where'd they go?
- I don't know.
One second,
you almost had them,
then they
completely disappeared.
We have to find them!
[bright organ music playing]
♪
[eerie music]
[snarling]
♪
[roars]
[crowd screaming]
♪
[snarling]
[roars]
If you're gonna kill me,
just get it over with.
Why would I do that?
I traveled across the stars
to transform you,
so you could end my loneliness.
Because tonight,
you become my bride.
[dramatic music]
♪
[groans]
[screams]
Oh, Flash,
Caitlin just popped back up.
She's at
the Ripley's Wild World,
just outside the city.
♪
Caitlin, what happened?
Where's Deathstorm?
Caitlin?
[snarling]
He said I'm not ready yet.
♪
[soft dramatic music]
It's incredible.
All my vitals are elevated,
my blood pressure is lower,
and so is my body temperature,
but that's not
the strangest thing.
My cells are in
a constant state of regenesis.
It's like I'm not aging at all,
at least not the way
I'm supposed to be.
Why?
Why would Deathstorm
try to make you stronger?
Ah.
Uh, Caitlin?
I'm sensing a massive amount
of grief inside of you.
It's--it's enough
for an entire family.
When I found you at the park,
there were
four more charred bodies.
Deathstorm's calling card.
Okay,
here's what I don't get.
The black flames that he emits,
how come they don't hurt you?
I don't think
that they're supposed to.
I think that
that's what's changing me.
When Deathstorm attacked me
again, he said,
"I traveled across the stars
to be with you."
But that my transformation
wasn't complete,
that I wasn't ready yet.
Ready for what?
To be his bride.
♪
I think he wants us
to be together
in wherever it is
that he's from.
And that what's happening
to me now is something
that he has to do
to make sure I'm prepared.
He was never trying
to kill you.
Barry,
I know it sounds crazy,
but if Deathstorm is
using the grief he consumes
to change me,
and he's saying
he needs more...
He's gonna feed again.
And as soon as he's full,
he's gonna come back for you.
Okay, that's it.
I am done waiting around
for the bachelor from hell
to come give Caity a rose.
We need to find this sicko
and end him,
before he does
anything worse to my sister.
[groaning]
Hey, you okay?
It's fine.
I'm gonna be okay.
I just... I gotta rest.
Frost, Cecile, stay with her.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find a way
to end this.
We're more than just
Team Flash--we're a family.
And if anyone tries to hurt
a member of this family,
we do whatever we can
to stop them.
[heroic music]
♪
Okay, Barr, so what now?
Yeah,
we might not have a plan,
but now we know
something we didn't before,
something I'm hoping
can help us.
What's that?
Where Deathstorm goes
when he disappears.
So when I was
chasing Deathstorm,
he opened a portal,
and even though I couldn't
get to Caitlyn,
I saw inside of it,
just for a moment.
And guys, I've seen
space like that before.
Inside your singularity,
right before you joined
the team.
Whoa, now.
So what this means is,
when Deathstorm disappears,
he's not just teleporting
around town.
No, he's jumping back and forth
between points
in dimensional space.
I think I know
what happened now.
When Ronnie's grief
traveled through
that singularity,
it created Deathstorm.
Only he's been trapped there,
trying to get back
across the stars to Caitlyn
ever since.
And now that he's complete,
he can move back and forth
between that hell dimension
and here at will.
All this time,
we've been wondering
why Deathstorm would
come after Caitlin,
seven years after Ronnie died.
He's been searching for his
plus one this whole time.
It took him this long because
of how far he had to travel.
So a death monster
from another dimension
traveling through outer space
to find his death bride.
Yeah, it's official.
I have heard everything now.
Great Benjamin Banneker.
Trans-dimensional particles.
Okay, now you're
just making stuff up.
No, no, no, no, look.
Now that I know
that his powers are
literally from
out of this world,
it makes me think
that we need something cosmic.
And folks, I know just
the gadget that we can augment
and use to defend ourselves
against this thing.
[exciting music]
The Mental
Augmentation Chamber.
The M.A.C. saved my ass
by absorbing the entire mass
of black hole energy
that I accidentally unleashed
a couple years ago.
I'm sorry about that again.
And black holes are composed
of trans-dimensional particles.
Exactly. Now, this is gonna
sound a little nuts.
But what if we adjust
the M.A.C.
so that instead of absorbing
trans-dimensional energy,
it emits
cosmic craziness instead?
We'd finally be able
to fight fire with fire.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's not like
we can just turn the M.A.C.
into a portable cannon
or shield.
What we would really need is--
A person to contain
all the energy.
Done and doner.
Look, I don't speak geek,
but I understand enough
to realize that you guys need
an anti-Deathstorm
in order to take down
the real thing.
Frost and Deathstorm's powers
are both based on cold fusion.
That could be the key
to pull this whole thing off.
Yeah, but Frost,
this is right up there
with some
of the most dangerous stuff
we've ever attempted as a team.
We can't ask you to do this.
You don't have to.
It's like I told Mom.
Dad created me for one reason.
To keep Caity safe.
I was literally born for this.
♪
So...
let's extinguish
the son of a bitch.
[ominous music]
♪
[hissing]
[snarling]
♪
Iris.
Thank God.
It's so good to see you.
Greg, move your head.