I've had 20 years to come up
with the perfect trick.
It's going to be my masterpiece.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I'm a huge comic-book fan.
I have been all my life.
I probably read the first Trickster
when I was in grade school.
He was a disgruntled acrobat...
...who was never able to achieve the stardom
he felt he deserved...
...and developed this pair of trick boots
that shot jet streams of air...
...so that he could literally run
through the sky.
The original Skywalker, right?
It was crazy, like his namesake...
...Jesse James.
He's running along and boarding airplanes,
holding them up and then running out.
So when you're 9 years old, this is fantastic.
If you have this super-powerful
larger-than-life hero...
...conversely, you have to have super,
you know, over-the-top villains.
One of the signature Flash elements
was the team-ups.
You'd see Flash and--
Surrounding him with like nine villains.
You know, Trickster, Captain Boomerang
and all of them.
You really got your 12 cents' worth.
The trickster...
...that's a classic figure in literature.
The person who fools people
into doing what he wants.
He's someone that loves gimmicks
and gadgets.
He's more in the world of magic,
so sleight of hand, misdirection.
There's sort of a perverse joy he gets
in annoying his adversaries.
You know,
you think that something really wonderful...
...and magical is about to happen,
and it blows up in your face.
HAMILL:
Bugs Bunny is a trickster.
So they can be very fun and benevolent...
...rather than sort of malignant and malevolent
like this one.
I had so much fun doing the original.
Right after they did the Trickster...
...they brought Mirror Master
and Captain Cold...
...and some of the more celebrated members
of the Rogues' Gallery.
And then I eventually came back
and did the season finale.
It's not guns that kill people.
It's these little hard things.
SHIPP:
The last Trickster episode...
...they did so many things to my Barry.
Flash.
I was facedown in a pool of bubble gum...
...I was tied up.
I was being given electric shocks,
I was being insulted. I was like:
"Did I piss off the writers
at some point during the season?"
[CACKLING]
HAMILL: I had a Trickster mobile, ha, ha,
I had all these gimmicks and gadgets and--
You know, for the 12-year-old in me,
I was just beside myself.
And like I say,
we just had a great, great time.
Right, old buddy? That's right.
[TRICKSTER LAUGHS]
HAMILL:
So this is a long time coming.
[LAUGHING]
MAN:
Thirty-six echo. Take three, pickup.
HENRY:
Can't you see he's using you?
He's not using me.
He's teaching me. Okay?
SHIPP: What's so fascinating
about the modern sensibility around comics...
...is that we go beyond just exploding cars...
...and little boxes with umbrellas,
brightly colored...
...that blow up and kill people.
I mean, we go beyond all that
to what's going on inside with these people.
You can see it right away in the costume.
Obviously, Colleen Atwood...
...the decision was made
to make the Flash costume more urban.
It's threatening.
There's a similar motif in the Trickster's.
HAMILL: You can see by this outfit,
he's much more subdued.
[CHUCKLES]
How do you like the shirt, folks?
It's like out of a carnival sideshow.
SHIPP:
Devon's is grittier.
Tricked you.
You know, they want it be more threatening
and they want it to be more urban...
...and contemporary.
HAMILL: Greg Berlanti and Andrew Kreisberg,
they've done such smart things...
...you know, having this
really compelling back-story.
He's sitting in Iron Heights prison doing life.
Gentlemen.
Yesterday hundreds of these parachute bombs
were released throughout Central City.
JAMES:
A fun idea.
[LAUGHS]
HAMILL: When Detective West and Barry Allen
come to him, he's helpful to a point...
...but he also is very deceptive.
He tells them that this guy
probably has found the Trickster's lair.
I love the set design
because you see they've put all these--
You know, his gimmicks and gadgets
from "Trial of the Trickster."
It's clever the way they've put this together.
[LAUGHS]
Our executive producers
were all avid watchers of the first effort.
When I was working with Greg Berlanti
on Dawson’s Creek...
...I never knew that the Flash
was his favorite character.
What we get is executive producers
who are not just doing it for the money.
They are enjoying
what they're coming up with...
...for the audience to enjoy...
...as much as the audience is.
HAMILL:
You never get to play this kind of thing.
So I'm really enjoying it.
SHIPP:
I hope that if I have value to this project...
...it's to get the hard-core audience
from when I was the Flash involved.
Our job is to hand off to the next generation.
HENRY: If the cops can't find you,
trust me, the Flash will.
[LAUGHS]
Here's hoping.
SHIPP: The interesting thing now
having Mark Hamill come back...
...is that we get the gravitas of Mark
and everything he brings from the old show...
...and we get a protégé.
So we almost get
this father-son relationship happening...
...between these two
completely distorted personalities.
JAMES:
You did me proud back in Iron Heights.
I was right to reach out.
HAMILL: It's really interesting to me because
I think it should be a generational thing.
I mean, it should be about the up-and-coming
rather than the past.
Why did you choose me?
You had the strength to fulfill my legacy.
Like most megalomaniacs,
he has this unbelievable ego...
...and I think he can't get over this kid
stealing his thunder.
TRICKSTER [ON SCREEN]:
It's a big bomb. It'll make a big bang...
...and then a big hole and then a big drop...
...in the population.
[CHUCKLES]
But never say....
Wait a minute.
Who's this guy stealing my shtick, you know?
He gets to do all the fun stuff.
No, no, no.
Take off my mask, you fraud.
Take off my mask!
[SOBS]
He's not rehabilitated in any way,
shape or form.
At one point, he says to his protégé,
you know:
"I've had 20 years
to come up with the perfect trick."
It's the Trickster.
It's the perfect Trickster episode.
I better skedaddle. Run, run, run.
HAMILL:
This is very preliminary.
I mean, if they do have long-term plans for him,
they'll probably get more elaborate.
SHIPP: Our executive producers
have so much up their sleeve...
...and they have a template
that allows them to do anything.
We have multiple universes overlapping.
HAMILL:
There's so much going on with back-story.
They've just done it very cleverly.
Because there's a new Trickster in town.
SHIPP:
That's the playground that we have.
And it's limitless.
They can do literally anything.
No telling what they have planned.