This is Francis Coppola, and I'm
here to give you my impressions,
my memories, my feelings about
the third film in what became a series.
This film is titled
The Godfather Part III.
Ironically, the real title that Mario
Puzo and I had given this film
was The Death of Michael Corleone.
Usually sequels of films in
the past had independent titles,
or at best it was The
Bride of Frankenstein.
The notion of the more literary Part II
had never really
happened in this country,
and The Godfather Part
II was the innovating film.
Ironically, many years later,
it's an indication of
my lessening influence
that Paramount prevailed
and the film, against our wishes,
was called The Godfather Part III,
but I would like to have the
audience think of the films, really,
as two sequels and an epilogue.
As we begin the story of the third film,
there were the haunting images of
the Corleone compound on Lake Tahoe,
that really we shot as a kind of pre-unit
even before we made the second film.
It was that estate that I stumbled
upon one day with some friends,
that seemed to suggest to me,
especially in that it was in ruin,
that there had been a powerful
family, perhaps, who had lived there.
Indeed it was true, it
was the Kaiser Estate,
and in a period in the '60s, perhaps,
they were there with their young people
and their speedboats,
and enjoying the boathouse
and the parties and the dances,
but now, as I discovered the estate,
it was being swallowed up by the lake,
and it was a ruin.
It suggested to me that perhaps this
was the ruin of the Corleone family,
and although we had originally
thought to begin the film
much as we had begun the first Godfather,
in fact, in general our plan
was to have this epilogue
be more like the first Godfather
than the second Godfather,
which of course was
told in two time periods.
But originally we were going to
begin just on the business deal
of the Cardinal coming
to Michael Corleone
and making his plea
that the Vatican had gotten themselves
in a bit of financial difficulty.
But later my collaborator, Walter Murch,
felt that we might be better off to stress
more the family and the personal side
before we got into the business.
You know, the famous sentence,
"It isn't personal, it's only business,"
well, in this case we wanted to say,
"It isn't business, it's only personal,"
which of course is the real truth
of Don Corleone's famous line.
We eventually decided
to begin in a ceremony
in which Michael was to
be honored by the Church
for his wonderful charitable gifts
of the Vito Andolini Foundation
and as Michael is given this
wonderful award from the Church,
we realize that he's a man who
almost has used this occasion
to pull back his family,
which effectively he
has lost due to his deeds.
And however good his deeds meant to be,
they were not good
deeds, they were evil deeds,
and consequently as we see him,
even in his Commendatore finery
receiving the highest award
the Vatican can bestow,
his face is a mirror of his soul.
It's ravaged and sickly,
and very, very heartbroken,
because what he values the most
is the thing that he has lost.
But he has his children.
And his children at
this point, I would think,
to Michael, mean everything.
His daughter and his son.
The Michael that we're dealing with is
very different than the Michael we know,
and interestingly enough,
one of the toughest decisions
and most heated debate
was over Al Pacino's hair in this film,
because I felt as
though it would be truthful
to show that Michael was no longer
that same handsome young man
with the beautiful hair which Al
has and which is so well known,
but he had more of that steel,
man-approaching-60 crew cut.
When I cut Al Pacino's hair it was
almost like cutting Samson's hair,
'cause it meant that this would
not be the Michael Corleone
that the audience had come to love.
This was a man, really, more in a crisis.
That was more interesting to
me because I was in a crisis.
I, at this point, was very
much like Michael Corleone.
And so when I thought
of making a third film,
I only could imagine we had to deal
with Michael Corleone as an older man.
Now, obviously this flies in the face of
a conventional notion
of movie-sequel making,
in which you try to really hang
on to the successful formula.
In the case of The Godfather,
what made the Godfather films
so successful to popular audiences
was how this figure, Michael
Corleone, seemed always to come on top,
and I was viewing Michael
from a much different perspective,
more how I felt about
myself, at the age I was,
trying to understand, really,
what is important in a man's life,
beyond fame, beyond wealth.
Those things don't
seem to really fulfill,
and I knew that what
does fulfill are your children
and seeing the life of the family go on.
Whenever I meet someone and they tell me,
"Oh, I have six children
and I have 23 grandchildren,"
I say, "Oh, you're a very rich man."
And they look at me and say, "Oh, no, no.
Not really,"
and I say, "Oh, no.
You're a very rich man."
And my mother, you see
her singing behind Eli Wallach,
my father you see to the left of
the frame conducting the band.
This really was the last time I was
to be with my mother and father.
My father passed away shortly after this,
on the night of the Academy
Awards, hit by a stroke,
by the shock of not having
won the Best Song category.
How typically wonderful of him.
He died in the way he lived.
Vincent is the son of Sonny
Corleone, with Lucy Mancini.
We remember in the first Godfather,
Lucy was one of the bridesmaids
and I imagined that there
would be a classic character,
the bastard son of
Sonny who, on one hand,
brings vitality and youth and
strength, very much like the old Sonny
and on the other hand is a dark sheep.
He wasn't raised in the
comfort and the affluence
of the immediate Corleone family.
Obviously we had to interweave the
beginnings of a conspiracy, of a plot.
So we introduced Joe
Mantegna as Joey Zasa,
interwoven with all of
this legitimacy and wealth,
there still are the
vestiges of the mob world.
Ah, there's my little granddaughter
Gia, the little pink girl on the floor,
as a little baby.
Don Novello plays a
kind of family PR fellow,
handling the journalists so that
it all comes out right for Michael,
because above all, what he craves
is the legitimacy that his
father had wished for him.
And we have the little girl cousins,
carrying notes to the older boys.
Of course, Vincent is so handsome
and one of the cousins, Mary,
has always had a shine for him
and just like an awkward 17, 18-year-old,
she comes and flirts with him
and of course, my own daughter
Sofia, plays Mary Corleone.
It's one of my favorite parts of
the film, because she is so real.
She is not an actress. She wasn't
an actress. She was an art student.
But she was Mary Corleone,
and I can remember as kids,
them interacting and having
little crushes on their cousins
and it was all so unacceptable
and so naughty, but they did it,
and flirted and of
course, this was the basis.
It was really Sofia that
was what I had in mind
when I created the character of Mary,
the kind of apple of her father's eye,
who would be able to be
the one to give the check
of all the enormous amount of
money they were going to bestow.
It moves me to this day to see that
scene and her little playful banter,
so real and…
It's true, you know, Sofia
came in for tremendous criticism,
because she was plunged
into an important role
without really having the credentials,
but mainly because I had
seen the story that way,
and at this point, I was making
the movie out of characters
who were in fact my sister or my
father or my mother or my daughter.
And since I meant Sofia
to be the vulnerable one
who would ultimately express the
great tragedy of Michael Corleone,
I chose to give my own,
and indeed, just as in the story
it was Sofia that they
shot the bullets at,
but they were really shooting them at me,
and I knew that.
But I'm thrilled to have
captured the reality of the family
by having Sofia play this part,
despite really what was a
conspiracy on many people's behalf
and all culminating in that
first article in Vanity Fair,
Tina Brown's Vanity Fair magazine,
that just pointed the world at Sofia
as if to say, "Look, he's vulnerable here.
Kill him here."
And that is what the
film ultimately was about,
that there is no worse
way to pay for your sins
than to have your children
be included in the punishment.
Obviously when you attempt
a work of many characters
with serious themes,
certainly that interweave
personal feelings,
psychological, perhaps,
feelings and plot and action,
one tempts a notion of going
where Shakespeare went
and few, if any, people ever
can be compared to Shakespeare.
In fact, that is the subject of Goethe's
The Apprenticeship of Wilhelm Meister,
as he compares himself really against
this extraordinary genius of our time.
One can be guided by Shakespeare and
I looked in Shakespeare for inspiration
in the story of an elderly man trying
to assure some place for himself
in the midst of a family in which
certain people were true and faithful
and others were more manipulative,
trying to gain from the ultimate
succession of power and wealth.
My sister, Tally, who
had been in all three films,
now was emerging as a stronger figure,
more like that woman in the
Scottish play of Shakespeare.
Of course, Andy Garcia as the bastard.
Kay, as the woman who
loved Michael Corleone
so deeply and so
romantically and so lastingly
and yet was forced to turn against him
because of the horror
that he became in her eyes.
All of these were the
potential that I hoped I could,
with Mario's great collaboration,
that I hoped that I could weave
together into a satisfying drama,
even though it would not really be able
to repeat the classic Godfather formula,
which is Michael in the end beating all
his enemies and emerging triumphant,
because, indeed, this film was
about the death of Michael Corleone.
Also, many of the family friends,
who had important functions…
Al Martino as Johnny Fontane,
now singing in his inimitable style
a song that our family jokingly
referred to as "Za Zeach His Own."
I had to get "Za Zeach
His Own" into the film
because after all, that's
what we sang in our house.
And of course, the son, the
little boy, Franc D'Ambrosio,
who just like Michael,
might have had the resistance
to tell his father that he
would go his own way,
this boy also tells his
father, but for another reason,
because just as my family
was made up of artists,
I would imagine that, "What if a
young man in the Corleone family
wanted to pursue an artistic career?"
And I always thought it
would be interesting if one day,
out of nowhere a young man came along,
sort of like Mario Lanza
did when I was a kid
and wanted to be an opera singer
and that would present
Michael with a real dilemma,
because as much as he might
want to suck his son in to be with him,
shoulder to shoulder in this new
charitable vision that Michael had
to pay back these
enormous amounts of money,
to undo the way that they were earned,
he could never fully capture his
son, because his son was an artist
and artists really do stand alone
and work to other
motivations than other people.
An artist is alone in his desire to
pursue the beauty and the tradition
that the artist's
tradition lays before him
and would never be involved,
be a lawyer or be a businessman,
as Michael seems to hope for him.
This was such an interesting experience,
because really it was many years
after the first two films had been made
and really it would never have been made
except for the difficulties
and the aftermath
of that extraordinary
period of productivity,
which took us through two
Godfather films, The Conversation,
Apocalypse Now and then ultimately,
what I like to think of
as "the ping-pong shot,"
that everyone was able to slam down
and put me into a position
of great debt and servitude,
which is of course, where
they like artists to be.
I always joke that if you ever want to
understand who's running the world,
or at any time in history
who's running the world,
just check who's employing
the artists and it will tell you.
So to revisit this
material was so interesting
because not only were we going
back to the story of this family,
we were working with it with
characters that we had begun
who were young people.
Al Pacino was a young man.
Diane Keaton was a young woman.
Everyone, my sister was a young girl.
I was young. My father was young.
Everyone was young and
here we worked on these films
and now, many years later, we're
all going to be brought together again.
In fact, I was in Rome, working
on a different film, a personal film,
which I hoped to make,
one called Megalopolis,
and you know, we were in a
position of somewhat limited resources,
and Paramount proposed
the idea of a third Godfather
and they had a script.
It was a very different kind of a script.
It didn't have very much in it
about Michael Corleone at all.
It tended to be more about
the Vincent Mancini character,
or a character like him,
and really featured
more a similar story of…
Except now drugs and cartels
and pretty much echoing the
kind of story it had done before.
And I felt, "Well, gee, if
you're going to go back,
let's go back and really make Michael
Corleone be the central character."
Indeed, he always was
the central character,
so how could you make another film
without showing what had become of him
and in what ways he paid for his sins?
I like to think that at the
end of Godfather Part II,
when you see those
final images of Michael,
that he's sort of been
given his comeuppance.
It's pretty clear that he's lost
everything and he's punished.
And then I began to feel, well,
maybe he wasn't punished
enough for what he did.
I mean, he killed his own brother.
He killed countless other people.
You know people who kill, I mean,
if you could just take two minutes
before you pull that
trigger or make that decision
and realize how many
people you're killing.
It's not just the person you're
killing, that person has got it easy.
It's the mother and the father
and the brothers and the friends
and the people who love them.
Any death is a hundred deaths
and more hours of heartbreak
than you can almost count.
So I have very, very strong
feelings about those people who,
for their greed or
for their self-interest,
would use violence and use
horror and use terror indiscriminately
without thinking what they're
doing to so many people.
So I really…
Especially that Michael was a good man,
and a young, attractive,
and promising young man,
his conversion from a
good man to an evil man
is more horrible than just some cretin
who never had a moral idea in his eyes.
So I just felt that Michael
had to be punished.
He had to die, and not in an
easy way, to express how I felt,
although I had great sympathy for him,
because in many ways I felt I
was like him in my own category,
not as a criminal, but in a
person who had gone, really,
from a sort of innocent
guy who just loved movies
into something involving
power and influence.
So I did, as with all characters,
Mr. Kurtz and Mr. Tucker or Mr Corleone,
I have tremendous personal feelings
myself that I might be like them.
George Hamilton was styled after
any number of Hollywood lawyers.
And a very funny situation, I'm
trying to get his hair to be gray.
It turned orange, it turned red.
Obviously, The Godfather
was a famous movie
and many people were
anxious to participate.
You'll notice in the family scene,
as another indication
of the Corleones' power,
and the parallel with the Coppola family,
you'll see Willie Brown,
who is of course, now the
mayor of San Francisco,
but a very charismatic and
important person in California politics
and was friendly with our family.
My brother August worked with him
to create the wonderful Fine Arts
Film Building in San Francisco State
and again, like the Coppolas,
these people would wander in and out
and Willy Brown came to
Rome to be in this scene.
It was a collection of important people,
people from the Vatican,
people in politics, family friends,
and uncomfortably for Michael,
the vestiges of his
father's early gang origins
as different small-time hoods,
such as a kind of Joey Zasa,
more in the fabric of the hoods,
perhaps, in the '70s and '80s
who were taking over,
who were really kind of a new
breed of tough businessmen.
Obviously these types of
wise guys have been portrayed
in many wonderful movies,
notably Marty Scorsese's films.
I sort of had, in this picture,
the obligation to try to do it all,
to satisfy myself with a personal story
of a man about my age at the
time of the story, Michael Corleone,
who no longer had the passion for success
and to beat everyone, and to get richer.
But was more thinking of the things
that really matter, which is to say,
your relationship with your children,
or the lack of relationship
with your children.
I myself have never
allowed that to happen.
Joe Mantegna was an actor
I had known for years before.
A wonderful person I have always enjoyed,
and it was really just a
question of trying to find a role
that would be suitable for him
and try to be a little bit of the more
well-dressed don of the era, in the '80s.
Bring that sensibility into
the mix of this chronicle, really,
that kind of spans so many years.
This picture also had another very
difficult handicap, if I may call it that,
is that it had to be
made, really, in a rush.
From the time we started the movie
till the time it actually
came out in the theaters,
I remember on Christmas Day,
was less than a year,
although even in the
scriptwriting phase, I said,
"What's the difference if it
takes another six months?"
It would give me and Mario a chance
to hone this complicated material,
but the company needed
the film that December
and my requests ultimately
were shrugged away
by the then-head of the
corporation in New York,
who I don't feel understood
anything about the Godfather films
or why they were successful.
It was clearly more for the stock price.
Ultimately I think they
were correctly assessing
that unless they had some big windfall,
that the company was vulnerable
and it would be taken over.
And indeed it was.
And so I had no strength to be able to
ask that the film be delayed six months,
which caused me a
lot of fear and frustration
because I didn't feel I
had it all quite together,
especially the ending,
which I spent countless
nights staying up over
and trying to reconcile in my mind
as to what would be appropriate,
although I must say that I'm extremely
happy with the ending of this film
and the way it echoed
the other Godfathers
in terms of an ending
sequence that was interposed
or parallel-cut with another event,
in this case the opera
Cavalleria Rusticana.
Interesting in this scene of Joey Zasa
confronting the bastard Vincent Mancini,
there is an incident
where he bites his ear.
That is right out of Cavalleria Rusticana
when the same thing happens
between Turiddu and Alfio,
and I've often felt that the music
from Cavalleria Rusticana and the story,
rustic chivalry and the
strange Sicilian notion
of revenge and insult,
this peasant village mentality,
really runs through all
of the Godfather stories,
and of course, maybe any
modern Italian mafioso story
and so I was very anxious to…
Since I had this third
opportunity to make a film
that hadn't been something I really
thought was ever going to happen,
that I could really use
Cavalleria Rusticana,
as part of, now, a story of the family
as they were on the highest, here,
of economic and social success.
When they were truly
wealthy and truly powerful
and truly longed to be
out of the criminal milieu.
The notion of the family photograph
as also an indication of who's included
and who's not included.
As you recall in the first Godfather,
they took the family photograph
and the father was very
anxious that Michael be included.
In this case, the fact that Michael
includes this kind of rough son,
illegitimate son of his brother Sonny
into the family obviously echoes that,
but also portends that some of the
story is going to deal with this collision
between the old ways, the old
passions, the old gangster behavior,
and the new sophistication.
That's my dad, as I always
remember him, conducting the band.
He never missed a cue in all my
knowledge in doing things with him,
since I was a young kid.
But on this picture, he missed a cue
and when he missed that cue, and I said,
"Dad, you missed the cue," he says,
"No, no, no. I didn't miss the cue,"
and I said, "Dad, you missed it."
And he sloughed it off but I knew
then, if my father would miss a cue,
that he didn't have much
longer to be with us, and he didn't.
Now Sofia was going
to dance with Al Pacino,
neither of whom could dance,
and quite on her own,
my little granddaughter Gia ran out on
the floor and wanted to dance with Sofia
and didn't want Sofia to dance
with Al and all through the scene,
the big ending, you could
see Gia, very, very upset
that Sofia was dancing with Al,
and just held onto her and held onto her.
It was so real.
You know, when you use non-actors
and you encourage them to play with you
and to participate with
you as, in effect, Sofia was,
you get something that
isn't poised and slick.
You get something that's real and
that's what, of course, I was going for.
It's hard for me to imagine now
the Corleone family
at this level of wealth.
I mean the Coppola
family became successful,
but not to the point where you could
give a $ 100,000,000 check to charity,
although it would be a nice thing to do.
But it was fun to put our family in
some sort of context with this family,
although there was much tragedy to come.
You know when film sequels are made,
they're made because above
all the studio wants to basically
keep mining the same mine
and make the same movie,
because works of art as
money-making endeavors
are extremely problematic.
You don't know when you give
someone some money to write a script
or some people to get together
and make a film, you have no idea
whether what they're going to
come up with will please an audience
to the extent that would make
that audience come to see it.
So the studio ultimately is in
the position of wanting to repeat
what they have that's successful,
try to do it as much like it,
and that's why you have
these successions of sequels…
Or even when they're not
sequels, you watch a movie,
I mean, it isn't surprising to see a
movie and realize it's the same plot
that you had already
seen in another film.
So I realized that
of course, in this film,
although my heart more was with
the family and the children of the story,
that I really had to have action
and the type of gangster violence
that people might have expected
from the previous Godfather.
And of course, Vincent
Mancini was the vehicle,
because he was young and a hothead,
when he was put in the
situation with this lovely journalist,
somewhat willful journalist
played by Bridget Fonda,
he had to demonstrate the kind
of cool, calculating personality,
that maybe you would have thought of
from Sonny, or in some sense, Michael,
in that he would even say,
"Ah, she means nothing to me.
What do I care?
Kill her if you want, I don't care."
Yet, he had to turn out
to be something of a hero
and win the audience's
attention as a man of action
because Michael wasn't going to
be that kind of man of action any more
and I couldn't think of, nor was
I interested in, making him that.
I was interested in the man's sense
of what he had done with his life,
rather than how he was going
to beat his new adversary.
So Vincent Mancini was clearly
the young man who was going to,
in a funny way, parallel the Michael
Corleone story of the earlier films
and show that rise to power
through his cunning and his bravery.
It's funny. I mean even as a director,
I had become like Michael and I
really wasn't interested in the blood hits
and how could we dream up some
spectacular way to shoot somebody
that no one had ever seen.
I just… To me, now, at my age,
the idea of being out on a set,
and having to tell the actors how to
hold their gun as they run into the room
to cover the FBI guy, I mean I just
could not possibly be interested in that,
and no doubt that's a great weakness,
as is, in this film, Michael's
lack of interest in those things,
which gave Connie Corleone the
chance to emerge as a strong woman,
almost like the original Godfather.
I heard from Mario Puzo that the
real person he based Don Corleone on,
and all those sayings and that wisdom,
that the real person he based
that character on was his mother.
It's interesting that
there are many things
that my power and youth and
passion and clout got me through
in Godfather II say,
where actors would say,
"Well, I'm not doing it unless
you pay me so much money,
or I won't participate,"
that I was able to very nimbly avoid
the problems in this third Godfather,
I didn't have the power any more.
So when I said, "Oh, it has to be
called The Death of Michael Corleone,"
which puts the whole film
in a totally different context,
or if Robert Duvall told me, "Oh,
well, if I'm going to be in the film,
I want to be paid as much as Al Pacino,"
or whatever he told me,
I don't even remember.
But I no longer had the
persuasiveness or the…
They didn't fear me, to
use a phrase from the movie.
So I ultimately lost Robert
Duvall very late in the game.
He was very pivotal to me,
because he was a brother.
He was really from the
first movie in the family
and I greatly reduced
the role of that lawyer.
My idea was that Robert
Duvall was the character
who had become very close
to the charities and the Vatican
and who had, as a brother,
brought to Michael this opportunity
to work with the Vatican Bank
and when I lost that, I
did a very fast rewrite
and tried to approach it a different way,
making the character of the
lawyer less a family character
and more like the kind
of lawyers I had met.
But when you lose someone in your family,
to me, it's the loss
that keeps on losing.
You don't lose them once.
You lose them every day from then on.
It's over and over, because everything
is different than it would have been
had you had that son
or father or brother.
In this case, losing Robert Duvall to
play Tom Hagen in this new modern story
was a profound loss
to me and to this movie.
Here we are in a scene that really
was the beginning of the whole movie.
This is the scene where the
representative of the Vatican Bank,
custodian and
businessman for the Vatican,
explains his dire problem
to Michael Corleone
in the hope of getting the
Corleone family to bail them out.
This material on the Vatican,
it's very hard for anyone,
especially when dealing with the Vatican,
to say something is true or not true.
But anyone who has read any history
knows that anything anyone has said
about the Vatican over the
thousands of years, that it was true.
The Vatican was as much an
institution of secular activity…
I mean Borgias were popes.
Every possible
conceivable crime and horror
was committed within
and without those halls.
So we're dealing with a fact
and I would respectfully submit
that everything I put into the
film dealing with the Vatican,
its manipulation of money,
the shadows around the
death of the Pope of that era,
I felt was true and learned of
that from people who told me.
Not the least of whom told me the
very strange manipulations of the fact
that the Vatican Bank for a
while owned Paramount Studios,
something that I just took
great glee in thinking about,
given that it was Paramount Studios
who wanted so badly to make this picture,
for whatever their financial reason was.
And way back at the time that I
was making the first Godfather
when I went up in the elevator
to visit Charlie Bluhdorn,
I would see mysterious men,
some of whose names are now legendary,
who played a role in the
enormous scandals of a later period
with the Vatican Bank and who
ended up dying either by hanging
or by a sort of mysterious execution.
So, I feel that what I did
in trying to take the
corruption and financial power
and improprieties to the highest level of
one of our highest spiritual institutions
was justified by personal information
and things and people I saw.
An interesting note of the
actor playing the Cardinal.
Obviously he is a kind of villain,
although a supposedly sympathetic one,
but he's Donal Donnelly, and
when I was a young filmmaker,
I desperately wanted to
have him play the leprechaun
in the film Finian's Rainbow,
and I tried so hard
to convince the studio
that the character of Og the
Leprechaun should be shy
and almost frightened of his own voice
because he was the
one they sent after Finian,
and of course the studio was sure
that the best person was Tommy Steele,
who was the least shy
person I have ever known,
very talented but the least shy.
And I wanted Donal Donnelly,
so years later I had the pleasure of
casting Donal in quite a different part,
but those are the little footnotes that
you bump up against that are amusing.
The scene of the Banco
Immobiliare takeover
was the first scene we shot
on this Godfather III picture,
and of course, it's always
a very frightening time.
Making sure that everyone looks
well and that the characters all seem to
suggest who they are.
There were some interesting
people who were extras in that scene.
One is Gregory Corso, who is the famous
and very, very interesting
Beat poet, friend of Kerouac
and Allen Ginsberg, he's in there.
I'll point him out when he pops up.
This was the first
day that, I think, Sofia…
No, we shot Sofia later, because
at the time of shooting this
we thought Winona Ryder
was going to play the
part of Mary Corleone
and so we had to go back
and save the alleged place.
That's Gregory Corso coming.
He just passed away this year.
That's Helmut Berger playing…
I forget his name now in the story.
But he was… I thought Helmut
was appropriately sinister
and very much like the real-life
figure that he's meant to stand for,
and the man who was
standing in the elevator
when I went up to the top of
the Gulf and Western Building.
This particular scene
was very traumatized
for a lot of reasons.
It had to do with the
fact that they didn't tell me
that they were ready for
the scene and the ADs, who,
especially in New York,
tend to be like jocks,
just kind of pulled her up
there and stuck her in there
with the photographer and
they said, "Okay, do the scene."
And they didn't… They wanted to
get the lighting or what have you.
And Sofia was a young
kid and I was furious
that they didn't have me go
up and prepare her for the scene
rather than traumatize
her in the way they did.
So whenever I see that scene…
That scene was in and out of
the picture and it obviously is not
as good a scene as
some of the earlier ones.
So, it annoys me that that was done.
Movie crews can be like
football players most of the time.
You have to realize that
Sofia had by now become
a cause célèbre, the
publicity of a father who had
put his daughter in the
movie, seemingly irresponsibly,
but my standpoint is that
we only put Sofia in the role
because the day before we
were to shoot it with Winona Ryder,
Winona Ryder dropped out and
there was absolutely nothing left
to shoot without the character
of Mary because we had been
stalling, waiting for a month
and the studio wanted me
to close down and was like
sending me lists of young women…
Wonderful actresses like Madeleine Stowe
and other women who were the
talented, beautiful actresses of the day
but I very much wanted an 18-year-old.
Someone that I believe
could be a girl like Sofia.
So, pressed with the pressure from
the studio to want to stop shooting
for three weeks to search for a
more conventional kind of actress,
I just basically exercised my
rights to put someone in the film
that I thought would be best.
That decision was then vilified
and became a story in itself,
but it's a decision that I've never
regretted and as I watch the film here,
and I get to see Sofia
and how real she was,
just like the kind of kid
she was supposed to be.
I'm happy I made that decision,
although Sofia is of course now
a woman of 29 and a successful director.
It's great for me to
have this record of her,
when she was a kid, and
even though it was rough on her
and to this day, follows
her, I think very unjustly,
I'm thrilled to have
this great home movie
that I can look at her as I
remember her at that age.
This is an interesting notion,
the Vatican would not allow us
to depict us going into the Vatican,
and there was a big fuss about it
and we were there shooting,
and no one knew what to do
and so what I did is I went on
the public street, by the Vatican,
and last minute, just had them set up
the costumed guard,
and the crossing gate,
but it was really just
going down the street.
Had nothing to do with the Vatican.
So it looked as though
the car was going in,
but of course it wasn't.
You know, these institutions
tend to, through the idea of…
Although they're public institutions,
be it the army or the Vatican
or anyone, nowadays, they
choose to control their image
by giving you access
or not giving you access
and since they owned the Vatican
and have for several thousand years.
Though it's…
I don't know how legal that
is, really, if you read the history.
Nonetheless, they control it
and then they're able to
perpetuate their position.
This was a fabulous
room in a great palace
where we were able to
introduce what was something
similar to the power
struggle in Italy at that time.
This is old history now,
but there was, in those days,
a very mysterious
Masonic group known as P2,
and it was perhaps an
alliance of very powerful
Catholic businessmen,
who were in control of things
and this was the almost mysterious
Mafia-like organization
on a higher level.
I felt that the story
of the Corleone family
seems to be a continual rise,
up higher and higher into politics,
into, you know, the
very citadels of power,
such as the Vatican and
organizations of foreign businessmen
and it was just more of the
same, that the higher you go,
you just run into the
Mafia, in a new form.
Not the Mafia in actuality
but in terms of practices
and it's very interesting to
me that wherever I go I am told,
be it the Mayor of New York or..
. People tell me things, of how,
"Saddam Hussein loves The
Godfather and always, to his inner circle,
quotes the lines of the Godfather."
And so in a funny way, it's
true that the higher you go
in this politics and language of power,
you run into the same
stuff that is going on,
when people are fighting
over a couple of city blocks.
This character, of course, was meant to
portray a highest level
of power in politics,
and all Italians know
who this man is meant to
be by a quote that is given
at the end of the picture
which he is very famous for,
as well as for his thick glasses.
But I was always very surprised
when this movie came out in Italy,
how none of the Italian journalists or
people were the slightest bit shocked
by any of the allegations
it was making about
the involvement of their
government with the Mafia,
or in the possibility that
their pope was murdered.
And the truth was that they sort of..
. It was old news.
They sort of all have known about it
and digested it and so there was
nothing the slightest bit controversial
about it in this movie.
That is Martin Scorsese's mother, Katy,
a most wonderful lady and a
great cook and a wonderful actress
and really a delightful,
delightful lady that we've lost.
But I'm so happy to
have her in the movie,
so I know I can see her, if I miss her.
When I was talking to
George Lucas recently,
and we were talking about
an actress and discussing her,
about how beautiful she was
and George looked at me and said,
"Yeah," he said. "She's okay.
But Sofia, she's really beautiful."
I found Andy Garcia just a very,
very nice young man to work with,
very talented, very self-motivated,
very much working for the project.
I do have to say that in my
career, one of the joys of my career,
of all the different movies I worked on,
is the cast have always
been my greatest friend,
or my greatest allies.
They've always helped the project
and always with such intelligence
and self-sacrifice.
I really, almost unanimously
throughout my career on all the projects,
I found that to be the
case and here was Andy,
working with this
now-controversial daughter of mine,
who had never really
acted except as a child,
when she was the little sister
in Peggy Sue Got Married
or she was in Rumblefish.
Sofia was always like my good luck charm
to have her be in my movies.
And Vincent was so kind to her in
the midst of the raging controversy
that we tried to make this movie with.
I loved the story of the daughter
who has a crush on her cousin,
because indeed, the
Coppolas, my side of the family,
really come from a union of two cousins.
My great-grandmother was a
young girl in the south of Italy
who was very talented with
embroidery and crocheting
and would occasionally scratch
her nose with her darning needle
and her nose became infected.
And the doctors, of course, of
that day only knew to amputate it.
And so my…
This beautiful young woman had no nose
and she was forced to
marry her own cousin,
so that someone would
take her and so my whole line,
my grandfather, Augustino
Coppola, was born of two cousins,
which of course, certain
aunts and relatives said,
"Yeah, that's why the
whole family is crazy."
So that love between the
cousins, I found especially intriguing,
but I think Michael's real
desire not to allow a sanction,
that love she had, was because
he knew that as far as he had come
from his father's roots,
that era before World War II,
the part that will never be made,
that was written but will never be made,
the rise of the Corleones.
Mario used to say, "Yes, the good years,
when we killed everyone
and no one killed us."
But Michael knows that
Vincent is a throwback to that
and for his daughter to love
him and perhaps marry him,
that it would put her in danger.
Ironically, who put her in
danger was him, himself.
Here we have a scene in which Joey Zasa
tries to enlarge his
piece of the crime family,
senses that Michael has lost interest.
I feel you can tell, I
have always said that
you know whether a man is on
his way up or on his way down.
I myself, you know, in years past
could say, "You know, I clearly am
"so full of anxious passion
to do these movies."
I'm certainly on the way
up," and just as I record this,
equally, I'm on the way down,
because I don't have the passion
for the kinds of things
that you must do in movies,
to have them be popular today.
I feel the only thing that
could give me that passion
is if I would be allowed to
try to explore something new,
but to be condemned
to make the same movie,
over and over again, it's
sort of like Jean-Paul Sartre.
It's sort of like
somebody's idea of hell,
that you have a medium, the cinema,
which maybe we've touched
8% of what its language is
and what it can do.
And to be told by the people who
own it, who make money with it,
who buy jewelry for
their wives with it, that,
"No, you can't any
more experiment with it.
"You can't take it into new territory."
You must do the same
thing over and over again."
That is a bitter, bitter pill to swallow.
Obviously, the big scene like this
harkens back to earlier Godfathers
when we have the so-called
five families, the old Mafiosi,
clearly this is the old kind of
story in which Michael Corleone
usually proves to outsmart them all.
There were many obligations
to try to have this film,
not only have some of the
values that I've been talking about
that were personally
more important to me,
but we had to drum up interesting
violent sequences or action sequences.
We had to kill a bunch of people in
a way we hadn't killed them before,
so we just did our best.
And I kind of went to my…
"I've got to kill 20 people.
God, I hate doing scenes
where I've got to kill 20 people."
Unless it was really something totally…
That I'd never imagined before.
And in the scene we had this idea that,
"Well, if you were in the
top of some Las Vegas hotel,
"how would you wipe out,"
"as was Michael's style to
do, all the opposition at once?"
"What if the tables were
turned and a guy like Joey Zasa,"
"this more new-style mobster"
"in more the image of
the Teflon Don of fame,"
how would he approach this?"
And I thought,
"How intriguing it
would be if just suddenly,
"everything just started vibrating
and you didn't even know why"
"and the walnuts were
rolling on the table"
"and the oranges were
rolling off the table"
"and turned out that the bad
guys had just engaged a helicopter,"
they'd just fly right up to the
window and machine-gun everyone."
So that's the way we thought we would go
and we would perhaps
never show the helicopter.
That would be sort of far out,
for filmmakers always love to do
things without showing anything
and usually those are the
best things, but in this case,
we did break down and
got some extra shots,
I believe, of the
specter of the helicopter.
Of course, Vincent Mancini
senses something wrong,
especially when this wily old
guy with one foot in the grave,
kind of goes out of the room,
to try to mollify Joey Zasa.
Vincent, who's sort
of closer to the street,
senses something amiss that
perhaps even Michael doesn't.
But Michael doesn't care
about this stuff anymore.
Michael doesn't care about
the gain of having
this turf or that turf.
This is an interesting little custom
that I think someone told me about,
that at these parties they
would just pass around
a tray of beautiful jewelry
and watches, probably hot,
and anyone could take what they wanted.
There's the vibrating
which just starts in now,
out of the glass window was this notion
of wiping out all of your
opponents in one easy move.
And of course all Michael has to really
lead him to freedom would
be this young nephew.
The incident of the coat, it
was something I read about
that this one guy really was
so hung up on getting his coat
that he ends up getting
massacred with the others.
It's a little bit based on Apalachin,
I think, when the FBI came upon
all of the Mafia leaders in one place,
eating steaks and having a good time.
So we imagined, how can
we make an unusual sequence
that could live up to some of the violent
sequences in the earlier Godfathers.
Violence is a hard thing to do, you know.
It's a… Without repeating yourself.
That's a funny statement,
"Violence is a hard thing to do
without repeating yourself."
In the end, it's about flesh
being torn, and blood. I hate it.
Michael, here, is clearly
not the guy in command of…
His wits are not as tuned to
survival as his young nephew is.
The younger Michael perhaps
would have outsmarted them.
And I ultimately feel
that's what audiences
who saw this picture wanted him to do.
They wanted to see the old Michael
who just was one step ahead of them
and it was hard to have him
be that and at the same time,
be more concerned with
matters of his heart and his soul.
This scene echoed,
quite a bit, Godfather I,
where after an attack,
the family sat around in the
apartment, had bodyguards.
Here, note that Michael
is drinking lots of water
and if you look through
the three films, you'll see
he has this tremendous
thirst to drink water.
This is his diabetes.
Now I had made two
Godfather films after really only
intending to make one, not
even very happily doing that
as it turned out, and
making a second one,
which was a very happy experience for me,
because we were able to
do it without any interference
and many years later, just as Michael
feels anxious to want
to get on with your life
and to mature and to
try to be a better man,
a better artist, you get pulled
back into something of your youth.
The past is always
having a war with the future.
I find I try so hard to be in the
future and to think of new things
and new thoughts, and always,
I'm pulled back by the past.
As I sit here, recording this commentary,
what is it other than being pulled
back into something of the past?
Because no one is ever interested
in the future, except artists, really.
Artists are the ones who
want to step forward, move on,
but every other part of
society wants them to stay back
where everyone is all huddled
against the storm, the past, you know.
They call it the
present, but it's the past.
Now characters like Neri,
played by Richard Bright,
are emerging as the Caporegimes.
Talia herself is the main
Caporegime in the family
as they plan to brace themselves
against this very, very
well-organized and financed onslaught.
Here, of course, Michael
really shows his vulnerability.
He is a man very sick from diabetes.
And I think this type of thing,
to try to express Michael's
ultimate aging and disillusion, is
what people did not want to see.
They don't want to see
Michael Corleone as a mortal,
as a man struggling with
what is a horrible disease.
They want to see him cool
and always on top of his enemies
and I think that was
one perhaps strong way
that in pleasing myself, I
disappointed my audience.
I feel it would have been
a wonderful dimension
that the character that, I think,
George Hamilton valiantly played…
Because people felt it was
very inappropriate that he be cast.
He's such a wonderfully funny
person and charming person.
The notion of having
him be in a Godfather film
was considered inappropriate.
And I think he valiantly played his part,
but you can see how much more complex
it would have been had
it been Bobby Duvall,
who was the family lawyer arranging these
high-level machinations with the Vatican.
And partly being even suspect.
Of course, with the Godfather
stories it's always a puzzle
as to who is really responsible.
Obviously we know that Joey
Zasa, played by Joe Mantegna,
was the front man, but you always wonder,
"Well, who's really behind it?
Who's really the villain?"
We've learned from
previous Godfather films,
that it's never the one that you suspect.
There's always someone
higher up, very high up.
Here, Tally begins to emerge as a…
I guess like the Caporegimes, there
was originally Tessio and Clemenza
and here you have Tally, or Constanza,
and Neri as the two main
lieutenants who are trying to…
Much as in Godfather I,
when Marlon Brando was
attempted to be killed and the family was
trying to protect him and
trying to protect themselves.
There is a parallel throughout
this movie with Godfather I,
more than the other
work I did on the films.
And whereas, for some reason, it
was all right to see Marlon Brando,
as Vito Corleone, the first Godfather,
in a state of weakness and illness,
it doesn't feel right to a certain
interpretation of The Godfather
to ever see Michael
Corleone in this status,
although to me, what is
about to happen here is
the beginning of a rebuilding of
what really means most to him.
I have no doubt that Michael,
despite the limitations of his
Sicilian-American upbringing
and how men are supposed to be
and how women are supposed to be
and wives are supposed
to be, he really loved Kay,
much as Diane and
Al really love each other
or loved each other or probably
will always love each other.
I felt we were dealing with real things
in the context of this romantic novel.
And I wanted to look at Al more like
a Marlon Brando figure
in the first Godfather,
although that character, Don Corleone,
in all of this jeopardy was at peace
because although he
had done terrible things,
somehow he had
managed to outwit the devil.
He had managed to emerge,
though a murderer and a gangland leader
and obviously a person who…
You would have to say an evil man,
he managed somehow to have
us feel that he was a good man.
This scene once happened to me.
I remember it very vividly.
I shot it just the way I remember it,
my son and my daughter,
coming in at a time
when it looked pretty bad for me
and for our family.
It's very touching to me to
have been able to encapsulate
something that I really remember,
with fiction, albeit with my daughter.
There was always
something intriguing to me
of the Italian girl who was privileged,
who, as we see there, had a
beautiful Alfa Romeo sports car
and was so fashionable and yet
drawn to these mean streets,
these rank hangouts, to
pursue the cousin she loved,
even though it was very, very
dangerous and forbidden by her family.
I find the story of Mary Corleone and her
relationship between
her father and her cousin,
were very moving to me, to
think what that must really mean.
Go against your father's will
because you love your cousin.
For those of you who
want to learn how to cook,
and I always felt The Godfather
at least should give a recipe
every once in a while, this is a pretty
authentic method of rolling gnocchi.
The whole secret of
rolling gnocchi really is
the touch when you flip
them over with your finger.
You can do it with a fork, too.
Gnocchi is made with an equal
part of flour and mashed potatoes,
a little bit of salt, and
you create the dough,
it's really a potato dumpling,
and then you roll it out
in these long tubular
strips as you'll see them do.
Then with a knife cut them into
little three-quarter-inch sections
and then you have to have the touch.
So you need your cousin
to help guide your
finger as you flip it around.
You get a little dimple in the gnocchi
and that's what makes them more tender
so they're not just
like little pellets of lead
when they come out of the water.
When they're cooked
they'll rise to the top,
so you don't have to dump the water.
You can just scoop them off the top.
And, you know, most gnocchi in
restaurants are too soft and mushy.
My gnocchi, I don't know
why, are just a little more firm,
but this is how you roll them.
You see the little dimple?
That's the secret, that little
dimple when they flip over.
I find this love story so sweet,
you know, so touching to me.
And both of them so young and…
I mean this holding of her hand
is just going to make such
unhappiness for the two of them,
it makes me want to cry.
Nothing but trouble will come from this.
And tragedy.
Here we are on very familiar turf.
We're at the Festa of San Gennaro.
The policemen on horseback
is an important element
that's established earlier
and of course, you know,
Joey Zasa, like any number
of civic-minded men of affairs,
John Gotti or others,
you know, really always tried
to reward the neighborhoods
and throw festivals with fireworks
and I think that's what
Joey Zasa is doing here.
The society of Anthony Meucci
is going to raffle off a Cadillac.
Meucci, for those who don't
know, is the Italian-American
who invented the telephone, they
say before Alexander Graham Bell.
At any rate, the two of them
long have been associated
with the invention of the telephone
and Italians always like to
say that it was really Meucci.
But many great technological
inventions have more than one inventor.
Television has three
or four that I can think of.
These great innovations
come about of the times
and sometimes more than one
person thinks of them, so, yes, it's true.
Meucci was an inventor of the telephone.
This is Elizabeth Street in New
York, incidentally where I live
when I'm in New York myself now.
I have a little apartment at
the end of it, maybe I'll see it.
You can see the way the horse
is being woven through this,
somewhat hopefully, mysteriously.
The little girl whose
face is shocked with…
Her name, I think, was
Jessica, a very sweet little girl
and I still get letters from her.
She must be a big girl now.
We always wanted to have a coup de grâce
performed by a guy on a horse,
dressed up as a New York cop,
so we got to do it for this movie.
So it was just like Godfather I,
while Michael was clinging for life,
or in a weakened state,
the family went ahead
and engaged in violence
which Don Vito Corleone
would have objected to
and now Michael does.
Of course, his sister, Connie,
and his Caporegimes
and Vincent himself said,
"What were we to do?
They were coming after us."
And Michael seems to
understand that it has to end.
That you just can't keep
outsmarting your enemy in this
back and forth, Oresteia type
of violence begetting violence.
To do that is to sacrifice your youth,
because ultimately it
will destroy the future.
Well, in all the trouble spots
of the world, I always wonder
in the Middle East and other places,
don't they think of their young people?
Don't they think that to constantly
trade violence for violence,
only begets more violence,
that they're just eating up
their own children, in a way.
But it goes on, even as I'm speaking
and will, no doubt, long after I'm gone.
That's a nice set.
That's Dean Tavoularis,
once again working with us in Rome,
shooting a film that was
supposedly set in New York in Rome.
It would have been wise, had
we perhaps had a little budget
to shoot more of a second
unit in New York than we did.
We did go around and
shoot streets and entrances,
but it would've been nice to have
more of the texture of New York in this.
You don't really feel it as
much as you should, I think.
Of course one of the
exciting things of this movie
was the fact that not only
did the cast come back
but all of the main
collaborators, those living,
and we had as our director
of photography, Gordon Willis.
We had Dean Tavoularis,
for wardrobe, however,
we worked for the first time,
with a new designer of the
costumes, was Milena Canonero,
picking up from the wonderful work
that Johnny Johnstone
had done on the first film
and Theodora Van Runkle
had done on the second film.
And also on the editorial team,
Walter Murch and Barry Malkin,
long-term collaborators.
And associate editor was Lisa Fruchtman,
who had worked also on Apocalypse Now.
So it was a family,
both in the crew and the team.
The producers were Fred
Roos and Gray Frederickson
and then Chuck Mulvehill provided
essential productorial services.
So the difficulty had to do with
trying really to get it all
done, get it all written,
pull these themes together all in
time to be released that Christmas.
I found it really pleasurable
to work with Eli Wallach.
His family came to visit one day
and they… Right in front of him,
they said, "Oh, don't let Eli overact."
And I laughed and smiled
because I just got such
a kick out of what he did.
I suppose one could say
that he laid it on a little thick,
but I certainly enjoyed
it and if it's a little broad…
It's I who enjoyed it. So I did it.
I always liked Eli Wallach.
I loved him in Baby Doll
and he was a pleasure to be around.
I love the idea of a character
who's this old, old, old, old man
who's always giving you advice, you know,
like "Well, I don't have
much longer to live,"
but really he's going to outlive you all
and he's going to have
the last laugh, almost.
His resolution in this movie
is particularly amusing to me.
And here in another Godfather tradition
suddenly we're in the beautiful
sunny setting of Sicily and…
This was a very
beautiful part of the shoot,
because we were really in Palermo
and outside of Palermo where
the people are so wonderful.
And anyone who sees this movie
and sees Sicily as a beautiful place,
this is not even a tenth of it.
It is the most beautiful island and
such sweet and hospitable people.
I think perhaps that's where
the Sicilians get the reputation
as being especially tough, it's
only because they are so open,
and so arms-embraced, that
if you take advantage of them,
you do something that can only be
responded to with the
most harsh response,
because they are very
trusting and great people.
These were beautiful settings in
Sicily, these wonderful palaces and…
Indeed, many of them were
the same locations we used
for the first and second
Godfather pictures.
This particular villa where he meets with
the old timers is the very first villa
where Michael had taken
his young wife, Apollonia.
Here we have, again,
actors from the past.
Franco Citti, who was
one of the two shepherds
who had been Michael's loyal bodyguard,
is now back, more elderly.
This is a new actor, playing the
part that Corrado Gaipa played,
if you remember, the old uncle
who had taken care of Michael
when he stayed at the villa.
This is his villa.
The name Lucchesi is
the man I referred to earlier,
who was the gentleman with the
thick black glasses and represents,
I won't say his name, the highest level
of political power at that time in Italy
and only recently has been
through many, many inquiries,
regarding his association with the Mafia,
which has all conveniently,
seemingly, been dealt with,
but everyone knows the truth.
I feel Al Pacino was very
brave in working with me
to take Michael outside
of the pre-fabricated,
Michael Corleone-type role.
I mean, starting from day one,
when we cut his hair,
which sort of really determined
the course we were going to go.
He wasn't going to be
the Michael Corleone
of the other two pictures
who was going to be one step
ahead of all the adversaries.
That he was going to be a
combination more of Marlon's character
in the first Godfather, and a kind of man
more concerned with
his hope of redemption,
and hope to be reunited with his family
to a hope of earning back,
if not the respect, but
the regard of his wife.
These were his concerns rather than
who was going to control the
cocaine business in West Long Beach
or these idiotic concerns that
the powerful men of our time are…
Who's going to own
cable or who's going to
figure out how they
can sell air to people.
Michael's concern is, I think, deeper.
And nothing is higher,
I would think for him,
than his relationship with his son,
who, while he wants to be
independent of his father,
still wants to express
something to his father,
"Accept me and how
I'm different, but also,
"understand that it means really more"
"that I can go my own
way and yet be your son,"
and love you, and
respect you as a father."
And I was moved by the thought
that this boy would sing an
old Sicilian song to his father
and not even know that it
was bringing back memories
of Michael Corleone's young wife,
who had been sacrificed in
the insane warfare between thugs.
At this point, we had the
footage of those old movies
and we said, "Oh, people will know
that he's thinking of the young bride."
And then we said,
"Well, maybe they won't.
"So, what the hell.
Let's just cut it in."
And also it was a parallel
to his beautiful daughter, who…
He recognizes, and very aptly,
that Apollonia was murdered
because she was the
wife of a Mafia gangster
and if the love of Vincent
was to not be exterminated,
that one day his own daughter,
Mary, would be killed
perhaps in the same way
that his young wife was.
These scenes with the
kids were very tough.
At this time, in Palermo, there
were Paramount executives,
kind of visiting and
staying in the hotel rooms
and at that point, Sofia was so frazzled
by the enormous lack of support
that she felt from all these people
and the idea that it had been such
a self-serving mistake to cast her.
I remember this scene in particular.
The pressure, poor kid.
Sofia showed that
she had a lot of strength
and grace during that period
and, of course, it didn't stop.
It went on for years, but it was…
This was a tough scene
and her confidence was pretty
much smashed at this point,
and the young boy too, you
know, who was a newcomer as well.
I think I stole that image
from a Visconti film,
the idea that there would
be just this old castle
and the curtain blowing
and some rock and roll music coming out.
At this time, in Palermo,
I was pretty much
hysterically trying to figure
out the ending of the movie.
There had been an ending of the script,
which basically was that sort
of Al Pacino and Diane Keaton,
and the characters of Michael and Kay,
have something of a reconciliation
and she does accept him
and when they go to church one Easter,
as they come out of their church,
some gunmen come and
shoot him and he falls down
onto the steps, bleeding, and
Kay goes up to him and says,
"Michael, Michael, are you dying?"
And he looks at her and says, "No.
" And then he dies.
Lying to her for the last time.
And I liked that ending
and that was the ending
and then I became really troubled
that just to kill him at the
end somehow wasn't enough.
You know the movie, in my mind,
was The Death of Michael Corleone,
so of course I have that gene
injected the wrong way into me,
that if it's going to be called
The Death of Michael Corleone,
then of course I'm not
going to have him die,
you know, perverse as that might be.
And I just…
I don't know, I just couldn't…
I couldn't digest that ending
and it's a little bit like the
experience on Apocalypse Now,
where the more I worked on the film
and the more I made it
more and more surreal
and more and more kind of philosophical,
the more the typical ending
of just a big battle at the end
just didn't satisfy me.
And so I really began to
try to think of another ending,
and I went into my typical mode
of staying up all night and writing
and trying to write
and talking to everyone
and asking Mario, "What can I do?
What can I do for the ending?"
And I must say that, this has
happened to me on other films,
and if you want to know which ones,
it happened to me for the
ending of The Cotton Club.
It happened to me for the ending of…
Recently, The Rainmaker.
And I really was troubled over
the endings, for different reasons.
For The Rainmaker, it
was because, in the book,
everyone knew that the kid
was going to win the law case.
So what was the drama in a movie?
I just struggled and tried
and tried and tried and…
For all of you young writers and stuff,
the amount of hitting
my head against the wall
and staying up all night and
then hating what I've done
and trying again…
But I must say that I very much
like the ending of this picture
of The Death of Michael Corleone,
partly because he doesn't really die.
It's worse than dying.
Here we have this mysterious
figure, Mr. Lucchesi, and you'll see,
he has these formidable-looking police.
So he's clearly a very important
person in the government,
if not the head of the government,
and he clearly is involved
with this traitor, whom
we now see as a traitor.
So just as we thought
Joey Zasa was just small-fry
in a simple, very shallow
level of the conspiracy
that Michael is up against,
not only the highest
levels of the Vatican,
but, surprisingly, that also puts
him at the highest levels of the Mafia,
which takes him to the
head of the Italian state.
The guy couldn't be in more trouble
with more powerful people if he tried.
This was a beautiful scene that
Mario had really been the
instigator of, as is, of course,
the case with so many of
the great scenes of this movie,
where the two plots really come together
and we have Michael's
personal story in his desire for,
really, redemption and forgiveness
and to be taken in the arms of God
and be still welcome as his child.
And equally the high
levels of the Vatican,
which is, in fact, so corrupt
and has always been so.
And so venal and mercenary.
So it takes you to two places at once…
And this story of the stone,
of course is a beautiful…
Says more than I can say about the Church
and the institution of the Vatican.
He is still being ravaged
by the diabetes, as my grandfather was.
He needs to have
information to understand
what forces are really
ranged against him.
But more important, and
again more important to me,
as it was to Michael
is these other issues that a man
sometimes comes to,
which are more personal
and more related to,
really, how he stacked
up as a man in his lifetime.
A lot of people ask me,
"Oh, you know, when you die,
"what do you want on your gravestone?
Do you want to be remembered"
for a movie?"
And I look at them and
I say, "Oh, you know,
just put, 'He liked little
children,' or something like that."
That's really what I was like.
And this is the point he's at,
except he's not so simple as I am
and he has darker ghosts
to exorcise from his life.
And here we have
the ancient tradition of confession.
But imagine taking Michael
Corleone's confession.
A wonderful actor, Raf Vallone,
movie star from years before,
played this scene and
contributed so much to this film.
But, you know, those guys watching
Godfather movies in New Jersey,
the fellows who know the
Soprano family and what have you,
they're not interested
in Michael Corleone's
confession, I assure you.
They're interested in what
he's going to do to all those guys.
Here, just visually, we
wanted to give the impression of
looking through the
grating of a confessional.
Of course, they were
outside in the garden.
So we shot through the flowers to
try to give the sense of the privacy
or the intimacy of a confessional.
I knew men like Michael
Corleone, it seemed to me,
those steel-haired, crew-cutted
men who were the leaders of
merchants' groups and Catholic charities,
Knights of Columbus,
former military people.
In a way, Michael is that, isn't he?
He is a former military man.
Those are the kinds
of strong, steel-like men
that I tried to base him on,
but show him really
in touch with his great, great regret
and his great, great guilt
and the weight of what
he had done all his life,
weighing on him with no one, no wife,
to comfort him anymore,
because he had also
destroyed that relationship.
A project that has so
many main characters
needs to provide an
introduction for each of them
and ultimately continue
their involvement in the story
and then obviously needs an emotional…
If not a resolution, but
an emotional culmination.
And, here, given so
much that has happened
to Michael Corleone,
his long relationship with his sister,
dating back to where he
had her husband killed,
and through the period
in the Lake Tahoe days,
when he was so
disapproving of her behavior
and now, almost as a collaborator
in this mob life that she
seems to have taken a shine to.
I thought it was moving
that she would help him
with his insulin shots.
I confess that this interest in diabetes
comes from my childhood experience
with my grandfather, seeing it.
He was blinded from diabetes.
I remember he used
to just touch our faces
and cry, 'cause he…
Especially with my sister Tally,
because he had seven sons.
He never had a daughter.
Everyone knows that it's so difficult,
chemistry between families,
the tremendous love you have,
and yet you have this
familiarity, you know them so well.
So that you know their positive
issues and their negative issues,
and you have such
resentment and jealousy,
and a sense of what wasn't fair,
what was fair.
The relationship with
Michael and his sister,
I would imagine, is as complicated
as my relationship with my sister,
who is playing his sister.
It's too much for me to think about.
In the great Mario Puzo style,
one must always introduce
an infallible killer.
You know, a killer who's better
than the last infallible killer
that had been in the story,
or someone invulnerable.
A kind of Luca Brasi figure who is so…
So formidable.
This young man is
actually a Coppola relative,
albeit his name is Russo,
from the town of Bernalda,
where my grandfather was from,
where the cousin with no nose and..
. He was quite a character.
I didn't know him,
obviously, until I went to Sicily
and he arrived in Rome and…
I know enough about
the family from the old
country to understand
who his part of the family was and…
So I tried to create a role for him
as the apprentice to this Sicilian
"ace in the hole,"
as Eli refers to him.
Mario's work always has these
forces set in motion,
invulnerable killers that you figure,
"Oh my God, as long as you
have Luca Brasi on your side,
nothing can ever happen to him."
And then all of a
sudden he kills that guy.
So you don't have him any
more and you begin to say,
"My God, we're totally vulnerable now."
On the case of Michael,
he was given these legendary bodyguards
who are the twins, who are
two identical twin brothers,
who indeed were twins,
the actors who played them,
who also were legendary,
never-can-be-defeated bodyguards.
So you get those kinds
of forces in the works
and then you surprise everyone
with who was able to kill whom.
Now we begin to prepare for the end,
with the poster of Cavalleria Rusticana.
It's always a great pleasure for
me to see Sofia in these scenes.
I must say it's…
It really warms my heart.
There I have my sister,
I have my daughter,
I have Diane, I have Al.
It was an unusual
experience working on this film
and to be with them all,
and so many years later.
I see in Sofia a little
bit of my mother, Italia.
Yes, the third film,
Godfather Part III, or The
Death of Michael Corleone,
it's very different than the other two.
It tries to hearken to them
through the many years,
but it's trying to do
something quite different.
It's about themes, I think, that
are more uniquely reserved for it.
I mean, the fact that the main
character performs such a different role
than he does in the other films,
where, of course, he's the driving force
that is the opposition to the conspiracy.
In this case, Michael is
really made vulnerable
by his own concern for
things other than business,
for personal things.
That's the real drawing
that my son made for me.
He did that, and it was in Godfather II,
and I'm surprised, when it opened up,
that we still have it.
These are the legendary twin bodyguards.
I thought I had some incident
which showed their prowess.
Maybe I didn't have time to include
it, but I thought it would be a good idea
to show them do something,
like, so spectacular that you figure,
"Well, these guys, no one is ever
going to get at Michael Corleone
while they're around."
There is my little granddaughter,
Gia, being carried by my daughter Sofia.
Gia's a nice girl.
She's now 14 years old.
I just saw her.
She's just turning into that
kind of lanky, tall teenager.
Here we begin an interlude in
which Michael sort of kidnaps Kay
and really was the sequence between them
that leads to a more of a
rapprochement, if not a romantic one,
but a spiritual one, in
which ultimately then
he was to be shot and that was the end.
And the whole superstructure
that I came up with,
with Cavalleria Rusticana,
and the interposing
the story of the opera
with the story of the family,
with the story of the daughter
being absolutely told
not to see the cousin,
all hopefully can be stirred
up and then ultimately resolved.
Again, when we shot Sicily
we always fought so hard
to have it be sun,
which is not the case, by the way.
So we always had to wait.
This little pathway down to the
door is the very same pathway
in a small town in Taormina,
where the men had come to take
Vito Andolini to the Mafia chieftain.
So just as Italian-Americans do,
we were visiting the actual places.
This church we used for the scene
when the little boy, Vito
Andolini was hidden in the mule,
and taken off to America.
So we did have the great pleasure
of going back to these towns…
And I see a donkey going by,
that's probably the director
trying to indicate or remind you
of the fact that the little
boy had been smuggled,
Michael Corleone's father, had
been smuggled out of this very spot.
I'm very interested in time
and in the unity of time
and how these things repeat.
This story of the puppet
show is so interesting.
It's the story of the Baroness of Carini,
and how she falls in
love with her own cousin
and is killed by her father.
I thought I was so fortunate
to find an Italian folktale
that is indeed done in puppet show,
that tells the story of
really what is sort of
happening in our story,
with the love of Mary for her cousin
and the fact that her father
condemns her to death.
These scenes were always
such a pleasure for me.
I always would go early, and
as I would drive to the location,
I would hear the band
rehearsing and I knew that my dad,
who was so fastidious
and serious about his work,
that he'd be there, you know,
an hour before everyone else,
having found some local musicians
and bringing the arrangements
of the source music
that he had just written.
And it was such a
pleasure to sit in the chair
while they were rehearsing
and put in my two cents
about how they should play the
music, which of course, you know,
not being a musician, I'm not
very much of an expert at anything.
But it was great, great,
great pleasure for me.
Here is the same courtyard where
Michael's young wife, Apollonia,
was killed when the car, the Alfa Romeo,
was blown up by the traitor bodyguard
who was played by Angelo Inf anti.
It is interesting to
have the same settings,
the same places.
This is the same room where
Michael opened the window
and beheld his young bride and
ironically, as life sometimes does,
here is his wife, standing
in the same place.
I guess, in life, there is some director
who puts people in the same place,
or who creates these
similarities and parallel reminiscences.
In a movie, you need
people like myself to do it,
but in life it happens very often.
I found, on this picture, Diane
Keaton such an intriguing person.
She really at this point
in her life, her career,
is such a kind of
gifted, brilliant woman.
She works very much in solitude
and has techniques to concentrate
and what she gives you
is really part of herself.
I guess always, but on
this picture all the cast,
all the people coming
together, there was a…
You know, they're so much wiser
and older and more world-weary.
There's a kind of
skepticism that they bring,
that the younger versions
of themselves didn't have,
when they were just
anxious to be in a project.
And, of course, when you
have intelligent people like this,
they all had opinions.
They had opinions on everything.
I'm sure, to this day they might
feel, "Oh, it would have been better
"just to end the film…"
As it was originally at the
end of this relationship,"
or not to have cast my daughter
or this or that.
But I was much more aware
of these actors as being
really fully-developed
adults with strong opinions,
and it makes it a little harder
to direct them because
you're constantly trying to
make sure the material is…
I won't say worthy of them, but
conforms with their view of things.
Naturally, of course, all actors tend
to think that the film is about them.
There's that wonderful line in the movie
where they ask the
nurse in Romeo and Juliet,
"What's Romeo and Juliet about?"
And he says, "Well,
it's about this nurse."
But that's a good thing, that the
cast puts you through that demand,
that they really ask you to
think through their characters,
as though they're the
only character in the piece.
But, yeah, I ended up
on this picture, feeling that
Diane Keaton was some sort of genius or…
That's a word I don't use very often.
What's the next level, you know?
Just some extremely
talented, brilliant, intelligent person.
The love of a man and a woman
when they have been through
so many years and have
seen and shared together
tragedy and shared great fortune,
almost is more difficult
than sharing poor fortune.
It's a wonderful thing.
It's a heartbreak to me that
so few people are willing to
withstand the difficulties of marriage,
to get to that point when
they're with a partner who's been
with them more than half their own ages.
It's a pity
that more people don't
preserve what a
long-term marriage can be.
I guess here we're
indicating for the first time that,
and of course showing
it in regards to Kay,
that things will never change,
that she'll always be the
woman behind the door
and that Michael,
although Michael has been
pretty not-attentive to business.
He suddenly, I guess, feels that
now with killing Don Tommasino
and the fact that they're
after him, that he has to.
Here we show somewhat authentically
what the selection of
the Pope would be like.
Of course, we've only
built a teeny part of a set.
I mean, what you see is what we built.
This is actually a curious
plot point, is that this pope,
whom we have had the experience of
knowing is a good man
and a spiritual man and a…
Really above any notion of corruption
is now to be the Pope.
It changes the plot,
when you think about it.
This is the customary
signal of the white smoke
from the Vatican that a
new pope has been selected
and the way that it's
done, we try always in films
that we work on to be authentic.
I believe these are probably
derived from some of the
lines of the real John Paul I.
From all indication, John
Paul I was a wonderful man
and a man who was really willing to
march into the future in a good way,
and it was perhaps the reaction
of more conservative
elements within the Vatican that…
And also the fact that he was aware
of so much of the financial corruption
that had been evident.
I won't mention names,
but in terms of the cardinals
who were entrusted to that,
that perhaps the notion of
a truly good, honest pope
would have been anathema to the forces
that had been woven around
that aspect of the Vatican.
Those who wish can read
the history of this period
and will recognize many
of the figures that I've tried
to depict in Mario Puzo's style,
which is to say, they're
sort of like real people,
but not really.
This scene was shot after
the film returned from Italy.
It was shot in New York and
it was shot because it was felt,
and I didn't disagree, it was
felt by the Paramount executives
and by Frank Mancuso in particular…
Who's a very, very sweet and nice man
and a good film executive,
who was in a tough
position at that point,
because they really needed
this picture to be done
and they needed it to be
a big financial performer,
and so they really wanted
it to be as much of a thriller
and to focus on the so-called
action parts of the plot, the revenge.
Here I have this character who's wailing
about his inability to be a good man
in his life, and it was felt that we
really needed a transfer of power.
That, "Okay, guys, enough of
this guy feeling sorry for himself.
"Let's get Vincent Mancini in there"
"and have him be like
the old Michael Corleone"
and get in there and
kill all the enemies."
So that's what this
scene was meant to do.
Of course, working with Al, I was
anxious to give Al the opportunity
to use his formidable
intelligence and talent
to really express the
other personal aspects
and in a sense, it was
a welcome opportunity
to let Al hand over the reins to Vincent,
knowing that Vincent was a hothead,
like his brother Sonny had been.
We're just going to get this movie
back into the kind of plot that, you know,
many people felt it should have
had right from the beginning.
I mean, who needs this
Michael Corleone mid-life crisis?
Let's get to the good stuff.
Reminds me of the time
on the first Godfather film
when they said they were
going to send in an action director,
because I was too
interested in the family parts.
You can just imagine. What if Michael
Corleone wasn't this type of man,
but still had his long
black hair, albeit older,
and he's sitting at his desk
and he's talking to Vincent
and you figure he's
got it all figured out
and he just throws a few clues out there?
That's all I would have had to
do to be the old-style Godfather,
but, you know, it didn't seem like
that really was what this was about.
So we had gone back to New York
after we had a rough cut of the movie
and there's always little
things that are left out,
a little shot of this or
a little piece of that.
I find in a day you can do 18, 20
pieces if you have just a little column
or a little piece of a door.
At this point, seeing the picture,
I don't even notice those shots any more,
the illusion is so complete, given
with the nature of what film is like
and how a piece that
you do somewhere else,
thousands of miles away, totally fits in.
This scene signified, of course,
in a way, Connie's rise to power,
because she is the sponsor of Vincent
and really very much
like the first Godfather
when I remember Marlon
Brando was feeding the fish
and Michael was sitting behind the desk.
Michael was then the,
kind of, Vincent character
and Clemenza and Tessio were saying,
"Please, Godfather, are you
going to be involved in this?"
And Marlon was saying,
"Well, you know, just,
"I'm going to feed the fish
and you'll do what they say."
Well here we are,
several generations later,
and it's really Connie
who is taking power
with some of the Caporegimes
and the transfer of power is made.
The family will be saved by Vincent,
who assumes he has now
been adopted, he is a Corleone.
He is now clearly the new Godfather,
as this simple ritual has come to mean,
but most important to Al, he
has been given this new position
with the promise that he will reject Mary
and will not continue this love affair,
which Michael feels will
only lead to her demise,
just as it did to the demise of his wife.
We shot the opera sequence of this
film at the Teatro Massimo in Palermo,
a beautiful, beautiful opera
house which we are seeing,
and which was in fact under
renovation and reconstruction,
so, although we could use the
exterior and certain interior portions,
we could not actually work on the stage.
It was all totally in reconstruction.
So we shot the family and the guests
and the night of the opening
of Cavalleria Rusticana,
with the son of Michael
Corleone singing the tenor role,
elsewhere in Rome.
This, interestingly, was
a model of the theater
that we found in a room and
we featured it in the lobby.
So once again, in Godfather
style, all the principal characters,
all the players are coming
together to some big event,
enemy as well as friend,
but now we know that Vincent Mancini,
now Vincent Corleone, who is the…
He is the Michael
Corleone of the story now,
is in charge, and so the attitude
is not so inattentive to business,
that Vincent is there to
protect Michael Corleone
and to vanquish these
very formidable enemies.
We have the super-duper twin
bodyguards who can do no wrong.
We know that there is another
killer, Mosca, with his young apprentice
who does the donkey sound.
That's a real song, by the way,
but it was useful to remind you,
the audience, who he was in
the sea of so many characters.
And here is Constanza, my sister,
bringing a little box of
pastry to Eli Wallach,
which I'm sure he's going to enjoy.
This is sad to me, because you
know, she's without explanation.
All those stories always break my
heart, like in La Traviata or, you know,
whenever there are lovers and
then one has to give up the other
and make it look like they
don't like him anymore,
but they're doing it, really,
because they do love them.
In this case Vincent, in order to
become the head of the family,
has promised to give up any
encouragement to the daughter,
under the watchful eyes of…
And she tries her little
18-year-old tricks with him,
you know, "Hey, you
still love me, don't you?"
But you know, it's not to be.
He knows that the
father has forbidden it.
Those kind of stories
are really sad to me.
So Constanza has brought
the cannoli to Don Altobello.
You've got to watch out for
cannoli in these Godfather movies.
Those are very, very good cannoli.
Those are real Sicilian cannoli.
What is notable about them is
they're not the little narrow
ones with the little cream,
these are the kinds…
It's hard for me to see my daughter cry.
The real issue with Sofia's
performance, I think, in this movie
was that she had that kind of
California-speak when she spoke,
and if you kind of just look at
the scene and look in her eyes,
you'll see that Sofia's
acting is extremely truthful.
It's what actors call, "She's full."
She's there.
And that's worth more than anything.
You would never want your
daughter to look at you like that.
So we were inside the Teatro Massimo
facing the boxes and the audience.
Of course, not in the stage.
Interesting side note to
this was my Uncle Anton,
who conducted the orchestra.
I'll tell some stories out of school.
My Uncle Anton is a great
operatic conductor and composer
and my father's younger brother.
And over the years, although as a
child I always remembered them so close
and staying up at night
and talking about Puccini
and talking about Turandot
and talking about music.
I always was very happy
with that relationship.
But over the years, for
reasons I don't understand,
they had a falling out.
So often the fallings-out come.
And it was my desire to really see
my uncle and my father work together,
and so I used my power,
perhaps erroneously.
And my father was totally
capable of conducting the opera,
but because he was so
busy writing all the music,
I tried to get them to share a few things
and really, I say, selfishly,
just so I could sit once again
and have them have dinner
and see them work together.
It didn't really work.
I mean, they were courteous to each other.
Their wives didn't
really get along so much.
And I think my uncle did a wonderful
job and it was a good association,
but my father really felt
that I had imposed this.
That level of old Italian, they're
very possessive about opportunities
and who gets the plums or
whatever you want to call them.
So one could say that this
was a successful experiment,
but perhaps also it
was a very stressful one
and attests to sometimes
the fruitlessness
of trying to force relatives
to work and be together.
But I thought it was a
somewhat authentic production
of Cavalleria Rusticana.
I staged it in a traditional way.
I was anxious to show how
the roots of The Godfather
go back to these simple village feuds
and characters that I knew
as a child, Alfio and Lola…
And I always love that
Turiddu sang that opening aria
backstage next to the harp, you know,
watching the conductor
on a television monitor.
You know, it's the
Francis desire to show you
how things work in the background.
But I liked this production
of the resolution of the story
woven against the simple peasant
story of Cavalleria Rusticana,
which I feel is in some ways the
basis of so much of what we did
in the first two Godfathers,
musically, as well as the drama.
Cavalleria Rusticana
deals with a young man
who comes back from the army
and has a love who is now
married to the coachman, Alfio,
and it has to do with jealousy
and insult in that rustic setting
and it's all about you
resolve things with knives
and you follow the
rustic codes of behavior.
I was in a real pickle with
the two super-bodyguards
because on one hand, I had
the killer to end all killers, Mosca,
and then I had the great twin
bodyguards who were also the greats.
So I had to come up and I must confess
that many, many, many, tough nights
of hitting my head
against the wall was used
and our stunt coordinator,
Buddy Joe Hooker,
came up with what I thought
was a very, very ingenious idea,
in which it would look as though
the twins bodyguard had
subdued and killed Mosca.
But in fact it was Mosca who had done it
and lured the other one,
and so ultimately he wins.
I try little touches, like to have
Franc D'Ambrosio as Turiddu
show this type of
Sicilian, cocky young man
and pull on his pants
the way Sonny used to.
I tried as best I could to integrate
the little story of jealousy and revenge
set in a Sicilian setting,
to show how these people
really grew out of that.
And like the other Godfathers, there
are many threads of possible murders
and resolution of the
forces that are arrayed,
and you have Neri coming in
and you have Mosca setting up,
obviously to assassinate Michael.
You have these various
bodyguards interacting,
and you have this ear bite,
by the way, just like Joey Zasa.
Vincent recognizes it.
That's how I saw it as a
kid in Cavalleria Rusticana.
I thought that was really weird,
that you would bite someone's ear.
So, now the bullet is almost…
There's my Uncle Anton.
Just as the bullet is about to
be really delivered to Michael,
the one bodyguard, his bodyguard,
has uncovered the assassin, Mosca,
just as you're in the most
dramatic part of the opera.
I think the young man
challenges the husband to a duel
and he sort of knows
he's going to be killed.
There are many…
You know, I hope for many levels here.
The satisfaction of the mother.
You know, mothers love
their sons, as do fathers,
but in a different way, and want to see
the son go through this difficult moment
of resisting the strong
influence of the father,
and the coming into the light.
The knife-killing on stage is
echoed by the killing in the boxes.
Well, you all know
this, it's pretty evident,
but that was what I had
hoped, that it could all…
Here it looks as though Mosca
is dead and the twin is pleased
that his brother has done this,
but if you look carefully, of course…
Mosca is alive and just holding him up.
That was pretty clever.
That was Buddy Hooker's idea.
The famous Lupara.
All of the symbols that are throughout
The Godfather, even in the first ones,
all the seeds are in that opera.
Now here the cast is on the
break and so they're in there
looking like shepherds with shotguns.
And therefore, my cousin, the one
who makes the song like the donkey,
just looks like one of
the actors from the play,
but indeed he has a loaded
Lupara, so he is more dangerous.
It's a kind of Pirandello idea,
where the drama of Cavalleria Rusticana
is intermingled with the real story.
No big deal.
Clearly all of the adversaries,
the corrupt priest
played by Donal Donnelly,
the nervous banker…
More things are
happening at the same time
in the halls of the Vatican where
the good Pope John Paul is sleeping.
For his evening cup of tea.
There were many threads
of the story to pull together
and of course the concept was
to try to pull them all together
interwoven with the opera.
The opera both as the root from
which all the Godfather sensibilities stem
as well as the modern
history that we were working in,
such as Vincent now
killing all of the conspirators
on the financial scam with the Vatican.
There are real people
who died in similar ways
as indeed this story is
based on, really, the truth.
Even, interestingly enough, you
have the procession in the opera
that very much looks like the
San Gennaro Festa in New York.
So we were recalling much imagery
hoping that it would remind you
not only of this film, but other films.
The death of Fanucci
in the second Godfather
or the Festa in the first one.
Now some of the news of
these various occurrences
are coming to Michael,
and so Mosca is thwarted
just as he was about to…
Having killed the two best
bodyguards, the twin bodyguards,
now Michael is taken out of his scope
and he must think of another
way to conclude his task.
So everyone is trying to kill everyone,
which is typical for these kind of people.
I've always enjoyed
working with Italian actors.
As I have said before, they
always come prepared with ideas
and they show it to you
and then if you don't like it
they'll come up with something else.
They never give you a hassle of having
to come up for them with what to do.
Clearly the imagery supporting the
very mysterious death of the Pope
with the Passion of Christ
as expressed by these simple
villagers, Sicilian villagers,
and the heartbreak
of Vincent's position with Mary,
that he knows he's breaking
her heart, but he must.
In order to protect the family
he must make that sacrifice.
Another plot line with Connie,
who was always the
favorite of Don Altobello,
as he just happily eats away
the cannoli she gave him.
The character Santuzza as the
specter of death is everywhere,
mingled with the ritual
of the Catholic Church.
This moment, it's sort of as though
Connie is killing her favorite uncle
and godfather, actually.
I think he was her godfather.
This was an interesting scene,
the idea that as all this is going on,
as you recall, Michael has
said to the Franco Citti character,
"One day I'll ask you for a service,"
and he goes to the high
halls of power and authority
and is totally frisked
so that there is no chance
that he has a weapon on him.
Talia was very good in this film.
She was very strong and very…
Almost satanic, the creature she becomes.
These are real quotes from
leaders within the Italian government.
For Italian people, it
might lead them to guess
who this character is meant to be.
These events depict both historical facts
and, I guess you could
say, political fantasy.
As I look back on this film, there's
a hell of a lot packed into this opera.
I wanted the film to end as
a tragedy in a classic sense.
And in a tragedy, you know,
there's always a certain way it's done.
There's someone dead on the steps
and the five best friends carry them off,
and it's sort of like
Hamlet or something.
I thought those steps were so
wonderfully like a classic setting.
The Baroness di Carini. For me,
this is the nightmare of nightmares.
They say that art imitates life. It's so
unusual how it does. How I've seen it.
But when this film was
finished and came out,
it was Sofia that they went after.
Walter Murch took the scream out for
the beginning, making it so agonizing.
Reminds me of the ending sentiment
of The Magnificent Ambersons,
yes, finally, after all
of this, over three films
and generations of
people working on the film,
Michael Corleone got his comeuppance.
And this is why we felt
the film should be called
The Death of Michael Corleone.
Interestingly enough, he dies at
such an indeterminate time in the future,
that Mario and I thought, as we
discussed the possible fourth film,
that the fourth film would be
much more like the second film,
in that it would be
told in two time periods.
That one time period would
be the period in New York,
sort of picking up from Godfather II
and taking you into the
time period of Godfather I.
You would see the Corleone
family in its rise to power,
and the main character really
would be Sonny Corleone,
and he would be juxtaposed,
very much in the way that
the second Godfather was,
with a modern story in which the main
character would be Vincent Mancini,
Sonny's son,
and his story would be Vincent,
of course, in a modern
period after this action,
in which he had really become
the head of the Corleone family
but it had gone into a realm of cocaine
and a dangerous relationship
with this tremendous drug trade.
But there would be two stories of
what Mario called "the happy years,"
which was the story of the
Corleone family coming into power
and indeed Don Corleone,
as played by Marlon Brando,
reaching his zenith,
and at the same time
the story of the rise.
It was the story of the fall of
the family in a modern context,
almost in a story
starring Vincent Mancini,
with the haunting he
had of this love that he lost
and his ultimate hunting down,
almost like a Pablo Escobar,
on the landscape of Colombia,
in which they are hunting
down this last gangster mogul.
And there would be one more scene
with Vincent and the
old Michael Corleone,
which ironically had happened, really,
earlier than his death scene at the end.
So it would be a movie
sort of like Godfather II,
that would interpose the rise
of the family before World War II
and the destruction of the family
in the person of Vincent Mancini,
but ultimately we never
really laid out the script,
although there are
parts of the old section,
the period before World War II,
but the new section was never worked on.
And Mario Puzo unfortunately died
before any opportunity was made to
have him work on the script with me.