I wanna show you something.
Wow.
Me and my dad built her.
900 horses of Detroit muscle.
It's a beast.
- Know what she ran in Palmdale?
- No. What did she run?
Nine seconds flat.
- God.
- My dad was driving.
So much torque the chassis twisted
coming off the line.
Barely kept her on the track.
- So what's your best time?
- I've never driven her.
Why not?
Scares the shit out of me.
That's my dad. He was coming up
in the pro stock car circuit.
Last race of the season.
A guy named Kenny Linder came up
from inside in the final turn...
and clipped his bumper and put him
into the wall at 120.
I watched my dad burn to death.
I remembered hearing him scream.
The people that were there said
he had died before the tanks blew.
They said it was me
who was screaming.
I saw Linder about a week later.
I had a wrench, and I hit him.
And I didn't intend
to keep hitting him...
but by the time I was done,
I couldn't lift my arms.
He's a janitor at a high school.
Has to take the bus
to work every day.
And they banned me
from the tracks for life.
I live my life
a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters...
not the mortgage, not the store...
not my team and all that bullshit.
For those ten seconds or less...
I'm free.
So how is it, anyways,
that the gang came to be?
- What?
- The gang.
The gang? No, they don't
call themselves a gang.
- What do they call themselves?
- They're a team.
- They call themselves a team.
- How is it the team came to be?
Well, that's
a whole lot of history.
I've got time.
Vince grew up with my brother.
He didn't ever actually grow up,
as you can tell.
But they were friends as kids.
And Letty, she lived down the street.
Always into cars, though,
ever since she was ten years old.
So, naturally,
my brother always had her attention.
- And then she turned 16...
- And then she had Dom's attention.
Yeah. Yeah, it's funny
how that works, isn't it?
Yeah.
How is it that Jesse
fits into the whole thing?
Well, Jesse and Leon
just sort of showed up one night...
and never ever left.
It's just the way my brother is.
Dom's like...
He's like gravity.
Everything just gets
pulled to him.
Even you.
The only thing
that pulled me in was you.
Being friends with your brother
is just a bonus.
That's good.
That's good. That's nice
to come first every once in a while.
You wanna go for a drive?
- Yeah?
- The hijackers have hit again.
Bilkins made his decision.
We're gonna move on Johnny Tran...
and his guys at 1700 hours,
unless you say otherwise.
If you agree, just say yes.
- Yeah.
- Who is that?
Just a wrong number.
Yes, sir. Yeah, I know, but...
Yeah, yeah. Yes. Yes, sir.
Yeah. I got it.
The DVD players
were purchased legally.
All we've got on Tran and company
are a couple of weapons charges...
and some outstanding
speeding tickets.
- So they're out.
- Yeah. Father bailed 'em out.
Is this the kind of intelligence
I can expect from you, O'Conner?
- You're gonna put this on me?
- I can put it on whoever I want to.
- Perks of the job.
- No way you're gonna put this on me.
Wait a minute.
Let me tell you.
I don't care if you have to
put a gun to someone's head...
and blow your cover
to smithereens.
You got 36 hours
to crack this bastard...
or you might wanna be thinkin'
about another career.
It's Toretto, Brian.
It always has been Toretto.
Tran and Hector are...
They're just fumes.
Well, I know you've been lying to me.
My question is this:
Have you been lying to yourself
because you can't see past Mia?
He won't go back to prison.
Well, that's a choice
he's going to have to make.
There's all kinds
of family, Brian.
That's a choice
you're gonna have to make.
You ready for this, jumpy?
Yeah.
Nice car. What's the retail
on one of those?
More than
you can afford, pal. Ferrari.
Smoke 'im.
- So what's wrong, Brian?
- Nothin', man. I'm fine.
Come on.
Obviously something's off.
Look. I have my good days, and I
have my bad days, like anybody else.
Brian, don't lose that cool.
That's your meal ticket.
My meal ticket? What?
I can't pay for my own shrimp?
- I got your shrimp.
- That's one thing about me.
You don't understand. I don't need
handouts. I don't take handouts.
I earn my way, every step.
I just gotta make a little something
extra on the side, like you.
What do you mean, like me?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- That's what I mean.
- What does that mean, like me?
- Don't try...
I'm not stupid, all right?
I know there's no way you paid
for all that shit under the hood...
There's no way you paid for all that
shit under the hood of those cars...
by doing tune-ups
and selling groceries.
Now, whatever it is you're in on,
I want in on it too.
- What is this?
- Read it.
- What is this for?
- It's directions.
To Race Wars.
We'll see how you do.
Then we'll talk.
- How's it goin', bro?
- What's up, man?
Welcome to Race Wars.
Great. Thanks a lot.
Baby. Hey, baby.
You should watch from the side.
I wouldn't want to get exhaust on you.
- Put your money where your mouth is?
- How 'bout I race you for that ass?
You want ass, why don't you
hit Hollywood Boulevard?
You want an adrenaline rush,
it'll be two large.
Right here, right now.
What's it gonna be?
You got it.
Another one bites the dust.
Come on. What do you got?
What ya got?
See ya.
Whoa. Bri, what's up?
What's up, Jesse?
What do you have in your hand?
Throwing down the pink slip,
just like you.
- The pink slip to what? TheJetta?
- Yeah.
- You can't bet your dad's car.
- It's all right.
I ain't losin'. This fool
is runnin' a Honda 2000. I'll win.
That way, me and my dad can roll
together when he gets out of prison.
They're gonna throw him right back
in prison after he kills you.
Shit. I'm up.
Visualize the win.
Visualize the win, Jesse.
- I'm serious. Listen to me, man.
- Who you racin'?
Don't do it. I bet you he's got more
than a hundred grand under the hood.
Too soon, junior.
Shit!
Oh, God.
Heads up, bro. We got problems.
- What?
- Jesse.
- Where's Jesse goin'?
- He just raced Tran for slips.
Oh, shit.
- Where's he going?
- He went to the car wash.
Whatever. Go fetch my car.
Go fetch your car?
We're not on your block anymore.
You'd better watch
who you talk to like that.
SWAT came into my house,
disrespected my whole family...
because somebody narced me out.
And you know what? It was you!
Go! Let him go!
Get off of him!
Dom, chill out, man.
Come on. Let's go.
I never narced on nobody!
- I'm asking you not to go.
- I'm doing this for both of us.
Don't give me that crap.
You're doing this for you.
- Why are you asking me to stay?
- Why do you insist on doing this?
Dom, please, don't.
- What's goin' on?
- What?
- You know what I'm talkin' about.
- No, I don't, Brian.
So what? You always have tears
in your eyes when Dom drives away?
- What is the matter with you?
- Come on.
What's your brother racin' off
in the middle of the night for?
I'm talkin' about the trucks.
You know about the trucks?
No, Brian. What trucks?
Jesus Christ.
- What?
- Listen to me.
Mia, I'm a cop.
What are you talking about, Brian?
What is this?
Ever since the first time I met you,
I've been undercover.
I'm a cop.
You bastard.
Get off of me, Brian!
Listen to me!
Everything I ever said I felt
about you was real, I swear to God.
You have to believe me. But right now,
this isn't about you and me.
Your brother's about to pull a job,
and we're almost out of time.
Those truckers, they're not
laying down anymore.
They may make it through the night,
but every law enforcement agency...
in California
is comin' down on 'em.
If you don't want anything to happen
to your brother, to Letty...
to Leon, to Vince, you have to just
get in that car with me right now.
You have to help me.
Mia, you are the only person
that can help me right now.
Please, Mia. Please help me.
Civics are stashed somewhere
outside of Thermal.
They wouldn't double back.
And Highway 10's too well-patrolled...
so what does that
leave us with then?
That leaves us with all this.
- Nextel.
- Yes, this is Officer O'Conner...
serial number 34762.
I need a cell phone trace.
- What's the cell number?
- Mia, what's the cell phone number?
Come on, Mia. She needs
Dom's cell phone number now.
323-555-6439.
Thank you. You get that?
All right. We're one man short.
Letty, I need you on the left side.
Your sister's right about this one.
This don't feel good.
Don't do that.
- Something's wrong.
- Stop.
We shouldn't be doing this
without Jesse.
Look. This is the mother lode.
We've been on this for three months.
After this, it's a long vacation
for everyone.
- Let's go.
- I hope so.
Listen. The other night
I had a dream that you and I...
were on a beach in Mexico.
- Really?
- Really.
Come on.
Let's make this happen.
- Keep on those scanners.
- Copy that.
All right. Let's go.
Yeah?
We traced the number
to the northbound 86...
mile 114 outside Coachella.
- We'll keep the trace open.
- Let me see this.
All right. I think
we're about 40 miles away.
What are you gonna do?
Okay! Go time!
We're all good, man.
I got nothin' on the scanners.
Keep goin'.
Don't! Get back in!
- He's got a damn shotgun!
- Back off! Get him off of there!
Shit.
Get me off this thing!
Pull up!
- Unhook yourself!
- Come back!
- Do it!
- Pull up!
- I can't...
- You can do it!
Pull up! I'll jump!
Come on!
I'm pullin' up to distract him.
Come on, boy.
Shot doesn't get better than this.
Son of a bitch!
Take me off of here.
I'm gonna unhook the wire.
Try it again.
One, two, three!
Unhook yourself!
- I can't get my arm free!
- Vince, grab my hand!
- My arm!
- Listen! Give me your hand!
- I can't get my hand free!
- I'm gonna pull you off!
Dominic, hold on!
Listen to me!
Shit!
Hold on!
Move out of the way!
I'm comin' to get him!
- Yo?
- Pull back for Letty.
- Get her out of there!
- I'm on it! Go!
I got her!
You get Vince off that truck!
Come on, baby.
You okay?
Come on, girl. You all right?
Come on. Let me look at you.
Come on. We gotta go.
Let's go.
- Take the wheel!
- What do you mean?
Put your foot on the gas!
- What the hell are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna get him.
- Put your foot on the gas!
- Okay!
- All right. Keep it steady.
- I got it!
All right. Hold on, Vince!
He's having a hard time holding on!
Get me a little closer!
All right!
- Closer!
- I'm moving in!
Hold it right there!
- Go!
- You gotta hang in with me!
We're gonna get you off this thing!
Give me your arm!
Look at me. Don't let go.
Come on, Vince!
Throw this arm around me!
Don't let go.
Come on, Vince! Get closer!
Vince, get closer! Come on!
Here we go.
Gotta jump.
Shit.
It's gonna be okay, baby.
I love you.
Watch her.
Come on, Vince.
Hang in there!
If we don't get him to an ambulance
in ten minutes, he's dead.
- Hold this. Hold the pressure.
- I got it.
Don't let go. Hold his arm up.
Yeah. Yeah,
this is Officer Brian O'Conner.
I'm off-duty M.A.P.D.
I need a life flight rollout
right away.
My twenty is Highway 86,
mile marker 147.
I got one trauma victim,
about 24 years of age, six foot...
maybe 200 pounds.
He's got a deep laceration to his
right arm with arterial bleeding.
And he's got a shotgun wound,
close-range, to his left leg.
Yeah.
Yeah. And he's going into shock.
Put the gun down now!
- Move your car.
- Bullshit. Put it down now!
- No more running.
- I'm not running!
- Where's Leon and Letty?
- They're long gone.
Then it's over. I didn't
call the police, but don't push me.
- Put the gun down! I swear to Go...
- You are the cop!
You're a cop!
Brian, I gotta find Jesse
before they do.
- I'm all the kid's got.
- I'll call in the plates.
P.D.'ll pick 'im up way before
Johnny even gets near 'im.
- Move your car.
- Dom, stop it! It's over! Please!
Mia, stay out of it.
Move the...
I am so sorry.
I don't know what I'm doin'.
I'm so scared right now.
I don't know what's goin' on.
- What were you thinkin', man?
- I don't know. I panicked.
I'm sorry. I don't know what I'm doing.
Will you please help me?
Call 911. You, call 911!
I used to drag here
back in high school.
That railroad crossing up there
is exactly a quarter-mile away.
On green, I'm goin' for it.
That's not what I had in mind.
- You know what you're doin'?
- I owe you a ten-second car.
I live my life a quarter-mile
at a time.
Nothing else matters.
For those ten seconds or less...
I'm free.