- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[BUTCHER] With great power
comes the absolute certainty
that you'll turn into a right cunt.
We got everything under control.
[REPORTER] An explosion
rocked Midtown Manhattan.
[MOTHER'S MILK] Soldier Boy.
[BUTCHER] And what you
gonna do when you find him?
You need us.
[STARLIGHT] You shot up an
untested drug from Vought.
[FRENCHIE] Nina.
[LITTLE NINA] Our
classified lab destroyed...
My powers are gone!
[LITTLE NINA] ... three
of my contacts disappeared,
so you're the one who pays the debt.
Black lives matter!
Supe lives matter, fucking ingrates!
Stop!
[DOCTOR] Nathan will never walk away.
- What the fuck?
- [BUTCHER] Crimson Countess.
Your lover boy's on his way here.
How much did the Russians pay you?
- They didn't.
- I loved you.
I hated you. We all did.
[EXPLOSION]
You're teaming up with a murderer.
Please don't go.
[INHALES]
[SIGHS] Past few days have
got me feeling a little, um...
well, philosophical.
Uh, these Supervillain attacks,
they've affected everyone.
Doesn't matter who you
are, where you're from.
We're all in this together.
And together, we can
imagine a better world.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ Imagine there's no heaven ♪
♪ It's easy if you try ♪
♪ No hell below us ♪
♪ Above us, only sky ♪
[BOTH] ♪ Imagine all the people ♪
♪ Living for today ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ You may say I'm a dreamer ♪
♪ But I'm not the only one ♪
♪ I hope someday you will join us ♪
[EXPLOSION]
Stop.
Deep. [SIGHS]
Is there anyone else that can
operate this thing? Seriously.
Ashley thought we should
get rid of most of them.
- What? You fired them.
- Here, I found it. I found it.
Okay.
Stop.
Zoom in.
Soldier Boy.
[DEEP] No, that's
impossible. He died, like,
- 40 years ago.
- Someone's cosplaying?
Look at his face. It's him.
- Or maybe CGI.
- It is not CGI.
You don't even know what CGI stands for.
[DEEP] It stands for "blow me."
[ASHLEY] I don't understand.
Where has he been?
Why did he kill Crimson Countess?
I mean, the two were, like, fucking
Kurt and Goldie. All
right, you know what?
This is fine. This is fine.
We dominate the news cycle.
I will call Haberman.
We'll message that we got
Soldier Boy totally under control.
Shut up.
You want to tell the
world that Soldier Boy,
hero of heroes,
is back from the fucking dead
and blowing up Midtown?
Before me, he was Vought.
His statue's in front of
the fucking building, Ashley.
Oh, my God,
if this gets out...
company's fucked. I'm fucked.
Oh, God. If the company falls, I fall.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God. Why is this happening to me?
This isn't fair.
This is so fucking unfair.
Okay.
I'll handle this.
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
You bury it. All of it.
The footage, no one sees it.
He fucks it up, it's your head.
Noir.
[SIGHS]
Why would he kill Crimson Countess?
He was your team leader,
you have any idea?
[SIGHS]
I'm really glad to have you
with me on this one, pal.
[SIGHS] Seriously. You're
the only one I can count on.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[SCREAMS]
- Uh... thank you.
- [ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[WHIMPERS]
[HUGHIE] What the hell?
Where's the Chop Socky Oriental Sauce?
They don't have that anymore.
Why the fuck not?
Uh, many... many good reasons.
Did you get the other shit?
Here you go, guv.
Oh.
Man, I missed bennies.
It's how we won D-Day, you know.
We were wired to the fucking gills.
[BUTCHER] Listen,
let's have a little chat
about this team-up, yeah?
Yeah, what the hell
do I need a team for?
The last one handed me to the Reds.
And we got you out
of that little pickle.
We wrapped up Crimson Countess
and delivered her like a
fucking Christmas turkey,
and I even sorted Gunpowder for you.
[SOLDIER BOY] Why am I supposed
to be impressed with that?
That's like killing
Emmanuel Lewis. [CHUCKLES]
[SNORTS]
[BUTCHER] Yeah, well, he grew
up a bit since you last saw him.
- [SIGHS]
- Hands off the fucking shield.
- Mm.
- [BUTCHER] Anyway,
you want payback on Payback, don't you?
Well, it just so happens
that we
are experts at
exterminating shitbag Supes.
You see, it's a whole different
world out there now, son.
We're here to help you find your way.
Well, I can find them on my own.
Uh, are you sure?
I mean, do you know what a GPS is?
Or... or Bluetooth? Or, I mean...
[CHUCKLES] ... the internet?
You made those words up.
No. No. No, those are real words, um,
and... and you need those to find them.
All right? You need us.
Kid's right.
And all we ask in return
is that you add one
more name to the list.
Who?
A right cunt named Homelander.
I've seen pictures.
Who is he?
He's the new you.
No one's the new me, pal.
But why him?
Let's just say you're not
the only one wants payback.
Hm. Hm.
All right.
You help me find the rest of my team,
and I'll help you with this Homelander.
[GRUNTS]
[SNORTS]
[INDISTINCT P.A. ANNOUNCEMENT]
♪ ♪
[CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[STARLIGHT] So, you
think that Soldier Boy
is going after the rest of Payback?
Countess wasn't strong enough
to fuck him over on her own.
She had help.
Soldier Boy's just getting started.
[STARLIGHT] Do you know
where any of them are?
[MOTHER'S MILK]
Those shady-ass TNT Twins
got an address in Vermont.
- Okay. Does Butcher have it?
- No, but he'll get it.
I think Soldier Boy is bulletproof.
This ain't for Soldier Boy.
Look, I'm pissed at those guys, too,
but we have to keep our heads on.
Why? Why do I always have
to take the high road?
You know, when white folks get mad,
y'all motherfuckers go berserk,
but I got to turn the other cheek?
Fuck the high road, fuck
Butcher, and fuck Hughie.
Hughie is not himself right now.
Hughie is a grown-ass man
that's made his own choices.
M.M.!
Please. Soldier Boy is gonna
kill more people. I mean, fuck.
Kimiko is in the hospital.
She lost her powers.
Frenchie isn't answering, Alex is dead,
and Maeve...
We're all we've got.
It's up to us.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Shit.
- [CELL PHONE CLICKS]
This is Starlight.
Yeah, of course, Ashley.
I'll be right there.
I got to go up to the
Tower for a little bit.
Now?
If I don't go, they're
gonna know something's up.
I'll be one hour.
Do I need to worry about you?
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
[NARRATOR] Even the greatest trees
must grow from a single seed.
Follow one proud Black man's
journey to the root of his roots,
as he takes the A-Train to Africa.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Hey.
It looks great.
Man, there's so much
strength in dignity.
What are you doing about Blue Hawk?
Okay, first of all, everyone at Vought
is just heartbroken over your
brother's tragic accident.
It wasn't an accident.
Blue Hawk went apeshit for no reason.
Well, he said he felt threatened.
- Threatened?
- Mm-hmm.
By what, a room full of Black people
with no superpowers?
Look, I've scheduled him for 12 weeks
of sensitivity training.
Fuck that. I want charges brought.
Okay, A-Train, persecuting Blue Hawk
will only make things worse.
This is a time for healing.
I don't give a shit.
I thought we got rid of
the Nazis around here.
[SIGHS] Vought rejects racism
- and Nazism unequivocally. Okay?
- Hmm.
Now, uh, can we talk about this later?
I have a lot going on today. Thank you.
You know, whatever. I don't need you.
I'll just ping his chip,
go get his ass myself.
No. Homelander wants everyone to present
a united front right now.
My brother is paralyzed.
I want some fucking justice.
Seriously? Justice?
- Yeah.
- You want justice?
- [GRUNTS]
Oh, fuck.
I have spent over 100 hours
in crisis management meetings
specifically figuring out how
to cover up your bullshit...
including all three of
your straight-up murders...
while you were out in
the club with your crew,
or getting your toe sucked by Popclaw,
who, let's not forget,
you also murdered.
Yeah, that's right. I know about that.
You did not give a shit
about all the collateral
you caused then.
Now, all of a sudden, you care
because it happened to you?
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah, that's right.
I said that.
Out loud.
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [DEEP] Homelander.
- What?
- Couple things. Uh...
Noir, he's, uh, he's gone.
What do you mean, he's gone?
He cut out his tracking chip.
No, he... he... he...
He... he wouldn't. Not
Noir. He wouldn't run.
Well...
He wouldn't do that to me.
He w... he wouldn't run.
Tell him... what we figured out.
Right.
We think Crimson Countess
was just the start.
We think... he's going after
his whole team, including Noir.
The good news is, that means we know
where he's probably headed next.
The twins. TNT.
They're the closest. Vermont.
Okay.
Okay? Really? Homelander,
thank you so much.
Shh, shh, shh.
You go there,
and you check it out.
- Yeah.
- And if Soldier Boy does show up,
then, uh...
- you call me.
- [DEEP] Yeah.
Uh...
- what should I tell the twins?
- I don't give a fuck.
Got it.
Babe, that was amazing.
Yeah, but, you know, I didn't
need you to jump in there
like that. I had the whole thing.
Hey, hey. [SCOFFS]
I'm just trying to help. Okay?
We're in this together, right?
Okay. Right.
Right. [CHUCKLES]
[DEEP SIGHS]
Why the long face, tiger?
What if I can't handle him?
I mean, if Noir ran...
Oh, you can handle him.
You're the top of the food chain.
Hey, hey.
When we were kids,
alone in the bad room,
I got us through it, right?
Don't I always?
- Always.
- No matter what.
No matter what.
And now, I'll get us through this.
Just as long as you
and me stick together.
But... what if Edgar's right?
What if it was a mistake
to take over Vought?
And... and...
and I am just talent, and
they all know I'm a fraud.
What do you care what a
bunch of mud people think?
[STAMMERS]
Come on.
Tell me the real reason.
I want to hear you say it.
- Say it!
- I want them to love me.
Yahtzee!
Only it never seems
to work out, does it?
Madelyn, Maeve, Stormfront,
even your own son.
So why do you keep running
headfirst into the same brick wall?
I don't know.
Pants on fire. You know.
It's because, deep down,
there's a part of you that is still...
human.
- No.
- Mm-hmm. Part of you is.
- Mm-mm.
- A dirty, shriveled,
anemic little part of you
that still mewls for approval, and love,
and a mommy, and a
daddy, and a boo-hoo-hoo.
Look at me, tiger.
Look at me.
We got to cut that part
of you out like a cancer.
And then, well,
then, my boy, you can finally be
who you were always meant to be.
Pure. Clean.
Like marble.
[GRUNTS]
These people would rather
die than be Soviet slaves.
It's too late.
Afghanistan is ours.
Wrong. It's free.
And I'll stand by our mujahideen
brothers until the end.
You know what else I'll do?
What?
I'll distract you.
[BOTH] TNT! Detonate!
[SCREAMS]
[SOLDIER BOY] These fucking twins.
You know they couldn't
hit their fucking marks?
Fucking unprofessionals
is what they are.
Hey, uh, yeah, Butcher's
gonna find them.
Why don't you, uh, why
don't you get some sleep?
Mm, no. I've slept enough.
[SIGHS]
- [UPBEAT JINGLE PLAYING]
- [ANNOUNCER] Dads. We know
you love taking your babies everywhere.
No matter where you
go, Starlight Diapers...
Do men really walk around like that?
Yeah. I mean, dads do.
Okay, well... [CHUCKLES]
Bill Cosby is America's dad, and,
tell you one thing, he wouldn't
be caught dead in that pussy gear.
Lot to unpack there. Uh...
The Cos. That's a real man.
[CHUCKLES] Holy shit,
did he make some strong drinks.
[WHISPERS] Holy fucking shit.
But, seriously, what
passes as a man today?
Christ on a cross.
I read that we were
ass up in Afghanistan.
The fuck is up with that?
Those were the good guys.
- I mean, when I left, it was, uh...
- Yeah, you know...
I mean, goddamn it. We... we
were ten and one, you know?
I lead the 116th onto Omaha Beach.
I was in the fucking Eagle's Nest.
I fought for this country.
[GEIGER COUNTER CRACKLING]
And what did I get for it?
Forgotten.
Left to rot by my own team.
[CHUCKLES]
You know, I wanted
some rug rats of my own,
with Countess. Yeah.
Ain't that a bitch.
You know, couple of
little boys. Raise them up
to be men.
Now... [SMACKS LIPS]
... now I got nothing.
Hey, um, can I ask you something?
What happened in Midtown?
I don't know.
I mean, your team wasn't there,
so did someone do anything,
or say something...
- I said I don't know.
- Okay. Okay, yeah.
♪ ♪
I blacked out.
About ten minutes.
When I came to, the damage was done.
I didn't mean to hurt those people.
I'm not a bad guy.
But that won't happen again...
right?
Only if they got it coming.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oi, oi.
You're bleeding.
Not mine. Got an address.
We're off to Vermont.
[TOMMY] Lord of the Seven Seas. Wow.
My man, I'm such an incredible fan.
Jesus, Tommy. Slather his balls
in peanut butter, why don't you?
Sorry. My sister's a goddamn bitch.
And, uh, TNT.
Right. I'm a big fan of yours, too.
Cool outfits.
Always felt you got railroaded
with that Starlight thing, by the way.
You know, like, what,
nowadays, you can't even
pay a lady a compliment.
- I know, right?
- You're disgusting.
Anyway, we are just
so pleased, you know,
have a big star such as yourself
grace our humble soiree.
You guys having a party?
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
[CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
Wait, is this... ?
This is Herogasm.
[MOANING]
[STARLIGHT SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
I'm really glad you're here.
I missed you.
- Who's joining us?
- They didn't tell you?
Hey, there.
[CHUCKLES] Hey, lady.
[BELL RINGS]
The mayor can say anything she wants,
but Homelander is the one working
- to catch the guy.
- Mm.
We're about to turn a corner here.
Absolutely, we are.
- Thank you, honey.
- Of course, sweetheart.
- That's reassuring.
- [CHUCKLES]
But there are 19 dead
and dozens wounded.
Congresswoman Neuman,
what do you say to the Americans
who are watching right now
- and feeling scared?
- Yeah, look, it's understandable...
What kind of a... a
nasty question is that?
Oh, no, it's fine.
I'm happy to answer...
Starlight just said, and I keep saying,
this is not a problem. [SIGHS]
I'm sorry, sir, I didn't mean...
[HOMELANDER] I don't have
time for your mediocre ambush.
Your job is to report facts,
not attack us when we sit
here and tell you the truth.
The American people, they know.
They know when someone's
telling them facts,
and they know when the
media is lying to them.
There is no problem.
It is safe to go out. Period.
You know what? We're done here.
[WHISPERS] Stupid fucking hack.
Up next, Chuck makes
empanadas with Rachel Ray.
We'll be right back.
- [WOMAN] And we're clear.
- [BELL RINGS]
[ASHLEY] You fucking
amateur. The next report
you're gonna be doing is
inside my fucking asshole,
you piece of shit.
Hey, uh, you free for a little catch-up?
You know what? I'm... I'm
a little slammed right now.
Oh, come on. Ten minutes won't kill you.
Hey, so, uh, where's Hughie?
Oh, he's just camping with
his dad for a couple of days.
[LAUGHS] Okay. Okay, good.
Oh, great. I thought he was avoiding me
- or something, you know...
- No, no.
... 'cause he was scared
I was gonna pop his head.
[SWALLOWS]
Hmm?
Come on, Annie.
Put them away.
I'm not gonna hurt you
or Hughie or your families.
Besides, you'd lose.
Then why are you here?
Because I want to help you.
Huh. Help.
From the psycho who blew up Congress.
Look, most of those guys
passed around deepfakes of me
on the House floor blowing bin Laden,
so I'm not exactly
overwhelmed with sympathy.
Annie, you need me.
You're all alone.
I mean, come on, that
"hashtag Homelight" shit?
That looks like you're
in a hostage video.
Blink twice if I'm wrong.
And, what, you got to
play nice with the guy
that throat-fucked you
on your first day of work.
And Maeve, they say Maeve is in rehab,
but you and I both know
she's probably dead.
I'm all you got.
Come on, Annie, you and I were friends.
None of that has changed for me.
Are you ever gonna get to the point?
You have 193 million
Instagram followers.
Lend me your influence,
and I'll lend you mine.
I can protect you from Homelander.
You'll finally be team captain for real.
And in return, you help
me goose my numbers.
I can finally get my
education reform bill passed.
We can make things better, Annie.
For my daughter,
for a lot of daughters.
Come on, what do you say?
You're right.
This whole place.
I'm so fucking tired...
... of listening to people tell me
I need to be shitty in order to win.
Fuck you.
And fuck Homelander, and fuck Vought
and this "whatever it takes" crap.
You're just gonna end up
sitting on top of the
steaming pile of shit
that you built.
I'm done.
I'm fucking done. I'm
not doing it anymore.
You're not gonna be doing anything
if Homelander kills you.
Yeah, maybe.
But then I'll know I'm not
working with a fucking nutjob.
So, either pop my head
or get the hell out.
Hey, keep this between us?
It'd be really tough to take
out America's sweetheart,
but not impossible.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I'm so sorry.
[FRENCHIE] No.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING] No. S'il vous
plaît, no. Don't do this.
His body is a masterpiece, no?
[INHALES]
Do you know the story
behind this one? [EXHALES]
Oh, years ago, my cousin
Kolya went State's witness, so
I send my Sergei.
Not even three bullets
could stop my attack dog.
Bar fight on the Basque coast.
He started it.
Oh, my beast. This is my favorite.
When Sergei was 14 years
old, he dropped a glass.
His father told him
to kneel in the shards
and not move until he said so.
Little Sergei did not shift an inch,
not even after his
father left to get drunk
and pass out in the whorehouse.
Oh, please, don't cry for Sergei.
He likes to be told what to do.
And he loves to be
punished when he's bad.
Makes him hard.
No.
So... Cherie...
- No.
- [LITTLE NINA] ... or Kimiko?
[FRENCHIE] No, don't do it.
Don't do this! Nina!
[LITTLE NINA] You must choose, Sergei.
If not, I will kill
both of them, and when you've finished
screaming, crying, I will kill you, too.
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
- Choose.
- No.
- [GUNSHOT]
- [SCREAMS]
- Fuck.
- [GASPS]
- [GUNFIRE]
- [FRENCHIE SHOUTS]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
No.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [COUGHS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[FRENCHIE] Kimiko, run!
[FRENCHIE] Kimiko!
No!
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS, GASPS]
[PANTS]
[GASPING]
Oh, fuck! [SCREAMS]
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
- [PANTING]
- [FRENCHIE] Mon cœur.
Mon cœur.
She's gone.
[PANTING] Nina's gone.
It's over.
- [SIGHS]
- [FRENCHIE] It's over.
Have you always had that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[SIGHS] I grew up in Harlem,
brownstone filled with family.
Grandparents, uncles, aunts, cousins.
One night,
there was a ruckus outside.
I looked out the window,
and it was Soldier Boy.
He had pulled up on some
kids that were trying
to boost a Benz, and so I
run and wake up my granddad.
"Grandpa, Grandpa. It's
Soldier Boy. Come look."
Soldier Boy takes the Benz,
and he hurls it through our house,
like a fucking freight train.
It missed me by about six inches.
And my grandpa...
One minute he was there...
... and then he wasn't.
And I woke him up.
I put him in that spot.
That is not your fault.
[MOTHER'S MILK] That's when
this whole OCD shit started.
I mean, I don't understand it.
All I know is that if I
didn't check the burners
three times a night,
Soldier Boy would come back
and kill the rest of us.
And I'm still that kid.
Still getting up in
the middle of the night,
checking the burners.
'Cause if I don't,
Soldier Boy's gonna come back,
and he's gonna kill my family.
I got to get this
motherfucker out of my head,
and end this.
Or it'll end me.
- [GASPS] Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Oh, hell nah.
- [STARLIGHT] Oh, my God.
- Invitation?
I got your invitation right here.
Hey.
Starlight. I did not even recognize you.
Come in. You are more
than welcome to party.
- Party?
- [LOVE SAUSAGE] Yeah.
The 70th anniversary of Herogasm.
- Fuck me.
- Oh.
- Oh, shit.
- Fuck.
You seem familiar.
You about to get
familiar with these hands
if you don't get this
motherfucking love sausage
away from my goddamn face.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- You are not Supe.
I'm with her.
For the fuck party.
Yeah. Um, mm-hmm. No, he's
very good at cunnilingus.
- Yeah, his tongue is just... Yeah.
- Oh, yeah?
He just gobbles that vagina right up.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom,
nom, nom, nom. [CHUCKLES]
- Mm-hmm.
- Love Sausage, huh?
This is good name for me.
I like it. Come on in.
[MOANING]
Oh, my God.
Oh...
All right, so once a
year, a bunch of C-listers
get together at one of their places
- to get they wicks wet.
- [MOANING]
- [GRUNTS]
- Stop.
- Herogasm.
- Mm-hmm.
- I get it.
- Holy ass-ramming.
Ew.
Aw, stop!
Holy ass-ramming. Holy ass-ramming.
- [SCREAMS]
- [MOANING]
[FEMALE SUPE] Come on. Come on my hump.
That's it.
- [GRUNTING]
- [ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
Poor Frenchie.
He's always wanted to see
this. He's gonna be heartbroken.
- [MOTHER'S MILK] You know what's fucked up?
- Hmm?
[MOTHER'S MILK] It's that it's
real fucking sex workers here
getting banged up, and
not in the good way.
[SCREAMS]
[MOTHER'S MILK] Not that
these Supes give a shit.
When Soldier Boy gets here,
it's gonna be a slaughter.
We have to get these people out.
What up, bro?
What the fuck did this motherfucker
- put on my jacket?
- Oh, my God. Okay. Um...
It's my favorite fucking jacket.
- Let's go find a bathroom.
- Some nasty-ass shit.
- This shit is sticky.
Let's go clean it up. Let's go.
- What the fuck is this shit?
- Yellowtail sashimi?
No. No, not in the
mood for that. Thanks.
- Goddamn it.
- [MALE SUPE] Throwing ropes.
- [GASPS, SCREAMS]
- [MALE SUPE] Oh, shit.
Lick it up, you yummy brown bear.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I can't.
I need a bathroom.
Right now.
[HUGHIE] Oh, okay. So,
this... this is an actual orgy.
That's what this is.
[BUTCHER] Fucking Herogasm.
Still a thing, eh?
It's my thing. I founded it in '52.
Me and this other Supe, Liberty.
Man, was she a firecracker.
[SOLDIER BOY CHUCKLES]
Frenchie's gonna be
heartbroken he missed this.
There are a lot of people in there.
Well, as long as they stay
out of my way, they'll be fine.
Okay, all right. Just,
uh, give me three minutes.
I'll jump in, I'll jump back out.
I'll tell you exactly
where to find the twins.
Nobody else in your way.
Three minutes.
[BLUE HAWK] Soldier Boy?
Nah, he's dead as dog shit.
No, he's not.
I swear, this is really happening.
Please, you need to help me
get people out of here, now.
Starlight, come on.
Do not let them do this to you.
- [SIGHS]
- This... this fear.
You heard what Homelander said.
Lamestream media's making a
fucking mountain out of a molehill.
- Do the research.
- Oh, my God.
This is real.
These attacks are real.
Soldier Boy is real.
Well, I just think you could stand
to be a little better informed.
Homelander's gonna
take care of it, okay?
I'm gonna go find a salad to toss.
Excuse me.
[MOANING IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
[MALE SUPE 2] You melted my cock ring.
- [LOUD MOANING]
- [WOMAN] Oh, Jesus, your stretching powers!
[DEEP] Oh, my God,
your mouth is amazing.
It's like a velvet
vacuum draining my balls.
[DEEP] Oh, yeah. You are so fucking hot.
Oh...
God, your legs go on for days.
- [GRUNTS]
- [SQUISHING]
Ooh. Ooh. Oh, my God.
- What the fuck?
- Shit.
It's not what it looks like.
What are you doing here?
Nothing. I'm not doing
anything. Why would you even...
This octopus was sick.
Why would you ask that?
- Homelander is gonna love this.
- No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Please, please, please.
Stop. Stop, stop, stop. No.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay. Look.
That's why I'm here. It's his idea.
What's his idea?
I said no cameras in the toilets, Tommy.
- Give it back.
- You're pathetic.
[TESSA] You know what?
Let's see how everyone
feels about close-ups
of their assholes without consent!
Fuck you. I'm done.
[DISTANT] I never want to see you again.
Oh. That's so sweet.
Uh, just, I got to give
my asshole a breather.
You know?
[TESSA] Then say goodbye to
that Westfield mall opening
next week in Poughkeepsie, 'cause nobody
is coming to see you without me.
[TOMMY] I fucking hate
you. I hate your mouth.
I hate the way your
jaw pops when you chew.
And I hated every second I spent
holding that clammy hand.
I should've killed you in the womb.
Ah, fuck you!
Fuck you!
Fuck you, Tommy!
- [BOTH GRUNT]
- Sorry.
Ah.
Hey, I know you like fucking Supes,
but I'm off the table.
That's not why I'm here, okay?
You're here, too, you know.
Whatever, Pornhub.
I don't have time for you right now.
Hey.
You never said you were sorry.
What?
For Robin.
You never apologized for Robin.
Jesus, you want to do this right now?
[HUGHIE] Yeah, I do.
You just get away with
everything, don't you?
Just running past all the
broken people you leave behind.
All right, you know what?
What?
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
♪ Let me see you shit the floor... ♪
Is that what you want to hear?
'Cause I am.
Okay?
It's fucked up,
seeing somebody that you
love get hurt like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm fucking sorry, Hughie.
[HUGHIE PANTING]
- Hughie. Hughie.
- How did you do that?
- Stop, stop!
- No. No, no, no. How the fuck did you do that?
- I'll show you again!
- No.
That is not going to happen.
A-Train, get out of here.
Not that you deserve the warning.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on.
- [PANTING]
- Is he here?
He's only here for the twins, all right?
Nobody else has to get hurt.
You don't get to decide who to
serve up on a platter here, okay?
These are real people. We
need to clear the house now.
This is about to be a fucking bloodbath.
No, it won't. I made Soldier
Boy promise not to do anything...
Hughie, stop it. Listen to me.
Homelander is coming.
The Deep told me.
When those two start fighting...
Please. Help me.
- You have to go.
- No. I need to stop him.
Annie. No, Annie.
Annie!
[GASPS]
Oh, my God... You teleported me?
What the fuck?
I saved you, Annie.
Jesus Christ. All I want is to save you.
You keep saying that, but
I don't need you to save me.
Right, God forbid I help you,
because I always have
to be the weak one,
- the one you have to rescue.
- No.
You always have to be the strong one.
You always have to be
so much stronger than me.
I thought that you
didn't care about that.
I mean, on our first date,
you said that it didn't bother you.
I know.
But it does.
Sometimes.
A little.
I thought the drugs had
fucked you up, Hughie, but...
... this is you.
This is all you.
[INHALES]
Halothane.
What'd you think you
were gonna do with that?
You killed my family.
Which one?
[BUTCHER] Oi.
Not him.
Twins are out there.
[SIGHS]
[PANTING]
So you get Homelander, but
I can't get Soldier Boy?
You're a fucking hypocrite,
Butcher. Now move.
I can't let you do it, M.
It'd be suicide.
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
Oh, come off it. What
you gonna do with it?
Move!
You're such a fucking idiot.
Can't even work the TiVo without me.
[CACKLING]
And there it is, sick fuck.
Hiya, kids.
That poop chute's had a workout, huh?
Looks like the Lincoln Tunnel.
[TESSA] Ben.
You fucked me, you selfish
piece of shit!
That's enough.
[WOOD CLATTERS]
- Nicaragua wasn't our fault.
- Yeah, swear to God.
Then whose fault was it?
If you tell me, maybe I'll let you go.
I... it was Noir. It was Noir's idea,
top to bottom.
He gave you to the Russians. Please.
- Noir?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
- Noir wouldn't take a shit
without Vought's say-so.
Please? It's the truth.
[RUSSIAN POP SONG PLAYING]
[LOVE SAUSAGE SPEAKING RUSSIAN]
[RUSSIAN SONG PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
- Give me your hand.
- It's been years.
Do you want to die?
[BOTH] TNT detonate!
[SCREAMS]
[DISTANT EXPLOSION]
- I got to go.
- [HUGHIE] Annie, wait.
Annie, Annie, Annie, just...
You can't go.
I can't?
I'm not gonna let you.
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Oh, shit.
No. No.
I don't want to hear it right now.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Blue Hawk!
- What?
- We got to talk.
Jesus Christ, not right now.
There's a psycho back there.
[GRUNTS]
The fuck? Get your fucking hands off me.
You hurt a lot of people.
You hurt my brother.
You're not gonna get away with it.
Not this time.
- [SCREAMS]
- Fuck!
[BLUE HAWK SCREAMING]
[HEART BEATING RAPIDLY]
[A-TRAIN GRUNTING]
[HEART BEATING FASTER]
God.
[EXHALES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- Help me.
S... someone please help...
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[DISTANT SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
Huh.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[GRUNTS]
Sorted?
What happened?
William Butcher and Soldier Boy.
Of course.
You are behind this.
This whole thing.
It really is all about me.
William, we made a deal
to fight to the death, you and me.
This is cheating.
Deal's off.
You were my hero growing up.
I watched all your
movies, hundreds of times.
You were the only one that
was nearly as strong as me.
Buddy, you think you look strong?
You're wearing a cape.
You're just a cheap fucking knockoff.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm the upgrade.
[GUN CLICKS]
[STARLIGHT] M.M. M.M.
M.M., M.M., please, I
need you. People are hurt.
M.M.! M.M. Please.
He doesn't control you.
We have to help these people.
It's up to us.
[SHOUTS]
You really had me going
for a minute there.
Oi.
What the fuck?
What have you done?
Scorched earth.
[YELLING]
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTING]
Do it!
Hughie!
Get out of here!
No fucking way.
[STRAINING]
[SHOUTS]
[ALL PANTING]
Let's see?
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Hey, please, no. Easy.
We need a doctor to
resew these stitches.
It was always me.
What do you mean?
I blamed the V for making me a monster
but...
that's not true.
It is just who I am.
No.
You are not a monster.
It seems no matter
how much we try to run,
we cannot escape our old lives, huh?
I suppose no one can run that fast.
Those things
Little Nina said about you
are NOT true.
[LAUGHS SOFTLY] Yeah.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
This is a bad idea.
Homelander helped make
me America's sweetheart.
He's gonna regret that.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm in Montpelier, Vermont.
Twelve heroes and civilians are dead,
a lot more are wounded.
Now, Homelander and Vought
are going to tell you
that it was the Supervillain
and that they have it handled.
They don't.
It was Soldier Boy.
I know I sound insane, but...
Soldier Boy doesn't care
about protecting Americans,
and he probably never has.
Most heroes don't care about you.
They only care about their image, and...
Homelander is the worst of them.
He's hurt people.
He's done something to Maeve.
I don't know what they're gonna
do to me for telling the truth,
but I'm going to keep doing it,
and I should've done it sooner.
I'm sorry.
And one more thing.
I'm not Starlight anymore.
My name is Annie January...
... and I fucking quit.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
♪ ♪