Oh, heavens!
My hair is so soft and so shiny!
And so wonderfully easy to manage!
Make your hair look bright and clean
When you...
It's 10 to midnight, Central City...
... and once again your mayor refuses
to take seriously...
- ... my demand for $ 1 million.
- Look, that's him! The Ghost!
- Forcing me to keep my end of the bargain.
- Who will stop him?
- So at the stroke of 12...
- Get out of here!
... downtown will go up
in the brightest display of fireworks...
- ... this city has ever seen.
- Where's Night Shade?
Think of me as you sift
through the rubble.
This is the Ghost...
... wishing you all
a very good evening.
Time has come for the Night Shade
to drop in on the Ghost.
Well, let's have a big round of applause
for our special guest.
Oh, I wouldn't waste your firepower.
It's useless. Television allows me
to be everywhere.
You can't blackmail an entire city.
Of course I can, fool.
I'm the future.
And you're far too late to stop me!
One more adjustment
before detonation.
Your show's cancelled, Ghost.
Try Ghostess.
You should've stayed in Helltown
frightening mobsters.
You're psychotic.
One man's psychotic
is another man's visionary.
Video is the future.
And I'm detonating the bombs
with a television signal.
I don't wanna blow up
those buildings...
...but an ultimatum is an ultimatum.
Maybe you shouldn't blow up
the hospital, Russell.
Damn it, Belle. You can't let
human sentimentality...
...stand in the way of progress!
Too much TV, Ghost.
You've got no attention span.
- What did you do?
- Shortwave jamming device.
What did you do?!
Russell!
But he's still in there!
- No one could survive that fire.
- Russell!
Russell! Russell!
The turn of the century.
Welcoming the new millennium...
...after a nice frozen sleep.
A city of tomorrow.
In my prime, no less.
1990?
A decade early.
But still the future.
- and buildings so decayed,
pedestrians should be issued hardhats.
People ask why I live in this town.
Don't touch that dial.
Make this the year you take the jump...
... into large-screen technology
from Wacky Walter's Video Emporium.
We got them all, 178 channels,
hi-fi surround sound, cable-ready...
A hundred and seventy-eight channels?
This is the future.
Look at this place, Julio.
Akira 5700 computers,
stacks of imaging systems.
I tell you, compared to this place,
we work in a cave.
- Fascinating. Let me ask you something.
- What?
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I'm returning Tina's computer.
No, what are you always doing here?
As much time as you two spend together...
Julio. Do you have any women friends?
Yeah. I got Sabrina.
She's my woman and she's a friend.
And thank you for listening to Lite FM.
Would get it through those locks...
...that Tina and I are just...
- Too incredibly stupid to see...
...what's going on in front of you.
What a surprise. Central City's finest.
- Who's she been talking to?
- Hey.
My car broke down,
so Julio gave me a lift over here.
Yeah, Barry forgets the simple things.
You know, water, oil, gas.
I'll drive tonight. We're going bowling,
do you want to come?
I'd love to join you and Mr. Gutterball,
but we've all got that telethon thing.
What do you mean?
- I thought you asked her.
- I forgot.
Sabrina put together this telethon.
All you have to do is answer phones.
- Yeah, on TV. It's not a very good idea.
- It's for a good cause.
- What, are you camera-shy?
- No, I just...
Come on. Call your mother,
tell her you'll be on TV.
- You too?
- It'll be fun!
- Fun? Oh, fun.
- Yes, it'll be fun.
Come on, three-letter word...
This is how far TV's gotten?
Reduced to a pinball game?
I expected more.
Much more. The monorails,
the undersea cities, the moon colony.
Where's my future?
Killer! Rack up, homey.
What? Excuse me?
That's a bad score.
Bad? I've already shattered
the record.
Oh, no, no. Bad. Like in good.
Oh, I see.
Orwellian doublespeak,
like in 1984.
'84? Oh, I can't remember
that far back, man.
Bad is good. Wrong is right.
I like it.
I could use a couple of smart kids
who know their way around.
It's time someone showed you
what total video really means.
Oh, my God, Tina!
Shirt.
It's about time.
If I'm gonna be on TV,
I might as well look my best.
You look terrific.
- Thank you, Barry.
- Yeah.
- You're looking pretty good yourself.
- This outfit?
- I just threw it together.
- So I see.
Play "Mr. Sandman."
You got it.
I cashed in my Christmas Club.
Thirty-five years of compound interest
will support me till the millennium.
- You're dead.
- Have you forgotten already?
No, no, you can't...
You can't be him. He's dead.
I'm not dead, Belle.
Touch me. I made it.
You made... Made what?
My little Ghostess, just like old times...
...almost.
Oh, no, stop. Please don't.
I don't underst...
You wouldn't accompany me
on my cryogenic journey.
You mean, the freeze chamber?
How could I? It just sounded so nuts.
They all said that back then.
But now we live in a future
I predicted.
The only reason I failed in the '50s...
...was the technology wasn't up
to my dreams.
But failure now is impossible.
I'm gonna put a stranglehold
on this city.
The tools are here.
Back to work, Belle. I ain't paying you
to pick up circus gigolos.
At last technology has caught up
with me.
Hey! Stop!
Baby...
...I only wish you had joined me
in my beauty sleep.
Yeah, you and me both.
Thank you. And I'd like to thank
my partner, Tony Bello...
Officer Murphy, thank you very much.
Now we know why Central City's a jungle.
Okay, we also want to thank Star Labs
for their generous matching fund.
- Okay, thanks.
- Relief Fund.
Tina, this woman, third time
she's called.
- Wants to set me up with her daughter.
- This is not a dating service, Mr. Allen.
Nicely put. Excuse me, pal,
I gotta sit here.
I want the people to get to talk to the voice
of the city. That's the kind of guy I am.
- Sabrina, you want some coffee?
- Yeah, I'd love some.
And take Julio with you, okay?
Before his eyes pop out of his head
like a couple of golf balls.
Right.
Would you excuse me, please?
Thank you. Julio, your woman
and your friend strongly suggests...
...you take a short coffee break.
- Yeah, java sounds really good right now.
- I thought so.
Listen, Tina, I could show you things
you never dreamed of.
That's Dr. McGee. And I think
I'd prefer to dream, thank you.
- Hello?
Finally gonna try out that magic act,
huh, lieutenant?
Better than one more rendition
of "My Way."
That reminds me, I need an assistant
to saw in half.
- You available Monday?
- My phone's ringing.
- Warren.
- Gentlemen, our host, Dr. Desmond Powell.
Chief of staff, Central Hospital.
Barry Allen, Julio Mendez.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleasure.
Hi.
If you will excuse us,
I've known your lieutenant...
...for over 30 years, and we just
don't get together often enough.
Over here, lady! Over here!
Whoa, wait a minute!
This is a telethon, sparky.
There's no cash here, only pledges.
I hate your show.
Now, everybody watch the TV! Now!
In the '50s, I controlled TV. But to see
through it, to travel the network...
... I had to wait 35 years for
a techno-society sophisticated enough...
... for my plans.
And from the looks of things...
... it's been worth the wait.
Of course, it's not the urban paradise
of tomorrow we all expected.
The future is like the present,
only older.
But there's plenty new here
now that...
- Watch out!
- Look out!
You should've paid that million
back in '55, Central City.
I wouldn't hold such a grudge now.
Ladies and gentlemen, is this great TV
for your pledge dollar, or what?
- Excuse me. Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- I told you this telethon was a bad idea.
- Okay!
- Lieutenant, they made a clean getaway.
- Yeah, with a truckload of equipment.
- Have you seen Dr. Powell?
- No.
Here I thought all of this
was behind me.
Mavis, I'm fine.
I'll see you later. Bye-bye.
Allen! Anything on
that telethon takeover?
Julio went through that control booth
with a fine-toothed comb...
...but the prints he found
belonged to employees.
- What's that, breakfast?
- Yeah. Yeah, it's my...
- Help yourself.
- I'm stumped.
He took video and broadcast equipment
and nothing else.
Well, maybe the guy just wants
to be on TV.
- What the hell is this?
- It's a lox and onion burrito.
- It's good though.
- Yeah.
- Morning.
- Hey!
- How's the head?
- It could be worse.
Like that pound of buckshot you took
out of me in '72, remember that?
- What are you doing down here?
- Last night, guy on the monitors...
...that was the Ghost.
The Ghost? Forget it.
Couldn't be the same guy.
He'd be in his 60s.
The Ghost? Ghost of what,
telethons past?
Back in '55, this costumed nut
with his own pirate transmitter...
...tried to blackmail the city on TV.
Yeah, he threatened to blow up
half the town...
...unless the city came across
with $ 1 million.
- What happened?
- They found the bombs ready to go...
...but the Ghost disappeared.
The newspapers claimed that
this masked fruitcake took him out.
- His name was the...?
- Night Shade.
Night Shade, a vigilante. As big a pain
in the keister as the Flash is today.
Wait a minute, Garfield. I heard the Flash
saved your neck a couple of times.
Well, yeah.
But the good guys should wear badges.
That's the law.
How come I never heard of this guy?
Back then the world wasn't
on videotape. It was different.
One thing hasn't changed.
The police still don't need costumed nuts...
...interfering in an already impossible job.
Right, Allen?
Now wait, this guy wore a mask...
...and he fought crime.
- The police can't do everything.
Some people thought of Night Shade
as a hero.
Did they ever find out who he was?
He faded away, forgotten.
I kind of wonder what sort of man
would wear a mask.
That kind of adventuring can't leave
much room for a normal life.
Barry, it was good seeing you again.
Warren, I'll call you later.
That was the Ghost.
I don't know how, but he's back.
Come on. Just come right on.
Russell!
It really is you!
Oh, it's wonderful to see you again, Skip.
The years have been kind.
What Belle told me, it's true?
The cryogenic tank?
Oh, I never thought you'd build
the blasted thing.
All original parts, Skip.
You astound me like nobody's business.
There's so much for me
to learn, though.
Computers used to fill a room,
not a briefcase.
Everything you predicted back
in the '50s:
TV everywhere, satellites, PCs.
Not everything.
Where are the rocket packs
and home helicopters and food pills?
But I knew video was the key
to my future...
...knew it was going
to make me rich.
That's why I need you, Skip.
You were my best technician.
There's a world of possibilities
for me to master.
- You must teach me.
- Oh, you'll be teaching me in a week.
Now, the equipment I took from WCCN
gives me complete pirate access...
...but that's no longer enough.
Everything is connected these days
through data network.
He who controls information traffic
controls the system.
So instead of using TV
to detonate bombs...
- TV is the bomb.
- Yeah.
By plugging into the system,
I can bring the city to its knees.
I don't have Night Shade
to worry about.
If he's not dead, he's an old man now.
No offense.
But the Flash...
...tell me about the Flash.
Freak of nature. Moves like lightning.
He's already busted
a couple of Mob outfits.
Nobody knows for sure
just who or what he is.
Well, one thing is for certain:
It's time to get the rest
of the equipment we need...
...and take the Flash out of the picture
at the same time.
What kind of city do we live in
when even a charity telethon is not safe?
A broadcast studio is a temple
of entertainment and information.
What is this world coming to?
Think about it, ladies and...
We interrupt this program
for a special bulletin.
Tonight at midnight,
the Ghost welcomes his guest...
... the Flash, at Star Labs.
We'll be live and direct.
Don't you dare miss it.
Now, be careful with that.
It's an Akira 5700.
Damage it, and we'll have to bloody well
raid the Kremlin for another.
Kremlins? You mean those cute
little fuzzy dudes from the movie?
That's everything we need, Russell.
Let's scram.
Another minute or two, Skip.
I wouldn't want the Flash to think
we've cancelled his appearance.
Then on with the show, Ghost.
Entrapment lasers.
In about 60 seconds, that cone
will shrink down and fry you to a crisp.
Thank you for joining us.
Let's go!
- My God!
- Night Shade?
I hate reruns.
This time, Ghost, I'm putting you
on ice for good.
Still using knockout darts?
Pretty soft for these hard times.
By the way, who the hell are you?
A colored guy.
Who would've guessed?
"Colored"? You really are a relic.
And you're just a tired old man
who's going to bleed to death.
Say goodbye to this year's model.
Dr. Powell?
My car, Gladstone bag, rear seat.
Doctor, what should I do?
It feels like a flesh wound,
hurts like hell.
You dress it and bandage it,
it should be okay.
That was pretty good. Now...
Yeah, help me get out of here.
- I'll get an ambulance.
- No.
It's all right. And, thanks.
It's nice to meet the man
who picked up the torch.
- Dr. Powell.
- Allen, what are you doing here?
Well, I was driving by
and I heard the alarm.
A friend of mine works
at Star Labs, so l...
- Dr. Powell, there's blood on your hand.
- Oh, it's nothing. Nothing.
- That'll be the squad cars responding.
- I can't let them find me like this.
Right, but look, I'll drive, okay?
Where to?
I'll show you.
You've seen enough already.
I guess I'll trust you with the rest.
How could I have been so stupid
at my age, putting on a mask...
...going after the ghost
like I was 25 again.
I can't believe this place.
Souvenirs of another life.
That diving suit was my first case.
These guys were scuttling boats
outside Central Harbor.
Those model airplanes,
hit man called himself the Aviator...
...loaded them up with dynamite
and tried to fly them into city hall.
- Yeah, but you stopped him.
- Yeah.
This is a beautiful car.
I welded steel plate on the inside.
Damn thing's like a tank.
Dr. Powell...
...what made you do it?
Why'd you become the Night Shade?
Someone had to be.
I came home from Korea,
this town was being squeezed...
...between the Mob
and a corrupt administration.
And making the law your own...
...enforcing it with your own gun,
that was okay?
After Korea, I couldn't kill anybody.
But...
...I sure as hell could put them down
for the count.
I modified this gun
to shoot tranquilizer darts.
Okay, but running around in...
Why did you put on a mask?
I was working outside the law,
I was black...
...nobody was gonna give me
any medals.
- Besides, I had to...
- Protect your loved ones.
Yeah.
You're pretty sharp, Allen.
Well, I was born and raised
in Central City.
How come I never heard
of Night Shade?
I was good copy for a while.
Then I quit, right after the Ghost.
Thirty-five years from now,
who'll remember the Flash?
Well, I don't know.
He's done a lot of good for the city,
don't you think?
Yeah, but...
Thank you.
- So did Night Shade.
People forget. Trust me.
Looks like you were having the time
of your life.
At the expense of everything else.
My health, my family,
my fiancée. She left me.
- She knew she had a rival.
- The night...
...the danger.
- Pardon me?
- Well, it must've been kind of addicting.
- Living a double life nearly destroyed me.
You take Garfield.
He's one of my closest friends.
I've taken lead out of him
at least a dozen times.
But I still can't share my secret
with him.
No, I guess not.
But tell me about the Ghost.
He used this crude form
of two-way television.
He could secretly make a set turn
into a sort of camera...
...to case buildings
for possible burglaries...
...to spy on people,
to blackmail public officials.
Finally, he planted bombs
all over the city...
...rigged to detonate on a TV signal.
- And held the city for ransom.
But I rigged this in '55,
jammed his transmission.
I thought for good.
It terrifies me to think
what he can do...
...with the technology he stole
from Star Lab.
Where am I, Skip?
You've broken into
the power and light, I think.
The Akira system let us go online
everywhere in the city.
Everything really is connected
these days.
From power I can reach telephone...
...from there, the water system.
One gigantic game, isn't it?
Do you wanna go through with this?
Actually wire yourself to that machine?
Absolutely.
This is crazy!
What's the matter, Belle?
You okay?
Sure. Sure, I'm okay.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- No, I'm not.
This just isn't working.
You just can't do this.
- Blackmail the city?
- The hell with the city!
You can't...
...come walking back into my life
after 35 years.
Let alone...
...not looking a day older.
Darling, I love you.
It doesn't matter.
But you've changed.
Even if you don't look any different.
I mean, what you're talking about, hooking
into these machines, it's just crazy!
I know what I'm doing,
don't worry.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I always have.
But you just can't come walking
into my life and still be 30.
It just isn't fair.
Should I get her, sir?
Time to enter the net.
I want to flex a little...
...see what I can do
with what we've just stolen.
And with the new knowledge
I've acquired...
...controlling the city's database
is just the first step.
Oh, boy. It's gotta be those yahoos
at water and power again, you know.
Yeah, we're lucky they shut down
the nuclear plant last year.
Hey, you see this white glove?
This means we're gonna do this
my way.
Hey, you! You can't do that.
I beg your pardon, sir.
Why don't you just back up?
- You're only licensed to sell on the sidewalk.
- Oh, boy.
Forget about it, fellas,
it's backed up all the way to Japan.
Hello, this is car 432.
We're on a break.
Hey, Mr. Wienie. Let me have a couple
of chilidogs, hold everything, okay?
Come on! Come on!
Oh, come on. This is eight hours
of work down the tubes!
Come on.
Crime Lab. Yeah, hold on a second.
Barry, the computers
have gone berserk, man.
What, have you got cartoons here?
Hello?
- Barry, the whole computer base...
- Tina, slow down.
We've got cartoons
on the computer over here.
I'd kind of enjoy it if it wasn't
destroying three weeks' work.
I have a very bad feeling
about this.
- What shall I do?
- We're back online here.
- Call me if it happens again, all right?
- Okay.
Bye.
Dr. Powell...
...the car radios, the traffic lights,
the computers. This is the Ghost.
He's just flexing his muscles
right now.
- Think he's got something bigger online?
- These are just pranks, a warm-up.
When he lets out all the stops...
...there's no way the police
will be able to stop him.
- Well, do you think he's capable of...?
- I saw his face.
The man has stopped time,
kept his youth.
- Lf he can do that...
- I can't let you go out there.
This is my past hunting me.
Now it's time for me
to become the hunter.
- Can you understand that?
- For God's sake, you could be killed!
Now I know how Tina feels.
The hell with it.
We're closed, pal.
You haven't changed a bit, Belle.
That voice.
The Night Shade?
Oh, sorry, I thought you were
somebody else.
You were right the first time.
Oh, not again!
Please, not you too!
Just leave me alone!
I really wish I could.
You're probably the only one
that can help me find the Ghost.
- Go away.
- I need to ask you...
...about him.
- He was out of my system...
...just a memory.
- Why couldn't he just stay that way?
- I wish he had.
That deep freeze...
...blew his mind.
He thinks he can do anything.
He doesn't wanna
just control the machines...
...he says he's gonna become
the machine.
Where is he, Belle?
He's...
...where you left him
after the showdown in '55.
What, that old pile?
It's been abandoned for years.
Yeah, it stayed abandoned
because he owns the building.
I went there right after the fire
and searched.
- There was nothing.
- A hidden room.
That's where he slept while I...
It just isn't fair!
I just can't pretend
I'm 20 anymore.
Neither can I.
- Night Shade.
- What are you doing here?
- Just watching your back.
- What makes you think it needs watching?
I was doing this before you were born.
Then why don't you show me
how it's done?
Okay.
The Ghost is holed up in
the old brewery on Shadow Lawn.
All right! Let's go down
there and get him.
Slow down, speedy.
You gotta have a plan. Hop in.
No. Bad for the image.
All I'm saying is that nobody's
done this before.
- You might not come back.
- A possibility.
But first I take Central City off-line...
...by just mischievously transposing
its entire communications network...
...its power core.
If you're serious about plugging
into the network...
...I can do the job. But you might be risking
an electronic lobotomy here.
I didn't survive three and a half decades
in cold storage...
...because I didn't know what
I was doing! Now, key me in, Skip.
I can feel everything, Skip.
Everything.
The very power of the city
courses through my veins.
I'm wired, Skip.
Wired to everything.
Time now to show Central City
what a comeback really means.
Good evening, Central City.
Don't bother adjusting your sets...
... I will control the vertical.
I will control the horizontal.
Now, the last time I spoke to you like this,
my demands were reasonable:
A cool million.
But the times have changed, and
my price has gone up a thousandfold.
So unless Central City opens
its treasury to me and my associates...
... I will shut everything down:
Power, gone. Lights, out.
Heat, water, shut down.
Computer records, payroll,
wiped away.
Air traffic, ground traffic,
without control.
"I'll foul up every telephone number
in the system.
No more 911."
- Just listen.
- Just imagine your hospitals...
... without their life's blood of energy.
- He's crazy.
- This will be a city of darkness...
- How can he do this?
- ... of desperate, hungry, thirsty citizens.
Complete and beautiful chaos.
My price:
- One billion dollars before dawn.
- What?!
- Russell, please don't. Don't do this, please.
- And remember, even if you do pay...
- ... I am the heart and soul of this city.
- What?
- Hey, what happened?
- What happened?
I'm telling you, Murph, this is worse
than the blackout of '71.
The blackout of '71 was one
of the best nights I ever spent in my life.
Oh, yeah, let me guess,
a motel room with Michelle.
Yeah, that's pretty close.
Actually, it was a stuck elevator
with the Corelli twins.
The Corelli twins were guys, Murph.
I know. And two of the worst poker players
you ever saw in your life.
- Honest to God, 2600 bucks, one night.
- Twenty-six hundred?
Commissioner, we're doing
everything we can.
I can't get ahold of any of my units!
Hello? Hello? What?
Two pairs of pants
and a cashmere sweater?
Lady, this is not Morty's Cleaners!
All the phone lines are crossed.
Get me a squad car to South and Grand,
we got looters.
Have some good news for me,
Mendez, please.
The hospital's on reserve power
just like us.
The Ghost is tapped into fire, ambulance
and police dispatch. We're operating blind.
Well, we can't just ram into the brewery
and take the guy on.
We don't know what the Ghost has
or what he's become.
You defeated him with this
once before. Maybe it'll work again.
That's Popular Science 101
compared to what he's got now...
...what he is now. Anyway, it's broken.
I'll fix it. Give me an hour.
You think this has a chance of working?
There's only one way we'll find out
if this rig'll produce power.
Good job, Barry.
Okay.
So let's take this relic into the '90s.
You can't really expect that
to work twice.
The future belongs
to the young.
I can handle Night Shade myself,
it's the Flash I'm concerned about.
Make sure he doesn't get in here.
I have a universe of microchip
technology at my fingertips.
But when it comes to disposing
of old things, the old ways are still best.
The old ways. Works for me.
Welcome to my world...
...where you, my friend,
have no power whatsoever!
Now I could just wipe you away...
...but first you must sample
my programming.
Tranquilizer darts.
- Night Shade!
- That's right. Night Shade.
At least I haven't lost it all.
Don't touch that dial.
Case closed, Night Shade.
What? Look! The lights
are coming back on!
Dr. Powell.
I've learned a lot working with you.
Yeah? Well, the next time you need me
for one of these little romps...
...forget about it. I'm retired.
I guess we're lucky we're not dead...
...or in a straitjacket.
There's not many people
who will ever know the thrill...
...when the sky goes dark,
the masks go on...
...and the criminal hearts
thump with fear.
Sorry...
...too many pulp magazines
when I was a kid.
But you know what I mean.
Do you ever reveal your secret
to anyone?
I have someone I share it with.
She helps keep me
on an even course.
She?
Good for you.
But if you ever need
anyone else to talk to...
...l'm here.
It does get difficult sometimes...
...speaking behind a mask.
- No. Don't.
I don't need to know.
And you don't need the complication.
You know, you ought to start
your own trophy room.
Allow me to donate the first exhibit.
And remember, my fast friend...
...these outfits we wear are just another
suit of clothes, not another man.
[ENGLISH]
www.tvsubtitles.net