- My name is Barry Allen
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present,
and now our world
is more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
[weapon clanking]
- Ah!
- What is that?
- It's a game my dad and I
used to play.
- It's a letter from my dad.
He's still alive.
- You put a power dampening
chip inside me
to take away my speed.
- Is that why
you've been so cold to me?
Why you don't want to spend
any time with me?
- Mom thinks
that she had good reason
to suppress my powers
in the future.
- I support her decisions.
- Let's just call it, Barry.
She's not coming. Again.
- She's probably
just helping with Jenna
so Joe
and Cecile can sleep in.
- Every day
for the past two weeks?
- They look really tired.
They do.
[computer beeping]
- Tripped alarm at Central City
Art Gallery.
Someone stole a Monet.
- At 10:00 a.m.? That's bold.
- CCPD's en route,
suspect heading west on Ruger.
[engine revving]
[sirens wailing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- The thief just turned
on to Ramirez off of Fifth.
- Almost there.
[engines revving]
♪ ♪
[horn honks]
He's not carrying anything.
- Because he handed it off
to someone else.
- Nora?
- Uh, where's he headed?
- I got him.
I can stop someone
on a motor cycle.
- No, Nora,
let Barry help, okay...
I know you did not
just cut me off, miss thing.
[engine revving]
- Gotcha.
- You okay?
♪ ♪
- This is why we train, Nora.
Every single day.
Not when you feel like it,
not because you're mad,
and why you
always have someone in your ear
when you're in the field
to help you.
- I know that.
- Then why did you turn me off?
- Because I can't
listen to you anymore.
It's always
the same condescending,
I-know-better-than-you crap.
I just want to be me
and you sit behind your desk
and you say "no"
every time
and I've been hearing it my
whole life and I'm sick of it.
- Your whole life?
- Yes, Mom.
Since I can remember,
and you never change.
- Iris.
You know, Nora, I wish you
would try to understand
who your mom is today,
and stop seeing her as who she
becomes in the future.
- That's for you.
- The hell is this?
- Well, that's the hours
to apply against my debt.
Fruitful hours spent getting
closer to uncovering
the identity of your
serial meta-killer, Cicada.
- And how's that?
- Well, I apply a complex
formula...complex for you,
involving the terminal
velocity and the weight
of the S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite
and the velocity of Barry
and Nora traveling
when they...
destroy the satellite, right,
allowing me to conclude that...
The debris from the satellite,
the satellite shrapnel,
and the man
who would become our Cicada
would be found
within this perimeter.
- And that took you how long?
- Oof, Dr. Snow.
Eighteen hours 'cause I'm only
semi-excellent at algebra.
- You know this is calculus,
right?
- Guys, look,
calculon, algebra,
either way it doesn't tell us
where the shrapnel fell.
- Mais non. You have to scan
the entire city
to find
the exact location.
- Okay, so you need Sally
the satellite to find
Sally the satellite
and we need Thomas Snow
to point us
to Thomas Snow.
- You lost him.
- At Thomas Snow.
- We've hit a dead end
with regards to my father.
I looked through all
of his notes and papers.
There's no more hidden
messages we could use.
A satellite to run DNA
recognition patterns but...
I thought losing him
when I was ten was hard, but,
the idea that he's out there
and I might not be able
to get to him...
- Maybe I can help you.
- I thought your powers
weren't working.
- No, not fully,
but this I can do.
♪ ♪
- You okay?
- I saw him.
I saw your dad in...in an office
sketching something
in a notebook.
I couldn't quite
make out what it was.
- Did you see anything else?
- Um, equations
on a chalkboard.
- We didn't have a chalkboard
in our home office.
- No, but tell us everything
that you saw.
What's on the walls, what's on
the desk, what he was wearing.
Leave nothing out.
- He had an ID.
It was, like, a yellow logo,
like a yellow state building.
- Yellow logo, so,
not a state building.
A university building.
[snap]
Hudson University.
- Professor Stein.
- And did you know him?
- I knew he admired him,
but I didn't realize
that they were friends.
Add that to the growing list
of secrets.
- Let's go drive.
- Thank you.
- It's what I do.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Natalie, come here. I have
a pre-wedding surprise for you.
[soft piano music]
♪ ♪
Flawless asscher cut diamonds
set in platinum.
Over 383 karats.
My great grandfather gave this
to his wife
on their wedding day.
Tomorrow, it's yours.
- Tomorrow?
That's torture.
[soft crackling]
- [giggles]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[bones cracking]
- Stop!
[crackling]
- Mazel Tov.
- [shrieking]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Can you describe the man
that you saw?
- I'd barely call him a man,
the way he moved.
And when he looked back at me,
it was terrifying.
- Could you see his face?
- No.
He was wearing
some sort of clown mask.
- And you're sure the necklace
is the only thing
that was stolen.
- Yes, and it's irreplaceable.
- Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
- Hey.
A nice surprise.
- Yeah, well, a million dollar
jewelry theft is still news
even in Central City, so.
- So, you're off the metas,
huh?
- Yeah, no, not today.
You know, I think I'm just
gonna follow up on this
while it's still fresh.
I'll see you tonight, okay?
- Okay, wait. Hang on.
I mean, we're working
on the same case.
Why don't we pool resources,
maybe solve this one together.
- Yeah, I don't know, Barry,
it's just...
- Come on, grab some Big Belly
on the way to S.T.A.R. Labs.
It'll be like a date.
- All right.
- All right. Come on.
- This is the life.
Seriously,
I could stay here forever.
No worries, no schrap from
mom...
- Wait, wait, wait,
what was that?
- Schrap.
- Schrap?
- Schrap. You know, like all
the nagging that mom does.
I mean,
she acts like she supports me,
but what she really
wants is a boring,
quiet daughter who just wants
to stay inside all day
instead of go out
and do anything
that might be
the least bit dangerous.
- Nora, this is the West house.
In it, every West
is given respect,
most especially your mother.
I am sure she raised you
as best she could.
- She raised me to be afraid
of the world.
But I'm a hero,
you know, like dad.
And we have to keep moving
until everyone
that needs us is safe.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry, what is this for?
- When Papa Joe comes back,
this table
is going to
finally be built.
You wanted to keep moving.
- Oh, do I have to?
- Yes.
All right, I'll make you
a deal.
For every chore you do
I'll tell you one thing Papa
Joe told me about your father
that didn't make it into
the precious Flash museum.
- Oh, Mama Cecile,
the museum has
a complete record of
all of Dad's accomplishments.
- Including the time Barry
ended up in an alternate past
filled with golden giants
called "Grodans"?
- Wait, what?
- Grodans.
- Done.
So then what happened?
- Not done.
Wait for it.
Huh.
Yeah.
- So, why exactly
does Caitlin have a key
to Professor Stein's
old office?
- Clarissa gave me a key.
She didn't realize that Martin
and my father knew
each other either.
I wonder
what he was doing in here.
- Well, perhaps Mr. Ramon
could vibe the chalkboard
and we could see
for ourselves.
What do you think?
♪ ♪
- What did you see?
- Hydrogen chains bonded
over and over.
Two oxygen
at absolute zero.
It's like it's
making heavy water.
- Not heavy water.
Ice.
- Another one of my father's
hidden messages?
- Ah.
- "Khione"?
- What kind of a message
is "Khione"?
- A clear one.
At least to me.
Look, monsieur Ramon,
you said that earlier that
you could see that Dr. Snow,
her father sketching
something, right?
That sketch that you could
almost make out...
Did it look
a little something like this?
- Good lord,
are you a speedster?
- Speed sketcher.
It's a modest talent.
- My father was drawing me?
- Not you.
Khione.
Khione, the Greek goddess.
Child of the North Wind,
whose realm was ice and snow.
- Khione.
Killer Frost.
- That means that whatever
Thomas was doing,
he knew that there
were two of you.
- Also, it stands to reason
that Thomas was there
at the point of creation
of Killer Frost.
- So, he knew the truth
about Killer Frost?
He knew who I really am?
- Right.
- Did I scare him away?
- No, this wasn't your fault.
Look, I don't know why he left,
but it wasn't because of you,
and we're gonna prove that.
♪ ♪
- You okay?
- Yeah, just lost my footing
there for a second.
- What...
- What did you see?
- You guys ever hear
of Viera Chemicals?
- Oh, it's an old chem lab
out in the Barrens,
but it's been shut down
for years.
- Well,
what are we waiting for?
♪ ♪
- You know, it's been great
seeing you out there again,
doing what you love.
- Yeah, I guess some girls grow
up wanting to be Supergirl.
I always wanted to be Soledad
O'Brien or Christiana Amanpour.
So yeah,
it's really great to reconnect.
[beeping]
- That's weird.
It says the hair I found
is human
but it can't pull any DNA.
- Maybe run it again?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- Come on, Novick.
You wanna improve
Gotham City's skyline,
you do it with a building
nobody can take
their eyes off of.
That's one of mine.
You go with me,
I'll design you a building
that makes the Burj Khalifa
look like a strip mall.
Architecture
means everything to me.
I mean, you tell me.
How many other architects
have won
the Pritzker Prize three times?
Good choice.
♪ ♪
- Where did you get this?
- By some really weird markings
at the bottom
of a large gift box
that I'm pretty sure
was opened from the inside.
- Okay, you know
you're opening all of our mail
from now on, right?
[computer beeping]
- Somebody called in a bomb
threat at Seaver Architects.
♪ ♪
What happened?
- That thing, it did this.
♪ ♪
- Flash.
[crunching]
[rumbling]
♪ ♪
- That thing destroyed
my life's work.
♪ ♪
- So, he squeezed his way
through an air
conditioning vent?
- Yeah, he could stretch
kinda like Ralph,
except he was wearing a...
- Clown mask.
- Yup.
- Just like the guy that stole
the Winehouse necklace.
- Mm-hmm.
We got a stretching clown meta.
- Yeah,
that's not creepy at all.
- Yeah.
- Did you find any more
of those weird lines?
- No, and if there's more,
they're buried underneath
tons of rubble, just like
our meta, unless he was able
to stretch out
of that one too.
Which...I'm sure he was.
The lines.
- What?
- Well, I mean, our meta can
stretch and contort, right?
What if his fingerprints
can too?
[computer beeping]
Got him.
Peter Merkel.
And he was arrested
for B&amp;E two years ago.
- Wait, Peter Merkel, the son
of Billionaire Theresa Merkel?
[sighs] Yup.
How does someone go from being
a member of high society
to stealing heirlooms
and blowing up buildings?
- Maybe we should attend
this gala she's hosting
and ask her ourselves.
- Uh, I don't know,
what if Merkel's there?
- So what?
We'll come prepared.
Some meta handcuffs for me,
a taser for you,
and we get to dress up.
- Barry.
- What?
- This is a meta investigation;
this is not date night.
- I'm just saying,
I look really good in a tux.
- [chuckles]
- When did this happen?
- The night your father
disappeared.
- Oh.
Well, well, well.
Liquid nitrogen.
That's a potent accelerant,
is it not?
Oh, this place
it would have gone up. Whoa.
- So, all my father's work
is completely gone?
- Well, not necessarily.
I mean, think about it.
Police listed this fire as
accidental,
but they didn't know
about the connection
to Caitlin's father, so...
- Ralph, my father told me
to come find him.
- Yeah, no, I know that,
but a guy who disappears
on the night of a warehouse
fire and who's hard to find?
- Well, if you think this was
arson, let me tell you,
if her father did this, well,
he would need a lot of help
covering his tracks, right?
- Yeah.
Maybe he got it.
- Listen, my mom may not be
the best person,
but there's no way she'd be
party to something like this.
- There's one way to find out.
- What, you want to question
the mother again?
You already did that,
and what did you get? Nothing.
- Well it's a clue.
Surely, we should follow it.
- You already know
that this is still
Tannhauser facility, okay?
So you're wrong.
- Oh, I'm wrong? I'm wrong?
I'm the one who figured out
Cicada's mask.
You couldn't figure that out.
You said you wouldn't doubt me,
that was your mistake.
- Enough, yeah, enough!
Just give me this.
♪ ♪
- Cisco?
Cisco?
[classical music playing]
♪ ♪
- You look amazing, by the way.
- Thank you.
- There's Theresa Merkel.
Come on.
- Wait. What are we going
to say?
We can't just ask her if
her son was recently hit
by dark matter into shrapnel.
- You'll think of something.
- Me?
[clears throat] So sorry.
Hi, Mrs. Merkel.
I'm Iris West Allen.
- Oh, I know who you are.
Don't you usually
write about lunatics
and the heroes
who catch them?
- Well, you know,
supporting the arts
is a citywide concern.
- Hmm.
- I'm Barry Allen.
- Ah. And you're obviously not
here to make a sizeable
donation which means you,
my dear,
are here on assignment.
All right, ask whatever you
like. You have two minutes.
- Well,
it's about your son, Peter.
When was the last time
that you saw him?
- That would be two years ago
when he broke
into his own house.
I was out of town,
and my staff had him arrested.
- Do you know
where Peter is now?
- No, and I don't care.
See,
I gave him the world.
The finest private schools,
his own wing to play in.
But he just
never appreciated it.
Enjoy the party.
- I feel kinda bad for him now.
- She's so cold.
Can you imagine
what that was like?
[piano music]
- Hey, you know what?
It's not a date
without a dance.
- Barry, wait.
I mean, this is work, right?
We just hit a dead end, so,
why don't we just go home?
- Hey, hey.
Just one dance, all right?
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- You know, we never really
had our first dance.
- Yeah, this is really nice.
♪ ♪
- Excuse me for a second.
[crickets chirping]
-  Hey. You okay?
- [sighs]
- She gave her only son
everything that she had
and it wasn't enough.
Just like I'm not enough
for Nora.
- You are nothing
like that woman in there.
- You're sure, Barry?
I mean, I love our daughter
with all my heart,
but she hates me.
Because I turn my back on her
just like Theresa Merkel
did to her son.
I lie to her
about everything that she is.
And I prevent her from living
the life that she deserves.
I'd hate me too.
- Iris.
You are never going to be
the person that Nora knows
from the future.
- That's the thing.
It's not even up to us.
I've already become her
and I didn't even
have a choice.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[eerie music]
- While you were unconscious,
I scanned your wounds.
There are still trace amounts
of aluminum-beryllium alloy
fused within your hands.
It's remnants
from Cicada's dagger.
- See, this is...this
is what I need.
I just need rest.
- No, Cisco, rest is not
going to fix this, okay?
Every time you vibe or breach,
the dark matter
is going to affect
your central nervous system,
causing you more and more pain.
Wait...which you must have been
experiencing all day today.
Why didn't you say anything?
- Because you're my friend
and you needed my help.
- Okay, but I would never ask
you to hurt yourself.
Every time you vibe
you are going to have
more and more seizures.
- Then what am I
supposed to do?
I remember when these powers
were a curse.
Seeing Thawne kill me
over and over.
Knowing that darkness.
I didn't want that.
I didn't want to be a hero.
These powers were a part of me.
I had to learn that.
And when I did,
they showed me everything.
I could vibe every clue.
I could breach us
wherever we needed to go.
I could bring my value
to the team.
If I can't take the pain,
that means Cicada wins.
- No.
Hey.
Listen, I get it, okay?
When DeVoe took away
Killer Frost, I was destroyed.
But you know what?
I'm still here.
And so are you.
Because you are Cisco Ramon.
Genius engineer,
prodigy hacker,
and the mechanic
who built a cold gun
that could stop
a speedster.
And you're my friend.
You're my friend who went out
there and hurt himself today.
Just to help me try
and find my dad.
And that wasn't vibe.
That was Cisco,
and that's the guy I need.
- That cold gun
was pretty amazing.
- It was stolen
almost immediately...
- Oh, immediately.
- But yeah,
it was pretty great.
- You know, this case
will keep until morning.
- Yeah, I know, it's just
Merkel's still out there.
And the gala was a dead end
and all we know
is that he committed two
completely unrelated crimes.
[soft music]
I don't know what to do
about Nora, Barry.
- Yeah.
Well, look. I mean, you know
I'm on your side with this.
If you dampen her powers
in the future,
it's because
you care about her.
You're doing it
to keep her safe.
- Yeah.
Just because I can protect her
doesn't mean
that I'm a good mom.
- This isn't like
what happened with Francine.
- Isn't it?
She left me and my dad kept it
a secret all to protect me.
And when she came back,
I pushed her away.
I barely had a chance
to know her before she...
I lost my chance to connect
with my mom and...
Now when I get older, Nora is
going to push me away too.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Well, it sure seems to be
going in that direction.
- Then choose
a different route.
Make a different choice
when you raise Nora.
If you don't want to be that
person, don't be that person.
- It's not that simple,
Barry.
- You're not your mom.
You're not Iris
from the future,
and you don't have to be, ever.
I think
you should stop worrying
about who you might become
and reconnect with who you are,
now.
- Yeah.
- Now, let's go home,
all right?
- Actually,
can I just meet you there?
I think I have a lead.
- Okay.
- [laughing] Shut up.
Dad did not keep singing.
- No way was your father
gonna let
the middle school
production of "Guys and Dolls"
turn out to be a disaster.
Okay, um, one more.
So, when your dad was
about ten,
there was a kid in his class
that lost his folks.
Kid stopped smiling,
barely spoke.
And for some reason,
all of the other kids in school
were being so mean to him.
So, your father had lunch with
this boy
every single day
for a whole year.
And when springtime came
and the yearbook came out
your father gave the kid
an entire page
and the photos
of his science fair project
made him "most
likely to succeed."
And then the boy
finally smiled.
- Wait, but dad
wasn't in yearbook.
That story
wasn't about dad, was it?
It was about mom helping dad.
Wait, were all those stories
you told me about mom?
- Nora, you're projecting
all of these feelings
that you have
about Iris 30 years from now.
You're not getting to know
who she is today.
These stories that I told you,
they're what made me fall
in love with the Wests.
Made me realize how special
this family is.
So...
If you liked them,
plenty more in here.
♪ ♪
[soft creaking]
[phone buzzing]
- Hey.
- Hey babe, I just spoke
with Mrs. Merkel.
I think I know
what Peter wants.
The Jewelry, the building,
they all meant something
personal to the victim.
He wants to deliver
the most painfully emotional
blow possible.
Just like his family did
to him.
- [sighs]
- You...you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sorry, that MO
fits perfectly.
Who do you think's
his next victim?
Ugh!
- Barry?
- Come and get him.
- Guys, Merkel kidnapped Barry.
- What?
- How's that even possible?
- He's got Barry's meta-cuffs.
- Well, that would do it.
- Who are you calling?
[phone buzzing]
- Damn it, Nora pick up.
- I'll ping Barry's cell,
see if I can get a location.
He's in Eaglesham apartments
on Simone Ave.
- I don't think he's in the
apartments so much as on them.
- Right.
- Okay, guys.
We don't have a speedster,
Cisco can't breach,
and Killer Frost
is out of commission.
We need to come up with a plan
to rescue Barry now.
- The extrapolator.
We can reach in and grab him.
- Great, where is it?
- Right.
Uh, about that...
I broke it.
- How did you break this?
Batting practice?
- It's not user friendly.
- You're not user friendly!
- Cisco.
- It's going to take me
at least an hour to fix it.
- Cisco, we don't have an hour.
- Well, I...
- No, but we do have me.
♪ ♪
Let's go save The Flash.
- [speaks French]
That was inspiring.
- You got a cuff key?
- Thanks.
I'll drive.
- Actually,
I wanna try something.
Saw it in a comic book.
Whoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
- Ah, you're choking me.
You're choking me.
[screaming]
Hey, I used to live there.
- Ralph.
- Oh, I got it.
[ominous music]
[eerie tones]
[crackling]
♪ ♪
- Police man.
Fancy cuffs.
- Peter,
you don't want to do this.
Look, I know
how you got your abilities.
The night of the enlightenment,
right?
You were hit by a piece of
the satellite, weren't you?
- Crushed!
Snapped.
Broken.
- Okay, well, I know people
who can help you.
People who could stop
your suffering.
- Suffering can't be stopped.
Especially hers.
- If you touch Iris...
- Don't want to hear your pain.
Only your wife's.
- Let him go.
- The wife.
You fire, he dies.
- Okay.
Okay.
Just don't hurt him.
[phone buzzing]
- Hey Caitlin, what's up?
♪ ♪
- You heard the lady,
Raggedy Dandy.
Let him go.
- [sighs]
Okay.
- Barry!
♪ ♪
- Mom. Holy schrap.
You just threw yourself off
a building to save dad?
- Yeah.
- That was beyond schway.
- You're crazy.
- I am.
- Thank you. I love you.
- I love you.
Oh, my God.
Ralph is still up there.
- I hope I don't land
on my keys!
- Ah.
- Uh.
- [groans]
You guys
still have those meta-cuffs?
- Iris West Allen, I know
badassery when I see it
and that was raw, unrefined,
cage-free,
non-GMO, badassery right there.
- You dove off a building.
- For me.
- Yeah, I guess I kinda did.
- What was going
through you mind?
- "Uh, please, God,
don't let me drop this key."
- I mean, weren't you afraid?
You're not a speedster.
- No, I'm not.
But my husband and my partner
and my best friend is.
- Well, not to interrupt
this wonderful moment
that I just interrupted, but,
you know, I helped defeat
that boneless bozo too.
- Mm-hmm.
- It wasn't so easy.
And that...God, that mask.
It's like one of those
porcelain dolls
that's gonna
kill you while you sleep.
- I thought it was more like
a ragdoll.
Yeah, that's right.
Still got it.
Hold your applause.
- Guess it's off
to Iron Heights
for slippery old ragdoll.
- Oh, wait, you're...you're
leaving?
- Yeah, um,
there's something I need to do,
but I'll be right back.
I promise.
[soft music]
- She looks happy.
- Yeah, she really does.
- I do that too.
- Oh.
I was writing
about what you did tonight.
It was awesome.
- Thanks.
I guess
it kinda runs in the family.
- Where did you get that?
- Oh.
♪ ♪
- Dad's always adding to it.
It's so silly.
- No, it's not. It's your life.
I mean, editor
of the school paper by age 11.
Exposing a corrupt school
teacher at the age of 15.
I mean, you never talk
about this stuff.
In the...the future, I mean.
It's, um, one of your
off-limits topics.
I'm not allowed
to ask about it.
- Look.
Nora.
I am not that person
in the future.
And nothing
is off limits to me, okay?
I'm not gonna sit
behind a desk and say "no."
I want you to live your life.
And...
I want you to be
a part of mine.
No secrets, no lies, just...
Us being who we are today.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
- Did you really stake out the
school bathroom in third grade
to prove that the school
janitor wasn't cleaning it?
- I'm gonna kill Cecile.
But, um, yes.
I was a real-life Nancy Drew
back then.
- Wow. That's cool, mum.
- Um, is it?
[both laughing]
- Shirley and I were talking
and while we realize our styles
are very different,
what we both like...
both:
Is a good mystery.
- So we put our heads together.
And after some
intellectual hair pulling,
we realized that if your mom
wasn't lying...
- And Tannhauser was still
somehow involved...
- There's only one sure place
somebody could hide
without anyone
knowing about it.
- A Tannhauser black ops site.
- There you go.
- I mean,
they've got dozens of them.
They were safe houses to test
dangerous pathogens for the CDC
but Mom hasn't taken
a government job in years.
They'd all be shut down.
- Yeah, that's why it's
the best place to hide.
- Okay, so how do we find them?
- Without Sally?
Uh, have you tried Google?
- Yes.
We just use their satellite.
- I don't think we can use
someone else's satellite.
- Or maybe we can.
When DeVoe took over Sally,
he also launched four
of his own satellites to bring
about the enlightenment,
but now that he's gone
maybe we can work around the...
Multiplexed
burst-model channels
and the inter-SV handoff.
- We've got eyes and ears.
We've got eyes and ears!
- I knew you could do it.
- Ah!
- Oh, sorry.
- That was dumb.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I introduce you to...
HAL, Robbie, Data,
and Colossus.
- I don't really like
those names.
But nonetheless,
those can help us
in tracking the shards
from the satellite?
- These babies can help with
anything and everything.
- Well, once we figure out
which one hit Cicada,
we can figure out
how he got his abilities,
maybe find some
kind of a weakness.
- So, what we are waiting for?
- Caitlin?
Do you know what this means?
We can locate your father.
- Wait, wait.
I, uh...
- Isn't this what you wanted?
- It is, I just...
- Okay.
When you're ready.
- Thanks.
- Greg, move your head.