I now pronounce you
husband and wife... again.
[clapping]
You know, even though future you
told us about your vow renewals,
like, a million times,
I still got pretty weepy.
Me, too.
I mean, the love in this room
when you two kissed...
We have such an amazing future
ahead of us.
Yeah, if we didn't change it.
I checked with Gideon, no changes
to the timeline, everything's fine.
Well, on that note, we should be
getting back to 2049 sooner or later.
Yeah.
Keep the future safe.
You're both gonna make great heroes.
- I already am.
- Yes.
I will make you proud, Dad.
I know.
Love you both.
Okay, everything seems the same.
It was so good to see Uncle Jay
and Aunt Joan again.
Is it weird that seeing Uncle Jay alive
just made me miss him more?
[loud whooshing]
What was that?
[stutters] I have no idea.
[door opens, closes]
Okay, kids,
I come bearing cheeseburgers.
Who's hungry?
Uncle Jay!
You were expecting someone else?
[chuckles]
Bart,
- are you okay, son?
- No!
Oh, okay.
We just...
We just missed you so much.
[Jay] Aw.
[Bart] He's alive.
Uncle Jay is alive!
[chuckles] Our Uncle Jay,
he's really... Did we do this?
We did, didn't we?
[laughs] Oh! This is so crash.
Cra... No!
No, not crash, the opposite of crash.
Look, that was a temporal wave
that washed over us, okay?
That means that when we went back to
help Mom and Dad stop the Godspeed war,
we changed the future.
[Godspeeds]
Kill The Adversary and his allies.
Yeah, but in a good way.
Well, yeah, totally. But we have to
figure out why the change has happened.
So...
Are, um, Mom and Pops gonna be
swinging by anytime soon?
Aren't they in Milan for
their anniversary at La Verità Rustica?
- Right!
- Yes.
Yes, the anniversary
of their wedding vow renewal.
Mm-hmm. Um...
But the rest of Team Flash
could pop by, right?
[Jay] Well, they're all kind of busy,
which you already know.
Now, why the third degree?
Oh...
- Oh, nothing, we're fine.
- Yeah, no, we... yeah.
Bart's fine, I'm fine.
Fine, fine, fine.
Well, thanks to your brother.
When that psychopath Godspeed
came for me a few months ago,
I thought my race
might be finally finished.
But then, Impulse saved the day,
prevented Godspeed
from destroying our total reality,
just like your dad always does.
That's how I know you'll make
a great Flash one day, Bart.
Oh, Aunt Rose!
Sends her love,
her botany club's running late again.
Who's Aunt Rose?
Rose.
My wife?
[chuckles]
What is up with you two tonight?
So, that's how we did this?
Yeah, when we chased Godspeed
through time using the cosmic treadmill,
only it wasn't built to handle
the energy of three speedsters at once.
Our tachyon energies must have
caused massive temporal fissures.
Oh!
This is why Dad has time travel rules.
According to this, Uncle Jay
never married Aunt Joan.
- [gauntlet beeping]
- [gasps]
Oh, my God! We erased her.
We erased her.
My gauntlet just confirmed it.
Is that one of those fissures
that we caused?
I'm sorry, how far back does it go?
How many are there? Can we fix them?
[whispers] Keep your voice down.
[exhales deeply]
Okay, we work backwards, identifying
everything new to the timeline,
figure out where things
first started changing,
and put them back
where they're supposed to be.
Okay.
Corrupt Mayor Bellows Jr,
farther back, Trickster invades Tibet,
farther back...
- Who's Booster Gold?
- [Bart] Keep going.
"Zoom attacks C.C.P.D,
Chief of Police Joe West."
Grandpa Joe wasn't Chief then, right?
But he is in this new timeline.
When did he get promoted?
There are no time fissures before that.
This is where the change happened,
and it altered everything
that follows, like dominos.
Okay, "Detective Joe West heroically
took a bullet during a jewelry theft,
the afternoon of December 31st, 2013."
And Dad couldn't help him
because he was still in a coma.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
If we save Grandpa Joe from getting
shot, things will return to normal,
and we get Aunt Joan back.
New Year's Eve, 2013,
here we come.
[both exhale]
What the hell are you wearing?
Something sexy.
[Bart chuckles]
It's smart, I'm incognito.
Dude, it's 2013, not 1913.
Look, there's Grandpa Joe.
I... I haven't done this in a long time.
What am I supposed to say?
Breathe, Detective. You got this.
Hey!
Counselor Horton, how are you?
I am crappy, Detective West,
so if you don't mind, I'm just gonna...
Yeah. Sorry,
we are celebrating New Year's here...
Oh, God, okay,
I'm gonna stop you right there.
Two things. One,
I have a ton of paperwork
back on my desk at the DA's office
and two, this one's important,
pay attention.
All men... are jerks.
No offense.
None taken.
Great! Happy New Year.
Damn.
Sorry, Detective.
Then again, her divorce
just finalized last week.
That wasn't worth mentioning?
I was gonna, but it just seems like
you two would make such a great pair.
Is today the day that Grandpa Joe
and Grammy Cecile start dating?
No.
I mean, I don't think that it is.
Okay, good, because stopping
Grandpa Joe from getting shot,
it's enough fixing for one day.
Okay.
Remember what we learned in 2049.
We have to stop what happens today,
and we cannot interact with anyone
who is connected to our family
while we are doing it.
Relax, no one's going to find out
who we are or why we're here.
Who are you two...
and why are you here?
Well...
how about it?
[Nora] Yes, of course.
Here you go, Detective.
Nora Moy and Bart Wade.
We're intern CSI's.
We are here to help out
because we heard that
one of your CSI's is...
- Under the weather.
- ...under the weather.
That's it, just crime fighters.
Couple of crime fighters, with science.
Sorry, it's been tense here
since the accident at S.T.A.R. Labs.
My new partner barely speaks to me.
Get him a cup of coffee.
I find the Java
really brings people together.
Yeah.
That is a great idea.
I want to buy the entire bullpen
coffee from the cart outside.
Take their orders. It's on me.
Maybe this will help break the ice.
Detective, we have so much science
to get done today,
so I don't know
if we're going to be able to...
- It's a lot.
- We do
have science,
but we are more than happy to help out,
and we will be back
in a flash, Detective.
Can you leave Detective West's
and mine on our desks while we're out?
Thanks a lot, guys.
That's the guy! That's the guy!
That's the guy that sacrificed himself
to stop Eobard Thawne, Mom's old fiancé.
- Yes, it is.
- Ow.
And now we are his coffee gophers,
when we're supposed to be
looking out for Grandpa Joe.
I'll take a hazelnut mocha latte.
This is ridiculous! Can I not just use
my superspeed instead, please?
What part of "don't change the timeline"
do you not understand?
Bart, unless we are absolutely
100% certain
that it won't make things worse,
we can't use our speed.
But... [groans]
Come on, Bart, I need you
to focus on the plan.
I have my gauntlet set to alert us
as soon as the jewelry robbery
goes down, okay?
That is where Grandpa Joe will be.
Right, and then we swoop in
and we save the day, that's fantastic.
But you do realize that every second
that we're standing here,
Grandpa Joe could be getting shot,
like now, or now, or right now you see...
Holy crap, stop!
No, because Grandpa Joe's safety
is on the line, and I need a coffee now!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- I just didn't see you.
- That's called inattentional blindness.
It's a phenomenon when an individual...
- Hi.
I'm Bart.
And you're?
You're studying temporal dynam...
How do you know
so much about quantum divergence?
Well, now, that's a surprise.
Tell you what, can you keep a secret?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
- I'm from the future!
- No way, me, too! What year?
No dude, I'm totally messing with you.
Time travel is impossible.
[laughs] Yeah...
but it is possible though,
mathematically,
if I'm reading
the title of your thesis correctly.
Yeah, I'm trying to prove
that Tolman's paradox
can give rise to quantum superposition,
and that tachyon exchanges between
two particles can generate superposition
and entangle molecular pairs.
Of course, it's the causal paradox
- I'm still trying to solve.
- [gauntlet chimes]
Oh, my God, you're like
the Elon Musk of your generation.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure Elon Musk
is my generation's Elon Musk.
- Well, I mean...
- I'm Avery.
And I'm Nora, his sister, and we should
really go. We have that thing.
Yeah, right. Yeah, we have that...
Avery, your research
is bleeding edge impressive.
Can you tell that to my boss
at Fast Track Labs?
Just once, I'd like to help run research
instead of running for coffee.
But, that's the intern life.
- You know what, I'm an intern, too!
- No way!
- Yeah, we just got coffees...
- Yeah, actually, you know what,
we both are, we both are interns,
and we should really go now.
That call we were waiting for?
- Yes.
- It just came in.
Oh, that one.
Um...
Yeah, it was really crash meeting you.
Is that a good thing?
If it's a good thing and you want to run
into me again, I make a coffee run
every afternoon.
That's good to know. Nice to meet you.
- This is you...
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Bye. Bye.
Bye. [clears throat]
- [alarm blaring]
- [siren wailing]
You watch the back entrance,
I'll watch the front.
Backup's en route.
- [Joe] Drop your weapon!
- [exclaims] Freeze!
Hey! This is a real gun.
Real bullets inside!
Kid, have you ever even
held a gun before?
Yes. This isn't my first heist.
Listen, most thieves don't wear
what they just stole.
Yeah, I forgot a bag, all right?
Hey, listen, I am only taking
the ethically sourced
conflict-free diamonds.
No blood diamonds for me. No, sir.
Listen, lower your weapon
before you have an accident.
Why don't you lower your weapon?
Stop!
If Grandpa Joe
was never supposed to be here,
then the gun was never
supposed to fire at all.
We can't cause another temporal flux.
Okay, you're just now mentioning that.
Well, I tried to
when we were in the coffee line,
but someone was too busy flirting.
- What do we do?
- Okay, um...
We need to examine our variables,
and we need to form a plan.
- First we need to consider...
- Oh, my God, I've got this!
[exclaims]
I am so sorry.
Those things are way heavier
than they look in the movies.
Turn around, hands behind your back.
- That was an accident.
- Hands behind your back!
I heard a shot.
- Are you...
- I'm fine, Detective.
- [siren wailing]
- You must have a guardian angel.
[groans] You shouldn't have done that.
So I moved Grandpa Joe
instead of the bullet.
- What's the big deal?
- This.
Look, now, more temporal particles
are in flux.
Bart, you made everything worse.
[sighs in exasperation]
[Bart] I don't even get it. [echoes]
He wasn't even a meta-human with powers.
[echoes]
[Nora] Well, now more metas are gonna be
turning up everywhere
now that the particle accelerator
exploded... [echoes]
Meta-human?
Then I'm not alone.
Bart, the whole timeline's in flux.
You might have changed the future
even more now.
[stutters] What did I do?
I saved Grandpa.
By moving Grandpa Joe
instead of moving the bullet,
you created a new series of events
changing the timeline.
It's what I would have warned you about
if you hadn't rushed in.
Okay, okay. Why don't we just go back
in time 15 minutes
and see for ourselves what we did wrong?
Oh, okay. So you want to
fix our time travel screw ups
by traveling back in time.
Again.
Well, when you say it like that...
Actually, there is a way
to observe the past without altering it.
I bet you that's the flash drive
with the surveillance footage
from the shooting.
- All we have to do is watch it...
- And see what went wrong.
Okay, follow my lead.
Don't go rogue.
Excuse me, Detective Thawne.
Is that the surveillance footage
of the incident?
The interns. Yes, it is. Why?
Hi, by the way.
We just figured you're doing
so much detecting around here
that we could just take this
back to the to the police station.
- And then we'll just give it back to...
- No, thanks.
You two should make another coffee run.
We already did that.
Did you?
Then why am I not holding
a decaf cappuccino?
Let us do this work
and you two do yours.
- Right away, Detective.
- Yeah, right away.
- We got to get that footage.
[Wanda] Let me get this straight.
Nobody knows
why the three of us are here.
Feels like we've been set up.
So, a woman's voice is in our heads.
Telling us all there's a job tonight.
Now, if you two jokers didn't promise
a score... who did?
[Mona laughs]
Me, big fella.
Pool table.
Utopia Casino's ringing in the New Year
with the biggest fête in town.
More guests means more bets
means more cash they'll need to cover.
They'll have ten mil in the vault, easy.
Not the worst plan.
But the party starts in six hours.
There's no prep time.
What if the cops show?
[Mona]
I'll know they're coming before they do.
'Cause ever since
that Particle Accelerator exploded,
I can hear people's thoughts.
Now, I thought I was the only one
with gifts.
Until I learned a new word.
Meta-human.
[chuckles]
It means we're all something more now.
Something greater.
And I am done living in fear.
Now, who's game?
I'm sick of hiding who I am.
So am I.
Watch it, Jack.
[laughs] See? Doesn't that feel better?
And with our powers, no one can stop us.
And if they try, I'll know what they're
planning before they even think it.
So you're the ace up our sleeve.
No. She's a queen.
[Bart] How are we gonna get that
flash drive without Grandpa noticing?
Watch, okay?
And learn.
Okay. I get it.
I'm the new guy.
You're busy.
And I heard you just lost your partner,
which has got to be tough.
Plus, one of our CSI's in a coma.
Then on top of all that,
you get shot down by Counselor Horton.
Who told you that?
Uh...
Everyone?
[Nora]
You could try lilacs and crumb cake.
Those are her favorites.
[Joe] That's good advice.
- Who was that?
- One of our new interns.
They're a little weird.
[Nora] Okay.
Now we can see where we messed up.
This is where it happened.
Where Dad was struck by lightning.
[thunder crashes]
[Nora] I got it.
Ooh! Super speedy save.
But hang on, I know her.
Oh, my God. That's Mona Taylor...
aka The Queen. As in the telepathic
leader of the Royal Flush Gang.
What is she doing here?
[Nora] Since when is there
a casino heist tonight?
The RFG didn't team up
until way after Dad put the suit on.
After Mona discovered
that there are other metas.
How could she possibly even know that
this soon?
Oh, Bart, she got the idea
to form the RFG years early from us.
And now 30 people
are going to die from a bomb.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to stop that heist.
Do you think I don't know that?
But if we start screwing with it again,
we could screw things up even worse.
What are we supposed to do then?
I don't know.
But we'll figure it out
just like we always do.
Dad would have gotten it right
the first time.
- Bart, don't go there.
- Why not?
- It's true.
- Listen to me.
Whatever happened,
it's both of our faults.
- We are in this together.
- Well, maybe we shouldn't be.
Every single thing I did today...
made everything worse.
I am not good enough.
And I will never be The Flash.
[thunder rumbling]
[whooshes]
[sighs]
[EKG beeping steadily]
Spoiler alert, Pops.
Your son's a big screw up.
- I knew you'd be here.
- I let him down, sis.
- Bart, listen to me. Nobody is perfect.
- You are.
- That is not true.
- Yes, it is.
You knew when to come back here.
You got the flash drive.
You even helped Grandpa Joe
and Grammie Cecile. You...
Yeah, you're perfect.
I'm a complete failure.
No.
No, you're not. I failed a lot, too.
For a long time, I fumbled
with my powers. I doubted myself.
But that's how we learn.
And yeah, every time I fell...
Dad picked me up.
Just like every time you fall,
I am going to pick you up, too.
Just remember what Dad always says.
"No matter how fast you run,
life is about the journey."
Bart, we are going to make this right.
It just takes time
to think things through.
[sniffles]
Thank you for the pep talk, sis.
And now I'm thinking,
to get out of this...
we're gonna need an expert
in time travel.
And I know just where to go.
[reporter] The rain
has not discouraged anyone
from partying in the New Year.
After the bizarre events of 2013...
[whooshes]
How did you get in here?
This place has a $12 million
security system and armed guards.
Hi, again.
Sorry to barge in on you like this.
We actually need your help.
It's regarding your theory
on temporal development.
Holy crap!
That, that, that whole getting coffee
while bumping into me in line,
that wasn't an accident.
It's classic espionage trick.
You were following me.
Ha ha!
And now you want to take me hostage
and steal all of Fast Track Lab's
corporate secrets. Well, do your worst,
'cause I'm not talking.
No. Avery, we're not going to hurt you.
We need your help to stop a crime.
Right. Why should I believe you?
Because we're time travelers
from the future
and we need you to show us
how your temporal theory
can help save people at a casino robbery
without actually changing the timeline.
Wow, that felt so good.
- I'm calling security.
- No, wait! We can prove it.
I could show you something
about your past or your future.
[Bart] But if you show her something
from the future,
she's going to have to wait until
it happens to actually prove anything.
Is that gauntlet using
integrated quantum circuitry?
- Yes.
- Last I checked, yeah.
Liquid processing unit.
AI nano cells.
This is decades away.
You guys are from the future.
We are. Which is why we need your help.
Ever since we arrived,
we've caused serious temporal shifts.
And now...
Thirty people are going to die.
It might be worse than you think.
The death toll keeps changing,
but the headline doesn't.
Because now it's solidified
into a fixed point in time...
Excuse me. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
...and that means that the heist
and the deaths aren't causally entangled
like the tachyon particle exchange
in my theory.
Which is looking more like fact.
It's too late to stop the casino heist.
But since the casualties keep changing,
they're not fixed in time.
So you can fix the timeline
and save all those people.
As long as you let
the heist still happen.
Wow.
- Okay. Thanks, Avery.
- Hold on.
I'm coming with you.
Avery, we can't risk you getting hurt.
But we will come back.
I promise you.
Ladies and gents!
[honking]
I say it's high time we rang in
the New Year...
[Mona speaks telepathically]
...with a bang.
Well, here's the drill, folks.
If you run, call for help or annoy us,
my... ooh, king...
will pop your skulls
with his bare hands.
So, please don't make him kill you.
Find the casino vault.
- Empty it.
- Done and doner.
And if we run into trouble?
Show them a winning hand.
Okay. Remember, you need to get
everyone to safety while I find the bomb
- and make sure...
- Let the heist happen.
Yeah.
Stay calm, Bart. You got this.
We got this.
Four minutes to midnight.
My queen, a couple was sitting
right there being quiet,
so I turned my back on them
for a minute.
Now they're missing.
Someone is inside here with us.
[Mona speaks telepathically]
Whoever you are, show yourself.
Or my king starts popping heads.
[woman whimpering]
[Nora] Bart, I can't find the bomb.
The Queen is going to start
killing people
unless I do something right now.
What? No, no.
You have to get everyone to safety.
No, time for plan B.
Just get the bomb before midnight.
There is no plan B.
Bart!
[Mona speaks telepathically]
Last chance.
[woman screams]
Wait! Wait!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait. Okay.
Let's all just... Let's just relax.
Okay? No need to lose our heads.
I am the casino manager, obviously.
Isaac is my name and you caught me.
I am the one that was helping
the customers escape.
But I am not doing that anymore.
I'm not going to do that anymore.
Um...
However, since dead people
aren't great for business,
how about I just look away?
You guys just take the money and leave.
Too late.
Tell me, what kind of casino manager
risks his neck on minimum wage?
One who's a really great employee.
Oh. Or you're a cop. Hmm?
Let's see what's inside
that beautiful mind of yours.
[Bart] No, no, no, no.
We've gotta fix this timeline,
to get back to this timeline... Future.
Wait. You're from the future?
[Bart thinking] She's so cute.
Please let her not have a boyfriend.
Avery, you're my future. My future.
Oh! [laughs]
That future.
Yeah, well... Love is grand.
Fine. Sit down.
Success, Mona. I mean, my queen.
Ten million dollars' worth, too.
Well, then we're done here.
Wait!
My king, my dear, drop the cop.
Drop the... Hey, wait!
- [groans softly]
- [Mona] Oh.
If you want to survive, don't follow us.
Just sit down. Stay put.
Enjoy the fireworks. All of them.
[Mona laughs] All of them.
[groans]
Sis, the RFG's MIA.
What's up with the bomb search?
[grunts]
It's almost midnight.
[timer ticking]
Bart, I found the bomb.
It's counting down to midnight.
But one thermal charge
couldn't level this whole building.
Before she left, the queen said,
"Enjoy the fireworks, all of them."
- [winces]
- Schrap.
There's more than one bomb.
We only have, like, 30 seconds.
Well, King knocked the hell out of me
and broke my arm.
I'm gonna need three minutes
to speed heal.
I can't get everyone out in time.
But we don't even have one minute.
It's okay, sis, you've got this.
You can find the rest of them.
But it took me forever to find this one.
Sis, you got this.
Think, think, think, think.
[gasps]
The heat signatures in the water tanks.
They must be masking
the bomb's thermal signature.
There it is. Intels are your thing,
sis, get excessive.
[whooshing]
Sis, it's almost midnight.
I know. I got them.
There were five.
You've got 15 seconds
to get rid of them.
- Where?
- [Bart] Anywhere.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four...
three, two, one.
[Bart] Greatjob, sis. You did it.
[Nora] We both did it.
[fireworks whistling]
Every witness to the casino robbery
says someone streaked them outside.
What do you think?
Too much champagne?
It beats the hell out of me.
But it looks like we're here
for a long night.
Well, a few Jitters goodies might help.
- Oh! Thank you, baby girl.
- Yeah.
Here's to 2014 not being so weird.
Not being so weird.
Hey, uh, you saved my dissertation,
right? Detective Pretty Boy?
[chuckles]
Sorry.
That's just what my dad calls you.
Although, I mean, he's not wrong.
You are a boy and you are pretty.
And, uh, that did not come out right.
I'll take any compliment I can get
from Joe West.
Or his lovely daughter.
Yeah. Um...
Well, do you have a name, Detective?
It's Eddie.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Counselor Horton, you don't have
anywhere more fun to be tonight?
Uh, yeah. I had to get an evidentiary
disclosure over to Judge Hankerson.
Um, so, look, about this morning,
I'm so sorry if I came off
a little harsh.
See, it turns out that being a lawyer
does not make getting divorced
any easier.
It's okay.
I know that splitting up
can be hard. Trust me.
Yeah. So when we bumped
into each other this morning,
I know that you were about to
ask me something.
But I'm not ready.
And I'm not going to be,
not for a while.
Of course, I understand.
Yup.
However, when I am ready,
whoever sent lilacs
to my office tonight,
ooh...
he'll be the first one to know.
Okay, so we stopped the shooting.
We fixed the timeline, and we fixed the
mistakes we made fixing the timeline.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Time to head back home.
Interns, you getting in on this?
[woman] All right, everybody, line up.
Tall guys in the back.
[woman] Joe, you get in the front.
Happy New Year.
[Nora] Nope. Mm-mmm.
[timer beeping]
Okay, just one photo.
[woman] Okay, smile everyone.
[timer continues beeping]
[camera flash clicks]
[fireworks exploding]
- I'm really glad you came back.
- Me, too.
Seriously. You haven't
just changed my research.
You changed my life.
Well, I always keep my promises.
I had to. You...
You helped save the day with
all your science bad-assery. I mean...
Which is why I...
Look, Avery,
before I go back to my time,
I know we just met,
but it's New Year's Eve, right?
And I just think that...
Bart!
Bart, It's been two minutes.
Come on. We really have to go.
See you again sometime, McFly?
I promise.
All right.
Here we go.
Wait. So I was dead? Killed by Godspeed?
Uncle Jay. I'm so sorry
for screwing up the timeline.
And if that means
I can't ever be The Flash...
I understand.
[laughs]
I'm sorry. Are you kidding me?
If screwing up the timeline
was a deal breaker,
your dad couldn't be The Flash.
Heck, when I first started
to time travel,
I ended up fighting Nazis
in World War Il.
And then lived on and off
in the past for 16 years.
But that was another lifetime.
So, you're not mad?
I'm alive.
Right? My Joan is back.
Why would I be mad?
Bart, you're on a journey.
Both of you.
You're going to make mistakes,
and sometimes, they can't be undone.
But you can always try
to make things better.
Right?
And that's what you did today.
Now, I got to get out of here.
I've got an important meeting
with President Luthor.
- President Luthor?
Gotcha.
Oh! [laughs in relief]
[Joe] Iris!
Come on!
This brunch reservation
ain't gonna get any later.
Joe, don't worry.
I'll make sure we're on time.
After surviving Armageddon,
we all deserve this.
Hey, you guys got
any resolutions for 2022?
I decided to forgive Mark
for all of his crime things.
What? He's turned over a new leaf
and I made him swear
to stay on the straight and narrow.
Anybody know anything
about Caity's new boyfriend?
Marcus? Anybody met him?
- No.
- No, I hear he's really cute, though.
I have a resolution, actually,
party less.
I know mine.
More family time.
That sounds like a perfect year.
All right, people, let's hurry it up.
Look at the face. Joe's getting hangry.
Okay, everybody, hold hands.
Bundle up.
- It's chilly in Paris.
- [squeals excitedly]