My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
...but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on the Flash:
- Iris West.
- Eddie?
- The Man in the Yellow, he took Eddie.
- I promise I will find him, okay?
Barf)'-
Think about your best friend.
It could be your wife, your father,
maybe someone you grew up with.
It's the person you can't wait to talk to
at the end of the day.
The person who knows everything about you,
who roots for you.
Now imagine you discover
your best friend has a secret.
No, not a secret. A universe of secrets.
Would you confront him?
Would you stay silent?
Either way, you know nothing
will ever be the same again.
Where is Thawne?
He took some personal time.
Yeah, uh, Eddie's been
going through some stuff, captain.
Yeah, aren't we all?
Got anything on these gold-store robberies?
Perps hit two more in the last week
and we got nothing.
- We're working on it.
- Waiting on results from the lab.
Pick up the pace.
And see if somebody can contact the Flash,
maybe he can help speed things up.
You know what I mean. Get going.
- Anything?
- No. I mean, I've looked everywhere.
Keep looking.
Of course, yeah.
H9)'-
- Uh, I'm heading out right now. What's up?
- Something happened.
And I'm not supposed to say anything,
but I couldn't keep quiet.
What happened?
The Man in Yellow,
he took Eddie right in front of me.
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay? Wha...?
- No. No, not at all.
- No, l...
- The Flash was there.
He told me to go home and not to talk to
anyone because he would fix it, but he hasn't.
I think the police should be out
searching for Eddie.
- No, Iris, I...
- My dad needs to know the truth.
Uh...
I think that...
...the Flash is right.
Joe and the cops, they're no match
for the Man in Yellow, Iris.
They would just get hurt.
So you think the Flash is out there,
right now, searching for Eddie?
I'm sure he's doing everything he can
to find him.
Yeah, well, I'm finding it pretty hard
to trust the Flash right now.
Well then, trust me. Okay?
Look, I'm so sorry about all of this. I...
Everything is gonna be okay.
I have to go.
Okay, back it up.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Get down!
H9)'-
You planning on keeping all those cameras
Wells used to spy on us?
Kind of creepy, don't you think?
First rule of mechanical engineering, dude.
Never waste good tech.
- Central City Gold Reserve's under attack.
- Gold?
That's the case Singh wants us on.
I'll be right back.
You picked a bad day for this, pal.
What was that?
Your eye movement is normal.
No signs of neurological damage.
Think the thief might have been
a metahuman...
...who put the whammy on you or something?
I don't know.
When Rainbow Raider got in my head...
...all I felt was anger.
But this was not that. This was...
...just overwhelming fear.
Huh.
Looks like when you went down,
the thief got disoriented too.
Maybe we both got whammied.
Then you know how it feels.
Hi, Barry.
Or should I say the Flash?
This is one of the few times
I would not wanna be Barry Allen.
I wonder what he's gonna say.
- We should absolutely not listen in.
- It's none of our business.
- But the Flash is our business.
- And Iris did just find out Barry's the Flash.
So by transitive property,
Barry and Iris are our business.
How did you find out?
When I touched...
...the Flash...
...the other night, I felt
a jolt of electricity.
The only other time I've felt anything
like that was when you were in a coma...
...after the accident.
Heh. I can't believe
I didn't figure it out sooner.
I can only imagine how angry you are.
I'm not angry, Barry.
I'm just disappointed.
Okay.
Does Eddie know?
Yes, he does.
Is that why he got kidnapped?
No, I don't know why Wells took Eddie. I...
Dr. Wells is the Man in Yellow?
Everything he's been doing...
...helping me...
...it was all a lie.
Wells killed my mom.
- Is he gonna kill Eddie?
- No, he's not. I'm gonna get Eddie back.
- I swear.
- The Flash said the same thing.
Look, Iris, you have to believe me. There
were so many times I wanted to tell you.
You were the first person I wanted to tell.
But then everything started getting crazy.
And I thought maybe Joe was right...
Wait, wait, wait.
You're telling me that my dad knew...
...and he told you not to tell me?
He was trying to protect you.
We both were.
Yeah, well,
maybe it's time you both stopped.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Yeah, if we could get another shipment...
...of the computers in here.
- I don't think that had anything to do with us.
- Nope.
I don't suppose you brought lunch.
Did you know that human beings...
...can survive up to two months...
...without food?
Is that how long you're planning
on keeping me here?
You know...
...I doubt it'll come to that.
You wanna tell me
what we're doing down here?
No.
You told me we're related,
that you're from the future.
- Prove it.
- Yeah, I don't have to prove anything...
...to anyone.
Well, I think you're full of crap.
And whatever you're trying to do...
...you're not gonna get away with it
because the Flash is...
Stop talking.
I heard you talked to Barry.
So this is what
my cold-shoulder treatment feels like.
Look.
Baby, the way I went about things, maybe...
No, I was wrong.
I was just trying to keep you safe.
You know, that excuse
is getting really old.
First, it was the police academy,
and then it was dating Eddie, and now this.
Sweetheart, you know
what the Man in Yellow is capable of.
He killed cops. He killed Mason Bridge.
Wells killed Mason?
- And you're covering that up?
- No.
No. No, no, no.
If the world finds out about Wells, they find
out about Barry. I'm trying to keep him safe.
Did you ever stop to think
that looping me in would keep me safe?
That if I knew what was going on out there,
I could prepare for it?
Maybe I could've helped you and Barry put the
bad guys away instead of being in the way.
I asked myself that question every day.
- Every time you post something on your blog.
- It's not just about Barry being the Flash.
You knew how he felt about me for God knows
how long, and you didn't tell me that either.
That wasn't for me to tell, Iris.
You know what? If any of you had been honest
with me, maybe Eddie would still be here.
He wouldn't have gotten involved in this
if I hadn't been dating him.
Are you saying
if you had known how Barry felt...?
What I am saying is that
what happened to Eddie is your fault.
This is work.
We can finish this talk.
Talking.
Yeah, that'll be new.
Yeah, boss.
I just got a call from Joe.
The Central City Gold Reserve is about
to transport $300 million in gold bars...
...to their Coast City vault.
Singh told Joe they think the Man in
the Mask is gonna make a play for it.
Okay, but we still don't know if he's
responsible for those weird images you saw.
How are they transporting the gold?
Sorry, no more ice cream.
But your music's playing.
Yeah, it means we're out.
Come on.
You might wanna kill the music.
We don't want any kids around
if our thief shows up.
Whoa, the truck just got hit by a landmine.
- Is Joe okay?
- We don't know yet.
Freeze! Drop your weapon!
Don't make me do this.
You Okay?
Yeah. You?
I didn't want you to have to shoot him
again. And I'm having a pretty bad day.
So is this guy.
Let's see what Goldfinger has
to say for himself.
General Eiling?
What is wrong with him?
- I pulled a bullet out of his shoulder...
- Which should hurt like hell.
And it didn't even seem like he felt it.
I did a complete body scan, and otherwise,
General Eiling is perfectly healthy.
So why is he just standing there
like a robot?
I just got off the phone with A.R.G.U.S.
- Officially, Eiling is on administrative leave.
- Unofficially...?
I spoke with Diggle's wife, Lyla,
and she said Eiling's been missing...
...for the past three months,
and A.R.G.U.S. is covering up for it.
Makes sense. Last time I saw the general was
when Ronnie and I broke Professor Stein...
...out of that military facility.
I'm sure they're covering that up too.
So where has he been since then?
General Eiling, why were you trying
to rob the gold reserve?
Maybe he's in some kind of a trance?
General?
Do you remember me?
Flash.
Ooh. How does he know you're the Flash?
I don't know.
- General...
- Eiling not here.
Eiling...
...bad.
Maybe it's some kind of psychotic break...
...presenting itself
as dissociative identity disorder?
Caitlin.
Caitlin...
...good.
Oh, uh, thank you?
Mm. Forget multiple personalities.
You guys have seen The Exorcist, right?
You and your movies.
Keep talking to him.
He seems to respond to you.
Uh, Why is Eiling bad?
Eiling...
...hurt me.
I hurt...
...Eiling.
Okay.
Uh, so if you're not Eiling,
then who are you?
I...
...am...
...Grodd.
Fear me.
What is a Grodd?
Oh. Grodd is a gorilla.
Five years ago, Eiling and Wells
were working on a project...
...to expand soldiers' cognitive abilities
during battle.
We didn't realize that Eiling was trying
to create soldiers with psychic abilities.
What do you mean, psychic?
Eiling was trying to create these super-soldiers
with telepathic and telekinetic capabilities.
When Wells found out about the terrible
experiments Eiling was doing...
...he shut down the project.
So our psycho-killer has a soft spot
for animals. That's sweet.
What happened to...
...Grodd?
We don't know.
After the particle accelerator exploded,
I went down to check on him...
...and his cage was empty.
So he could've been affected
by the same energy that hit Barry.
When the dark matter hit Grodd...
...all the drugs and serums that Eiling
injected him with could've activated.
Maybe the accelerator explosion
created a meta-gorilla.
I think we know what happens
when a super-intelligent ape...
...who's pissed off at humans
escapes captivity.
Cisc0's right. About the first part.
This is the first brain scan
that I did on Grodd.
Whoa. His primary motor cortex and Broca's
area are lit up like a Christmas tree.
From Eiling's experiments.
And this is the brain scan
that I just did on Eiling.
His brain is lit up in the exact same way.
So Grodd and Eiling
are connected somehow.
I think that somehow Grodd is transmitting
neural signals to Eiling's primary motor cortex.
Mind control. Telepathy.
Who knows what Grodd is capable of now?
What do we think Grodd wants? Revenge?
I do not like the fact
that Wells rescued Grodd.
I don't think it's a coincidence
that this gorilla shows up...
...at the same time we're looking for Wells.
Grodd and Wells did have a special bond.
It wouldn't surprise me
if Wells was using Grodd to distract us.
If we find Grodd, we find Wells.
- If we find Wells...
- We find Eddie.
And I'm gonna help.
Know anything about gorillas?
I just might.
There have been reports
of some sort of animal down in the sewers.
Mm. Alligators...
...C.H.U.D.'S...
...R.O.U.S.'s.
Am I the only one
who watches movies around here?
Uh, a few months ago,
two sewer workers went missing.
The search party reported hearing strange,
animal-like noises down in the tunnels.
Where exactly did they go missing?
- Uh, Fifth Avenue and 10th Street.
- There's an access point to the sewers...
...about two blocks east of that intersection.
- I'll start there.
Not alone. I'm coming too.
Huh. Wading through miles of rats, roaches,
and human excrement? Count me out.
Count me in.
It's your monkey.
Cisco, take the rest of these flares, light
them, drop them as we go. It's our path back.
Give me that banana.
Okay.
- Stay close.
- Definitely.
I'm not going anywhere.
Thanks for sticking up for me.
Of course.
For what it's worth, Barry feels
really terrible about lying to you.
He should.
You lied too.
Your fiancé.
Ronnie. Yes.
Uh, I thought he died
in the particle-accelerator explosion...
...but it turns out he just caught on fire.
Oh.
But he's okay?
Yeah, he is.
Good, I'm glad.
I can't believe
I'm looking for a supernatural gorilla.
I'm terrified of regular gorillas.
What was that?
Oh. Oh.
Whoa.
Hey, hey, guys. Look at this.
Incredible.
Looks like we're in the right place.
Somebody wanna tell me
what we're looking at here?
Grodd. He's evolving.
He's getting smarter.
Getting smarter. Great.
If I hadn't seen Jurassic Park, I wouldn't
be nearly as frightened right now.
So if he's getting smarter,
you think he might be getting bigger too?
That must have been
a truck passing over, right?
Cisco?
Barf)'-
- We gotta get out of here.
- Barry's out cold.
Joe.
Dad.
What...? What are you doing to me?
Help!
Cisco, help me!
No help here.
I can... I can hear you in my head.
You are telepathic.
Please.
Please. No, no, no.
Father hate gun.
Father. Father. You mean... You mean Wells.
Wells? Is that what you mean?
Where is he?
$5235;;.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Here. Is this what you want?
You can have it. It's yours. Take it.
Grodd hate banana.
Please, please.
You're experiencing a spike of activity
in your primary motor cortex.
It's the same thing we saw in Eiling.
The images you saw
were some kind of psychic attack by Grodd.
First, Eddie gets taken by the
Man in Yellow, and now my dad...
We're gonna save both of them.
I promise you.
I put a tracker in the tranq dart you shot
Grodd with. As soon as it activates...
I can't wait for that. I will search
every inch of that sewer if I have to.
What happens if you find them?
What happens if Grodd takes over your mind
the same way he did with Eiling?
Can you guys build me something?
Some kind of tech
so he can't get into my head?
I don't know.
Maybe if Doctor Wells were here.
I don't understand.
Every day you guys figure out
a way to help people.
All of the Flash's powers
and all this equipment...
...and you can't save Eddie and my dad?
We'll figure something out.
Fast.
- Iris.
- I can't get that sound out of my head.
My dad screaming.
Why did he insist
on going down there with you?
He's always preaching about being safe...
...but not once does he think about
running into danger himself.
- Iris...
- No, Barry. He's just a regular cop.
He's not some metahuman
with super powers.
He's not you.
You're right, he's not me.
And this isn't his fault.
None of this is his fault.
Look, yes, maybe Joe told me
not to tell you that I was the Flash...
...but I didn't have to listen.
I could've told you.
A hundred times I could've told you,
and I didn't.
Yes, I should've, so
you're right to be mad.
But don't be mad at your dad. Be mad at me.
Okay.
Okay, explain to me how the person
I thought I knew better than anyone...
...has been keeping secrets from me.
Big life-changing secrets.
You were supposed to be
my best friend, Barry.
- I am your best friend.
- How can you say that...
...when the most important things in
your life, things that matter most...
...things you're supposed to share,
you kept all of them from me?
You lied to me about everything.
I know, Iris. I know.
But you haven't been entirely honest
with me either.
What...? What are you talking about?
At Christmas, when I told you how I felt,
you said you didn't feel the same way.
But I just feel like, I don't know,
maybe things aren't that simple.
Am I wrong?
I'm gonna check on Cisco and Caitlin.
You know they're gonna find me.
And you, you're not as smart
as you think you are.
Oh, really?
Because I'm a genius where I come from.
Imagine how smart that makes me here.
- Because you're from the future?
- Mm.
With a name like "Eobard,"
I guess you'd have to be.
Oh, no. Eobard is a distinguished name
for a distinguished member...
...of a distinguished family.
Depressing to think all of my descendants
are as crazy as you.
No, no, no.
The Thawne bloodline is chockfull
of influential politicians...
...scientists, captains of industry.
Failures, such as yourself...
...are just the exception.
And what exactly makes me such a failure?
Tough question, Eddie. Where to start?
Oh, how about your career
as a police detective?
It's spectacularly uneventful.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
No, we have seen. I have seen.
I am from the future.
And you are the only Thawne...
...to be all but forgotten by history.
A waste of a life, a waste of a man and...
Oh, no.
You don't even get the girl.
What are you talking about?
Observe, if you will, the byline.
Barry marries Iris and not you.
We're just gonna have to give this ring...
...back to Grandma Agnes.
You, Eddie...
...won't be needing it.
An anti-telepathy strip.
It uses magnetic resonance to neutralize
any foreign neurological stimulus.
So it'll protect Barry
from being mind-controlled?
That's the hope. But we have no way
of knowing if it actually works.
It'll work.
The trackerjust came online.
We have Gr0dd's location.
Iris...
...I want you to know,
all the times I imagined you being here...
...it was not like this.
Get my dad back.
Barry, what's your ETA?
All right, I'm in position.
Wait for my signal.
- So the red, that's Barry?
- Yes.
And the blue?
ls Grodd.
Okay, here goes nothing.
- The steam's working. Grodd's on the move.
- I don't understand. What's the plan?
He's maneuvering Grodd into a tunnel
5.3 miles from Barry.
- So Barry can do what?
- Same thing he did to Girder.
Supersonic punch, baby.
Hit it.
The supersonic punch failed.
Here we go.
It's okay, Cisco. The headset's working.
Yes. Okay, uh,
try some speed punches on him.
- This isn't working.
- Okay, what if you try...?
Barf)'-
Barry.
- The headset's offline.
- Sounded like it impacted with something.
Human weak-
Barry's brain activity is off the charts.
Worse than last time.
- What's happening?
- Grodd's attacking psychically.
- He's paralyzed.
- Come on. There's a service train coming.
- Do something.
- I can't stop it.
You have to get out of there now.
What do we do?
Barry, listen to me, okay?
You have to concentrate on my voice.
Whatever is happening to you,
you have to fight it.
I know you can do this.
I know how strong you are.
Stand up to Grodd. You can do this.
Please.
Barry, do it for me.
Iris.
- Joe.
- Barry.
Please, get me out of here.
Barry.
I'm bringing him home.
Mr. Allen.
How nice of you to visit.
How long do you intend
to keep me prisoner?
Your brain scan's normal which means
Grodd is no longer controlling you.
This prison is for metahumans,
so you're free to go.
You will get what's coming to you
eventually.
I'm not ashamed of my actions, Mr. Allen.
You've seen what these metahumans
are capable of.
Soon your prison won't be enough.
Not all metahumans are dangerous.
You're afraid that I know you're the Flash?
Don't get your tights in a twist.
I've known for months.
If I wanted to come after you,
I'd have done it by now.
But you think you're gonna need me.
Harrison Wells turned
me over to that beast.
He used me like a damn puppet.
So like it or not, we have a common enemy,
you and I.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a gorilla to hunt.
I said be still.
You have three fractured ribs.
I'll be fine.
Dad, you need to rest.
I can't believe Grodd became so violent.
What was his lair like?
Did he eat the banana?
Does he like King Kong?
He's more of a Planet of the Apes ape?
Uh, terrifying. No. And I didn't ask.
Hmm.
You mind if I talk to my daughter alone?
When I was with that gorilla...
...I thought: "I'm gonna die down here."
And all I could think about was...
...how you and me were in a fight.
Dad, I was so afraid that
something would happen to you.
My life started when you were born.
And sometimes...
...my incredible love for you,
it blinds me, and I forget...
I forget what a brilliant
young woman you are.
How you're capable
of making your own decisions.
Daddy, I know that everything that you do
is out of love.
So love me enough
to always tell me the truth.
- Yeah?
- Deal. Deal.
Okay.
- Ow.
- Oh.
Oh, my bad.
Oh, my bad. Oh, my God.
Maybe it's a good thing
we didn't catch Grodd.
Where would we put him?
I mean, the pipeline isn't exactly equipped to
hold a super-intelligent, telepathic gorilla.
Joe mentioned that
Grodd called Wells, "Father."
Wells must've ordered Grodd
to come after us.
It's why Grodd didn't kill Joe.
I think Joe was right. Everything Grodd
did, it was just to distract us.
What's going on? You okay?
Just thinking about this headset.
It wasn't strong enough.
You could've been killed out there, man.
No, dude, your tech worked.
And it proved that we don't need Wells.
The three of us took on Grodd
and rescued Joe.
Together, we can do anything.
Actually, it was the four of us.
Hey.
H9)'-
How did you know I was here?
This is your spot.
Yeah, it's a special spot.
It's where I first met the Flash.
All those times, you were standing
right in front of me and I had no idea.
I don't even know you anymore.
Iris, what you were saying to me...
...when I was down in the sewer...
You know why I wasn't afraid?
Because you were there.
Even though I really was scared,
having you there...
...is how I could stand up to Grodd.
Every time I falter...
...or make a mistake...
...the thought of you is what picks me up
and keeps me going.
Look, what I'm trying to say is...
...even though you didn't
know everything...
...about my life this past year...
...that does not mean
that you weren't a part of it.
You were.
Every single day.
Without you...
...there wouldn't be the Flash.
I've thought about what you said...
...and maybe you were right.
I have been thinking about you...
...about us.
...but I can't do that anymore.
Eddie is the man that I live with,
the man that I love...
...and he's still missing.
I know.
I'm gonna bring him back.
And after that?
I don't know.
- So now what?
- Now...
...I have the key.
The key to what?
Time to go home.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org