Re-synced and Edited By : piDhoxx
http://IDFL.US
--- Original Subs By ---
peean91
I knew Harvey Dent.
I was his friend.
And it will be a very long time
before someone inspires us...
...The way he did.
I believed in Harvey Dent.
- Dr. Pavel, I’m CIA.
- He wasn’t alone.
You don’t get to bring friends.
They are not my friends.
Don’t worry, no charge for them.
And why would I want them?
They were trying to grab your prize.
They work for the mercenary
a Masked man.
Bane?
Get 'em on board.
I’ll call them in.
The flight plan I just filed with the agency...
...Lists me, my men, Dr. Pavel here.
But only one of you.
The first one to talk...
...get to stay on my aircraft!.
Who paid you to grab Dr. Pavel?
I didn’t fly so good!
Who wants to try next?!
Tell me about Bane!
Why does he wear the mask?!
A lot of loyalty for a hired gun!
Or peraps he's wondering
why someone would shoot a man...
...before throwing him out of the plane.
At least you can talk.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who we are.
What matters is our plan.
No one cared who I was to like put on the mask.
If I pull that off, will you die?
It would be extremely painful.
You’re a big guy.
For you.
Was getting
caught part of your plan?
Of course.
Dr. Pavel refused our offer in favor of yours.
We had to find out, what he told you.
Nothing!... I said nothing!
Well Congratulations!...
...you got yourselves caught.
Sir!
Now, what’s the next
step of your master plan?
Crashing this plane...
...With no survivors.
Mayday!... Mayday...!
No!
They expect one of us in the wreckage, brother.
Have we started the fire?
Yes. The fire rises.
Calm down, doctor.
Now this is not the time for fear.
That comes later.
Harvey Dent's Day.
May not be our oldest, public holiday...
...but we’re here tonight because it’s
one of the most important.
Harvey Dent’s uncompromising stand,
against organized crime.
Have made Gotham a safer place...
...than it was at the time of his death,
Eight years ago.
This city,
has seen a historic turnaround.
No city is without crime.
But this city is without organized crime...
...because the Dent act gave law
enforcement teeth...
...in it's fight against the mob.
Now people are talking
about repealing the Dent act.
And to them I say...
...not on my watch.
I want to thank the Wayne Foundation
for hosting this event.
And I’m told,
Mr. Wayne couldn’t be here tonight...
...I’m sure he’s with us in spirit.
And now,
I’m going to give way to an important voice.
Ever lay eyes
on Wayne at one of these things?
No one has. Not in years.
That people put their faith in a
murderous thug in a mask and a cape.
A thug...
...who showed his true nature...
...when he betrayed
the trust of this great man...
...and murdered him in cold blood.
Sweetheart, what's so fast with the chow?
Shrimp balls?
Jim Gordon...
- Thank you.
- ...can tell you the truth...
About Harvey Dent.
Let him tell you himself.
Commissioner Gordon!
The truth.
I have written a speech.
Telling the truth about Harvey Dent.
Maybe the time isn’t right.
Maybe right now...
...all you need to know is that there are...
...one thousand inmates in Blackgate prison
as a direct result of the Dent act.
These are violent criminals, essential cogs
in the organized crime machine.
Maybe for now, all I should say about,
the death of Harvey Dent’s is this...
...it has not been for nothing.
Did you see the guy who owns the house?
No.. you know,
I heard he never leaves the east wing.
You know, I heard he had an accident?.
Yeah, That he’s disfigured.
Mr. Till...
...why are your people using the main stair case?
And where is, Mrs. Bolton?
She’s up at the bar, Sir.
Can I help?
The east drawing room.
Unlock the door,...
...put the tray on the table,
Lock the door again.
Nothing more.
I’m sorry Miss. Tate,
I tried. But he won’t to see you.
And you know,
you must not take it personally.
Everyone knows,
that Wayne’s hold up in there...
...with eight inch nails,
paving into mason jars.
It's very good of you to let me on the grounds.
Why are you wasting your time...
...trying talk to a man,
Who throw away your investment...
...on some Save-The-World vanity project?
He can’t get your money back.
I can.
I could try explaining,
that the Save-The-World project...
...vain or not...
...is worth investing in, Mr. Daggett.
But you understand only money...
...and the power you think it buys.
So why waste my time, indeed?
Second shift reports in...
You should spend
some more time with the mayor.
That’s your department.
Anyone shown him the crime stats?
He goes by his gut. And it...
...continues bother him no matter,
what the numbers.
Must be popular with his wife.
Not really.
He took the kids and moved to Cleveland.
We have plenty of time for visits.
The Mayor's going to
dumping him in the spring.
Really?
But he’s a hero.
War hero.
This is peace time.
Sorry. Sorry!
I’m so terribly sorry, Mr. Wayne.
It is Mr. Wayne, isn’t it?
Although you, don’t have a long nails....
...or facial scars, Sir.
That what they say about me?
It’s just that no.
No one ever sees you.
That’s a beautiful necklace.
Reminds me of one
that belong to my mother.
It can’t be the same one...
...because her pearls are in this safe.
The manufacturer clearly explained...
...is uncrackable.
Oops...
Nobody told me it was uncrackable.
I’m afraid
I can’t let you take those.
Look.
you wouldn't beat up a woman...
...any more than I would beat up a cripple.
Of course.
Sometimes exceptions have to be made.
Good night, Mr. Wayne
- Can I have a ride?
- You read my mind!
Let's go!
Ms. Tate was asking to see you again.
- She's very persistent.
- And quite lovely.
- In case you were wondering.
- I wasn't.
- What are you doing?
- Examining print dust.
We've been robbed.
And this your idea of a sounding the alarm, is it?
She took pearls, tracking device and all.
- She?
- One of the maids.
Perhaps you should stop letting them
in this part of the house.
Perhaps you should start learning
to make your own bed.
- Why were you dusting for prints?
- I wasn't. She does.
Sir!
The Congressman Gilly's wife been calling
in apparently The Congressman never made...
...it home after the Wayne
Foundation event.
That's the job for the police.
When you and Dent clean up the
streets, you've cleaned them good.
Pretty soon we will be chasing down an...
...over due library books.
And yet, here you're...
...act like we're still at war.
- What's your name, son?
- Blake. Sir.
You have something you
want to ask me officer Blake?
It's about that night.
This night, eight years ago,
the night Dent died.
The last confirm sighting of
The Batman.
Who murders those people,...
...takes down two SWAT teams, brakes
Dent's neck and then just vanishes.
I'm not hearing the question.
Don't you want to know who he was?
I know exactly who he was.
He was The Batman.
Let's go see about
The Congressman's wife.
Master Wayne!
You haven't been down here in a long time.
I'm trying to finding more
about our jewel thief.
I ran her prints.
Unless she loss a lot of weight...
...she was wearing someone else's
fingerprints. She's good.
She may be.
but we have a trace on the necklace.
We do, so I cross reference
the address she went back to...
...with police data on high
end thieves and these...
...and Selina Kyle.
Database’s are full of close
calls and tips around the fences.
She's good, but the ground
is shrinking beneath her feet.
We should send the police
before she fences her purposes.
She won't.
She likes it too much.
And they weren't what she was after.
- What was she after?
- My fingerprints.
I was printer toner mixed with
graphite on the safe.
It gives you good pull
and and it's untraceable.
Fascinating. You two should
exchanging notes over coffee.
So you're trying to set me
up with a jewel thief?
At this point, I'd set you up with a chimpanzee...
...if it'd bring you back to the world.
There's nothing out there for me.
And that's the problem.
You hung up your cape and your cover
but you didn't move on.
You never went to find a life,
you'll find some how...
Alfred.
I did find someone.
I know, and you lost them.
But that's all part of living sir.
But you're not living. You're just waiting.
Hoping things to go bad again.
Remember when you left Gotham?
Before all this, before Batman,
You've been gone for seven years.
Seven years...
...I've waited,
hoping that you wouldn't come back.
Every year, I took a holiday.
I went to Florence's cafe.
On the banks of the Arno.
Every fine evening, I'll sit there
and ordered a Fernet Branca.
I had this fantasy.
That I would look across the tables...
...and I'll see you there.
With a wife maybe a couple of kids.
You wouldn't say anything to me,
Or me to you.
But we both know...
...that you made it.
That you were happy.
I never wanted you...
...to come back to Gotham.
I always know that there was nothing
here for you....
...except pain and tragedy.
And I wanted something more
for you than night.
I still do.
It washed up here a couples of times a month.
a more when it gets colder.
Homeless sheltering in the tunnels.
And we pulled him from
the base...
...but other than that, we didn't touch it.
What?
His name is Jimmy.
He's from St. Swithin's.
He's the boy on my group.
I coached the ball.
Jimmy had not around for a months.
No, why?
Blake, you know why.
He aged out.
We don't have the resources
to keep the boys on after 16.
I thought the Wayne Foundation
gave money for them.
Not for the past couple of years.
He has a brother here, doesn't he?
Mark. I'll tell him.
I'd like to. If that's alright.
You know, he was
doing down there in the tunnels?
A lot of guys go in down in the
tunnels when they aged out.
They said he lived down there.
They says there's work down there.
Work?
What kind of work you can find in the sewers?
More than you can find out here I guess.
- So you know about him.
- Of course.
Do you think he's coming back?
I don't know.
You brought a date?
I like someone around
to open doors for me.
Right hand, I got partials.
Very nice!
Not so fast handsome.
You've got something for me?
Oh yes.
I don't know what you're planning
to do with Mr. Wayne's prints...
...but, I'm guessing you need his thumb.
You don't count so good huh?
I count fine.
In fact, I'm counting to 10 right now.
Okay.
My friend's outside,  just hit send.
This place is a little dim.
I'll light up in a minute.
Trust me.
Is everything okay?
Great. Catch you later.
It would've been a lot easier...
...to just give me what we agreed.
We can't have loose ends.
And even in that dress,
no one going to miss you.
No.
But my friend over there...
Every cop in the city is missing him.
That's cute! But they're not going
to be looking in a place like this.
I don't know,
you did use your cell phone.
Police!... Get down now!
Help me!.. Help me!..
Help!
Keep some pressure on that, Sweetheart.
Call me?
- Careful, Miss.
- He's bleeding. You gotta help him!
I've got The Congressman.
There!
The manhole! Get this out.
Get the GWPD down here!
You three!... down with me!
You two!... you go down!
Cover the next exit!
What? He went down there?
We're going down there, right?
That was a gas explosion, kid.
What gas? It's a sewer.
No one goes in there until
we know what's down there.
We know who's there Sir,
a police commissioner.
Someone get this hot head out of here.
And where's that G.W.P guy?
Why are you here?
Answer him!
I was asking you.
It's a Police Commissioner.
And you brought him down here?
We didn't know what to do.
- We just thought...
- You panicked.
And your weakness cost the lives
of three others.
No. He's a little...
Search him, then I'll kill you.
He's dead.
So show me his body!
The water runs to any one of the out flows.
We'll never find him.
Follow him.
Follow him?
Detective! Detective!
Hey!... Hey!... You awake?
I need to see Bruce Wayne.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wayne doesn't
take unscheduled calls...
...even from a police officer.
If I go get a warrant for the
investigation of Harvey Dent's murder...
...it still counts as an unscheduled?
How can I do for you officer?
Commissioner Gordon been shot.
He chased a gun man down in the sewers.
When I pulled him out, he was
babbling about an underground army.
A masked man called Bane.
Shouldn't you be telling this to
your superiors officers about this?
They asked if he saw any giant alligators.
He needs you.
He needs The Batman.
Commissioner Gordon, thanks...
He doesn’t know or care who you are.
But we have met before.
There was a long ago,
I was a kid at St. Swithin's...
...used to be funded by
The Wayne Foundation.
It's an orphanage.
My mommy died when I was small in a car accident.
But I don't remember it.
My dad got shot a couple of years later
for a gambling debt.
And when I remember that one,
Just fine.
Not a lot of people knows what it feels like, do they?
Be angry in your bones.
I mean they understand.
The fosters parents.
Everybody understands...
...For a while.
Then they want the angry little kid
to do something he knows he can't do...
...move on.
After a while they stop understanding.
They send the angry little
kid to a boy's school.
I figured it out too late.
You got to learn to hide the anger...
...practice smiling in the mirror.
It's like putting on a mask.
So you show up this one day.
In a cool car...
...pretty girl in your arms.
You were so excited!
Bruce Wayne, billionaire orphan?
We used to make up stories about you man.
Legends.
And you know the other kids,
that's all it was, it's just stories.
But when I saw you,
I knew who you really were.
I seen that look on your face before.
It's the same one
that I taught myself.
I don't know why you took the fault of
Dent's murder.
But I'm still a believe in The Batman.
Even if you're not.
Why did you say that
your boy's home
used to be funded by
The Wayne Foundation?
Because the money stopped.
Might be time to get some fresh air...
...start paying attention of the details.
Some of details might need your help.
Have you checked that name, Bane?
He’s a mercenary.
No other known name.
He and his man were
behind a coup in West Africa.
They've secured a mining operations
for our friend, John Daggett.
- And Daggett brought them here.
- So it seems.
- I'll keep digging.
- Yeah.
Alfred, why did The Wayne Foundation
stopped funding the boy's home in the city?
The foundation is funded...
...by the profits of Wayne Enterprises.
There have to be some.
Time to talk to Mr. Fox,
I think.
I'll get him on the phone.
No.. No.. No.. No.
Did we still have any car around the place?
Yes, one or two?
I need an appointment at a hospital for my leg.
- Which hospital?
- Which ever one Jim Gordon's in.
I've seen worst cartilage in knees.
- It's a good?
- No.
That's because there's no cartilage in your knee...
...and not much of any use in
your elbows or your shoulders.
Between that and scar tissue on your kidney...
...residual concussive damage to
your brain tissue...
...and the general scarred over
quality of your body...
...I cannot recommend you to go
heli-skiing, Mr. Wayne.
Right.
We were in this together.
Then you were gone.
The Batman wasn't needed anymore.
We won...
We strung a lie.
Now there's evil rises again
where we try to bury him.
The Batman has to come back.
And if he doesn't exist anymore?
He must.
You got them wallet, do you?
You took my wallet!
No I didn't!
Get out.
She took my...
Arghh
Now.
Crazy!
I don't know why he's so upset about.
It's only 60 bucks in here.
You got to wear the watch.
Who's that?
Another stiff convety climb out of his sport car.
Well that's Bruce Wayne!
Mr. Wayne, over here!
- I'm not sure if my assistant put me on...
- Right through here, Mr. Wayne
Thank you so much.
Bruce Wayne at a charity ball?
Miss. Tate, isn't it?
Even before you became a recluse,
you never came to these things.
Proceeds goes to big fat spread.
This is not about charity.
It's about feeding the ego which
ever society hag laid this on.
Actually this is my party, Mr. Wayne.
And the proceeds will go where they should,
because I paid for the big fat spread myself.
You spread generously?
You have to invest if you want
to restore balance to the world.
Take our clean energy project.
Sometimes, the investments
just doesn't pay off.
I'm sorry.
You have a practiced apathy, Mr. Wayne.
But a man who does not care about the world
doesn’t spend half his fortune...
...on a plan to save it.
And isn’t so wounded when it fails...
...but he goes into hiding.
Have a good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Mind if I cut in?
Thank you.
You're don't seem happy to see me.
- You're suppose to be a shut-in.
- I felt like some fresh air.
Why didn't you called the police?
I have a powerful friend
who deals with things like this.
It's a brazing costume for a cat burglar.
- Yeah? Who are you pretending to be?
- Bruce Wayne, eccentric billionaire.
- Who's your date?
- His wife is in Ibiza.
She left her diamonds behind
though, worried it might get stolen.
It pronounced 'Ibitha'.
You wouldn't want any of these folks realizing
you're a crook now. Social planner.
You think I care what everyone
in this rooms thinks of me?
I doubt you care anyone in
any room who thinks of you.
Don't candescent, Mr. Wayne.
You don't know me a thing about me.
Well Selina Kyle.
I know you came here from
your walk-out Old Town...
...a modest place for a master jewel thief.
Which means that either you're saving
for retirement or...
...you in deep with the wrong people.
You don't to get judge just because you
were born the master bedroom of Wayne....
Actually, I was born in the Regency room.
I started out doing what I had to.
Once you're done what you had to,
They never let you do what you wanted to.
Start fresh.
There's no fresh start in today's world.
Any 12 years with a cell phone
would find out what you did.
Everything we do is collated
and quantified everything sticks.
Is that how you justify stealing?
I take what I need from those
who have more than enough.
I don't stand on the shoulders
of the people with less.
Robin Hood?
I think I do more to help someone
than most of the people in this room.
Than you.
I think maybe you're
assuming a little too much.
Maybe you're being unrealistic
about what's really...
...in your pants other than wallets.
Ouch.
You think all this can last?
There's a storm coming, Mr. Wayne.
You and your friends better
battered down the hatches...
...because when it hits, you’re all gonna wonder
How you ever thought you could live so large...
...and leave so little for the rest of us.
You sound like you're looking forward to it.
I'm adaptable.
Those pearls
do look better on you than it did in my safe.
But I still can't let you keep them.
You scared her off!
Not likely.
I still lost my ticket.
- Your wife said you're taking the cab home.
- My wife?
Just you, sir?
Don't worry, Master Wayne.
Takes a little time to get back in the swing of things.
Bruce Wayne.
As I live and breathe.
What brings you out of prior sleep, Mr. Wayne?
I see you haven't lost your sense of humor...
...even if you have lost
most of my money.
Actually you did that.
If you follow all your entire RND budget to
a fusion project that you get mothball...
...your company is unlikely to thrive.
What are the options?
Well if you're not unwilling
to turn on the machine.
I can't. I can't, Lucius.
Well then sit tight.
Your majority keep dagger at bay...
...while we figured out a future for the
energy program with Miranda Tate.
She has supported the project all the way.
She's smart and quite lovely.
We all just want what's best for you, Bruce.
Show her the machine.
I think it over.
Anything else?
Nope. Why?
These conversations always used to
end with an unusual request.
I retired.
Let me show you some stuff, anyway.
Just for old times' sake.
I figured you had to shut this place down.
Oh, it was always shut down.
Officially.
What's the new stuff.
After your father died,
Wayne Enterprises...
...has set up 14 different defense subsidiaries.
For years, I've been shuttering and consolidating
all the different prototypes under one roof.
- My roof.
- Why?
Keep them from falling into the wrong hands.
Now you just showing off.
Defense department project.
Tight Geometer Urban Pacification.
Rotors are configured
to maneuver between buildings...
...without recirculation.
What it's called?
It has a long uninteresting
Wayne Enterprise’s designation.
I just the took of calling it
The Bat.
And yes Mr. Wayne, it does come in black.
Works fine, except for the autopilot.
Take a better mind than mine to fix it.
A better mind?
Well I was trying to be modest.
A less busy mind, yours.
It should be a painful.
You’re welcome to try it, Alfred.
Happy watching.
Thank you, Sir.
Not bad.
Not bad at all
If you're seriously
considering going back out there...
...you should hear the rumors
surrounding Bane.
I'm all ears.
There is a prison
in a more ancient part of the world.
A pit where men are thrown to suffer and die.
But sometimes
a man rises from the darkness.
Sometimes, the pit sends something back.
Bane?
Right.
Born and raised in hell on earth.
Born in a prison?
No one knows why or how he escaped.
But they do know once he did, he was
trained by Ra's Al Ghul, your mentor.
Bane was a member
of The League of Shadows.
And then he was excommunicated.
And any man
who is too extreme for Ra's Al Ghul...
...is not to be trifled with.
I didn't realized I  was known
for trifling with criminals.
That was then.
Then you can just strap up your leg
and put your mask back on,...
...but that doesn't make you what you were.
If this man is everything what you say he is,
then the city needs me.
The city needs Bruce Wayne,
your resources, your knowledge.
It doesn't need your body,
or your life.
That times has past.
You're afraid if I go back out there,
I'll fail.
No.
I'm afraid that you want to.
You can't short the stock if
Bruce Wayne goes to a party.
Wayne's coming back has change.
- Changes, is it good or bad?
- I vote bad.
- On what basis?
- I flip the coin.
I said no rye man.
Rookie! Loose the helmet!
We need faces for camera.
Come on let's go scalping.
This is a stock exchange.
There's no money you can steal.
Really?
Then why are you people here?
You got to get in there!
- It's a hostage situation.
- No! This is a robbery!
They have direct access to
the online trading desk.
I'm not risking my men
for your money.
Sir, you going to ask you to move.
We have a situation here.
It's not our money,
it's everybody's.
Really? Mine is in my mattress.
If don't put these guys down,
that something in your mattress maybe
be worth a whole hell of a lot less.
Cut the fiber cable and
take out that cell tower.
- Thank you.
- That will slow them down.
They cut the Fiber.
- The cell's working.
- For now.
Get all this barriers up.
I want all of them up.
No one gets in or out of
any of these streets.
- Where am I suppose to move it?
- Back it up.
Just stay in your vehicle, okay?
How much longer does
the program need?
Eight minutes.
Time to go move out.
Everybody up!
You two, move!
Thank you.
Steady!
I got something!
Do not shoot! We've hostages!
Hold your fire!
Go! Go!
Hey, let me go!
Please! Help!
- Shoot the tires!
- There's no shot.
Now back off! Back off!
They've got hostages!
Police are pursuing
the 4 suspects from
downtown in respond to
a hostage situation
Gotham PD...
What's going on with the lights?
I can't pick up anything!
Who the hell was that?
Oh boy you're in for a show tonight, son!
Please! Help!
Sorry!
Put that thing away before
you hurt yourself.
Get in!
Let's go. You, get in the car!
We've spotted The Batman!
I want all everyone in.
Every car patrol, street
cops and off duty too.
Call them in now!
I'm going to do what
Jim Gordon never could.
- What's that?
- I'm going to take down The Batman.
...the 4 suspect are carrying two hostages...
...that they kidnapped them at
the Gotham Stock Exchange.
Witnesses reported that ...
It seems hard to believe.
But report are suspects
are now being pursued...
...what appears to be, The Batman.
Well what do you know?
Sir, what about the armed robbers?
Please! Let me go! Please!
One bike has pulled off.
No hostage. Shall we pursue?
Negative. Stay on The Batman!
- He's getting away.
- Who do you want to catch huh?
Some robber or the son of a bitch,
who killed Harvey Dent?
Eight years and he has to pick tonight.
He's drawing the cops off Bane.
Please! Just let me go! Please!
Transefering Complete
We lost him.
How could you lose him?
He's got a lot of firepower.
What?... You don't ?!
He heads back downtown.
And he's as dumb as he dresses.
Close it up, gentlemen!
Like a rat in a trap, gentlemen!
Who might've the wrong animal there, Sir ?!
You're sure it was him?
Bane says that Batman interfered,
but the task was accomplished.
What about the men they've arrested?
He said and I quote,
"They would die before talking."
Where does he finds these guys?
Open the champagne!
- And can we get some girls in here?
- Be careful what you wish for!
- Cat got your tongue?
- You dumb bitch!
Nobody ever accuse of being dumb.
You're dumb, for coming here tonight.
I want what you owe me.
One doesn't get...
Nice outfit.
Aren't those heels make
it tough to walk?
I don't know.
Do you think?
- So where is it?
- Where's what?
The program  "The Clean Slate".
The Ultimate Tool for a
master thief with a record.
Hold it right there!
- Where is it?!
- "The Clean Slate" ?
When you type in someone's name,
date of birth...
...and a few minutes they're gone,
every database on earth.
Sounds a little too good to be true?
You're lying!... Riken Data took
it to the prototype stage.
That's why I bought them.
But they had nothing.
It was a gang-land myth.
Stay back!
I'm not bluffing!
They know.
They just don't care.
You gotta be kidding me.
No guns, no killing.
Where the fun in that?
My mother warned about getting
into cars with strange, Man.
This isn't car.
See you around
You're welcome
I had it under control.
Those weren't street thugs.
They were trained killers.
I saved your life.
In return, I need to know what you did
with Bruce Wayne's fingerprints.
Wayne wasn't kidding about a powerful friend.
I sold his prints to Daggett.
Something that doesn't even exist.
I doubt that will get the better of you.
Hey when a girl's desperate...
What's he going to do with them?
I don't know.
But Dagget seem pretty interested
in that mess at the stock market.
Miss Kyle...
So that's what that feels like...
I've seen you in the television coverage, you've
got your taste for wanting destruction back.
I retrieved this.
Aren't the police suppose
to be investigating them?
They don't have the tools to analyze it.
They would if you gave it to them.
One man's tool is another man weapon.
In your mind perhaps, but there aren't
many things can't turn into a weapons.
Alfred, enough!
The police weren't getting it done
Maybe they might have. If you hadn't
made the side show of yourself.
You I didn't had it in me.
You don't. You got to glow at the
police force, a married chased...
...with a lot of fancy new toys from Fox's.
What about when you come up against him?
What then?
I'll fight harder. I always have.
Take a look, his speed, his ferocity, his training.
I see the power of believe.
I see The League of Shadows insurgent.
- You said he was excommunicated.
- By Ra's Al Ghul.
Who leads them now?
Ra's Al Ghul was The League
of Shadows and I beat him.
Bane is just a mercenary,
we need to find out what he's up to.
Trade of some kind. Coded.
And my fingerprints courtesy of Selina Kyle.
Give this to Fox.
He can crack the code...
...and tell us what trades they were executing.
I'll give this to Mr. Fox,
but no more.
I sewed you up, I set your bums,
but I wont bury you.
I buried enough members in
The Wayne family.
You're leaving me?
You see only one end
to your journey.
Leaving is all I have
to make you understand.
You're not Batman anymore.
You have to find another way.
You used to talked about finishing
about a light on that awful cave.
Alfred, Rachel died
knowing that we had decided to be together.
That was my life beyond the cave.
I can't just move on.
She didn't, she couldn't have.
What did she had?
I can't change that.
What if before she died,
she’d written a letter?
Saying she choose Harvey Dent over you?
And what if to spare your pain....
...I burned that letter?
How dare you use Rachel...
...to try and stop me.
I am using to choose, Master Wayne.
Maybe it's time we all start trying
to out smart the truth...
...and let it have it stay.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
You expect to destroy my world...
...and then think we're going to shake hands?
No.. No..
- What this means.
- What is your mean?
It means your hatred
and it also mean losing someone.
Who I've cared kept for since I first heard
his cries echoes through this house.
But it might also mean.
Saving your life.
And that's more important.
Good bye, Alfred!
Alfred?
- Answering your own door?
- Yeah.
Page 3.
Seem you made a series a laud
put options on the future exchange.
Verified by thumb print.
Those options expired at midnight last night.
Long term we may be able to prove
it was a fraud but for now,...
...you're completely broke.
And Wayne Enterprises is about to fall
into the hands of John Daggett.
The weapons.
...We can't let Daggett get his hands
on the applied sciences.
Applied sciences is all lock
up and off the books.
The energy project however
is a different story.
Miranda Tate.
We need to convince the board
to get behind her.
Let's show her the reactor.
We're meeting her there in 35 minutes.
So you better get dressed.
You brought me out here to show me this, Mr. Fox?
Bear with me, Miss. Tate.
Please keep hands and
feet in the car at all time.
This is it, isn't it?
The reactor is beneath the river.
So it can be instantly flooded
in an event of a security breach.
Is Bruce Wayne really that paranoid?
I fail to give an answer on that one.
I thought you might like to see
what your investment builds.
No fossil fuels, free clean energy
for an entire city.
Three years ago, a Russian scientist published
a paper on weaponize fusion reactions.
One week later,
your reactor started developing problems.
I think this machine works.
Miranda, if it were operational...
...danger to Gotham would be too great.
Would it make you feel better to know
that the Russian scientist...
...died in a plane crash six months ago?
Someone been working hard,
with Dr. Pavel...
...Someone will figured out a way to...
...make this power source into
a nuclear weapon.
I need you to take control
of Wayne Enterprises and this reactor.
- To do what with it?
- Nothing.
Until we can guarantee it's safety.
And if we can't?
Decommission it, flood it.
Destroy the world's best chance
for a sustainable future?
The world is not ready, yes.
Bruce, if you want to save the world...
...you have to start trusting it.
I'm trust you.
It doesn't count.
You have no choice.
I could've flooded this chamber at
any time in the last three years...
...I'm choosing, to trust you.
Please.
Alright ladies and gentlemen,
this meeting will now come to order.
Then I would like to point out that
we have a non-board member here.
There is highly irregular, even if
his name is above the door.
Bruce Wayne's family built this company.
- And he himself has run it...
- Into the ground!, Sir.
Does anybody disagrees?
Check the share prices this morning.
Crazy gambling on future
is not only cost Mr. Wayne his seat...
..it's cost us all.
A lot of money and he has to go.
I'm afraid he has a point, Mr. Wayne.
Well back to business.
How does it feel to be one of the people, Wayne?
Mr. Wayne, they're towing your car.
I didn't know that you're off the board.
Looks like you'll need a ride huh?
Mr. Wayne, will you get a ride?
What the hell did Miranda Tate get the inside
track on the Wayne board?
I mean, she been meeting with him?
- She been sleeping with him?
- Not that we know of.
Oh clearly you don't know much
of anything, do you? Where's Bane?
- We told him it was urgent.
- Where is that man?
Speak of the devil, and he shall appears.
What the hell is going on?
The plan is preceding as expected.
Really? Do I look like I'm running
Wayne Enterprises right now?
Your hit on the stock exchange,...
...it didn't work my friend.
And now you have my construction crews...
...going around the city at 24 hours a day.
How exactly is that suppose to help
my company absorbs Wayne?
- Leave us!
- No!... Stay here.
I'm in charge.
Do you feel in charge?
I have paid you a small fortune.
And this gives you power over me?
What is this?
Your money and infrastructure
have been important...
...till now.
- What are you?
- I'm Gotham Reckoning.
It'll end of all the damn you've been living on.
You are pure evil.
A necessary evil.
No!
Well you've started quite a mess.
To protect the people closes to me.
Maybe you're a loner, right?
You didn't have a family.
There are always people
that you care about.
But you didn't realize how
much until they're gone.
The idea was to be a symbol.
Batman can be anybody.
That was the point.
- Well it damn good to see him back.
- Not everybody agrees.
I'll figured that out in the end.
We got anything on Bane's whereabouts?
Yes, I have 500 pages of tunnel
records and a flashlight.
I could use some help actually.
You know what,
drop me in the old town.
- I don't think so!
- That is not how it works.
- That is...
- He's not a mark.
and he doesn't have a cent
to his name, anyway.
Yeah, It's not much.
But it's more than you got right now.
Actually, they're
letting me keep the house.
The rich doesn't even go broke
like the rest of us, huh?
My powerful friend might hope
to change your mind about leaving.
- And how would he do that?
- By giving you what you want.
It doesn't exist.
He says it does.
He wants to meet tonight.
Why?
He needs to find Bane.
He says you know how.
- Tell him I'll think about it.
- Okay. I like your place.
Mr. Wayne
I'm sorry, that to clear your money.
No. you're not.
- Can we help you officer?
- Yeah.
John Daggett's body was found
in a dumpster an hour ago.
Thought you might wanna know.
Why?
Well his name is all over this permit I just...
...pulled to half the tunnel under Gotham.
That is MTA maintenance, sewer
construction and others things...
What did you get with the
tunnel searches?
Remind me
to tell detail to keep hot heads out.
We had teams down there.
It's a huge network.
Well Get more, man.
Work a grid.. I want him found.
Yeah. The Masked Man.
We're on it.
Lose the uniform.
You’re working for me now.
We could use some hotter heads around here.
Sir, Daggett's death could only be a coincidence.
You're a detective now, son.
You're not allowed to believe
in coincidences anymore.
Nobody's answering.
No.
I'm... on my own now.
Do you have keys?
I never needed them.
I hope you didn't liked reaching my money.
Suffering this character.
I'll take care of your parents legacy, Bruce.
Who's this?
Where is Alfred?
He left...
...taking everything...
What's that?
Our power has been shut off.
You're good at that.
When I was a child,
we had almost nothing.
But on the nights,
when we had a fire, We felt very rich indeed...
I assumed your family was wealthy.
Not always. Not when I was young.
An old mistake.
I've made a few myself.
More than a few.
I could leave, tonight.
Take my plane and go anywhere we wanted.
Some day perhaps. Not tonight.
Don't be shy.
Wayne said that you can get me
"The Clean Slate".
That depends...
On what?
On what you want it for...
...I have acquire it to keep it out
of the wrong hands.
Still don't trust me, huh?
How can we change that?
Start by taking me to Bane.
Your asked.
From here, Bane's man patrol the tunnels...
...and they're not your average brawlers.
Neither am I.
- He's behind you.
- Who?
Me.
Where do you think you're going?...
Less a little bully.
I had to find a way to stop
them trying to kill me.
You made a serious mistake.
Not as serious as yours...
...I fear.
Bane.
Let's not stand on so moody here.
Mr. Wayne.
Peace has cost you your strength.
Victory has defeated you.
The adaptability and deception.
Powerful agents to the uninitiated.
But we are initiated aren't we, Bruce?
Members of the League of Shadows.
And you betrayed us.
Yes.. You were excommunicated by
a gang of psychopaths.
I am, The League of Shadows.
I'm here to full-fill Ra's Al Ghul's destiny!
You fight like a younger man,
there's nothing held back.
It's admirable, but mistaken.
You think darkness is your ally?
You've merely adopted the dark.
I was born in it.
Molded by it.
I didn't see the light
until I was already a man...
...by then was nothing to be blinded.
Shadows betray you,
because they belong to me.
I'll show you
where I had made my home.
Whilst preparing to bring justice.
Then I will break you.
Your precious armory.
Great fully accepted.
We'll need it.
Oh. yes!
I was wondering what would weight first.
Your spirit...
...or your body?
Get me Commissioner Gordon.
I got a line up of Congressman's kidnapping.
- Excuse me, miss!
- Yes?
I'm going to need to see your
ticket and identification, please.
Do you mind?
I showed your picture to The Congressman.
Guess what?
- Don't tell me... Still in love?
- Oh head over heels.
Pressing charges though.
You've made some mistakes, Miss Kyle.
- Girl's got to eat.
- And you have an appetite.
Why would run? You can't hide
from us with a record like this.
- Maybe it's not you I'm running from.
- Who then? Bane?
What do you know about him?
About you should be as afraid of him as I am?
You can offer you protection.
Okay.
When I spotted you, I was looking for
a friend of mine. Bruce Wayne.
Did that killed him?
I'm not sure.
Why didn't you just...
...kill me?
You don't fear death.
you welcome it.
Your punishment must be mastered here.
You're the charger?
Yes.
But not of your body.
Of your soul.
Where am I ?
Home.
Where I learned the truth about despair...
...as will you.
There's a reason why this
prison were a hell on earth.
Hope.
Every man who has lotted here over
the centuries...
...looked up to the light
and imagine climbing to freedom.
So easy... So simple.
Unless you break man turning into seawater
for uncontrollably fast.
Many have died trying.
And then here can be no true despair
without hope.
So, as I terrorize Gotham...
...I will feed it's deeper hole
to poison their souls.
I would let them live so
they can survived...
...so let you can watch them trampling
over each other...
...to stay in the sun.
You could watch me torturing
an entire city.
And then when you truly understood
the depth of your failure...
...we will fulfill Ra's Al Ghu's destiny.
We will destroy Gotham.
And then, what would you've...
...when Gotham is...
...ashes.
Then you have my permission to die.
You're locking her up in here?
The Dent act allowed non-segregation
based extraordinary needs.
First time she broke out of women correctional,
she was 16.
Little closer, dear.
Why honey?
You want to hold my hand?
She's going to be fine.
I still don't see the need of a board meeting
for the energy project.
Bruce got a lot of things right...
...keeping the board in the dark
was not one of them.
Oh. Good of you to join us,
Chair President.
All I need now is one more
Ordinary Board member.
- Mr. Fox, would you like to nominate?
- No...
...I will volunteer.
Where are you taking us?
You were right, Commissioner.
Would you excuses us, please?
What happened?
Your mask man kidnapped the
Wayne Enterprise’s Board.
He let most of them go, but he took
three of them into the sewers.
No more patrols.
No more hide and seek.
Get every available cop down there
and smoke him out!
The Mayor won't want panic.
So it's a training exercise?
I'm sorry, I didn't take you seriously.
Not you, you telling me The Batman
have gone.
So you chase up the daggers
leads anyway you can.
Yes, sir.
He asks how much you would pay
to let you die?
I told him... I told him
you have nothing.
You tell for the pleasure.
They pay me more than dead...
...to keep you alive.
He will try to climb.
Has anyone, every made it?
Well, Of course not.
He say there's one who did.
A child.
A child born in this hell.
Bane.
An old legend. Nothing more.
What they really tease me, you wanted to see,
is happening soon.
Fire in the hole!
Turn it on!
I only need one other Board member,
there are eight others waiting.
I won't do it.
Alright stop!
Lucius, you will kill this man and yourself.
And you'll barely slow them down.
Go on then, do you work.
Take them up to the surface.
People of their status
deserve to experience the next era...
...of Western civilization.
I've been to half of Daggett's cement plants,
some odd...
...location they pour for underground
construction.
Anything strange about the pouring?
Honestly, Commissioner. I don't know
anything about civil engineering.
But you know about patterns.
Keep looking!
It's done.
This is now a four megatons nuclear bomb.
Pull the core out of the reactor.
No!... You cannot!
This is the only power source capable
of sustaining it.
If you move it, the core will depleted
in a matter of months.
- Five, by my calculations.
- It will go off!
And for the sake of your children Dr. Pavel...
...It did I hope it does.
Hey.
Hey!
That was you in front of
The Stock Exchange wasn't it?
When?
When half the city cops try to pull onto castle street...
...and your truck and your truck was
shutting them out.
Oh yeah... you're the cop.
Detective.
And, As detective we're not allowed
to believe in coincidences.
What were you doing here?
What are you working on?
Commissioner, it's Blake.
I got two dead witnesses and a lot of questions.
Call me when...
Wait a minute.
Four barrels of polisobutilen.
That looks like motor oil right next to it.
Jesus!
They're not making cement,
they're making explosive.
Patch me through Foley.
Foley is overseeing the operation.
They're heading into a trap.
We seeing literally thousand
of police heading into the sewer.
Mr. Mayor, literally thousands of police...
It's just a training exercise.
That's all.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
...I got tickets to watch our boys
trash Rapid City.
Foley.
It's a trap. Pull all of them out!
Bane has been pour concrete rigs
with explosives.
Where?
There's a ring, surrounding the tunnels!
They're going to blow it
and trap the cops underground!
Pull 'em out.
Pull 'em out!... Now!
That's a lovely lovely voice.
Let the games begin.
Citizens!...
...Take control.
Take control of your city!
Foley ?.
Jesus, Blake!
Every cop in the city is down
in those tunnels!
Not every cop.
Sir, Are you okay? I'm a police officer,
I need your car right now.
Play the corners, rookie.
Get the coat, son!
This, this is the instrument
of your liberation.
Satellite show some radiation spike.
Whatever it is, it's nuclear.
Identify yourself to the world!
Dr. Leonid Pavel. Nuclear physicist.
Pavel was confirmed dead,
plane crash on an...
...agency pull out of Uzbekistan but
it looks like it's him.
And what, What is this?
It's a fully prime neutron bomb
with a blast radius of six miles.
And who is capable of disarming
such a device?
Only me.
Only you.
Thank you. Good doctor.
Now, this bomb is armed.
This bomb is mobile and the identity
of the trigger man is a mystery.
For one of you holds the detonator.
Now we came here not as conquerors...
...but liberators to return control of this
city to the people.
At the first sight of interference
of the outside world...
...or to those people attempting to flee.
This anonymous Gotham-might.
This unsung hero will trigger the bomb.
And now, Martial Law is in effect.
Return to your homes...
...hold your families close and wait.
Tomorrow you claim
what is rightfully yours.
Hold back the fighters.
Start high level reconnaissance flights.
Get the president on the line.
Tanks and planes cannot stop us
from detonating our device.
Send a negotiator to discuss term...
...of access to supplies and communication.
How many of you are there, Son?
You don't have enough man to stop...
...twelve million people from
leaving this island.
No... No we don't.
But you do.
Why the hell would I try help
you to keep your hostages?
If one person crosses this bridge...
...Gotham gets blown to hell.
The people of our greatest
city are resilient.
They have proven this before
and they will prove it again.
We do not negotiate with terrorists.
But we do recognize realities.
As this situation develops, one thing
must be understood above all others.
People of Gotham,
we have not abandoned you.
What does that mean?
It means we're on our own.
I have to get in front of a camera.
Well sir, they will kill you the second
you show your face.
Bane says he's giving Gotham
back to the people.
They need to know I could lead.
Bane is not going to let that happen.
- Then he will show his true colors.
- And you'd be dead.
Behind you, stand a symbol of oppression.
Blackgate Prison,
where a thousand men has...
...languished under the name
of this man...
Harvey Dent.
Who has been held to you as
the shinning example of justice.
We're just keep moving you until we
can get you in front of a camera.
You have been supplied with a false idol...
...to stop you tearing down
this corrupt city!
Let me tell you the truth
about Harvey Dent.
From the words,
of Gotham Police Commissioner.
James Gordon.
"The Batman didn't murdered Harvey
Dent, he saved my boy."
"Then took the blame for
Harvey's appalling crimes,"...
..."So that I could threw my shame,"...
..."build a lie around this fallen idol."
"I praised the mad man who tried
to kill my own child,"...
..."But I can no longer live with my lie."
..."It is time to trust The people of Gotham
with the truth"...
..."And it is time for me to resign."
And do you accept this man resignation?
And do you accept the
resignations of all these liars...
...of all the corrupt?
Those men locked up for eight
years at Blackgate.
With denied parole under the
Dent act based on a lie?
Gotham needed a hero.
It needs it now more than ever.
You betrayed everything you stood for.
What's the point?
Far out there when the
structures failing...
...and on the road, weapons city
more than...
...shackles.
Letting the bad guy getting hit.
One day...
...you may face such a moment of crisis.
And it that moment...
...I hope you have a friend like I did.
To plunge their hands into the filth.
So that you can keep yours clean.
Your hands looks funny-filthy to me, Commissioner.
We take Gotham from the corrupt.
The rich.
The oppressors who for generation has get you down
with myth of opportunity...
...and we give it back to you.
The people.
Gotham is yours.
None shall interfered.
Do as you pleased.
And start by storming Blackgate.
And freeing the oppressed!
Step forward those who would serve.
To an army, a world will be raised.
The powerful will be ripped from their
decadent years...
...and cast out into the cold world
that we know and endure.
Courts will be convened.
Spoils will be enjoyed.
Blood will be shed.
The Police will survive...
...as they learn to serve
true justice...
This great city...
...it will endure.
Gotham will survive.
He says you must first
fix your back.
How does he know?
He was the prison doctor.
A morphine addict.
When heard of this pleasure
of powerful evil.
Including your mask friend.
How?
Many years ago...
...it was a time of plague.
Some of the other
prisoners attacked Bane.
The Doctor humbling attempt
to rebuild the damage...
...left him in perpetual agony.
The Mask hold the pain at bay.
Bane, was the child who struck out?
He was born here?
Legend is that it was a mercenary
who worked for a local warlord.
They felt in love with the
warlord's daughter.
They were married in secret.
But the warlord found out.
The mercenary was condemned to this pit.
But then he exiled him instead.
The mess I understood that it was the
daughter who secure his release.
But what he could not know...
...was the true price of his freedom.
She took his place in the pit.
And she was with child,
the mercenary child.
Innocence cannot flower underground,
it has to be stem out ...
One day...
...the doctor forgot to lock the cell.
But the child had a friend.
a protector.
Who showed the others that this
innocence was their redemption.
It was to be priced.
The mother was not so lucky.
This is Bane's prison now.
It wouldn't want this story told.
There's a vertebra.
Protruding from your back.
It has to be put back.
Stay like this until you stand.
Did you not think I would
return, Bruce?
I told you I was immortal.
I watched you... I watched you die.
Owh... they're many forms of immortality.
Once I had a wife.
My great love.
She was taken from me.
You were the mercenary.
Bane is your child, your heir.
I'm here to ensure
The League of Shadow fulfills...
...it's duty to restore balance to civilization.
You yourself fought the decadence
of Gotham for years.
With all your strength...
...all your resources...
...all your moral authority.
And the only victory you
achieved was a lie.
Now, you understand?
Gotham is beyond saving.
And must be allowed to die.
No!
No... No!
What's that?
This was someone's home.
Now, it's everyone's home.
There's storm coming remember?
That is what we wanted.
It's for the bus, in case
there's a chance to evacuate.
Any news, from the Commissioner?
The less you know father.
How are the boys doing?
Well we had more power on,
so they get some TV.
It's good to see you, Father.
Hey Blake, you be careful out there.
They hunting down cops like a dog.
Why build yourself?
I'm not meant to die in here.
Here or there, what's the difference?
I told you it can't be done.
You told me a child did it.
But no ordinary child.
A child born in hell.
Forged from suffering.
Harden by pain.
Not a man from privileged.
We got blues in the ground, Sir.
Just waiting on intel.
Do you have ID?
Of course, Not.
How can we trust you?
We don't have any choice.
Commissioner Gordon.
Captain Jones, Special Forces.
Captain, glad to have you here.
It's our job sir.
Now how many are all you are they?
Well there's dozen,
I rather not say exactly.
The man trapped underground,
numbered almost 3,000.
- What kind of condition are they in?
- They been getting in food and water.
- Can we break them out?
- Yes, sir.
Take out the mercenaries guarding the
outflows south of Ackerman Park...
...blow the rubble, we can make a hole big
enough for 10 at a time.
I'm in contact with my partner down there.
They're just waiting for the day.
Commander, they haven't seen
daylight for three months.
Police officers who haven't seen
daylight in three months.
What about the bomb?
The satellite can't pick up
any radiation hot spots.
They keep it on a truck.
It must have lead lined roof.
- They're moving constantly.
- Good, so you know the truck?
Well it's one of the three.
We've been tracking it.
Decoy.
You're not really think
he's coming back, do you?
Doesn't matter what I think.
Actually it does. You should put
your faith in something more real.
But the routes don't vary much.
- What about the trigger man?
- No leads. It's a bluff.
Bane wouldn't gave control
on that to someone else.
We can't take that chance.
Until we have the trigger
man, we just track the device.
And mean while, Gotham
lives under a warlord?
Like some failed state?
Dialed it back, officer.
The situation is unprecedented.
We can't do anything to risk million of lives.
Can't you tell? Aren't you going to
tell them what actually is going on?
Captain, the situation is more
complicated than you think.
There's someone you need to meet.
Came up stairs looking for
a vantage point.
Found the people who runs the
corporation living up here.
What corporation?
Wayne Enterprises.
Mr. Fox would you like
to brief the captain?
Mrs. Tate is fully aware
of the situation.
And a CEO of Wayne Enterprises,
I have to take responsibility for it.
- Why?
- We built it.
You built the bomb?
It was build as a fussion reactor.
First of it's kind
Bane turned the core into a bomb,
and remove it from the reactor.
That's the important part.
As the device's fuel cells deteriorates...
...it becomes increasingly unstable
to the point of detonation.
This bomb is a time bomb.
And it will go off in 23 days.
Regardless of the Bane's revolution
or what we...
...and the outside world
choose to do.
Your peace-man plan may not be
as practical as you thought.
Could you disarm it?
I could reconnect to the reactor.
To stabilize it.
Let's move away from this
location and call it in.
Alright let's go!
Let me take it from here.
You stay and look after these folks.
Someone sold us out.
I'd die before I talk.
How about your schedule, Captain.
There were people living upstairs.
Round them up for judgment.
And hang them...
...where the world to see.
He says that the leap of
freedom is not about strength.
My body makes the jump.
Surviving is spirit, the soul.
My soul, is it ready to escape
with my body?
Feel is why you afraid?
No, I'm not afraid.
I'm angry.
Bruce.
Why did we fall?
You do not fear death.
You think this makes you strong?
It makes you weak.
Why?
How can you move faster than possible?
Fight longer than possible?
Without the most powerful
impulse left in you.
The fear of death.
I fear death.
I fear dying in here...
...all my city burns...
...there's no one there to save it.
And then make the climb.
How?
As the child did.
Without the rope.
That fear will fight you again.
Ah surprise for your journey,
that's wonderful.
What does that mean?
Rise.
No.
There's been a mistake.
Take me to Bane!
Where's Bane?
There's no mistake Mr. Stryver.
You are Philip Stryver.
Executive Vice President of
Daggett Industries...
...who for years has been living
off the blood and...
...sweat
of people less powerful than him.
Call, Bane.
I am one of you.
Bane has no authority here.
This is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now chooses yours,
exile or death?
Death!... Death!...
Ex... Exile.
Sold.
The man of the cold sweat.
You follow the thick ice. If you
try to swim, you're dead in minutes.
So no one made it?
Where the hell are they?
It's not like we have a lot of time here.
How long?
The bomb goes off tomorrow.
We have about 18 hours to do something.
To do what?
To mark the truck. Get a GPS...
...on it so we can start to figure out
how to bring it down.
That's it?
Foley.
Where is Foley? Damn it!
You shouldn't be out in the streets.
Jim, he's not here.
You let your wife come to the door,
when the city is under occupation?
What did you do? Bury your
uniform in the backyard?
You saw what they
did to the special forces.
Have you forgotten all the years
we were out on patrolled?
When every gang banger want to plant
one as soon as our back are turned?
Now is different and you know it.
This guys run the city.
The government is done a deal with them.
Bane's got their balls on the ice
that's not a deal.
If you move on Bane, the trigger-man
is going to hit the button.
Do you think he's given control
of that bomb to one of the people?
You think this apart of some revolutions?
There's only one man with his
finger on the button, that's Bane.
Look. We all got to keep our heads
down until they can fix this.
If you had family here...
That's only get fix from inside the city!
Look Peter...
...I'm not asking you to walk down grand in
you dress rules...
...but something has to be done.
- I'm sorry, Jim. I gotta...
- Keep your head down..
...What's good that going to do tomorrow
when that thing blows.
You don't know that's a happens.
I hear you're looking for men, Commissioner?
How about me instead?
Miss. Tate, I ehm...
I can't ask do do that.
Please.
What you did?
Nothing.
I didn't take anything.
You steal from us?... Little bastard ?!
Now you boys know you
can't come in my neighborhood...
...without asking politely.
Never steal anything from
someone you can't outrun, kid!
Pretty generous for a thief.
I thought they killed you.
Not yet.
- If you expecting an apology...
- I wouldn't suit you.
I need your help.
- And why would I help you?
- For this, "Clean Slate".
You trust me with that...
...after what I did to you?
I admit I was a little let down.
But I still think
there more to you.
In fact that, I think that.
For you, this isn't just a tool.
It's an escape route you want
to disappear, start fresh.
I couldn't even get off this island.
I could give you a way off once
you to get me to Lucius Fox.
I need you to find out where they're
holding him and take me in.
Why do you need Fox?
To save the city.
Who says it needs saving?
Maybe I like it this way.
Maybe you do.
But tomorrow that bomb is going off.
Get your powerful friend
on the case?
I'm trying.
But I need Fox.
Once it approaches, flick the switch.
The needle hit 200, you
give me the signal.
I'll will mark truck. Okay?
Heads up!... Heads up!
I got it!
Mercenaries at your 6.
Stand still! Keep your hands
where we can see them!
Commissioner Gordon,
you're under arrest.
On who's authority?
People of Gotham.
No lawyer. No witnesses.
What sort of due process is this?
You guilt have been determined.
This is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now what will it be?
Death or exile?
Crane, if you think we're going
out on that ice willingly...
...you have another thing coming.
Death then.
Looks that way.
Very well. Death!
By exile.
Bring her to me.
Hey. Going down. Get things ready.
Let's gear on.
Spot this one on the spot.
Got a big day tomorrow.
We all do. Not everyday
bag Bruce Wayne.
Bruce?
You okay?
You pick the hell of time to go
on vacation, Mr. Wayne.
How long until that core ignites?
That bomb goes off in 12 hours.
Unless we can reconnect
it to the reactor.
- Can you get Miranda out of here?
- Not tonight. I'm sorry.
Do what necessary.
Tonight I need you.
What for?
To get me back in the game.
Sorry, to spoil things boys but
they want these guys to themselves.
I won't forget about us, Miranda.
I know.
- I like your girlfriend, Mr. Wayne!
- He should be so lucky.
Any move I make on Bane or the
bomb, the trigger-man will set it off.
They won’t use radio or
cell, too much interference.
Infrared don't have the range.
It had to be a Micro-burst.
Long-range.
- Can you block it?
- Yes.
But I need the EMP cannon
guidance mounted on the Bat.
Remember where you parked it?
It fly okay?
Yeah.
Even without the autopilot.
Thanks.
Autopilot?
That's what you're there for.
Thing's clear. Come on, quick! Climb.
Lock it up!
Who are you?
Light it up!
Mom check it out.
Honey, take a look.
Impossible.
Keep her close.
He'll come for her.
Where's Miranda Tate?
Bane took her.
He holds up city hall,
surrounded by his army.
This blocks detonator signal to the bomb.
Get it on to it before sunrise.
If I hit the button when starts.
When what start?
War.
You missed a spot.
If you're working alone...
...wear a mask.
I'm not afraid if they see me
standing up to these guys.
The mask is not for you, it's to
protect the people you care about.
Count to five and throw.
Hey no offense,
but you got something bigger in that belt?
What now?
All out assault on Bane.
But you need to get
people across the bridge.
Why?
In case we fail. Leave an exodus.
Save as many lives as you can.
You don't need me here?
You given me an army... Now, go.
Thanks.
Don't thank me yet.
Well I might not get the chance later.
You shouldn't have.
All in town tunnel blocked by debris.
But the cannon have anough fire
power to make a path for people.
Wait until the fighting begins!
You going to wage your war
to save your stuck up girlfriend?
To start it, throttle.
I got it.
We have 45 minutes to save the city.
No... I got 45 minutes to get clear
of the blast radius.
Because you don't stand a chance
against these guys.
With your help, I might.
I open that tunnel, but then I'm gone.
There's more to you than that.
Sorry to keep letting you down.
Come with me!... Save yourself!
You don't owe these people anymore.
You given them everything.
Not everything.
Not yet.
Disperse!
Disperse or be fired upon!
There's only one police in this town.
Open fire.
- Here it comes.
- Get ready!
So you came back to die with your city.
No.
I came back to stop you.
Now!
That's impossible.
Come over the fifth!
Get on the bus, guys.
You come with me. You too.
Hey you, you and you, Come here.
Everyone else get on the bus!
Okay ?!
You guys, you're going to knock on doors and
spread the word. Okay?
The bomb going to go off.
Get out by South Street tunnel...
...or over the bridge.
You go, you do two blocks, you get
back to the bus. Alright? Go!... Go!...
Is he back?
Keep your eyes open.
Go... Go...
Cover the doors.
Where is the trigger?!
Where is it?!
You never gave it to any
ordinary citizen.
Where is it?!... Where's the trigger?!
Where is it?!... Where is it?!
Tell me where the trigger is it.
Then...
...you have mypermission to die.
I broke you.
How did you come back?
You think you're the only one who
could learn the strength to escape?
Where's the trigger?
But I never escaped.
But the child...
...Child of Ra's Al Ghul's who made the climb.
But he's not the child of Ra's Al Ghul.
I am.
Although I'm not ordinary.
I'm a citizen.
Miranda?
Why?
Thalia.
My mother named me Thalia before she was killed.
The way I have been killed if not for my protector.
Bane.
Good bye.
I climbed out of the pit.
I found my father.
And brought him back
to exact terrible vengeance.
But by that time...
...the prisoners and the doctor had their
work to my friend.
My protector.
The League took us in.
Trained us.
But my father could not accept Bane.
He saw only a monster,
whose very existence.
Was the reminder of the hell
he left his wife to die in.
He excommunicated Bane from
The League of Shadows.
His only crime...
...was that he loved me.
I could not forgive my father.
Until you murdered him.
He was trying to kill millions
of innocent people.
"Innocent" is a strong word
to throw around Gotham roose.
I honor my father by finishing his work.
Vengeance against the man who killed him is
a simply a reward for my patience.
You see?
It's the slow knife.
The knife that takes it's time.
The knife that wait years, without forgetting.
Then slip quietly between the bones...
...that's the knife that cut deepest.
Please!
Maybe that knife was too slow.
The truck is under attacked.
Gordon. You gave him a
way to block my signal
No matter.
He's bought Gotham eleven minutes.
Come on!... Come on!
Stay back! What are you doing?
Blake. MCU, I'm getting these boys to safety.
You're going to get us all killed.
Anyone cross this bridge,
they'll blow up the city.
It going to blow up anyway.
We need to open this bridge, now!
Detective, if you take one step forward,
we will shoot you.
If you do two step forward,
we will blow the bridge.
Go back to the bus and wait for me alright?
Just go back and wait.
They've prepared a convoy.
We must secure the bomb
until it detonates.
Don't kill him. I want him
to feel the heat.
Heat the fire of 12 million souls.
You failed.
Good bye, my friend.
Keep moving forward!
Take back the stairs!
Shoot them.
Shoot them all.
We both know that
I have to kill you now.
You have just to imagine the fire.
About the whole no guns thing.
I'm not sure I feel strongly
about it as you do.
Pull up.
Stay level.
We have to force them to
the entrance of the reactor.
I need you on the ground.
I'll be leaving. Go!
The situation has changed!
Your orders are out of date!
I'm a cop like you
and I'm walking out there.
Please do not shoot me!
Shoot at his knee.
Nothing like a little air superiority.
Detective, please stop!
Please, detective! Stop!
Stop walking!... Blow it!... Do it!...
They have to get that bomb here
and you got ten minutes.
They're pushing us to the entrance
of the reactor.
They're going to try to reconnect the core.
Idiots!
You son of bitches!... You killed them.
You're just following orders!
Alright boys get in circle,
bow your heads.
Not much longer.
Let's get everyone back in the bus.
Okay?
Go!... Go!... Go!... Go!...
Back in the bus!
There's no where to go.
On the bus!
You got to the truck EAST!
Stay straight!
Give me a hand!
We can get a cable on it!
Fox showed me how overwrite reactor.
Oh. Dear.
Including the emergency flood.
There's no way this bomb will be stopped.
What are you doing?
Protect them from the blast!
We're going to be alright!
Double time! Go!
It's an atom bomb!
You think they need to hear that, right now?
You want to watch them die without hope?
Come on!
Prepare yourself.
My father's work is done.
- What are you doing?
- I can get it out over the bay.
- Set it to fly over water and eject.
- No autopilot.
You could've gone anywhere, did
anything but you came back here.
So did you.
I guess we're both suckers.
- I never cared who you were.
- And you were right.
Shouldn't the people know the hero
who saved them?
Hero can be anyone.
Even a man knowing something as simple...
...and reassuring putting
a coat around a young boy shoulders...
...to let him the world hadn't end then.
Bruce Wayne?
Vlad, they go!... You too!...
Come on, father.
Hey heads down!... This is it!
No!... That's Batman!
That's detonation.
It's out over the bay, it's clear of the city.
"I see a beautiful city."
"And the the brilliant people
rising from this abyss. "
"And I see the lives, for which
I lay down my life."
"Peaceful, useful, prosperous
and happy."
"I see that I hold a sanctuary
in their hearts."
"And in the hearts of
their decedents."
"Generations ends."
"That's the far,
far better thing that I do..."
"...than I had ever done. "
"And It's a far, far better rest that I go to."
"Than I had ever known."
I'm so sorry. I failed you.
You trusted me.
And I failed you.
Can't I change your mind?
About quitting the force?
You know you said about
structures becoming shackles.
You were right.
And I can't take it that in justice.
I mean...
...No one ever going to know
who saved the entire city.
They know.
It was The Batman.
Mr. Wayne's will is not amended to
reflect his more modest estate.
Nonetheless, they're considerable
assets to dispose of.
The content of the house are to
be sold to settle the state accounts...
...and the remainders left in it's
entirety to Alfred J. Pennyworth.
The house and grounds are left to the city
of Gotham on condition...
...that they never be demolish, altered
or otherwise interfered with.
That they shall be used for one purpose,
and one purpose only.
The housing and care of the city's
at risk and orphan children.
And I clerk and help anyone with
a small correspondences and instruction.
Blake, John?
Nothing here.
Alright.
Try my legal name.
You should use your full name.
I like that name, Robin.
Thanks.
Why are we even worrying
about stabilization software?
This entire autopilot system
is completely obsolete.
Please, I just need to know
what I could've done to fix it.
But Mr. Fox it's already been fixed,
software patch, six months ago.
Check The ID on the patch.
Bruce Wayne.
- Any news on the missing item?
- Not yet.
Better leave no stone unturned.
We can't leave a string of pearl
on the manifest flaws.
piDhoxx
A Member Of IDFL™ Subscrew
--- Original Subs By ---
peean91