My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my
friends' power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Events will align that allow
Team Flash the chance
to discover your identity.
It is of no concern.
I could whip up
a predictive algorithm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
I can run through
my quantum cerebral chip.
We'll find him in no time.
If you've miscalculated
by even a decimal...
There is not a decimal, a fraction,
an infinitesimal variable
beyond my thought!
The name we're looking for
is Clifford DeVoe.
92% match to our psychological
profile. No other DeVoe comes close.
- Can I help you?
- We were just hoping
to talk with Clifford DeVoe.
Is he here?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
How may I be of help?
The effects...
...of Taoism...
All right, class.
Write your essays on
this list of topics.
You have two weeks to complete them.
Does anyone have their notes
from earlier?
I'm afraid I can't read
my own handwriting.
Class dismissed.
I know that look.
I felt the same after my 11:00 a.m.
Introduction to Fluid Mechanics
and Physical Thermodynamics class.
See, I was trying to explain turbulent
flow rates and, ten minutes in,
I wanted to pull my hair out.
It's a good thing I know
water flowing to the axis
of a tube is called...
You better get this right.
Laminar.
- So, you do listen.
- To you, always.
Nothing matters to them if it's
not digestible in YouTube videos
of talking babies
or inane pet tricks.
Have you seen the husky singing
"Like a Virgin?"
I made you smile.
How can we enlighten them
if their minds are too small
to handle the gift
of knowledge anymore?
Well, your plan will work.
We just need to re-fashion
the delivery system.
It's not the plan that's flawed.
It's my ability to execute it.
- Clifford...
- I'm simply not smart enough.
You are the most
brilliant mind I know.
It's not enough.
Not yet.
What?
At this point it's just a concept.
I call this my thinking cap.
Just like their minds have gotten too
small to handle their full capacity,
mine's too small to deliver it.
This can change all that...
If you build it, of course.
Your dream is my dream.
And your passion is my passion.
I'm nothing without you.
I hope it's not too sweet.
- This is amazing.
- Just like my wife.
Somehow she finds time
to take care of me
and still keep
an immaculate household.
And her three-cheese macaroni,
second to none.
Sometimes I think
I'm the luckiest man alive.
Gentlemen, how can I help?
The name "DeVoe" came up
in an investigation of ours.
We would just like to ask you
some questions, if that's okay.
Why him? DeVoe's a common name.
Yes, I'd wager
at least 1,100 individuals,
give or take a few,
with that last name
in the Central City area alone.
The name's been identified
for its connection
to four separate criminal cases.
So, you think my husband is
a witness to these crimes?
No, we'd like to eliminate him
as a suspect.
- You can't be serious.
- It's all right, Marlize.
Do go ahead.
So, Professor,
what brought you to Central City?
I grew up in South Africa.
And after studying history
and econometrics
at the University of Johannesburg,
I took a teaching position at Oxford.
That's where we met.
He swept me off my feet.
We've been together ever since.
It did take a tenured offer
from Central City University
to lure me away
from the Oxford faculty.
That was four years ago.
Question. Do you know Ramsey Deacon?
No. Should I?
What about Becky Sharpe?
- No. I'm afraid not.
- Ralph Dibny?
- Mina Chaytan?
- Mina Chaytan. Yeah.
That name's familiar.
Isn't this the Native-American woman
that left abruptly?
- You know, the anthropologist?
- Yes, I remember.
I was so sad to see her go.
You were colleagues.
Did she mention her work?
No, but Mina was an animated woman.
Then again, people like us,
who see education
as a calling, we often are.
That painting...
It's beautiful.
The samurai,
they were formidable foes.
They'd often make unstoppable enemies
to their opponents.
You wouldn't want to cross one.
So you spent time in Japan?
The feudal history of Medieval Japan,
it's one of my areas of expertise.
Then you must speak the language.
He also speaks French, Italian,
Mandarin, several other languages.
Here's the thing. I love teaching.
It gives me the opportunity
to broaden perspectives.
But you can't just inspire people
to be better.
You somehow need to change
the way people think.
Clifford. My husband is very passionate,
but also needs his rest.
Is there anything else
we can do to help?
No. Thank you. If we have any more
questions, we'll get in contact.
- Barr.
- Yeah.
You know where to find me.
Well? Is it him?
I don't know, Barr.
This shy college professor
who likes mac-and-cheese
doesn't exactly seem like
a criminal mastermind to me.
I mean, come on.
It wouldn't be the first time
somebody played nice, and then
turned out to be our bad guy.
The Council of Wells
gave us his name for a reason.
- They gave us one name out of...
- 1,100.
1,122, to be precise.
He was off by 22.
I mean, isn't that
a little suspicious?
Not if he Googled himself.
I'm just saying there's
something weird about this guy.
He likes samurai.
Who doesn't? Have you seen Zatoichi,
- The Blind Swordsman?
- ...The Blind Swordsman?
- Best Criterion collection.
- Great box set.
- Ever.
- Okay, think about this.
If the Council's right,
that means DeVoe arranged for me
to come out of the Speed Force
exactly where he wanted.
- Even you couldn't do that.
- You have a point.
- Okay, let's cover all our bases.
- Agreed.
Okay, Cisco, Harry, you guys
wanna see what kind of
digital footprint
you can get on this guy.
Caitlin, you've got friends at CCU.
Let's see what kind of person
we're dealing with.
- Will do.
- Dad, CCPD,
- background check.
- On it, sweet one.
And you...
- You all right?
- Yeah.
But thank you for asking.
You know, I think Human Resources
might not be okay with this,
us being co-workers and all...
Yeah. I think they'll let it slide,
considering I get to marry
the co-worker of my dreams
a week from now.
You know, sometimes I feel like...
- Like what?
- Like I'm the luckiest man alive.
Molecular physics,
condensed matter, cosmology,
even relativity, all these fields,
will be revolutionized overnight.
You've infused my design with life.
We still have a problem.
There's currently no way to power
a prototype this sophisticated...
We'll find a solution.
Expanding a mind
to an infinite capacity
requires an expanding energy source.
Where are we going to find
that kind of power?
- Can you tell us how?
- Turn that up.
It'll change the way we think about
science, about quantum mechanics,
about molecular physics. Once
my particle accelerator goes online
it'll blow the doors of science
off their hinges.
That's amazing.
We needed a power source
unlike anything imaginable.
Well... It seems
Harrison Wells just imagined it for us.
Instantly... Change lives.
History moves in cycles.
We must, therefore,
learn from what came before us
in order to carve a path
for what's to come.
Because those who don't learn from...
Because those who don't learn
from history are doomed to repeat it.
Class dismissed.
Don't forget your reading material.
Chapter 11,
on the counter-culture backlash
and its influence
on the Reagan Administration.
Mr. Allen... Twice in one day?
Yeah. I'm sorry to bother you again.
Look, I do have a stack
of mid-term exams...
Yeah, no. I understand you're busy.
This won't take long.
I just wanted to ask...
Where were you four years ago
on the night of January 7th?
Honestly, Mr. Allen, I have no idea.
How far back does this
investigation of yours go?
I'm not at liberty
to discuss that with you.
Also, do you ever use public transit?
What, like the subway?
I mean, imagine me in a wheelchair...
More like a bus.
Is this really necessary?
I'm just being thorough.
Fine. I prefer Lyft.
They're wheelchair friendly.
Honestly, Mr. Allen,
how are my vehicle options important,
or a date I can hardly remember?
I'm just trying to establish
a timeline and solve a mystery.
Mysteries are for novelists
and archaeologists.
You were supposed to be
ruling me out as a suspect.
Instead, it seems like
you've got your guy.
No. This is just procedure.
Feels like persecution.
Now, can I get back to you or do I
need to accompany you downtown?
No, of course not.
Just email me.
And again, I'm sorry to bother you.
So this is an example of meta DNA.
This is the DNA
you brought me from DeVoe.
It's completely normal.
Do you see all the differences?
Clifford DeVoe is not a meta.
Did you two find anything?
Well, he's never been arrested,
he pays all his taxes
and his mortgage,
he has a very reasonable 401k plan.
Donates to the Sierra Club,
volunteers at an orphanage,
is a Big Brother.
Dad didn't find anything either.
He says that he's an
upstanding member of the community.
Yeah, I talked
to some friends at Oxford.
They said DeVoe's
a little absent-minded,
but everybody likes him.
Guys, I'm telling you Clifford DeVoe,
he's not what he seems.
That could just be the wheelchair.
I mean,
- you do kinda have a bad history...
- No!
That wasn't me.
Come on. He's too perfect.
Okay, I just... I've a strong feeling
that he's hiding something.
You don't believe me.
No, it's not that
we don't believe you, Barry.
It's just... Right now,
DeVoe seems like a good guy.
Guys, it's him.
I thought we were done just
assuming people are villains.
All right, you know what? Vibe it.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Oh, my God!
You were right.
That mac-and-cheese
looks unbelievable.
See, that doesn't sound
very villainous, does it?
Barry, can I talk to you outside?
Okay, so do you wanna tell me
what's really bothering you?
My spidey sense is just tingling
way off the charts.
Barry, is there any chance
that this is about the wedding?
- I mean, maybe you're feeling...
- No, I'm not nervous.
But you're not acting
the way that you normally do.
Look, Savitar and Kadabra warned us
about someone named DeVoe.
This DeVoe guy
could be behind everything.
The bus metas. Me coming out
of the Speed Force
at the wrong place. The Samuroid.
Barry, is there a possibility
that you were so determined
to find the bad guy
and get ahead of everything
that you're seeing things
exactly the way you wanna see them?
No, I...
Maybe. I don't know...
Look. In seven days, I am going
to marry the man that I love.
But right now I have to lock down
a new DJ,
because the last one got fired
for drinking too much
and wouldn't stop dancing
with the father of the bride.
Joe might be into that actually.
Which is exactly why
I need to go home.
And I would really like your help.
Ready for the press conference?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Thank you.
My name is Harrison Wells.
Tonight... The future begins.
The work my team and I will do here
will change our understanding
of physics, will bring about
advancements in power,
advancements in medicine,
it'll bring about advancements.
Period. This is the future.
And trust me, it'll be here
faster than you think.
What does it mean to you?
Hey! My laptop.
It's got my dissertation!
Well, it would appear
tonight's entertainment
is not limited to the stage.
What's the first thing you'll do
once the accelerator is online?
Crack open an expensive bottle
of Dom Perignon with my staff.
I ride them very hard,
and they've earned it. Yes?
Those protesting this accelerator
believe it could
open a black hole in Central City.
But is it not more likely to cause
a benevolent phenomenon
like a Higgs-Boson bridge?
The only phenomenon
that will occur this evening
is one that has been calculated
to the tiniest detail
to the tiniest decimal point.
So you've foreseen
every possible outcome?
Yes, I have, Miss...
Mrs. Marlize DeVoe.
DeVoe...
DeVoe.
I expect that would make the
gentleman to your right
your husband.
Clifford DeVoe.
I'm a big fan of your work.
Sir, I believe it'll have
an enormous impact on our future.
Thank you for coming.
And, Professor... Good luck.
Wells is lying.
He knows
the accelerator won't succeed.
He'd risk an explosion?
No. I think he wants one.
Only the fallout from dark matter
being released into the atmosphere
will produce variants
we cannot yet predict.
We need to delay our plan.
No. This is even better.
We'll have all the power we need.
No, it's too risky.
I'm willing to take the chance.
The blast is the only thing
that can power the cap.
We should wait.
Try and find another way.
This is the only way.
Shut it down! Shut it down!
Ready, my love?
In position.
Shut it down! Shut it down!
It's starting.
What's happening?
Clifford!
Clifford! No... No, no.
Don't you dare leave me.
I thought I'd lost you.
How do you feel?
Enlightened.
Hey, Allen. Singh wants to see you.
One second.
I don't know, Allen.
Singh's making that face again.
You might wanna hurry.
Trust me, I understand.
- Mr. Allen.
- What's this?
- Close the door, please.
- Yeah.
Continue, Professor.
First my home, then my classroom.
What's next,
our bedroom where we sleep?
Joe and I just wanted...
On behalf of the Central City
Police Department,
I'd like to extend our sincerest
apologies for this intrusion.
Mr. Allen?
Yeah, I'm sorry
for disturbing you, Mr. DeVoe.
Professor DeVoe.
Thank you for coming in.
What the hell were they doing here?
They just filed
a complaint against you.
Said you harassed them.
No, I wasn't harassing them.
Why are you bothering them at all?
It's a case we're working on.
What case?
- It's something that...
- Do me a favor.
Stay away from the nice professor
and his wife.
Captain, DeVoe seems very...
Very what?
And unless the answer is
"guilty of a very specific crime,"
you are way off base.
So are you, Joe.
You should know better than that.
We don't just show up at someone's
house and start asking questions.
We follow protocol.
Anybody home?
Hey.
Hi. Dad said
you were having a bad day, so...
What? No. I'm fine. I'm great,
actually. How are you doing?
What?
What are you...
What is this?
His wife, Iris. She's helping him.
No, listen. Okay, look.
She's not Susie Homemaker with her
perfect mac-and-cheese,
she's a Stepford wife.
She's got two doctorates, you know?
One in mechanical engineering
and another in advanced robotics.
That's how they work.
He comes up with the plans,
but she executes them.
She's some kind of mechanical genius.
So you think DeVoe
and his wife are super-villains?
- Yes.
- Listen to yourself, Barry.
What?
DeVoe's already filed
a complaint against you.
I know, I...
Look. Cisco, Harry,
my Dad, Caitlin...
They're the best and they have
found nothing on DeVoe.
We're getting married
in a week, Barry.
Please, for the sake
of your job and my sanity,
please, let it go.
I've solved them.
Solved what?
Riemann's Hypothesis,
Hilbert's Fifteenth Problem.
The Standard Conjectures on Algebraic
Cycles, and the list goes on.
Clifford, this is incredible.
Ask me anything.
Who was Jack the Ripper?
The prevailing theory
is there was a London barber
by the name Aaron Kosminski
who committed the crimes.
He also suffered schizophrenic
and delusional tendencies.
But...
It was his nurse at the Colney Hatch
Asylum, Catherine Jewell.
It's like every little bit
of knowledge now
resides inside my brain.
I know every answer
to every question ever asked.
You're incredible.
We're incredible.
You made all this possible.
We now finally have
the means to bring to the world...
Clifford, are you okay? Clifford.
Clifford... Clifford.
What are you hiding, DeVoe?
Imagine your body is a river.
There's a dam blocking your legs.
My gastrocnemius muscles
are degenerating, aren't they?
Well, yes.
- The symptoms are similar to...
- Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis.
But your muscles are decaying faster
and more rapidly than typical ALS.
I believe this is something else.
Is that your medical diagnosis?
That I have a case of something else?
It's just, we've never seen
a case like yours before.
An increase in complex
fasciculation potential
explains the axonal membrane
hyperexcitability, but it doesn't...
Of course.
When gamma wave activity
exceeds 50 hertz,
my acetylcholine receptors draw away
from my nerve receptors
instead of toward them.
What did you say
you're a professor of?
History.
What's his prognosis?
Life expectancy for typical ALS
is about two to five years.
In this chrono dispersion,
it'll be half that.
Complete paralysis will come first.
Excuse us, please.
This doesn't make sense.
My mind is drawing energy
from my body.
Like a parasite feeding
on an ailing host.
We're so close to everything
we've ever dreamed of,
only for it to be ripped away
by this body.
No, no, no...
We can stop this, Clifford.
I'll never give up.
2,600 individuals
developed the meta gene
and they use it to rob jewelry stores
and summon tornadoes.
I use mine to save humanity
and I'm condemned?
Dying wasn't part of our plan.
Guys, I found a camera
in the Samuroid head.
Where did it lead back to?
Where do you think?
DeVoe.
So, you pinged the camera to his
computer's IP address? Good.
Well, no, I didn't ping it.
Well, then, how did you
figure out it was him?
- Well...
- This camera isn't even active.
No. I heard it.
It was making a noise.
- Noise?
- Yeah.
Inside the Samuroid head.
It was buzzing and then
I found that thing inside.
He's been watching us for weeks.
And I could've proved it,
but his wife came back too soon.
Too soon? From where?
- I don't...
- Barry...
Tell me you did not
break into their house.
Well...
- Wow, okay.
- No.
Guys... No, that sounds bad.
You have to listen to me.
This guy wants us to think
he's unassuming and weak.
But he's not.
He's powerful and smart.
And he's been ahead of us
every step of the way.
- He's ahead of us right now.
- Easy, Allen. Calm down.
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Hey. We just don't want you to do
anything else you'll regret.
Anything else?
What do you mean? What have I done?
For starters, breaking and entering.
Oh, my God! I don't understand
why you don't see what's going on.
He probably has cameras everywhere.
At the lab, at CCPD.
I mean, he's always watching us.
Hey, Joe. What is it?
- Hey, I found something.
- Barr, stop.
I just don't feel safe anymore,
you know?
I mean, I thought the police
were supposed to protect people.
I haven't done anything to you.
You broke into our home.
We're good people.
We don't deserve this.
I don't want you to worry anymore.
Mr. Allen will stop all of this
immediately, I assure you.
Stay away from us.
I told you to stay away
from those people.
Captain, you have to listen to me...
You're taking two weeks off.
And that is not a request.
You're suspending me?
You're lucky I'm not arresting you.
Use your time away to consider
your future in law enforcement.
- What is this?
- A restraining order.
I have to stay 500 feet away
from Clifford DeVoe.
And are you going to?
Barry.
This is not you. You've gotta stop.
- I can't.
- You can't or you won't?
I don't know anymore.
I've faced a lot of bad guys.
People that would hurt
the ones that I love,
destroy everything good in the world,
and think nothing of it.
But this guy, he feels more dangerous
than all the others combined.
And we still barely know
anything about him.
It scares the hell out of me, Iris.
Barry, how many times have we been
up against the unknown?
- This is different.
- How?
Ever since I came back
from the Speed Force,
I have been constantly
and genuinely happy.
My friends are safe.
Joe is going to be a dad again.
And, next week, I get to
marry the love of my life.
I have more to lose now
than ever before.
Yeah, but... What about
after Cecile has the baby?
Or after we get married? Or...
Even when we have our first child?
You know, as time goes by, there's
gonna be even more for us to lose.
And people are always
gonna be coming after us.
You can't let that consume you.
You just have to live in the moment
and face it as it comes.
How are you not scared?
Because we're the Flash.
Clifford? Clifford. Clifford.
Get away from me.
I'm trying to help you.
If you really wish to help, construct
a temporal vortex distortion chamber
and prevent me from ever
becoming this atrocity.
This is what we wanted.
I cannot grab a damn book
from the shelf!
What am I, Marlize?
You are my husband.
Your husband is gone.
No.
Let me die.
I'm not going anywhere.
This body will expire.
It will last longer with this.
You are in violation
of a restraining order, Mr. Allen.
Well, you could call the cops.
Do you intend to harm me?
Then pray, do tell,
what is so paramount
that you'd risk incarceration?
I wanted to look you
in the eyes and ask...
Who are you, really?
Who's asking?
Barry Allen...
Or the Flash?
- How did you...
- Oh, please.
Your little secret was one
of the more underwhelming revelations
I have uncovered.
I was born the same evening you were,
January 7th.
The night S.T.A.R. Labs'
particle accelerator
bathed Central City
in gene-altering dark matter.
We were both struck by lightning.
I knew you were affected.
How did our tests
not show your meta DNA?
For such a fast man,
you're rather slow.
I'm smarter than you.
You and your "science team"
have devised no strategy, no action,
no coordinated effort
for which I'm not already prepared.
The Samuroid.
The bus metas. It was you.
But why reveal yourself now?
Because I have nothing
to fear from you.
Yeah? I'd think twice about that.
I have a team of some
of the smartest minds from across
- the multiverse.
- Yes.
Your Council of Wells.
Could any one of those clowns
identify what my abilities are?
You could gather every genius
on every planet
and you still couldn't out-think me.
Plenty of metas have come after me,
the people that I love. You know
the one thing they have in common?
They failed.
You've done wonders all these years
punching gorillas
with rudimentary powers.
Chasing mad men shooting icicles.
Those were children with
play guns. Savitar. Zoom. Thawne.
Their powers are nothing compared
to the power of limitless thought.
That's your ability.
Your intellect was amplified
by the particle accelerator.
You may be
the fastest man alive, Allen,
I'm the fastest mind.
So this is how we begin whatever
twisted game you have planned.
No, Mr. Allen. You've already lost
and you never even realized it.
Congratulations on
your upcoming nuptials.
I'll be thinking of you.
There is something
I need to tell you.
I confronted DeVoe.
Oh, come on! Barry,
he could get you arrested.
No. He won't. He wanted me to come.
How do you know?
Well, for starters,
he knows I'm the Flash.
So, you were right all along.
We didn't believe you.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
DeVoe's been playing all of us.
How?
It's his powers. He has
an intelligence beyond anything
we could have imagined.
He's orchestrated everything
that we've encountered.
He's moved us like chess pieces
in a game we didn't even know
we were playing.
How do we stop someone
who has super intelligence?
We're pretty smart.
Maybe we're not.
The Thinker.
It's good. Apt sense of menace.
Nailed it in one.
Guys, it's gonna take all of us
to stop him.
Sounds like y'all could use a hand.
Wally!
- Good to see you, Son.
- You, too.
How was Blue Valley?
Self-reflection and a battle
with a starfish from outer space
gives you perspective.
So you found
what you were looking for?
I don't know, to be honest.
Well, we are glad you're home.
Looks like you found
the guy behind the bus metas.
Yeah.
So, you wanna suit up, take him down?
No. Now, it's his move.
But I think we take our time.
Formulate a plan.
What now, boss lady?
We get married.
He came to you.
Just like you said he would.
He's finally seized control
of his fear.
He drew his strength
from those he calls "friends."
Sounds like you admire him.
It is fascinating. In the chain
of 4,900 possible events I predicted,
there was one which resulted
in them calling me "The Teacher."
I prefer "The Thinker."
They will be the first to experience
the enlightenment.
You've been unplugged for too long.
I'm nothing without you.
Proceed.
Your body's deteriorating faster
than the chair can handle.
It will survive long enough.
You're really gonna let them
get married?
What is knowledge without love?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::