Five, four, three, two, one.
Ready or not, here I come.
[TV playing indistinctly]
-[hinges squeak]
-[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[clattering]
[window banging]
Hey, Dad?
Dad!
[thunder rumbling]
[speaking indistinctly]
You're gonna stay with Aunt May
and Uncle Ben for a little while.
-I want to go with you.
-No.
Doesn't like crust on his sandwiches.
[sobs]
And he likes to sleep with
a little light on at night.
-[Richard] Mare, come on.
-Oh, God.
[Richard clears throat]
Dad.
Be good.
[thunder crashes]
[school bell ringing]
[boys laughing]
Sorry.
Morning, Flash.
Good morning, Parker.
Hey. It's, uh… It's Peter, right?
-Mm-hmm.
-I really like your photos.
-Oh, thanks. Thanks.
-Uh, listen, are...
Are you busy Friday night?
Uh…
[laughs] Cool.
Uh, can you take pictures
of my boyfriend's car?
I just-- You know, I really want
to frame a good one for his birthday.
That's really nice of you.
Wow, that's such a nice thought.
Um, yeah, I'll have
a look at the old, uh--
-The old schedule.
-Okay.
-[teacher] Parker.
-Yes, sir?
Want to keep that skateboard?
-Yeah.
-Keep it off the ground.
-Sure. Yeah.
-Wheels up.
Like that?
-[teacher] That's it.
-Okay.
[shutter clicks]
[students chanting]
Eat it! Eat it! Eat it! Eat it! Eat it!
-[chanting continues]
-Eat your vegetables, Gordon. Come on!
Come on! Hey, Parker, come on.
Get a picture of this. Come on.
I'm not going to take a picture.
Put him down.
-Come on.
-Put him down, man.
Gordon, don't eat it. Don't eat it.
-Take the picture, Parker.
-Put him down, Flash.
-[chanting continues]
-[Flash] Take the picture.
Put him down,
Eugene!
-[students groan]
-Whoa!
Hey, man.
[students gasping]
Come on! Get up, Parker!
-[groans]
-Get up! Come on!
-[student] Get up, Parker.
-Come on!
[students groan]
[breathless]
I'm still not taking the picture.
Stay down, Parker!
Who wants one more?
-One more! Huh? Huh?
-Flash!
Flash, we still on for after school today?
My house, 3:30?
I hope you've been doing your homework.
Last time, I was very disappointed in you.
No, Flash, how about we go to class?
-Hmm? How about it?
-[school bell ringing]
[Flash] Whatever.
[grunts]
[panting]
[all chattering]
I thought that was great,
what you did out there.
It was stupid, but it was great.
You should probably go to the nurse.
You might have a concussion.
What's your name?
You don't know my name?
No, I know your name.
I just want to know if you know your name.
Peter.
-Parker. Peter Parker.
-Okay. Okay, good.
I'd still go to the nurse, though.
-You're Gwen, right?
-Gwen Stacy.
[whispers] All right.
[Peter] Hey.
I'm making spaghetti
and meatballs tonight.
You're serious? Spaghetti and meatballs.
Since when don't you like
spaghetti and meatballs, huh?
-Oh, my God.
-What's up?
-What happened to your face?
-Oh, I'm all right.
Just-- I fell, skating.
-It's all right.
-Oh.
[grunting]
Ben Parker, don't you even think about
leaving that filthy box in my kitchen.
-These are my bowling trophies.
-[May] Oh. Then, by all means,
please leave that filthy box
in my kitchen.
-What happened to you?
-[May] He fell.
Why you kids ride those things,
I'll never know.
'Cause it's stupid and dangerous.
Remember when we were stupid
and dangerous?
-No.
-Trust me, we were.
[Peter chuckles] Good to know.
Hey, where's the flood?
-[Ben] Follow me. I'll show you.
-[Peter] You serious?
-[Ben] Yes.
-All right.
[Ben] I think it's the condenser tray.
[Peter] No, too much water
for the condenser tray
or the heat exchange tubing.
This has got to be the fill line.
That's the only thing
that makes any sense. [chuckles]
Can you fix it?
No, not tonight. I'll go by
the hardware store tomorrow.
Good deal. And meanwhile,
put this on your face.
[chuckles]
How's the other guy look?
Come on. I know a right cross
when I see one.
Yes or no. Do I have
to call somebody's father?
-No, no.
-All right.
Well, I wouldn't tell your Aunt May.
I pity the poor kid
who'd have to suffer her wrath.
Hey, before you come up,
see if there's anything else worth saving.
[Peter] Okay.
[clattering]
[Ben] Plumbers don't fix appliances.
-[May] Yes, they fix appliances.
-[Ben] They fix pipes and pump things.
If you ask them to--
I forgot all about that thing.
It was your dad's.
-[Peter] Yeah.
-He asked us to keep it safe for him.
-[Ben chuckles]
-[dish clatters]
He saw it in the window of that leather
shop over on Ninth Avenue.
He was 19. What does a 19-year-old kid
need with a briefcase?
-And guess who sold it to him.
-[mouths] I don't know.
Your mother. That's how they met.
He asked you to keep this safe? Why?
There's nothing in here. Have you looked
in here? There's nothing here.
Your father was
a very secretive man, Peter.
[laughs] Yeah, I know.
Who's that?
Do you know who that is?
Some guy who worked
with your dad, I guess.
Just take this off the table,
all right? We're going to eat. Off.
-And wash your hands now.
-All right.
Go on.
[Richard]
I need you to be a good boy, Peter.
-Where are you going?
-There's something, uh…
something your mom and I have to do.
[object clunking]
[sliding and clunking]
[click]
[beeping and whirring]
What is this?
"Zero, zero, Decay Rate Algorithm."
[knock on door]
Yeah, one sec, one sec.
[clears throat]
[computer beeps]
Come in.
-You okay?
-Yeah. What's up?
Oh, my God. You look just like him.
-Can I come in?
-Yeah.
[chuckles] Listen, um…
I don't have much education.
You know that, Peter.
Hell, I stopped being able to help
with your homework when you were 10.
What I'm trying to say is, uh…
I know it's been rough
for you without your dad.
And I know we don't talk much about them.
-Yeah, it's all right.
-No, it is not all right.
I wish I could change it, but I can't.
Curt Connors.
That's the name of the guy
in the picture with your dad.
They worked together for years,
and they were close.
But after that night,
we never saw him again.
He never even called. Not once.
Go figure.
She's pretty.
-Uncle Ben.
-What?
You're a pretty great dad, all right?
[typing rapidly]
[all chattering]
-Excuse me.
-What?
-Can I help you?
-Oh, uh…
I don't know. I'm here to see Dr. Connors.
Right. You'll find yourself to the left.
You are here for the internship?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Okay.
-You'll find your badge to the left.
-Oh.
-Are you having trouble finding yourself?
-No.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay, Mr. Guevara.
-Gracias.
-De nada.
[host on recording] Welcome to Oscorp.
Born from the mind
of our founder, Norman Osborn,
the Oscorp Tower houses
108 floors of innovation.
Our scientific minds
are pushing the boundaries
of defense, biomedical,
and chemical technologies.
The future lies within.
Welcome to Oscorp. My name's Gwen Stacy.
I'm a senior at Midtown Science,
and I'm also head intern to Dr. Connors.
So, I'll be with you for
the duration of your visit.
Where I go, you go. That's the basic rule.
-If you remember that, all will be fine.
-[Rodrigo] What's wrong with you?
-And if you forget that--
-[Rodrigo] Listen!
Listen. Tell them Rodrigo Guevara
is down here.
Please, just tell them
Rodrigo Guevara is down here!
My name's Rodrigo!
Well, I guess I don't need to tell you
what happens if you forget that.
Shall we?
Come around this way.
-Good afternoon, Gwen.
-Dr. Connors.
Welcome. My name is Dr. Curtis Connors.
And yes, in case you're wondering,
I'm a southpaw.
-[all laugh]
-I'm not a cripple, I'm a scientist,
and I'm the world's foremost
authority on herpetology.
That's reptiles, for those
of you who don't know.
But like the Parkinson's patient
who watches on in horror
as her body slowly betrays her,
or the man with macular degeneration
whose eyes grow dimmer each day,
I long to fix myself.
I want to create a world without weakness.
Anyone care to venture a guess just how?
-Yes.
-Stem cells?
Promising. But the solution I'm thinking
of is more radical.
-No one?
-[Peter] Cross-species genetics.
[interns murmuring]
Person gets Parkinson's
when the brain cells
that produce dopamine start to disappear.
But a zebra fish has the ability
to regenerate cells on command.
If you could somehow give this ability
to the woman you're talking about,
that's that. She's…
She's curing herself.
[intern] Yeah, you just have
to look past the gills on her neck.
-[other interns laughing]
-Shh.
Heh. A-And you are?
He's one of Midtown Science's
best and brightest.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm. He's second in his class.
-Oh.
-Second?
Yeah.
You sure about that?
-I'm pretty sure.
-[cell phone ringing]
-[beep]
-I'm afraid duty calls.
I'll leave you in the more-than-capable
hands of Miss Stacy.
Nice meeting you all.
If you'd like to gather round.
[film narrator]
Welcome to Oscorp's tree of life.
Our planet's tree of life is immense.
At Oscorp's Cross-Species Division…
-Hi.
-…we endeavor to explore new methods…
[clears throat]
What are you doing, Rodrigo?
-Oh, yeah.
-What are you doing here?
I work here.
I don't work here.
I was gonna say I work here,
but it seems like you, in fact, do,
so you know that I don't work here.
Are you following me?
No, I'm not following you, no.
I'm not. I had no idea you worked here.
-Then why would you be here?
-I just snuck in because I…
I love science.
You love science.
-I'm passionate about it.
-So you snuck in?
-I have to lead this tour group.
-I know.
So I'll ask you more about this later.
Do not get me in trouble.
-I promise you I won't.
-Stay with the group.
All right. Guys?
I'm gonna take you
to the bioreactor room now.
[Peter] Sorry. Yo.
Sorry.
[lock clicks]
[chattering]
[mechanism whirring]
[latch clicks]
[low whirring]
[rumbling]
[mechanism whirring]
[gasping]
We received the results
from the mRNA sequences this morning.
They were disappointing.
So, define "disappointing."
Another dead end.
It's the decay rate algorithm.
-And this is to be expected.
-Expected? You said you were close.
We are close, but it's gonna take time.
[visitor] He doesn't have time.
Norman Osborn is dying, Dr. Connors.
Save him.
Or we'll both lose our heads.
[chuckles]
All right, give me the badge.
Aw.
Give it to me.
[spider chittering]
Sorry.
[yelps]
[car horns honking]
[passengers chattering]
[heart beating]
[yelps, grunts]
Disgusting. Now I smell like beer.
Uh, sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't mean to…
I didn't… I didn't…
Get your hand off her.
-I'm trying to get my--
-[onlooker 1] Yo, man.
-[laughing]
-Are you kidding?
-I'm sorry.
-Are you freakin' kidding me?
-[onlooker 1] Hey, get him, Rudy!
-Hey!
[groans]
Man, I'm sorry!
Oh, man, are you all right?
[onlooker 2] Take him down!
-[attackers grunting]
-[bystander yelping]
No, man, no. Not my board.
-Please, dude, don't--
-[yelling]
[Peter] Sorry!
Sorry. Sorry. Oh.
-[attackers groaning]
-I'm so sorry.
[conductor on PA] Coney Island, next stop.
Next and final stop, Coney Island.
[sirens wailing]
[dog barking in distance]
-[door opens, closes]
-Uh, hey. Hey. Hey.
-Sorry. I'm late. I got--
-We've been so worried.
-I know. I'm sorry. Watch out!
-[fly buzzing]
That's a fly, Peter.
[fly buzzing]
-Yeah.
-[fly buzzing]
I'm so sorry I kept you guys up.
I'm insensitive. I'm irresponsible.
[whispers] And I'm hungry.
Drinking?
-[Peter] What's this?
-I don't think so.
This is your meat loaf.
[chuckles]
This beats all other meat loafs.
Something is very wrong.
Yeah.
Nobody likes your meat loaf.
I got it.
He took the frozen macaroni and cheese.
I noticed that.
Why didn't you tell me
-you didn't like my meat loaf?
-Um…
You could have said that
to me 37 years ago.
How many meat loaves have I made for you?
[water running]
[sighs]
[groans]
[birds chirping]
[alarm clock beeping]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[blinds rattling]
-[clicking]
-[squishing]
-Peter.
-Hmm?
What are you doing up there?
I'm, uh…
Homework.
Be careful.
Sure.
[doorbell rings]
[Peter] Dr. Connors.
Uh…
-You don't remember me. I, uh…
-You're the intern from the other day.
Yeah, yeah. That's right, yeah.
I'm sure you're a very nice young man,
but this is a home.
I'll ask you to make an appointment
with my office.
I'm Richard Parker's son.
Peter?
I'm afraid I can't help you much, Peter.
I don't know why they left
or where they were going.
Good reflexes.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I read your book.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
It's something, you know.
So you really think it's possible,
-cross-species genetics?
-Yes, of course.
But for years, your father and I were
mocked for our theories.
Not just in the community at large,
but at Oscorp, as well.
They called us mad scientists.
And then your father bred the spiders,
and everything changed.
The results were beyond encouraging.
They were spectacular.
We were gonna change
the lives of millions.
Including my own.
Then it was over.
He…
He was gone.
Took his research with him.
And I knew without him, I…
I…
I was angry.
So I stayed away from you and your family.
And for that, I'm truly sorry.
Say…
Say it worked. Say y-you got it to work.
Like, how much would
the foreign species take over?
What could the side effects be?
It's hard to say,
considering no subject survived.
-The problem was always--
-The decay rate algorithm?
-Right.
-Can I, uh…
-[Connors] Of course.
Extraordinary.
How did you come up with this?
[chuckles]
Peter, how would you feel
about coming to see me at the Tower,
-one day after school?
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-[whistle blows]
-[coach] Number one. Run it, buddy.
[student] Let's go, Reggie.
Rejected!
You did that on purpose, Flash!
No, but I should have.
You better watch your back.
Hey.
All right?
Give it up, Parker.
[player 1] Come on, man.
Oh. One sec.
Why don't you take it from me?
[onlooker] Whoa.
[player 1] That's right, Flash.
Take it, man.
Go ahead. Take it.
[students murmuring and laughing]
Just take it.
All right, how about this?
All right?
How about that?
[player 1] Come on, Flash.
-[player 2] Come on, Flash. Do something.
-[player 1] Stop playing, man.
-[player 3] Take it from him!
-Come on, Flash. Take it.
[player 2] Yo, Flash. Let's go.
-[player 1] Let's go!
-[player 3] Do it. Stop playin'.
[player 4] Let's go, Flash! Come on!
[players grumbling]
What you doing, man?
All right, bring it! Come on,
Parker! Come on!
[cheerleaders scream]
[principal] Peter's behavior is just
completely unacceptable.
They're not gonna make us pay
for the backboard, you know that.
I don't care about the backboard.
-Was that true?
-What?
What I heard in there just now.
Did you humiliate that boy?
Yeah, I did. [sighs] But…
-But what?
-This guy, this guy deserved it.
-Did he?
-Yeah.
Is he the kid that hit you?
Is he?
Yeah, yeah, but…
So all this is about getting even.
If so, I guess you must feel pretty good
about yourself now, right?
Am I right or wrong?
[sighs]
Yeah, I thought so.
Well, thanks to this
little escapade of yours,
I had to change shifts at work.
So, you have to pick up
Aunt May tonight at 9:00.
Understood?
-Is that understood?
-Yeah, yeah.
Okay, good.
She looks familiar.
She's the girl on your computer, yeah.
He's got you on his computer.
I'm his probation officer.
Don't forget Aunt May.
[laughs] Okay.
He's a character. That's my-- my uncle.
He's a pathological liar.
He thought you were someone else.
Oh, man, you don't have me
on your computer?
I took a photo of the debate
team and you're on the team, so…
-Right.
-So he must have seen--
Um, I-- Because I was touching up stuff.
-You were touching up stuff?
-[laughs] Come on.
I was, I was... I'm not
going to answer that.
[both laugh]
Did you get expelled?
No. No, I didn't get expelled.
I got community service.
Um, so, uh, you want to, uh, I don't know…
Um...
-Want to what?
-I don't know.
Just, uh…
Um…
I don't know, we could--
I don't know, we could, uh…
Or we could do something else,
or we could…
-If you don't feel like-- We could--
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, either one.
-Really?
-Sure.
Okay. All right, good. Sounds good.
Cool.
Okay.
-I-- You know, I can't right now.
-Yeah, no.
-I'm so busy right now.
-I know, me too. Ugh. [laughs]
But, uh, maybe, uh…
-Yeah, just, you know…
-Some other…
-Time, all right.
-[Peter laughs] Okay.
-Bye.
-All right.
[grunts]
[yelling]
Whoa! Whoo!
[gasps]
[whoops]
[Connors]We have protein structure,
rDNA, chromatography,
transgenics testing-- That's X-ray video.
That's the only one on the planet.
We have, um,
-human line testing over--
-I remember that.
-[Peter] I've seen that before.
-The Ganali device.
[Peter] Yeah, I remember
a picture of that in my dad's office.
The idea was so simple.
Load it with an antigen.
It creates a cloud, which can be dispersed
over a neighborhood, even an entire city.
Theoretically, you could
cure polio in an afternoon.
-[Peter] It's incredible.
-[Connors] Well, others disagreed.
You know, what if the device
were loaded with a toxin?
What if you wanted to opt out?
You can't run away from a cloud,
after all, so here it lies,
gathering dust.
What you see here is
a computer model of a lizard.
Now, many of these wonderful creatures
have so brilliantly adapted
that they can regenerate
entire limbs at will.
You can imagine my envy.
We're trying to harness this capability
and transfer it into our host subject,
Freddy the three-legged mouse.
Enter the algorithm now.
[cell phone rings]
-[cell phone rings]
-[Connors] Do you need to take that?
[cell phone rings]
[beeps]
[computer] System ready
for gene insertion.
[Peter] Okay.
Check.
See what I'm trying to do?
-[Connors] Preempt the proteins?
-[Peter] Preempt the immune response.
[computer] Beginning trials.
Pending... Pending...
Failed. Subject deceased.
-Come on, come on…
-[computer] Pending…
Failed. Pending. Failed. Pending.
Failed. Subject deceased. Pending.
Peptide algorithm accepted.
-Regrowth complete.
-Hey!
Vitals normal. Blood pressure normal.
Limb regeneration successful.
[Connors] Extraordinary.
[Peter chuckles]
And thank you.
Meet Fred and Wilma,
our three-legged mice.
Here you go.
Hey, buddy, I got you.
Okay.
Careful, don't want
to stick you by mistake.
Human trials aren't until next week.
[both chuckle]
There.
Hey.
Hey, I thought you, uh…
Didn't you forget something?
-What?
-[cell phone ringing]
Now, don't answer that,
but I'm glad to know it's working.
You owe your aunt an apology. Big-time.
Be a man, get in there and apologize.
I'm sorry, Aunt May, I…
Honestly, you don't have
to apologize to me.
-It's your unc--
-[Ben] The hell he doesn't.
Ben…
Look, I'm sorry, Uncle Ben.
I got distracted.
-I was at Oscorp.
-Oh, he got distracted.
-Yeah.
-Your aunt, my wife,
had to walk 12 blocks alone
in the middle of the night
and then wait in a deserted subway station
because you got distracted.
Ben, sweetheart, honestly.
I am completely capable
-of walking home by--
-You will not defend this boy!
-I'm not defen--
-You are defending him.
-Listen to me, son.
-Yeah, go ahead.
You're a lot like your father.
You really are, Peter,
and that's a good thing.
But your father lived by a philosophy--
A principle, really. He believed that
if you could do good things
for other people,
you had a moral obligation
to do those things.
That's what's at stake here.
Not choice.
Responsibility.
That is nice. That's-- that's great.
That's all well and good. So where is he?
-What?
-Where is he?
Where's my dad?
He didn't think it was his responsibility
to be here and tell me this himself?
Oh, come on, how dare you?
How dare I? How dare you?
Where you going?
Peter, come back here, please.
Ben, leave him alone for a while.
He'll be all right.
[glass crunches]
Peter!
Peter?
[cashier] It's $2.07.
[coin clinks]
Uh, it's $2.07.
Yeah. No, I know.
Yeah, you're holding up the line. No.
You can leave a penny,
you can't take a penny.
-What?
-You can leave a penny anytime,
you have to spend $10 to take a penny.
It's store policy.
You gonna pay? You're holding up my line.
-I don't have two cents.
-You can't afford your milk,
just step aside.
What, Daddy didn't give you
enough milk money today?
It's two cents.
We're talking about two cents.
Just step aside, kid.
Really?
[cashier muttering]
Yo, not cool, bro.
[car horn blares]
[cashier] Hey, man, stop!
Somebody stop that guy!
Hey, kid, little help?
Not my policy.
Somebody stop that dude!
Hey! Hey, stop!
-Somebody stop that dude!
-[woman gasps]
[woman gasps]
Hey!
[grunting]
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
[Peter] Oh, God, oh, God.
Uncle Ben, Uncle Ben.
Call an ambulance!
Someone call an ambulance!
Uncle Ben, Uncle Ben.
Oh, God, oh, my God…
[groaning]
Oh, God…
[panting]
No…
[sobbing]
Oh, Jesus.
Witnesses gave a description
to the sketch artist.
I need you to take a look.
No, I don't know him.
[officer]
I didn't expect you would, ma'am.
Homicide detectives are on it.
We'll see what they turn up.
[whispers] Okay.
Uh, can I-- Can I have that?
Sure.
There's one other thing.
He has a star tattooed on his left hand.
[sobbing]
[Ben on recording] Peter,
I know things have been difficult lately
and I'm sorry about that.
-I think I know what you're feeling.
-[phone beeps off]
[students chattering]
Hey, Parker.
Not today, Flash.
Hey, come on, man, I just want to talk.
-[students gasping]
-[panting]
It feels better, right?
Look, your uncle died.
I'm sorry. I get it.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
Peter…
[sirens wailing]
[people chattering]
-Listen, stay away from him, understand?
-[Peter] Hey!
-Stay away from Joey, understand me?
You like beating on girls?
You like beating on old men?
Hey, pal? Just keep on walking.
You're in the wrong place, buddy.
When was the last time you were in Queens?
I asked you a question, man.
-Nicky, no!
-That the gun?
You gonna kill me, too?
[victim screams] Hey! Stop it!
[Nicky] Hey, get off!
-[victim] Wait, oh, don't hit Nicky!
-[bystander] Back up!
[victim] This guy is crazy!
Get him!
[grunting]
-Get back here, man!
-Get him!
[thug] Follow him!
[thug] Go around, man! I'll follow you!
[thugs yelling in distance]
-Go, go, go!
-There he is!
[thug] Can't get away, man!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[officer]
He has a star tattooed on his left hand.
[gasping]
[grunts]
[thugs panting]
-Oh, yeah?
-[thug] Come on!
[Peter yelps]
[Nicky] I know what you look like!
You hear me?
I've seen your face!
[exhaling]
[sighs]
Is that all you got?
Just take it, take it.
[grunting]
[video narrator] Engineered from
genetically enhanced spiders,
Oscorp's BioCable tensile
strength is unparalleled.
We're just beginning
to understand all the potential
industrial applications.
A single pellet can safely store
several hundred meters
of the lightweight cable.
[yelps] Mother--
[grunts]
[exhales]
[gasps]
Whoo!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[police dispatcher] Attention, all units
in the confines of Precinct 13,
receiving a 10-30 on West 19th
Street and Broadway.
Assailant is Caucasian male,
mid-30s, 170 to 180 pounds,
shoulder-length blond hair.
Last seen on foot heading
eastbound on 19th Street.
[helicopter approaching]
[car horn honks]
-[Peter grunts]
-[civilian] Hey!
[groans]
[horns honking]
-You got a description?
-Well, no, he-- He wears a mask.
A mask?
Yeah. Most of his victims are suspects,
some of them with serious rap sheets.
They're calling him a vigilante.
-Okay, he's not a vigilante.
-[shrieks]
He's an anarchist.
[criminal] Help me, somebody! Arrest me!
-Please, get me out of here!
-[bystander] Hey, look!
[all chattering]
Spandex... Spandex...
Everything... Spandex.
[student] Extraordinary velocity vector
is a function of both mass
and acceleration.
Come on. You know better than anyone
that the weight of the bob
on any pendulum has
no effect on swing speed.
[student] It doesn't affect frequency,
but it's totally a factor in momentum.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Aunt May. Yeah.
Eggs? Organic, got it.
[lock beeps]
[beeping]
[latch clacks]
[sighs]
[rustling]
[clears throat] You know, in the future,
if you're gonna steal cars,
don't dress like a car thief, man.
What are you? You a cop?
Really? You seriously think I'm a cop?
Cop in a skin-tight red and blue suit?
You know, you're-- you're--
You've got a mind
of the true scholar, sir.
I-I was going more
for the guys who do the luge.
Good thinking. Good thinking.
Use the window. Get out the window.
There you go. You got it. Whoa.
Crotch!
-[thief] Just let me go.
-Is that a knife?
-Is that a real knife?
-Yes, it's a real knife.
-My weakness, it's small knives.
-Just let me go.
Anything but knives!
-Oh, it's so simple. That was cool.
-What the hell is this?
Webbing that I developed myself.
I don't think you really want to know.
Come on, let me go! [groans]
One second. Hold on, one second.
-Knock it off, man. No!
-[sneezes]
-Come on, let me go. Stop it!
-[laughs]
Dude, that isn't funny.
-It is kind of funny.
-Come on. Help!
-Shh.
-[muffled grunting]
[distant siren wailing]
-[groans]
-This could have gone a lot worse.
Now, hold still.
[muffled grunting]
-[siren wailing]
-Oh! Boys in blue here!
-Yo, I got him.
-Freeze!
-He's not going anywhere.
-You in the tights, don't move.
-You serious?
-Who are you?
No one seems to grasp
the concept of the mask.
Freeze!
I just did 80% of your job.
Huh? And that-- That's how you repay me?
[sirens wailing]
[officer] Hold it right there!
[horn honking]
[grunts]
Whoo-hoo!
All right, well, that was fun.
[horn honking]
-Bus! Hey, there, everybody.
-[woman screams]
-[horn honking]
-[driver] What are you doing?
Whoo!
Hey, watch out!
I'm swinging here, I'm swinging here.
[horns honking]
[Spider-Man whooping]
So, 38 of New York's finest
versus one guy in a unitard.
-Am I correct?
-[officers muttering]
You don't have to wait up
for me, you know.
-Yes, I do.
-No, you don't.
-Okay. [sighs]
-Where were you?
-I was out.
Did you get the eggs?
Nope. Forgot the eggs.
I'm going to get them now.
No, you most certainly will not.
Not at this hour.
Look at me, Peter.
Take off the damn hood and look at me.
[gasps]
Peter.
Where do you go? Who does this to you?
Please go to sleep, Aunt May.
Please tell me.
Aunt May, please,
please, please go to sleep.
I can't sleep.
Don't you understand? I can't sleep.
[kettle whistling]
[whistling stops]
Peter, listen to me.
Secrets have a cost. They're not for free.
Not now, not ever.
[Connors]
Cross-species genetics is finally working.
I've used the lizard DNA
to help Freddy regrow that limb.
[visitor] It's a miracle.
No, it's hard work and promise
and it's a step closer to the primate lab.
But he doesn't have time
for every little step.
-Little?
-I just mean he can't wait.
Well, he'll have to.
-Unless he wants to be a lab rat.
-That's not what I'm saying.
[Connors] So, what are you saying?
You have to start human trials.
-Now.
-No, I don't.
And no, I won't.
-Well, then he's going to die.
-People die.
Even Norman Osborn.
-We are not finished.
-Human trials?
Where on earth are you going to find
the people to volunteer?
For what? As far as anyone's concerned,
it's for a winter flu shot.
I might think the Veterans' Hospital
is a place to start.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I don't think I am.
It's a little late for shock
and indignation, Curt.
About 15 years late.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Richard Parker wore it well.
On you, it's a cheap suit. As it was then.
I had nothing to do with that.
Is that what you told his son Peter?
I don't know what you're saying.
You don't know, or you don't want to know?
I'll remind you what happened.
Richard Parker said just about the same
thing then that you are saying now.
The clock is ticking, Dr. Connors.
I, um…
I won't.
Fine.
The formula is ours now anyway.
Say good-bye to that arm
you have dreamed of.
I'm shutting you down.
Have your office cleared out
by the morning.
Your toys can be
taken away, too, you know.
Right, Freddy?
[all chattering]
-Hey.
-Hi.
-How's it going?
-Where you headed?
-Uh, Monday, B track.
-Oh, it's Thursday.
-It's Thursday?
-What happened to your eye?
What?
-Your eye. It looks bruised.
-Oh, yeah, yeah, no, I don't…
Maybe I got a rash or…
It's pretty bad.
Have you gone to the nurse?
Mm-hmm.
Do you like branzino?
-Like, a fish?
-Mm-hmm. No, no. I know. I know.
Well, if you want,
you can come to this address
at, uh, 8:00 tonight.
My mom's making branzino. So…
Oh, it's apartment 2016.
I didn't write that part down.
I don't know why I… [laughs]
-I can remember it.
-Oh, okay.
-[school bell ringing]
-2016.
[groans]
[grunting]
[tapping quietly]
Hi. [laughs]
How did you get out there?
Uh, the fire escape.
Your doorman's intimidating.
[Gwen] It's 20 stories.
Yeah. It's all right.
-This is your room.
-Yes, this is my room.
Books.
-Shoes.
-[laughs]
Oh, hey, uh…
I got your mom, uh, these.
-Oh, lovely.
-Yeah, they're beautiful, right?
-They're beautiful.
-They were… They were nice.
No, they're beautiful.
-I'm sorry.
-No, it's impressive.
They actually held together very well.
-I'm gonna keep these.
-[laughs]
You have your suit in there?
My suit?
It's for dinner.
Are you going to wear that?
-That's, um…
-Hey, hon.
-You must be Peter.
-Dad, this is Peter.
Hey. Nice to meet you, sir.
Nice to meet you. Dinner's ready.
-Hope you like branzino.
-Who doesn't?
-[sizzles]
-[gasps, laughs]
Emma, it's Curt.
-Is he there?
-[Emma] I'm afraid not, Doctor.
The car is taking him
to the Veterans Hospital in Brooklyn.
No, no, no, no. He can't, Emma.
You-- You-- You have to stop him. He--
[Emma] I would, but I always lose him
when he's on the bridge.
I'll make sure Dr. Ratha
returns your call as soon as possible.
[groaning]
[panting]
I'm going to Holton Avenue,
across the river. I'm in a hurry.
[cabbie] Okay, you want me
to take the tunnel or the bridge?
-Bridge! Take the bridge.
-All right, we're gonna do that.
-Hey, man, you all right back there?
-[groaning]
-Are you tweaking, man?
-[panting]
-[growls] Just drive.
-Okay.
[tires screech]
[all chattering]
You're having trouble there, aren't you?
The head goes on the other--
Simon, help Gwen's friend with his fish.
-Oh, I… I got no idea.
-First time.
-[whispering] Branzino.
-George, tell us about your day.
Oh, yeah, Dad.
Did you catch that spider guy yet?
No, we didn't catch him yet. But we will.
He's an amateur who's assaulting civilians
in the dead of night.
He's clumsy, he leaves clues,
but he's still dangerous.
He's assault-- He's assaulting people?
I'm not sure. I mean, I saw that video
with him and the car thief,
and I think most people
would say that he was
providing a public service.
Most people would be wrong.
If I wanted the car thief off the street,
he'd already be off the street.
So, why wasn't he, then?
[laughs awkwardly]
Let me illuminate you.
See, the car thief was leading us to
the people who run the entire operation.
It's been a six-month-long sting.
This is called strategy.
I'm sure you're aware
of the term "strategy."
You've probably heard
about that in school?
-Yeah.
-Good.
[mouthing] I know.
Well, obviously,
he didn't know you had a plan.
[stutters] You seem to know an awful lot
about this case.
You know something that we don't know?
I mean, whose side are you on here?
I'm not on anyone's side.
I saw a video on the Internet--
Oh. You saw the video on the Internet.
Well, then the case is closed.
[Peter] Well, no, I'm just saying,
if you watch the video--
Maybe I should send you a link?
It looks like he's really trying to help.
Yeah, sure. On the Internet,
he's being made out
to look like
some kind of masked hero or something.
No, no. I'm not saying he's a hero.
I don't think he's a hero at all.
-What are you trying to say?
-I'm saying, he's trying to help,
that it looks like he's trying
to do something maybe the police can't.
Something the police can't?
-I don't know.
-What do you think we do all day?
Think we just sit around eating doughnuts,
with our thumbs planted
firmly up our asses?
-[Mrs. Stacy] George.
-Daddy.
[George]
That what you think we do down there?
-Up your what, Dad?
-Howard.
I think he stands
for what you stand for, sir.
Protecting innocent people from bad guys.
I stand for law and order, son.
That's what I stand for, okay?
I wear a badge.
This guy wears a mask like a…
You know, like an outlaw.
He's hunting down a bunch of criminals
that all look the same,
like he's got some sort
of personal vendetta.
But he's not protecting
innocent people, Mr. Parker.
Let's get some air, Peter.
-Dad, we need to talk.
-[George] Yes, we do.
Thank you for having me.
I'm sorry if I insulted you.
That was not my intention.
You're welcome.
Branzino was real good, Mrs. Stacy.
Thank you.
[Mrs. Stacy] You're welcome.
-[Simon] Dad.
-[George] Yeah?
[sighs]
[Gwen] Well, that was something.
[chuckles]
I'm sorry. You know I thought he was
going to arrest me at one point?
Nah, I wouldn't have let him arrest you.
-What happened to your face?
-I'm going to tell you something.
Oh. [laughs] Okay.
I've been bitten…
So have I.
[whispers] Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I gotta tell you this one thing.
I gotta tell you this one thing,
and it's about the--
the vigilante
and the car thief, all right?
-Oh, okay.
-What?
-No, no, no. Don't…
-I don't want to talk about that.
Okay, no, forget that.
I'm not gonna talk about that.
I'm gonna talk about me, okay?
-What about you?
-It's impo--
I-I wish I could just…
I can't. It's hard to say.
-Just say it.
-I don't know.
Say it.
[sighs]
What? What?
What?
Okay, then, forget it.
[Gwen gasps]
[mouths] You?
-You're Spider-Man.
-Shut up.
[Mrs. Stacy] Gwen?
Gwen…
Uh, your father wants you
to come inside right away.
Okay.
-Okay?
-[Gwen] Yeah.
-Gwen.
-I'm coming.
[laughs]
[sirens wailing]
[tires screeching below]
Oh, I'm in trouble.
[panting]
[horns honking]
[crowd shouting]
Will you please go and find out
what is going on, Alfred?
[crashing]
Oh. Excellent.
Whoa! Hey!
[crowd screaming]
[bystander 1]
Hey! What is that? Oh, my God!
-[bystander 2] I don't know!
-[bystander 3] Get back in the car!
[bystander 4] Oh, my God!
Help!
[roaring]
[civilian screams]
[car alarm whooping]
[grunting]
[roaring]
[growling]
Oh. Oh!
Incoming!
[groans]
Oh… [grunts]
[gasps]
[crowd screaming]
[growls]
[father] Somebody help!
Help me! My kid is trapped!
[growling]
[grunting]
[kid] I want my dad! Help!
-Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
-Help!
-Hey, buddy, it's okay. It's all right.
-Get away.
-[yelps] Help!
-Hey, look.
Huh?
Just a normal guy, all right?
You want to hold on to this?
Hold my mask. All right.
What's your name?
-[Peter] Jack?
-Yes.
Let's get you out of here.
-[metal creaking]
-Okay, stay very still.
-All right.
-Okay, I got you.
Okay, now, look. I'm gonna undo the belt.
You're gonna hold on to that seat
in front of you, okay?
-On three?
-All right.
-Okay, one, two, three.
-[grunts]
You see how easy that was?
You did a great job. [laughs]
All right, okay.
-[Jack screams]
-[grunting]
Jack, climb now.
-I can't.
-Yes, you can.
[grunts] Put-- put it on. The mask.
It's gonna make you strong.
Jack, trust me. Put it on.
There you go. That's it.
That's it, buddy. That's it.
Okay, now, climb. Come on, Jack.
-[panting]
-Do me a favor. Little faster, okay, bud?
You're doing great, buddy.
You're doing great.
That's it. Keep coming. Keep it coming.
Keep coming.
-No!
-[Jack screaming]
[yells]
[grunts]
Jack. Oh, God. Thank God.
[panting]
You okay?
My son. My son.
Oh, my son. My son. [sobs]
Who are you?
Spider-Man.
[web thwips]
[roaring]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[sighs]
Beautiful.
-[reporters clamoring]
-Settle down, guys.
Settle down, boys. Settle down.
-[reporter] Come on.
-[George] Listen.
At approximately 9 p.m. last night,
an incident took place
on the Williamsburg Bridge.
[George on radio] Much of what occurred
is merely speculation at this point.
However,
several eyewitnesses to the crime,
as well as our own preliminary findings,
have positively placed
one individual at the scene.
Which is why, this morning,
I am issuing an arrest warrant
for the masked vigilante
known as Spider-Man.
[reporters clamoring]
[anchor] And lastly, city council members
met with homeowners and airport officials
in the first of four meetings scheduled...
It's so beautiful.
Knows how to bite, though.
-Who else knows about this?
-Just you.
Really?
Hey, you-- you don't…
You don't believe what
the police are saying, do you?
Of course not.
Does it scare you? What you can do?
No.
What did that thing
on the bridge look like?
It was real big. Too big to be human.
You gotta lay low.
No, can't do that.
You've got to.
I mean, why…
Because of last night.
Those people on the bridge.
Whatever was attacking them would have…
would have killed them.
So I-I-I gotta go after it.
That's not your job.
Maybe it is.
I really liked kissing you.
You're an amazing kisser.
[chuckles]
Well, you know, it was…
It was good for me, too.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
Yo! Who did that?
Hello!
[Connors] It's not nice to snoop.
I gave everyone the week off.
-Yeah.
-Shouldn't you be at school?
No, I got a-- I got a free track.
I want-- I wanted to ask you a question.
How would a predator track a reptile?
Oh, they don't.
Most reptiles are at the top
of their respective food chain,
kings of their domain.
They gotta have vulnerabilities, right?
Why the sudden interest
in the cold-blooded?
Just asking a question.
I got-- I got-- I got school stuff.
Biology profiles to do.
-Oh.
-So, because of the cold blood,
would they react to changes
in temperatures?
You'd have to catch one first.
Did you know there's a rumor
of a new species in New York?
Beautiful and quite large.
What do you know about it?
Have you seen it?
No, it's not yet classified.
But it can be aggressive…
if threatened.
Doc, you all right?
Never been better, Peter.
Never been better.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
I have a new project I'm working on.
I need to be alone.
Good. Good, good.
Good.
Don't worry, Mr. Parker. I'll be back.
Wonderful things are coming.
Wonderful things.
[low growling]
[growling and munching]
Fred?
Mr. Mayor, I can assure you,
if there was
a giant dinosaur running around
the streets of Manhattan,
you would be the first to know.
So tell your son he can
rest easy, all right?
Yeah. You and me both, sir.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Mr. Parker, why are you not in school?
-Got a free track.
-Okay.
Well, I do not have a free track,
so make your point quickly.
Okay, fine. There may not be a dinosaur
running around Manhattan,
but there is something more dangerous,
and I know who it is.
-You know who it is?
-Dr. Curtis Connors.
-He's a biochemist--
-Of Oscorp?
-That's right.
-Okay.
Dr. Curtis Connors, who's
also my daughter's mentor.
-Is that who you're talking about?
-That's the one.
Okay. You know, recently, Dr. Connors gave
Gwen a glowing college recommendation.
It was beautiful. When I read it, I cried.
But you would have me believe that he,
in his spare time, is running around
dressed up like a giant dinosaur?
Not dressing up, and not a dinosaur.
He has transformed himself
into a giant lizard.
-[sighs]
-Let me ask you a question.
Do I look like the mayor of Tokyo to you?
I'm telling you--
I'm telling you the absolute truth.
This man has worked for his whole life
on cross-species genetics.
He lost one arm
and has been trying to grow it back.
But there was something imbalanced
about the equation, and he has turned
into a full lizard.
He's using lizard DNA. He is dangerous.
And he's planning something
horrific, I know. I know.
Okay. All right, I get it.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna go back to hanging out
with the citizens of Tokyo,
and I'm gonna go back
to protecting the citizens
of this fine, fair city of ours.
Sergeant Butler, would you please
escort Mr. Parker back to school?
Captain Stacy, I'm not messing around.
Just bring him in, just call him in.
You have to call him in.
He is a danger to everybody.
-Just, please, listen to me.
-[Butler] Let's go.
-Jimmy. [sighs]
-Hmm?
Get me everything we have
on Dr. Curtis Connors.
-Okay? Right away.
-Yeah.
[Connors] Subject, Dr. Curtis Connors.
Current temperature, 89.7.
Steady for 48 hours.
Blood panels reveal
lymphocyte and monocyte readings
consistent with subject's past.
Clotting rate vastly improved.
Marked enhancement in muscle response,
strength, and elasticity.
Eyesight similarly improved.
Subject no longer requires
corrective lenses.
This is no longer about curing ills.
This is about finding perfection.
In attempt to redress
regenerative relapse,
dosage has been increased
to 200 milligrams.
[electronic beeping]
[web strand vibrating]
[web creaking]
[squeaking and chittering]
[camera shutter clicks]
[grunting]
-You stopped me once.
-[camera clicks]
You won't stop me again.
-[growls]
-[Spider-Man grunting]
I'm getting stronger every day!
[grunting]
[low growling]
[camera shutter clicks]
[high-pitched whirring]
[muffled grunting]
[gasping, coughing]
Oh, that sucked.
[panting]
[growling]
[camera clicks]
Peter Parker.
[growls]
[roars]
[typing]
[Gwen chuckles] Come in.
You should maybe, uh, consider
coming in through the lobby.
[both laugh]
Also, my father is under the impression
that you require psychiatric attention.
-Oh, really?
-Peter.
-What happened?
-You should see the other guy.
[panting]
The other guy, in this instance,
being a giant mutant lizard.
Hey, Gwen, honey, do you want cocoa?
-Howard's making some cocoa.
-Shh.
[Peter sighs]
No, Dad, I do not want cocoa.
Honestly, I'm 17 years old.
Okay. I just thought I remembered
somebody saying last week
that her fantasy was to live
in a chocolate house.
Well, that's impractical.
And fattening.
[door slams]
Chocolate house.
-Sorry, Dad.
-It's good.
I just… I can't, um, have cocoa right now,
because I'm working--
I'm doing this, um…
I have, uh… I have cramps.
Oh.
I feel kind of pukey and just
sort of, I don't know, like, emotional.
-Like, I keep crying…
-Good, good.
It's brutal.
You don't want to know.
Trust me, it's, like, bad.
Got it.
-Thanks, Daddy.
-[George] All right.
[peter groaning]
Easy, Bug Boy.
-[whispers] What'd you call me?
-[both laugh]
[Peter whispers] I'm going
to be all right.
-No. No.
-[whispers] Yes. Yes.
I know what this is.
[whispers] What is it?
Every day, for as long as I can remember,
my father has left every morning,
and he's put a badge on his chest
and strapped a gun to his hip.
And every day, for as long
as I can remember,
I haven't known if he was
going to make it home.
[whispers] I got you.
[whispers] Okay?
I gotta stop him, though.
I have to, 'cause I created him.
[whispers] What do you mean?
I gave him an equation…
that made all of this possible.
Something my father
had been working on, you know?
Secretly. Now I realize
why he kept it a secret.
Point is, this is my responsibility.
I have to fix it.
[whispers] Peter.
[whispers] Hey.
Let's get out of here.
-Let's just get out of here.
-[both laugh]
Just for a minute. Can we?
-No. No.
-Yeah. Yes.
-Yes. Yes.
-No.
-Yes.
-If my parents see me leaving, I'm dead.
Your parents aren't
going to see you leaving.
[whooshing]
[Connors] Peter Parker.
Spider-Man.
I'm not the one who needs help.
There will be no more
loneliness, no more outcasts.
Species-wide distribution could…
could enhance humanity
on an evolutionary scale.
One has to adapt to survive.
"That, changing like the snake,
I might be free
to cast off flesh
wherein I dwell confined."
[Connors] Would you give it all up
after all you know you can do?
All the power you feel?
I can save them!
[gasps]
[grunting]
You're not going to get
in the way of my plan, Peter Parker!
[all chattering]
[rattling]
[growling]
[students screaming]
Go. Go!
[snarling]
[grunting]
[growling]
Nowhere to hide, Peter.
All these souls, lost and alone.
I can save them. I can cure them.
There's no need to stop me, Peter.
[roars]
[growls]
You're not thinking straight, Doc.
Stop this! This isn't you!
Let's talk this out.
Doc!
[grunts]
Oh, boy.
All right. So you don't wanna talk?
-[roars]
-There you go.
Don't… [grunts]
Make me… have to… [groans]
Hurt you!
[yells]
That is disgusting.
[muffled grunting]
Gwen.
[growls]
[rapid thwipping]
I'm gonna throw you out the window now.
What? [screams]
[gasping]
[growling]
[sirens approaching]
[Spider-Man] Uh-oh.
Somebody's been a bad lizard.
[classical music playing over headphones]
[music fades]
[grunting]
[panting]
[distant clattering]
[clattering]
[sirens approaching]
[via bullhorn] This is Lieutenant Williams
from the New York City Police Department.
We've got this building surrounded.
[chattering]
[officer] Alpha, let's move ahead. Go!
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
-Hey.
-[Gwen] Where are you?
I'm fine. I'm okay.
I'm down in the sewer, I'm tracking him.
I gotta stop him before anyone gets hurt.
But we need an antidote.
Do you know how to run a serum?
-Yeah, I do it for Connors all the time.
-Okay, great, great, great. Okay.
L-l-l-listen, I need you to go to Oscorp.
I need you to access
the cross-species file.
-It's a blue serum. File 12389.
-Okay, got it. On my way.
[equipment beeps]
I spent my life as a scientist
trying to create
a world without weakness,
without outcasts.
I sought to create a stronger human being,
but there's no such thing.
Human beings are weak,
pathetic, feeble-minded creatures.
Why be human at all
when we can be so much more?
Faster, stronger, smarter.
This is my gift to you.
Oscorp.
-[officer] Captain Stacy!
-What?
We have a confirmed sighting, sir.
The Lizard's headed toward
Canal Street station.
-What about Spider-Man?
-He was inside the high school.
I want that Spider-Man off the street.
[growling]
[gunfire]
[roars]
[car alarms wailing in distance]
[gunfire]
[cops shouting]
[cop screams]
-[snarls]
-[groans]
[growling]
[groans]
[coughing]
[scanner beeps]
[siren wailing]
[car horns honking]
-[siren wailing]
-[gunfire]
[roaring]
[dispatcher over radio] The lizard
creature has released a biological agent.
All efforts at stopping him have failed,
and he is now proceeding
north on 7th Avenue. Over.
[tires screeching]
-[Gwen] Hi.
-Hey. Hey, where are you?
-[Gwen] I'm at Oscorp.
-You have to get out of there right now.
-The antidote is cooking.
-No, no, no. Connors is on the way.
He's coming to you right now.
He needs the dispersement device.
-He's gonna infect the whole city.
-There's eight minutes left.
You're gonna wait there for 8 minutes
after what I told you?
People are gonna die! You leave right now.
Listen. That is an order, okay?
I'm gonna get everybody out.
Did you hear what--
Gwen! Gwen! You Mother Hubbard.
Are you serious?
[beeping]
[alarm blaring]
He's heading south.
Stand down now, or we will open fire.
You are surrounded. There is no escape.
Go, go!
[grunts]
[horn honks]
[low buzzing]
[cops shouting faintly]
[officer 1] Clear!
[officer 2] Clear up top!
[officer 3] Clear, sir!
[officer 4] All clear here, sir!
[men grunting]
[officers grunting and groaning]
Freeze!
Down on the ground.
Put your hands behind your head. Now!
Parker.
It's headed to Oscorp!
And your daughter's there right now.
You gotta let me go.
Hold your fire!
[grunts]
Well, Paul, if I didn't see it,
I wouldn't believe it.
I won't venture to say exactly
what it is that's crawling up
the north side of the Oscorp Tower,
but clearly it is not human
and it is very, very strong.
-[rumbling]
-[alarm blaring]
-[gasps]
-[alarm stops]
[computer] Time remaining, one minute.
[growling]
[footsteps approaching]
[hissing softly]
[growling]
[footsteps approaching]
[clattering in distance]
-[Lizard roars]
-[Gwen screams]
-[gasps]
-[footsteps receding]
[electronic beep]
[computer] Antidote complete.
[beeping]
[grunts]
[groans]
Oh, man.
[reporter 1]
We are now getting the latest details.
This is just coming in.
The New York Police Department
has called for a city-wide evacuation,
everything south of 54th Street.
If you are south of 54th Street,
you have to move out
of the area immediately.
[growling]
[sirens wailing]
[reporter 2] Spider-Man appears
to be heading towards Oscorp.
He looks injured, and it's really not
clear if he's gonna make it.
That's the guy who saved
my boy on the bridge.
Troy, they're clearing us out.
Something bad's going down in Midtown.
Hey, are you still friends with Matthews,
that crane operator down on 6th Avenue?
-Yeah.
-Get him on the phone for me.
The cops are evacuating
everybody. Who the hell cares?
Get him on the phone for me.
[grunts]
[crowd clamoring]
Hey, Charlie, get me Enriquez
on 54th Street!
-[Charlie] You got it.
-Angelo, get your mug over here.
Wolski! You're getting some overtime!
[crane dispatcher]
All tower cranes on 6th,
swing your jib arms over the avenue.
Boom angles at 90 degrees.
Spider-Man needs those big boys
high and lined up.
Let's give him a clear approach. Over.
[grunting]
[grunts]
Come on, Parker.
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[screams]
[siren whoops]
[police radio chatter]
[Lizard roars]
[siren whoops]
-Hey.
-Dad! I have to get this to Spider-Man.
-Get in the car. Let's go.
-No. No, it can stop The Lizard.
-Get in the car.
-You don't understand!
Yes, I do.
Your boyfriend is a man of many masks.
I get it.
Give me this.
Get in the car.
Please make sure he's okay.
[computer] Initializing Ganali device.
Detonation in T-minus two minutes.
[Lizard roars]
[roaring]
[grunts]
[panting]
[growls]
[hissing]
[grunts]
[roars]
-[hissing]
-[grunts]
[ice crackling]
[groaning]
[yells]
Poor Peter Parker.
No mother, no father.
[snarls] No uncle.
All alone.
[shotgun pumps]
He's not alone.
[roars]
[ice crackling]
[grunts]
[roars]
[computer]
Detonation in T-minus 45 seconds.
Hey! Gift from Gwen.
I got this, Peter! Go!
[grunts]
[computer] T-minus 30 seconds.
[roars]
[gunfire continues]
[grunts]
[computer]
Detonation in T-minus ten seconds.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
[grunting]
[skin crackling]
No.
No!
[metal groaning]
[grunting]
[panting]
[straining]
[skin crackling]
[screams]
[yelling]
[crackling]
The Captain.
Captain!
[gasping]
The Lizard.
[whispers] It's okay. We stopped him.
-Oh. Okay.
-Let's get you out of here.
-[groaning]
-Come on.
[whispers] Okay, okay, okay.
Look at me. You need to stay with me.
-Help's on the way, okay?
-You need to…
You need to be gone when they--
when they get here.
-Okay? [groans]
-I'm not going anywhere.
I was wrong about you, Peter.
This city needs you.
Here.
You're gonna need this.
You're gonna make enemies.
People will get hurt.
Sometimes the people closest to you.
So I want you to promise me
something, okay?
Leave Gwen out of it.
Promise me that.
Huh?
You promise me.
[exhales]
Oh…
[yells]
[sirens]
[reporter] An eerie calm has set in
over New York City.
Apparently, some sort
of aerosolized antidote
was launched from Oscorp Tower,
which seems to have
counteracted the biotoxins.
Residents of Lower Manhattan
can rest peacefully
knowing the alleged
mastermind of this terror plot,
Dr. Curtis Connors, is behind bars.
We've got John Niles for
a report in Lower Manhattan.
-John, what do you see?
-[door opens]
[groans]
[unzips backpack]
-Sweetheart, it's all right.
-[crying]
It's all right.
[groans] Rough night.
It's gonna be all right.
[thunder rumbling]
Where have you been?
Hi.
My father died.
[thunder rumbling]
There was a funeral.
They shot off…
rifles and they made speeches.
Two of my teachers showed up.
And F-Flash showed up.
Everyone was there but you. [crying]
Can't do this. Can't do this.
[sniffling]
-I'm sorry. I can't, I can't, um…
-What are you saying?
I can't see you anymore.
I can't.
He made you promise, didn't he?
To stay away from me…
so I'd be safe.
[sighs]
[May] What a pretty girl.
Yeah.
That's what Uncle Ben said.
Did you ask her out?
Why?
Can't.
I'm just no good for her.
Peter Parker, if there's
one thing you are, it's good.
Anyone has a problem
with that can talk to me.
[Ben on recording] Peter, I know
things have been difficult lately,
and I'm sorry about that.
I think I know what you're feeling.
Ever since you were a little boy,
you've been living with
so many unresolved things.
Well, take it from an old man,
those things send us down a road.
They make us who we are.
And if anyone's destined
for greatness, it's you, son.
You owe the world your gifts.
You just have to figure out
how to use them.
And know that wherever they
take you, we'll always be here.
So come on home, Peter.
You're my hero.
And I love you.
-What's up, Parker?
-What's up?
-[Peter] Hey. How's it going?
-[Flash] You coming along, man?
That's a cool shirt.
[school bell ringing]
Yeah. Dude's-- dude's crazy.
But chicks dig him.
[instructor] Come on, guys.
You heard the bell. Get to class.
[teacher] I had a professor once
who liked to tell his students
that there were only ten different
plots in all of fiction.
Well, I'm here to tell you he was wrong.
There is only one.
"Who am I"?
Mr. Parker.
Tardy again.
Well, at least we can always count on you.
Sorry, Miss. Ritter, won't happen again,
I promise.
Don't make promises
you can't keep, Mr. Parker.
[whispers] Yeah, but those are
the best kind.
[Ritter] Okay, class, open your books.
Let's begin on page one.
[sirens wailing]
[grunts]
[thunder rumbling]
[voices echoing in distance]
[lock clicks]
[thunder crashing]
[sinister visitor] Hello, Doctor.
Did you tell the boy?
Tell him what?
Did you tell the boy
the truth about his father?
-No.
-Well, that's very good.
So we'll let him be for now.
You should leave him alone!
[thunder crashes]