- [speaking Russian]
[metal thuds]
[dramatic music]
[helicopter beeping]
- [screaming]
[computer beeping]
- Air traffic control's
reporting
a helicopter in distress.
- Why is it every time
I come to visit,
all hell is breaking loose?
♪ ♪
- Oh no, it's gonna hit
the new Seaver Building.
- It's okay.
Barry's on it.
- What am I on?
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
- Always have to make
an entrance,
don't you, Kid Flash?
- What can I say?
It's great to be back.
♪ ♪
[bamboo flute music]
- A lotus flower.
- Okay, that is
seriously beautiful.
- Yeah, I'm definitely
gonna need you
to teach me how to do that.
- The lotus is one
of the eight auspicious symbols
meaning purity
and renunciation,
practice which I'm
currently being guided through
by Bhikkhuni Amala,
the Buddhist nun
assigned
to my Peace Corps camp.
- Wow, purity and renunciation.
Guess that means
more wine for me.
- [laughs]
Just being here celebrating
with family, new friends
is all the joy I need.
- Look at you
getting your Zen on.
[soft dramatic music]
- It's working.
- Who is that?
- That's my brother, Wally.
He looks so happy.
- [sighs quietly]
- I wish I was there.
- [sighs]
[ethereal tones]
I'm sorry.
I couldn't hold the window
any longer.
- It's okay.
It was so good to see them,
even if it was
just for a second.
- You miss your family.
- Yeah, well, I've been trapped
in here for weeks and...
Losing my sense of time
like I'm in some sort of dream.
All the while,
my family is out there
with that...that thing
that isn't me.
- I hope they
don't forget about you
as quickly as my Joseph
forgot about me.
♪ ♪
He used to come to my mirror
every day and try
to figure out
a way to get me out.
- Does he know
that you're still in here?
- I don't know.
- Barry calls me
his lightning rod.
He used to say
that he could find me
anywhere in the universe.
- Seems like there's nothing
he wouldn't do for you.
♪ ♪
I haven't seen
my husband in years.
I haven't touched him
in 72 months...
312 weeks...
2,190 days.
2,190.
- 2,190.
- Eva, listen to me.
Breathe.
- 2,190.
[eerie music]
2,190.
- Hey, Iris, everything okay?
- Um, yeah.
- Greetings, Earth Prime-lings!
- Babe, you're home early!
[upbeat music]
Wow, you look...
- I know, right?
- Wow, hey, bud.
- Hey.
- Caitlin: You're finally back.
- I am.
Well, after a while,
all the post-Crisis
anomaly hunting
starts to catch up
with you...
that, and I wanted to wash
all the Atlantean fish smell
off of these clothes.
- Mm-mm.
- Hugs from here.
- "Welcome home"?
You guys shouldn't have.
- Shame.
- Well, it's good
to see you, friend.
- Wally West?
What?
Where have you been?
Welcome home...
[whimsical music]
"Welcome home"...I see.
I am crashing your party.
- You know we're always happy
to have you back,
Crocodile Dundee.
Come on, let me make
you a drink.
- Ah, you know me too well.
[snoring]
- Okay, babe, I think we should
probably get you home.
- Mm, yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
It's, like, 4:00
in the morning in Atlantis,
so, yeah, should probably
go to bed.
- Yeah, we should get home
and relieve the babysitter.
- Hon, I gotta go back
to the office.
- What?
- I can't get any work done
since Nash
moved in across the hall.
- I can give you a ride.
I'm working a late shift
at the "Citizen."
- Perfect.
- Good night, guys.
- Good night.
- Bye-bye.
- Uh-uh-uh-uh, we got this.
- Okay, won't argue with that.
- Boy, they...you ready?
Let's do it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, what was that?
- Uh, nothing.
It was, uh, just a hiccup.
Just a little hiccup.
- A hiccup?
Is that the first one?
- Uh...
- Hey, Barry.
Are you all right, man?
- No, I mean, I've had
a few little things.
[grunts]
It's still sore.
My speed healing was weird
for a little bit,
but, I mean, it's fine now.
It was just my body
still recovering from Crisis.
- Barry.
- Yeah?
I didn't just come back
to see family.
Lately, I've been sensing
that there's something wrong
with the Speed Force.
- [as Yoda]
Hmm, a disturbance
in the Speed Force, you feel.
That's terrible Yoda.
- Bhikkhuni Amala helped me
discover a way
to communicate
with the Speed Force...
to seek guidance by projecting
my consciousness into it
while leaving my body behind.
- Damn, I've never been able
to do that.
It just usually comes to me.
- As your mother, right?
Yeah, I remember
from the lightning storm.
For me, it's different.
It's more of a voice
inside my head guiding me,
but a few months ago,
that voice just went quiet.
Now every time I try
to reach out...silence.
When was the last time
the Speed Force came to you?
- Uh, I mean,
it's been a while,
but, listen, I don't think
there's anything wrong
with the Speed Force.
You know, I mean, if there was,
it would let me know, you know?
Or I don't...besides,
I'm sure there's
a simple explanation
for all this.
Trust me.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[pop music]
- One oat milk vibe-accino,
extra hot with two sugars
and three short sprinkles
of cinnamon to go.
- I said three sugars
and two sprinkles of cinnamon.
[speaking Russian]
[discordant pulse]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Alexi?
- I thought you'd go down easy
in that fancy helicopter
of yours.
I guess now...
[speaking Russian]
- Frida.
- Hello, Maria.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Maria!
[patrons screaming]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- Maria Volkova,
Russian socialite.
One minute,
she's here sipping java,
and the next minute,
she's a mummy?
- This is the same woman
I saved from the helicopter,
but she was young.
She was full of life.
- Well, based on her
signal joint T-cell receptors,
she was 110 years old
when she died.
- Damn.
So the helicopter accident...
that wasn't random.
Someone targeted her.
- Not just any someone.
You see the kinetic energy
levels on the body?
- Yeah, they're almost zero,
like someone removed it all.
- Therefore slowing down
the victim,
which is how Maria
was aged so many years.
I mean, real time, it would
have been like a second passed,
but, for her,
it was almost a century.
Why does this feel so familiar?
Wasn't there someone
who could, like, slow...
- If you're thinking
it's Turtle...
- Yeah.
- It's not.
This meta doesn't
just slow down time.
She can create
potential energy force fields
around individual victims,
aging them centuries
in the blink of an eye.
This wasn't Turtle.
This was Turtle 2.
[dramatic music]
- Sorry, I was just waiting
for you to come up
with a better name.
- No, it's Turtle 2.
Less is more.
- Well, what matters
is her real name,
Mrs. Frida Novikov.
We busted her for running
an international drug ring
out of her apartment.
We deported her back to Russia.
- Well, apparently,
she didn't stay put.
Everywhere I went on my trip,
I heard stories about Novikov.
I came home early to check out
her old haunts,
and maybe find a clue
about what she's up to.
[chuckles]
I just didn't expect
she'd come back home too.
- Well, we better figure out
why she's back
before she ages anybody else.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go
pull her file.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
I'll see if I can work
up a way to take
the wind out
of her sails for good.
♪ ♪
- [knocks]
The prodigal hacker returns.
Regale me with the adventures
of the great,
globe-trotting Cisco-lorian.
- [laughs]
I'll tell you
all about it later.
Right now, I'm trying to stop
a meta who can slow down time
by reworking
the Velocity-X formula
to speed her up
and neutralize
her kinetic energy meta-powers,
so I'm gonna focus on that.
- [knocks]
Knock-knock, Doc,
I just need your...
I need to know if,
on your trip...
you saw anyone else
from any other Earths.
- Other people?
- That's right.
- From other Earths?
- Uh, okay, not really,
because any doppelgangers
who managed
to make it here...
they would all be dead by now
due to
neurological degeneration.
- What if they
were already dead?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You gotta be kidding me.
- What?
- The great myth buster
suddenly believes in ghosts.
- [chuckles]
No.
No, I'm not talking ghosts.
I'm talking survivors.
- Oh, survivors.
- Yeah.
- Sure...spooky.
Look, survivors, ghosts,
whatever you wanna call them,
it's not possible.
Crisis made sure of that.
Remember?
- I...
- You wouldn't have been able
to see anything like that.
- All right, fine,
well, then you missed
something out there.
- I missed something?
- You missed something
because...
- Do you know how many hours...
how much time and energy
I spent cataloguing
everything I saw out there?
- I need your help finding
an answer that makes sense!
Okay?
So drop your little Velocity-F.
- X!
- X...
and help me track
something that really matters.
- I'm trying to find a criminal
I've been after for weeks.
That matters!
- To you.
Well, I guess
on all your travels
you finally learned to focus on
someone else besides yourself...
not.
[knocks]
- Nash, need something?
- Nope.
♪ ♪
- Wally:Barry's acting
like nothing is wrong.
[sighs]
I shouldn't get frustrated.
Amala says,
"pride is the enemy of peace."
- Huh.
You know, I don't think
Barry will ever have
the same relationship
with the Speed Force
that you do.
Not after what happened.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I don't know
the full story,
but last fall,
Barry and the Speed Force
had an incident.
- He did not tell me that.
Maybe he's trying
to work up the nerve?
- Maybe, but if
that disturbance you're sensing
is real, do you really
have time to waste here?
♪ ♪
- Okay, you two are seriously
the best looking siblings
in the world.
- The Abhidhamma teaches us
to avoid self-infatuation,
but I may need you to forward
me a copy of that one.
- [laughs]
- See you later.
- Mm-hmm.
- Bye.
Pretty cool camera, right?
I asked Cisco to pick it up
from Quimby Labs in Germany,
but he definitely made
some modifications.
- You need to delete
that photo right now.
- Why?
- We shouldn't be taking photos
of "Citizen" employees.
I mean, if that got online,
another of Black Hole's
assassins like Hoshi
could track our moves.
- Right, sorry.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, did you talk to Joe?
He was gonna pull
Novikov's file.
- What happened between you
and the Speed Force, Barry?
- [sighs]
Wally,
I'm working a case, all right?
- If something bad happened,
that might be
what's causing all these
problems with our powers.
- You...listen, you don't know
what you're talking about.
- I believe
that you can solve this, Barry,
if you face the Speed Force.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- It doesn't wanna talk to me.
- How do you know that?
- Because an enemy
infected my mind
with nightmares and visions.
- [gasps]
- When it tried to help me,
I attacked it,
so if you think the Speed Force
wants to hear from me...
- Barry.
- Then you...you
don't understand
what the Speed Force wants.
- Barry, we're already here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We're in the Speed Force.
You took me in here?
[chord echoes]
[booming low tone]
- Something is wrong.
[thunder rumbles]
We need to find her.
- What the hell is that?
Wally.
This is my old room.
What?
- [ethereal gasp]
- What's...what's going on?
What's happening
to the Speed Force?
- We are dying, Barry Allen.
♪ ♪
- That's not...
How is that possible?
- Because of what you did.
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder crackling]
- No, no, no, Wally,
we have to go back.
I have to talk to her.
I have to talk to her!
- Barry, what did you do?
- The Speed Force...it's dying.
This is why our powers
are broken.
This is what we have been
sensing this whole time.
- Look, it's not...
it's not possible, all right?
I mean, the Speed Force is
an infinite source of energy.
It's like gravity or light.
It doesn't just die.
- No, it didn't
just die, Barry.
She said it's dying
because of what you did.
- [sighs]
- Barry, this is your fault!
- Ramsey was infecting me.
I mean, I didn't have a choice.
- I'm not even talking
about what you did to her.
I'm talking
about what you did after.
You betrayed the Speed Force
months ago,
and you didn't say
nothing then.
You didn't say nothing when you
came back from Crisis either,
and you started noticing
something was wrong
with your powers.
You could have told me, Barry.
We might have gone
into the Speed Force.
We might have saved it
before it was too late.
- I didn't...I didn't...
- But instead
you blew me off...
- I...
- Again and again!
- I...Wally, I didn't know
anyone else was affected.
- Oh!
- All right?
I'm sorry.
- Barry, you don't get it.
We are all connected.
When I used to talk
with the Speed Force,
sometimes it would show me
visions of different futures,
different possibilities
of how things could go.
There was always
one common thread.
There was always a speedster
that would pick up
our mantles,
like a chain of lightning
stretching through centuries.
[soft dramatic music]
I saw my kids...
running with their kids.
I saw Nora.
But now that chain
of lightning...
it ends with us.
- Okay, Wally, it's not
too late though, all right?
I mean,
we still have our speed.
We can go back in there.
I can save her.
- No, you saw it, Barry.
The Speed Force
is beyond repair.
And if you think
that I'm gonna bring you
back in after everything
that you have done...
- Wally...
- You need to find
another teacher.
- Wally...we...we...
[sighs]
- [chuckles]
[eerie music]
[screams]
- The tachyon enhancer's ready.
I can't project
my consciousness
into the Speed Force,
so I need you
to monitor my position
while I enter it physically.
- Certainly, Barry Allen.
- [breathes deeply]
Okay, start the protocol.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my beautiful boy,
you came back.
- Of course I did.
You said the Speed Force
is dying.
[thunder cracks]
I see this lightning
everywhere.
I can fix it, though.
I can...you just...
you tell me what to do
and I'll do it.
- It's too late.
- I won't accept that.
I caused this.
I have to save you.
- You didn't hurt me.
- I attacked you.
You remember?
- Barry, Barry,
that's not why I'm dying.
A few months ago, a substance
entered the Speed Force...
something that we'd
never encountered before.
We tried to contain it,
but it contaminated us.
It upset the balance
of our energies.
[thunder cracks]
- The green
and white lightning.
- It is infernal power
beyond the laws of our nature.
[dramatic music]
- No.
You said you're in tune
with the multiverse.
Does that include
the Speed Force?
You could give me
the energy boost I need.
During Crisis,
I made the Spectre give me
his energy so I could enter
the Speed Force again.
I am responsible.
I did this.
I killed the Speed Force.
I didn't know.
I wouldn't have...
I never would have...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
- Barry Allen, we forgive you.
You did the right thing.
You saved our universe.
You never could have foreseen
what that cost.
[groaning and wheezing]
You only have a few steps left
before we're gone
from you entirely,
but I know
you will use them well.
The lightning chose you,
and it was the best decision
that we...
I ever made.
You showed us
the greatest force of all.
[sobbing]
[tender music]
I love you.
I love you,
my beautiful,
beautiful boy.
♪ ♪
[whispering] Mom.
Mom. Don't go, mom.
- Joe:
The Speed Force is dead?
I don't even know what to say.
Do you still have your powers?
- From what I can figure out,
we still have
a residual amount
of Speed Force inside us.
But the more we use up,
the less we have left
until...
- Until it's gone forever?
[tender music]
- Oh, my God, son, I didn't...
I can't even imagine
what you're going through.
And Barry.
- Dad, this is his fault.
He could've come to me
months ago.
We might've fixed things.
But instead, he had to do
what he always does
and assume he's the only one
that can handle it.
- Well, Wally, did you even
need to tell him like that?
I mean, we both know
that Barry
will beat himself up
all by himself.
- He will.
[sighs]
I guess that wasn't very Zen
of me at all, was it?
- Wally, sit down please.
♪ ♪
Do you remember what you
were like when we first met?
'Cause I do.
You were petulant, stubborn.
Every little thing
pissed you off.
You didn't want a father
or a sister or a brother,
but look at the man
that you are now...
the sensitive, intelligent,
compassionate man
that you have become,
and it's not because
of some mystical energy source
out there.
It's because you did the work.
Now your responsibility is
to continue to do the work
to be that man.
Do you understand me, son?
♪ ♪
- [knocks]
- Yeah?
- Captain, we've got
the other informant
waiting in custody.
- Thank you.
Uh, this is
that Frida Novikov case.
She got deported because two
of our informants were part
of her smuggling ring,
one of them being your friend
from the helicopter accident,
Maria Volkova.
- That's why Novikov
targeted Maria.
She's out for revenge.
- Well, the other informant
I'm gonna put in WITSEC soon.
I will find you later, okay?
Hey, whatever
you're going through
with the Speed Force
and your powers,
Barry is going
through the same thing.
Remember that.
I love you.
- I love you.
Alright.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- Cisco:Not right now, Cait.
I'm busy
with the mobile BARI unit.
- Let me get this straight.
You were trying to bioengineer
a formula to stop a meta-human,
and rather than
call your friend
who's a bioengineer,
you went with Bluetooth?
- Yeah, I'm trying
to stop Turtle 2 here.
- Yeah, I know.
It's all you've been doing.
You don't have any time for me.
You totally blew off Nash
when he asked for your help.
I mean, you might as well
still be on your trip.
- Yeah, well, maybe my trip
didn't turn out
exactly as planned.
- What are you talking about?
You got to raid Egyptian tombs
and explore Atlantis.
- I thought,
after all those adventures,
I would come back different,
like Wally
or like you and Frost,
but I went around the world,
and I...
♪ ♪
And I feel
like I'm back where I started.
- Cisco,
I know you feel responsible,
but we're gonna stop Turtle 2.
I promise.
We're Team Flash.
It's what we do.
But in the meantime, I wonder
if maybe you don't have
some other responsibilities
that you'd like to address...
ones that are
a little closer to home.
- [sighs]
Yeah.
You're right.
While I'm doing that,
maybe my friend the bioengineer
would like to take over.
- Absolutely.
♪ ♪
- Wally:I've been looking
for you, man.
- [sighs]
- I thought maybe
you'd be home.
- No.
[tender music]
[sighs]
I'm not ready to tell Iris.
I'm not ready to tell anyone.
I found out what really
happened to the Speed Force.
It died because
of what I did in Crisis.
I took the Spectre's energy
so I could enter
the Speed Force.
His energy started a meltdown,
and now it's gone, Wally...
For good because of what I did.
- You were trying
to save the universe.
Any hero
would have made that call.
I would've made that call.
♪ ♪
Amala told me a story once
about a mother
who lost her only son.
She was so heartbroken,
she asked the Buddha
to bring him back to life.
He said he would...
but he had one request...
a mustard seed from a family
that had never lost
a loved one.
So she went from neighbor
to neighbor asking for seeds,
and when she would ask,
"Has anyone
in your family lost someone?"
The answer was always yes.
The Buddha was trying
to have her understand
that as much as she suffered,
she wasn't alone.
When I found out
the Speed Force was dying...
I forgot how much
you were suffering too.
And I'm sorry.
I am.
- I did this.
I deserve your anger.
- So do something with it.
We can't punish ourselves
for the mistakes we've made.
That's a closed door.
But we can take responsibility
for our actions...
no matter how great
the obstacle to overcome.
- Amala teach you that too?
- No.
You did.
- Caitlin:Guys, we've got a
problem.
Facial rec just picked up
Frida Novikov outside CCPD.
[dramatic music]
- You really think
one criminal's
worth all this backup?
- If this file is right,
I don't think Novikov
is gonna give up,
and I'm not putting another
informant into WITSEC
unless we're prepared.
♪ ♪
- Pomedlenneye, Captain.
Slow down.
- Where is Olga Zhuravlev?
I know she's here.
Bring her to me.
- So you can turn her
into a pile of bones?
- I am just taking from her
what she stole from me: time!
Now, you have five minutes
to bring her to me
or you all will die.
- She has Joe.
- Cisco was working on a way
to stop Novikov.
- So where is he?
- Nash:Come in.
- I wanted to apologize
for being a jerk.
But I wanna make it right,
so what do you say
we do some
multiversal ghost busting?
Ah, Crisis, the gift
that keeps on giving, huh?
[chuckles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You're not Nash.
- Hello, Cisco.
- Thawne.
- That's right.
Now, where were we?
Good-bye.
- You're in Nash's body.
No powers.
♪ ♪
- I don't need my powers
to kill you.
[stun gun crackling]
- Nash?
But he's so full of hatred.
- That's not Nash.
- The new Velocity-X
is ready to use on Novikov.
I just have to put it
into an injector gun.
- Okay.
- But we can't run it there.
If we do, we'll use up speed,
and we have no idea
how much we have left.
- Yes, we can.
We just have
to use it responsibly.
Okay, the fastest route
to CCPD is in a straight line.
We can run it.
We just have to phase as we go.
- It's ready.
- You with me?
- Always.
♪ ♪
- Time's up, Captain.
[laughs]
- Novikov, stop.
You don't have to do this.
- I know I don't have to.
I want to.
♪ ♪
Zip off again,
and I'll age him 1,000 years.
- Listen to me.
Listen.
We can't do anything to make up
for the time that you lost,
but if you take responsibility
for the time
that you have left,
you won't lose anymore.
I promise.
Please let us help you.
- I don't want your help.
- We know.
Thanks for the tip, Flash.
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
- Let's see how you handle
our version of time.
- I held her in my arms.
[tender music]
I watched her die
all over again.
♪ ♪
The Speed Force is dead
because of me,
because of my choices.
I just wanted to save everyone.
To save you.
- And you did.
Barry, none of this
is your fault.
- Now I won't be able
to save anyone.
What am I supposed to do
without my speed?
- Maybe this is for the best.
- What?
- Everything happens
for a reason, right?
Maybe you weren't supposed
to be the Flash forever.
I mean, don't you think
that after everything
the Speed Force
has put you through...
all the pain,
all the heartache,
all the death...
Don't you think
you deserve a real life?
Barry, all the world's problems
on your shoulders...
that shouldn't have been
your burden to bear.
- You're serious.
- I am.
This could be our chance
to have a normal life,
to start a family.
You deserve to be happy
just like everyone else.
Don't you want that?
- Cisco:Barry, we need you
in the pipeline right now.
There's something
you need to see.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco:Somehow, he's taken
over Nash's body.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Hi, Flash.
- Thawne.
What do you want?
- What do I always want?
To kill you.
And I'm done being patient.
I can't wait
to slit your throat.
When I do, when I get out...
believe me.
I will get out.
I'm going to kill you...
And then I'm going
to kill your family,
and then I'm going
to kill your friends.
I'm gonna kill
all your friends,
starting
with your new pal Nash.
- No.
- No?
- Whatever you've done to him,
we're gonna stop you.
- But isn't it true...
that in a few short weeks,
you're going to be powerless
to stop me, right?
Because your Speed Force
is dead.
I can feel it.
And that's what you get, Barry,
for trusting
such a puny, pathetic force.
That's why I built my own.
And I'm coming.
I'm coming for you.
[dramatic music]
- We're done here.
- Tick-tock.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
What did he mean,
the Speed Force is dead?
- [sighs]
- Hey.
You sure you wanna go already?
- If I'm gonna get
to the next Peace Corps project
in time, I gotta get going.
- You know, it'd be
a whole lot faster
if you just got a flight.
- I know, but I need to walk.
I need to have an open mind,
be ready to embrace new ways
of helping others
without my powers.
- I'm so sorry about that, son.
I obviously didn't want
your trip home
to end like that.
- It's okay, Dad.
Even if things don't unfold
the way you expected,
don't be disheartened
or give up.
The one who continues
to advance will win in the end.
- [laughing]
[tender music]
♪ ♪
You sound more like a parent
than I do now.
- Oh, you know,
it's a Zen thing.
- [chuckles]
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you too...
too damn much.
You be careful, okay?
- Mm-hmm, yes.
Dad, keep an eye on Iris
for me, will you?
[ominous music]
There's something different
about her.
Just make sure she's okay.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Bye-bye.
- Bye.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- Spectre energy.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, yeah, well,
that's just energy
we don't understand yet.
That's something
we can figure out, right?
- Absolutely.
We can run some tests,
figure out how to track it...
- Thanks guys, but I want
your help with something else.
I've been thinking
about what Thawne said...
- You mean how
he's gonna kill us all?
Yeah, me too.
- How he built
his own power source...
the Negative Speed Force.
If he can make one, then...
[dramatic music]
So can we.
I need your help to build
an artificial Speed Force.
♪ ♪
That's how I can get
my speed back.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I thought I deleted this.
[dramatic music]
[floor creaking]
Iris?
- Yeah, I'm not Iris.
- [gasps]
- Sorry you had
to find out this way.
- Wait...wait, no...
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.