BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother, but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
BARRY: Previously on The Flash...
- No!
- The man who saved Central City.
Why did you wanna kill me?
He promised he'd take me home...
- Who?
- Zoom.
Wells killed my mother.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can and can't trust.
S.T.A.R. Labs is now safer than ever.
People can'tjust waltz
in and out of here.
Exactly.
Stay where you are.
My name is Jay Garrick.
And your world is in danger,
Barry Allen.
Please, just let me explain.
I mean you no harm.
How do you know my name?
I know all your names. Caitlin Snow.
Cisco Ramon. Detective Joe West.
Enough! That part about "explaining"
needs to happen right about now.
This world is in danger.
What other worlds are there?
When you created the Singularity
above Central City,
you also created a breach
between my world and yours.
I'm sorry. A breach?
Yes. A portal, connecting our two Earths.
And what precisely is your concern?
A few days ago, you found a dead man
named Al Rothstein at the nuclear plant.
But then, a different Al Rothstein
tried to kill you.
Atom Smasher.
That man was from my world.
If he got through the breach,
I suspect there'll be more to follow.
Okay. So, Jay,
how exactly do you know all this?
Where I came from,
I was a speedster like you.
They called me the Flash.
JAY: Before I arrived on your Earth,
I was in a fight with a man named Zoom.
Zoom?
I've heard that name before.
Atom Smasher, he said
Zoom sent him here to kill me.
Who is this guy?
He's a speedster, like you and me.
And fast.
Maybe the fastest of all, but evil.
He is an unstoppable demon
with the face of death.
We were engaged
in our fiercest battle ever,
racing throughout my city,
but I wasn't fast enough to stop him.
(SCREAMS) Zoom had me beaten.
(SCREAMING)
He was about to kill me, when suddenly,
there was a blinding light,
and the sky split open.
A breach, between my world and yours
caused from the Singularity.
It pulled me in
and I somehow ended up in your world.
Powerless. Unable to return home.
What do you mean?
I lost my speed.
How?
I'm not entirely sure.
So, you've been in Central City
for six months.
Why haven't you come to see us before?
I'm in a foreign world here, Detective.
I didn't know who you all were.
Took me that long
to piece it all together.
So that's how you know our names.
You've been following us.
Look, I know how this sounds.
The existence of another Earth,
you, another Flash?
It all came as an unexpected shock
to me, too.
I just wish there was something
I could do to convince you.
There is.
We're gonna do some tests on you.
See if you're telling us the truth.
Because if you're not, this Zoom
is not gonna be your only enemy.
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
Where the hell am I?
(DISTORTED) You wanna go home?
You only have to do one thing.
- What's that?
- (DISTORTED) Kill the Flash.
So, Mr. Garrick, how long have you been
the Flash on your world?
Not long enough to call me "Mister."
(LIGHT CHUCKLE)
Please, it's Jay.
Jay, of course.
On my world, I've been the Flash
for about two years.
And how did you get your speed?
I'm not really sure. I was at my lab
trying to purify heavy water
without any residual radiation
when there was a blinding light.
Uh, I fell into a coma.
When lwoke up, I could run
almost as fast as the speed of light.
Sorry, did you say "lab?"
Are you a scientist?
Well, certainly didn't work at a place
like this but yeah.
I had a respectable solo operation.
Part-time chemist. Part-time physicist.
Part-time superhero.
Hmm.
I can forget that
superhero part now though, huh. (CHUCKLES)
Is any of this possible? A breach
to another Earth? It's not, right?
The contrary. Just recently,
the many-different-worlds theory proposed
interaction with parallel universes
was plausible.
Now, if what Mr. Garrick's saying is true,
that theory's been proven
sooner than we all thought.
It doesn't add up.
I'm gonna be honest here.
I don't understand
what the hell any of you
are talking about.
So, Jay is saying he's from,
like, a mirror world.
Or a parallel universe,
that's very, very similar to ours.
Multi-verse would be
a more apt description.
Nope. Not helping.
- Bless your heart.
- Okay, see if this helps.
This is our Earth.
Let's call it, Earth One.
And this second Earth,
let's call it, Earth Two.
This is where Jay claims to be from.
And these other Earths,
three, four, five, to infinity.
All of them are nearly identical to ours,
and, uh, they all exist at the same time,
giving us endless alternatives
to what we have here.
For example, uh, the Joe West
on Earth Two, your doppelganger,
he might not be a detective. He could be
a Nobel Prize-winning physicist.
And you, the Barry Allen here
is the Flash,
but over there,
he could be an electrician.
So I'm assuming that
the people on all these other Earths
work to make money to pay bills and such?
- I would imagine.
- So we got that in common.
I'm heading back to the station. Call me
when this makes a little bit more sense.
I'm still trying to wrap my head
around the whole idea of time travel.
(CHUCKLES)
There is one problem that remains.
If Mr. Garrick is telling the truth,
there is a breach
somewhere in Central City
that we need to find. And close for good.
Yeah, but how do we find it?
We don't even know what to look for.
Well, I suggest we put our heads
together and come up with a solution.
Not literally, of course.
Those days are over.
What'd you find?
Well, Jay's heart rate
is extraordinarily low.
And he does have
regenerative capabilities.
Other than that,
I'm not seeing any evidence
of the speed force in his system.
We don't even have proof that he's
a speedster, much less from another Earth?
- Not necessarily.
- What does that mean?
Well, Jay doesn't know this,
but while I was testing
his heart rate, blood pressure
and motor responses,
I also measured his autonomic reactions
while we were talking.
You gave him a lie-detector test?
And he passed it.
What if he's not a good guy,
and he just wants to find our weaknesses?
Keep running tests.
See what else you can find out.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
PATTY: Detective West, sir.
Yes. Officer...
Spivot. Patty Spivot.
Captain Singh mentioned
there may be positions available
on your anti-meta-human task force.
Yeah. Everybody quit.
There is no task force anymore.
Well, I know someone
who's interested in being on it.
Me.
You do realize that meta-humans
- have super-powers, right?
- Yeah.
And even if they didn't,
you wouldn't be a good fit for the team.
Because I'm a woman?
I didn't mean to imply that.
Good, because I know
how difficult this job would be,
but I think I'm an excellent candidate.
I triple-majored at Hudson
in Biology, Chemistry and Physics.
I'm in prime physical condition. And,
I rated top of my class in marksmanship.
Your class? You don't even have
your stripes yet.
Soon. Been on thejob seven months, sir.
Are you aware of what happened
to my previous partner?
Detective Thawne, yes.
I know that he died,
and the one before him,
Fred Chyre, died, too.
But the one before, that's not dead,
just transferred.
I'm sure it had nothing to do with you.
Listen, Officer...
Spivot. Patty Spivot.
Yes, Spivot. The answer's no.
All I'm asking for is a shot, sir.
Please, just an interview.
You just had the interview.
Didn't get the job.
I hope you understand
why we have to do this.
I get it, kid. You're doing
what you think you have to.
But you'll all realize soon enough
that this, the tests,
it's unnecessary.
I want to help you, Barry. Not harm you.
You're not the first person
that's said that to me.
If what you told me about Zoom is true,
that he sent Rothstein here to kill you,
instead of locking me up in here,
you better start listening.
Because if Zoom is involved,
you are going to need
a lot more than just me
at your side to stay alive.
CISCO: Barry, there's a fire at the
waterfront. Fire Department's en route.
I'm on my way.
Be careful.
(HONKING)
(SIRENS)
(CHATTERING)
That was the Flash!
(PANTING)
That was a big fire.
(PANTS) It's out, Cisco.
Copy that. See you in a bit.
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
I thought it'd be harder than this.
(GRUNTS)
Barry? Hello? Are you there?
- What was that?
- THE FLASH: I don't know.
But we need to find out.
- Barr.
- Hey.
What are we dealing with here?
(SIGHS) Well, definitely a meta-human.
Got a pretty solid look at him
between punches
and he was, like, made of sand?
- Sand? Okay.
- Mmm-hmm.
These walls are too porous
to pull any prints.
I can't even get one off the boat.
But check this out.
There's gasoline burns everywhere.
Water didn't go off.
Sprinklers weren't working.
This was arson.
Excuse me, Barry Allen?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
Two days in a row, Officer.
What a coincidence.
Or kismet,
if you believe in destiny or fate.
- I'm Patty. Patty Spivot.
- Hey.
I'm really excited to meet you.
I'm a huge fan.
- Excuse me?
- Your forensic reports.
I read them sometimes. Who am I kidding?
All the time. I've actually read them all.
(CHUCKLES)
Wow, I don't think
that I've read them all.
They're always so detailed, you know.
They really paint a picture
like you were somehow actually there
when somebody was being brutally murdered.
Thank you.
Uh, anyhow, I found, uh, something.
Well, I think I found something.
It's just a theory,
but I would like to show you.
Great.
So, this right here
is the point of origin of the fire.
And look. I don't know
a sand blaster on the market
that can make a cut that precise. So,
I think a meta-human may have done this.
Here. I took a sample for you.
Uh, there's also some fingerprints
on the back of the pipe.
Should've gone into CSI work.
I love the science,
but out here's where all the action is.
- Isn't that right, Detective West?
- (CHUCKLES)
The answer's still "no," Officer...
- Spivot.
Yeah.
What was that about?
I'm trying to join
the anti-meta-human task force.
Ah.
But you heard him.
Hey, he's kind of like your dad, right?
So, do you have any advice
on how I can crack his "no" code?
Yeah, I've been trying to pick that lock
- since I was 11.
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
So, if you figure it out,
how about you let me know?
- Deal.
- All right.
- It was nice to meet you, Barry.
- Yeah, you, too.
(CLEARS THROAT)
CAITLIN: His blood pressure is low,
his heart rate is low,
his oxygen levels are impressive.
Yeah, but nothing compared to Barry's.
No, but he's certainly
in the physical specimen range.
- In more ways than one?
- Hmm?
Oh, I wasn't paying attention.
That's enough for today, Jay. Thank you.
BARRY: Found it at the crime scene.
I mean, it's gotta be
from the meta-human that attacked me.
Huh.
- What is this stuff? Sand?
- (SIGHS)
It's not sand. It's human cells
whose myosin-two protein
have migrated to the cells' periphery.
Jay's a fellow science nerd.
Those cells have the ability
to rearrange and harden,
giving them the appearance of sand.
Mmm, how do you know this?
They belong to a meta-human
I've fought before named Sand Demon.
I know you're new here,
so I'm just gonna break it down for you.
The whole naming the bad guys thing,
that's myjam.
But you know what?
I'm gonna let you have that one,
'cause I actually kind of like it.
I'm not mad at that one.
Is that Barry's sweatshirt?
Oh, uh, sorry. lt was all we could find.
I was gonna say 'cause it looks
a lot smaller on you, right?
(CHUCKLES)
I gotta do this thing.
So, who is this Sand Demon?
I don't know his name,
but I know how to stop him.
You know what,
I think we'll be fine on our own.
Look, Barry, I don't know what else
I can do to prove to you I'm on your side.
I've been poked, prodded, I even
subjected myself to a full body scan.
I was being thorough.
Sand Demon's from my world.
Let me teach you how to stop him.
Yeah, I don't need you
to teach me anything, Jay.
Zoom sent Rothstein here to kill you.
He must've sent Sand Demon here
to do the same thing.
Don't you get it?
Anyone close to the Flash,
all of you, are in a lot of danger!
All right. If you were so good,
you would've caught him already.
Let's get Jay back to his cell.
Whoa.
Hey, Beautiful Mind.
I think you need to take a breather.
(SIGHS)
After some lengthy calculations,
I believe I have discovered
the key to proving
the proposed breach theory.
Exotic matter.
Huh.
You mean like trans-dimensional energy.
Precisely. Exotic matter,
trans-dimensional energy
will theoretically leak
from one universe into another.
Now, if this breach
Mr. Garrick is talking about is real,
if there is indeed a hole in our universe
which leads to his Earth...
We can make some adjustments and
upload an electrophotography program
to the S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite
and essentially photograph
the exotic matter leak.
Thereby giving us
the locale of said breach.
Last time I saw the kit,
it was in the fabrication room.
I shall return.
- Oh-hoo-hoo!
- (LAUGHS)
Getting goosies. All right.
Let's see what you're made of.
It's too much.
(ECHOING) Barry?
(ECHOING)
I thought it'd be harder than this.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
What's happening to me?
Hey.
I found our meta. His name is Eddie Slick.
We tracked those prints to his address.
All right. Where are you?
I'll meet you there.
- Too late, he made me.
- What? Joe!
(THUD)
(MAN GROANING)
So, can I be on your task force?
That look familiar?
- How about now? What's it look like?
- A fire.
There you go, genius. It's the fire
you started in the third ward last night.
Man, I didn't start
no fire there last night.
What, were you out of town?
Your cat get sick?
- (SCOFFS)
- Well, let me guess.
You don't start fires anymore.
You've been rehabilitated.
Yeah, I've done it before. So what?
I didn't do this one.
I always start a fire
with somethin' that's hard to trace.
You know, like acetone or somethin'.
Or maybe you don't need to use
accelerants anymore.
Iron Heights can hold people like you now.
You know that, right?
What, you think I'm one of those
meta-human freaks?
If I had powers, you don't think
I would've used 'em to get away from you?
- December 2013. Where were you?
- Why?
Answer the damn question. Where were you?
Blackgate Penitentiary.
You don't believe me? Check your records.
Jimmy, I need you
to confirm something for me.
So, Joe told me what you did.
I'm impressed.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, all I did was, you know,
run the other print
from the electrical pipe,
and track Slick down from there.
- That's all?
- (LAUGHS)
- Yeah.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
How's it going with Joe?
Any closer to cracking his "no" code?
Are you kidding me?
He's like the permission Sphinx.
Or like a magic eight ball
with just one answer.
Or like, you know, the Bridgekeeper
protecting the Holy Grail.
What is your quest?
- To join your task force.
- No.
- BOTH: Aah!
- (BOTH LAUGH)
Amazing!
Well, maybe I can
put in a good word for you.
That would mean a lot to me, Barry.
- Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
- lt's me.
Okay, so Slick wasn't in Central City
the night
the particle accelerator exploded.
He's lying.
He's a dirt bag and an arsonist,
but he's not lying about this.
He's not a meta, Barry.
Slick is the guy who jumped me.
Do you think it's possible
that the Slick in there has a...
A doppelganger?
(SIGHS) I don't know.
MALE NEWSCASTER: Yesterday's surprise
broadcast from a Star City vigilante
who is calling himself the "Green Arrow"
has spawned a massive outcry...
Catchy.
I hate it
when they put a color in their name.
- Yo.
- The sample you gave us...
- Yeah.
Not sand. Definitely human cells.
Yeah, I know. It's not him. I get it.
I hate to say it,
I think this Earth Two theory
- is starting to make sense.
- For real?
What, you think Jay is lying
about the Sand Demon?
I don't know. That's my point.
But I'm not gonnajust believe some guy
that walks in here and says a few things
that sort of check out.
"Sort of?" He was right about Zoom.
We don't even know anything about Zoom.
Or what is Zoom? ls Zoom even real?
Right now, that's just, you know,
a story around a campfire.
I mean, have you discovered a breach yet?
Not yet, but we know how to now.
Have you found one thing to suggest
that Jay is a speedster?
Is the speed force even in his system?
It doesn't appear to be, no.
See? We are scientists.
You are a journalist.
We test, we prove, we report.
That's what we do!
Except, right now, nobody here
wants to do any of that, except me.
(SIGHS)
Can we have the room for a minute?
What has happened to you?
Are you... Me?
Yes, you. The you that I grew up with.
The you that is my best friend.
The you that became the Flash. I haven't
seen that you in a very long time.
A lot's changed, Iris.
Yeah, it sure has. You have learned
how to not trust people.
What is it about Jay that you don't like?
I don't know. Uh...(SCOFFS)
It's because he reminds you
of Harrison Wells.
I trusted that man. For months.
We all did.
And you know what?
Eddie is dead, Ronnie is dead.
And a whole lot of other people
in this city, they are dead
Because we trusted him.
I'm not gonna let us
make that mistake again.
Barry, not everyone is Harrison Wells.
Besides, you defeated him
because you trusted in people,
because you believed in them.
This team that you have here,
they will follow your lead.
They'll do what you say.
But if they think
that you don't believe in them,
it won't be long
before they don't believe in you.
Get to walking. I don't want to see
your ugly mug around here again.
Sayonara.
- We didn't have probable cause.
- I get it.
One thing you should know
about dealing with these meta-humans,
nothing is ever as it seems.
Speaking of which,
you're the only person here
who wants to be on my task force.
You wanna tell me
why you're so hell-bent on being on it?
You want to tell me
why you're so hell-bent I'm not?
Didn't I just tell you I didn't want
to see your ugly mug around here again?
Well, you're gonna have to,
Detective West,
so I can get to the Flash.
(GRUNTS)
Hey!
I like you. You'll do the trick just fine.
Finally come to your senses?
Sand Demon kidnapped a police officer.
A woman that I know.
And you need my help?
I need you to help us
save her before something happens.
Guess you're gonna have to
trust me now, huh, kid?
We're looking for any structures
that promote humidity.
Greenhouses, grow rooms,
anything of the sort.
His body will literally start
to fall apart if he becomes dehydrated.
- Like dry sand.
- Exactly.
Sand Demon always attacks on two fronts.
He creates a diversion,
then strikes when you're distracted.
Okay. Then what do we do?
We use your speed to get to him
before the distraction can happen.
Jay, how do I stop somebody
who can slip through my fingers?
The way I never was able to.
With lightning.
Yo-oh!
- Are you about to pull a Zeus right now?
- What are you talking about?
Barry's going to hurl lightning
from the energy he creates when he runs.
Because lightning plus sand equals...
Glass.
Time to learn something new, kid.
(CHUCKLES)
All right.
(IMITATES LIGHTNING)
Give me a sec.
Hey,. are you good?
That was Singh.
C.C.P.D. still hasn't found anything yet.
Irony is, I didn't want Patty to have
anything to do with the damn task force
in the first place.
And she gets taken because of me.
No, no, no.
This isn't your fault, all right?
It's hard not to think that.
Well, look, we're gonna find Patty,
all right? Whatever it takes.
(SIGHS)
Flash is coming for you, you know.
Yes, I'm sure he is.
You can't beat him.
I don't care what powers you have.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Is that why you need to build
that concussive bomb?
Yeah. I know what it is. I'm a cop.
I've seen one before.
This isn't gonna kill the Flash.
I am.
This is gonna kill you.
You know you got lucky, right?
You think you were chosen,
the rest of us don't mean anything,
but it's not true. You werejust
at the right place at the right time.
Getting those powers
didn't change who you are.
They only highlighted the worst parts
of who you already were.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe not.
Either way, you and the Flash are about to
find out what those worst parts are.
(BEEPING)
I've searched all the vacant buildings
in Central City,
and none of them fit the description
that we need.
And I've looked at
any draw upticks on the electrical grid.
Nothing out of the norm, I'm afraid.
We gotta do whatever it takes.
I'll be back.
Okay, come on.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(ECHOING)
Flash is coming for you, you know.
(ECHOING) Yes, I'm sure he is.
PATTY: You can't beat him.
I don't care what powers you have.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Oh, no.
(PANTS)
Mr. Ramon? What are you doing down here?
I figured out where Patty is.
And how, exactly, did you do that?
Just a hunch.
We gotta tell Barry.
(THE FLASH GRUNTING)
Again.
(SIGHS)
(PANTING) I've been doing this
for an hour. It's not working.
It's because you're trying to rush it.
This is the one time
when you need to slow down.
Let the energy pass over you,
then simply direct it
to where you want it to go.
All right, Jay, I don't know
if I'm gonna get this in time.
You'll get it. I believe in you.
The last person who helped me like this
was a man that I looked up to. Idolized.
He taught me how to get faster,
how to get stronger,
how to use my powers to save people.
That same man murdered my mother.
It's a tough break, but I'm not him.
Yeah.
I know where they are!
The abandoned Woodrue grow house.
That's where Slick's keeping Patty.
Dude, greatjob.
And I was thinking, if I were Sand Demon,
and I were attacking a speedster
on two fronts,
I would probably wanna slow you down,
like, by using a concussive bomb,
or something like that.
That's a good thought.
He's actually used one on me before.
His body absorbs the blast,
so it doesn't affect him.
Well, kid, you're gonna have to
think of something.
You know what,
what if we give Slick a diversion?
He knows you, right?
You said you went up against him.
Yeah, but, Barry, I don't have my speed.
He doesn't know that. You got your suit?
Sure. Well, except my helmet.
Helmet?
Silver kettle helmet? Gold wings?
Don't tell me you guys found it.
(CHUCKLES)
Never thought I'd see that again.
It was my father's,
from the War of the Americas.
Did you just say War of the Americas?
I wish you would've just told us
you lost your helmet.
Would've saved us all a headache.
Well, you sure you want to do this, Flash?
Yeah.
Let's go see what you're made of, Flash.
(DEVICE TURNS ON)
I'm in the security feed. Go, Barry!
Is that you, Flash? Found your way here?
I came quite a distance.
Thought you were dead.
You were wrong, like usual.
Let the girl go.
Have at it. But you touch her,
she goes boom!
Yeah, and I think even you aren't
fast enough to save her.
(GRUNTING)
Quite a bit slower on this Earth,
aren't you, Flash?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHING)
You don't have your speed, do you?
Slick's distracted. Go, Barry!
(EXPLOSION)
(GROANS)
- Jay!
- Barry!
Patty's alive.
Must be my lucky day.
Zoom sent me here to kill you.
Now I get to kill the Flash
from two worlds before I go home.
(GROANING)
CAITLIN: He's choking Jay!
Barry, you gotta do something now!
Come on!
(YELLS)
(PANTS)
You Okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. Nice shot, kid.
Flash?
BOTH: Coming.
- You're pretty good at this.
- (CHUCKLES)
Had a lot of practice over the last year.
It was really courageous
doing what you did today.
Standing up to the Sand Demon
without any powers.
Uh, Barry did all the work.
I just stood there and took a few punches.
It was more than a few.
This is a lot harder than I thought.
Losing something that was
such a big part of who I was for so long.
I lost something
that was a part of me, too.
It's hard.
But it gets easier every day.
You just have to find a new way to live.
Just because it's a different life,
it doesn't mean it's a worse one.
And, speed or no speed,
in my book, you are still a hero today.
I'm just sorry
we did not realize it a little bit sooner.
Especially me.
- I'll leave you two speedsters alone.
- (CHUCKLES)
So, I hear they call you
the "Scarlet Speedster?"
- Yeah.
- (CHUCKLES)
- What about you?
- "Crimson Comet."
- Mmm.
- What is it with
alliteration and nicknames?
Hey, look, Jay, uh,
so thank you for all your help.
And for being so patient with me.
Anytime, kid. You're a quick study.
Took me a lot longer to learn
how to toss lightning, believe me.
I suppose I had the right teacher.
It's gonna be a lot harder
to take down Zoom.
Who is this guy?
No one knows. He showed up around
the same time as when I got my powers.
Killed a lot of people in my world.
I spent about two years tracking him down,
but he was too smart.
Too quick. He's always one step ahead.
You really think he'sjust
bringing these guys here to kill me?
Zoom was obsessed with destroying me.
Now he wants to destroy you?
Yeah.
He needs to be the best.
And he will do whatever it takes
to ensure he's the only speedster.
In any world.
- JOE: Officer Spivot.
- Detective.
- You're supposed to be home resting.
- I'm okay, sir, really.
Look, I'm sorry you got mixed up
in all this mess because of me.
It's not your fault.
Do you really think you have
what it takes to be part of my task force?
I know it, sir.
Well, I always check the jacket
of anyone I'm considering for it.
In my research on you, I found out
we got a mutual acquaintance.
Mark Mardon.
I need you to be honest with me here.
Why do you want to do this?
Mark Mardon killed my dad.
He had a little shoe shop
down on Chesterfield.
It was a cash business,
and one night, he went to Fairfield Bank
to make his weekly deposit,
and the Mardon brothers showed up.
While he was waiting in line,
Mark shot my dad
in the face for a few hundred dollars.
Then, a few months later,
Mark and his brother got powers.
Two murderers got super powers.
So that's why I'm here, sir.
That's why I'm so hell-bent
on being on your task force.
'Cause there's some bad people out there
and they can do anything.
And I may not have powers,
but I want to stop them.
You're the only person I know
who wants to do that, too.
Monday, 8:00 a.m.
Don't be late.
But, late for what?
The task force, Detective.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
FRANCINE: Joseph.
Hi.
Been a long time.
Yeah, it has.
Why are you here?
Because you didn't return my calls.
And I wanted to see you.
And our daughter.
Any progress with the electrophotography?
The satellite picture
of the city's still rendering.
While we wait,
care to tell me what's going on with you?
What? Nothing.
Two hunches in one day.
Slick's locale and that he'd be using
a concussive bomb to thwart Barry.
Do I need to inform you of the odds
of such a prediction?
Something's happening to me.
I'm starting to perceive things.
Horrible things. lt started after
Wells killed me in the other timeline.
It came back
when Atom Smasher attacked on Flash Day,
and then again when Sand Demon showed up.
I get a vibe, and then a vision
of something that's already happened.
And then it's gone.
That's how I knew where Slick was.
Cisco, this is amazing. We have to
study this. Figure outjust what to do to.
No, no, no, we're not doing any of that.
And we're certainly not
telling anybody either.
Cisco, lwould think
you'd be the one most intrigued
with knowing exactly what this is
and how it works!
I'm seeing things I don't want to see,
and knowing things I don't want to know.
I just want it to stop.
Professor, I don't want anyone
to know about this.
Not yet.
It's okay to be afraid, you know.
Wells told me this was in my future,
that he gave me this power.
But everything he did was evil.
That's what scares me, Professor.
You have to promise me
that you won't tell anyone about this.
I promise.
(MACHINE BEEPS RAPIDLY)
Oh, wow.
It appears that while we were indeed
successful in closing the Singularity,
- there was an unfortunate side effect.
- What are you talking about?
Using electrophotography, Cisco and I
were able to search Central City
for any signs of energy
entering our Earth from another dimension.
From any breaches,
as Mr. Garrick described them.
But of course,
there isn'tjust one breach.
There's 52 of them,
scattered throughout the city.
Uh, these breaches are pockets of time
and space, folded into and upon itself.
But the most significant breach of all
appears to be this one.
And where exactly is that located?
It's here. Inside S.T.A.R. Labs.
And just beyond that breach
is an entirely...
(STUTTERING)
(BODY THUDS)
Professor! Professor!
TOUR GUIDE:
I'd like to personally welcome you
to the Scientific and Technological
Advanced Research Laboratories.
Or, as it's more commonly known,
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Founded in 1991,
S.T.A.R. Labs is leading the world
in exciting new technological discoveries
that, as our motto suggests,
are truly bringing us
tomorrow's world today.
Specializing in artificial intelligence,
genetics, and meta-human...
Oh.
Are we in for an unexpected treat.
It is my absolute honor to introduce you
to the founder of S.T.A.R. Labs,
the savior of Central City,
Dr. Harrison Wells.
(APPLAUD)
Hello, kids.