Barry, there's a high-speed chase,
heading south on Milton Ave.
We lost them.
(LAUGHING)
Not gonna lose him, though.
You wanna bet?
Oh! (LAUGHS)
Oh, you wanna play? Okay.
All right, get ready to bring it!
They're not slowing down.
Of course not.
MALE ROBBER 1: There's a route!
The tunnel, take the tunnel!
CISCO: They're headed for the
Fifth Street Tunnel!
Satellite can't project in there!
What, you just thought of this now?
I didn't think he'd actually try to
outrun The Flash.
Lightning, lightning toss!
He wants to do the lightning toss!
No. No lightning.
It's a hologram, remember?
-Just... (STUTTERS)
-No. No, no, the wind-up!
So we can block their fuel division.
Yes, of course.
All right, Cisco.
This is where all those countless hours
gaming in your basement
are about to pay off.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Fingers, don't fail me now.
Leeroy!
(ROBBERS SHOUTING)
-My eyes!
-What is this?
I need a breather.
(CHUCKLES)
I didn't think
this hologram thing was gonna work.
But so far, so good!
I mean, I figured if they could get
Tupac rapping again at a concert,
we could definitely get The Flash
running around Central City.
-It's not going to last.
-There it is.
It's not gonna be long
before someone figures out,
"Oh, wait, you never say anything,
"you never touch anything,
or wait, you never go indoors."
Okay. Well, without Barry's speed,
this is as good an idea as any.
Actually, I beg to differ.
I think a better idea, instead of playing
hoodlums and holograms,
would be to rebuild
the particle accelerator
to get Barry's speed back.
BARRY: Yeah, Wells,
that's what you keep saying.
That's right.
Look at what that explosion did
to this city.
Not to mention, the last time
we tried something like that,
we blew a hole in the universe and
created, like, 50 portals to your Earth.
Which is exactly how Zoom and
his henchmen got here in the first place.
I told you.
I know how to contain the explosion.
-BARRY: Really?
-HARRISON: Yes.
You know how to contain
a dark matter explosion
that last time just radiated
all of Central City?
You tried this on your Earth, remember?
Didn't go so well.
And even if you could contain it,
I thought you said that Barry couldn't
tap into the Speed Force anymore.
It wasn't connected
the first time he got his powers.
Look, I have your Wells' data.
The Harrison Wells from this Earth,
I have his science.
I know what chemicals need to be
in your body.
I know how the lightning needs to bond
with the dark matter from
the particle accelerator explosion.
I can recreate the circumstances to
get you your speed back.
This will work. Your subterfuge,
(CHUCKLES) it's not gonna last.
But more importantly,
it's not gonna save Snow.
It's not going to bring your Caitlin back.
You wanna be ready?
Should Zoom return, if Zoom returns,
when Zoom returns,
there is only one way to do it,
and that's by getting your speed back.
-Hey.
-How are you?
-You made it.
Yeah. (SIGHS)
-BARRY: Look at this.
-HENRY: Come inside. Get warm.
BARRY: Yeah. Wow.
(SIGHS)
-Sure is a pretty drive up here.
-HENRY: It is that.
(SIGHS)
I can't help but wonder
why a speedster needs a car.
Because I am no longer a speedster.
You lost your powers?
I gave them up to save Wally, Joe's son.
Zoom had him.
So it was either give him my speed, or...
I couldn't let Wally die.
No, you couldn't.
Now Jay has taken Caitlin,
and we have no idea how to save her.
Jay took Caitlin?
Jay... (CHUCKLES AND STUTTERS)
Turns out Jay Garrick
is not The Flash from Earth-2.
He's Zoom.
Garrick?
Garrick, yeah. Why?
My mom's maiden name.
Well, maybe, maybe Wells is right.
Maybe I should try to get my powers back.
How would you do that?
By recreating
the particle accelerator explosion.
-And getting struck by lightning again?
-Mmm.
That doesn't seem like
the safest option, does it?
No.
I've watched you grow,
ever since you became The Flash.
And I am so proud of that man.
But ask yourself,
do you really need powers
in order to be that person?
It just feels like every time
something good happens in my life,
it's taken away.
Well, maybe it's time
we did something about that.
(SYSTEM COMPUTING)
Looks like The Vacuum.
Uh... What's The Vacuum?
No Fringe on Earth-2. Noted.
IRIS: What is that thing?
That is how
Barry's gonna get his speed back.
This is what you've been working on
in the workshop?
Someone has to worry about Zoom.
Okay, Barry cannot do this.
-Well, he has to, Ramon.
-You keep calling me that. But that's...
Dante?
(GASPS)
What'd you see? Zoom? Did you see Zoom?
No. I saw my brother.
I gotta go.
Let's see where everybody is. Hey.
Henry?
Iris. Hi.
It's so good to see you.
Oh, you, too.
I guess Barry dragged you back
for a bit, huh?
Looks like maybe for good.
Wait, what? Seriously?
Yeah, yeah. I figured I've spent
enough time away from my son.
Have you told Dad?
Nah. I wanted to tell him in person.
Yeah, I think he's with Wally at C.C.P.D.
I'll give him a call. Okay. (LAUGHS)
-Good to see you.
-Dad, let's get settled.
(SNIFFLES AND SIGHS)
Your sister called,
checking in when we'd be home.
As in, we need to get going?
Thanks. You know your sister.
POLICE OFFICER 1: Okay, move it, let's go.
(GRUMBLING)
Do you ever get sick of this, Joe?
Being a cop?
Oh.
Looks like someone inherited
the West I-need-to-help-people gene.
It's just, ever since The Flash saved me,
I just...
I don't know if designing cars is what
I'm meant to do with my life.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Well, I'm sure there's something out there
that'll satisfy your need for speed
and helping people.
But until then,
you should stick with engineering.
It's much safer.
We should get going before Singh comes up
with something for me to do.
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS) Zoom!
Hello, old friend.
Stay away from him.
Do not move.
Or what?
You've tried your guns on me once before.
CAITLIN: No!
Don't hurt them.
Let them go, please!
Tell everyone that this city is mine.
Anyone who disobeys me
will meet their end.
All right. Clear out.
JOE: Caitlin's with Zoom.
Why would he bring her here?
To show power.
It's exactly what he did on my Earth.
-What are you talking about?
-First thing he did was murder people.
Slaughtered a bunch of policemen,
then recruited
every meta-human he could find.
And those that disobeyed, he killed, too.
Where are the police now?
Outside the precinct.
He'll kill them, Joe. He'll kill them all.
Not with Caitlin with him.
She talked him out of killing everyone
when he took over C.C.P.D.
That's what we're gonna rely on?
Snow talking him out of it?
Joe, you need to
get those guys out of there.
What if they set up at Jitters?
It's a good idea.
It's just a block away from the precinct.
HARRISON: And then what?
What happens next?
You saw what Zoom did on my Earth.
He will do
the exact same thing here, Barry.
We need to get you your powers back.
-There must be another way.
-There's not. There's not.
JOSEPH: I'm gonna get word to Singh.
Get him to set up a task force at Jitters.
-And then what?
-JOSEPH: I don't know yet.
But I'm gonna make sure
Wally and Jesse are safe.
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS) You know they're going to
figure out a way to stop you, right?
Who? Barry? Wells? The police? No.
(LAUGHS)
Nobody can stop me now. Not anymore.
So, what's your plan?
You're just gonna kill everyone?
Not everyone.
Then why are you keeping me here?
Because I don't want to be alone anymore.
I'm never going to be with you.
You think that you're not like me,
but I've seen the darkness
inside of you, Caitlin.
Just like it was inside Killer Frost.
All you have to do is unlock it.
-(SONG PLAYING)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CISCO: Hey.
There she is.
Still refuse to dress
like a grown-up, I see.
-One grape soda.
-Uh...
No. I'm good. Thanks.
So, what's wrong?
What, something has to be wrong for me
to want to catch up with my brother?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, that's usually the way
it works with you, isn't it?
Actually, I had this feeling
that I should come and see you.
And make sure you're okay, so...
Don't tell me I'm gonna be kidnapped by
Snart and his pyromaniac friend again?
Us. You, me, us.
They kidnapped both of us.
Yeah, well, you're not the one
who almost had his hands frozen off.
Lucky I can still play the piano.
Although my octaves haven't
quite been the same,
but not that that matters to you.
Dante, I called you. More than once.
But of course, you didn't answer.
Like I said, only when something's wrong.
(SCOFFS) Yeah. Okay.
I don't know why I thought
that whole experience,
that was it,
that was gonna bring us closer.
Cisco, we haven't been close
since we were kids.
I don't think anything's
ever going to change that.
All right.
We'll bring down some more supplies later.
How you can reach us.
And exactly how long
are we supposed to be in here?
Until someone lets you out.
This isn't ideal. None of it.
But Zoom's here.
And until he's taken care of,
this is what we're doing.
This is the safest place
for the two of you right now.
-What are you going to do?
-Whatever we can.
Joe, let me do something.
Wally, there isn't anything
you can do right now.
Sit tight.
Okay, what about the... Bathroom.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
This room have Wi-Fi, at least?
(SIGHING)
JOSEPH: Wally and Jesse are all good.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
So this is what it takes to
get Barry his speed back.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. Yeah.
It's not uncomplicated, but almost there.
I told you before.
Once Barry makes up his mind,
it's impossible to change it.
Well, then we need to convince him that
this is the only way
before he decides not to do it, right?
You shouldn't have to convince anyone to
do anything against his will.
Joe, we're talking about Barry, right?
I mean, I can't... I can't imagine
you don't feel the same way.
Henry, right now, I don't know
what the right thing to do is.
Seems clear to me.
This isn't just about your son, Henry.
This is about the people in Central City,
about saving those people.
This is about stopping Zoom.
Your daughter is safe.
This could kill my son.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
The last time he was struck by lightning,
he was in a coma for nine months.
-How did that happen?
-I know what I'm doing.
You are messing with something
that is out of your control.
And what if it did work?
I mean, what then?
Joe, he's goes up against Zoom?
(STUTTERS) The monster that snapped
his back and almost killed him?
And then took the one thing
that he's convinced now that
he needs in order to make him whole?
This is the way. This is the only way.
The people of Central City need The Flash.
Guys...
(SIGHS)
I know that you care about me,
each of you, in your own way.
And you all have your own
point of view on this.
But this decision is mine.
I have to make it on my own.
DANTE: Can you put the Diamonds game on?
Ah! Sports. That's my cue.
All right, well, this was fun.
Um, good hang.
Oh, wait.
You're gonna take care of that, right?
-Dude, you invited me.
-Unbelievable.
Hey, hold up!
(INAUDIBLE)
No.
What? Cisco. Hey, wait.
(CISCO PANTING)
Yo, I need a lift home.
You still don't have a car?
Some of us don't have a fleet of
company cars at our disposal.
Dude, it's on the way.
Yeah, okay...
(BOTH GRUNTING AND GROANING)
-You okay?
-Yeah.
(BOTH PANTING)
Hello, Vibe.
Simmer down, Reaper,
we got no beef with you.
Maybe not.
But I've got beef with you, Vibe.
-Why does he keep calling you that?
-I don't know.
You killed my brother. So now you die.
Oh, my God.
You're Princess Bride-ing me right now.
You must have me mixed up
with somebody else, Inigo.
I don't think so. My brother was Reverb.
Remember now?
(GASPING)
Move!
-He looks...
-Get... Get in the van!
-He looks like...
-Now!
God, I knew there was something wrong!
Every time I see you, we get attacked by
lunatics with crazy weapons!
-(METAL CLANKING)
-(GLASS SHATTERING)
Come on, he's gonna
blast us with that thing!
CISCO: No, he's not.
Go, go!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You wanna tell me exactly what
you've gotten us into this time?
HARRISON: He calls himself Rupture.
Another meta-human under
Zoom's control from my Earth.
Great, so he's bringing
more of his friends over.
It's what I told you that he would do.
Okay, well,
Zoom must've lied to fake Dante
and told him I was the one
who killed Reverb,
'cause dude wants me dead.
We gotta do something.
What else do you know about him?
He gets his power
from that scythe he wields.
Thing's legit, too.
It almost took half the van with him.
All right, then that's what we need to do.
We need to figure out a way
to get it away from him.
Right. (SIGHS)
Okay. All right, I'm sure
I can come up with something.
I just have to figure out a way
to not tell Dante
why this psychopath looks
exactly like him.
You know what you need to do.
(SIGHS)
I need a minute.
IRIS: Hey.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
This should be an easy decision. (SCOFFS)
Why isn't it? (SIGHING)
I mean, it's not like you're picking out
what sweater you're going to wear.
Getting hit by another
particle accelerator explosion?
I mean, come on.
What if something goes wrong? What if...
I thought bringing my dad here
would make this easier.
(CHUCKLES)
It's just made it a lot harder.
Yeah, I can understand
him not wanting you to do it.
He just wants you to be safe.
What about you?
I mean, I don't know if I could go through
what I went through last time
if you get hurt.
Are you okay?
Not really.
What's up?
Do you remember when I told you
that I didn't want you going to Earth-2
if you felt like
you didn't have anything left here?
Yeah.
Because Patty left.
It wasn't just because of Patty.
What do you mean?
Barry, you've always had
someone to come home to.
Me.
I've just been thinking a lot lately.
About us.
What Wells said
about us being married in the future?
And on Earth-2?
And I can't help but wondering if,
maybe, we were meant to be together.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
So,
(STUTTERS) When I told you
how I felt about you last year...
I wasn't available in that way.
But... But I am now.
Why are you telling me this now?
Because,
Barry, I need you to know
that it doesn't matter to me
if you're The Flash or not.
(VOICE BREAKING) You, Barry, that's who
I want to see if I have a future with.
I mean,
if you still want that, too, of course.
Um,
I should go see
if Jesse and Wally need anything.
Okay.
Come on.
Yes.
-(SIGHS)
-(DOOR OPENING)
ZOOM: And?
RUPTURE: He got away. But I'll find him.
ZOOM: Later.
RUPTURE: He needs to pay for
what he did to my brother.
And he will, later, Rupture.
What do you want me to do?
The police have gathered again.
They think I've spared their lives.
Tonight, show them they're wrong.
You disapprove.
You said you would spare them.
I need to teach them a lesson.
Is that why you change your voice,
so that everyone will be afraid of you?
JAY: (ECHOING) I'm not a monster!
As you once said,
(DISTORTED VOICE)
I'm nothing but a monster.
Can we come out now?
-JOE: No!
-HARRISON: No!
(SYSTEM BEEPING)
Something's blinking over here.
-HARRISON: From C.C.P.D.
-That's Caitlin.
What about Caitlin?
She sent us a message.
Rupture is gonna attack Jitters tonight.
We gotta move, Barry.
What are you gonna do, slugger?
Having The Flash might be the best way to
stop Zoom and all the metas
he's sending over.
But look, I... Until we know for sure
that setting off the accelerator
will work,
it's too risky,
not just for me, for the entire city.
-Yeah.
-(STUTTERS) There are countless others
that would be affected
if the explosion is not contained.
-Yes, but, Allen...
-Stop, Wells. Look, I'm sorry.
I've made up my mind.
(SIGHS) I'm sorry.
We're gonna have to figure out
how to do this without The Flash.
Joe, did you reach The Flash?
-He'll be here.
-Great. These guys are almost ready.
Keep it on one.
Hey, we're all set up.
Are you sure this is the best plan?
Look, I know you can't help as The Flash,
but stopping one of Zoom's cronies
sends him a message
that we won't be intimidated.
You think I made the right decision?
I don't know, Bar.
Whether you made the right one or not,
you're gonna have to live with it.
Yeah, all right.
What is this?
You went to another Earth?
You weren't supposed to read that.
It was on your desk.
It was addressed to Mom and me.
So, yeah, I read it.
Look, I gotta go, okay?
We'll talk about this later.
No, man.
We're gonna talk about this right now.
Okay! Let's talk about this now.
What did you want me to say?
"What up, fam?
"I know you probably don't care, but I'm
going off to another Earth for a hot sec.
"If I don't make it
back in time for dinner,
"it probably didn't go so well."
Why did you even go in the first place?
Because my friends needed my help.
What kind of help?
-They needed me to vibe.
-Vibe?
That's what that lunatic called you
who attacked us.
What aren't you telling me, Cisco?
I have powers.
Powers?
What, you're like a meta-human?
I was affected when the accelerator
went off two years ago.
And now I see things, vibes, of people.
Like, visions?
So that's why you called me.
Yeah.
I had one of you.
At least I thought it was you,
until your World of Warcraft
doppelganger showed up.
-You killed his brother?
-No.
I didn't kill his brother. Of course not.
Why wouldn't you tell me any of this?
Because you're right.
It's just like you said.
We haven't been close in years and...
And there's nothing
we can do to change that.
Look, I gotta go.
Just wait for me here, okay?
You all set, Cisco?
Yeah, we're set.
Here he comes.
Now where has everybody gone?
Flash. Not who I was expecting,
but you'll be a nice warm-up.
Too slow, Rupture.
Come on, Flash!
-All right, time to win an Oscar.
-Let's do it.
-Get up.
-Are we the guys you were looking for?
Hope you like being alone,
'cause you won't be talking to anyone
in Iron Heights.
Cisco, we got him. All good.
-Okay, we're live! Sir...
-Get back. Get that camera back.
Get back.
Breaking news coming out of
Jitters coffee shop.
CCPN has learned that a meta-human
was just apprehended
after an altercation with The Flash.
-That's right...
-You told them Rupture was coming.
How?
You are smart, aren't you?
You betrayed me!
You said you would spare them.
-I guess now we're even.
-Jay, no!
My name is Zoom.
Oh, my God.
No!
Make sure you get this.
-What the...
-They gotta get out of there.
Everybody move!
Barry, don't!
No!
I told you what would happen
if you disobeyed me.
Hey, stop! Stop!
God... You've made your point.
Not quite yet.
You're an even bigger disappointment
than your brother.
Central City, The Flash you've seen
in your streets is a fake.
A hologram meant to give you hope.
But there is no more hope,
there is no more Flash,
and there's no one left
to protect your city from me.
Tell the rest of your force, Captain,
that their policing days are over.
You're only alive because of Caitlin.
Try something like this again,
and my affection for her
won't stop me from killing you,
or the rest of this city.
Did you see this?
That's what you left to go do, wasn't it?
Look, man, I know you're mad at me,
and we haven't been close in a long time.
I want things to change.
You're my brother.
Okay.
You know that wall's not just going to
open for you, right?
It might.
Yeah. Trust me. It won't.
We shouldn't be in here.
We should be out there, with them.
Why? So Zoom can take us again?
No. So we can help stop him.
What are we gonna do?
I mean, we don't have any powers.
I don't know.
But you're pretty quick at
solving "unsolvable problems."
Let's figure it out.
I will see what I can do.
It won't be long now.
He's moving faster
than he ever did on my Earth.
So what's next?
Next, he'll recruit
every meta-human he can find,
and then force them to do what he wants.
How many could be left?
We defeated most of them, didn't we?
No. You're not even close.
This is the list of meta-humans
from my Earth.
Ones that are the known, anyway.
Particle accelerator explosion
was contained on my Earth.
That didn't happen here.
Then why wouldn't we know
about other meta-humans here?
Because of The Flash.
And now that everyone knows
that he's not around...
They'll start coming out of the woodwork.
We don't know that.
What more do you need?
I told you he'd recruit meta-humans,
we've seen him do that.
I told you he would kill those officers,
we saw him do that, too.
What more do you need?
Let's do it.
I wanna do it.
One of those cops that Zoom
killed tonight, he had a son.
Same age I was when Mom was murdered.
Now another kid has to grow up
without one of their parents
because The Flash wasn't there
to stop that monster.
I left this city unprotected
by giving up my powers to Zoom.
I enabled him to rule this Earth.
I need my powers back.
Let's do it.
Let's set off the particle accelerator.
So how does this work?
It's an abbreviated version of
the accelerator evil Wells built,
except Harry is isolating
the antimatter and dark energy
to direct it to Barry
instead of the entire city.
Good. Last thing we need is
more meta-humans
running around Central City.
So Barry just gets in,
you turn it on and that's it?
Yeah. No.
Not exactly.
In addition to recreating what happened
with the particle accelerator explosion,
we also have to recreate
what happened to Barry.
Getting struck by lightning.
That's right.
Wait, so how are you going to do that?
It's not even raining outside.
Well, Ramon, you have the wand?
The one I made for Mark Mardon?
No, the one you built
for the Harry Potter convention.
Yes, of course the one
you built for Mardon.
How do you know about
that Harry Potter convention?
Get the wand, get on the roof.
-Why the roof?
-Because we're gonna need a lightning rod,
and that, Ramon, is going to be you.
All right, I'm on the roof.
I've never actually been up here before.
I think I can see my apartment from here.
Now head straight to the satellite, Ramon.
When I give you the signal,
you're going to create
a lightning storm above you.
So I'm just supposed to stand here
in the middle of a lightning storm?
Really, Ramon, chances of being struck
are slim, indeed.
Yeah, not when you're the one causing it!
All we need is one lightning bolt
to strike the satellite.
The satellite's circuitry's
connected to the breach room.
Barry's in the breach room. Just do it.
Yeah, I'm doing it.
Mozart better watch out.
Cisco Ramon's about to
conduct something nasty.
You're gonna feel these clamps,
but they're necessary.
You good?
Yeah. Are you?
I'll be fine, Joe.
Barry, whatever happens,
it will never change the way
that I feel about you.
Son, you don't have to do this
if you don't want to.
Being The Flash,
that's the best version of me.
If I don't have my speed,
I'll never be that person anymore.
I have to do this.
Okay.
You ready, Allen?
All right then. Here we go.
Think of it as hot-wiring a car.
Right, so there's a motor inside the wall.
So all we have to do is
provide electricity to make it turn on.
Exactly.
So let me just do a little here...
-Do you feel that?
-Yeah, what's happening?
The particles are becoming unstable.
Ramon, get ready.
I'm gonna release the chemicals
into his system.
Why are you doing this?
The night Barry was struck by lightning,
he was doing fingerprint analysis.
Those chemicals got in his system then,
and they are going in now.
So you're injecting them into him?
We have to recreate everything
that happened to Barry that night.
I'm okay, Iris.
Hold on, Barry!
-He's going hydrostatic.
-Almost there, almost there!
-Wells!
-Almost there!
-Ready, Ramon!
-Ready!
Now!
Expecto Patronum!
Great Scott, it's working!
No!
Initiating collision.
Barry!
It worked! Is everyone okay?
What happened?
No. What did you do to my son?
You thought you could give
The Flash his speed back?
Well done.
You killed him instead.
Dad, no...