- All right.
Prepare to die,
Klamulon scum!
The USS Engager is
about to crash the mode
on your asses.
- How do I turn this on?
Oh, cool!
Okay, all right.
Here we go.
Oh, come on, why do I have
to be the squid clam warriors?
- Because you're the enemy,
and I'm the hero.
Okay?
That's how this works.
Now, raise your shields
because I'm ranked top ten
on the global leaderboards,
and you're about
to get your butt kicked.
[lasers blasting]
Hey, hey!
That's my ship!
That's my global ranking!
No, no, no, no.
Go, go, go.
Go somewhere.
You hate this game.
- Not anymore.
[tablet beeping]
- Oh, crap, uh...
[yawns]
- Hi, Bart.
- Oh, Mom,
it's crazy you called.
I was just pulling
an all-nighter
studying for this midterm.
- Yeah, no, you weren't.
- Yeah.
No, I wasn't.
- Never try to fool someone
who's won two Pulitzers.
- Look, Nora,
I'm glad I have you.
Your last story did so well
that I would like you
to write a follow-up piece.
- Yeah, sure.
When's the deadline?
- Uh, if you could get
something to me--
- Mom, Mom?
- Yeah, that looked like
more than just bad service.
[dramatic music]
- Bart?
Nora, is that really you?
- Uh, sis,
is it just me,
or does Mom look really young?
♪
- Oh, shrap.
[heroic music]
♪
[lightning crackling]
- Mom, what's
the last thing you remember?
- I was in my office
with Taylor.
Then I got lost
in the timestream.
Guys, I need to talk to
your dad about what happened.
- Oh, Dad's off-world
with Uncle Jay.
- But past-Dad is
still looking for Mom.
I know he's gonna
figure this out.
We should really
get you back to 2022.
[soft music]
♪
[both grunt]
[dramatic music]
- Wait, what was that?
Why can't you run back in time?
- I've seen
those particles before.
Mom, I think this Still Force
is keeping you here.
- Why would Deon do that?
- Aah!
- Mom!
- No.
No, it's gone.
I'm okay.
- No, you're not.
Sis, what are we
supposed to do?
We don't even know what
this time sickness stuff is,
let alone how to cure it.
- Or how Mom got infected
in the first place.
♪
- I know this is a big step.
- Yeah, I'll say.
- Now, that--
that's a superhero.
- Are you sure I,
like, need to wear this?
Maybe we're moving too fast.
- These suits
monitor our vitals
and allow us
to communicate with each other.
That keeps us safe
just in case something happens.
- Like my connection
to the Negative Speed Force?
- I know you can handle this,
and I will be there with you
every step of the way.
[soft music]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Let's get back to training.
♪
[tense music]
- You're at Mach 1.7.
♪
1.78.
- Wow, that's double
her last recorded speed.
- Meena,
your heart rate's in the red.
You need to slow down.
- No, I can get to Mach 2.
- You're pushing yourself
too hard.
- I told you,
I got this.
[panting]
[screams]
♪
- Hey.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm fine.
I just...
I just got the wind
knocked out of me.
- What were you thinking?
Speed healing doesn't
make you invincible.
- Don't you think I know that?
[somber music]
♪
I'm sorry.
And you're right, okay?
♪
I'm a disaster.
[sniffles]
♪
- I'll talk to her.
- Get it together, Meena.
Get it together.
Oh, God.
You got this.
Pull it together.
Okay.
[groans]
I'm done.
[sighs]
♪
I'm sorry, Flash.
I appreciate everything
you've done for me, but...
I'm not ready for this.
- Meena, why are you
pushing yourself so hard?
- You can lap the planet
in seconds.
I can barely stay
on a treadmill.
Flash, how am I supposed
to be a hero?
- You already are.
- No, I'm not.
Flash,
I don't have what it takes.
- I think you do.
- Why?
Because, honestly, when I first
built that machine, I wanted...
♪
I wanted...
nothing.
Look.
I'll never be
the person you are.
♪
Holy crap!
You're--
- Officer Barry Allen, CSI.
- So the fastest man alive
is a badge with a day job?
♪
That's so--
- Ordinary.
Yeah, that's my point.
You'd be surprised
at people's capacity
to rise up and help others
during a crisis.
They just need to be
given the opportunity.
That suit,
that's your opportunity.
I think you're gonna be
surprised at how well it fits,
but you have
to give yourself the chance.
♪
- [sighs]
Damn, that's good.
- [chuckles]
I have my moments.
♪
- Fine.
I'll give it a shot.
Besides,
I already have my own suit.
I guess all I need is
my own superhero name.
- No, you already
have that too.
♪
Fast Track.
- Fast Track.
♪
[ominous music]
- So you are here
to fulfil my destiny?
Well, you can start
by getting me out
of this prison
and then...
giving me my speed back.
- Oh, you'll get everything
that you deserve, Thawne.
- Is that right?
And just what is that
going to cost me?
- Just one thing.
♪
Your life.
- No, no!
Wait, no!
[electricity crackling]
- Ahh!
[dramatic music]
♪
[alarms beeping]
[dramatic music]
- What is it?
- There was just a major
energy surge at Lian Yu.
- What kind of energy?
- The temporal isotopic kind.
- Deon.
- Let us know what you find
when you get there.
After last time,
I reached out to Cisco.
S.T.A.R. Labs now has a secure
comm link to the island.
[ominous music]
♪
- Find anything, boss?
- It's Thawne.
He's dead.
It's like his body was aged
a hundred years in an instant.
- Which the Still Force
could easily do.
- Why would Deon
kill Thawne now?
It doesn't make any sense.
- Deon hasn't been himself
since we went
to search for Iris.
- Sorry, Bar.
Gotta bounce.
- That's exactly
what I was afraid of.
Her time sickness
has infected his mind.
Chester, can
our isotopic sensor find him?
- No, it worked last time
because Deon exited
the Still Force for a moment,
but now that he's disappeared,
we're flying blind.
- With the power to travel
across the past,
present, and future,
he could turn up at any moment.
♪
- So you were out patrolling
last night?
You told me
you were working late!
- I was, kinda.
Look, babe, you don't
have to worry about me.
Guess what,
I don't just throw emotions
in and out of people now.
I can induce vertigo too.
- You mean like Rosa Dillon?
- Yeah.
- Babe,
that's not a good thing.
- Well, it's not like I'm
some kind of supervillain, Joe.
I would think that
you would be happy for me.
- I am, but I just wish
I knew how all this happened.
- Oh, yeah,
speak of the devil,
we are about to have a visitor.
[soft music]
Wait for it.
[knock at door]
Come on in, Rosa.
- Hold up, hold up.
Ain't nobody invite
your criminal behind in here.
- Really,
because I think she did
when she stole all my powers.
- Uh...
- Wait, you what?
Cecile, is that
why you leveled up?
- Okay, time out.
I think--
I think that I can explain.
- You think?
I want my powers back.
Why do you think
I was tailing you?
- Wait, you what?
- I was tailing her.
Right after my powers
went missing,
I got a mental image
of her in my mind,
so yeah,
I thought I'd swing by
to see if I could get
to the bottom of all this.
- Now, that makes sense,
but how did Cecile end up
with your meta-power?
- I, um--hear me out.
You know
how I can throw emotions
into somebody else,
I can take them--
- Yeah, I taught you that.
- Right.
It seems like now,
somehow I can actually
tap into the powers
of any psychic that's nearby.
Okay, you live off
of Third Street, right?
- Yes.
Last night,
I was out patrolling.
There was somebody
who needed protection
from a mugger,
and I thought to myself,
I wonder if I could use
Rosa's vertigo powers.
And I tried it,
and I did it,
and it worked.
That can't be a coincidence.
[claps]
- Congratulations,
you cracked the case,
but I still don't have
my powers back.
You got an explanation
for that too?
♪
- No, she doesn't.
- No, I don't.
- Then what am I
supposed to do?
- I don't know.
What?
My theory is just that.
It's a theory.
- Then you need to test it.
♪
- Hey, David.
Sorry to bother you, man.
I need a favor
from the chief of police.
I need two visitor passes
to the Meta Wing
in Iron Heights ASAP.
Thank you so much.
♪
- So that's what's causing
my life to be a nightmare.
- I'm afraid so.
It's a negative tachyon,
and your body
is flooded with them.
They're the cause
of your time sickness.
- So how'd they get there?
- I don't know.
But the negative
tachyons inside of you
are increasing exponentially,
and that's putting
an incredible strain
on your physiology.
Your body can't
withstand this forever.
- [grunts]
- Mom!
- It's okay.
- [grunts]
♪
I saw the Forces--
Bashir, Deon, Alexa,
but something happened.
They were different.
Why would I
see something like that?
- All I can theorize is
that somehow your sickness
must also be triggering
some kind of temporal visions.
♪
- It's the only way.
- Agreed.
But someone needs to stay here
to keep Mom safe.
- You were with Dad in the
Speed Force, I'll stay here.
- I'll go to 2022 and get help.
- Are you sure
that's a good idea?
- No, but if anybody
can help save Mom,
it's Dad.
♪
[machine powers down]
- You're gonna
burn yourself out.
You've been training
all morning with the Flash,
and now instead of resting,
you're pushing yourself
even harder.
- Eobard,
you're worrying too much.
- Meena, you need to ease up.
- Not yet.
I need to keep training.
- Why,
so you can kill yourself?
What's gotten into you?
- [panting]
Eobard, what's the point
of having these powers if--
[rumbling]
[dramatic music]
♪
- We've been looking
for you, Eobard.
- Who are you people?
- Who we are isn't important,
at least not to a dead man.
- Whoever or whatever you are,
you need to get the hell out
of my building...
♪
Before I make you.
- Ooh, I like her.
- Well, don't get too attached.
Playtime's almost over.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You'll find out soon enough.
- I'm not kidding.
Back off!
- Or what?
[chuckles]
You have no idea
who you're up against, do you?
- Then enlighten me.
- We're the true Forces
of the universe,
ones written in darkness.
And we're here
to kill you, Thawne,
so you can fulfil your purpose.
♪
Don't look so negative.
I promise I'll make it fast.
♪
- I won't let you hurt him.
- I was hoping you'd say that.
- I can taste her fear.
[smacking lips]
Ooh, amuse-bouche.
- Hold on.
♪
- Too easy.
Looks like
you're the last Thawne left.
[chuckles]
Hope you enjoyed
your time, man,
'cause you're all out.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What is it?
- He's coming.
[tense music]
- Ooh.
Not fast enough, Flash.
Besides,
this ain't your kind of party.
- I'm gonna crush you
like a grape.
♪
What the--
[both panting]
♪
- Who are they?
- Oh!
- Whoa, whoa!
- It's my speed.
Something's wrong.
- Well, it probably
had something to do
with that light show
you just put on.
- No, it's like when Meena
attacked me at the dam,
only much stronger.
- They tried to kill Eobard.
- Just like at Lian Yu.
- And that's
just the beginning.
You see,
there's only room
for one set of Forces
in the universe--
negative ones--
and we're tired
of sharing our turf.
- Speed Force Nora
and the others,
what did you do to them?
- Oh, he just gave them
a case of the Mondays.
It'll be a while
before you see them again.
- Why are you doing this,
and what does it
have to do with me?
- You're not the Avatar.
You just being here
makes us weak.
- So sacrifices
gotta be made, Flash,
and you've gotta pay
for what you did.
♪
- I don't care who they are.
I won't let them hurt Eobard.
- Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- All right, we need
to get you some help.
Come on.
- I think it just arrived.
- Uh, Chester?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm so sorry
about the hacking comms thing,
but once I saw
the Flash's vitals,
I had to track him down.
You think you could bring
the Flash to S.T.A.R. Labs?
- Yeah.
Be there in under a minute.
- Good,
'cause he's got company.
- The best kind.
♪
- Caitlin,
why are you helping me?
I thought
you gave up on Frost.
- I had,
but after I saw your designs,
I realized I'll never stop
trying to bring her back.
I can't.
[somber music]
♪
- Okay, if all goes
according to plan,
the pod's cerebral circuitry
should stimulate,
and then reactivate
Frost's residual subconscious
left inside your mind.
- And then
I'll get her voice back.
- Yeah, and when
she's with us again...
- We can pick up where we left
off and build her a new body.
♪
- Hey, what if Barry
discovers what we're doing?
You know, he pulls you out,
destroys the CRC?
- Then we'll find another way.
♪
[air hissing]
- It was like slamming
into a brick wall.
It didn't matter
how fast I was.
The negative tachyons
in Mom's body
won't let her travel
through time.
- I still can't believe we have
to fight Negative Forces
or that they even exist.
- True that,
and what'd they mean by,
"Thawne's not the Avatar"?
- [sighs]
- Dad, you said that it was
just Negative Deon,
Alexa, and Bashir,
but there was
no Negative Speed Force Nora.
Where was she?
- This other Deon said
I had to pay for what I did,
and I took away
Thawne's speed
by severing his connection
to the Negative Speed Force.
- Which might have
erased Negative Nora.
- That must be
why they're weaker now
and why they blame you.
- Maybe they think
that killing Thawne
will somehow bring back the
Negative Speed Force Avatar.
- Hold on, if they're tired
of sharing their turf,
they'd want to level
the playing field.
- By weakening
the Forces we know.
♪
Iris' time sickness,
it was never about her.
I mean, they knew
Deon would try to help.
- And Mom's sickness would
spread to the Positive Forces.
- Taking them out
of the picture.
- Wait, hold up,
what happens
if the bad Forces end up
being the only ones left?
- Then every speedster we know
could cease to exist.
- Leaving the entire planet
unprotected
from the Negative Forces.
- Nora, you need
to run back to 2049.
You and Bart have
to watch over Iris
while we face the forces here.
- But you're still too weak
to fight again.
Dad, if they come back--
- They will.
But nobody's
gonna die tonight.
We're gonna find a way
to save your Mom and end this.
I promise.
♪
- Bar, these Forces,
they're literally gods,
and there's three of them.
How are we supposed
to fight that?
♪
[dramatic music]
- It's all three
isotopic energy masses:
Electrochemical, temporal,
and geothermic.
- They're gathering strength
on their own planes
of existence.
That's what's bleeding through.
♪
- Look, guys,
I know this feels different.
That's because it is.
This is personal to them,
which means it's not
gonna be an ordinary fight.
We need to be ready
for anything.
Have you heard back
from Cecile yet?
- Yeah, Joe said
she was at Iron Heights
and that it's important.
She thinks she might know how
her powers are leveling up,
but she'll be here
as soon as she can.
- Good, 'cause we're gonna need
all the meta-power we can get.
♪
- Mona, I don't have much time,
so here's how it's gonna go.
I'm gonna take those off,
you're gonna read my mind,
tell me what I'm thinking
if you can.
- With pleasure.
- Don't get any ideas, Mona.
She's taking the cuffs off,
but this is
a meta-interrogation cell.
The walls are meta-dampened,
so you won't be able
to read anything except us.
- Like I want to read
that empty mind of yours.
- Watch it.
- Or what?
You're gonna put me back
in prison?
- Can we save it
for the playground, ladies?
And, Mona,
no tricks.
♪
- Now, let's have some fun.
[eerie music]
♪
Oh.
What did you do to me?
My telepathy's gone.
- Oh, excuse me!
Somebody has a potty mouth!
And no, Rosa, you are not
the good cop in this situation.
- 'Cause you stole
her powers too!
♪
What is it?
[overlapping chatter]
- I can hear them--
all of them, everyone.
I can hear the entire city,
all of their thoughts.
[overlapping chatter]
- An ordinary fight.
- Barry.
- We need to be ready
for anything.
- Barry.
We have to go.
- What the hell, Horton?
- No, no way.
She said these walls
were meta-dampened.
How can you read every single
mind in town all at once?
Even I couldn't do that.
- I don't know.
I don't understand it either.
- I think I do.
Look, I don't know how,
but, Horton,
you're becoming one
of the most powerful metas
this city has ever seen.
The planet,
for that matter.
- What?
♪
What's happening to me?
[ominous music]
♪
- You're telling me
this is just some sick play
by the Negative Forces?
Damn.
- The negative tachyons
replicating inside Iris' body
keep increasing.
I don't know if she'll survive
another temporal attack.
- There's gotta be
something we can do.
- There is, pray that
Barry can find the strength
to defeat the Negative Forces
because it's the only way
to cure Iris and save her life.
♪
- Hang on.
- There's no time
to stop and talk.
I need to keep training
for our next fight.
- Hey!
I know you,
and that adorable brow furrow
thing you're doing,
that only happens
when something's
really bothering you.
So you want to tell me
what's wrong now?
I mean, aside from cosmic
forces trying to kill me,
because you have
been pushing yourself
beyond your limits all day
and you still
haven't told me why.
And with the way
things are now, I get it.
Look, I'm scared too, okay?
But whatever happens,
let's face it together.
♪
- I told Barry this morning
that I could never
be a hero like him.
[sighs]
I don't have what it takes.
- So he convinced you
otherwise,
and that's why
you're training so hard.
You're afraid
of letting him down.
- No.
I'm afraid of letting you down.
- What?
- Eobard, this was
always supposed to be you.
And it should be.
This is your dream.
- You're keeping it alive.
- That's what makes it worse.
I never wanted
to be a speedster.
I still don't.
Eobard, I wanted to share
meta-powers with the world
so people could
heal their bodies
and live fuller lives.
[soft music]
That was my dream.
I'm afraid of losing it.
- You're not,
because what you're doing now,
risking your life to fight
side by side with the Flash
to make me safer,
to make the city safer...
♪
Meena, it's the same dream.
And you may not be able
to share your speed,
but you're doing
something far greater.
You're sharing yourself
with all of us.
♪
And I couldn't be prouder.
- [sighs]
♪
[chuckles]
How did I get so lucky?
- Blame it on a résumé.
♪
- God, I wish the B.L.O.C.
wasn't only programmed
to just me.
If only there was a way for me
to share this gift with you.
♪
- You can.
I'm sorry.
I just came down
to check on your training.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Meena, I've...
- It's fine.
- Been trying all day
to find a way to give us
a fighting chance
against the threats
we're facing with no luck,
but you just found the answer.
♪
- Which is?
- I'm gonna teach Meena
how to share her powers
and turn you into a speedster.
[epic music]
♪
[lightning crackling]
[dramatic music]
♪
[machine powers down]
- Okay, people.
According
to S.T.A.R. Labs' satellites,
those isotopic energies
are on the move.
- Let me guess,
they're headed straight for us.
- The Negative Forces want
a fight, let's give it to them.
- You guys know the plan.
Just keep them occupied
long enough for us to do this.
♪
- Okay.
Now what?
- Take Eobard's hand,
listen to my voice,
and concentrate.
- All right.
Let's do this thing.
- You're gonna
need this first.
♪
- Flash, what happened
to me at Keystone Dam,
what if it happens to Eobard?
- It won't,
for the same reason
you were able
to become yourself again.
The love you have for
each other balances you both.
[lightning crackling]
♪
- What is this, the B-Team?
You gotta be kidding me.
- Clearly,
y'all have a death wish.
- I'm a little disappointed.
- Get used to that feeling.
♪
- [screams]
[rumbling]
[tense music]
♪
- Nothing's happening.
- Transferring speed
isn't just about energy,
it's about how you feel.
You're sharing more
than your powers,
you're sharing yourself.
Imagine giving
the most important part
of yourself to another
by letting them in.
♪
[electricity sparking]
- [laughing ominously]
♪
- No way,
you're not this strong.
- Allegra, now!
- [grunts]
Okay, that's really bad.
- [cackling]
Ooh, Allegra, time to play.
- I'll make this fast.
[grunts]
♪
- Do your worst lady.
That's an inverse energy trap.
Good luck fighting yourself.
♪
- I feel alive.
But there's so much hate,
it burns.
♪
- The negative speed force
is trying to influence you.
You have to fight it.
You have to help each
other find a balance.
[electricity crackling]
- ♪ I'm over here
[chuckling]
Boo!
♪
So close.
Psst!
[cackles]
Ooh, you're bad at this.
[cackling]
Poor orphan Allegra,
the power of light
in your hands,
but born into a life
of darkness.
- What is that,
some kind of evil poetry diss?
'Cause you're gonna need a lot
more than that to scare me.
- [cackles]
Why would I scare you...
when I can kill you?
♪
- I can't
hold them much longer.
- The field's breaking down.
She's too strong.
♪
- [cackling]
[cackling]
- [grunts]
♪
- No, don't give up,
don't give up.
We've got to buy them
as much time as we can.
- It's too late!
You're all out.
- Ahh--
♪
- Meena,
remember what I told you,
this is your chance,
your moment.
You can do this.
You can be a hero.
And you're not alone.
[electricity crackling]
♪
- Looks like
y'all gotta bounce.
Permanently.
♪
- Back off, all of you.
That's your only warning.
♪
- Seriously,
that's all you got?
- It's three
against one, Flash.
- You don't stand a chance.
- Good thing I brought backup.
♪
[tense music]
- It's time for some payback.
- You sure we can do this?
- As long as we work together.
♪
- Ah!
- [grunts]
- Where'd he go?
- I'm guessing not far.
♪
- Ahh!
- Mom!
Mom, you have
to stay with us this time.
- The Forces
he's fighting--Barry.
It's a new moment in time.
- What does she mean?
- It's another vision.
I think she's seeing
something from 2022.
- This can't be happening.
Time is changing.
- Whatever's happening
in the past
is connected
to her time sickness,
and now it's
literally changing the future.
- Which means we have
no idea how this'll turn out.
- I can't--agh!
- No, Mom, stop.
Wait, we're not losing you.
- Agh!
- No, no, wait, no!
- Sacrifices
gotta be made, Flash.
- What is it?
- The visions,
they're not random.
♪
- You can't win, Flash.
We're weak, but so are you,
which means we can
handle anything you dish out.
♪
- This might be our only window
to win this fight,
but to do it,
I need you two to hold them
here while I get ready.
♪
- I have to give in.
- No, Mom, you can't!
- I have to.
It's the only way to see
what's really happening.
- Iris, wait.
- You're not the Avatar.
You just
being here makes us weak.
- And you gotta pay
for what you did.
- What are you doing?
We needed that to find Iris!
- Sacrifices gotta be made.
- No, the sacrifice
isn't Thawne.
♪
It never was.
- The real sacrifice is...
♪
[soft music]
- Iris?
Iris, Iris.
No, no, no, no...
♪
I told you, Flash,
we're tired
of taking the backseat
to those sorry-ass opposites
of yours.
Sacrifices had to happen.
♪
And that ain't the only one.
[chuckles ominously]
♪
- Huh--what?
[tense music]
- [groans]
- Eobard?
Eobard?
- Get back!
♪
Something's wrong!
Agh!
Ahh, ahh!
- What's happening to him?
- [screaming]
[dramatic music]
- Ahh!
- Agh!
♪
- Ahh!
- Thanks
for the resurrection,
Flash.
♪
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.
[electricity crackling]