This is a fucking mess, son,
but don't you worry.
Daddy's home.
What's up, shit birds?
You have five minutes
to make your opening st...
You guys fucking ready?
So...
Noir's a vegetable.
And you didn't do this.
Look, there was no terrorist.
It was Vought.
It's a fucking coup.
Victoria Neuman's making a team
that can keep tabs on the Supes.
If you're interested.
I still want to fight Vought.
I just... I want
to do it the right way.
Not covered in
quite as many guts.
- Maeve!
- I'm sorry.
You're gonna leave me
and Elena alone.
You're gonna stop
hunting Starlight,
- or I release this.
- Becca's alive.
She had a little boy, Ryan,
spitting image of Homelander.
I do not want my son
to have to go
through what I went through.
Ryan, no!
Promise me that you will
save him no matter what
and you will get him back to me.
People love what I have to say.
They believe in it.
They just don't like
the word "Nazi."
That's all.
Becca!
Where... is my son?!
Storm front.
I knew you'd be here.
How could you do this?
I loved you.
You'll always be in my heart.
But the Fourth Reich is
in my soul.
Join me,
and we can reign together
for a thousand years.
- Never.
- You and I are the same.
Perfect genetic specimens.
Think of how beautiful
our children could be.
They would be
the best of both of us.
Flawless Aryan Kindersoldaten.
No.
They'd be monsters.
Like you.
Your choice, Liebchen.
But not even you
could stop me alone.
He's not alone.
What?
Can't let you guys have
all the fun.
Guess this means
we're breaking up.
Nazi bitch.
Die, Untermensch.
Grab the flash drive!
She's too strong!
How can we beat her?
As a team.
Homelander!
Over here. This way.
Maeve,
right here. Look to your right.
Maeve!
To your left! Left!
Maeve, over here!
Here with Adam Bourke,
- the director of Dawn of The Seven.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- It seems like all those reshoots paid off, my friend.
Right, well,
after the, you know,
"Stormfront's a Nazi" thing,
we had real talks about
shelving the movie or just
dumping it on Vought Plus.
But, uh, the fans spoke
with those
"Release the Bourke Cut"
hashtags.
You guys, I love you!
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- How do I... look?
- You look perfect.
Okay.
Oh!
Starlight, Starlight!
- Starlight!
- Starlight, to the right, to the right!
Starlight, over here!
Starlight, this way!
Starlight, look this way!
Singles, please.
- Starlight!
- One second.
- Move over, other guy!
- Okay.
No, no, no. Over here.
Singles, please.
Over here, to the left!
To the left!
Just a couple more shots!
It's quite the star
you've got there.
And thanks to Congresswoman
Neuman for joining us tonight.
I hope it demonstrates
Vought welcomes the oversight
from the Bureau
of Superhuman Affairs.
We've been able to root out
a few bad apples together.
- Thank you.
If I could just steal him away.
Do me a favor and kill me.
- Only if it's murder-suicide.
- Okay.
Nadia! Nadia!
Hey! Nadia!
- Another picture, please.
- Hey, Nadia!
A-Train, it's been over a year
since you've raced.
When are we gonna see you
on the track again?
Real soon.
You know, but we had reshoots,
I've been training.
But that race is coming,
full speed ahead
for the A-Train.
But it's been over a year,
and the people are wondering...
Only questions about the movie.
- Thank you so much.
- Okay, thank you.
- Um, we have Black Noir here for you.
- Black Noir.
Hughie, my man.
I love the big dick energy, bro.
- Who you wearing?
- A-Train, right here!
I have no idea.
Good. I didn't give a fuck.
Guys!
Pic!
Who'd have thought, after
everything we've been through,
- that we'd be here together?
- Okay, one more time.
Right in the camera.
Yeah.
Who'd have thought?
How could you not know all along
that Storm front was a Nazi?
Well, I am just a man
who fell for the wrong woman.
- Uh, but, uh...
- Fell for the wrong woman.
But out of crisis comes change.
- Out of crisis comes change.
- So I spent the last year
really slowing down
and reconnecting with myself.
And I am very excited for
everyone to meet the real me.
You shitty fucking director!
Tony Gilroy had
to reshoot all your shit!
I know I'm a fraud, babe!
I'm a fraud!
- Oh, fuck!
- Pull my hair!
- Fuck yeah!
- Yeah, pull my hair!
- Yeah, I'm pulling it, baby!
- No, pull it out!
Yeah, yeah!
Mr. Campbell.
Uh...
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
Jesus Christ!
Not quite.
You look sharp.
French blue.
That suits you.
What are you doing here?
I found that little asshole
we've been on all month.
He's having a knees-up
at a penthouse tonight.
Okay. Who's your source?
My source is
none of your fucking business.
Look, me and the Boys,
we're all set up.
We just need you to, uh...
give us a green light.
Okay.
Um, I'll talk to Neuman.
Or you could take
your tongue out of her ass,
slap on your big-boy pants
and make a fucking decision.
You got something
you want to say to me?
I think
I just fucking said it, son.
Just photos.
No violence or maiming
or-or-or-or torture
or curb stomping
or setting anyone on fire.
Oh, uh...
I'll get you
them expense reports you wanted.
Tomorrow.
♪ Don't stop, hey...
♪ Don't stop...
God, what is he doing?
- Give it to her, babe.
- Oh, my God.
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go...
Am I really
seeing what I'm seeing?
All she needs now is a vagina.
The little asshole.
Hey.
I'm Tyler.
- What the fuck?
- Yeah! Did you see that?
Excuse me.
I want you inside me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Oh, yes.
- Ready?
- Oh, yes.
I'm gonna rock
your fucking dick, babe.
Yes.
Ah, that's it.
Okay, Okay.
Oh, don't... don't stop.
Don't stop.
Get to the prostate.
Yes.
Oh, don't stop.
No!
Is okay.
- Get the fuck out!
- Is okay.
I see nothing. I go, okay?
Wait!
You can't leave.
No, no, no, no, no.
No! No, put a in!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
He's trying to get in my ass!
Get him out!
Fucking bitch!
Oh, no!
No, go!
Go on, son.
Have a bump.
Fucking lightweight.
No, no, no.
Call the bureau.
You're gonna let him live?
Governor's orders.
And put that little cunt
on his side.
Jiminy Cricket's OD'ing.
- Morning, morning.
- Mm.
Good morning.
What do you say I brush my teeth
and we do things to each other?
I say go get the Aquafresh.
Okay.
♪ She's been living
in her uptown world...
Come on,
I know you have it in you!
Keep pushing! Go!
Hey, Dad, you got to move
the phone away from your face.
- Just...
- How's th... Oh, yeah, okay.
- There you are. Yeah.
- There we are. Um, so...
Funny story. Um, you know
my dentist, Dr. Horowitz?
- Mm-hmm.
- I was getting a crown, and he said
he was a huge Starlight fan.
- Oh, is he?
- Like, out of the blue, and I'm like,
"Well, you know,
she's dating my son."
He was, "What?!" So, um...
I gave him your number.
Dad, why would, why would
you give him my number, Dad?
- Why would I give...?
-  - Dad?
Dad, you got to move,
you got to move the phone away
- from your fucking face.
- Sorry, sorry.
- You know, I was... anyway.
- Listen, I, uh,
I got to get to work, so we'll
see you for dinner on Sunday?
- Yeah.
- I'll talk to you soon.
- Bye-bye.
- I love you...
He's sweet.
Yeah. So, uh, you gonna
stay over again tonight?
Don't know. It depends.
Um, you gonna bring Aquafresh?
I would brush with Monistat
if it meant I could
have sex with... you.
That's very romantic.
All right, I'll see you later.
Have a good day.
♪ She'll understand
what kind of guy I've been...
- Hey, good morning.
- Hello.
- Campbell.
- Morning.
- So a Tri-Delt from Wesleyan
caught a Supe masturbating
outside her window.
Okay, how's she know
it's a Supe?
Window was on a 737.
That's a Supe.
Uh, okay, I'll have an I.D.
for you by tomorrow.
Thanks, Ivy.
That's Hugh Campbell, right?
He helped bring down Storm front?
And he's dating Starlight.
♪ Uptown girl,
she's been living...
Awesome.
From serving
his country as a soldier
to serving the American people
as Secretary of Defense,
a Democrat who reaches
across the aisle...
Give me a bite.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
...unite and heal America...
You want the Valtrex
before or after?
You love that bagel so much
you're gonna fake herpes?
I could have herpes.
You don't think
I could have herpes?
How'd surveillance go
with Termite last night?
You know, I haven't checked in
with Butcher yet, but...
I'm sure it went fine.
Don't... No, don't give me
that face.
I'll bet you a crisp $100 bill
- something got fucked up.
- You don't know that.
Okay, take the bet.
I'm-I'm not gonna
take the bet, but...
- Uh, wow, really?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, still, Butcher
delivers every time.
And I have to apologize
for him every time.
Look, Butcher's the guy
you want in a shooting war.
No question.
But we're in peacetime.
Oh, my God.
So worth the herpes.
It's great.
Hi.
Can I help you?
I'm just waiting to see Nadia.
That's Congresswoman
Victoria Neuman.
You have the wrong person.
We're best friends.
I will give her the message.
This way, pal.
Tony.
She'll remember.
I.D.?
There you go.
Go ahead.
Cheers.
Straight ahead.
Butcher!
All right, lad, how are you?
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Eh?
Look at you. Here you go.
You'll never guess what that is.
You done your homework?
I hate math.
Aunt Grace gets pissed
when I'm wrong.
Yeah, you and me both.
Mom used to help.
She was really good at math.
Yeah.
She was a clever one.
I had another nightmare.
Same one? Your Dad?
This time, he...
...burns everything down
and then kills me.
One day, you'll be tough enough.
And then he can't hurt you.
But till then,
you're safe here
with the colonel.
Honest.
Connect Four.
Oh, you...
you cheeky little blighter.
You could stay if you want.
Well, that's
a generous offer, Grace,
but I ain't banged
a blue hair since I was a lad.
You know, calling you an asshole
is an insult to assholes.
My point is, Marvin got out.
Maybe there's hope for you, too.
I shouldn't get
too close to him.
I would just fuck it up.
I hear you've been on the
straight and narrow all year.
No drinking, no killing Supes.
You even follow Hugh Campbell's
orders without strangling him.
Now you're just being cruel.
I know you're not doing
all that for yourself.
So then who?
Exactly.
That alone makes you a better
man than your father ever was.
Maybe you're not
such an asshole.
Get the kid a fucking burger
now and then, would you?
There he is!
Bro!
Bro, come here.
Hey.
It's great to see you.
Did you just have
the slot before me?
Yeah, I'm just stumping
for my book Deeper.
Went awesome.
I sent you a copy.
Did you not get it?
Don't worry, I got,
like, hundreds of them.
I'll send you more. It's about
how me and my wife Cassandra
escaped that fucking cult.
You remember my wife
Cassandra, right?
Oh, did you see that profile
that Malcolm Glad well
did on me in The New Yorker?
He called me "the next
Leah Remini." No big deal.
I mean, my numbers are
going up, Coach.
Put me back in the game.
How?
How did you get
the slot before me?
Uh...
It was a fucked-up mistake.
- That talent booker is so fucking fired.
- I'm asking him.
I'm asking you.
I don't... I, uh...
I don't know. I don't know.
But it's...
fucking ridiculous.
I-I should never go before you.
Obviously.
I'm a nobody compared to you.
You want to know a secret?
I didn't even write
the fucking book.
Shia LaBeouf's ghostwriter did.
Uh, it's crazy.
It's stupid. Sorry.
That's very sweet of you
to say, Deep.
Good to see you.
You, too, sir.
- Hey.
What was that?
I actually think
that went pretty well.
Let's get to the elephant
in the room.
The mainstream media
won't leave it alone.
- Mm.
- How could you not know
that Storm front was a Nazi?
Well, okay.
So let me say it again, Cam.
Um, I may be a superhero,
but I'm also just a man
who fell in love
with the wrong woman.
Well, we all know
what that's like.
Right, yeah.
Look, I-I'm not perfect,
Cameron.
Far from it. Uh...
I know I'm bulletproof
on the outside.
But in here, this?
It isn't.
I'm just as human
as all the rest of you.
More with Homelander...
after this.
And we're clear!
That sounded really good.
Who's the birthday girl? Hey!
Want to see what I got you?
- Yeah.
- Ooh, you're gonna love this.
Yeah, boy!
- See how it fits.
- All right, all right, all right.
- That looks great.
- Birthday photos.
- Oh, Jackie, can you take this?
- Oh. Sure.
Thank you.
Oh, Todd, Todd! Over here.
Photos!
Photos, photos.
- Okay, with Jackie? Okay.
- You know what?
- It's okay. All right.
- Let's all say, um, "Happy birthday, Janine!"
Happy birthday, Janine!
Oh, silly face, silly face.
Now superhero!
Give us a superhero.
You don't have to do that.
- Oh, I don't mind.
- Marvin?
You taking your Lexapro?
I'm fine, Monique.
This is just me helping out
at my daughter's birthday party.
Great party, by the way.
Yeah, she's...
She's having fun.
I'm sorry about
all the superhero stuff.
- She insisted, and...
- It's all good.
It's behind me now. I'm over it.
You've seen me
in the last 12 months, right?
I'm straight.
It's ancient history.
- I know.
- Hey.
You got a couple of hours
on Friday night?
I was thinking maybe we could
meet over at Cafe Delfini's,
have some tilapia, go over
some co-parenting things.
Mm, co-parenting things?
- Yeah.
- Really?
Where we had our first date?
Strictly business.
Scheduling things, like soccer
practice, dance recital...
You got to move on, Marvin.
The way you moved on
with Todd or...
Sorry.
Happy birthday, baby!
V24, huh?
Marketing is
still testing the name.
But it's the future, Bob.
One dose of this temporary V
gives a soldier
24 hours of powers.
Give or take.
And then they return
right back to normal.
How stable is it?
Still ironing out the kinks.
And if it's temporary,
that means the DoD
has to keep buying doses.
At how much a hit?
Two million, roughly.
So over the course
of a month-long operation,
that's 60 million per soldier.
600 million per squad.
Campaign going well, is it?
I appreciate your contribution
to my super PAC.
People do love
a cowboy in the White House.
I hear they're even
calling you Dakota Bob.
So how would it look
if you pass up
the opportunity to give
our brave soldiers superpowers?
Supes in the Army are
an unmitigated shits how.
What Black Noir did
to that Hard Rock Cafe in Lagos?
Should be brought up
on war crimes.
You're right.
I'm sorry?
You are absolutely right.
The problem, of course, was
making the super into heroes.
I don't follow.
Making them figures
to be worshipped.
The fame, the movies,
the depraved sex...
it ruined them.
Cone of silence?
In five years, I hope to be out
of the superhero business
entirely.
Bullshit.
This should be
a serious company.
A defense
and pharmaceutical company.
Not a day care
dealing with spoiled children
and dead prostitutes.
But the point is,
you won't have to worry
about any of that.
Because your soldiers will
only be super...
temporarily.
The product...
finally perfected.
Stan...
when you say Compound V...
- V24.
- ...do you know what the public hears?
Gestapo.
Swastika.
And that's your fault.
You used a Nazi to sell it.
Compound V is
radio-fucking-active.
It's not gonna fly in Congress.
I still have a few strings
that I can pull in Congress.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, really?
I got good news and bad news.
- What do you want to hear first?
- The, uh, good news.
There's no good news.
Bad news is,
Termite's off the table.
- What?
- Vought just closed
a big endorsement
for him with Terminex.
We've been chasing Termite
for months!
I know, but after Butcher
force-fed him a metric Belushi
of coke, I didn't have
much leverage, did I?
It was just a little coke
'cause he was...
- small.
- Anyway...
he's going to the Global
Wellness Retreat in Malibu,
and in return we're getting
Cold Snap, Stacker and Air burst.
Fucking B-listers! Really?
Three B-listers, real assholes.
Cold Snap for domestic battery.
It's not a bad trade.
How much is Supe collateral
down this year?
- Sixty percent.
That's 60% more people at home
with their kids,
and we did that.
Hughie, you and I built
this place.
And we did it the right way
without being covered
in blood and guts.
Right?
Y-You're irritating, but...
- but yes.
- Okay.
So, please, just...
trust me.
You must be having
a fucking laugh.
That little cunt crawled up
a guy's cock
and blew him to bits.
He almost killed Frenchie,
and you're just gonna
let him go
'cause Stan Edgar asked nice?
Supe collateral damage
is down 60%.
Oh, come off it.
That's that twat Neuman talking.
She has locked up
more Supes this year
- than every other year combined.
- Then you're a fucking twat.
Hughie, you're working
with Vought!
I'm...
Fuck me. I should've done
Termite when I had the chance.
Look, look, look,
things are good.
We're actually winning.
Winning, are we?
Yeah.
Locking up a couple of nobodies
ain't winning.
They got all the money
and all the power,
and they want us dead.
We're outmanned and outgunned,
and we got to put
them cunts in a box
before they do it to us.
If you would just
compromise a little bit...
"Compromise"? Fuck you.
Your whole life's a compromise.
Hey, at least
I have a fucking life!
I didn't mean that.
Look. Look.
Can we just stop dancing
around this?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I left.
- You think I give a shite?
- Yeah, I think you do.
I think you're pissed
that M.M. and I both left.
M.M. was a bit of a loss.
You not so much.
Butcher...
it's been a year.
You can stop all this.
It's okay to stop.
To move on.
She would've wanted you to.
Oi, Stevie fucking Wonder!
Will you knock it off?
You're doing me fucking head in!
Jesus fucking Christ.
Everyone's losing
their fucking minds.
Hey.
Forget it.
Or maybe they're just
trying to be happy.
I thought it sounded great.
Homelander and Queen Maeve.
- Oh, my God, they're leaving us!
- Take these two!
- Whoa, no.
- Just these two, please!
No. What?
So they can tell the world
that we left the rest of them
to fucking die?
No. You stay back!
All of you, stay back!
You stay the fuck back,
or I'll laser you, goddamn it!
I'll laser
every fucking one of you!
Excuse me, Starlight.
I need the room.
I got a meeting with Stan.
Actually, I invited you both.
Have a seat.
- Great.
- Oh, uh...
I remember when you first
arrived, Starlight.
A farm girl from Kansas.
Bright-eyed like Dorothy in Oz.
Iowa. And not a farm.
Oh, well, look
how far you've come.
Polling at 96,
a new Vought record.
I don't have to tell you
that our brand has been a bit...
tarnished since that
nasty business last year.
But you have restored
a wholesome,
trustworthy image to the company
when we needed it the most.
Which is why
the board wants to make you
cocaptain of The Seven.
What?
Co...
Cocaptain?
But-but...
Homelander is captain.
I mean, you're-you're captain.
This will be
beneficial to you both.
Your numbers are down,
what, uh, double digits?
The public still associates you
with Storm front.
This would be a real bump.
A rising tide lifts all boats.
That's very thoughtful
of you, Stan.
Um...
- When does the board vote?
- They already did this morning.
All that's left is for
Starlight to say yes.
No. I mean, I mean,
I'm flattered,
thank you, but no, thank you.
If anybody, it should be Maeve.
- Maeve doesn't have a 96.
- Nobody does.
Except you, apparently.
Homelander?
Could you give us a moment?
Look, I'd really like
to keep discussing this.
Absolutely.
Set a time with Samantha,
and we'll get you in.
Mm, great.
- No problem.
- Excellent.
My schedule is pretty full, but
I'll try and find you a window.
Okay, sir, there is no way.
I mean, you saw him. He's...
He can get as pissy as he wants.
As long as I'm CEO of Vought,
he's under control,
and we both know why.
Y-You know that he can,
he can probably hear you.
Good. I hope he does.
Starlight.
Real power...
isn't this.
It's the ability to bend
the world to your will.
You would decide
what The Seven do.
What causes they support.
Full authority
to fill the team's empty slots.
I'm offering you
real power.
You should think about it.
It's been almost a year since
Church Chairman Alastair Adana
has been seen in public.
Yeah, well, they say he's on,
uh, sabbatical, but who knows?
What I do know is that there are
literally thousands
of tortured souls
who are trapped
in that church right now
who want to escape
just like me and my wife did.
- That's very brave.
- Thank you.
Your book Deeper has been
a game changer.
Obviously, you've had
your past troubles,
but I think people are surprised
at how sensitive
and insightful you really are.
After your last TED talk,
Vanity Fair called you
- "the Thinking Person's Superhero."
- They did.
With only
three contestants left,
who will join The Seven?
Will it be Supersonic?
He first exploded onto
the scene as Drummer Boy.
♪ Kick off those Uggs and slide
up next to me, all right...
Hero, Christian
and triple-threat member
of the multiplatinum group
Super-Sweet...
♪ Got Netflix in my mailbox...
When he broke hearts
everywhere by dating
a certain rising star
on the Capes for Christ circuit.
But that was long ago.
Today Drummer Boy has become
a man, going solo,
changing his name to Supersonic
and setting his sights
on American Hero.
And maybe on an old flame.
Or is it Starlight who's
keeping the fires burning?
Live wire... please hang up
your cape and go.
Two contestants will
win coveted slots in The Seven.
So who will go home,
and who will be
the next American Hero?
Hi.
Oh, my God. Come on.
- Hi. Hey. Hi.
- Hi!
Hughie, what's up, my man?
How's it going, guys?
What are you guys doing?
We're running lines, actually.
For a reality show?
Right?
The reality behind the reality.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, um... oh, man,
I was in the, uh, control room,
and they had this, like,
- bio thing on you.
- Oh, God, I'm sorry.
Yeah, that boy band shit is
so embarrassing.
You know what, I really like
- "Rock My Kiss."
- Really?
- I do.
- Did you? I... I actually...
Wait, I thought
it made you puke.
- Shut up. Shut up!
- It's true.
What are you guys, what are
you, what are you talking about?
Okay, be careful. I can still
kick you off the show.
He has a right to know.
Come on, we were, what, 19?
- Eighteen.
- Okay, so 18, the band
was performing at the opening
of Voughtland St. Louis.
But before the show, Annie
and I snuck into a cant in a.
And they had those... I mean,
those yards of margarita...
I must have drank
a quarter mile.
So, middle of the show,
we bring out Starlight
to do a number.
And Little Orphan Alky
steps onto the stage,
and she just pukes
in front of a festival crowd.
I mean, the tweens,
they lost their shit.
Humiliating.
Wow, that's... I-I had
no idea you drank back then.
Oh, yeah, Miss Goody Two-Shoes,
she had a fun side, big time.
And-and really great
you guys are still...
so close, just really,
really great.
You have nothing to worry about.
No. No, no, no, totally.
He's gross.
And you've known him
your whole life.
And he, you know, took your
virginity, so why would I worry?
Okay, it was a mutual
taking of virginities.
And you know what,
it happened so long ago,
and only a couple of times.
- Wait, really?
- Yeah, you know, we were really religious,
and we weren't married,
so it felt weird having sex.
I mean, sex-sex.
We did a ton of butt stuff.
I'm fucking with you.
Okay.
- Come on.
- Yeah, never do that again.
Wow, uh...
Cocaptain, huh?
Wow, that's, uh...
- Is it crazy?
- I mean,
Vought's the worst thing
that's ever happened to us,
and now you want
to be their Ronald McDonald?
So, yeah, a little crazy.
Yeah, but first female cocaptain
of any super team.
Ever. I mean...
think about what that would mean
to millions of girls.
I'm sorry, I-I'm just...
surprised, I guess.
I mean, is this
your mom talking or you?
I'm the one whose feet bled
at all of those pageants.
Okay? I've paid a lot.
And, finally, finally,
I could have some real power
that I could use, and I
could make trouble at Vought.
Do some real good.
Or Homelander can murder you.
Someone needs
to stand up to this guy.
- And that has to be you?
- Not just me.
I mean,
I could bring good people
into The Seven
who could help me.
What, you mean
like your boyfriend?
It's not a good look, Hughie.
No one even bats an eye
when a man climbs the ladder.
Okay, you're right,
you're right, you're right.
Look, I'm-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
So I'll...
see you later tonight?
Don't bother with the Aquafresh.
Hey, Homelander.
What are you drinking?
- Shake Shack.
- Oh.
You want one?
I'll go grab a P.A. for...
Oh, no, no. Thank you, though.
Yeah.
I see you got the extra
whipped cream in there, huh?
Yeah.
Yummers.
I guess you wanted to cram in
as much "fat fuck"
as possible, huh?
- Did I do something wrong?
- You think I haven't seen you?
Shoving back two dozen cupcakes
in the break room?
Nine servings on Miro's
truffle risotto night?
- Hmm?
- Hey, man.
You know I need
30,000 calories a day.
Maybe when you actually ran,
you did.
But now you're
just eating your feelings.
Making us look ridiculous.
"The Fastest Man Alive."
What a fucking joke.
- Fuck you, man.
- What did you say?
Nothing. Nothing.
- What did you say to me?!
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Shit!
I'm so sorry.
I-I didn't mean it.
- Say it.
- I'm s...
- Say it!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But not everyone
rejects Storm front.
A group called the Storm chasers
still celebrate
her racist dogma.
After finding
each other on 4chan,
the Storm chasers rallied online
in the days and weeks after...
How are you?
Wonderful now that you're here.
Is something wrong, my love?
You know, I'm just...
skulking around
like a frightened schoolgirl.
Apologizing
when I've done nothing wrong.
Today, uh, they made
Starlight cocaptain.
No.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
My poor baby.
I don't know how much more
of this I can take.
No one suffers like you suffer.
Let me help.
Honestly...
I have to put up
with these fucking people.
They hold that video
over my head month after month.
They took my son from me.
They want me... Here you go.
See, they want me
weak, castrated.
They should be worshipping me.
Tremble at my feet.
Put a knife
to their children's throat
like Abraham to Isaac,
if I say so.
Oh, they will.
When you lead an army
of Aryan Ubermensch
to their victory.
What? No.
- Yes. Yes.
- No.
No, no! How many times
do I have to tell you?
We don't need
a fucking master race.
I'm the master race.
That's the point.
That's the whole point.
No, you have to.
It took a hundred years,
but we finally found you.
- No, no.
- It's your destiny.
Oh, my God. Whatever.
Just, uh...
- rest.
- What?!
No. Please.
Please!
I heard Termite walked.
My lead was good. What happened?
Don't ask.
Well, we got to talk.
I think I have something.
Soldier Boy. So what?
Remember how he died?
Stopping a nuclear meltdown
in Ohio.
'83, '84, I think,
got buried beneath a reactor.
Always thought it was bollocks.
Yeah, you thought right.
Read.
- What's B.C.L. RED?
- If you believe
the rumors, it's the thing
that killed Soldier Boy.
Some kind of gun or weapon
or something.
Had to have been
a fucking H-bomb.
He was nearly as strong as...
Ah.
If we can find this... weapon
or whatever it is,
maybe we can use it
to blow Homelander's
fucking brains out.
If it is real,
not some fucking fable.
Payback.
- What a bunch of fucking wankers.
- I'll say.
When The Seven passed them
as the number one super team,
Crimson Countess sent me
a box of cat shit.
She was fucking Soldier Boy.
And, uh, Gunpowder was
his sidekick.
If anyone knows
what happened to him, they do.
Your mate Noir was in Payback.
Why don't you ask him?
Even if that walking tumor
could talk,
it wouldn't be to me. Here.
What's this?
It's Temp V.
One shot makes you
a Supe for 24 hours.
I mean, they think.
It's still in R&D.
Oh, great, so powers, maybe.
Maybe my bollocks swell up
like footballs.
- Yeah?
- Payback may be a bunch of fuck holes,
but they're strong.
And they're dangerous.
If you're going against them,
you're gonna need it.
And what makes you think
that me,
of all people, would want
to turn into one of you?
This is our best chance
to kill Homelander.
Don't fuck it up.
If you want
to watch me have a wank,
it'll cost you a tenner.
May I come in?
Where's Ryan?
He's at 673
Nosh My Bollocks Ave.
You want a pen and paper?
You know
I could just pull you apart
limb by limb.
Make you tell me.
Nah, that'd be worthless.
Victim always goes into shock.
You got to start small.
Fingers, toenails, ears.
He's my son, William.
My family.
I'm gonna find him
sooner or later.
Look, uh...
I don't mean to be rude,
but can we just skip to the part
where you laser
my fucking brains out?
Oh, for Christ sakes.
Where's the sport in that?
No, look at you.
It'd be like putting down
a wounded dog.
You're the one
with your tail between your legs
on all them fucking talk shows.
And then they go
and make Starlight cocaptain.
That's got to sting.
Touché, William.
Touché.
What are you doing here?
Vought and the fucking bureau.
The wheeling and dealing.
And-and-and-and giving
and taking.
Just to keep everything
exactly the same.
And you and me?
Well, they treat us
like old playthings
and put us up
on the fucking shelf?
Hmm?
Treat us like we're obsolete.
Doesn't that make you angry?
Yeah.
It does.
What if...
what if it doesn't
have to be that way?
What if...
you and I...
Well, what if we share
a different destiny?
Something... a little more...
scorched earth,
shock and awe,
blood and bone.
And in the end,
only one of us left standing.
Isn't that what you want?
Too fucking right.
More than anything.
Mm-hmm.
I look forward to it.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Nadia! Hey, Nadia!
Hey, Tony.
How you been?
Not as good as you.
I see you on TV
all the time, Nadia.
I'm not Nadia anymore.
You can't come around
the office calling me that.
We were best friends.
That was a long time ago, Tony.
We should tell everyone.
You have a platform now.
We should tell everyone
about Red River.
It's not that easy, Tony.
I need people to know
what happened to me.
Tony, I can't.
Please.
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, Tony.
Why'd you have to come
looking for me?
It's me.
I'm in trouble.
Fuck! Um...
I need...
I need a team.
Alleyway,
East 12th and Broadway.