My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
The Quark Sphere,
filled with Barry's
unique genetic marker,
and programmed to
track his specific DNA,
using the electrical
current of the Speed Force.
Once we track Barry and we pull him out,
the Quark Sphere will
trick the Speed Force
into thinking he's still there.
What is happening?
We're moving so quickly
that everyone else is still.
- Flash.
I'm your father's doppelganger.
Jesse, you're a speedster.
Yeah, it's pretty cool, right?
- Everything okay with Jesse?
- Yes.
I spent the summer assembling
a support staff for her,
but then Jesse goes and
kicks me off the team.
They took a vote. I'm out.
I don't even have a
home to return to now.
- Barry...
- Iris...
What... I'm...
- You're moving with me, okay?
- What?
You're moving as fast as I am,
- like in the courtroom.
- Why? Didn't you...
I can't. I... I can't.
- What? What's wrong?
- I can't.
What...
I can't save us this time.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
Ready when you are, Barry.
- I'm ready!
- Are you serious?
Come on, Cisco, just one more.
She said two hours ago.
Look, you know he's not gonna
stop until he makes it through.
Come on, you know how Barry gets.
- One more.
- Thank you.
All right, here we go.
Three...
two... one.
Now!
Damn it!
- One more.
- Iris?
Uh, Barry, look, why don't we take five?
No, not until I get
this, all right? Come on.
- Listen, Miyagi...
- What?
I've been here all day,
opening breaches, all right,
so unless you wanna
rub your hands together
and do some magic shoulder popping...
I'm not rubbing your shoulder.
That's what I thought. I'm taking five.
- Hey, come on!
- I'm taking five!
I...
I don't understand why I can't get this.
Well, probably because
you've been up all night.
But that shouldn't matter.
Look, Barry, a bridge
closes in three picoseconds.
DeVoe's could shut even faster.
Look, I'm just saying
that this might not even be
the best plan to catch him anyway.
It's a plan, you know.
It's the only one we have right now.
Well, and what if he uses
his force field against you?
You don't know how to get out of it yet.
I don't know, Iris, but,
I mean, we need something.
We have no leads on the
next three bus metas,
no way to track DeVoe,
no way to stop him.
I mean, he can't be this smart.
I'm sorry, but, I mean,
we've been at this for months,
and we have nothing.
I mean, maybe that's the problem.
You know, sometimes you have to...
take a breather and let
the answer come to you.
- Do something else for a bit.
- Like what?
Like...
date night, for starters.
You know, we haven't
had any quality time,
just you and me, since our honeymoon.
- Which was severely cut short.
- Mm-hmm.
I know we're the Flash, but we...
We're also Barry and Iris.
No, you're right, yeah.
All right, I'm gonna make
a reservation tonight,
someplace very romantic.
Oh...
Sounds perfect.
How is it we live
together, work together,
sleep in the same bed together,
but it stills feels like
we don't spend any real time
as husband and wife?
Allen, West Allen,
Cortex now!
- I have no idea.
- Mm-hmm.
Let's go.
What is this?
This is a signature field,
mapping every time DeVoe's
gone in and out of his layer
in the pocket dimension.
- All of these?
- All of them.
So, how did you do this?
I didn't do it, actually. Ramon did.
But all I did was just come up
with a really complex
and eloquent algorithm
to track the warping signatures.
Don't do that, all right?
Don't do that. Don't be modest.
- All right? It's unbecoming.
- You're unbecoming.
You wish I was unbecoming, all right?
Do you know that these are DeVoe?
These are DeVoe, all right?
This is when Marlize grabbed him
from Izzy at Lawrence Hills.
This is when he showed
up at Iron Heights prison.
- This is DeVoe's house.
- And this is the alleyway
in the city center,
where he abducted you.
How long has this been going on?
- Oh, wait for it.
- The past three years.
- Three years?
- DeVoe orchestrated everything
to get the people he wanted on the bus.
He's been planning this a long time.
We got a planner, just like Thawne.
- Just like Thawne.
- So, how do we use this?
All we can do right now
is just wait for the
next marker to appear,
try to get the jump on him.
That and keep an eye on Ralph,
using the old buddy system.
Has anyone seen Ralph today?
No, he's downstairs, moving in.
He's very nervous.
- I don't know why.
- I don't know why either.
He's a superhero.
People with powers
are ready for anything.
Ah! Son of a breach!
- Sorry...
- Jesse.
I just came in through the breach room.
Hey, Jesse, welcome back.
What are you... What are you doing here?
Wally's not here.
Uh, you know, an apology
cube usually works better
when there's an actual apology on it.
You get the sentiment.
What's this?
That is a, uh, mental activity dampener.
It's for DA Cecile Horton.
It keeps her from hearing
other people's thoughts.
Kinda clunky.
That's what she said.
Literally, that's what she said.
The second version's more streamlined.
And what's all this?
Those are thoughts, musings.
How to stop DeVoe.
Wow, he's really in your head, isn't he?
Yeah, a lot of people are nowadays,
thanks to you.
Look, I thought you
wanted me to come here
so we could talk about this.
No, I want you to stop
bringing up your mother.
I will, once you deal with her death.
- I have.
- No, you haven't.
Yes, I have. She died!
Years ago, she died.
There was nothing I
could do to save her.
End of story. Life goes on.
Yeah, for everyone but you.
Look, Dad, when Mom died,
you didn't talk about it...
- There's nothing to...
- Ever.
And you've been upset ever since.
You've been miserable,
and you make everyone
around you miserable.
I mean, why do you think I
asked you to leave my team?
Your team's a bunch of idiots.
- Okay.
- No offense.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
I came here to stop DeVoe.
No, you stayed because of DeVoe.
A distinction without a difference.
Dad, there is always going
to be some bad guy to stop,
- or algorithm to write...
- Yeah, that's it.
- Or problem to solve.
- Yeah, that's my point.
Exactly.
Look...
I didn't want to talk about her death,
but... I did,
and it helped a lot.
Trust me, you are never going to be able
to move on with your life
until you talk about this.
Jesse! I can't!
I...
Look, Jesse...
Your mother...
You'll never understand.
Yeah. I guess I won't.
What?
Get down!
- You all right, Jonesy?
- I'll live.
Here. Put pressure on it.
Help's on the way.
Who the hell are these guys?
They came out of nowhere.
I don't know, but they want
whatever is in that container.
Where is that?
One of the hangars out at Waid Airfield.
My dad said CCPD was
escorting ARGUS there
this morning for something.
- He's there, Barry.
- Yeah, we gotta go.
- We'll meet you there.
- Cool, I'll come too.
Could use the distraction.
Come on, Flash.
Guys, seven officers
and ARGUS agents down.
They just blew open the
ARGUS transport container.
West side of the hangar.
One armed assailant inside.
Got it!
Come on.
It's ready.
- Stay down!
- Hey! Hey!
Move! Move, move!
Just you and us now.
Nice work, everyone.
It's over.
For all of Central City.
No...
Barry...
We're too late.
- Oh, that's a nuclear bomb.
- I know.
And its core has already gone critical.
I know.
The second we slow down, it's over.
I know. That's not helping.
Well, how long do you think we have?
We just have to keep moving
till we figure out a way to stop it.
Oka... okay, we could
run it to the Badlands.
No, if we run that long,
it'll speed up the reaction.
We won't make it outside
the city before it explodes.
Well, we can't run
everyone outside the city.
I know.
We're talking hundreds
of thousands of people.
I mean, if there were more
than just the two of us,
there's not enough time.
Wait, that's it.
- Jay Garrick.
- What about him?
Uh, he might know what to do.
Go to Earth-3, get him,
bring him back here as
fast as you can, okay?
I need you right now, man.
Hey.
Whoa, what is going on?
You're moving with me at super-speed.
What?
Is this what it looks like when you run?
More or less.
I have to say, it's a little uneventful.
Hey... come with me.
I'm guessing this is
our Ark of the Covenant.
Something like that, yeah.
Whoa...
Yeah, that will
definitely melt your face.
That... that looks like an
experimental fission engine,
deuterium isotopes.
That would make this an
inertial confinement cage
to stop the radiation.
But with enough pressure,
the isotopes inside, they split,
they produce heat, they produce light.
It starts out blue,
turns yellow, turns purple,
and then it's game over.
Just please tell me there's
a way we can undo it.
I think we're way past that point.
- We have to do something.
- I...
What if... what if I
breach it to a dead earth,
- like I did with Fallout?
- Of course, yeah.
That's a great idea. All right, do it.
What's wrong?
I think I might be all breached out.
I... I don't know,
I think I breached one
too many times today.
No, that's not it.
A breach is a folding
of space-time, right,
so when we're moving this fast, we...
When we're moving this fast,
when we're moving in Flashtime,
then we don't have the time necessary
- for a breach to form.
- Exactly.
Then that means I can't...
That means I... I can't...
Hey... hey...
What's wrong?
I don't know.
You're not a speedster.
Your body can't handle
moving this fast very long.
I gotta let go, all right?
Come here.
All right.
Wait... ask Harry.
He'll know.
All right.
I hope so.
A-Allen...
- Wells, hey...
- Uh, why are you touching me?
- Th...
- Listen...
Am I in... am I in...
Yes, you're in Fla...
You're in Flashtime, yes.
Flashtime? What is Flashtime?
I didn't... Cisco just came up with it.
Wait, you did this with Ramon
before you did this with me?
- Hey, we don't have time!
- Hey, listen, the alarm...
Yes, the alarm that we left
for was an ARGUS transport.
- It had a fission engine in it.
- And it exploded?
That's why I'm in this Flashti...
Wait... Jesse. Where's Jesse?
She's... no, she's fine.
She left. She went to...
Okay, Allen, that's great,
because if this city's gonna explode,
you need to send her as far
away from here as possible...
No, listen... listen, she went
to Earth-3 to get Jay Garrick.
- She's coming back?
- Yes, we need his help.
Allen, no, no, no, no,
we cannot let her...
Hey! Right now, I need your help, okay?
- How do I stop the reaction?
- You can't stop this.
What do you mean? Then what do I do?
You can't... you have to
send it away from here.
- Well, I can't. We tried...
- Open... have Ramon open a...
Cisco can't... he can't.
Cisco can't open a breach.
- He can't.
- 'Cause there's no time.
- Exactly.
- But you can.
- What do you mean?
- Allen, you can.
- No, I can't.
- Listen to me...
- What are you talking about?
- Allen, listen to me,
space-time breaches and the
portal to the Speed Force
operate under different physics.
You open a portal to the Speed Force.
You send it there.
What will it do to the Speed Force?
- What is... why am I weak?
- Wells...
I know. Wells, hey...
hey... It's the speed-the...
Listen to me, will an explosion...
- The speed's affecting me.
- I know.
Will an explosion that
big affect the Speed Force?
I don't... think so.
What? What do you mean
you don't think so?
- I don't know.
- Wells, hey, look at me...
What the heck?
- Get her out of here.
- I'm gonna... I'll try...
- Allen... Allen...
- All right.
- How'd you do that?
- Um, I'm not sure.
I've... I've been able to do it
ever since I came out
of the Speed Force.
- That's a hell of a new trick.
- Look, right now...
I know. Jesse showed me the nuke.
- We're in trouble, kid.
- Well, I don't know.
Wells has an idea that
he thinks might work.
Yeah? What is it?
We send the bomb into the Speed Force,
let it detonate in there.
- Like hell you will.
- What do you mean? Why not?
Because, Flash, if you do that,
we may lose the Speed Force forever.
What do you mean we might
lose the Speed Force?
An explosion that size
could destroy it completely.
If that were to happen,
every speedster across space and time
would lose access to
their speed instantly.
Every speedster?
Even if it got rid of Thawne
and every other evil
speedster in the multiverse,
you cannot do this.
I won't let you.
Well, I'm sorry, Jay,
if this is the only way to
save everyone in the city,
I have to.
Barry, listen to me...
Harry didn't know anything
about the Speed Force, okay?
None of us really do.
And this isn't just about speed.
You're talking about destroying
an essential element of the multiverse.
Nobody knows what the
consequences will be.
You were trapped in
there longer than I was.
- If anyone can underst...
- Then what, Jay?
What's your idea?
Uh, okay, look...
I mean, did my dad have any other ideas?
No... but we couldn't
talk for very long.
Jay, I'm sorry, I just...
No, it's all right, kid. I get it.
All right, back to basics.
In nuclear fission,
enormous energy is created
by a chain reaction of atoms
splitting and releasing neutrons.
It's nearly impossible
to reverse this process,
but, theoretically...
you could restore stability.
How?
One way is to offset the loss of mass
- by nuclear fusion.
- Great.
You have some sort of
machine lying around here
that could generate that kind of energy?
No, we don't.
But the other way,
considering our predicament,
seems more promising.
Which is what?
Cooling it down.
We need to hurry.
Hey.
I see all these frozen
people around me, Flash,
and this time, it's not my fault.
We need your help.
Three of you now. What's going on?
- The cargo in this container.
- It's a nuclear bomb.
Yeah, and it went kaboom.
- Dandy.
- Come here.
Whoo, it's toasty in here.
We need you to cool it down.
You want me to cool
down a nuclear reaction
that's already gone critical?
You're serious?
Quickly, please, Ms. Frost.
All right, let's give it a whirl.
Didn't go quite how I expected.
Tr... try again.
Oh, no...
Huh, so that's what heat feels like.
You're burning up.
Come on.
All right, it's okay.
All right.
I have to let you go, all right?
Barry?
Don't let Caity die.
Okay.
Now what?
Guess we have to find that
fusion machine after all.
- Wait a second...
- What?
What if we're the machine?
How so?
Well, you said that we could
offset the energy of the bomb
with the energy from nuclear fusion.
Theoretically.
Right, and the reaction in
that container's giving off,
I don't know, 3 million tons of energy?
- Give or take.
- So, 3 megatons of energy,
that's 3 billion joules.
Each lightning bolt gives off
roughly 1 billion joules, so...
So if we all throw a lightning bolt
- at the same time...
- It could be enough.
That's enough. That'll
work. Let's do it.
- Whoa.
- Jay!
Hey...
- Hey...
- I'm...
I'm not used to going this long.
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
- Damn legs...
- It's all right.
Don't work like they once did.
It's okay.
I'm not gonna be able to
finish this one, Flash.
- I'm sorry.
- Just rest.
I'm so... sorry.
It's okay.
Barry, the two of us can't
produce enough lightning power
to offset the energy from that bomb.
I mean, even if we had
full speed, which we don't,
at least I don't.
We have to send it into the Speed Force.
- You... you heard what Jay said.
- And Harry said it'd be fine.
No, he said he thinks it would be fine.
Barry, my dad never
thinks anything, he knows.
Jay was right, we can't do it.
Damn it!
Okay, what if...
I don't know, what
if we run back in time
and stop this bomb from ever going off?
No, Jesse, we can't do that.
Yeah, well, it's kind
of our only option.
It's not an option.
Even if it saves the
city and everyone in it?
It's not saving them, okay?
The second you alter the timeline,
everything changes,
especially the people you love.
Trust me. I learned that the hard way.
Yeah, well, maybe a
new version of my dad
isn't the worst thing in the world.
Look, Jesse, whatever
problems you two have,
they're not gonna get solved
by forcing him to do
something he doesn't want to.
He has to make that decision.
Oh, God.
The reaction's combustion's
reached its final phase.
I think we're slowing down.
So everything else is speeding up.
Barry, I don't have any more ideas.
Me either.
I don't know how much longer I can run.
All right, you have to get out of here.
Use the speed you have
left to get back to Earth-2.
- Your dad wanted you to leave.
- Yeah, I heard.
So you'd be safe, Jesse.
He loves you, all right?
More than anything.
- Go.
- No, I can't just...
Go.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
I wish I could tell you this
while you could still hear me,
but...
I know how happy Mom made you
and how sad you are now that she's gone.
But I just... I don't know
why you won't talk about it.
I know maybe I don't need to,
but...
I just want you to be happy again.
That's all I've ever wanted.
I've got to think of something.
Oh, come on.
- Barry...
- Iris...
What... I'm...
You're moving as fast as I am...
- What?
- Like in the courtroom.
- Why? Why? Didn't you...
- I can't...
- Oh, my God, what?
- I can't.
Uh, what?
I can't save us this time.
What do you mean, you can't save us?
- There's a bomb...
- What?
A nuke, it's already gone off.
- I can't stop it.
- Wait-but there's a way.
There's gotta be something
that you can do, Barry.
No, listen, I tried.
We tried everything.
We tried lightning, we
tried cooling it down,
reaching into a dead earth,
but there's nothing that will work.
- I don't know what to do.
- Okay.
Hey, as soon as I stop, it's gonna...
I know. I know. Hey... hey, it's okay.
I don't know how much
longer I can hold out.
- I'm so tired.
- Okay.
It's okay, Barry.
Oh, my God, you're burning up.
I've been at this for a while...
- Okay.
- For me.
Hey... hey, look at me, look at me...
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be sorry.
- Look at me. Be here with me.
- I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
This isn't exactly
the quality time I was imagining, but...
It's still nice.
Every moment with you,
Barry, has always been nice.
Every moment.
You're my lightning rod, Iris.
What?
You said you tried
to use lightning. How?
We tried. It... it didn't work.
If it was powerful enough,
it could've fused the split atoms,
it could've negated
the effects of the bomb,
but I can't do it alone.
I can't generate that kind of energy.
No, you can't...
but the Speed Force can.
What?
When you went into the Speed Force,
the... the lightning from the storm...
One of those bullets
would be more than enough,
but I... I can't.
How... how could I
draw that out? I can't.
No, listen, when we freed you,
Cisco and Caitlin,
they used a Quark Sphere
programmed with your genetic marker
to trick the Speed Force into thinking
that you were still in there.
I just need to get that sphere,
and the storm will chase me.
It's like you said,
a lightning rod to
bring out the lightning.
- Come back to me.
- As fast as I can.
Here we go.
Ahh!
Jesse?
You're here.
I'm here.
Barry?
Barry!
Flash!
Flash?
Are we dead?
No.
That's good.
Today, I showed you how
easy a city can fall.
Mark my words,
nuclear power will bring only
destruction to the world.
You'll see it again,
and when you do,
you'll all remember the
name, Veronica Dale,
and fully understand my actions.
Eden Corps! Eden Corps!
Eden Co...
I feel like she's saying, "Eden Corps."
As in blasting everybody
back to the days of the Garden of Eden.
This was to air after the city fell.
Found her manifesto at her apartment.
Environmental activist
turned animal liberator
- turned domestic terrorist.
- Turned craycray.
How did she find out about
the ARGUS drop anyway?
Somebody must have tipped her off.
- DeVoe.
- But why would he, or she...
Whoever... why blow up the whole city?
Why kill nearly everyone here?
Maybe there is no method to the madness.
Well, this was fun, as usual,
but it's time for the ol' Crimson Comet
to head back home.
Thanks for your help, Jay.
Yeah, if it wasn't
for you two and Jesse,
it'd be a completely different
story in the news right now.
You were a big part of that, Iris.
Credit where credit's due.
My sentiments exactly.
So, when you get home, you need to rest.
Your glucose levels are pretty low.
Thanks. When I get back,
I think I'll be doing
nothing but getting rest.
Meaning?
I've been at this hero game a long time,
a long, long time,
and after today,
I'm thinking about trying
my hand at something new.
Like what?
For starters, training
someone to take over.
There's another Flash on your earth?
There will be...
soon as I'm done training her.
Her?
Well, do you think we're
good with the Speed Force?
Well, if not, we'll
find out soon enough.
Always a pleasure, Flash.
Always.
So, you need to rest as well, Mister.
No running, no Flash.
- Your system is taxed.
- I'm good.
You will be, but you not yet.
That's right. Anything
comes up, we got it.
Iris, make sure this man rests.
I'm on it.
- Long day.
- Yes, it was.
You know, I realized a couple of things
- when I was in Flashtime.
- Yeah, what's that?
Well... I'm more than
fast enough to catch DeVoe.
We just need to know
when he's coming out of
the pocket dimension sooner.
Yeah. We'll figure that out.
What's the other thing?
You were right about taking a breather.
Mm.
Just... a moment with you,
being grounded again,
everything becomes more clear.
Scooch over.
I'm sorry about date night.
Don't be.
PowerBars and sweatpants, it's...
all I really need.
Uh, this is my exit.
Your... oh...
Right.
Yeah.
Jesse...
the reason that I can't talk about...
You know what, it's... it's okay.
- You don't have to explain it.
- I don't-I don't?
I thought that's what you wanted.
Yeah.
Um...
I don't know, I thought
making you confront
all the emotions that
you have with losing Mom
would help you move on...
And be happy again.
But I can't decide when
you're ready to do that,
only you can, so I'm... I'm sorry if...
No, don't be sorry. It's okay.
I do want you to know, though,
if the time comes and...
you wanna talk about it,
I'm here.
Actually... if that's the case,
why don't you stick around
for a little bit longer?
What, you wanna talk now?
No... I'd like you to listen.
Have a seat.
I'm going to fix this to your forehead.
- What is that?
- It's the streamlined version
of DA Cecile Horton's
mental activity dampener.
- Nice upgrade.
- Thank you.
But I thought this was, uh,
supposed to block out people's thoughts?
Not anymore.
Now...
it allows you to hear them.
Your mother...
I don't know... I don't
know how... I don't...
You see, when you have a love...
Had a love...
Like your mother and I had,
and you lose that love...
Anyway, um...
Maybe this will help you understand
why it's been so hard for me.
Because in the vast night sky,
you are the only star I see.
Mom.
She's a miracle.
Jesse.
She's just like me.
Sweetie, come here.
Be with me.
Thank you, Ally.
- So...
- So?
Jesse seemed better when she left.
So do you.
Did you guys have a nice talk?
Well, it was actually
more of a listening session than a talk,
but we're good, yeah, both of us.
That's good, Harry.
Yeah, and what about you?
- What?
- Come on.
I know you well enough to know
that something's on your mind.
What is it?
It's... Killer Frost.
What about Killer Frost?
I don't know anything
that she says or does.
It's scary and alarming
to have this person that
you know nothing about
living inside of you.
But for the first time,
I remember what she did.
What do you remember?
Barry taking her into Flashtime,
- trying to freeze the bomb...
- Mm-hmm.
And...
Killer Frost being... worried.
Worried about... what? About dying?
About me.
Interesting.
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to drop that.
- It just slipped out of my hands.
- That's okay.
Oh, gosh, my first...
Killer Frost, and I go and ruin it.
- Typical... typical me.
- That's not....
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I just get so clumsy when I'm nervous.
What are you nervous about?
Um, I'm... I'm supposed to
be meeting some people here
for the first time, and
I've got the jitters,
which... Is what this place is called.
Hey! It is.
- Apt name, don't you think?
- I do.
It's funny, you know, you get nervous,
you get the jitters, you go for coffee,
and the caffeine acts as a stimulant,
which makes you shaky, which
could also be known as...
- The jitters.
- Exactly.
Okay, ri... I get it.
Okay.
We're gonna go.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Um, I'm really very, very sorry.
Don't worry about it. Good
luck with your meeting.
- I hope it goes well.
- Thanks.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
It did.