My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
His tears are more than just water.
It's like a love drug.
I think I can read minds.
Cecile's a telepath.
That's way more important
than getting Allen out of prison.
Cecile filed an appeal last week.
We have no new evidence,
so that doesn't matter.
Did you know the oscillating cameras
aren't the only ones in this wing?
You're The Flash.
You said to call you when
I was ready to do business.
Do you have another fish to sell me?
Welcome to my own personal meta-block,
built on the ruins of
the first Iron Heights...
Completely off the
books and camera-free.
Yes, yes, less history
lesson, more window shopping.
Mina Chaytan...
Her powers bring effigies to life.
Now, that is a nifty trick.
Can she animate anything else, hm?
How about my finger?
Oh, I like her, she's feisty.
You are going to love me,
and I'll come willingly, gorgeous.
Sylbert Rundine... He can shrink objects
and return them to original size.
I know a drug smuggler who'd pay
a pretty pence for that man.
Ramsey Deacon... Controls technology.
And Becky Sharpe...
Can manipulate luck
on the quantum level.
I smell a bidding war.
And who might this be?
Something you've been
wanting for a long time...
A speedster.
C'est pièce de résistance.
Terms are the same as always.
Any metas you sell, we
split the profits evenly.
So, who would you like?
Oh, well,
eenie, meenie,
miney,
all of them.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Drakkar Noir,
onions,
and liverwurst?
Oh, no.
Earl Cox.
Earl!
- It's the cops.
- It wasn't me!
I'll fight every one
of you, ha-ya, ha-ya!
Oh, hello, Ralphy.
How'd you get in here, Earl?
Door was unlocked.
No, it wasn't.
Was after I picked it.
Ow, oh, look at you.
You went all Zac Efron on me.
You drank so many six
packs you'd have grown one.
Nice suit, Earl.
Ah, thank you kindly...
Armani knockoff, I love it.
Listen, it's always great seeing you,
but if you'll excuse me,
I got a very busy day.
Clear your calendar, slim,
'cause I've got a score that'll
knock your honey glazed
holiday ham into next Christmas.
Yeah, I don't think any of those words
mean what you think they do.
How about these words for you?
A rich, old heiress hires me
to find her other boyfriend,
the pool boy, as a gold digger.
Turns out, he is.
But pool boy is willing
to share said gold
with someone who can help
him keep up appearances,
so to speak, and that, my friend,
is your specialty.
Are you in?
I don't do that kind of stuff anymore.
Ralph Dibny needs to concentrate.
- You see this?
- I got friends now.
They're good people.
They helped me, uh,
turn over a new leaf.
- Are they, now?
- Yeah.
We'll see.
Meaning?
Meaning,
I love you, Ralphy, I really do.
But you let people down,
especially the good ones.
They get close to you,
place their trust in you,
and then, bam,
you screw up,
every single time.
So, when you let your new friends down,
give your old one a call.
Thanks for coming, Cecile.
I know Barry isn't too optimistic
about the appeal hearing.
Don't lose hope, Iris,
we still have a few days to prepare.
I know, but it's not like
we've come up with any new ideas
for clearing Barry's name.
A bigger issue is
we don't seem to have Barry.
- Mrs. West-Allen?
- Warden Wolfe.
Unfortunately, you won't be
able to see your husband today.
He was in an altercation.
What... An altercation?
A prison yard fight.
What? Is he okay?
Oh, he's fine, he's fine,
he wasn't harmed and he wasn't at fault,
but per Iron Heights protocol,
everyone involved is in
isolation for the week.
And is he safe there?
Oh, he couldn't be more safe.
Actually, it's a pretty
common occurrence.
Safe until midnight...
and then Allen and the
others belong to Amunet.
The important thing to
know is, he's in good hands.
You can rest easy at night.
Thank you, Warden.
Yes, thank you.
What's wrong?
Wolfe is trafficking meta-humans?
Is everybody crooked in this town?
Ah, he always did look smug
in those Italian wool suits.
Oh, my God, he's literally
wolf in sheep's clothing.
It's kind of the perfect
partnership, I mean,
Amunet deals in metas,
and Wolfe has a prison full of them.
And him being the Warden,
he can make some inmates disappear
without raising any eyebrows.
I'm gonna go talk to Singh.
And say what?
Your pregnant girlfriend
with gestational
psychic powers told you?
Yeah, Joe, Singh's just gonna think that
you're a father desperate
to get his son out of prison.
Well, if we don't figure out
something before midnight,
that's exactly what I'm gonna say.
Hey, where's Harry? He can help.
He went to Earth Two,
he's checking in on Jesse,
so...
- Great.
- Okay, well,
we're out of legal options,
and Cisco can't breach
Barry out of the meta-wing,
so, how do we stop this?
Hey, guys, got your
alert, sorry I'm late.
- It's okay, Ralph.
- No, it's not okay.
I ran into this old
business partner of mine.
This guy... He's just a big, fat creep.
He's always sticking
his nose in my business.
Oh, my.
And he's so shady.
He's got these beady eyes
and this crooked smile.
Just a real two-faced rat
from head to toe.
- Well...
- Freaky.
What?
He's a two-faced rat, he is.
What's wrong with my voice?
Do you hear that?
Um...
That's him right there.
That's him, do you see him? That's him.
That's him, that's him, that's him,
Right there, there he...
there...
That's me, that's me.
What is happening?
You somehow willed your body
to shape shift into Earl's appearance.
Seems like your cells can do
a lot more than just elongate.
Ugh, brilliant. How do you undo it?
Undo this? That? This?
Control Z?
Control...
Guys, I think I just figured
out how to stop Warden Wolfe.
If Ralph could shape
shift into Braveheart here,
then he could easily
shape shift into Wolfe
and meet Amunet before midnight.
And call off the whole deal
before it ever even happens.
Right.
Angala what now?
If he doesn't stop soon,
I'm gonna ask to be sold early.
Being a meta-prisoner
or a meta-pet...
What's the difference?
Difference is Amunet Black.
She captures metas,
sells them to the highest bidder.
Mob bosses, drug traffickers, gangs...
Just imagine how our powers
could be used in the wrong hands.
I ain't gonna be nobody's weapon.
We gotta get outta here.
Agreed, but how?
Wolfe and Amunet's latest
criminal undertaking
throws an annoying wrench in our plans.
What shall we do?
I don't know.
You,
you don't know?
My mind is consumed
by a near infinite web of variables,
more plentiful than there are atoms
in an exploding star,
so for the moment,
I do not know.
I fail to see the humor in this.
I heard that in your mind...
A flash of stimuli racing through
your ventromedial prefrontal cortex,
where belief is formed...
and doubt.
I don't have any doubt.
And if you had asked,
instead of reading my mind,
then you would know.
I do know.
As for your earlier inquiry,
it's not about what we are going to do.
It's about what Barry
Allen is going to do.
Sitter, how goes it?
Hold your horses, almost done.
Looks like the trap got
clogged with a bunch of hair.
I'll head underneath, make
sure the stack is clear.
Good to go.
Thank you.
Okay, how's this?
You know that painting in "It,"
the one that comes to life?
It's like that.
This is impossible.
We might as well just gift wrap Barry,
hand him to Amunet, and call it a day.
No, Ralph, this is not impossible.
Your polymerized cells are
linked to your thoughts.
You should be able to change
into anyone you can think of,
just like when you squeezed
your belly into abs.
Okay, uh, first off,
I have been working out,
so this is au naturel now.
And second, that was just some abs.
This is an entire person.
Look,
when I first learned how to vibe,
I had to learn how to clear my mind
of all other thoughts.
You think you can do that?
Okay, uh,
all right, I'll try.
Do better than try.
Barry's life is in your hands,
and we're all counting on you.
I think what you meant to say was,
"No pressure, Ralphy."
- Here we go.
- All right, focus.
Be Wolfe.
Be Wolfe. Big, bad Wolfe.
Oh, wow, sweet, chiseled
cheekbones, I did it.
Wow, maybe I can save Barry.
Oh, uh-oh.
Uh, a little help?
Next, we need to work
on his motor skills.
Well done, boy.
And hey, for the record,
I was already planning on making
that stuff that you used, so...
Sure, right after your
lunch tray crowbar method.
Can we continue on with the
breaking and exiting, please?
You want us to follow
a cop on a prison break?
I'm not a cop in here. I'm a prisoner.
And I'm not about to let Amunet turn me
into a weaponized slave, are you?
Okay, you convinced me, let's go.
I'm staying.
What? Why?
Because I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
Last time I was out there,
I almost destroyed the whole city.
Yeah, she can stay.
No, we're all leaving.
Becky, if Amunet sells you,
your powers will be used
to hurt a lot of people.
The only way to prevent
that is to escape with us.
Please, trust me.
Yay, oy, big happy.
Now what?
Wolfe said that this wing
was built on top of the old prison.
I also heard the plumber talking about
piping underneath us.
Once we're far enough
away from the meta-wing,
we'll get our powers back.
That's how we get our freedom.
Ew...
Aw, my bad, tiny.
Hey, as soon as we get out,
I'll steal you a brand
new pair of Timmy Choos.
It's Jimmy. I'm a size six.
You're so sweet.
If you wanna use your
powers for something useful,
you could help me steal
back some native artifacts.
If you two plan on going back to crime,
you might as well just turn around.
The Flash will just run you back here.
Same goes for all of you.
Don't look at me, I'm reformed.
From now on, I only commit legal crime.
Legal crime?
The stock market.
Come on, we have a long way to go.
Augmentation is complete.
Your chair will serve its purpose.
You have outdone yourself
once again.
That melody in your head.
You don't recognize it?
It was playing...
The first time we danced, yes.
So, you do remember?
June 27th, 1997,
at 8:13 p.m.,
in the countryside in the
small hamlet of Boars Hill.
It was also the first time we kissed.
And the first time I realized
I wanted to spend the rest
of my life by your side.
Marlize,
I forget nothing.
Perhaps our song was once
at the forefront of my consciousness,
but now...
That song playing in your head
makes it difficult
to read your thoughts.
Quite difficult.
Perhaps that's on purpose.
Of course not.
I know this unforeseen change
concerns you.
But fear not.
Once this next phase is complete,
I will erase every doubt from your head.
Wolfe man to S.T.A.R. base, I'm here.
Ralph, to help you stay as Wolfe,
I'm gonna hand you over to Joe, okay?
He's gonna quarterback.
Ralph, you copy?
Yep.
So, what's the next move?
Preferably something
without a lot of moving.
Okay, Amunet's point man is Norvok,
so you're gonna have
to talk to him first.
Grab a drink, act like a hard-ass.
Barkeep,
something cold and
frosty, if you please.
Jeez.
That's on you, bro.
Snake's on the brain, 5:00.
Stay focused, Ralph,
no distracting thoughts.
Gingold on the rocks.
Hand it to me, please.
The hell you doing here?
I'd like to talk to Amunet,
please, about the deal.
You could talk to Amunet at the deal.
Damn it, Ralph,
nobody talks to Wolfe like that.
He's the Warden of the most
dangerous prison in the Midwest.
Demand some respect.
Listen, you lapdog.
Set the meeting with your boss now,
or I'll pull on your eye snake
and strangle you with it, understood?
All right, all right.
Let me see what I can do.
Oh, God.
- 'Sup?
- Ralph, you okay?
Yeah, fine, yeah.
No problem here.
I'm definitely holding it together.
Yeah, that doesn't sound too convincing.
I have complete control
of the situation.
Ol' Dibny won't let his friends down.
Wolfe.
Amunet's ready.
Then let's not keep her waiting.
Are you sure this is the right way?
Do you hear the water
in this sewer drain?
It's moving in this direction.
We keep going this way,
we'll head away from the prison,
find our exit.
Wow, good catch.
You must've been a really smart CSI.
A CSI who killed a teacher
in his own apartment and
left evidence everywhere.
Yeah, doesn't sound so smart to me.
Hey, speaking of,
maybe we shouldn't be...
Crap.
Hey, easy, easy.
Rundine, easy.
We let him go, he will out us.
- We can't do that, can we?
- Deacon.
What are you doing?
No, we can't hurt him.
We have to do more than hurt
him... we don't have a choice.
No, hey, we do not have to kill him.
Yes, we do.
No, we don't, all right?
Just duct tape him.
Come on, let's move.
Looked like it hurt.
Ding, ding!
Boys, have some orange slices.
Mommy needs to work, okay?
♪ Warden ♪
I'm going to assume this is not one
of those good emergency meetings...
A few hours before a major
criminal undertaking, hm?
We have to delay the deal.
What?
My ears outside tell me
the police have been tipped.
I don't know how.
Maybe CCPD
hacked into the cameras.
You said there were no cameras.
- I did?
- Mmm.
Yes, I did say that.
But then, afterwards,
I installed a few.
- Did you?
- Mm.
Hmm,
something seems off
with the big, bad Wolfe,
if you even are Wolfe.
Stay in it, she's testing you.
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
I'm the same man you've
always dealt with.
Okay, and who would that be?
The one who gives you your merchandise.
And trust me,
you need me a lot more than I need you.
So, when I say the
deal has to be delayed,
it's because the deal has to be delayed.
Okay.
What the hell?
What?
You know, sometimes I hate
being right all the time.
Ralph, get out of there.
Uh...
Damn it.
Get me Wolfe, yeah?
I understand your concern, Amunet,
but you have my word.
Your metas are exactly where
they're supposed to be...
Locked up tight and in their cells,
waiting for you to claim them, heh.
Very good, I'll see you then.
Find them!
I mean, there has to be another way.
There isn't.
There is one card left to play:
go to Iron Heights,
and stop the deal before it happens.
You're talking about finding Amunet,
plus a prison full of armed meta-guards
on their turf.
This is the only option we have left.
You guys can do this.
Let's go.
Ralph.
Yeah, uh, maybe not this time.
What? Why?
Look, you...
You're gonna have a better chance
saving Barry without me.
Ralph, you know that isn't true.
I just screwed everything up.
You know what could happen
if I screw it up again?
- You won't.
- Okay, you know what?
Maybe we just need to talk this out,
let's go visit with
Dr. Hallway, come on.
Look, bud, talk's not gonna fix my head.
I just can't do it this time, guys.
Sorry I let you down.
Hey.
Hey, Ralph.
Looks like we're finally
in the old prison.
We must be close.
Getting closer than we think.
Hey, I know this lock.
It's the same kind they use
in the general population wing,
which means there are no meta dampeners
on the other side of this door.
We get through, we get our powers back.
Well, that's all I needed to hear.
Out of the way.
You good?
No brains, no brawn.
Allow me.
I may not have my powers...
But I don't need them
to hack my way out of trouble.
Give me a few minutes.
Come here.
What, no, I'm fine,
it doesn't really hurt.
Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- I mean, it hurts a little.
Yeah, come here.
There.
Thanks.
Guess I forgot what it feels like
to punch someone in the
face without my powers.
Judging by the swelling,
I'd say you have a fracture
on either the fourth
or fifth metacarpal.
- How...
- I used to fall down a lot.
Super klutz.
So, what are you gonna
do when you're free?
I hope it's not more of what you did
to get you in here.
Oh, no, trust me,
I am so over prison jumpsuits.
Orange is not the new anything.
Neither is gray, neither is gray, so...
So, what then?
I don't know.
Using my powers just
hurt those around me.
My good luck just jinxed everyone else.
You know, you seem to
really care about people...
Not like the type of person who'd
take someone's life.
I didn't kill that teacher.
I wouldn't take a life.
You know, not every meta uses
their powers to hurt people.
Some use them to help others,
to protect people.
Our powers don't decide who we are.
We do.
Ralph?
Hey, Ralph, you in here?
Ick, the light!
It burns!
All right, come on, time to get up.
I can't, I'm dead.
Okay, I don't know
what's going on with you,
but I'm betting it has
something to do with the reason
you literally fell apart at the bar.
I told Cisco that a talk
from him's not gonna help.
So, a talk from you
is not gonna help either, Caitlin.
Okay.
I'll get somebody else.
Hey...
Hello, Stretch.
They call me a man who elongates now.
Hm, they should call you pathetic.
So, you screwed up, get over it.
You are a mean lady.
I am just telling you
what you need to hear.
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna
miss you when you leave.
Leave?
Is that what this is about?
Well, yeah.
Everybody leaves Ralph Dibny eventually,
that's how this whole thing works.
I screw up big time,
and, tch, they take off.
This time, the people
who are gonna leave
are actually my friends.
They're the first ones that I've had
in a really long time.
That's stupid.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't
expect you to understand,
you kidnap and stab all your friends.
Right, I'm the queen of
letting these people down.
But you know what? They're still here.
No matter how much I disappoint them,
they still show up for me.
I don't really understand it,
but I think that's part of
this whole friends thing.
So, unless you do something worse
than kidnap and stab them,
I think you're gonna be just fine.
You really think so?
Yes, I do.
Huh.
You know, that actually
wasn't a bad pep talk.
Well, it's your turn next time.
If I ever decide to
go full villain again,
you can give me the lame heart to heart.
Full villain?
Wait...
Wait.
I know how to fix this.
I gotta see a girl about a guy.
Thank you, Frosty Oprah.
Presto.
Everyone's powers work?
Yep.
Ah,
I can smell all the tech
within five miles of here.
Thank you, Barry, you saved us.
You did good, boy.
Not good enough, it seems.
Everyone back inside,
and you'll live to see another day.
I think the only one
who should be worried
about surviving right now is you.
There's no cavalry.
No one's gonna see what happened here.
It's just you and us, Wolfe.
You want revenge?
Understandable.
Just one thing...
If you're thirsty for vengeance,
you might wanna start with The Flash.
Barry Allen is The Flash...
The same man who put you behind bars
and who will, no doubt,
recapture you after your escape.
That was probably his plan all along...
Is all that true?
I'm gonna squash you so quick,
you won't even know what hit you.
No, not quick.
Let's take our time.
The Flash on his knees.
Suppose there is justice, after all.
Let's see how fast he can run
when he's the size of a flea.
Stop!
Stop.
What are you doing, runt?
Deciding who I am.
You're not gonna hurt him.
Join us, or get out of the way.
Either way, we're taking him.
Good luck with that.
Oh.
Toldja.
Shoot to wound.
They're no good to me dead.
They most certainly are not.
Amunet, you're early.
And you are exactly as I suspected,
a liar,
who's obviously in way over his head.
But no matter,
I will clean up your mess for you.
Step aside, boys.
Mommy needs to work.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Not again.
Oh.
DeVoe.
Oh, I don't pay me enough for this.
Powers won't work.
Mine neither.
He must have blasted us with something.
Who the hell are you?
I am your destiny.
No!
Help me.
Too late, Mr. Allen.
Oh, what an inconspicuous body.
This will be quite useful.
Not so fast, Warden.
You won't take my body.
I don't want your body.
I want your life.
Good-bye for now, Mr. Allen.
What happened?
DeVoe.
Well, party's over.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I'm staying.
What? Barry...
I was only willing to do this...
Try to break everybody out
because Wolfe was gonna sell us,
but that's not gonna happen now.
I'm staying
till you find a way to
get me out of here legally.
It's the only way I'd
ever really feel free,
you know that.
This could be our only
chance to save you.
We all have to decide who we are.
This is who I am.
Breakout in progress.
Engage lockdown.
Code X prison breach.
Repeat, we have a Code X.
Move, move, move!
Get against the wall.
Cell block secure.
New evidence, Ms. Horton...
That's what you told this court
had come into your possession,
only I haven't heard it or seen it,
nor have the circumstances
changed in any way
that would convince me
to move for a retrial.
So, unless you have
something more to add,
this appeal hearing is over.
I understand, your honor, I do,
if we could just wait
a few more minutes,
I am sure that...
I am tired of waiting.
Either you have something new to add,
or you don't.
Which is it?
We have nothing further, your honor.
Then I hereby deem Barry
Allen's appeal den...
Wait.
DeVoe?
Nope, not DeVoe.
It's Ralph.
I believe you are looking for me,
Your Honor.
I don't know how any of this happened.
You were found in Barry Allen's loft.
You were dead.
I was stabbed.
I heard a voice saying something about
framing someone, then I blacked out.
- It's gonna work.
- And this morning,
I woke up in my own home.
Mrs. DeVoe, does any of
this make any sense to you?
No,
I am just as surprised
by all of this as everyone.
Your Honor,
the city has had reports in the past
of people who have appeared dead,
only to later emerge very much alive.
That's impossible.
Impossible, Your Honor,
is it as impossible
as a man who can run faster
than the speed of sound?
I submit that Central City is home
to the impossible.
I have as many questions
as you have, Your Honor,
and I am looking forward to
working with the authorities
to solve this mystery.
Yes, I'm sure that CCPD
will be very interested in this.
As for Barry Allen's appeal...
I guess the court must deem that
Clifford DeVoe is alive and well.
Barry Allen is hereby
cleared of all charges
and ordered release from
Iron Heights Penitentiary immediately.
You're home.
- You're my home.
- Aww.
Oh, he couldn't wait to do that.
How you feeling, Barry, you okay?
I'm feeling great, yeah.
Well, you look like you
could use a good meal,
and don't you worry,
I made a fresh batch
of Grandma Esther's meat loaf.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just like you like it.
Meat loaf? Gross.
I just meant, meat loaf is
a grossly undervalued menu item
in most restaurants, I think.
You guys,
now that I'm free, I
don't care what I do.
I'm just so happy to be
back with all of you again.
Team Flash.
Today, we celebrate Barry.
Tomorrow, we go back to stopping
the man that framed you.
I'll drink to that.
Here, here.
You okay, Barry?
Yeah, it's DeVoe.
Barry, we're gonna stop
him, I know we will.
No, that's not it, he...
There was nothing keeping him
from going inside the meta-wing
and absorbing the powers
of every meta in Iron Heights...
Peek-a-boo top weather wizard.
Yeah, I mean, he could've
stolen their powers and more,
but he didn't.
He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers for something...
All of them.
We know a bus meta.
Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm late.
Just couldn't get this left glute
to shape shift back
to its normal, perky...
Why is everyone looking
at me like I'm a dead man?
What's all this?
Well, after last night's success,
I thought a toast was in order.
Success?
Is that what you call last night?
Yes, how would you describe it?
Barry Allen was...
supposed to remain
in the meta-human wing
at Iron Heights, but he's now free.
Even Team Flash has good luck sometimes.
And the bus metas?
We were supposed to wait
till all of them were captured.
But you only got four.
I said I would retrieve
them from confinement.
I never said when or where.
There is something else on your mind,
isn't there?
Warden Wolfe's death.
He needed to die.
I just don't recall it
being necessary for our plan.
The chair can wait till morning.
For now, to the enlightenment.
To the enlightenment.
I love you, Clifford.
Yes, and I, you.
♪ I think I'm going out of my head ♪
♪ Yes, I think I'm going out of my head ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --