- My name is Barry Allen, and
I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one fast
enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Who's Cicada?
- You'll never catch him.
- This is Sherloque.
- He's the greatest detective
in all the multiverse.
- I'm a detective as well.
- I'm here to catch
your killer.
- So we're dealing with
a meta-human Jack the Ripper.
- In my history, he never
killed Gridlock or Block.
They're completely different
victims.
He's early.
- Because the timeline changed.
- Because of me.
[girl breathing heavily]
[indistinct shouting]
[suspenseful music]
[people screaming]
- Guys, this is mad crazy!
There are, like,
fireballs in the sky!
Holy...
I'm gonna get a better look.
♪ ♪
[gasps] There he is!
This is gonna be lit.
Wait, there's two of them?
Oh, my God, guys.
What was that?
This is cray!
What is going on right now?
Is the world, like,
ending right now?
Oh, my phone.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
You just saved my life.
You are the second speedster
who just, like,
saved the world.
Can I just get a...
can I just get a...
selfie.
♪ ♪
What the...
[Cyndi Lauper's
"Girls Just Want to Have Fun"]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I come home
in the morning light ♪
♪ My mother says, "When you
gonna live your life right?" ♪
♪ Oh, Mother dear,
we're not the fortunate ones ♪
♪ And girls,
they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have ♪
♪ That's all
they really want ♪
- Oh.
[chuckles]
- ♪ Some fun ♪
[smoke alarm beeping]
♪ When the working day
is done ♪
- Uh...
Sorry.
[beeping continues]
- What are you doing?
- Uh, nothing. Go back to bed.
I'm just making some breakfast.
[chuckles]
- Like I could go to sleep
after the smell
of Jitters coffee.
So, uh, I see you still know
your way around the kitchen.
[playful music]
- What's happening?
- Uh, hey, babe.
- Good morning.
- Um, I, um, was thinking
that we could have
breakfast together.
Right?
Like a family.
- I love it.
- Yeah.
- Do you...Hi.
♪ ♪
- Do you need any help?
- No, no. You guys just sit.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
What...do we have here?
- Well, these are pancakes,
as you can see,
but I made them
into little lightning bolts.
Well, the batter
kind of got away from me,
but you see
the little zigzag...
- No, no, no. Yeah, yeah.
I totally see it, yeah.
- Yeah.
[camera shutter clicks]
- What are...what are you doing?
- Uh, I am
just getting evidence
that you make lumpy pancakes
in every time period.
- [clears throat]
- Let's try it out.
[crunching]
Mmm. Lumpy, but delicious.
- Yeah? Oh, thanks, babe.
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
- [crunching]
- I'm sorry, um, when did you...
when did you get a phone?
- Uh, Dad got it for me
a couple days ago.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Nora suggested it. I mean,
I thought it was a great idea.
We're always in and out
of S.T.A.R. Labs, so I just...
you know, it'd be easier
to text and call.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that totally
makes sense.
[silverware clattering lightly]
- You guys excited
to cheer me on
at the charity softball game?
- Softball, schway.
- I just hope I don't get
stuck in right field this year.
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
- You, uh, gave
your number out already?
- Yeah, just to the team
and Sherloque.
Actually, this text message,
I think, is from him.
- [chuckles] I don't think
he's much of a texter.
- [chuckles] No.
He, uh, wants us to come
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'm gonna go get ready.
- You haven't had anything
to eat yet.
- Mm. I'm not really
a breakfast person.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
You know,
I thought having her here,
we would finally
have a chance to connect,
but it's like every time
we take a half-step forward,
we end up taking
six steps back.
- I-I mean, don't give up.
She'll come around.
I have a feeling.
- Yeah.
- Well, not if I keep
making food like that.
- Hey, no, this really is good.
It is. I mean,
it's a little, like...
- Wait, wait, stop. Just stop.
- Dark, but...No, it's...
- I'm going to make you
a banana. It's fine.
- You're going
to make me a banana?
- I'm going to make you
a banana.
- Thanks.
- Wait, no,
I asked for everyone.
Where is the little, uh...
- [chuckles]
Cisco is laying low
at his parents' house
while he heals up.
- Well, that's not very brave
on his part.
I will have a conversation
with him next time I see him.
So, Team Flash.
How will this handsome,
master detective
of all the multiverse,
Sherloque Wells,
pay off his debt to us...
and catch this
homicidal maniac together?
Well, we'll begin
by asking ourselves
a few obvious questions.
How he became a meta-human?
- Well,
power manifestation varies.
The particle accelerator...
- I don't think we're
interrupting Sherloque, right?
- Right.
- Sure, but you bring up
a good point, Dr. Snow.
What do we know so far
about this Cicada?
- Well, we know that
he's killed two people
and almost a third.
- Exactly right.
If I could gently be
a little more specific,
not just people, right?
Meta-humans.
- Also, Joe said he got the
feeling that Cicada's a dad.
- Right. Cicada...parent.
- His dagger dampens powers.
- Not just dampens
the powers, right?
He commands this dagger, right?
It is like
an extension of himself.
So we know...
- Maybe they acquired
their powers at the same time.
- Yes, very good, Dr. Snow.
So, acquired powers...
together.
So...
there we are, Team Flash.
Very simple.
We unravel this puzzle,
and we have a pathway
to tracking Cicada.
- Cool, or we just answer
a much more basic question,
like what's up
with his weird mask?
- Well, the mask conceals
his identity.
That's what it's for.
- Right.
What I'm suggesting is,
if we find out what
the mask is for,
we'll find out the man
underneath much faster.
- 37 times I have caught
Cicada, right?
And not once was this mask
angle very useful, right?
[speaking French]
But you know what?
The more hours I bill you,
the less money I owe you.
So, if you want to spend your
hours pursuing the mask angle,
well, then be my guest.
[slurps]
- Okay, great.
Sounds like a plan.
- We got to get going.
- Yeah, yes.
- Good stuff.
- I hope you score a touchdown.
- [chuckles] It's softball.
- Ah, score a basket.
So, baby giraffe...
lead on, my friend.
[slurps]
[indistinct shouting]
- Wow.
- Look at these guys.
They think they're
so much better than us.
- Because they are, Bar.
I mean, without Captain Singh
or my dad, it's...
- Huh.
- Huh, what?
- Jonesy isn't here yet.
Hey, Detective Rowell,
what do you think?
Maybe third base for me?
- Right field, Allen.
- Babe, I love you,
but leave the hot corner
to someone who can actually
field a ball, okay?
- Play ball!
- Come on.
- I mean...Good luck!
- Yeah.
- You're going to nail it.
- Right field.
Oh, God.
- In right field.
Not the hot corner, but...
Guys, come on!
- ♪ I'm back, back,
back in the game ♪
- ♪ Hey, oh, hey, oh ♪
- ♪ I said I'm back, back,
back in the game ♪
- ♪ Hey, oh, hey, oh ♪
- ♪ Now it's go time, go time,
got me on a roll ♪
♪ The only way is up,
I feel it in my bones ♪
♪ One step at a time,
see you at the finish line ♪
- Safe!
- ♪ Hey, oh, hey, oh ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ Back in the game ♪
- Wow, he really is slow.
- Yeah, Papa Joe told me all
the stories
about what an awful athlete
Dad was growing up.
- Well, believe me,
they're true.
- Let's just be grateful
that he has coordination
when it counts.
- Yeah.
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
- Hey, what is that, Nora?
- There is this really great
app called Spyn Zone.
The push notifications
let you know the second
anything happens in the city.
- Like Iris' Website?
- Uh, yeah, kind of.
It's just a lot more
up to date than that,
and it's, like...
it's really cool.
This girl's, like,
really in the know.
- Oh.
Yeah, Spencer Young.
I know her.
Yeah, I see her all the time
working on her laptop
at Jitters.
She...she actually was
a junior reporter at CCPN
when I worked there,
but...
she didn't last very long.
- Why not?
- Well, she wanted to be famous
and make a name for herself,
but she didn't care
how it happened.
- Well, I think she's cute.
- Yeah, I mean,
she may be cute,
but she's never fact-checked
a thing a day in her life.
- She's doing something right...
she has three times
as many followers on her app
as you do on your blogs, so...
I'm going to get something
to eat.
- Ooh, wow.
[bat cracks]
- Ah, come on, Allen!
- Oh, honey.
Oh.
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
[pulsating]
- Cecile? What's wrong?
- Something's not right.
Something's not right.
♪ ♪
- Is that Jonesy?
- [gasps]
Hey, somebody stop him!
- Everybody move!
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
[whirring]
- Hey, hey!
Nora, hey.
- Huh? What?
- What happened?
- You just saved everybody.
♪ ♪
[siren wails]
- [sighs]
Bomb squad finished
their sweep.
They said it's all clear.
- Okay.
- Nora, how did you know
what was happening?
- I don't know.
[stuttering]
One minute I was going
to get food,
and the next I was
in the outfield with Dad.
- And you don't remember
anything else?
[phone chimes, vibrates]
What's that?
- A notification
from Spyn Zone.
- Already? That was fast.
- Allen, CSI time.
- Uh, we're up. We'll meet you
back at S.T.A.R. Labs
as soon as we can.
- Yeah.
- Iris,
if Cicada sees that post...
- Yeah, he may pick Nora
as his next target.
[sighs]
[car door opens]
[dramatic music]
- Well, you have brought us
to the location
you first encountered
Cicada.
- That's right.
How did you know that?
- I know everything.
I'm a master detective.
Look, I looked at
the CSI file of Barry Allen.
There is no evidence
of Cicada DNA, right?
And moreover,
look at this location, right?
All the traffic through here...
you can never pull DNA
from here.
- It's a good thing
we're not here for DNA.
- What we are here for, then?
- We're here to find out
why Cicada wears that mask.
- Oh,encore with the mask!
- Do you think he's allergic
to fresh air?
- No.
- No, he wears that mask
for a reason.
- All right, look, 37 times
I've caught Cicada.
Not once, not one time
was the mask
a key part of the evidence.
- Yeah, that's true.
But you said this Cicada is
different than all the others,
so why wouldn't his mask
be different, too?
- Maybe it's just a mask to...
You know what?
You want to pursuit mask angle,
be my guest.
What do you expect
to find here?
- When I was getting
my ass kicked,
I noticed that the more
he exerted himself,
the heavier his breathing got.
- That's what happens.
- So, I thought...
if one of those breaths
was strong enough...
[chuckles]
We might just get lucky.
- How we are going
to get lucky?
- Barry found traces
of fluoropolymers here.
- So?
- So the Internet told me
they're prone to flaking.
I'm here to get some of them.
- The Internet also tell you to
contaminate your crime scene?
Very good,
master detective.
♪ ♪
- Turns out
industrial respirators use
a protective coating
around the nostrils
that are made from this.
And when this exposed
to another compound,
dimethyl sulfate,
fluoropolymers tend to emit
a very distinct odor
- Burnt onions.
- Right.
[exhales deeply]
[sniffing]
We find out
where this is used,
we're going to find our man.
Elementary.
- Elementary.
- No shrap, Sherlock.
- [sighs]
It's Sherloque.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Spencer?
- Iris West, wow.
Long time.
How are you?
- Uh, yeah, yeah,
I'm good. And you?
- Good. Married that CSI guy
you were dating, huh?
- Uh, yeah.
- Any kids yet?
- Um, no. Not...
[cell phone clicking]
Uh...
No.
- You know,
I followed your lead.
Started my own blog,
left CCPN.
Now we are both
Charleine Foster Kanes.
- Right.
- BTdubs, those Professor DeVoe
stories...respect.
Metas are clickbait
right now, right?
- Yes, which is why I wanted
to talk to you, actually,
off the record,
of course.
- Yeah, for sure.
What's up?
- So, uh, I recently found
a source who thinks
that metas
are being targeted.
- Ooh, juicy.
Who?
- Well, no one knows,
not even CCPD.
But these metas,
including speedsters
like The Flash and XS,
they are all in danger.
- XS. That new lady speedster
has a code name.
[gasps]
Oh, like her size!
Right, extra small.
Did you coin that?
- No, no.
Look, the point is,
writing articles about XS
could make her a target.
- Or it could make her famous.
I mean, people are already
obsessed with her...
and my app even more.
Besides, a little threat
never stopped you
from writing about
The Flash back in the day.
- That was different.
- Because it wasyour blog?
What...do as I say, not as I do?
- Look, please stop, okay?
Before someone gets hurt.
- The only one who's going
to get hurt is you
when I make
your blog irrelevant.
♪ ♪
[device whirring]
- What is this for, Allen?
- Just trying to get
some answers, Jonesy.
Would you send that to Caitlin?
- I told everyone everything
I know, which is nothing.
- You don't remember a thing?
- No.
Okay, God's own truth, Allen...
all I remember is waking up,
getting ready for the game,
leaving my house,
and the next thing I know,
I wake up in the field
after that bomb went off.
I mean, where would
I even get a bomb?
- The evidence lockup.
It was part of
the inventory we seized
from the Jansen-Moretti case.
The cameras in the lockup
show you stuffing that bomb
in your backpack this morning.
♪ ♪
- Joe, no one got hurt.
- They could've.
The woman I love, my baby...
you could've killed them.
♪ ♪
I watched you come up, man.
- I'm sorry, Joe...
but I swear, I don't know
how this happened.
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Move, move!
- How many we got?
- Hey, what is it?
- Fire at CCPN. First
responders are across town.
- We got to go.
♪ ♪
- Finally.
- Okay, the building's
already been evacuated.
Fire trucks are on their way.
- Okay, let's just get inside
and put the fire out.
- [stuttering]
I've never done this before.
- Come on.
Seriously, move!
- That's okay. We're just going
to create a vacuum.
♪ ♪
- Fine.
I will make you move.
Enjoy this news, Flash.
♪ ♪
- All right, I'll walk you
through it. Once we're inside...
[whirring]
- What? Where...
where are you going?
- Nora, what's wrong?
- He just ran away and left.
- His suit's GPS
has him west, way west.
- Barry? Barry.
♪ ♪
He's not listening.
- Uh, guys,
what do I do here?
- Okay, Nora, you're going
to have to do this by yourself.
Okay? But I'm going
to help you.
- Okay.
- Okay, you need to get
to the heart of the fire
and extinguish it from there.
- I got it.
- Rotate your arms
in tight circles.
You need to move them
in opposite directions,
creating twin vacuums.
- [breathing heavily]
Come on, Nora.
Dad's done this
a thousand times.
You can do this.
♪ ♪
I'm doing it!
- Keep going.
♪ ♪
[applause]
- Whoa.
[cheers and applause]
[giggles]
- Great job, Nora.
- Thanks, Mom.
♪ ♪
Hey...hey, did you find Dad?
- [breathing heavily]
What the hell?
- I'm glad you were there
to put that out.
It could've been a lot worse.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Don't thank me. Your mom
walked you through it.
- You were really great
out there.
- So there was some
weird activity with your scan,
but everything looks fine.
- Hmm.
- What's the last thing
you remember?
- Standing outside
CCPN with Nora.
Next thing I know,
I'm in Vegas.
- That's exactly what happened
to me and Officer Jones.
- So maybe
the abnormal activity
was some sort
of hypnotic induction?
- I don't know.
I feel like one of us
would've noticed somebody
trying to hypnotize me.
- Yeah, and why would someone
hypnotize us to save people?
- Publicity.
Spencer Young wants to get
famous by making you famous.
- You don't know that.
- She admitted it
when we talked.
- Why would you go talk to her?
[dramatic music]
- Hold on, look at
the timestamp on the post.
7:52 p.m.? Nora and I were
still with Jonesy,
and the fire at CCPN
hadn't even been reported yet.
- I guess you'll always be
the first one to the scoop
if you're the one making it.
- So she's some sort
of early edition meta
who creates stories?
- Fake news taken
to a whole new level.
- Maybe she's some kind
of meta psychic
who predicts the news.
- [sighs]
- That still doesn't mean
she hypnotized us.
- Yeah.
Caitlin, can you download
the cortical biometrics
from Nora's suit and run it
against my scans?
- On it.
- Thanks.
- What are you thinking?
- [sighs]
We need to figure out if
Spencer's responsible for this.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
- Google for the win
on finding out
where Cicada's mask is from.
- Google for the win.
So you think
Cicada's hiding out here,
just lurking behind
those doors.
- Yeah, as a matter
of fact, I do,
because my search also told me
that Szrek Chemicals
uses dimethyl sulfates
in most of their products.
So guess what.
I'm gonna take down Cicada.
- Oh, well, we shall see,
giraffe.
♪ ♪
- May I help you?
- Hi, how are you? I'm...
- Elongated Man. I know.
- Sherloque Wells, yes,
master detective.
You know, we'll sign autographs
later...we have some business.
- Uh, we just want to know
if we can ask you
some questions, please.
- About?
♪ ♪
What about our masks?
- Do any of your employees
wear them?
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
Follow me.
[indistinct chatter]
- Yep. Every worker,
every plant wears one.
- How many plants?
- Three in Central City
and Keystone.
- Mm.
- 14 in the Midwest alone.
- So probably thousands?
- Yeah, and we're not the only
facility that uses them.
♪ ♪
- Thank you for your time.
- Hey, I, uh...
[chuckles]
Love that pear meme going
around the last few weeks.
Classic.
[laughing]
- Mm, classic.
I have a suggestion for you.
Maybe the next time you do
a Google search,
advance to page two.
Hmm?
♪ ♪
- So here's the meta-watch,
Press that button. If Spencer's
a meta, it'll beep.
- And if she's meta...
- It means she could be
dangerous, so come right back.
- Yes. One of us
would go with you,
but she knows both me
and your dad, so...
- I got it.
- Okay, We're here
if you need us, all ri...
[can door opens, closes]
- Um...
- I see her.
- All you need to do is get
within five feet of her,
hit the button,
in and out.
- I know!
- You see what I mean?
♪ ♪
Half-step forward,
six steps back?
- I mean, you guys did great
with the fire, though.
- Thank you.
You should totally name
one of your drinks
after that new female
speedster, XS.
- Hey.
- Whoa. Hi.
- Hi.
Sorry, Spencer.
- That's okay.
Do I know you?
- Uh-oh.
- Uh, Nora...
you have to press the button.
- Um, no.
No, you don't know me.
- But you know me.
- Yes, I do.
Uh, sorry.
You're Spencer Young.
I read all your stuff
on Spyn Zone.
It's a really good app.
It's fantastic stories
and really good writing.
I'm a...I'm a really big fan.
- Nora..
- I always enjoy meeting a fan.
[quirky music]
Especially when they're
as adorable as you.
- What's happening?
- She's flirting with
our daughter. I'll be back.
♪ ♪
- What?
- Hold down the fort.
- Iris, wait.
[van door closes]
♪ ♪
Huh.
- Do you have a name?
- Nora, hey. [chuckles]
- Wait, y-you know her?
- Uh, I do.
[stuttering]
Well, she's actually...
This is, actually...
- Did you want
to check your watch?
I think we're running
a little bit late. [chuckles]
- Right, yes. Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- All right, well,
I'm going to peace out.
[dramatic music]
But I hope to meet
cute you again sometime.
♪ ♪
Nora.
- Well, I guess
she's not meta.
- I guess not.
♪ ♪
- Oh, no. No, no, no.
Nora...look, I don't care
that you think she's cute.
She's dangerous, okay?
You need to stay away from her.
- Shecould be dangerous.
- Nora, I am trying
to protect you here.
- [scoffs] Has that been
your thing my whole life?
- What does that even mean,
honestly?
I mean, is that why
you've been so cold to me,
why you don't want
to spend any time with me?
I'm...I'm just trying
to get to know you.
- Just drop it.
- Nora, I don't under...
- Look, you lied to me!
- I would never lie to you.
- Yeah?
What do you call that?
♪ ♪
You put a power-dampening chip
inside me
to take away my speed.
And until six months ago,
I didn't even know
I had powers.
My whole life has been a lie
because you have been trying
to protect me.
Well, guess what.
I don't need you to do that.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[beeping]
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- What you doing?
- Well, Nora blocked me.
So I'm trying to use
the quantum computer
to access her phone and
force her to accept my calls.
But I am no...
hacker.
- Don't you think that's
a little extreme?
- Yes, Barry,
it's very extreme...
and crazy and desperate, but
I am feeling extremely crazy
and desperate, okay?
[sighs] I thought giving her
space would, you know,
have her eventually
come around,
but it turns out
she's not the problem. I am.
I mean, I don't know how
I could do something
like that to her, Barry.
- Iris, you didn't do anything
to her.
You can't blame yourself for
something future-you might do.
Yes, I can, Barry,
and it's not a might.
I suppressed
our daughter's powers.
I kept a huge part
of who she was a secret
for her entire life.
I did that.
- Look, she'll forgive you.
- What if my dad did something
like that to you
after the particle accelerator
exploded?
See?
I don't understand how I could
do something like that to her.
- Look, I don't know
why you do it,
but I don't need to.
I know that anything you do for
our family, it's out of love.
So, whatever reason future-you
has for doing this,
I have faith that it's
the right thing to do,
and so should you.
- Yeah, well, I'm having
a really hard time
believing that.
- Well, then it's a good thing
I have enough faith in you
for the both of us.
All right?
♪ ♪
- That's unusual.
[keys clacking]
- [deep voice]
Dr. Snow.
- Aah!
- Oh, Dr. Snow.
I have frightened you,
Dr. Snow.
- I assume you came here
for some other reason
than murdering me?
- Oof...
[speaking French]
If I was to murder you,
Dr. Snow,
I would not do it in such
an obvious fashion.
Look, I have a theory
on the identity of Cicada.
I request your assistance.
- Uh, okay.
I was just finishing up.
- Not your expertise,
your assistance.
I need you to punch me
in the chest.
- What?
- Right here, above the...um,
dee-aphragm. How do you say?
- Diaphragm?
- Diaphragm, right.
In the solar plexus
as hard as you can.Allé.
- Listen, Sherlock...
- Ugh.
- Loque.
- [speaking French]
So this is one of those things
where you are just the brains
and not the brawn?
You don't have the guts.
You lack the courage.
You're soft.
Probably you couldn't even
hit me in the spot.
[clears throat]
- For the record,
I know what you just did.
- And?
- And it worked.
- Très bien.
Then...allé.
♪ ♪
Ooh!
[coughing, groaning
- Oh, uh, are you okay?
♪ ♪
[wheezing]
- You sound just like...
♪ ♪
- Cicada.
[alarm blaring]
- What do we got?
- CCPD is getting bombarded
with calls from people
at the soccer game
at Central City Stadium.
- It's all over
the news, too.
- Okay, I'm going to get
over there.
- CCPD already cleared out
the stadium.
- Find the bomb,
and we'll help you disarm it.
- What's going on?
- I'll tell you on the way.
Come on.
♪ ♪
Nothing, you?
- No.
- [sighs]
Iris, there's no bomb.
♪ ♪
- Guys, look at the timestamp
on Spencer's post.
- 11:05 a.m.
- Yeah, and now look at
the time that CCPD
got the first call
about the bomb sighting.
- It was five minutes later.
- Hey, can you bring up
Officer Jones' brain scan?
I'm going to run the code
of Spencer's post
through the decompiler.
♪ ♪
Let's see what's underneath.
- Got it.
♪ ♪
[cell phone clicking]
- Done. The brain scan.
The code is an exact match.
[whirring]
- Barry, it's the headlines.
- What?
- That's how Spencer's
hypnotizing people.
They're reading her headlines!
Don't look at them.
- Aah! Too late!
♪ ♪
- Nora's been hypnotized.
She's trying to kill me.
Nora, you got
to snap out of this.
- What I have
to do is kill you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Caitlin, take over.
- Where are you going?
- To get my family back.
- Hurry up
and kill him already.
♪ ♪
[both grunt]
[gun fires]
- Time to bounce.
♪ ♪
- Hey, you're going to be okay.
All right?
Nice shot!
Guys, do we know
where Spencer is?
- I can't ping her phone. CCPD
disabled all the cell towers
in the area to prevent
a remote bomb detonation.
- She must be local
in order to put those headlines
up on that
big screen, right?
- She's at the stadium.
- She's here.
♪ ♪
Looks like you'll be trading
this cell in for another.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
All right, Spencer's all locked
up in Iron Heights.
- The Mayor's resigning.
- What?
- I'm surprised
she lasted this long.
- Luckily, I was able to get
a quote from her
exonerating Officer Jones
for my article.
Post will go up tomorrow.
- Papa Joe will be relieved
his friend's in the clear.
- Yeah.
Well, at least now,
with Spencer behind us,
we can concentrate
on bigger fish.
- Yes, we can.
So...
- Uh, Sherlock...
- Sherloque.
- He thinks he's found a key
to Cicada's identity.
- A crucial clue to help us
solve our little mystery.
So we all know the distinctive
sound of Cicada's breathing
due to the respirator
in the mask.
But not just that, because
also his lungs are injured.
- But injured from what?
- Historically, there is an
event that causes David Hersch
to always become Cicada,
but not this time.
There's a different Cicada
because...
- Because Nora helped me
destroy the satellite.
♪ ♪
- Monsieur Allen, Nora's strike
through the satellite
changed the trajectory of
the debris, and now the debris
has hit a new person
and injured...
our new Cicada.
- Okay, but how did
that give him his powers?
- DeVoe flooded the satellite
with dark matter.
It makes sense that the pieces
would be saturated.
- So Cicada and the dagger
were created
the night
of the Enlightenment.
- Acquired powers together.
- Well, listen, Sherloke...
- Sherloque.
- I got to hand it to you.
That's very impressive.
- It's quite a breakthrough,
right, Monsieur Dibny?
One that I cannot take
any credit for.
No, all the credit,
all the praise
goes to you,
Monsieur Dibny.
It was your instincts
to follow the mask, right?
Well, you were right,
and I was...
less right.
♪ ♪
I apologize.
- Okay, guys, I'm sorry.
The dagger part
still doesn't make sense.
I mean, things cannot
become metas, right?
- I don't know about that.
♪ ♪
[scoffs]
Our satellite didn't
just create new metas.
It created meta-tech.
- Which puts meta-human
abilities in the hands of...
anyone.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Hey.
Caitlin says
you're going to be fine.
I'm sorry for suppressing
your powers, but...
I think it was
the right thing to do.
- Yeah. No, I-I...
I get it. I mean,
I was trying to kill Dad.
I would've done
the same thing, too.
- No, that's...
[sighs]
That's not what I mean.
I'm talking about
in the future.
♪ ♪
- What?
- I know that you're upset
and angry.
And honestly, I...
Before today, I couldn't
even imagine a situation
where I would do something
like that to you.
But after seeing the choice
that I just made...
I know that whatever reason
I would have
for keeping your powers
a secret, it...
it must have been
a good one, Nora.
It must have been
to protect you.
- No.
What happened today...
has nothing to do with what
happens in the future.
You didn't suppress
my abilities my whole life
because I was brainwashed
or attacking people.
You did it to control me.
♪ ♪
My whole life
I felt like I was different
than everybody else,
but I didn't know why.
You took a choice away
from me
that I didn't even know
that I had...
♪ ♪
A choice to be a hero,
like my dad.
♪ ♪
- What's going on?
- Nothing, we're just talking.
- No.
Mom thinks that she had good
reason to suppress my powers
in the future, but she doesn't
know what that reason is.
♪ ♪
- I'm sure it's a good one.
Look, Nora, I don't have
to visit the future
to know what kind of mother
Iris is going to be.
She cares about family
more than anyone I've ever met.
Okay? And...
I support her decisions...
past, present, and future.
♪ ♪
- Then I guess I need
to rethink what the meaning
of family is.
- Nora, wait.
- Do you know what hurt
the most
about learning I had powers?
Not hearing it from my mom.
♪ ♪
- It's all right.
- [sobs]
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
- Hi.
- Nora, hi.
- Um, it's kind of
a long story,
but can I stay here?
- Get in here, kid.
- Are you sure it's
not too much trouble?
- It's fine. Maybe talk
about the reason later?
But for now, there's some fresh
pillows and blankets upstairs.
- Thanks, Papa Joe.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
Aah!
[metal crumples]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
- Greg, move your head.