(Barry)
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
(Barry)
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
And find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
(Barry)
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
(male narrator)
Previously on The Flash...
(Barry)
It's Clyde Mardon.
I think he can
control the weather.
(Clyde)
I didn't think there was
anyone else like me.
I'm not like you.
You're a murderer.
[gunshots]
I love you, Iris.
He and I are just
best friends.
So how do we catch somebody
that even I can't keep up with?
We can fashion
an electronic barrier
To trap the reverse-flash.
The super capacitors,
The containment field
is fluctuating.
I still don't know why
the containment system failed.
I must have missed something.
You think Dr. Wells
killed Barry's mom?
I don't know yet, but I do know
that wells keeps secrets,
And this may be one of them.
(Clyde)
I got a plane to catch!
Come on, Clyde!
Aah!
Damn it.
[door closes]
I think I got one of them.
Your luck's gonna run out
one of these days,
Little brother.
You've been telling me that
since I was Ten, Mark.
Because I've been taking care
of you since you were ten.
Look, it's gonna get
choppy.
You might want to
strap yourself in.
You just can't help yourself,
can you?
[chuckles]
Oh, my god.
Clyde.
[screams]
♪ Blame it on the night
I never would've pegged you
as someone who likes to bowl.
Oh, this is one of my favorite
places in the world,
And I'm guessing
one of the only sports
That I can destroy you at.
Oh, okay,
you think so, huh?
I'm pretty sure, yeah.
Okay.
[chuckles]
(Iris)
Hi, guys.
Iris, Eddie, hey.
What are you guys
doing here?
We thought it would be fun.
Barry and I have been bowling
here since we were kids.
Why don't you guys join us?
Uh...
We don't want to
interrupt your date.
No, it's... it's okay.
Are you sure?
Of course.
It'll be fun.
♪ So blame it on the night
Ha-ha!
Do you smell that, Barry?
That's defeat.
You never told me you were
such a big fan of bowling.
Sure I have.
This is one of my
favorite places in the world.
(Iris)
Oh, ho ho!
Ohh!
Ha-ha!
I am impressed, Allen.
I heard the owner was
thinking of selling.
Maybe you could write a piece
on the place?
Um, I'm still iffy on whether
bowling is an actual sport.
I've wondered the same.
Well, sport or hobby,
I am still better than you.
[chuckles]
All right, well, I'm serious,
a little bit of press,
The lanes could be
designated
As, like, a landmark
or something.
Yeah.
Oh, Eddie, you're up, man.
Oh, right.
Whoo.
Go get 'em, babe.
(Coroner)
Recording start.
Central City Coroner's report,
file 28527.
Petechial Hemorrhaging in
the Mucosa of the lips
And the interior of the mouth,
the strong odor of bleach,
And the presence
of a postmortem ligature mark
All suggest the decedent's
manner of death, is...
Homicide.
Can I help you?
Yes, you can.
I want to know who killed
Clyde Mardon.
He was shot by a cop
a little over six months ago,
And I want his name.
That's privileged
information.
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave.
Shame.
Ooh!
[panting]
Please.
Cop's name.
Now.
I perform hundreds
of autopsies a year.
Perhaps this will
jog your memory.
[both laughing]
Oh, buster keaton.
That guy was a genius.
- Yup.
- I can't believe
You've never seen
this movie.
Must have been before my time.
I gotta make you a must-see
movie list, pronto.
(Wells)
Please do.
While I am more than happy
To spend an evening watching
old movies with you, Cisco,
Do you not have your brother's
dinner to attend?
Yeah.
I was gonna ask caitlin
To come with me, but then
I got a much better idea.
Which was?
To not go at all.
Oh.
Things are not any better
with your family?
You're missing the movie.
Right.
Okay, you know what,
I'm gonna be honest with you.
Things have actually been
pretty fantastic...
Since I stopped
seeing them so much.
[alarm chiming]
Silent alarm has been tripped
at the Central City morgue.
Why would anyone want to
rob a morgue?
[phone chimes]
I got to go.
Emergency at the morgue.
- Bye.
- See you at home.
Hey, Linda, sorry,
I should go too.
They're going to need someone
from the crime lab.
I'll see you.
Well, um... That was fun.
Yeah.
[dogs barking]
Taxi!
Oh, come on,
I'm gonna be late!
What's going on?
What do you see?
A dead body.
(Cisco)
Barry, you're in a morgue.
You're gonna have to be a little
more specific than that.
The Coroner, he's dead.
[police siren blaring]
The mayor's made this
high priority.
Copy that, captain.
- Aah.
- Oh.
Allen, my fiance
just bought me this!
Yeah,
I'm so sorry, Captain.
Eh! Just help Joe
find out who did this.
Mm-hmm.
What's with all the water?
Did the sprinkler system
go off or something?
[sighs]
No, I checked
All the sprinklers.
They're all intact.
But look at this.
What is that, ice?
Mm-hmm.
The coroner has multiple
impact bruises on his torso,
All the size of a tennis ball.
Judging by the amount of ice
and water on the ground,
I'm guessing he was
killed by Hail.
Hail?
In here?
Yeah.
Do you think this was snart?
No, his cold-gun couldn't
have done this.
(Thawne)
Joe, we got something.
The Coroner's office
just installed
An automated
dictation system.
Listen to this.
(Coroner on tape)
Please, no more.
(mark on tape)
I'll stop when you tell me...
(Coroner on tape)
Stop.
(Mark on tape)
Who killed him?
I know that voice.
That's Mardon.
- I want a name.
- Clyde Mardon's dead.
It's not Clyde Mardon.
It's his brother, Mark.
(Coroner on tape)
It was detective West.
He shot him. Detective Joe Jest
killed your brother.
(Mark on tape)
He will pay for what he did.
[Coroner screaming on tape]
So Clyde Mardon
has a brother?
And both brothers
survived the plane crash,
And then
the dark matter released
From the particle accelerator
explosion
Affects them both
in virtually the same way.
Yeah, only mark's powers
seem to be a lot more precise.
To be able to control
the weather like that, indoors?
You'd have to be
a weather wizard.
Ooh, been waiting since week one
to use that one.
- Mm!
- Trigeminal Headache?
- What?
- Trigeminal Headache.
Brain freeze.
Then why don't you just
call it a brain freeze?
So I'm guessing you
running around a twister
In the opposite direction isn't
gonna to do the trick this time.
I just remembered.
During our run-in with mardon,
Clyde Mardon,
I was tinkering with something
To help attract
unbound atmospheric electrons.
Like a grounding mechanism?
Yes, 'cause the only way
that mardon can
Control the weather...
[phone vibrating]
Is if he can tap
into the atmosphere's
Natural electrical circuit,
and if we
Take away that circuit,
clear skies.
Singh's checking in.
I gotta go.
Yeah, I'll meet you
at the station.
Joe, we'll find mardon.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried at all.
Well, he's taking
being targeted
By a revenge-seeking meta-human
rather well, I must say.
Don't worry, barry.
Joe will be fine, I promise.
Yeah, no, I know.
I actually wanted to talk to you
about something else.
- Mm-hmm?
- Um...
Look, last night,
on my way to the morgue,
I saw something.
What'd you see?
I was running and I turned
and I saw myself.
Or I don't know, another flash
running beside me.
Interesting.
Yeah.
What do you think it was?
Could be an optical illusion,
a mirroring effect
Caused by wind shear and light,
a speed mirage, if you will.
It didn't seem like that.
It was...
He seemed real.
I tell you what.
Let's focus on finding Mardon,
And once he's safely contained
in the pipeline,
We'll investigate this.
(Captain singh)
Where are we at with mardon?
No one at the morgue
saw or heard anything.
We're canvassing
known associates,
Seeing if he reached
out to anybody.
Maybe can get a lead
on where he's holed up.
All right, why don't we let
thawne do that?
Because nobody knows the mardon
brothers better than I do.
I mean, Chyre and I
tracked them for years.
I know how they think.
Which is why you should
coordinate
The investigation from here.
Hey.
(West)
If you guys want to
keep that smile
On that pretty face, she doesn't
hear about any of this.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey, dad.
- Mm.
- Hi.
- Hey.
So, what are you guys
working on?
You got any good leads
for an honest reporter?
Things are actually pretty quiet
around here right now.
Can you guys
give me a minute?
Yeah, me and Barry were actually
gonna go grab lunch.
We were?
Right, yeah, yeah.
[chuckles]
Duh.
Hey.
Ever since last night,
You've barely said a peep.
What is going on?
I didn't like
the way I felt
Watching you and barry
last night.
Eddie,
Barry, he's just...
Like family.
I know, and I know
You two have a long history
that pre-dates me,
But iris, we live together.
You're my girlfriend,
And someday, hopefully,
you'll be more.
I don't like feeling
like the odd man out
Every time you and barry
are together.
And I shouldn't have to.
Eddie, barry is always
gonna be a part of my life.
I get that, but something's
changed between you two.
Whatever that is,
I am not okay with it.
[sighs]
Mm.
I haven't had one of those
in way too long.
Felt appropriate.
So, you want to talk about
what's been going on with you?
What do you think's been
going on with me, Barry?
You just seem
a bit cavalier,
Considering what
we're up against.
[chuckles]
We aren't up against anything.
- Joe, come on, I...
- Look, I'm fine.
Can we just change
the subject, please?
Sure.
Actually, you know,
I could use some advice.
About what?
Uh, you know,
just relationship stuff.
Oh, you mean, like,
that girl, Linda?
No, actually.
With Iris.
Things between us have gotten
a little complicated... Again.
[laughs]
You're asking
your adopted father
For advice about being in love
with his daughter,
Who just so happens to be
dating his partner?
I know, I know.
Things have gone
way past complicated.
Sometimes, me and Iris
have these moments,
And when I'm looking
into her eyes,
It's hard not to think
That she's feeling
the same way I do.
Look, you already told iris
how you feel,
So unless she comes out and
says she feels the same way,
All you can do is
hold on to those moments.
Man, it is coming down.
Yeah.
[thunder rumbles]
[radio jingle]
(male radio announcer)
And it's another beautiful day
here in central city.
Not a cloud.
Mardon.
[thunder rumbling]
[sparking]
You're confined to the precinct
until Mardon's caught.
David, you said it
yourself.
That son of a bitch
killed my partner.
And I'm not gonna lose you
the way I lost Fred Chyre.
Look, I can't stop you
being pissed, Joe,
But I can keep you safe.
Maybe your daughter
can contact The Flash.
I'm not getting her
involved in this.
Allen, make sure
he doesn't go anywhere.
I need to be out there.
Joe, you're always
the first one
To tell me when I'm not
thinking clearly.
I took down Clyde.
I can take down
His dirt bag brother too.
You didn't do that alone,
remember?
You're right.
How are any of these guys
going to protect me?
They don't know. They don't know
what Mardon's capable of.
All right, well,
lucky for you,
Your friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs do.
[sighs]
"The Flash: Speeding his way
into our lives?"
That's a little on the nose,
don't you think?
[scoffs]
I want to show you
something.
Simon Stagg.
Remember him?
Hasn't been seen in,
like, six months.
I thought the rumor was
he was a recluse.
You know,
went all howard hughes.
This was taken the night
that Stagg went missing.
The last person to leave
stagg industries
The night that Stagg disappeared
was Harrison Wells.
This doesn't prove anything,
Mason.
It's enough for me
to develop a theory.
Every trail in this files leads
to one person, Harrison Wells,
Which is why I need for you
to start asking
Your friends who know him
some questions, Iris.
Linda.
Hi.
Last night was fun.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah.
Look, I just wanted
to apologize.
Apologize...?
Well, for interrupting
your date with Barry.
I shouldn't have done that...
And I'm sorry.
You know, Iris,
When you told me that
Barry had feelings for you,
I thought it was just
the typical weird crap
That women do to each other,
But last night, I realized
what you didn't tell me,
And what's kind of irritating
Is that you have feelings
for him too.
N-no, Linda, I mean,
it's not like that.
One thing you learn about people
when you work here, Iris,
It's usually what isn't said
that's the real story.
So it sounded like something
was kind of bothering you
On the phone.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, it's fine.
So the other night
was fun, right?
Yeah.
Did Eddie have a good time?
Linda?
I think so.
You don't think we were
too... You know.
No.
Okay, good.
So the reason that I called you
was because my sort of advisor
At the paper is always
teaching me lessons,
Tricks of the trade,
how to get good story,
And one of the things
he's repeatedly telling me
Is to follow your hunch,
see where it leads.
Sounds like good advice.
Yeah, it is.
Except in this instance,
that hunch involves you.
Well, you can ask me
anything, Iris.
It's about Harrison Wells.
What about him?
Well, I mean,
a lot of strange things
Have been happening
in Central City this past year.
The Flash, the burning man
people going missing.
He was there
at Stagg's office
The night that Stagg
went missing.
And you think that Doctor Wells
is what, responsible?
I mean, I don't really know him,
but you and your friends do.
Uh-huh.
Barry, in your heart of hearts,
do you think it's possible
That there's more to Harrison
Than people have been
led to believe?
Harrison wells is a good man.
If you're looking
for a story,
Then you're not gonna
find one with him.
I call it the Wizard's Wand.
Subtle.
How does it work?
Think of it like an
active lightning rod.
You just point it at the sky,
and it'll suck up
Whatever energy's floating
around it like a sponge.
And it'll stop Mardon?
It'll certainly
slow him down.
If there's no atmospheric
electrons available to him,
There's no way for him
to control the weather.
Good work, Cisco,
as always.
If you excuse me,
I'm gonna go stretch my legs.
You okay?
You seem a little off.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, somebody at...
Somebody at picture news
got it into Iris's head
That something suspicious
is going on with Dr. Wells.
Like what?
That he knows what happened
to Simon Stagg.
Apparently, nobody's
heard from him or seen him
Since the night
I stopped danton black.
What'd you tell her?
That she's wrong.
And she is.
(Cisco)
Keep this handy.
I'll protect you
from Mardon's powers.
(West)
Yeah, Cisco, I got it.
Hey, Joe... I know you got
a lot going on right now,
But... You mentioned Doctor Wells
might have had something to do
With Barry's mother's murder.
Why did you think that?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I was wrong.
But you seemed
really sure of it.
Look, Cisco, I can't talk
about this right now, okay?
[sighs]
I heard you were looking for me.
Here I am.
Mardon.
Hey, Joe.
I can call you Joe, can't I?
Figured we don't got to be
too formal
Seeing as you put two bullets
in my brother's chest.
Your brother killed
my partner
And a whole lot
of innocent people,
And threatened to kill
even more.
[thunder rumbling]
Yeah, Clyde was no saint,
but he was family.
If you can't protect
your family,
The least you can do
is avenge 'em.
[thunder crashing]
This is between us.
Nobody else needs to get hurt.
But they are gonna get hurt.
Joe!
No!
I'm not gonna be so easy
to put down, Joe.
Take him down!
No, run!
Huh!
Joe!
[grunts]
[wind swirling]
Captain!
David.
All right, Cisco,
I'm heading home.
Cisco?
All right, fine,
I will watch
Every episode
of The Walking Dead with you.
Hey, you couldn't have stopped
Mardon from attacking
The police station.
It's not your fault.
No, that's not it.
What do you think
of Dr. Wells?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, do you think
He's capable of doing
something bad?
Is this because of what Barry
said he heard?
Ever since the particle
accelerator exploded,
There's always someone who's
got it in for Dr. Wells.
No, no, it's more than that.
Joe said that maybe
Dr. Wells was somehow involved
In of Barry's mother's death
and her murder.
That's absurd.
Yeah, I know,
and that's what I said,
And we proved that
that wasn't the case,
But I'm just saying,
some things aren't adding up.
Like what, for example?
Come here, look at this.
The night we trapped
The Reverse-Flash
In the force-field,
he escaped
Because the containment system
failed,
But I checked that data
three times,
And the super-capacitors
were still fully charged
When he got out.
The numbers don't add up,
Caitlin.
There's no reason that
the containment system
Should have failed.
I'm sure there's
a perfectly good explanation.
One perfectly good explanation
Is that wells did something
to the trap.
Are you suggesting
that Dr. Wells is in league
With the man in the yellow suit?
I'm... We all saw that thing
nearly kill him that night.
Yeah, nearly.
[sighs]
Cisco, what you're saying
Doesn't make any sense.
That's crazy.
Can you keep Wells out of
S.T.A.R. Labs tomorrow morning?
- Thank you, Barry.
- Yeah.
This isn't how I thought I'd
finally meet David's Co-workers.
He speaks
very highly of you.
Really?
David's all bark.
A very loud bark.
[both chuckle]
How is he, doctor?
(doctor)
We're stabilizing him.
He's experiencing some paralysis
in his lower extremities.
Oh, my god.
The hardest thing
to gauge right now
Is the extent of his
neurocognitive deficits.
So he may not be
the same person you remember.
Can I see him?
I'm sorry, visitation's
for family only.
Being his fiance
makes him family, doctor.
Uh, sure.
Will he be able to return
to the force?
I'm actually not sure
he'll be able to walk again.
Joe, where are you going?
I need to end this.
Not by yourself.
Yes, by myself!
I know him!
I can find him.
I don't want
Anybody else getting hurt,
especially Iris and you.
Iris is fi...
Mardon said he was
going to avenge his brother.
That goes beyond me.
It goes all the way
To you and her.
You stay with Iris,
and you keep her safe.
Do not leave her side.
Yeah, all right.
Hey, have you seen
Iris West?
She went to see her dad.
- You're Barry Allen, right?
- Yeah.
Her friend/brother?
Or is that brother/friend?
Friend is fine.
Oh.
I'm Mason Bridge.
Oh, you're the guy
who thinks
Harrison Wells is
some mad genius?
Oh, no, no, no, I never said
he was crazy.
He's a sociopath and a liar,
for sure.
Really?
You don't see it?
All the time you two
spend together.
Excuse me?
Sometimes when I'm bored,
I follow him around.
And for the most part,
he keeps to himself,
Except when he's
meeting up with you,
Which he seems to do
quite a bit.
And then one time,
he met up with Simon Stagg,
And then poof,
no more Simon Stagg.
So you're saying Wells
knows where Stagg is?
No, I'm saying Wells
killed him.
Ah.
All right, well,
Even if I believed you, which
I don't, he's in a wheelchair.
How could he possibly
have done that?
I have evidence
in a secure digital file
That will explain everything.
What... what evidence?
You'll just have to
read about it
In the Sunday paper,
like everybody else.
[machine powering on]
Let's see if you can tell me
What really went wrong
that night.
[man yelling]
Hey!
Joe.
Eddie.
You shouldn't be here.
And you shouldn't be chasing
after mardon alone, partner.
You find anything?
Not yet, but this was
an old Mardon brothers' hideout
About six years ago,
so it's a long shot.
But listen, Eddie...
Save it.
I'm not leaving.
[line ringing]
Hey, have you heard from dad?
He's not answering his cell.
Uh, no.
I haven't talked to him.
[sighs]
I'm starting to worry about him.
What are you doing home
so early?
I was looking for you, actually.
I just met your friend Mason,
And he said he had
some kind of proof
That Dr. Wells did something.
Do you know what it is?
No, he hasn't told me.
All right.
So, how are things going
with Linda?
Why do you say it like that?
Like what?
Like how you used to always
say "Becky Cooper."
Oh, come on.
Becky Cooper was a nightmare
of a high school girlfriend,
And you should have
never dated her.
Okay, so you're saying that
Linda is "Becky" material?
I mean, I wouldn't
go that far.
She's... Hot and nice
and smart
And she is really good
at her job.
I just...
I don't think that
she's the right one for you.
Then who is?
What?
I don't understand.
This doesn't make any sense.
[machine sparking]
Somebody was here
very recently.
He left this here for me.
Where to next?
[wind gust]
Ooh!
Joe!
[bell ringing]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Small miracle you only broke
the one leg, Joe.
The night I got sucked
out of my plane,
I broke almost every bone
in my body.
[winces]
It was excruciating.
At least you got a small taste
of what that felt like.
Still...
Guess you'll never know what
it really feels like to be god.
That's what your brother
said to me,
Right before I killed him.
Aah.
I don't need these powers
to end your life.
Then do it.
That's what you came here
for, isn't it?
An eye for an eye?
Oh, Joe.
I want so much more
than an eye.
(Wells)
I often forget
how important it is
To step away
from my ever present routine.
Thank you, Caitlin.
This morning has been
a refreshing change of pace.
You can have more
than two hard-boiled eggs
For breakfast, Dr. Wells.
What can I say?
I guess I'm a creature of habit.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I believe these were to-go.
Actually, I thought we could
sit here and enjoy them.
Why not?
We've seen what mardon can do,
but do not forget,
He is not invincible.
I can't believe
this is happening.
(Thawne)
He is still a man,
at best, a criminal.
We'll find him.
(Thawne)
We will find this dirt bag...
Hey, look at me,
all right?
I promise I will bring him
back to you.
(Thawne)
Whatever you need to do...
Okay.
I want you all to scour
this city until we find Joe.
Move out!
[phone vibrating]
Hello?
(Mark)
I have your father.
He's a little broken,
but still alive.
If you want him
to stay that way,
Come to the waterfront,
south side.
Oh, and iris,
you tell the police,
Your father's dead.
She's on her way.
He has my dad.
He says if I tell anyone,
he'll kill him.
He wants me to meet him
at the waterfront.
All right,
I'm coming with you.
Okay.
Let's go.
- Barry.
- Hey.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
No, Linda, I'm sorry,
I really can't right now.
Of course not.
Look, it's not like that.
It's an emergency.
I have to go right now.
You know, Dr. Wells,
I just...
I want to thank you again
For all that you've done
for Ronnie.
One thank you will suffice,
I'm sure.
You know, Caitlin,
if Cisco were to adjust
The radial velocity parameters
on the S.T.A.R labs satellite,
We might be able
to better detect
The vortex of a forming storm,
and if we could detect
Those air updrafts,
no matter where they originate,
No matter how small, we might
be able to locate Mark Mardon.
That's a great idea.
So why don't we go
to S.T.A.R. Labs
And alert Cisco?
Let me just get these to-go.
Hi, could I get these
in to-go cups?
Sure, just a second.
[distorted voice]
My goals are beyond
your understanding.
[typing clacks]
[speaking backwards]
Dr. Wells,
we meet at last.
My goals are beyond
your understanding.
I can't believe this.
Oh, I'm not like The Flash
at all.
Some would say,
I'm the reverse.
Congratulations, Joe.
You're my plus-one today.
Front row seats
to watch everyone
And everything you ever loved
destroyed.
Pretty girl too.
Such a shame.
Please, she's my daughter.
Clyde was my brother.
He's a thief
and a murderer.
She's an innocent girl.
She'll pay for the sins
of the father then.
Mark...
[muffled yelling]
They'll all pay.
[thunder rumbling]
[clapping]
You're incredibly clever, Cisco.
I've always said so.
You're him.
The Reverse-Flash.
You and I have never been
truly, properly introduced.
I am eobard thawne.
Thawne?
Like Eddie.
Let's call him
a distant relative.
The night that we trapped
The Reverse-Flash,
You almost died.
Mm-hmm.
There were two of you.
It's an after-image,
A speed mirage, if you will.
[panicked breathing]
Joe was right.
You were there that night,
15 years ago, in Barry's house.
You killed Nora Allen.
It was never my intention
to kill Nora.
I was there to kill Barry.
Why?
You're his friend.
You've been teaching him
how to...
Go faster, I know.
A means to an end.
And I'll tell you why.
Because I have been
stuck here,
Marooned here in this place
for 15 long years.
And The Flash
and The Flash's speed
Is the key to my returning
to my world.
To my time.
And no one is going to prevent
that from happening.
I can help you.
You're smart, Cisco.
But you're not that smart.
Do you know
How hard it has been
to keep all of this from you,
Especially from you?
Because the truth is,
I've grown quite fond of you.
And in many ways,
you have shown me
What it's like
to have a son.
Forgive me, but to me,
you've been dead for centuries.
What do we do?
He'll find us.
Oh, my god.
[thunder rumbling]
Iris, you need to get
out of here, okay?
You need to get as far away
from here as possible.
- I am not leaving you.
- Iris, please!
Listen to me,
ever since the night
That you told me
how you felt,
I have not been able to
stop thinking about you.
At first,
I was really mad,
And then I realized that
the reason that I couldn't
Stop thinking about you
was because I didn't want to.
I've never stopped
thinking about you.
[thunder rumbling]
Aah!
Caitlin.
Barry, I need to talk to you.
Dr. Wells, he isn't...
(Barry)
Hey, there's no time for that
right now, all right?
There is a tsunami
heading for the city.
(Barry)
How do I stop it?
Theoretically, if you can
create a vortex barrier
Along the coastline,
a wall of wind,
That would be able to sap
the tidal wave of its energy
Before it hits the city.
By running back and forth.
How fast?
I don't know if you can
run that fast.
(Barry)
I am so sorry.
I didn't want you
to find out this way.
Go!
[roaring]
Aah!
[people screaming]
[panting]
[dogs barking]
Taxi!
Oh, come on,
I'm gonna be late!
Oh, boy.
(man)
Greg, move your head.