Cleaned, corrected, dashes removed, re-synced
and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
If you ever need anything,
I will race over in a heartbeat.
Same.
Well, as fast as I can run.
Advanced Technology
Operating Mechanism... A.T.O.M.
What are you gonna
use it for?
To protect the people
of this city.
You think Dr. Wells
killed Barry's mom?
I don't know yet.
But I do know
that Wells keeps secrets.
The way that
he described running...
feeling the wind
and the power...
it's like he was talking
from experience.
Harrison Wells is
The Reverse-Flash.
Eddie, we need your help.
Pedal to the metal.
We've got a 10-31 in progress.
Shiny Diamond,
18th and Olive.
That's only a few blocks
from here.
Has every crook in Central City
gone crazy?
This is the third attempted
robbery tonight.
Barry.
We got another one.
Hello.
18th and Olive.
Got it.
Who's this?
Oh. Indecent exposure.
Powell Park.
That ain't something
you should be showing people.
They're getting away, guys.
They're not getting away,
Eddie.
Let's get these bozos
up ahead of us first,
and then we'll worry about
the idiots at the Shiny Diamond.
All right.
We're gonna run out
of room, though.
I'll take care of that.
What do you think
he meant by that?
Oh.
That's what he meant.
I think we lost them.
Oh, no, you didn't.
And by the way,
you're under arrest.
We need to go.
Now. Come on!
Uh-uh.
Freeze.
You guys missing these?
On the ground.
So, uh, I'm just curious, but...
have you guys not heard of me,
or what?
Nice work, detective.
- Good night, Dr. Kang.
- Good night.
Oh... ow!
Victim's name is Lindsay Kang,
engineering professor
at Hudson University.
- Just got tenure.
- Hey.
So, her whole body's covered in
these puncture wounds
you see on her face.
Bite marks maybe.
Whatever it was, she must have
gone into anaphylaxis.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
The blood sample should tell us
everything we need to know.
I'll run tests
back at my lab.
They can do it faster at
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well, yeah, but,
I mean, it's just...
It's just what?
It's kind of weird being there
right now.
Barry, you know we have to
play it cool with Wells.
If he finds out
we suspect him...
I know.
I get it.
I just think that we should tell
Cisco and Caitlin.
They could help us.
The more people who know,
the more chance
Wells is gonna find out
we're on to him.
I mean, what if one of them
slips up?
Or panics?
- Or what if...
- What?
What if
they're not on our side?
No.
Absolutely not.
They're not involved in
whatever he's planning.
I mean, Wells is their boss,
their mentor.
They've been with him
for a long time.
I've seen plenty of people
make the wrong choice
for loyalty.
Please do not include them
until we can be sure.
All right.
Death by apitoxin.
Honeybee venom.
Bees.
Why did it have to be bees?
Y'all, I don't do bees.
Ain't nobody got time
for bees.
But when a honeybee stings,
the stingers are literally
torn from their abdomen,
and they die.
But there were no stingers
in the body
and no dead bees in the car.
A honeybee can only deposit
.1 milligrams of apitoxin
when it releases its stinger.
And yet, Ms. Kang was found
with enough venom in her system
to kill a herd of elephants.
It appears not only is
a meta-human
controlling these bees but also
increasing their toxicity.
Bees communicate
by releasing pheromones.
Maybe this meta's controlling
them through secretion?
Anyone want to join me
in getting a beekeeper suit?
I'm pretty sure
I can outrun a bee.
Just don't run into a lake.
Bees will wait for you
to come up for air
and then they'll sting you.
Discovery Channel.
Turns out there's a lot
to discover.
Felicity,
what are you doing here?
Can you guys come outside
for a sec?
What exactly
are we waiting for, Ms. Smoak?
Up there.
Is that a bird?
It's a plane.
It's my boyfriend.
Hi.
I'm Ray.
So he seems
a little tall for you.
Barry Allen, are you jealous?
Je... no.
No, I'm not jealous.
I just... I really wish
you would've called
before flying in.
Oh, no, he flew.
I drove.
I'm serious, all right?
Now is not the best time.
Why?
What's going on?
Ah, well, my ears popped,
so that's something.
You're lucky
you didn't break your neck.
What is it with billionaires
being superheroes?
So have you... picked a name yet?
I'm kind of partial to
The Atom.
Shoo.
You married to that, or...?
Your A.T.O.M. suit...
it's quite the technological
achievement, Mr. Palmer.
I'm impressed.
And he is never impressed.
Well, thank you,
but I can't quite seem to
keep it up.
He means the suit.
- Yeah, I mean the suit.
- Yeah.
I can attest that
everything else works just fine.
There's nothing
we need to fix in...
That area.
No, no, no.
The sex is great.
God, there's two of them.
I know from Felicity
that you have been
very helpful with Barry
and the Flash suit,
and I was hoping to get
another set of eyes on my...
- Problem.
Any friend of The Arrow's
is a friend...
- Hell, yes.
- Uh, guys.
We kind of have a lot
going on already.
There's the
meta-human killer
that can control
a whole swarm of bees?
Cool.
I mean, awful.
I'm sure Caitlin and I will
provide ample support, Barry.
And I will be happy to
sit this one out.
You...
Ray, why don't you stay here
and work on your suit
while Barry and I run to
Jitters for some java?
Sounds like a plan.
- Coffee?
- Sure.
- Hey, Detective.
- Iris.
What are you doing here?
I am following up on my story
about crime in Central City.
Or lack thereof.
Could someone be working
with The Flash?
No.
Of course not.
You caught a flasher,
armed robbers
in a getaway car,
and two jewelry thieves
last night.
I'm just that good.
What is going on with you
lately?
You've been acting
really weird and withdrawn.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think that
you were hiding something
from me.
Iris, I'm... I'm not hiding
anything from you.
Do you ever go to work?
Oh, you're funny.
Okay, I can't keep lying to Iris
about The Flash.
You have to.
It's really starting
to affect our relationship.
We haven't had sex
in two weeks.
Which you didn't want
to know about.
Keeping her in the dark
keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
Well, I'm her father.
And I'm her boyfriend.
When does my vote
outweigh yours?
When you become her husband.
You know I left Starling City
to get away from
the mood and brood,
but it looks like
it followed me here.
I know.
I'm sorry.
It's like I said before,
now is not the best time.
Barry, I have been through
enough with you
to know when you're
holding something back.
Is this because I told Ray
your secret?
Because he is trustworthy,
Barry.
He wants to help people,
just like you.
I know, that's not what
I'm worried about.
It's...
I really don't want to
put anyone else in danger.
In danger of what?
Barry, hey.
Eddie, hey.
- You remember Felicity.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Great to see you.
Yeah.
What is wrong with you?
Is everyone in Central City
in a bad mood?
I thought Central City was
supposed to be the fun one.
It's, um...
- It's not...
- Felicity knows.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
So everyone but Iris.
It feels that way.
How do you lie to
everyone you care about?
For starters,
don't think of it as lying.
Think of it as protecting her
from getting hurt...
with a fib.
But Iris can tell
I'm hiding something,
and it's putting
this distance between us.
I have an idea.
Why don't we all
go to dinner tonight?
A little wine and dine
is sure to bridge the gap.
Come on, we all had fun
last time.
Sure.
Why not?
Barry Allen, fifth wheel.
Well, I can't make
my 3:00 meeting this afternoon.
Also, confirm my dinner
reservation for tonight.
Last time,
they couldn't find it,
and that was unacceptable.
Thanks.
You see that bad man
over there?
Tell your sisters it's time.
So you put solid oxide
fuel cells into the belt?
Yeah, it's the only place
to hide the hardware.
Hmm, well, they should be
generating enough energy
to power the suit.
It could be
the operating temperature.
I mean, you're essentially...
Overheating the system, yeah.
I figured.
But if we insulate them
with a ceramic compound...
We may improve
the operating efficiency.
You really are quite clever,
Cisco.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
You're incredibly clever,
Cisco.
How do you turn
this thing on?
Cisco?
You okay?
Yeah.
I haven't been getting
enough sleep, so...
Cisco, we need you up here.
Killer bees are at it again.
Get a hold of Barry.
Another bee attack.
Folston Tech.
I'll see where Joe is.
- Bee careful.
- For real?
Bad pun. Sorry.
Just don't die.
I'm too late.
Where are the bees?
I don't know.
There's no sign of them.
Found them.
How do I get out of here?
Take the northeast crossway.
It's the quickest way
out of the building.
Guys, they're everywhere.
I'm surrounded.
Barry!
Barry.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
Barry, stay with me.
Cisco!
Barry doesn't have a pulse.
- Step away from him.
- What? Why?
We need to jumpstart his heart.
There's a defibrillator
in the suit.
Charge it to 360 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
Hit him again.
400 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
Barry.
Joe.
That is it for
the defibrillator.
It is completely fried.
You're lucky to be alive,
Mr. Allen.
I was very specific
that you not die.
Yeah, that's a pretty big thing
for her.
Cisco, what happened out there?
I followed your directions
exactly.
I'm sorry.
I led you the wrong way.
The schematics that we had,
they... they weren't up to date.
What, they weren't up to date?
What do you mean?
That's never happened before.
What, you think Cisco
was trying to get you killed?
No.
Why would he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know.
That's why I was joking.
Barry, it's our job
to protect you, and today,
we failed, but that'll just
serve as a warning
for all of us to be
more vigilant in the future.
Good news... the apitoxin
is out of your body.
Your levels are
back to normal.
Terrific.
Ray, Felicity.
We're gonna be late for dinner.
Are you sure that's wise,
Barry?
You just died.
Maybe you should
order in tonight.
Yeah, we could
totally cancel.
I'm fine.
Alive. Hungry.
All right?
Let's go.
- That was weird.
- Yeah.
Why didn't we get
invited to dinner?
Oh.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
Wow, Iris.
Check you out.
Hi, Felicity.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hey.
Guys, this is Ray Palmer.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Barry.
Bienvenue chez
Massimo Restaurant.
Mr. Palmer,
your table is ready.
Great.
Shall we?
Yes.
Hey, how did he get
a reservation here?
We've been trying for months.
I don't know.
Here's your table, sir.
I thought it'd be nice
if it was quiet,
so I bought out
the entire restaurant.
Too much?
Just a tad, sweetie.
Joe.
Oh, Cisco.
Hey.
You just saved me a trip
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I got some info
on our second victim.
Name's Bill Carlisle.
He was recently hired
at Folston Tech
to beef up
their robotics division.
Robotics?
That's just like
the first victim.
Wow.
That is weird.
That's not why
you stopped by.
No, I wanted to talk to you
about Barry.
Okay.
Is there something
going on with him?
Something he's not
telling us?
What do you mean?
He hasn't really been
himself lately.
Not that I'm aware of.
It's like something is just
really bothering him.
Well, I think he's got
his mind trained on
catching the bad guys, Cisco.
And he's probably worried about
when The Reverse-Flash is gonna
show his face again.
Oh, I'm not like The Flash
at all.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I'm fine.
It's just... I've got
this crazy headache.
Thank you for the file
and the talk.
- So how did you two meet?
- Work.
Well, actually,
I bought the company
where Felicity was employed,
and so she was forced
to join me at Palmer Tech.
It's not as creepy
as it sounds.
So you two work closely
together?
- Mm-hmm.
- Interesting.
I guess you guys share
all of your thoughts
and feelings and...
Yeah... I share everything
with Felicity.
It's nice that you guys have
that level of communication.
Oh, well, no,
not every-everything.
I mean, sometimes it's good
to just shut up.
I get that.
Some things are better left
unspoken.
Really?
I-I don't find that
to be true.
Oh, thank God.
It's the food.
Food's here.
Our first course
on the tasting menu
is a quail egg frittata.
Bon appetit.
Barry.
I got to admit, I envy you
spending so much time
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Harrison Wells is, like,
a personal hero of mine.
I mean, it's amazing just
to actually
be in the same room with him.
I'll be right back.
Just excuse me.
Okay.
Well, I, um...
have to pee.
Okay, you've been acting
super strange
ever since Ray and I
got to Central City.
What is going on with you?
And don't say
it's a bad time.
Oliver might be joining
the League of Assassins,
Laurel's the Black Canary, and
Thea's training with Malcolm,
so I know about bad times.
Okay.
Joe and I found out that
Wells isn't who he says he is.
He...
He is the man
that killed my mother.
Oh, my God.
But he's been helping you.
Get faster, stronger.
I know.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can
and can't trust.
So you think Cisco and Caitlin
are helping him?
That's impossible.
- Is it?
- Yes.
They were trying to
save you today, Barry.
- They did save you.
- Wells has also saved me.
Many times.
I thought that Wells was
a great man,
and I was so wrong about him.
What if I'm wrong
about everything else too?
Hey, guys.
Uh, things are getting
a little intense in here.
Please can't we just have
a nice evening?
Okay, so it's my fault that
we're not having a nice evening?
I am your girlfriend.
Who you live with.
I shouldn't have to beg you
to talk to me.
If I could talk to you
about this, I would, believe me.
But I can't.
You know what?
I am not hungry anymore.
- Iris.
- You know what?
When you are ready
to act like
we are two people
who love each other,
call me.
I'll be at my dad's.
Thank you for dinner.
I've got to go.
Uh, emergency at
S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Go.
- Sorry.
Well, only 17 more courses
to go.
Containment breach.
Foreign object detected.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Where is he?
Thank you.
Let's see what makes this bee
so poisonous.
You saved my life.
That is one odd-looking bee.
That's 'cause it isn't a bee
at all.
It's a robot.
No way.
Unbelievable.
This bot's got a 360-degree
vision system.
I mean, we're talking
multiple micro-cameras
all coming from various angles
at the same time.
Which means...
It can see all around
the room at once.
That is...
Amazing.
Disturbing.
It's also next-gen hardware
that's nowhere near the market.
So we're not dealing with
a meta-human?
It's just a mad scientist.
Cisco, you said
the second victim,
Bill Carlisle,
was a robotics engineer.
Let's cross-reference
his previous employers
with those of Lindsay Kang.
Allow me.
Mama's been away from
a keyboard for far too long.
Okay.
They both worked
at Mercury Labs.
Let's call Joe.
I think it's time we paid
a visit to an old friend.
Twice in one year, Harrison.
You really are vying for
comeback scientist of the year.
Always a pleasure, Christina.
To what do I owe this visit?
Did you finally find
my tachyon prototype,
or are you here to
blackmail me for another one?
Do you have another one?
We came here for information.
Bill Carlisle and Lindsay Kang.
Former employees who were
recently murdered.
My God.
I wasn't aware.
Stung to death
by robotic bees.
You're looking
for Brie Larvan.
Brie Larvan?
A quite brilliant roboticist
who once developed
miniature mechanical bees
for agricultural use.
Kang and Carlisle warned me
that Brie was weaponizing
the bees for military use,
so I terminated her.
Well, it seems that you would be
on her hit list too, Doctor.
You've got to let us
keep you safe.
I'm all too familiar
with your inability
to protect things, Harrison.
I can take care of myself.
Good day, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Hey.
Okay, so we found
our queen bee.
Brie Larvan.
She's a roboticist.
Joe is running a trace
on her current location,
but so far nothing.
Good.
Where is Ray?
Oh, he's working on his suit
with Cisco.
I like Ray.
He seems like
he's a really good guy.
He is a good guy.
Just like Cisco.
And Caitlin.
Girl.
Is that why you called me here?
I know that you're in
a tricky situation,
but that's when you need
your friends to have your back.
And how can they
if you won't let them?
It's not that simple.
What if Joe is right, and
I tell them, and it backfires?
Wells isn't just their boss,
Felicity.
He is their mentor,
their hero.
My hero.
Look, it's...
I don't know what to do.
When I first met Oliver,
before I knew he was The Arrow,
he would... he would ask me
to do weird things for him
like decrypt
a bullet-ridden computer
or hack some company.
And when I would ask him why,
he would come up
these ridiculous excuses.
And I always knew he was lying,
but I would help him anyway.
- You know why?
- Hmm?
Because I knew Oliver was
a good person with a good heart.
And Cisco and Caitlin?
They're no different.
Hey.
So you're really
staying here tonight?
Tonight.
Tomorrow night.
The night after that.
Do you think that
Eddie is cheating on me?
No.
Eddie's not that kind of guy.
Well, then
I don't know what else
he could be hiding from me.
Iris...
Remember when we were kids,
and Joe would come home
from work
with that blank expression
on his face?
Yeah.
The "Earth to Joe" look.
How could I forget?
I never understood that look
until I started
working for the CCPD.
Showing up at crime scenes and
seeing someone murdered...
it can be ugly work.
And I'm lucky.
I get to hide behind
the science of it
and just stay in my lab,
but Eddie,
he's out there every day
in the darkness.
I just... I think that maybe
if he doesn't want to talk
to you about his work,
it's probably because he wants
to keep you in the light.
What?
I'm just surprised.
You going out of your way
like this
to help me see
Eddie's point of view.
I mean...
Eddie makes you happy.
All I ever want is
for you to be happy, Iris.
Welcome home.
It is so fun to watch
grown men play with their toys.
You're so lucky.
Ray is so nice and smart
and hot.
Yeah, it's kind of like
I'm dating Barry
but in Oliver's body.
A sentence you will
never repeat to anyone.
Your secret's safe with me.
It must have re-activated.
And if it's being
controlled wirelessly...
I can trace its signal
and figure out
where it's trying to go.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, boy.
What?
The swarm is headed for
Mercury Labs.
Brie Larvan's going after Tina.
Hello, Dr. McGee.
You gonna open the window,
or should I buzz myself in?
How do we stop them?
She's got to be
remotely piloting
those bees from somewhere.
We need to stop this bug-eyed
glasses woman.
And her mini bandits.
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
Got her. She's in
an abandoned greenhouse.
Barry, you have to
take out Brie.
It's the only way to stop
these nanodrones.
What about Dr. McGee?
The defibrillator
in your suit is broken.
You cannot risk going near
Mercury Labs.
Bees can't penetrate my suit.
- I'll go.
- Whoa.
We haven't tested out
the new power system yet.
We'll do it now.
- I'm following you.
- I'm driving.
And I'm kissing you.
Dr. Wells...
Mr. Palmer will protect Tina.
Go.
You fired me,
destroyed years of my research.
You took everything from me.
What you were doing was wrong.
You wanted to harm people,
not help them.
I did what I had to do.
You mean ruin my life?
Sure.
Now I'm doing what I have to do.
Found her.
Felicity, can you jam
their frequency?
I already tried, but I might
be able to redirect them
onto a new target.
Ray, get ready for incoming.
We have the technology.
It's over, Brie.
I know you're trying to
kill Dr. McGee.
You think that she betrayed you.
I can imagine how that feels.
You think you understand
the sting of betrayal?
I'll show you what it means
to be stung.
Barry.
Barry, I hacked into
the bees' frequency.
I'm controlling them.
I'm the queen of this hive.
Oh, she's good.
She's like my nemesis.
I've never had a nemesis before.
I kind of like it.
Okay, Cisco.
Now what?
Ray, get to the ocean.
If the bots follow
you into the water,
their electronics will fry.
Got it.
Wait.
But so will my suit.
Cisco, I'm fried.
I'm losing propulsion control.
Can you see the van?
Yeah.
We'll catch you.
- You will?
- We will?
We will.
All right.
Keep it steady!
- Whoo!
- The Atom lives.
Oh.
Let's work on some softer gloves
for next time, okay?
Sorry.
Oh, you want to bring it?
It's been brought.
Rude.
Felicity, right now
would be a good time
to do something.
Stay away from Barry Allen.
- Felicity!
- Got it.
Boom.
Drop the mic.
It's metaphorical, of course,
because I don't have
a real mic.
Brie's restrained.
Call CCPD.
Ah.
Some kind of team you have here.
Helps to have friends
in your corner.
Are you okay?
Cisco!
Come on.
Please.
Wake up.
Cisco's been stung.
He's going into shock.
I'm on my way.
Come on, stay with me.
Hold on.
Back up.
I'm gonna try something.
Cisco.
Either my fear of bees is over
or it just got a lot worse.
Thank God you're okay.
I've never had anybody
take a bee for me.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, bro.
Cisco, you're a hero, man.
- Dr. McGee.
- May I come in?
Yeah, of course.
What can I do for you?
I wanted to apologize.
I should have listened to you
when you warned me about Brie.
Perhaps next time I will take
the CCPD's offer of protection.
After we lost
your tachyon prototype,
I can understand why
you were hesitant to trust us.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
I couldn't help but notice
some tension
between you and Dr. Wells.
That's all in the past.
Do you mind if I ask
what happened between you two?
I ask myself that same question
all the time.
15 years ago, Harrison and I
were thick as thieves.
We were promising
young scientists
in Starling City.
He was such a kind man.
Then everything changed
after Tess died.
They were gonna get married?
I understand how grief
can affect someone,
but this was more than that.
It was like, after that day,
Harrison Wells became
a completely different person.
Good day.
Bye.
Doctor.
How's Cisco?
Happy to be alive.
And sad that Ray is leaving.
It was a really brave thing
he did, risking his life.
Selfless.
Yeah.
It definitely was.
And another end to
another exciting adventure
in Central City.
Ah, yes, thank you.
Ray, thank you
for all your help.
- Oh.
- And I hope you
figure out the problem
with your suit.
- I already have, actually.
- Oh.
All this time,
I've been looking at
the power source
the wrong way.
I kept thinking
we needed to go bigger.
But the solution, as always,
is simply to go smaller.
Oh.
Great.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna be.
Thank you for your advice.
I won't even charge you
the 5¢.
Bye, Felicity.
Bye, Barry.
Hey.
What's up?
I, um...
I spoke to Barry last night.
Oh, yeah?
He was trying to help me
understand
why you've been so off lately,
why you might be having trouble
connecting with me.
Really?
What did he say?
It was a good explanation.
Valid.
But the truth is,
it doesn't matter,
because when
you love someone,
you tell them everything.
So if you love me, Eddie,
you'll tell me what is going on
with you, or...
Or what?
You know what.
All right, all right,
who's ready for some...
♪ Karaoke ♪
We are not
going to karaoke, are we?
No.
This is everything we know
about my mother's murder
and The Reverse-Flash.
I've been gathering information
on him for a long time.
And this is everything we know
about Dr. Wells.
I don't understand.
What do Dr. Wells
and The Reverse-Flash
have to do with each other?
Um...
They're the same person.
That's impossible.
Look, Caitlin,
it took me a long time
to believe it too,
but it's him.
Dr. Wells is a speedster?
He's paralyzed.
Is he, though?
And why would he kill
Barry's mother?
It doesn't make any sense.
Cisco.
Say something.
I've been having these dreams.
Mostly at night,
but sometimes during the day.
But they don't really feel
like dreams.
They... they feel real.
What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is The Reverse-Flash.
And...
he kills me.
Greg, move your head.