My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs, I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Meet Joss Jackam.
She's a delinquent teen
turned amateur storm chaser.
That weathervane, Doesn't
it look a lot like...
The staff she was carrying, yeah.
It's infected with a satellite shard.
Our satellite didn't
just create new metas.
It created meta-tech.
Every time you vibe or breach,
the dark matter is going to affect
your central nervous system, causing you
more and more pain.
- We need to talk.
- Yes, Nora.
Yes, we do.
You've been gone a long time, Nora.
You're lucky I came back at all.
Really?
I can tell you have questions.
Ask them.
- You killed my grandmother?
- I did.
- In front of my father?
- He was a boy.
- Nora...
He was just a kid!
You're right,
and I think of that moment every day,
how it changed the course of destiny
for him,
for you,
for me.
I never knew he had that
kind of hatred inside of him,
but he does because of you.
And I have that same
hatred inside of me for him!
Or at least I did.
I was inspired by him, as you are.
I wanted to know him, as you do.
I wanted to be him. I
wanted to be the Flash.
You will never be the Flash.
Exactly!
And that realization is what broke me.
That's the realization that led me to do
the things that I did.
The terrible, horrible,
evil things I did.
I've been coming here for so long.
Why didn't you tell me what you did?
I thought you must know.
Your mother would've told you.
I was wrong. I see that.
I'm sorry, Nora.
I don't trust you anymore.
Have I not given you everything?
The chance to go back and
know a father you never knew?
To learn from him? To run with him?
To run with the Flash.
I showed you how to
time travel because...
I want to help you.
No, the only person that
you ever help is yourself.
Who told you that?
Your father?
For as long as I can remember,
all I ever thought about was myself,
and that will not be my legacy.
That will not the
legacy of Eobard Thawne!
Let me help you!
I don't want your help.
Not anymore.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So we've got some good
news and some bad news.
The good news is that CCPD
is still stationed outside
of Grace's room and will remain
so until Dwyer's been caught.
But the bad news is,
that means Dwyer won't
be visiting her again anytime soon.
And then the worse news is,
we have no idea where
Cicada could be hiding.
Can't we just track him by
the dark energy in his dagger?
Well, we can but only
when he uses it, which,
thank God, hasn't been recently.
And he's not showing up
on facial recognition?
Unless he decides to make an
appearance, we've got zilch.
Which reminds me, where
the rest of Team Flash is?
Where's baby giraffe and young Nora?
Ralph's visiting his mom. He
said to call if we need him.
- And Nora is...
- Right here.
I just stopped by the loft
to pick up your blue suit.
I figured you'd had enough of green.
Hey, I made that green
suit work, though.
What is, uh, that for again?
Mama Cecile's first day
back to the courtroom
and Dad's testimony
against Weather Witch.
Joss Jackam's trial is later today.
It starts in 30 minutes.
Well, since my dad is
with Jenna visiting Wally,
why don't I come with you
guys and help support Cecile?
Yeah. When are they
coming back, by the way?
- They've been gone forever.
- Uh, he's not sure.
After having a psychopath
break into his home,
I don't think he's in any rush
to bring a newborn back to Central City.
Besides, Cecile has a lot on her plate
with this being her
first day back at work.
I can't wait to see Weather Witch
get what she deserves.
Hey, you ready to get those
shards out of your hands?
Hell yes!
I haven't been able to
play PS4 properly for weeks.
See you in there.
Hey, you feel that?
Feel what?
That's the feeling of free time.
AKA unbillable hours,
so we better not be seeing
any invoices from you
in the near future.
Oh, that's all right.
This is one mystery
I will solve for free.
The state versus Joslyn Jackam,
Criminal Court of Central
City, meta-crime number 99512.
Welcome back to my
courtroom, Miss Horton.
I trust your maternity
leave was enjoyable?
Thank you, Your Honor.
I am very happy to be back at work.
Yeah, there never really is enough time
with a newborn, is there?
There is not. You may proceed.
Thank you, Your Honor.
The prosecution intends to prove
that between November 20th and 27th,
Joslyn Jackam used this device,
a so-called piece of meta-tech,
to unlawfully and intentionally
harm the citizens of Central City.
Her meta-crimes include
massive property damage at Iron Heights,
the grounding of 21 separate flights
at Sheldon County Airport,
and the attempted murder
of her own father, Mark Mardon.
Now, this attack on her father was...
Uh...
Uh, the...
The attack on her
father was premeditated.
Um, and...
the prosecution is seeking the...
Are you okay?
Uh...
yeah, it's just a...
feeling.
I'll be fine.
The prosecution is seeking the
maximum sentence, Your Honor.
Gotcha.
All right, almost done.
Micro-scale surgery is not the easiest.
Is that why you missed
these the first time?
Hey, now!
All right, there you go.
Your hands are officially
dagger shard free.
Hallelu.
One more thing.
Mm, meta-sutures for meta-wounds,
that's clever.
Ah! Note to self, ice
healing actually hurts.
Don't be a wuss.
Wuss. You're the wuss.
Looks like you've got this whole
Caitlyn/Killer Frost thing down pat.
- Eh, not totally.
- I got it.
But it is getting easier
to switch to Killer Frost
when I need to.
So those sutures should stay
frozen while the wound heals.
Once they melt, you can
take the bandages off.
You'll be good to go.
I have to confess.
I've actually really enjoyed
not having my powers lately.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I got used to being Cisco
again sans Vibe-age, you know?
And not having villains
breathing down my neck
once a week, I have to
say, is pretty schway.
Well, if we're gonna defeat Cicada,
we need a fully functioning Vibe.
So hopefully this does the trick.
Here, souvenirs.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Opening statements are underway
in the trial of Joss Jackam,
otherwise known as Weather Witch.
Just saying, nothing wrong
with three or four martinis at lunch.
It is when you get in
your Lamborghini and drive.
Sir, sir, focus here.
Touch your nose.
Hey! That's my car!
And then what happened, Miss Pellett?
She created some kind
of lightning tornado.
I wasn't sure if any of
us were gonna make it.
I got to go.
One moment, please.
I got to go. There's been a car theft.
What are you talking about?
You're my lead CSI witness.
You're on the stand in 30 minutes.
I'm sorry. It's a
Lamborghini, all right?
The cops aren't gonna be able
to keep up with this thing.
- It'll be quick.
- 30 minutes.
- All right.
- Miss Horton?
Hmm, where were we?
Guys, the car just turned north on 8th,
- headed towards Wakefield.
- Got it.
Get ready to take control of the wheel.
- What are you gonna do?
- Get the driver.
Here we go.
Dad!
- What's happening?
- I can't stop vibrating.
- Guys! We need your help!
- Guys!
- With what?
- With...
With that?
I can't stop phasing.
And I can't counter-phase him forever.
Okay, that's not good.
If you keep going but you don't,
then you could...
fall to your death.
- Yeah!
- What are we gonna do?
- Let him.
- Uh...
What?
Yes, if you phase through the floor,
you're actually gonna
fall into pipeline cell
directly below us.
And the dampening unit
will negate your powers.
Unless we don't time it right.
In which case, your torso
would be severed from your legs
as you enter the cell.
- Not helping.
- Stop, stop.
Okay, stop. I tr... I trust you Cisco.
Move to the right.
No, my right.
Cisco! Come on!
Okay, stop right there!
- One step back.
- Cisco!
Actually, never mind, one step forward.
Okay, ready? Three, two, one, go!
What's going on with me?
So...
the car you touched
was saturated with unstable dark matter.
And because you were
phasing at the time,
it caused your body to destabilize
on a cellular level.
When I got close to the driver,
I saw dark matter veins flare up,
just like on the back of
Spencer Young's phone.
So the car is a piece of meta-tech?
That or whatever was controlling it.
How long is he gonna
have to stay in there for?
Without the help of the power dampeners,
it could take up to a day?
No, no, no, no! I-I have to
present evidence on the stand
in, like, ten minutes.
Cecile's gonna kill me.
- That's not good.
- Um...
I could do it.
You can't be serious.
Well, when Dad made me official,
he submitted my paperwork to the court,
so I'm qualified to
present forensic evidence.
I can do this.
I cannot believe this is
happening on my first day back.
It's my first day back. Okay.
Go to the court reporter. Check in.
Tell her that Barry was
in a traffic accident.
Yes.
And, Nora, when you're
up there on the stand,
you just follow my lead.
- Got it?
- Mm-hmm.
Don't worry. Nora can handle this.
It's not that.
I've decided I'm gonna
pursue a lighter sentence.
Why the change of heart?
Because I keep feeling these
waves of remorse coming off of Joss.
I think she just wants to start over
so she doesn't turn out like her father.
So, Miss West, can
you explain what effect
these conditions had on
the Sheldon County Airport?
The facility was hit by winds
ranging from 150 to 250 miles per hour.
Wow, that's... That is pretty dangerous.
And yet not a single person was injured.
Well, no, but that was because...
What about these lightning
marks on the tarmac?
Would you say that that is common,
given the nature of the weather
during the incident in question?
Yes, but luckily, in this case,
the lightning only hit the runway
and not the surrounding structures.
The structures where all
of the passengers were.
I would say that is pretty lucky indeed.
Your Honor, the prosecution rests.
So that's it? You're not
gonna ask me anything else?
Well, it would appear so.
Mr. Lee, I think you're up.
Miss West, is my client a meta-human?
No, but she used meta-tech.
Specifically a weather staff
that was corrupted by dark matter.
So one could say it was
the staff, not my client,
that attacked the Sheldon
County Airport that night?
No, one couldn't. She used that staff.
But isn't this just an
ordinary weather staff
corrupted by dark matter?
These are your words.
- Yes, but...
- And since dark matter
was able to corrupt a tool
and turn it into a
weapon of destruction,
isn't it also possible it
could corrupt the defendant?
No. Dark matter doesn't
make you do things.
She pointed lightning at a
hangar full of scared families.
Your Honor, there were
little kids in that hangar.
Did you know that... that
lightning is five times hotter
than the surface of the sun?
That is the kind of power
that the defendant unleashed
upon those people.
She did this.
This was her choice,
and she can't be trusted.
No, Miss West, you must sit down.
I know, but, Your Honor...
- Sit down!
- No! She's right.
I'm guilty,
and I should pay for what I did.
- What you doing?
- Get a load of this.
You know those shards you removed?
I ran a biochemical analysis on them
and the tissue from my hands.
You know how to do that?
I picked up a thing or
two from Caitlin Snow MD
over the years, and I found this.
That's my tissue right
after I got sliced.
Mm-hmm.
That's from today.
Almost all the dark matter is gone.
The shards weren't dampening my powers.
They were removing them.
So the dagger has
anti-dark matter properties.
Yes!
Cisco, if we can synthesize
that into a serum,
we could get rid of
Cicada's powers entirely.
And not just his powers, everyone's.
- Everyone's?
- Caitlyn,
we could make a meta-human cure.
You think we need a meta-human cure?
Don't you?
Um...
Okay, maybe not.
But I seem to remember
a time when you did?
Sure, when I first
discovered Killer Frost,
I wanted to get rid of her.
But when she was gone, it felt
like a piece of me was missing.
Besides, we have seen meta-human powers
do really good things.
Okay, yeah! If you
can build an ice bridge
to avoid rush hour traffic,
but what if my existence
gives everyone around me
radiation poisoning like "Fallout"?
Those metas, we created
them against their will.
No, Thawne created the
particle accelerator
and he sabotaged it.
And who shattered the
satellite full of dark matter
and created God knows how many metas?
We did that.
This cure could give
meta-humans a second chance
at having a normal life.
Maybe not everyone wants
a normal life, Cisco.
Watch out!
Who does this lady think she is?
What the hell?
Who are you?
Your ride. Let's go.
So Joss Jackam never
made it to Iron Heights.
Nope, and the transport driver said
that the woman who
took her used something
that completely shut down his truck.
Pause.
That. Look familiar?
Ugh, another piece of satellite shard.
So the fob is the meta-tech?
Yeah, probably sends out
some kind of dark matter pulse
that overrides any
guidance system in seconds.
So as long as she has an engine,
she can control it and we still
don't even know who we're looking for.
Maybe we do. Hey, can you fast-forward?
Stop.
Yeah, look, that salute.
She's definitely military.
Okay, let's run that face
through the DOD database.
Raya Van Zandt.
Former air force, ace pilot, mechanic,
and expert in vehicle operations.
She was dishonorably discharged.
Call sign was Silver Ghost. Huh?
The rest of her military
record was sealed.
Okay, well, I'm gonna see
if my dad can call in a favor
and maybe we can get a copy.
Yeah, and in the meantime,
it looks like we have two
bad girls to track down.
I'm not so sure, Nora.
I mean, Cecile said that
she could feel Joss' remorse.
Come on, Mom. That was a show.
I mean, do you think this
escape was a coincidence?
Uh, well, we don't know yet, Nora.
Yes, we do.
Raya got that fob to break Joss
out of the prison transport.
I guarantee you Joss is a part of this.
How do you know that?
Because bad people don't change.
Hey, guys, any way
you could send down some food?
Welcome to home base.
Home base of what?
The Young Rogues.
There's been enough old
men running this town.
Our turn.
I have my eyes on a few candidates,
but for this job, plan on
it just being you and me.
Um, I'm not planning anything!
I don't even know who you
are! Just take me back!
You ever heard of A.R.G.U.S.?
It's an off-the-grid facility
primed with bleeding-edge tech,
and it's protected by one
of the most advanced
security systems on Earth.
The only thing that can short it out is
a billion jolts of electricity.
So a few bolts of lightning.
You're the Weather Witch, right?
Beneath this wall is the
facility's power junction.
You hit that and we
have a four-minute window
to get something that
will make us unstoppable.
No, look, even if I was gonna help you,
and I'm not,
I need my weather staff
to control any of that,
and right now, that is in police holdup.
So if you could just take me back.
Okay.
To do what?
Turn myself in.
I see.
You don't want to be like your dad.
I get that, but it's too late.
You're a criminal. So am I.
And those people out there,
trust me, all they think is,
"Like father, like daughter."
But I guess you need to
find that out for yourself,
don't you?
Find me when you do.
Thank you.
- Well... right.
- Yeah.
That will hold you
until you get out... oh!
Uh, can I ask you a question?
Uh, do you have a minute?
Yeah.
Yes, you're not going anywhere.
So, um, last year, you
came out of the Speed Force
and you were writing a
kind of a symbol language.
Do you remember that?
- Yeah, I remember.
- And apparently,
Cisco could only translate
one of these phrases. Right?
So far, yeah. I mean,
Gideon couldn't even do it.
Gideon.
Right, Gideon.
So what do you think that language was?
I don't know. It was some
kind of, uh, chronolinguistics.
Chronolinguistics that
you got from your time
in the Speed Force, which
is all time at once, right?
Past, present, future.
What do you think this
language was? Future, maybe?
Why? Is this about Cicada?
Cicada? No, no. No, It's just, um...
le mystère, huh?
I'm a detective. I see
mystery everywhere, so...
- Uh-huh.
- Uh, all right. Thank you.
See you next time.
Okay... oh! Ah, before I forget,
the Legends, uh, dropped
off some, um, books
to help you pass the time.
- Huh.
- "Uncaged Desire."
Your kind of caged desire.
- Hope you enjoy it.
- Huh.
- See you next time.
- Thanks.
Yeah, probably not very good.
See you!
What is it?
According to Doppler, it's
a hurricane in Central City.
No, it's not a hurricane. It's Joss.
I'm on it.
What, no Flash today?
Figured he wasn't needed
to stop a fake hurricane.
Guess we can add
damaging private property
to your résumé.
Look, I just need your help.
Oh, stop with the sorry act.
That ended when your
friend helped you escape.
She is not my buddy,
and I did not escape.
Look,
I want to turn myself back in.
Oh, you really expect
me to believe that?
My dad is the career criminal,
not me.
I just...
I want to show everybody
that I'm not the person
that they think I am.
Then what do you need me for?
You're a hero.
If you vouch for me,
people will know that
I'm telling the truth.
Look, I will tell you everything.
I'll even show you
where that woman took me.
Just give me a chance.
If anyone asks, you never saw this.
Thank you, Major Morgan.
Please tell the lieutenant general
that my dad and I owe him one.
Special delivery. One Weather Witch.
What? I thought you were gonna help me.
I'm trying to turn myself in.
No, I-I didn't escape.
I-I was kidnapped.
Will you please tell them?
Sorry, I don't trust criminals.
She's all yours.
No! No, no! This is a misunderstanding!
This is unfair!
If I could just talk to her, please!
Your father does the exact same thing.
When something's on his mind, he runs.
Nothing's on my mind, Mom.
I got to take a look at
Raya Van Zandt's DOD file.
Oh, yeah, did you find the connection
between her and Joss?
Well, there doesn't seem to be one.
Really?
Yeah, she left the air force
after a failed mission overseas,
and then she spent two
months on desk duty,
and then she was
dishonorably discharged.
But it seems like she has a
pretty good service record.
Exactly, so clearly the
DOD had egg on its face
and Raya became its scapegoat.
I'm just saying, Nora,
not everyone is as bad as they seem.
Raya, Joss. I think everyone
deserves a second chance.
If you don't believe
me, ask your father.
He gives more second chances
than anyone I've ever met.
Come on. Come on.
Yes. Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
What the hell are you doing?
Well, I was distilling dark matter ore
from Cicada's dagger shards.
But I can't really do
that anymore, can I?
Whoops.
Why did you do that?
You're smart. You can figure it out.
When are you gonna figure out that
a meta-cure could actually help people?
Listen, I heard all
about it, short stuff.
But you know what? Caity and I,
we're doing just fine,
and so were you until Cicada
got all up in your head.
Don't do that. This isn't just about me.
Oh, the hell it isn't!
And... and you know what? I get it.
He tried to kill you.
You're trying to create
something that'll save us all.
Yeah, I am!
All of us!
Barry, Iris, Nora, they have a family.
Even you and Caitlyn have
your weird little family.
But what about my family?
I want a wife to grow old with.
I want a kid.
And I don't want them
to wonder all the time
if their dad is in trouble,
if he's even gonna make it home tonight.
Cisco, you don't have to
choose between having powers
and having a family.
Yeah? Well, some of us do.
I'm not the Flash.
I don't want to be the Flash.
I want to be me.
A cure is the only way.
Or it was.
What?
Oh, come on, girl.
You're reading Mick's book?
This is...
surprisingly well-written.
What's going on?
Just having a hard time believing
some people can change.
How come?
'Cause after everything
that you've seen,
don't you think that
bad people stay bad?
Not always.
When I first met Leonard
Snart, he was a criminal.
Probably the worst criminal in the city.
But I...
You know, I knew
that there was a good
person in there somewhere,
and look at him.
Turned out to be a Legend.
Died a hero.
If he can change, anyone can.
You really believe that?
Yeah. I do.
What about Eobard Thawne?
I think...
part of being a hero
is being able to see the good in people.
So yeah, maybe someday in the future...
even Thawne could change.
Besides, if we don't believe in people,
who will?
Very funny!
I got 595s!
We got a lot of vehicles! Let's go.
Copy that. Suit up!
We've got multiple 595s
in our own parking lot!
Get out there quick!
Requesting more backup! We've got a lot!
What are you doing here?
Doing what no one else
is gonna do for you...
Offer you a second chance...
Weather Witch.
That's it.
That's where the power junction is.
Give it everything you got.
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know, sir.
But it knocked out security
grids 41 through 60.
Ten years and $24 million later,
the stealth automobile,
AKA the SAM, was born.
Rumor has it that
everything under its hood
comes directly from WayneTech.
This is a $24-million prototype?
What can it do?
Let's find out.
Is it Joss or Raya?
I'm guessing both
because someone just stole
a very expensive vehicle from A.R.G.U.S.
after a very precise lightning strike.
It's a next-gen prototype
with all the bells and whistles.
If bells and whistles could
explode and murder people.
And supposedly it's untrackable.
So how do we find it?
- We don't search for the car.
- We search for them.
If Joss made lightning strike again,
it means she has her staff.
Oh, so we can track the
dark matter in it. Nice!
I got the location.
Okay, remember, Nora,
whatever you do,
don't touch the car
while using your powers.
Hey, Caitlin, can I
steal you for a second?
Joyride's over, Silver Ghost.
Joss, I need to talk to you.
Hard pass.
Got to love remote detonation.
Icy roads ahead.
Oh, my God. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, Raya!
Raya!
Holy Buckaroo Banzai.
It phases?
Whatever phase-trick they just used,
it jammed our tracking.
We can't get a lock on them
if she doesn't use that weather staff.
XS is gonna come after us.
Let her try.
Hear no evil, see no evil.
We're invisible.
Hey, Cisco?
Can you connect me to
the car's comm system?
No, but best I can do is
have you send out radio waves,
and if the car's nearby,
it'll pick them up.
Do it.
Joss? Joss, it's XS. I
hope you can hear me.
You tried to tell me something earlier.
You tried to tell me
that you wanted to pay
for the crimes that you committed.
You said you weren't a
criminal like your father.
You asked me to give
you a second chance,
but I didn't listen.
Now I'm asking you for a second chance.
Joss, this isn't who you are.
Nora, the car's headed straight for you.
I don't see anything.
Nora, look out!
How the hell did I lose control?
Hey, hold on to me.
This is gonna feel weird.
Well, at least we got their wheels.
What's left of them.
Thanks for the last-minute rescue.
- For the what?
- Icing up the road.
I didn't ice the road.
What? Who...
And...
time! 24 hours are up.
Okay, I double-checked with Caitlin,
and there doesn't seem to
be any unstable dark matter
in your biometric scans.
Okay.
Man, it feels good to be out of there.
We definitely missed you, Dad.
Sorry I haven't been able
to help with everything.
Do we know where Joss and Raya are now?
No, we got nothing yet.
But you were right about Joss.
She saved my life.
If she hadn't iced over the road...
But she did because
you connected with her.
It's like Dad said,
she just needed someone
to believe in her.
Sounds like you found
your own Leonard Snart.
Well, time might prove
me wrong, but I think so.
I hope so.
I'm sorry I messed up
your first day back.
It's all right, Nora.
There's always day two.
- I'm happy you're back.
- Thanks.
Hey do you wanna help me find Cisco?
I gotta get this extrapolator
thing recalibrated.
I went to go see Joe in
Tibet, and I ended up in Fiji.
Being a parent sure is hard sometimes.
Yeah, it is.
But there's nothing like it.
Okay, well, we can't
both be the basket case.
"We're all pretty bizarre.
Some of us are just
better at hiding it."
Come on, "Breakfast Club"?
It's one of the only movies
Killer Frost and I actually agree on.
Let me guess, she's into Bender?
- Totally. She loves him.
- Yeah, makes sense.
- I'd ship that.
- Put that on.
It's cold where we're going.
Your dad's old lab.
- Mm-hmm.
- Cool.
Caitlin, why did you bring me here?
Because despite our
last encounter with him,
he did create a meta-gene.
So I was thinking that
you could use his research
to do the reverse.
Um, okay,
don't look now, but if
I didn't know any better,
I'd say this feels a
lot like you helping me
make a meta-human cure.
I couldn't stop thinking about
what you said about how a cure
would give you a second
chance at a normal life.
No friend would stand
in the way of that.
But there is a difference
between you standing in my way
and you actively helping me.
I still think this is dangerous, but...
maybe if I'm involved, we
can have some ground rules.
Like the first and most important,
we will never, ever
force a cure on anyone.
Okay.
Rule number one.
We're not just here to make a cure.
We're here to make a choice.
Nora.
You either trust me, or you don't.
There's no in-between.
Fine.
I don't trust you.
But I'm willing to give you
the chance to change my mind.
Well, that might take some time.
And time, as you may recall,
is not on my side.
Minutes are minutes,
seconds are seconds,
and there's very few of them left.
I want to believe that
there is good inside of
you somewhere, Thawne.
Let me prove there is.
Okay.
What's next?
Hello, Dr. Wells.
Hello, Gideon.
I have access to all the files?
- Right?
- Of course.
Which files would you like me to locate?
I would like you to locate the files
from Nora West-Allen.
I'm sorry, Dr. Wells,
but all entries have
been permanently deleted
by Nora West-Allen.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --