My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
The court
orders that Mr. Allen
should be remanded
to Iron Heights Penitentiary.
- Get comfortable.
- I didn't kill anybody.
Yeah, sure. Everyone's innocent here.
Especially that guy. Big Sir.
Twelve markers, twelve metas.
Now that we know how many there are,
we can go right to them.
- I don't want any trouble.
- Too late.
Thanks. I was just wondering
why you helped me.
Because your dad helped me.
He operated and saved my life.
Cecile, are you sure
we even need a crib?
I used to plop Iris on some cushions
and call it a night.
Well, I'm glad to hear
you got all your parenting mistakes
out of the way with your first kid.
I think she turned out pretty good.
Oh, babe. I cannot believe
I'm so big already.
You know, I was barely
showing at this point with Joanie.
All right, best I got.
What do you think?
Mmm-hmm.
- Are they?
- Are they what?
- Too tight?
- Um...
Hey, you just said that
you thought my clothes are too tight.
Do I look bad?
What? I didn't say that.
What do you mean,
"When is it gonna go back to normal?"
I didn't say that either.
Look at me.
- My lips aren't moving.
- What are you talking about?
I heard you. I...
- I can still hear you.
- What the hell is going on?
Why can I hear what you're thinking?
Oh, my God. Joe.
I think I can read minds.
Heart rate's 170 bpm,
and there's no sign of
dark matter in the amniotic fluid.
So the baby's not a meta?
Nope, it's a perfectly normal baby...
"Girl." You were gonna say
"baby girl."
- I'm having another daughter?
- I'm gonna have a sister.
Well, I guess we can
cancel the announcement party.
Boy, girl, that's 50/50.
Let's test your skills for real.
What number am I thinking of?
Three. Eleven. Twenty-five.
Three again. Bulbasaur.
What the hell is a Bulbasaur?
So weird.
Why would I be thinking about
Pokémon at a time like this?
- Yep. Definitely a telepath.
- But how?
If the baby is not a meta, then
where did these powers come from?
Nope, I wasn't on the bus.
No, I was not abducted by aliens.
No, I didn't inherit
a mystic totem from my grandma.
Really, guys? Why are you
still thinking about Bulbasaur?
- 'Cause he's the cutest one of all.
- Okay.
My best hypothesis is
this is actually triggered by
your latest phase of pregnancy
and it's actually latent dark matter
that's been in your brain since
maybe the first
particle accelerator explosion.
Think of it like
gestational diabetes.
But it's not.
You can fix that with insulin.
Right, but it's temporary.
I mean, the symptoms
should recede after childbirth.
Hmm.
Okay, we'll give you guys a minute.
Joe, you're literally thinking,
"I'm worried about Cecile."
I just want you
and the baby to be okay.
I know.
But, hey, maybe this will
turn out to be a good thing.
I've always wondered
what goes on in that head of yours.
Cecile's a telepath.
Well, that's way more important
than getting Allen out of prison.
- Not!
- Sick burn, Har.
Please don't encourage him.
Yeah, as a former prisoner,
- I can tell you...
- No, that was gorilla prison.
Gorilla prison is worse.
They throw their scat at you.
I can tell you that Allen is sitting
in his cell suffering while...
this guy, DeVoe,
continues his plan unabated.
Harry, Cecile
filed an appeal last week.
We have no new evidence,
so that doesn't matter.
We have satellites on the DeVoes.
And they haven't made a move
in weeks, so that doesn't matter.
Well, Barry is in gen pop,
so worst case, he can always
phase out or I can breach him out.
Then he'd be a fugitive.
And by the way, Ramon, why do we not
have eyes on him in there?
Hey, it's a pain trying to get
into an analog camera from here,
- no matter how hard I hack.
- Hack harder.
We're nowhere.
This team is nowhere
and this is the team
that got Barry out of
a pan-temporal speed prison
and we can't
spring him from a county jail?
Harry, we are working
just as hard as you. Okay?
And, yes, it kills me to admit it,
but we are at a roadblock.
So Barry is just gonna have to...
Hold on.
I mean, I can't even imagine
what he's going through.
Read 'em and weep, boys.
That's it.
I'm dealing next round.
You know, there's
something fishy about you, Allen.
I'm fishy?
You tried to murder me and Joe.
Well, if you can't play cards with
somebody who tried to murder you,
you'll never play cards in here.
Knew I'd regret
inviting you to this game.
You may be big,
but you got no poker face.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- Deuces again.
- Okay, I'm out.
- Hey, you can't take that.
- It's my last pudding.
Then you shouldn't have
thrown it in the pot, dumbass.
Dumbass?
A politician who gets caught
with his pants down.
Yeah, I'd say you're a dumbass.
Well, maybe
I'll just take the whole pot then.
- Guys, come on.
- Don't screw with me, Bellows.
Or what? You gonna shoot me?
That's right.
You only shoot unarmed men.
What the hell are you looking at?
Is that really why you're in here?
You shot an unarmed man?
Yeah, I'm just another bad guy.
Now get the hell out.
If my dad really risked his life
to save yours, then...
I doubt you're just another bad guy.
Hey, why don't you just tell me
what really happened?
"A suspect was arrested last night
after a botched robbery.
"While attempting to steal
from a Mercury Labs shipping crate,
"David P. Ratchet, alias Big Sir,
"allegedly shot
and killed a security guard.
"An eyewitness
called in the shooting."
"Ratchet was
previously arrested for fighting."
The only forensic evidence
were bullet casings from the scene
that matched the cartridge of a gun
you owned.
Okay, time to go.
Hey, firearm identification like that
can have errors.
It's practically junk science.
I said, time to go.
You didn't kill that guy, did you?
There was another guy.
He was my size, my frame.
I heard the shots,
I tried to save the guard.
Wrong place, wrong time.
- Why didn't you just tell me that?
- 'Cause it doesn't matter, Allen.
It didn't matter to the cops.
Not to my lawyer or the jury.
They took one look at me
and decided I was the guy.
That guy could still be out there.
If I was that guy,
I would have ditched this crap town
a long time ago.
Central City loves her heroes.
And I should know,
I'm your new mayor.
But we all agree,
doing business in a city
with meta-humans
can be a little risky.
Technology companies in Central City
are robbed at nearly 30 times
the national average.
That's second
only to Star City, folks.
Which is why I'm proud to unveil
Kord Industries' newest
advanced research facility.
Designed to be the most
secure building of its kind.
Complete with
super-speed motion detectors,
sonic vibration defenses
and laser beams that don't freeze.
Believe me, no one is breaking into
this building anytime soon.
I hate this city.
Cecile. Hey, babe,
what are you doing here?
I needed a helper
- and, well, she wanted to help.
- Yeah.
Cisco said you were working a case
about an R&D lab that vanished.
I figured maybe I could help
dig up some clues,
now that I'm a meta.
Babe, you're not a meta.
I can hear every one of these people.
Dark matter
definitely left its mark here.
I figured as much.
That patrolman, right there.
He is cheating on his wife.
Ah...
Never trust a mustache, I always say.
I have a mustache.
No, you have a sexy goatee.
He has a creeper mustache.
Red tie.
Oh, baby, red tie does not like his boss
very much.
She's been doing this
all the way over here.
- Mmm.
- And that lady right there. Joe...
Joe, she is a thief.
Thief!
Staplers.
She's been stealing them
out of her office for months now.
She damn near
cleaned out the supply closet.
Baby, I love you
and I think it's great that
you have these new powers, but I...
Oh. You want me to go.
I don't want you to go.
No, no, no. It's just 'cause
you wanna do your job.
I totally get it. Go. Stop crime.
- Love you.
I can hear everyone. It's so fun.
Hey.
The closest security cam I can find
is from an ATM across the street.
The footage is choppy, but...
Look at that.
- Did he just...
- Pull a Chevelle out of nowhere.
I'm gonna run those plates.
See if I can get an ID on the dude.
Copy that.
Yes, I'll accept the charges.
Hey, Barry.
So Barry asked you to ask us
to get this guy out of prison?
Barry has gotten close to this guy
who says he's innocent.
It was a case of mistaken identity.
Well, from what I could
find out on CCPN's archives,
Big Sir's case
does sound a bit suspect.
Fifteen years ago, he was
found guilty of shooting a guard,
but there was no apparent motive.
- Only one eyewitness?
- Mmm.
Studies have shown that
line-up composition,
verbal and non-verbal cues
can all lead to
unintended false identifications.
Look, this is all just fantastic,
but we're not really gonna do this.
Yeah, I mean,
we've already got a lot on our plate
just trying to free one innocent man.
We all want Barry to be free,
but I don't know that there's
much else we can do right now.
We kinda hit a wall.
We're not gonna get through that wall
while we are working on this.
It's just one case.
Yeah, and it's a case
that we have to take.
Allen has made one request of us
since he's been incarcerated.
A request
that doesn't even involve himself.
We have to take this case.
It's unsettling
how convincing you can be sometimes.
I got a plate match on the Chevelle.
It's registered to a perp who has
multiple
breaking and entering priors.
"Sylbert Rundine."
Why does every villain in this city
have a name that sounds like
it came out of a comic book?
He must go by something for short.
Syl. Sylbie.
- Bertie.
- What do we wanna do about this case?
Well, my dad, Cisco and Ralph
are gonna question Rundine
and I'm gonna call Cecile and see
if she can pull up
the case file on Big Sir.
You won't even have to say it.
"Bertie"? Are you for real with that?
Yeah.
I bet you five bucks it's Bertie.
You're on.
Hey.
Allen, you're stirring up my dust.
Oh, sorry.
Um, I've got some news.
So I have some friends that I thought
could help with your case
- and they've agreed to do it.
- CCPD cop friends?
Not exactly.
But, um, if there's anybody
that can prove you innocent,
it's these guys.
'Cause they did
a bang-up job of clearing you.
That's not really...
- I mean, my case...
- Look,
just call them and tell them to stop.
I don't understand
why you're not excited about this.
What you're peddling, it's dangerous.
- What's dangerous?
- Hope.
I've been in here long enough
to understand that in prison,
hope is the most dangerous thing.
Wait. Did you get that
from Shawshank?
No, I got that from being in prison.
Tell your friends
to stop wasting their time.
Sylbert Rundine?
It's the CCPD.
- You Sylbert Rundine?
- Bert.
"Rundine." The "E" is silent.
So close.
I'm Detective Joe West.
These are my associates.
We're looking into a robbery
that took place.
Wanted to ask you some questions.
Okay.
- Do you own a 1970 Chevelle?
- Well, I used to.
Oh, my glob.
Is that a replica of DARPA's HTV-3X?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't you know not to
mess with another man's toys?
You mean "figurines."
Yes.
Yes, he does.
Wow.
This is a perfect replica.
It even has a tiny automatic
navigation control system.
This is the reason
I don't have any money in my savings.
- Oh, I get it.
- Is this you?
Yeah, hard to believe.
Fifteen years ago,
I was a bit of a gym rat.
Hey, Joe.
It's a pretty nice figurine.
Well, gentlemen,
I was just about to head out.
So, if you guys are good here...
Fifteen years ago, did you spend
any time around Mercury Labs?
Cisco, get us to the alley.
Damn.
He wasn't that quick, was he?
You guys check down there.
I'll check the streets.
Okay.
Guys, he's here!
Hey, hold it right there.
Oh, that feels weird.
Joe, he's getting away!
I think we got bigger problems.
- This is...
- Ridiculous.
You okay, guys?
Are we doing okay? Are we doing okay?
Does it look like we're doing okay?
We're two inches tall, Caitlin!
Yeah, I'm like Cisco-size now.
Is this always how you see the world?
Oh, that's really funny, man.
I guess your body
just finally shrunk down
to a size that's proportional
to your brain!
Ralph, have you tried just
stretching back to normal size?
Uh...
Oh, my back! Geez Louise.
Okay, you know what?
Maybe I can breach us out of here.
Really thought
I was gonna go further than that.
How many fingers am I holding up?
What fingers?
You're no less annoying at that size.
Hey, guys. I think I got something.
So, I wasn't able to pin
Ray Palmer or the Waverider,
but I was able to reach Felicity.
So, Ray uses dwarf star alloy
to power the shrinking capabilities
in the A.T.O.M. suit.
But on October 10th,
Palmer Tech's
last depository of alloy
was stolen from
Central City's facility.
October 10th, that's the day
Barry came out of the Speed Force.
So he hits the facility,
then he hops on the bus.
So, a dwarf star alloy
plus dark matter
equals Rundine's shrinking powers?
Not exactly.
Nature doesn't work to scale.
If the human body were to shrink,
we can't lift our skeleton.
So Rundine's power
must be able to shrink
the space between atomic bonds.
Miniaturize tech, so you can steal it
and then make it big
so you can sell it.
- Hey.
Ratchet's trial records.
Oh.
You really think the guy
who shrunk that building
is the same guy
we need to free Barry's friend?
Well... I mean, look.
Be easy to mistake them, right?
I mean, they certainly
had a resemblance.
Rundine hit up the warehouse a month
after they picked up Big Sir.
Still, that's a big coincidence.
I keep saying it. There is no
coincidences when it comes to DeVoe
and that includes Barry's cellmate.
Well, I can't sell that to a judge.
So, if we wanna get Big Sir out,
we're gonna need
a confession from Dr. Shrinker.
Dwarfstar!
What the hell is that?
Well, that's what I'm naming him.
See, "Dwarfstar."
- Oh, God.
- Yeah.
Oh, it takes a lot of time
to breach here.
Who spit gum on the floor?
I'm a gumshoe!
Not gum on a shoe!
Oh, my God. Get him off, get him off!
Ugh.
You guys are
going in the hamster cage.
Ugh. Hamster cage?
Don't drop me! Don't drop me!
Harry, this is not your fault.
Yeah, well, it kinda...
Don't read my mind, okay?
What am I thinking now?
- Oh, God.
- Great.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go build a
reverse polarity dwarf star matrix.
Great name, Ray Palmer.
Was "electron-degenerate
sub-atomizer" taken?
Electron...
Oh, you have no idea
what Harry was talking about.
Or what anyone
around here is ever talking about.
- I gotta call Barry.
- Okay.
I can hear you, Iris, and there is
nothing wrong with me and Joe.
Right. Yes. Totally.
It's just that if you ever,
you know, think
there is something wrong,
I know someone who could help.
That's all.
I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
Thank you for
seeing us on short notice.
- Lucky us.
- Of course.
The reason that we're here today is
I've been experiencing some
unusual pregnancy symptoms.
You know,
the first time I was pregnant,
it was a really long time ago,
and things were very different
at that point.
Eggs, bread, olive oil.
I'm sorry, are you...
Are you making a grocery list?
Of course not. I would not...
So, tell me more about
the symptoms you're experiencing.
It's almost as if I have become
aware of Joe's thoughts.
- Like I read his diary.
- My diary?
Your pregnancy
made you read Joe's diary?
What do you mean,
you're taking his side?
I don't take sides.
You just think that I'm in the wrong.
- I would never think...
- Maybe this was a bad idea.
No, no. No, babe,
we're not done here.
Therapy scares you
and you don't like this woman
- hearing all your business.
- Cecile... That's not true.
And now you just wanna go, you think
this whole thing is a waste of time.
Cecile, stop.
You're thinking about
a pink elephant over and over?
You're trying to block me out.
Can I just ask one question?
Really, a pink elephant?
Why are you hiding
your thoughts from me?
Because you're making me do it.
Cecile, when we got back together,
I promised you
that I would never keep any secrets
from you again.
Except now, it feels like I have to.
Hey, they found him.
His name is Sylbert Rundine,
he's been arrested
for a whole bunch of crimes
like yours.
And he used to look
just like you, too.
You're getting out of here.
Wow, you have a hard shoulder.
So yesterday
I tell you what happened,
and today you find the guy.
- That happened in a...
- "Flash"?
- Snap.
You cops and your blinders.
Probably got the wrong guy again.
Well, technically they haven't
gotten him yet.
You see? Something always goes wrong.
Why do you have to make this so hard?
It's okay to believe.
Yeah?
Why it is so easy for you to believe?
You know my dad was in here
for a crime he didn't commit, right?
Do you know what happened?
After 17 years,
the man that killed my mom confessed.
My dad got to go home.
Why shouldn't you get
to go home, too?
Seventeen years, huh?
You think they'll catch Rundine?
You really think it's gonna happen?
I promise. You're getting out.
So, in hindsight, I can see
how putting you guys in
a hamster cage could be humiliating.
- You think?
- Sorry for that.
For the record, this is awesome,
but why do you guys
have a giant LEGO set anyway?
It is a three-dimensional model
of the place
where I was predestined
to be brutally murdered
by a twisted future version of Barry.
That guy.
But what a difference a year makes.
What did you do to my bazooka?
Well, I turned your bazooka
into an embiggening bazooka,
with the help of the dwarf star alloy
we stole from Rundine's apartment
and improving upon
Ray Palmer's amateurish schematics.
Presto chango.
Embiggening bazooka.
Now, if you'll just hold on...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
We're gonna do this now?
Well, yeah. Rundine's in the wind.
These two are small,
we need to embiggen them,
- and we need to free an innocent man.
- Okay, first of all,
"embiggen" is not a word,
and second of all,
shouldn't we test this first?
Hey!
I'll be a test subject. Come on.
- Take me.
- Sure, why not.
That's the spirit. Here we go.
And...
- West. You should probably...
- Mmm?
Oh, God, yeah, sorry.
And three, two, one.
Nope. Still tiny.
Hey, are we supposed to be
doing that?
- Oh, no.
- Their cells are exploding.
Whatever that embiggening gun did
to Ralph and Cisco
seems to have destabilized them
on an atomic level.
- How long do they have?
- At this rate,
I would guess, complete
cellular explosion within 10 hours.
You know, man, prison pudding is
so much better than outside pudding.
Obviously.
Any news from your friends?
Um, no, not yet, but they're probably
just busy tracking Rundine.
A seasoned criminal like that
knows how to not be found, you know.
Yeah, I get it, man.
Hey, um...
Do you have any plans
for when you get out?
No, I really haven't thought about it
very much.
Oh, come on, you've gotta
have something that you've dreamed of.
Like opening a business or climbing
to the top of Mount Everest.
- Bungee-jumping.
- This ain't the movies, Allen.
This is real life, man.
Reality is, I ain't got nobody
or nothing
waiting for me on the outside.
Even if I do get out,
I'll probably end up
at the docks anyway.
Okay, look. I spent most of my life
in love with a girl
who was way out of my league.
Now she's my wife.
Sometimes things do end up
like in the movies.
Jiaju.
- Come again?
- Jiaju.
Tiny village in China.
Beautiful place.
Very secluded.
Monks all take a vow of silence.
Inmate Allen.
- A word?
- Yeah.
I see you've made a new friend.
Yeah, I guess I have.
I find that interesting.
Especially since I was just asked
to turn over inmate Ratchet's
case file to the DA
who represented you for your trial.
Coincidence?
Not everyone that's in here
deserves to be in here.
Have you ever heard
the name Aaron Miller?
No.
Miller was a prisoner here who took
to studying at the law library.
One day, Mr. Miller decided
to take on the appeal
of a fellow inmate's case.
When he was
invariably unsuccessful
that fellow inmate
stabbed Mr. Miller to death.
Your friend may look like a man,
but he is unquestionably a monster.
Everyone here is a monster.
And if you insist on continuing
to bait them,
I guarantee you,
you will get mauled.
- All right, coming in hot.
- Oh, hey, you don't have to do all that.
Listen, I did not inherit
my dad's skills in the kitchen,
but a decaf herbal tea,
that I can do.
So, if it's okay with you,
I just was wondering
if I could talk to you about Joe.
Um, yeah, of course it's okay.
Oh, no, honey, it's not about that.
We have zero problems
in that department, as you can tell.
Okay.
TMI. But okay.
I really thought
being able to read his mind
would make our relationship stronger,
not push us apart.
Well, how does my dad feel
about your new powers?
He thinks it's gonna take
a little getting used to.
Yeah, but how does he feel?
Look, we all know that my dad thinks
that he's this cool, grounded
man of mystery.
But we all know
that he's actually just...
A big softy.
But if you really want to get closer
to my dad,
you need to stop focusing
on what he's thinking
and find out what he's feeling.
Maybe we could use
a biochemical treatment
and target the pituitary glands,
flood them
with human growth hormones?
No, that would
just accelerate their...
It'll make things worse.
- Guys?
- What?
- Yeah.
- Guys?
- What?
Little Ralphy needs to use
the little boy's room.
Didn't you just go?
My bladder is literally the size
of a hummingbird's right now.
Come on, Caitlin.
Help a wee fellow take a wee-wee.
- Can you...
- Me?
I'm not touching it.
Fine. I'll take you there, but you
have to find your own way out.
- Thank you.
- Could've just gone in the bushes.
Gross.
The embiggening bazooka
made us unstable, didn't it?
Yeah. No! What? No!
Why would you say that?
I can see it all over your face.
- What?
- Your face is huge.
I'm watching your emotions on IMAX.
Yeah. Yeah.
This was supposed to be an easy W,
all right?
An easy victory. All we had to do
was capture Rundine.
Couldn't even do that for Allen.
- Okay, so you tried.
- Yeah, I failed. Because I'm stupid.
All right?
Too stupid to help Allen's friend,
too stupid to fix you,
or too stupid to stop DeVoe.
Ow! What was that for?
Believe me,
I'd punch you in the arm if I could.
Look, I know you're not used
to going up against
someone you can't outsmart
like DeVoe,
but you really are stupid
if you think you're too stupid.
You wanna help Barry?
You wanna free him?
Get out of your own way
and un-shrink us.
You weren't shrunk, all right?
That's not how his powers work.
His powers...
work by not just
removing the space between the atoms,
but also taking out
the gravity particles
and the dark energy so that
when he embiggens an object...
He's refilling it with
the same combination of energy
- he extracted.
- Yes.
- Harry, if you wanna fix us...
- We need to put you back
in Rundine's line of fire.
Central City's Weather
Services Agency
is always on the cutting edge
of radar technology.
Which is why I'm so excited
to show you the newest addition
to our stationary airship fleet.
Now, let's go take a closer look.
What do you mean we only have
20 minutes until we explode?
Actually, it's only 18 minutes
before your equilibrium
totally destabilizes.
You're gonna blow up
in under 20 minutes
unless we re-expose you
to Rundine's energy blast, okay?
Okay, so facial recognition
just picked him up
at Weather Services Airfield.
I think he's trying to skip town.
Okay, I'm gonna stay here
and try to figure out a cure.
Hey, sir, you need to leave.
The museum is closing for the day.
I know.
I just thought this would look great
on my shelf.
Red alert! Red alert!
Everyone, evacuate!
- Gotta go faster, gotta go faster.
- Do you wanna drive this thing?
Kinda do. Ramon! Remember, when
Rundine tries to shrink the van,
you've got to get in the path
of his blast. You understand?
Copy that!
We're heading into the hangar now.
- Uh, guys, I think he sees us.
- You're not getting big again.
I'll go left, you go right.
Harry, try and flank him.
We're gonna come around the other side.
Copy that.
Evasive maneuvers!
I know. I'm doin' it.
Oh, boy.
We've got to figure out
how to get him to fire at us.
Abort!
We're falling too fast.
Think light thoughts.
I'm thinking
how you nearly got us killed.
Think lighter.
Snow!
- Tell me you got something.
- The cure's not done yet.
Only one minute
until the boys go nuclear.
- I don't wanna explode.
- What do we do?
We go to Plan B.
I'm gonna shrink you down
to the subatomic level, boy.
Oh, is that right?
I'd like to see you try.
I'm big again. I'm big again!
Remind me to never again breach into
any of Harry's stank-ass pockets.
Hey. Sorry again about stepping on you.
Hey, you saved me a trip
to the chiropractor.
I guess so.
You did it.
Yeah, I guess I did.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
one will be provided for you.
Hands behind your back.
Rundine.
Fifteen years ago,
did you rob a Mercury Labs warehouse?
Give us a confession now,
I guarantee the DA
will cut you a deal.
Mercury Labs.
That's the one
that Ratchet got fingered for.
I laughed so hard
when that guy got arrested.
You want a confession?
Find a priest.
I'd rather rot.
Yeah, all right, thanks.
Hey, Joe, just hold on a second,
all right?
Ain't good news, is it?
Rundine won't confess.
My friends tried everything.
I mean, the DA offered
every deal she could, but...
I'm so sorry, man...
Look, you were right about everything
in here.
You know, I made you a promise and...
I let you down.
You damn idiot.
You did not let me down.
I forgot what hope felt like.
It's not a bad thing.
I'll see you around, kid.
Hey. Sorry.
It's okay, Barr.
I just wanted to say thanks
for trying, you know.
And I'm sorry
to send you on this goose chase.
Barry, that place you're in
is full of walls.
When you hit one of those walls,
you find a way to get through it.
Don't lose your faith.
There's too many people
counting on you.
Out here and in there.
Yeah.
Nope.
Nobody leaves
until we're both good again.
Okay.
What do you want from me, Cecile?
I want to know why me having
these powers is so upsetting to you.
You have the powers. Read my mind.
Uh-uh. No. No, no.
Me reading your thoughts
is what got us into all of this.
I want to know how you feel.
Cecile, you being able
to read my thoughts...
It makes me feel vulnerable
in a way that I don't like.
You being able to hear
every scared, dumb thought of mine,
I just don't want you
seeing me like that.
But I would never think less of you
for the thoughts
that cross your mind.
How could you not?
Okay.
Joe, your Grandma Esther's noodles,
they taste terrible.
Okay, they are terrible.
That woman had no business
ever messing with a wok.
Wow. Okay. Wow.
And I think that I've been using
semicolons wrong my entire life
which leads me to believe
that I don't even know
what a semicolon actually is.
Also, I would like to buy
a new pair of pants, 'cause...
But I haven't yet 'cause I'm afraid
to go into the store
'cause I think the salesperson
is gonna judge me
because, truthfully, even I think
that I am just a little bit crazy
for having another baby at this age.
Oh, baby.
You are not crazy.
That speech you just gave
was a little, but you're not.
Those are my scared,
dumb, vulnerable thoughts.
You think any less of me?
- Of course not.
- Mmm-mmm.
Look, I can't promise you that
I'm gonna stop reading your mind.
I don't even really know
how this all works yet.
But I can promise you
that nothing you ever think
will change my opinion of you.
And even when you're not thinking it,
I know that you are
the brave, brilliant,
devastatingly handsome man
that I love.
And the one thought
I hear you have the most
is that you love me, too.
- And I do.
- Yeah.
Based on my scans,
Ralph and Cisco's cells
have re-formed and re-stabilized.
I can attest my bladder
is completely back to normal.
- Fourth Big Gulp today.
- Hmm.
I miss when we could just pick him up
and carry him out of the room.
Right?
Hey, you just passed up a dig
at Dibny. Sure you're all right?
You know, we reopen a case
against an innocent man
and, oh, somehow stumble upon
the actual culprit.
A culprit who, by the way,
has meta-human powers
that we are
partially responsible for...
It's like you said.
There are no coincidences
when it comes to DeVoe
and these bus metas.
What's DeVoe doing?
What's his motive?
Does he want
Sylbert Rundine incarcerated?
Or to have Big Sir set free?
Or for Cisco and I
to become itty-bitty meta-humans?
Well, whatever his plan is,
we'll figure it out.
And we're gonna stop him.
And bring Barry home.
On your feet, inmate.
Is there a problem, Warden?
As you know, inmate Ratchet
mysteriously disappeared last night.
Where do you think he went?
Well, I couldn't say.
In an effort
to locate inmate Ratchet,
I reviewed
the security camera footage.
Did you know the oscillating cameras
aren't the only ones in this wing? Hmm?
Once you started stroking
inmate Ratchet's hopes of freedom,
I had a camera installed
right by your cell.
And when I checked that camera,
I learned who you truly are.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Then let me be specific.
You're the Flash.
It's no use denying it
or trying to run.
You're clearly already showing
the effects of the drug cocktail
I put in that snack
you so seemed to enjoy.
Why?
Why would you do this?
I did warn you.
Everyone in here is a monster.
That'll be all.
You said to call you
when I was ready to do business.
Oh, hello, Warden.
Do you have another fish to sell me?
I do.
And it's a big one.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::