My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Iris's mom is alive.
And you thought you could pay me
to walk away
from my own daughter.
Last time you walked away
for free.
When you created
the singularity,
you also created
a breach--
a portal connecting
our two earths.
You really think he's just
bringing these guys here
to kill me?
Zoom is obsessed
with destroying me.
Now he wants to destroy you.
I'm starting to perceive
things--horrible things.
We have to merge the inner
and outer event horizons
by separating in the eye of it.
No!
Ronnie died saving me,
and I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, get back.
Come here.
Professor Stein,
can you hear me?
Everyone secretly thinks
they've figured out
what their life
is gonna be like,
but what no one ever considers
is that life has
its own plans for you,
whether you like them or not.
And so you're left
with a choice.
You can either embrace
the change and move forward,
or fight it, and be left behind.
Dude!
I knew you could do it.
That was some touchdown, man.
You won us the game!
Hey, no, man.
We won us the game.
Hey, that's not what
the cheerleaders were saying.
Oh, yeah? For real?
A'ight.
Jefferson, great game.
Hey, thanks, coach.
I'm not the only one
that noticed.
Lot of scouts in the stands
tonight,
and after that touchdown,
they all pulled out
their cell phones.
You're gonna get your pick
of colleges, son.
You really think so?
I know so.
You get home and celebrate
with your mom.
Everybody, run!
Oh!
Hey, hey, come on, man,
I got you!
We gotta get inside the tunnel!
Ugh!
Aah!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hold him steady!
He's dropping out.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Cisco, we're losing him!
Got it!
Oh, Dios mio.
Thank God.
He's getting worse.
Look, I did what I could
to re-engineer
Doctor Wells's
original stabilizer
to quell the reaction,
but I don't know
what he used as a power source.
Best I could find was
the one from his wheelchair.
And how long will that last?
Well, that's the problem,
is we had already used up
most of its energy trying
to dampen the metas' powers
during our little rogue air trip
with Weather Wizard and company.
I think we got a few days tops.
And he's stuck in bed?
Yeah, when he wakes up,
I'm gonna transfer
the stabilizer to this,
give him a power cane,
get him moving.
We gotta figure out
a way to save him.
I think I might know
how to do that.
When the Particle Accelerator
exploded,
the dark matter that collided
with Professor Stein
fused with the Firestorm matrix
and altered
the normal molecular processes
that occurs within his body.
Those highly reactive
molecules needed
something to bond with
in order to stabilize.
And that's where Ronnie came in.
Yes, and now that
Ronnie is no longer
a part of Professor Stein--
Those molecules don't have
anything to bond to.
And the longer he goes
without merging,
the more unstable he becomes.
Ugh.
All right, so, what do we do?
We find another...
participant.
Okay, cool, so,
how do we do that?
Are we just gonna make
a Tinder app
for potential meta-humans?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
merging with Stein
and randomly bursting
into flames
sounds like the biggest
"swipe left" of all time.
I mean, even if we could
find someone willing,
Stein can't just merge
with whoever he wants.
No he can't,
but I have done some research,
and found two potential
candidates
that might be compatible
with him.
They both were affected
by the dark matter,
and they were both admitted
to the hospital
showing symptoms
of gene rearrangement mutation.
And they both share
the same blood type
as Professor Stein and Ronnie.
All right.
I mean, this is more
than organ donation.
We'll need more
than tissue typing
to see if their bodies
are compatible.
If I can isolate
the genetic locus
of the two candidates
and cross-reference it
with the mutations
in Professor Stein,
I might be able to find a match
and save his life.
What do you need to do that?
All right, blood samples
from both potential candidates.
Damn, that was fast
even for you.
I may have skipped
the asking for permission part.
Let's see if we can't
find a match.
You were two in that picture.
You'd just got some shots.
You were so mad at the nurse.
You kept saying,
"She pinched me."
So we took you to the park
afterwards to cheer you up,
gave you your first
ice cream cone,
which was a mistake, because
all we heard the next month was,
"Mint-choplat chip,
mint-choplat chip."
Oh,
that's where the obsession
started.
Babe, you don't have to do this.
If you don't want to meet
your mother tomorrow, I get it.
No, it's okay.
I want to meet her.
I need to meet her.
It's gonna be fine.
Mm.
My brave baby girl.
Take after you.
Love you.
Love you more.
Barry?
Hey, I was just looking for you.
I would've called, but I don't
have your number yet, so.
Oh, yeah--
No, no, no, I just wanted
to show you this.
These were just found
in an alley
off of Eastwood Avenue.
What are these, teeth?
Shark teeth.
And I have an eyewitness
that says
he saw a shark walking
on land--a man-shark.
- Man-shark?
- Yeah.
Sounds like
a bad sci-fi movie.
Or awesome sci-fi movie.
Totally.
Um...
Are you for real?
You think there's actually,
like, a shark--
Yeah, I mean, I know
it sounds really wacko...
- Mm-hmm.
- But, I mean,
nothing seems impossible
now that
we have meta-humans,
right?
And I thought it would be fun,
you know,
for us to work together again
on a case.
Yeah, I mean,
I really--
I'd love to work on anything
with you.
Um, it's just, you know,
meta-humans aren't
really my thing.
Oh, okay, yeah, that's fine.
I can handle it.
No, you--look,
how about I just--
I'll run a test,
see where the teeth came from.
That would be amazing.
- All right, cool.
- Thanks.
Yeah, sure.
Detective Spivot.
Detective.
How's your man-shark case
coming?
It's good.
I was just gonna go
and canvas the area,
see what else I can dig up,
and Barry here agreed
to run some tests for me.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
So, progress.
Thanks again.
Mm-hmm.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were flirting
with my partner.
What, Patty?
No, I'm--
What are you talking about?
I'm not--
What is it with you and Iris
and my partners?
Hey, how is Iris, by the way?
Eh, she's pretty nervous
about seeing her mother
after all these years.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what, I gotta go.
It's Cisco.
It's about Professor Stein.
Okay, go.
I'll cover you with Singh.
All right, thanks.
Well, I must admit,
I never imagined
the Sphinx's riddle about a man
requiring three legs
would ever apply to me,
but if this device
keeps me mobile,
then I will gratefully oblige.
Hopefully, you won't need it
for much longer.
There was no agglutination
in the blood samples,
and cross-matching
was negative for both,
and it appears that
the dark matter
from the Particle Accelerator
explosion
mutated their genes
in a very similar way
it did to yours.
I think they're both
potential matches.
So who do we go with?
Well, my first choice
is Henry Hewitt.
He graduated summa cum laude
from Hudson University
with a double major
in Applied Physics
and Bioengineering.
A Hudson boy,
I like him already.
Now, what about this other guy
Jefferson Jackson?
High school quarterback,
4.0 student.
He's got the physical
attributes.
And it looks like more of his
alleles match than Hewitt's.
Doesn't that mean
that he's more compatible?
On paper, perhaps,
but Hewitt is a scientist.
Clearly, he's trying to make
something of his life.
I think he'd be open
to something like this.
I think we should meet
with both of them
before we make a decision.
That's an excellent idea.
I'll see if I can
get Hewitt here.
All right, in the meantime,
we'll go meet with
Jefferson Jackson.
And I will try to find
something else
to help keep you stable.
♪ Anything you want ♪
♪ Anything you need ♪
Are you sure this is
the right place?
Yeah.
Jefferson's a mechanic.
Could indicate
a strong technical aptitude.
That's a positive.
Oh, prone to allergies.
That's definitely a negative,
not to mention
his taste in music.
Would you prefer Celine Dion
instead?
I got the "Titanic" soundtrack
in the back there.
No, thank you.
Jefferson Jackson, right?
People call me Jax.
Ooh, catchy.
My name's Barry Allen,
and this is Martin Stein.
We're with
the Department of Safety.
It's a small,
newly formed agency.
Very new, we probably don't
even have a website yet, do we?
You need to see our licenses?
I mean, we're all
up to code here.
No, no, nothing like that.
We are compiling data
on people who were affected
by the Particle Accelerator
explosion two years ago.
Look, man, I lost
enough time in my life
'cause of that stupid thing
going wrong.
Now, you don't got a car
I can fix, I can't help you.
If you would consider coming
back to S.T.A.R. Labs with us,
I believe we can help you.
Help me how?
Well, we know what
the Particle Accelerator did--
Look, I already told you,
I don't talk about that night.
Why is that?
Because that's when
everything changed.
I got hit hard.
When I woke up,
I was in the hospital.
Busted up leg, torn ACL.
The look on my mom's face,
I knew any dreams I had
of playing pro ball were over.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, well...
look, I gotta get back to work.
Yeah, um...
Here, it's just...
it's our number.
Just think about it, okay?
Thank you for putting this
together, Joseph.
Iris's idea, not mine.
Hey, baby.
Hi, Dad.
Iris...
this is Francine.
Hello.
Hi.
Hello, Iris.
Can I get you a coffee
or something?
Um, no, thanks.
Let's just sit.
I can't get over
what a beautiful young woman
you've become.
And a journalist?
I'm so proud of you.
Why are you here?
Why now, after two decades?
I want to make this
right with you.
How about you start
by apologizing
for walking out on us?
I am sorry, so very, very sorry.
There's so much you don't know.
I'm sure that you've
been through a great deal,
and I can appreciate
you feeling like this is
suddenly the right time
for you to want me in your life,
but that doesn't mean that it's
the right time for me.
Iris...
No, Dad, it's okay.
I've thought about this a lot,
and it wasn't fair for me
to make you the bad guy.
So I want you to hear this
from me.
I don't hate you, Francine.
I do wish you well,
but we have lived separate lives
for over 20 years.
Let's keep it that way.
I've always thought
my destiny was
for greater things.
And people, of course.
Well, when it's all
said and done,
flying will be
the least impressive
of your new abilities.
Man finally achieves
the promise of the Atomic Age.
Caitlin, what's going on?
Hi, I'm glad you're back.
This is Dr. Henry Hewitt.
This is Barry Allen and
Professor Martin Stein.
How do you do?
The illustrious Martin Stein.
I've read all your papers
back at Hudson,
especially on transmutation.
Fascinating.
- You're a legend.
- Oh, please.
I think you're overestimating
my contribution to the field.
- I--I appreciate your enthusiasm.
- Isn't he great?
He's got an ego
the size of Texas,
but, yeah, he's all right.
So, where's Jefferson Jackson?
We just need more time.
We don't have more time.
I couldn't find
another power source
for the cane
and that thing's running out.
Okay, then let's do the merge.
Hewitt's in.
What do you mean?
You told him the details
of the Firestorm Matrix?
Absolutely, becoming Firestorm
is a huge life change.
He needs to know what
he's getting himself into.
If I remember correctly,
vector, variance, hypotenuse--
Proton, neutron, go H.U.!
Aw, look at that,
that's so cute.
We'll have two Professor Steins
if this works.
It's gonna work.
Yeah.
Okay.
When I put this splicer
on your chest
you're gonna feel a rush.
That's a molecular primer
being released into your body.
Then you can make
physical contact
with Professor Stein, and...
Firestorm Matrix will take over.
Easy enough.
Ready?
No time like the present.
Thank you, my dear.
Okay.
Try again.
This is unexpected.
Something's supposed to be
happening, right?
Why isn't it working?
I don't know.
Uh, well,
looks like you two aren't
compatible after all.
I'm just gonna...
So all this was for nothing?
Believe me, no one is
more disappointed than I am.
Yeah, don't be so sure
about that.
Next time, try to get
your act together
before you get
someone's hopes up.
Move the show-and-tell
to next Tuesday,
remind me to call Richard
tomorrow
about the shareholders meeting,
and where are we
with the replacement
for Doctor Snow?
Uh--
Applied sciences.
Stop!
Don't move!
Harrison?
Detective West,
Thank you for coming.
Doctor McGee,
this is my new partner,
Detective Spivot.
It's nice to meet you.
I was saddened
by Detective Thawne's passing.
Please extend my condolences
to your daughter.
Thank you.
On the phone
you mentioned this was
a sensitive matter.
It is, and I called you directly
because I've always appreciated
your discretion in the past.
Of course, can you tell me
what was stolen?
It's not so much what was
stolen, but who stole it.
The person who broke into
my facility last night
was Harrison Wells.
Harrison Wells is dead.
I seem to recall
the circumstances
around his passing were
a bit inconclusive.
Is there any possibility
he could be alive?
Zero possibility.
I knew the man
for over 20 years.
I know who I saw.
The only thing distinctively
different was...
he's walking again.
Like I said,
I trust your discretion.
You have full access
to the facility.
Thank you again, Detective.
First a shark-man,
now a dead man walking.
We need to call Barry,
get him in here first.
Barry can't hear
about any of this.
What--why?
Because he's got
a lot on his plate.
He's got a friend who's sick
who he needs his help,
and Harrison Wells is the man
who murdered his mother.
Once he hears that--
Is he okay?
He's fine, but...
not a word to him or anyone,
okay?
Okay.
Yeah, it's just,
I'm not really good at lying.
Well, you better learn, quick.
Yeah, definitely.
Spivot, go on ahead.
Sure.
This is the last time
you ever show up here.
Do you understand?
I needed to talk to you again.
How much clearer
do we need to be?
Iris and I do not want you
in our lives.
Leave, please.
Go home, live your life.
Joe, there's something else.
I wanted to tell you
when I first saw you, but--
What is it?
Few months ago,
I started getting weak.
The doctors ran
a bunch of tests,
they couldn't figure it out.
But finally, they did.
Said I have something
called MacGregor's.
Supposedly it's pretty common
among ex-addicts.
Told me I had till the end
of the year if I'm lucky.
Is--is that why
you came back?
I just want my daughter
to know me...
this me.
I'm really glad
you decided to come.
I thought S.T.A.R. Labs
had to shut down.
It's under new management.
Huh.
Whoa, what kind of treadmill
is that?
Cosmic.
Cool.
So, let's get started.
You got some kind of
"Billion Dollar Man" technology
that gonna fix my knee?
Actually, Jax, this isn't
about fixing your knee.
What are you talking about?
When the Particle Accelerator
exploded,
the energy wave
that collided with you
is known as "dark matter."
And it didn't just hurt
your knee.
It--it changed the molecular
structure of your body.
Whoa, hold on, Grey.
So you're saying I'm like
one of those meta-humans
I keep hearing about
on the news?
Yes, I am.
Please, call me Professor.
We think you have
potential capabilities.
What kind of capabilities?
The same as Professor Stein:
the ability for your body
to process fission and fusion.
And you can harness
excess energy
and turn it into these massive
nuclear blasts.
And you can fly.
There's also that.
So you're saying
you can do all this?
Only during times of convergence
with a willing partner.
Convergence?
You and me?
Yes.
No, this is crazy.
No, Jax, this is your chance
to right the wrong
that was done to you.
Yeah, sorry,
you got the wrong guy.
I don't want nothing
to do with this.
Wait a second, we are
giving you the chance
to be a superhero,
and you're gonna say no
that quickly?
Yeah, not my kind of thing.
If the man isn't willing
to participate--
Look, I saw your
test scores, Jax.
Your grades were good enough
to get into college,
but you didn't go.
Why?
Is this the type of guy you are?
One setback and you fold?
Well, then maybe
you're not the guy for us
anyway.
Well, maybe I'm not.
Jack--
Maybe this just wasn't
meant to be.
Cait, come on, I mean,
Jax could be our last chance
at saving Professor Stein.
He said no to being a superhero.
Who does that?
I mean, you didn't say no
when you had the chance.
Cisco, would you?
Chance to have superpowers?
Sign me up.
Look, we're asking Jax
to change his entire life,
to sacrifice what he does have.
I mean, that's not a decision
that can be made lightly.
It took me a long time
to figure out this whole
hero thing.
Exactly, which is why we need
someone who wants to do this.
Where are you going?
To get Hewitt back.
We have to try again.
Human DNA?
Yup, definitely not
a man-shark.
Not even a land shark, Ma'am.
Well, thanks for testing it
for me.
Yeah.
What are you gonna do now?
I don't know, probably file it
under "never gonna happen."
I have another case anyway.
Oh, anything I can
help you with?
No, no, no, no,
Detective said definitely n-not.
Is everything all good?
Sure, why?
I don't know,
you're just acting
kind of different.
No!
No.
I'm the same old P. Spivot,
you know?
What--actually, I have to go,
but thank you so much
for testing this,
and I'll see you.
Okay, I--
Yo, Joe.
Hey.
You good?
Everything all right?
Yeah.
No, I'm--
just had hell of a day.
Yeah?
Iris's mother,
she told me she was dying.
Yeah, and I know Francine.
She's telling the truth
about this.
Okay.
Does Iris know?
Not yet.
Did--
did you need something?
Uh, no, no.
I just, um...
Patty said you that
you don't want me on some case
that she's on with you.
No.
I was checking out a lead.
I'll let you know.
All right, cool.
What is up with you
and my partner, anyway?
Come on, I--
Bar, you can't
take your eyes off that girl.
I don't know what
you want me to tell you.
I mean, she's great, you know.
She's adorable and funny
and we have
a lot in common, but--
"But, um."
I don't know.
She's not Iris, I guess.
Right.
You've known Iris
since you were ten.
You've been in love with her
since forever.
I mean, you two are friends now,
but she was your first love.
You're never gonna feel
the same about anybody else,
but you can't let that stop you
from exploring something new.
Yeah.
And in happier news,
remember Flash Day,
the downtown celebration
to honor
Central City's
one and only superhero?
Well, just weeks--
Hewitt, you have
those nucleosome results?
Tomorrow.
I told you
I needed them tonight.
And I'm telling you
you'll have them tomorrow.
You know, I know you think
you're smarter than
everyone here, Hewitt,
but I'm sick of
your not doing your job,
your not showing up.
If I have any more trouble
from you, you're done here.
What, you're gonna
take the test away
and give it to another
lab rat of yours?
You're gonna report me
to the board?
Or maybe you're thinking
of firing me?
I'd like to see you try!
Now get the hell out of my lab!
What's being describedas
a "spontaneous
energy malfunction"
erupted last night
at Eikmeier Technologies.
Wanted for questioning
is scientist Henry Hewitt.
Hewitt's dormant abilities
must have been triggered
when we attempted the merger.
This could be catastrophic.
If his powers are
anything like mine,
he requires
a grounding mechanism
to stabilize his volatility.
Otherwise--
Yeah, he's gonna pop his top,
and he's got a long history
of violence,
according to his police record.
Police record?
I didn't find a police record.
Yeah, of course not,
it was sealed,
but guess what,
ya boy hacked in and--
hold on, wait for it.
One count battery,
two counts aggravated assault,
court-ordered
anger management therapy.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
He even knew
your Hudson nerd song.
Whoa, you okay?
It appears Mr. Hewitt's
stability
isn't the only one in question.
I think I need to lie down.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
Thank you.
Professor Stein is
getting worse.
And Hewitt's like this
because of me.
And now Jefferson Jackson
will never come back
because of what I said.
I just didn't believe
that he has what it takes.
This isn't because
you didn't believe in him.
Sometimes, great possibilities
are right in front of us,
and we don't see them,
because we choose not to.
I think that we need to be open
to exploring something new.
She's dying?
A few months left.
I just don't think
I can see her, Dad.
And that's fine.
But you and me need to be
crystal clear about this, Iris.
If you want to have
a relationship with Francine,
it's okay with me.
You don't have to protect me.
I'm a grown man and
I've dealt with these feelings
a long time ago.
So you--you just
believe her?
She's done some bad things
in her life,
but she wouldn't lie about this.
Dad, she shows up
out of nowhere,
and only says that she's dying
after I told her to stay away.
Look, she didn't come
to Central City to see me.
She came because of you.
I just wanted you
to know everything
so you can make
the best decision for yourself.
I mean, she is still
your mother.
Either way, whatever you decide,
just know, I got your back.
I know.
Let me guess,
you don't got car troubles.
I came to apologize.
I'm sorry for what I said.
It's fine.
Apology accepted.
Look, we could really
use your help
to save Professor Stein.
That desperate, huh?
Yes.
My husband, Ronnie,
he used to be
Professor Stein's other half.
He actually helped
build the Particle Accelerator,
and when it exploded,
he was affected by it too.
Ironically, that's how
he got the chance
to show the world
what he was truly capable of.
And he died saving this city.
Wait, he was the guy that flew
into the black hole?
That was him?
He was a hero.
You can be one too.
I never wanted to be a hero.
What I wanted was
to go to college,
but we couldn't afford it.
Football was my way in,
until that got taken from me.
I know.
Look, I know
the Particle Accelerator
took something from you.
But it also gave you
something in return,
something even more spectacular,
the opportunity to be
part of something bigger,
to be part of a team
that's working to protect people
from losing what you lost.
I believe you were meant
to be a hero.
Whoa, hold on.
I've been looking for you,
Dr. Snow.
Hey, look, man, we're--
ugh!
You did this to me!
But it's not
what you promised, is it?
Is it?
Come on!
Where to?
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Caitlin.
- What's wrong?
- Come here.
Oh, good, you're here.
This thing, it ran out,
like, 30 minutes ago.
His temperature is 142 degrees
and rising fast.
He's going into rapid oxidation.
We need to find a coolant.
I think it's too late for that.
I'll do it.
I'll merge with him.
You said this is a chance
for me to be
a part of something bigger
than myself,
to help people.
That's what I want.
You're sure?
Once you merge, there's no
going back on this.
And you said I could fly, right?
- Damn right.
- Okay.
So what do I do?
Okay, well,
here's the abridged version.
Professor Stein?
- Professor Stein?
- Clarissa, five more minutes.
No, Professor,
you have to get up.
Jax is here.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Jax is here.
- Here, grab onto me.
- Jax?
Yeah.
This is it.
Whew.
You came back, Jefferson,
thank you.
Well, like my coach always said,
"Out of yourself
and into the team."
So, how's this work?
Okay, all you're gonna do
is touch him.
And then what happens?
You become Firestorm.
Okay.
Jax?
Is Professor Stein--
How will I know?
Hello, Jefferson.
Now you know.
Oh, so I get Grey as my copilot.
Did no one ever inform you
of that fringe benefit?
So when do we get to take this
for a test spin?
Uh, how about now?
It looks like
Hewitt's re-charging
at Central City High School's
football stadium.
Wait, that was where I got hurt.
Cisco, cut the power
to the field
so he can't draw anymore energy.
I'm on it.
Stand by.
Boo-ya ka!
Hewitt!
You need to stop!
This is not who you are!
Stein?
You chose him over me?
That's who I'm supposed to be!
I deserve the Firestorm Matrix!
Move, now!
Calm down, Jefferson, focus.
Use your natural athleticism
to gain control.
Hey, you okay?
I was a quarterback.
I know how to take a hit.
Hey, guys,
cutting the power didn't work.
It's like the more we anger him,
the stronger he gets.
That's it, it's like
one of those, uh,
controlled fusion devices.
Um...
Tokamak?
Yes, exactly,
and the more powerful
they become,
the more unstable they become.
Barry, make him angry,
and he'll blow his fuse.
You up for a little game
of "catch me if you can?"
Let's go for it.
Okay.
Hey, Hewitt, over here!
Paging Dr. Hewitt.
Boo!
Aah!
Man, you are not good at this.
Do you need a hug, Doctor?
Aah!
Come on, Hewitt,
give me your best shot!
Now.
Is that all you got, Hewitt?
Man, no wonder you didn't
make the cut
if that's how you fight.
Aah!
Not bad for your first go
at this.
Well, I had a great coach
to help me through it.
Isn't that right, Grey?
Despite my initial
reservations, we make
a pretty fantastic team.
Welcome aboard, Firestorm.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
You have no idea
what this means to me.
My dad told me you were sick.
You know, I wasn't sure
that I could believe you,
so I did some checking.
Turns out you're
telling the truth.
I would never lie to you
about something so big.
Really?
'Cause I was actually thinking
that I could give you
another chance
after hearing that news.
But you're still lying,
still keeping secrets.
I'm an investigative reporter,
Francine.
I uncover things that people
want to keep hidden,
like having a son.
Iris--
He was born eight months
after you left Central City.
Let me explain.
Who's the father, Francine?
Is it my dad?
Do I have a brother?
Wait, you know, I don't even
want--I don't want to know.
I mean, I wouldn't
be able to tell
if you were telling the truth
or if it was
another one of your lies,
anyway.
Oh.
I want you to leave.
You stay away from me, and
you stay away from my father.
If he finds out that he might
have a son that grew up
without even knowing him,
it would crush him.
Just...
Leave us alone.
Iris, I was--
And how is Mr. Hewitt?
Seems like that last burst
of energy has burnt him out.
Our Tokamak's gone dark.
Yeah, we're just gonna keep him
safe and sound in the pipeline
till he decides to keep
quiet about all this.
So you're gonna
meet up with Clarissa?
We're meeting in Pittsburgh
in three days.
Why Pittsburgh?
A colleague of mine
was monumental
in helping train Ronald and me.
She's graciously offered
to help the two of us as well.
How's she gonna help us?
Well, there were many aspects
of our abilities
that we never quite achieved.
Hopefully now, we can
fully realize that potential.
Oh, my dearest
Dr. Snow.
Ronald may be lost to us,
but he will never be forgotten.
Speaking of...
this was Ronnie's.
He always used it to
find his way back home.
I want you to have it.
Thank you.
You know,
this whole thing is strange,
being 50% of someone.
Yeah, but you're 100% a hero.
I went ahead and recalibrated
the splicer
so the merging should be
even smoother now.
Thank you.
If I may offer
a bit of parting advice.
Cisco, I know you're scared,
but this ability you have
is a gift, not a curse.
It's natural to be apprehensive
about the unknown,
but look at Jefferson.
He took a leap, and it changed
his life for the better.
The very thing that makes
you different
is what makes you special.
Tell your friends.
And now I believe it's time
to take this show on the road--
or to the sky,
if I am to be literal.
Are you ready, Jefferson?
All right.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
That was one hell
of a leap of faith
that kid took,
merging with Professor Stein.
Yeah, it was.
There's a lesson in there
somewhere for you.
Things aren't always
what they seem.
Our fears can play tricks on us,
making us afraid
to change course,
afraid to move on,
but usually,
hidden behind our fears
are second chances
waiting to be seized...
Second chances at life...
- Whoo!
- At glory...
Whoo!
At family...
At love.
And these opportunities
don't come around every day,
so when they do,
we have to be brave,
take a chance,
and grab them while we can.
Zoom wants you dead.
Oh, my God, it's real.
Hey!
Put him down!
Put your hands--
your fins in the air!
Who the hell are you?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com