This season on The Flash...
I went back in time
and created an alternate timeline,
a whole new existence.
I created Flashpoint
and changed everything.
- Who are you?
- Savitar, the god of speed.
You said that I trapped you
in the future. Where?
The only place that could hold me,
the Speed Force.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes.
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
- Good luck with that.
- We don't want to fight you.
We're your friends, your family.
- Caitlin, I love you.
- I never loved any of you.
Caitlin's working with Savitar.
- Caitlin is dead.
- Not to me.
- I know who you are.
- I am the Future Flash.
When I have control of all of time,
it will be you
who is abandoned and forgotten.
And I only need for Iris to die, so that
you are driven so far into the dark
that I can be born.
I'm gonna stop you.
- It didn't work.
- You lose, Barry.
No!
Iris.
Oh, no...
Iris? Iris.
B.A.
What?
H.R.?
Dad...
Dad.
Baby?
Yeah.
I don't understand.
It was H.R.
Until the next one.
H.R.?
Hi.
Let's get you out of here.
- Where is everybody else?
- Couldn't tell.
Barry or Savitar would know I was coming.
- Let's get you out of here.
- Okay.
Get her.
- We can't outrun them.
- No, we can't.
What are you doing?
I'm the reason Savitar found you.
- I need to remedy that.
- Not like this.
Give me that.
Don't! I'm the one he wants, okay?
Please, don't hurt him.
H.R.
Tracy...
- No, no, no...
- It's okay.
Why are you doing this?
I couldn't be a coward.
I'm not a coward.
- But we just found each other.
- I know.
Our story will be brilliant.
You will be brilliant.
You will be glorious, Tracy Brand.
You will be.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
I love you.
- B.A.? B.A.
- I'm right here.
Will you tell Cisco...
Please tell him...
Will you tell him that, for me?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Now,
go stop Savitar.
H.R. H.R.
Savitar took the Speed Force bazooka.
Bye-bye, Vibe.
Keep him alive.
What? Why?
Because I need him
to build something for us.
Iris West Allen.
It changed back.
- Does that mean what I think it means?
- Yeah, Joe.
The future is ours again.
Savitar?
- Something's wrong.
- What is it?
She's not dead.
- How is that possible?
- H.R.
He took her place.
H.R.?
- I thought you said H.R. lives.
- Not anymore.
If Iris doesn't die...
That means the future is changing.
So is yours.
What?
H.R. is dead. I can't believe that.
- Is Tracy all right?
- Not good.
She just wants to be alone.
There'll be time to mourn.
Right now, we need to figure out
our next move.
So, for the millionth time,
I am lost on all this time travel stuff.
What happens now with Savitar?
Iris didn't die.
So that changes things, right?
I mean, since Iris didn't die,
future me never goes down
that same dark path.
I never create Time Remnants
to fight Savitar.
And if future you never creates
these Time Remnants,
then Savitar himself is never born.
Precisely.
Once the time paradox catches up with him,
then he'll be erased from existence.
- But I saw him, he didn't disappear.
- Not yet.
But he will, Joe.
Any guesses how long that's going to take?
Maybe a few hours.
You can do a lot of damage in a few hours.
Well, guys, we can't just sit around
and wait for Savitar to disappear.
But Savitar won't become Savitar
if he's erased.
Not unless he pulls off whatever
he's got in mind
before the paradox hits him.
He stole the bazooka for a reason.
- Yeah, why?
- I don't know.
But, remember,
he's been planning this for centuries.
He wants to be a god.
He must need the bazooka and Caitlin
to achieve his goals.
- Anybody got any good news?
- Actually, voila'.
- What is that?
- This, Detective, is a cure for Caitlin.
You're kidding. You figured it out?
Not by myself.
With the help of Caitlin's mother.
This is experimental gene therapy.
This will rewrite Caitlin's meta-DNA.
This will bring back Caitlin.
I searched the forest.
Savitar and Caitlin were gone.
- So was Cisco.
- Savitar has them both.
You better have a plan B.
Because I don't think your plan A
worked out too well.
Fix this.
Fix what? The Speed Force bazooka?
I didn't name it.
If I didn't name it, I didn't make it.
And if I didn't make it,
I don't know how it works.
You know enough about it
to alter what it does.
I see. You want me to alter it. Well,
what do you want me to alter it into?
Like a hair dryer? Or a waffle maker?
I know, maybe something that's going to
fix that thin-crust pizza you call a face.
An intra-dimensional quantum splicer.
A splicer?
I do have a plan B.
I open a time portal,
exposing the Speed Force.
You shoot me with that,
and I become fragmented
throughout all of time.
The past, present, future.
After that, the paradox can't reach me.
You want to splice yourself
throughout time.
Exist in every single
moment that ever was.
All of us aware and connected
through one consciousness.
I'll be everywhere.
Every hour, every minute.
And then I will rule from the Big Bang
until the end of the world.
You wanted us to build this thing.
Well, why do you think
I let you idiots live?
Tracy Brand trapped me in the Speed Force
in the future.
All I had to do was get her
to build this a little earlier
and have my best friend
make all the adjustments.
- I'm not your friend.
- Get to work, Francisco.
How about I sit on my ass and let you
obliterate permanently from existence.
How does that sound?
That's your plan?
Do it or you'll Reverse-Flash me?
Not you.
Her.
You know what I'm remembering?
Julian just got back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
He has the cure.
He can turn her back.
You can have her back.
You're so close.
But not if she's dead.
So put that mechanical genius
to good work.
Make me what I need,
and I will let you both go.
I hated Thawne.
And Zoom.
They took so much from me.
And I've hated Savitar for threatening
to take you away from me, too.
But he didn't.
I know.
There is strength in anger.
I've used it before.
And so we sit here with our anger,
trying to think of a way to hurt Savitar
or maybe kill him.
And I just don't think that hate's gonna
get it done this time.
What do you mean?
Something that Snart said to me.
That the Flash should stay a hero.
All the way.
And sometimes that's not about who can
punch the hardest or run the fastest.
So, what are you going to do?
The last thing he'd expect.
I wasn't sure you'd come.
Must be an odd sensation.
Getting new memories.
You having an uncertain future.
What do you want? I'm busy.
Doing what?
Getting erased from existence?
We will see which one of us gets erased.
Are you still planning on becoming a god?
Cisco and Caitlin are still alive,
- if that's what you're worried about.
- I know.
You need them, right?
To pull off your grand ascension.
Look, Barry,
if I wanted to talk to myself,
I could've done that back at my lair.
What do you want?
- I want to help you.
- Really?
You don't have much time before
the paradox reaches you.
Come back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Let Cisco and Caitlin go.
And let us figure out a way to save you.
You really think I'd trust you?
You showed up.
So you remember me coming here.
Did I have any tricks up my sleeve?
Was I planning on blindsiding you?
I don't know, Barry.
Maybe I get off on watching you grovel.
No, I don't think that's it.
I think you're hearing me.
I'm still in there.
Deep down,
buried beneath the scars and the pain,
that part of you that must feel so lonely.
But it also knows what it's like
to have a family.
To have friends.
You can have all that back.
We can stop hurting each other.
I remember when I was six
and I begged Mom and Dad to let me
go to the Science Expo in Midway.
And we got a flat tire on that dirt road.
No spare.
So we were towed to that garage
in a tiny one-street town.
Of course, we were stuck there all day.
Then we got ice cream and French fries
with gravy at that little diner.
And then that night we watched
the local fireworks show, and...
It actually turned out to be a great day.
It's my favorite memory of Mom and Dad.
What was the name of that town?
Masonville.
I'm still in there.
Come home.
You make a move toward Iris...
He won't. Killing Iris won't save him now.
Not anymore.
- Where's Cisco? Where's Caitlin?
- They're safe.
I was asking him.
Show me that you can help me.
Then I will tell you
where your friends are.
You tell us now or you go up in smoke.
This is bloody insanity.
- What is he doing here? He's a...
- Stop! Guys!
It's okay. Everyone just...
Iris, stay away from him.
Look at me.
It's okay. Look at me.
We're going to help you, okay?
Thank you.
Right.
Well, since our guest here has both
of our resident scientists hostage,
what temporal problem
can we help you with?
Tracy built the Speed Force trap.
Maybe she has an idea.
- Tracy's our best bet.
- Am I?
So, you're Savitar?
I hear you're about to have
a really bad day.
- Good.
- Tracy...
He stole my future.
Why does he deserve one?
I shouldn't have come here.
No. We'll get her to help us.
I think I know someone who might
be able to get through to her.
I'm not H.R.
My name is Harrison Wells.
I'm from a different Earth.
In the multi-verse... How to explain this?
You're his doppelganger?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Look, these people,
they are good people.
And they need your help.
By helping the bad guy that
I spent weeks trying to stop?
No.
I won't do it.
The only reason I agreed
was because of H.R.
H.R. needs your help.
H.R. is dead.
That's why you need to stay,
because of what Savitar took from you,
because of what Savitar took
from H.R., everything.
H.R. paid the price that he did
because he loved these people.
Because he loved you.
And when the moment came,
H.R. didn't run.
It's strange being back here.
You remember S.T.A.R. Labs?
I remember everything.
This is where we came up
with the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
Who?
You haven't gotten there yet.
So, how's this gonna work?
Where will I live?
- What do you mean?
- Are Wally and I gonna be bunkmates?
Am I supposed to just rejoin Team Flash,
fight some rogues?
What kind of life
were you thinking I'd lead?
I hadn't gotten that far yet.
How do we explain me at the wedding?
And do I sit bride-side or groom-side?
Look, I mean,
we don't have all the answers.
You know, we're gonna figure it out.
Together.
No.
Not together.
Love and hate,
they're so close,
it's easy to mistake one for the other.
You're gonna spend the rest
of your life with him.
But I remember giving you the ring.
Singing to you.
Asking you to marry me.
I can't do this.
Yes, you can, okay?
I will be here for you.
I tried to kill you.
I killed H.R.
And you're going
to have to live with that.
But we won't give up on you, okay?
That is not what we do.
There's a way through this. For all of us.
Where are Cisco and Caitlin?
I'll bring them home.
What is it?
There's energy radiating
from the breach room.
That's not breach energy.
That's the Philosopher's Stone.
It's releasing all its energy.
- Savitar.
- It looks like it's gonna blow.
Wally, get everybody out.
Is it finished?
Yeah, it's finished.
Fantastic.
You know,
Savitar's gonna turn on you one day.
No, he won't.
A bad guy like Savitar
always turns on his partners.
- Not this time.
- Wake up!
You're only saying that
because he needs something from you.
Once he's done with that,
it's over for you.
- How'd it go?
- As I expected.
I was a fool to think otherwise.
Where did he go? What did you do?
I got rid of a problem.
A few of them.
Now I can fix mine.
- Are we ready?
- Yes.
Do it.
Caitlin.
Listen to me. He'll do it.
He'll kill you.
I'll take my chances.
Gypsy?
Wait! No!
- You don't care that they got away?
- No, it doesn't matter.
It's time.
Ow.
I had that. I was getting through to her.
You were almost killed.
Maybe that's how it looks
to the untrained eye.
These eyes are highly trained.
And I know you were in danger
because I vibed it across the multi-verse.
I can't believe this is the thanks I get
for saving you.
This isn't thanks.
This is the opposite of thanks.
Wait a minute.
How did you vibe that I was in trouble?
Because we are connected.
Jackass.
Guys?
Oh, my God.
I thought something happened to you guys.
Two-Face told me you guys were dead.
We're okay.
- Gypsy.
- Guys.
Harry.
- Here to help.
- Good.
I know what he's up to.
We have to hurry.
I must become immortal
before the paradox reaches me.
Today I become a god.
This is why I brought you here.
The Speed Force doesn't like it
when speedsters mess with time.
Get ready.
See you later, Hunter.
The one thing
Black Flash can't fight, cold!
Finally, to be a god.
What? No!
I've been waiting a long time to do that.
- Garrick. How did you...
- He didn't.
I did.
By changing the polarity
of the climbing arc,
I changed her Speed Force splicer
into a Speed Force skeleton key.
Didn't think I was actually gonna let you
become a god, now, did you?
Let's end this.
Go!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Go ahead, Cisco. Go bad.
No. I never will.
But I will give you a choice.
You want to be Caitlin again?
Here's your chance.
Look out!
You'll pay for what you did.
And you can die the same way twice.
I knew you didn't have it in you, Caitlin.
I only have a few minutes left.
I can feel it.
But before I go, I'm gonna kill Joe.
And Wally and Iris.
If I'm going to die,
then everything you love
is going to die, too.
How's it feel to get so close
to your ascension,
and end up on the ground?
Now I see...
- It's written.
- Nothing's written.
Do it!
You kill me, you become me.
Either way, I live!
I'll never let the pain and darkness
determine who I am.
I'll never be you.
All these months,
you were trying to save me from him.
Look at that, I saved you.
When I think of H.R.,
I'm reminded
of a story that John Lennon once told.
When Lennon was five years old,
his teacher asked him
to write down what he wanted to be
when he grew up.
Lennon wrote "happy."
His teachers said
that he didn't understand the assignment,
and Lennon said
that they didn't understand life.
H.R. understood life.
He wasn't a genius
and he didn't have super-speed,
but when we needed him the most,
he was our hero.
He was my hero.
Mine, too.
Good on you, mate.
Thanks for believing in me, H.R.
I've been looking
for the right time to tell you.
Tell me what?
Right before H.R. died,
he asked me to give you a message.
Tell Cisco, this took strength
and he gave it to me.
I know that you've had a connection
with every Wells that we've met, but...
I don't know.
There's something about this Wells.
Yeah.
Something.
I'll be right back.
Well, well, well.
I guess you're not shopping
at Villains "R" Us anymore.
I'm sorry about H.R.
I'm sure he would have
appreciated you coming.
- Why did you come?
- I don't know.
- Maybe you wanted to come home?
- I don't have a home.
Yes, you do, Caitlin.
You do, with your friends. With me.
I'm sorry, Julian.
I'm not Caitlin anymore.
You're not Killer Frost.
No, I'm not. I'm something else.
And I need to figure out what that is.
On my own.
- Hey.
- Cisco.
Let me go.
- Stop it.
- It's not funny.
- I know.
- Why are we laughing?
We should not be laughing.
Today of all days.
I think H.R. would've approved.
Probably.
Are you okay? I mean,
with what you did?
I'm sure one day it'll hit me.
In the future, which I have again.
We have. Every day of it.
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
I think we have the song picked out
for the dance at our reception.
Yeah, that reminds me.
I can officially mail these.
What are these?
Save-the-date cards for our wedding.
On one of my braver days,
I filled them out.
I never mailed them, not knowing if
I would live to see the ceremony, but...
But now I guess it's safe to...
Delivered.
I wasted a lot of money on stamps.
Thank you very much.
Are you ready to be Iris West-Allen?
I've always been Iris West-Allen.
I've always been yours.
What is that?
There's never been an earthquake
in Central City.
That wasn't an earthquake.
You found something?
Everything is barbecued.
I'm gonna try to establish
an uplink to the satellite.
That's not good.
Hey, Wally, can you reverse
the polarity on the neutron flow?
On it.
Central City University just reported
an earthquake of 6.6 on the Richter scale.
- That's not an earthquake.
- Then what was it?
Earthquakes come from down below. This...
This is something else.
It's getting bad out there.
Emergency services
will soon be overwhelmed.
Guys, 7.2, that last one.
- Cisco.
- Yeah. We're on. Guys.
What is that thing?
That's definitely not a breach.
Holy plutonium.
What even emits that many kilojoules?
The Speed Force.
- But Savitar is dead.
- That's the problem.
It's the Speed Force prison.
It needs an occupant.
When you freed me, we emptied it.
Without a prisoner...
It goes unstable.
And now it's bleeding energy
onto our Earth.
Okay, so how do we stop this?
By giving it what it needs.
Which is what?
The Speed Force is unbalanced.
I have to stabilize it.
- What? How?
- By running into it.
No, you can't.
Barry, you'll be trapped in there forever.
If I don't go, the whole city,
maybe even the entire planet
could be destroyed.
Cisco, there's got to be
another way, right?
Barry, Central City needs the Flash.
And they'll have one.
They'll have one.
All right?
- All right?
- Yeah.
Mate...
Do you mind sticking around?
Anything for you.
Barry, Wally and Jay
said they were in hell.
Barry, it's your mother.
That's the Speed Force.
Barry isn't going to hell.
But like all runners must eventually,
he's reached his finish line.
His race is over.
You can't take him with you.
She's not taking me anywhere.
I have to go.
Why? Why are you being punished?
This... All of this,
it started with my mistake.
With Flashpoint.
This is my penance.
This is my redemption.
My beautiful boy,
it's time to rest.
- Don't mess it up with her.
- I'll do my best.
They're all gonna look to you now.
I'm not a hero like you.
You've always been my hero.
All this time we're trying to save Iris,
you're telling me
that we should've been trying
to save you, too?
You did save me, Joe.
You took an 11-year-old boy
with a broken heart
and you gave him a home and so much love.
No son ever felt more love from a father.
No father ever felt more proud of a son.
Barry?
It's time.
Barry.
This is unfair.
I know.
We were supposed to have our happy ending.
I'm ready to be Iris West-Allen.
And you always will be.
But you need to keep living your life.
Keep growing.
Keep loving.
Keep running. For me.
Promise me you'll run, Iris.
I promise.
I gotta go.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::