My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
The court orders that Mr. Allen
should be remanded to
Iron Heights Penitentiary.
- Get comfortable.
- I didn't kill anybody.
Yeah, sure. Everyone's innocent in here,
especially that guy: Big Sir.
12 markers, 12 metas.
Now that we know how many there are,
we can go right to them.
- I don't want any trouble.
- Too late.
Thanks. I was just
wondering why you helped me.
'Cause your dad helped me.
He operated and saved my life.
Cecile, are you sure we need a crib?
I used to plop Iris on some cushions
and call it a night.
Well, I'm glad to hear you
got all your parenting mistakes
out of the way with your first kid.
I think she's turned out pretty good.
Oh, babe.
I cannot believe I am so big already.
You know, I was barely showing
at this point with Joanie.
All right, best I
got. What do you think?
Mmhmm.
- Are they?
- Are they what?
- Too tight.
- Um...
Hey, you just said that you thought
my clothes were too tight,
- Do I look bad?
- What? I didn't say that.
What do you mean when is
it gonna go back to normal?
I didn't say that either.
Look at me.
- My lips weren't moving.
- What are you talking about?
I heard you. I...
I can still hear you.
What the hell is going on?
Why can I hear what you're thinking?
Oh, my God, Joe...
I think I can read minds.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Heartrate's 170 BPM,
and there's no sign of dark
matter in the amniotic fluid.
So the baby's not a meta?
Nope, it's a perfectly normal baby...
Girl.
You were gonna say baby girl.
- I'm having another daughter?
- I'm gonna have a sister?
Well, I guess we can cancel
the announcement party.
Ha-ha-ha!
Boy, girl, that's 50-50.
Let's test your skills for real.
What number am I thinking of?
Three. 11.
25. Three again.
Bulbasaur.
- What the hell is a Bulbasaur?
- That's so weird.
Why would I be thinking about
Pokémon at a time like this?
Yep, definitely a telepath.
But how?
If the baby is not a meta,
then where did these powers come from?
Nope, I wasn't on the bus.
No, I was not abducted by aliens.
No, I didn't inherit a
mystic totem from my grandma.
Really, guys? Why are you
still thinking about Bulbasaurs?
He's the cutest one of all!
Okay, my best hypothesis is
this is actually triggered by
your latest phase of pregnancies,
and it's actually latent dark matter
that's been in your brain since...
maybe the first particle
accelerator explosion.
Think of it like gestational diabetes.
But it's not. You can
fix that with insulin.
Right, but it's temporary.
I mean, the symptoms should
recede after childbirth.
Okay, we'll give you guys a minute.
Joe, you are literally thinking,
"I'm worried about Cecile."
I just want you and the baby to be okay.
I know.
But hey, maybe... maybe this
will turn out to be a good thing.
I've always wondered what
goes on in that head of yours.
Cecile's a telepath?
Well, that's way more important
than getting Allen out of prison!
- Not!
- Sick burn, Hare.
Please don't encourage him.
As a former prisoner, I can tell you...
No, that was gorilla prison.
Gorilla prison is worse.
They throw their scat at you.
I can tell you that Allen
is sitting in his cell,
suffering, while this guy,
DeVoe, continues his plan unabated.
Harry, Cecile filed an appeal last week.
We have no new evidence,
so that doesn't matter.
We have satellites on the DeVoes.
And they haven't made a move in weeks,
so that doesn't matter!
Well, Barry's in gen pop, so worst case,
he can always phase out,
or I can breach him out.
And then he'd be a fugitive.
And by the way, Ramon,
why do we not have eyes on him in there?
Hey, it's a pain trying to get into
an analog camera from here,
no matter how hard I hack.
Hack... harder.
We're nowhere.
This team is nowhere,
and this is the team
that got Barry out of a
pantemporal speed prison,
and we can't spring
him from a county jail?
Harry, we are working
just as hard as you, okay?
And yes, it kills me to admit it,
but we are at a roadblock,
so Barry is just gonna have to...
Hold on.
I mean, I can't even imagine
what he's going through.
Read 'em and weep, boys.
That's it.
I'm dealing next round.
You know, there's something
fishy about you, Allen.
I'm fishy? You tried
to murder me in jail.
Well, if you can't play cards
with somebody who tried to murder you,
you'll never play cards in here.
I knew I'd regret
inviting you to this game.
You may be big, but
you got no poker face.
Deuces again?
Okay, I'm out.
- Hey, you can't take that.
- It's my last pudding.
Then you shouldn't have
thrown it in the pot, dumbass.
Dumbass?
Politician who gets
caught with his pants down.
Yeah. I'd say you're a dumbass.
Well, maybe I'll just
take the whole pot then.
- Guys, come on.
- Don't screw with me, Bellows.
Or what? You're gonna shoot me?
That's right. You
only shoot unarmed men.
What the hell are you looking at?
Is that really why you're in here?
You shot an unarmed man?
Yeah, I'm just another bad guy.
Now get the hell out.
If my dad really risked
his life to save yours,
then...
I doubt you're just another bad guy.
Hey...
why don't you just tell
me what really happened?
"Suspect was arrested last night
after a botched robbery.
While attempting to steal
from a Mercury Labs shipping crate,
David P. Ratchet, alias Big Sir,
allegedly shot and
killed a security guard.
An eyewitness called in the shooting."
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you...
"Ratchet was previously
arrested for fighting..."
The only forensic evidence
were bullet casings from the scene
that matched the cartridge
of a gun you owned.
Okay, time to go.
Hey, firearm identification
like that can have errors.
It's practically junk science.
I said, time to go.
You didn't kill that guy, did you?
There was another guy.
My size, my frame.
I heard the shots.
I tried to save the guard.
Wrong place, wrong time.
Why didn't you just tell me that?
'Cause it doesn't matter, Allen!
It didn't matter to the cops,
not to my lawyer, or the jury.
They took one look at me,
and decided I was the guy.
That guy could still be out there.
If I was that guy,
I would've ditched this
crap town a long time ago.
Central City loves her heroes.
And I should know. I'm your new mayor.
But we all agree, doing
business in the city
with meta-humans can be a little risky.
Technology companies in Central City
are robbed at nearly 30
times the national average.
That's second only to Star City, folks.
Which is why I'm proud to unveil
Kord Industries' newest
advanced research facility,
designed to be the most
secure building of its kind,
complete with super-speed
motion detectors,
sonic vibration defenses,
and laser beams that don't freeze.
Believe me, no one is breaking into
this building anytime soon.
I hate this city.
Cecile, hey, babe.
What are you doing here?
Uh, I needed a helper, and,
well, she wanted to help.
Yeah. Cisco said you were working a case
about an R&D lab that vanished.
I figured maybe I could
help dig up some clues,
now that I'm a meta.
Babe, you're not a meta.
I can hear every one of these people.
Dark matter definitely
left its mark here.
I figured as much.
That patrolman, right there,
he is cheating on his wife.
Uh, never trust a
moustache, I always say.
I have a moustache.
No, you have a sexy goatee.
He has a creeper moustache.
Red tie... Oh, baby.
Red tie does not like
his boss very much.
She's been doing this
all the way over here.
- Hm.
- And that lady right there.
Joe? Joe, she is a thief.
Thief!
Staplers, she's been stealing them
out of her office for months now.
She damn near cleaned
out the supply closet.
- Baby?
- Huh?
I love you, and I think it's great
that you have these new powers, but I...
Oh. You want me to go.
Uh, I... I don't...
I don't want you to go.
No-no-no, hey, it's just
'cause you wanna do your job.
I totally get it. Go. Stop crime.
- Love you.
I can hear everyone. It's so fun!
Hey. The closest security cam I can find
is from an ATM across the street.
The footage is choppy, but...
- Look at that.
- Did he just...
Pull a Chevelle out of nowhere.
I'm gonna run those plates,
see if I can get an ID on the dude.
Copy that.
Yes, I'll accept the charges.
Hey, Barry.
So, Barry asked you to ask us
to get this guy out of prison?
Barry had gotten close to this guy,
who says he's innocent.
It was a case of mistaken identity.
Well, from what I could
find out on CCPN's archives,
Big Sir's case does sound a bit suspect.
15 years ago, he was found
guilty of shooting a guard,
but there was no apparent motive.
- Only one eyewitness?
- Mm.
Studies have shown
that lineup composition,
verbal, and non-verbal cues,
can all lead to unintended
false identifications.
Look, this is all just fantastic,
but we're not really gonna do this.
Yeah, I mean, um, we've
already got a lot on our plate
just trying to free one innocent man.
We all want Barry to be free,
but I don't know that there's
much else we can do right now.
We kinda hit a wall.
Well, we're not gonna
get through that wall
- while we're working on this.
- It's just one case.
Yean, and it's a case
that we have to take.
Allen has made one request of us
since he's been incarcerated,
and the request doesn't
even involve himself.
We have to take this case.
It's unsettling how convincing
you can be sometimes.
I got a plate match on the Chevelle.
It's registered to a perp
who has multiple breaking
and entering priors:
Sylbert Rundine.
Why does every villain
in this city have a name
that sounds like it
came out of a comic book?
He must go by something for short.
Syl. Sylbie. Bertie.
What do we wanna do about this case?
Well, my dad, Cisco, and Ralph
are gonna question Rundine,
and I'm gonna call Cecile
and see if she can pull up
the case file on Big Sir.
You won't even have to say it.
Bertie? Were you for real with that?
Yeah, bet you five bucks it's Bertie.
You're on.
Hey.
Allen, you're stirring up my dust.
Oh. Sorry.
Um, I've got some news.
So, I have some friends
that I thought could
help with your case,
and... they've agreed to do it.
CCPD cop friends?
Not exactly,
but, um, if there's anybody
that can prove you
innocent, it's these guys.
'Cause they did a bang-up
job of clearing you.
That's not really...
I mean, my... my case...
Look...
just call them and tell them to stop.
Uh, look, I don't understand
why you're not excited about this.
What you're peddling, it's dangerous.
Wh... what's dangerous?
Hope.
I've been in here long enough
to understand that in prison,
hope is the most dangerous thing.
Wait, did you get that from "Shawshank"?
No.
I got that from being in prison.
Tell your friends...
to stop wasting their time.
Sylbert Rundine!
This is CCPD!
Are you Sylbert Rundine?
Bert... Rundine.
The E's silent.
So close.
I'm Detective Joe West.
These are my associates.
We're looking into a
robbery that took place.
Wanted to ask you some questions.
- Okay?
- Do you own a 1970s Chevelle?
- Well, I used to.
- Oh, my glob.
Is that a replica of DARPA's HTV-3X?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't you know not to mess
with another man's toys?
You mean figurines.
Yes.
Yes, he does.
Wow.
This is a perfect replica.
It even has a tiny automatic
navigation control system!
This is the reason I don't
have any money in my savings.
Oh, I get it.
Is this you?
Yeah, hard to believe.
15 years ago, I was a bit of a gym rat.
Hey, Joe, pretty nice figurine.
Well, gentlemen, I was
just about to head out,
so if you guys are good here...
15 years ago,
did you spend any time
around Mercury Labs?
Cisco! Get us to the alley.
Damn. He wasn't that quick, was he?
You guys check down there,
I'll check the streets.
Okay.
Guys, he's here!
Hey! Hold it right there!
Oh, that feels weird.
Joe, he's getting away!
Seems we've got bigger problems.
- This is...
- Ridiculous.
You okay, guys?
Are we doing okay?
Does it look like we're doing okay?
We're two inches tall, Caitlin!
Yeah, I'm, like, Cisco's size now.
Is this how you always see the world?
Oh, that's really funny, man.
I guess your body just
finally shrunk down
to a size that's
proportional to your brain!
Ralph, have you tried just
stretching back to normal size?
Uh...
Ah! Oh! My back! Jeez Louise!
Okay, you know what, maybe
I can breach us out of here.
Really thought, uh...
I was gonna go farther than that.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Four fingers.
You're no less annoying at that size.
Hey, guys, I think I got something.
So, I wasn't able to pin
Ray Palmer or the Waverider,
but I was able to reach Felicity.
So, Ray uses dwarf star alloy
to power the shrinking capabilities
in the A.T.O.M. suit,
but on October 10th,
Palmer Tech's last depository of alloy
was stolen from Central City's facility.
October 10th,
that's the day Barry came
out of the Speed Force.
So he hits the facility,
then he hops on the bus.
So, dwarf star alloy plus dark matter
equals Rundine's shrinking powers?
N... not exactly. Nature
doesn't work to scale.
If the human body were to shrink,
we can't lift our skeleton.
So, Rundine's power
must be able to shrink
the space between atomic bonds.
Miniaturize tech so you can steal it,
and then make it big so you can sell it.
- Hey.
- Ratchet's trial records.
- Oh.
You really think the guy
who shrunk that building
is the same guy we need
to free Barry's friend?
Well... I mean, look.
Be easy to mistake them, right?
I mean, they certainly
had a resemblance.
Rundine hit up a warehouse
a month after they picked up Big Sir.
Still, that's a big coincidence.
I keep saying it:
There's no coincidences
when it comes to DeVoe,
and that includes Barry's cellmate.
Well, I can't sell that to a judge,
so if we wanna get Big Sir out,
we are gonna need a
confession from Dr. Shrinker.
Dwarfstar!
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's what I'm
naming him, see, Dwarfstar.
Oh, God.
Oh, it takes a long time to breach here.
Who spit gum on the floor?
I'm a gum-shoe!
Not gum on a shoe!
Oh, my God, get him off, get him off.
You guys are going in the hamster cage.
Hamster cage?
Eh, don't drop me. Don't drop me.
Harry...
this is not your fault.
Yeah, but it kinda i...
Don't read my mind, okay?
- What am I thinking now?
- Oh, God.
Great. Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go build a reverse
polarity dwarfstar matrix.
Great name, Ray Palmer.
What, was electron-degenerate
sub-atomizer taken?
Electron-de...
Oh, you have no idea what
Harry was talking about,
or what anyone around
here is ever talking about.
I gotta call Barry.
Okay.
I can hear you, Iris,
and there is nothing
wrong with me and Joe.
Right, yes, totally.
It's just that if you ever,
you know, think there
is something wrong,
I... I know someone who could help.
That's all.
I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
Thank you for seeing us on short notice.
- Lucky us.
- Of course.
The reason that we're here today is,
I've been experiencing some
unusual pregnancy symptoms.
You know, the first time I was pregnant,
it was a really long time ago,
and things were very
different at that point...
"Eggs, bread, olive oil"...
I'm sorry, are you...
Are you making a grocery list?
Of course not.
I would not do...
So... tell me more about
the... the symptoms you're experiencing.
It's... it's almost as if
I have become aware
of Joe's thoughts.
- Like... like I read his diary.
- My diary?
Your pregnancy made
you read Joe's diary?
What do you mean you're taking his side?
I don't take sides.
You just think that I'm in the wrong.
I would never think...
- Maybe this was a bad idea.
- No-no-no, no-no-no, babe.
No, we're not... We're not done here.
Therapy scares you,
and you don't like this woman
hearing all your business.
Cecile... I... that just...
That... that's not true.
And now you just wanna go.
You think this whole
thing is a waste of time?
Cecile, stop.
You're thinking about a
pink elephant over and over?
You're trying to block me out.
Can I just ask one question...
Really? A pink elephant?
Why were you hiding
your thoughts from me?
Because you're making me do it.
Wh...
Cecile, when we got back
together, I promised you
that I would never keep
any secrets from you again.
Except now, it...
It's like I have to.
Hey. They found him.
His name's Sylbert Rundine.
He's been arrested for a whole
bunch of crimes like yours,
and he used to look just like you too.
You're getting out of here.
Wow. You have a hard shoulder.
So, yesterday, I tell you what happened,
and today, you find the guy.
- It happened in a...
- Flash?
Snap.
You cops and your blinders.
Probably got the wrong guy again.
Well... technically, they
haven't gotten him yet.
You see? Something always goes wrong.
Why do you have to make this so hard?
It... it's okay to believe.
Yeah?
Why is it so easy for you to believe?
You know my dad was in here
for a crime he didn't commit, right?
Do you know what happened?
After 17 years,
the man that killed my mom confessed.
My dad got to go home.
Why shouldn't you get to go home too?
- 17 years, huh?
- Yeah.
You think they'll catch Rundine?
You really think it's gonna happen?
I promise.
You're getting out.
So, in hindsight,
I can see how putting
you guys in a hamster cage
could be humiliating.
- You think?
- I'm sorry for that.
For the record, this is awesome,
but why do you guys have
a giant LEGO set anyway?
It is a three-dimensional model
of the place where I was predestined
to be brutally murdered
by a twisted future version of Barry.
That guy.
But what a difference... a year makes.
Whoa.
What did you do to my bazooka?
Well, I turned your bazooka
into an embiggening bazooka,
with the help of the dwarfstar alloy
we stole from Rundine's apartment,
and improving upon Ray
Palmer's amateurish schematics,
presto-chango, embiggening bazooka.
Now, if you'll just hold on...
Whoa, whoa-whoa-whoa,
we're gonna do this now?
Well, yeah.
Rundine's in the wind.
These two are small. We
need to embiggen them,
and we need to free
an innocent man, so...
Okay, first of all,
"embiggen" is not a word,
and second of all,
shouldn't we test this first?
Hey!
I'll be a test subject!
Come on! Take me!
- Sure, why not?
- That's the spirit.
Here... here we go. And...
- West?
- Hm?
You should probably, um...
Oh, God, yeah. Sorry.
And... three, two, one.
Nope. Still tiny.
Hey, are we supposed to be doing that?
- Oh, no.
- Their cells are exploding.
Whatever that embiggening
gun did to Ralph and Cisco
seems to have destabilized
them on an atomic level.
How long do they have?
At this rate, I would guess
complete cellular explosion
within... ten hours.
Oh, man, prison pudding
is so much better than outside pudding.
Obviously.
Any news from your friend?
Um, no, not yet,
but they're probably just
busy tracking Rundine.
Seasoned criminal like that
knows how to not be found, you know?
Yeah, I get it, man.
Hey, um...
you have any plans for when you get out?
You know, I really haven't
thought about it very much.
Oh, come on, you've gotta have something
that you've dreamed of,
like opening a business
or, uh, climbing to the
top of Mount Everest,
- bungee jumping.
- This ain't the movies, Allen.
- This is real life, man...
- I...
Reality is, I ain't got nobody or nothing
waiting for me on the outside,
and even if I do get out,
I'll probably end up
at the docks anyway.
Okay, look, I spent most of my life
in love with a girl who
was way out of my league.
Now she's my wife.
Sometimes, things do end
up like in the movies.
Jiaju.
- Come again?
- Jiaju.
Tiny village in China.
Beautiful place. Very secluded.
Monks all take a vow of silence.
Inmate Allen...
a word?
- Yeah.
I see you've made a new friend.
Yeah. I guess I have.
I find that interesting,
especially since I was
just asked to turn over
Inmate Ratchet's case file
to the D.A. who represented
you for your trial.
Coincidence?
Not everyone that's in
here deserves to be in here.
You ever heard of the name Aaron Miller?
- No.
- Miller was a prisoner here
who took to studying at the law library.
One day, Mr. Miller decided to take on
the appeal of a fellow inmate's case.
When he was invariably unsuccessful,
that fellow inmate...
stabbed Mr. Miller to death.
Your friend may look like a man,
but he is unquestionably a monster.
Everyone here is a monster.
And if you insist on
continuing to bait them,
I guarantee you,
you will get mauled.
All right, coming in hot.
Oh, hey, you didn't have to do all that.
Listen, I did not inherit my
dad's skills in the kitchen,
but a decaf herbal tea, that I can do.
So, if it's okay with you,
I just was wondering if I
could talk to you about Joe.
Um, yeah. Of course it's okay.
Oh, no, honey, it's...
it's not about that.
We have zero problems
in that department,
as you can tell.
Okay.
TMI, but okay.
I really thought being
able to read his mind
would make our relationship
stronger, not push us apart.
Well, how does my dad feel
about your new powers?
He thinks it's gonna take
a little getting used to.
Yeah, but how does he feel?
Look, we all know that my dad thinks
that he's this cool,
grounded man of mystery,
but we all know that
he's actually just...
- A big softie.
But if you really want
to get closer to my dad,
you need to stop focusing
on what he's thinking
and find out what he's feeling.
Maybe we could use a
biochemical treatment
and target the pituitary glands?
Flood them with human growth hormones?
No, that will just accelerate their d...
It'll make things worse.
- Guys?
- What?
- Yeah?
- Guys!
- What?
Little Ralphie needs
to use little boys room.
Didn't you just go?
My bladder is literally the size
of a hummingbird's right now.
Come on, Caitlin.
Help a wee fellow take a wee-wee?
- Can you...
- Me?
Well, I'm not touching him.
Fine, I'll take you there,
but you have to find your own way out.
Thank you.
Could've just gone in the bushes.
Gross.
The embiggening bazooka
made us unstable, didn't it?
Yeah... no. What? No!
Wh... why would you say that?
I can see it all over your face.
- What?
- Your face is huge.
I'm watching your emotions on IMAX.
Yeah. Yeah, this...
This was supposed to
be an easy W, all right?
An easy victory.
All we had to do was capture Rundine.
Couldn't even do that for Allen.
- Okay, so, you tried.
- Yeah, and I failed,
because I'm stupid... all right?
Too stupid to help Allen's friend,
too stupid to fix you, or
too stupid to stop DeVoe.
Ow! Wh... what was that for?
Believe me, I'd punch
you in the arm if I could.
Ah!
Look, I know you're not
used to going up against
someone you can't outsmart, like DeVoe,
but you really are stupid
if you think you're too stupid.
You wanna help Barry?
You wanna free him?
Get out of your own way and unshrink us.
You weren't shrunk, all right?
That's not how his
powers work! His powers...
Work by not just...
removing the space between the atoms,
but also taking out
the gravity particles
and the dark energy,
so that when he embiggens an object...
He's refilling it with
the same combination
- of energy he extracted.
- Yes.
Harry... if you wanna fix us...
We need to put you back
in Rundine's line of fire.
Central City's Weather Services Agency
is always on the cutting-edge
of radar technology,
which is why I'm so excited
to show you the newest addition
to our stationary airship fleet.
Now, let's go take a closer look.
What do you mean we only have
20 minutes until we explode?
Actually, it's only 18 minutes
before your equilibrium
totally destabilizes.
You're gonna blow up
in under 20 minutes,
unless we re-expose you to
Rundine's energy blasts, okay?
Okay, so a facial recognition
just picked him up at
Weather Services Airfield.
I think he's trying to skip town.
Okay, I'm gonna stay here
and try and figure out a cure.
Hey. Sir, you need to leave.
The museum is closing for the day.
I know.
I just thought this would
look great on my shelf.
Red alert! Red alert! Everyone evacuate!
Gotta go faster. We gotta go faster.
Do you wanna drive this thing?
Kinda do. Ramon, remember,
when Rundine tries to shrink the van,
you've got to get in
the path of his blast.
- Do you understand?
- Copy that.
We're heading into the hanger now.
Uh, guys?
I think he sees us.
You're not getting big again.
I'll go left, you go right!
Harry, try flanking him.
We're gonna come around the other side.
Copy that.
Evasive maneuvers! Evasive maneuvers!
I know, I'm doing it.
Oh, boy.
We've gotta figure out how
to get him to fire at us.
- Abort!
- Ah!
- We're going too fast.
- Think light thoughts.
I'm thinking how you
nearly got us killed.
Think lighter!
Snow, tell me you got something.
The cure is not done yet.
Only one minute till
the boys go nuclear.
- I don't want to explode.
- What do we do?
We go to plan B.
I'm gonna shrink you down
to the subatomic level, boy.
Oh, is that right?
I'd like to see you try.
I'm big again!
Remind me to never again breach into
any of Harry's stankin' ass pockets!
Hey. Sorry again about stepping on you.
Hey, you saved me a
trip to the chiropractor.
Yeah, I guess so.
You did it.
Yeah, I guess I did.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
one will be provided for you.
Hands behind your back.
Rundine...
15 years ago,
did you rob a Mercury Labs warehouse?
Give us your confession now,
and I guarantee the
D.A. will cut you a deal.
Mercury Labs...
That's the one that
Ratchet got fingered for.
I laughed so hard when
that guy got arrested.
You want a confession?
Find a priest.
I'd rather rot.
Yeah, all right. Thanks.
Hey, Joe, just hold
on a second, all right?
Ain't good news, is it?
Rundine won't confess.
My friends tried everything,
I mean, the... the D.A. offered
every deal she could, but...
I'm so sorry, man.
Look, you were right
about everything in here.
You know, I-I made you a promise and...
I let you down.
You damn idiot.
You did not let me down.
I forgot what hope felt like.
It's not a bad thing.
I'll see around, kid.
Hey, sorry.
It's okay, Bar.
I just wanna thanks for trying, you know,
and I'm sorry to send
you on this goose chase.
Barry, that place you're
in is full of walls.
When you hit one of those walls,
you find a way to get through it.
Don't lose your faith.
There's too many people counting on you,
out here and in there.
Yeah.
_
Nope.
Nobody leaves until
we're both good again.
Okay.
What do you want from me, Cecile?
I wanna know why me having these powers
is so upsetting to you.
You have the power. Just read my mind.
Uh-uh, no, no-no, me
reading your thoughts
is what got us into all of this.
I want to know how you feel.
Cecil, you being able
to read my... thoughts,
it...
It makes me feel vulnerable
in a way that I don't like,
you being able to hear every scared...
dumb thought of mine.
I just don't...
want you seeing me like that.
But I would never think less of you
for the thoughts that cross your mind.
How could you not?
Okay...
Joe, your grandma Esther's
noodles, they taste terrible.
Uh, no, they are terrible.
That woman had no business
ever messing with the wok.
Wow, okay. Wow.
And I think that I have
been using semi-colons wrong
for my entire life,
which leads me to believe
that I don't even know what
a semi-colon actually is.
Also, I would like to buy a
new pair of pants, 'cause...
But I haven't yet, 'cause I'm
afraid to go into the store,
'cause I think the
salesperson is gonna judge me,
because, truthfully, even I think
that I am just a little bit crazy
for having another baby at this age.
Oh, baby...
You're not crazy.
That speech you just
gave w... was a little...
You're not.
Those were my scared, dumb,
vulnerable thoughts.
You think any less of me?
- Of course not.
- Mm-mm.
Look...
I can't promise you that I'm
gonna stop reading your mind.
I... I don't even really
know how this all works yet.
But I can promise you
that nothing you ever think
will change my opinion of you.
And even when you're not thinking it,
I know...
that you are the brave, brilliant...
Devastatingly handsome man that I love,
and the one thought I
hear you have the most
is that you love me too.
And I do.
Yeah.
Well, based on my scans,
Ralph and Cisco's cells
have reformed and restabilized.
I can attest my bladder is
completely back to normal.
Fourth Big Gulp today.
I miss when we could just pick him up
and carry him out of the room. Right?
Hey, uh, you just
passed up a dig at Dibny.
Sure you're all right?
You know, we reopen a case
against an innocent man,
and, oh, somehow stumble
upon the actual culprit,
a culprit who, by the
way, has meta-human powers
that we are partially
responsible for, it's...
It's like you said:
There are no coincidences
when it comes to DeVoe
and these bus metas.
What's DeVoe doing?
What's his... motive?
Does he want Sylbert
Rundine incarcerated?
Or to have Big Sir set free?
Or for Cisco and I to become
itty-bitty meta-humans?
Well, whatever his plan is,
we'll figure it out.
- We're gonna stop him.
- And bring Barry home.
And bring Barry home.
On your feet, Inmate.
Is there a problem, Warden?
As you know, Inmate Ratchet
mysteriously disappeared last night.
Where do you think he went?
Well, I couldn't say.
In an effort to locate Inmate Ratchet,
I reviewed the security camera footage.
Did you know the oscillating cameras
aren't the only ones in this wing? Hm?
Once you started stroking
Inmate Ratchet's hopes of freedom,
I had a camera installed
right by your cell...
And when I checked that camera,
I learned who you truly are.
Um, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Then let me be specific.
You are the Flash.
There's no use denying
it or trying to run.
You're clearly already
feeling the effects of
the drug cocktail I put in
that snack you so seem to enjoy.
Why? Why would you do this?
I did warn you...
Everyone in here is a monster.
That'll be all.
You said to call you when
I was ready to do business.
Hello, Warden.
Do you have another fish to sell me?
I do...
and it's a big one.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --