- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly,
with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one fast
enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
To be able to control
the weather like that indoors.
- He'd have to be
a weather wizard.
- This is Sherloque.
- He's the greatest detective
in all the multiverse.
- I'm here to catch
your killer.
- The only part
of the satellite
that would have dark matter
levels that high...
- Is the core, which is where
Cicada's dagger came from.
- We got a list from FEMA
of everyone
who reported injuries
the night of the Enlightenment.
- Two of them are twins
whose father is deceased,
third is a ten-year-old girl
by the name of Grace Gibbons.
- So if my dad's right
and Cicada's a father, then...
- We may have just found
his daughter.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Excuse me, could you tell me
where Grace Gibbons' room is?
- One sec, let me check.
Actually, yeah,
she's that first room
right on the right.
- Great.
- Just where do you think
you're going?
Into my patient's room
is what I looks like.
- I'm sorry.
I am Barry Allen.
I'm with the CCPD.
I was hoping to speak
with you, actually.
I'm looking
for Grace Gibbons' parents.
Specifically her father.
- I'm sorry, but the girl's
parents are deceased.
- Are you sure about that?
- I can show you her charts.
See for yourself.
She came in with
a wave of new admissions.
No legal guardian listed,
no next of kin.
The sad truth is,
our staff is the only family
this little girl has left.
- Okay.
Thank you for your help.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[knocking at door]
- Orlin Dwyer,
are you in there?
It's CCPD.
Open up.
Orlin Dwyer?
- Hey, listen, man,
I don't care
what that guy says,
he was drunk
and I was defending...
- This is about your sister,
Mr. Dwyer.
There's been an accident,
a meta attack.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Careful.
- I know, I know.
- This is a critical time.
- Okay.
- Steady hands.
- Yeah.
Call time of death.
- It's okay.
It's a pie.
It's not supposed to be
a piece of cake.
- Wow.
[laughs]
Hey, thanks for helping.
With Cicada's trail
running cold,
at least we have the extra day
to prepare
for our first Thanksgiving
at the loft.
- What about Joe and Cecile?
- They're celebrating
with Cecile's family this year.
So, yeah, this year it's just
gonna be the five of us.
- I'm down.
- Six, actually.
Killer Frost just RSVP'd.
- What...you guys can just talk
to each other now,
even without the mental
activity dampener?
- Yeah, today's actually
the first time.
- Wow.
[laughter]
- Oh, gosh.
Hi, guys.
- Yo.
- Sorry we're late.
It seems like
everyone and their grandma
is getting
pre-holiday manis and pedis.
- Ooh, let's take photos
and post them
on that old-fashioned Insta
thingy that you guys use.
- [grunts]
- Those two seemed to have
really patched things up.
- Yeah, Nora's getting closer
to Iris than she is with me,
and the timing couldn't have
been better.
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
Nora was so young
when I disappeared in
her future,
so this would be her
first memory of Thanksgiving
with both her parents.
Feel like it's my job
to make it
the most perfect
Thanksgiving ever,
- And #HandModels.
- Wow, I feel famous already.
Oh, man.
Mom, um...
I'm sorry.
- Sorry for what, Nora?
- For not giving you a chance
to show me how great you are.
This year I'm just really
thankful to get to know you.
The real you.
- I'm thankful too.
You know, the West-Allens have
never missed a Thanksgiving.
No guerrilla army,
no evil speedster,
no giant wormhole in the sky
could break that streak.
- Yeah, the singularity.
So the Flash Museum has
a 3-D model of Dad
just running straight into it
to save the city.
God, it must have been so epic
to be there.
- Actually, it was...
terrifying to be there.
We didn't know if your dad
was gonna come back.
[somber music]
Ronnie didn't.
- What?
The museum says that...
that Dad just saved everybody.
- I guess there's things
the museum left out.
Like your Dad giving himself
to the Speed Force
to save the city.
That was another time we said
good-bye thinking...
might be a one-way trip.
- Sounds a lot like what took
him from us in the future.
I didn't know Dad had
so many close calls.
- Look, your dad
is always gonna
wanna put his life
on the line for others.
That is what I love most
about him,
but, yeah, it...it
does keep me up at night.
- Did he come back?
- No, the records I falsified
convinced him for now.
- So we're safe?
- Orlin, I think you need
to stay away.
- Good idea.
I won't visit till
after the weekend.
- No, I think you need to stay
away for good.
It's getting too risky.
- You want me to give up Grace?
No, no, no, listen,
you can't put me on hold.
I don't care about
this next of kin crap.
I don't want this kid.
Hello?
[groans]
Damn it.
Hey...
what?
- It's breakfast.
- Yeah, it is.
Um...
Okay.
[sighs]
Now look, it's only
a few days old.
It's still good, I swear.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffs]
[cans clatter]
- I don't understand.
Explain again to me
what the difference
between this day
and every other day
in America?
- It's a holiday
when we all get together
and celebrate
and eat a ton of food.
Like, a gross amount.
- Again, what the difference
between this day
and every other day in America.
- That's legit.
- Hi, guys.
What's going on?
- This guy,
he try to explain
the Thanksgiving holiday.
He's failing miserably.
What is this holiday?
Please explain.
- It's very simple, actually.
It's just about getting
together to celebrate
our loved ones and family.
- So simple, this is why I
don't understand this holiday.
I don't have any family.
- Didn't you have, like,
seven marriages?
- I did have seven marriages.
Five wives, seven marriages,
but no family.
This holiday
is a cruel holiday.
[alarms blaring]
- What's going on?
- I'm seeing a massive
electrical surge
at the downtown power station.
- Barry, Nora, you're up.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Guys, what's the problem?
Everything looks...
[both scream]
- I think we found it.
- It's lightning.
- Skies were clear
a minute ago. That storm must
have come out of nowhere.
- Uh, we got a bigger problem.
There's an experimental
cold fusion core
from Mercury Labs in the plant,
and if it blows...
- Iris:It could take out
the whole block.
- I see it.
[lightning crackles]
- Nora, you've got to evac all
the workers to safety. Barry...
- Yeah, I know,
I got to grab the core.
- No, no, no,
something doesn't feel right.
- Just listen to Iris.
Grab the workers from inside.
[lightning crackling]
♪ ♪
[groans]
- Dad!
Dad!
[crying] You guys,
he's not breathing.
- He's going into
cardiac arrest.
She needs to restart his heart.
- What...how do I do that?
- Rub your hands together
to create lightning,
and then give him
a chest compression.
- [breathing rapidly]
Okay! Okay.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
It's not working!
[sobbing]
- We lost him.
- No! No!
[crying] No!
[grunts]
Please. Please. Please.
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[both panting]
- He's back.
- [crying]
- [breathing harshly]
- I promise I'm okay.
- Caitlin.
- His vitals are stable.
Speed healing to the rescue.
- He shouldn't have
needed rescuing.
- Nora, I know you're upset,
but if that core would
have exploded
it would have caused
a lot of damage.
- It did cause a lot of damage.
Dad died.
- We made the best decision we
could, given the circumstances.
- Maybe someone else should be
making our decisions.
- Wow, all right, well,
so much for mother-daughter
holiday time.
- She did just have to bring me
back to life.
Let's give her a minute.
- Okay.
- In the meantime,
where did that storm come from?
- A storm like that coming
and going,
disappearing in a matter
of minutes,
it shouldn't be possible.
- Unless someone was making
it possible.
I mean, we've seen that before.
- Weather Wizard.
But Mark Mardon is serving
a life sentence
at Iron Heights.
- Let's make sure he's doing
just that.
Let us know if any other
weather anomalies
pop up on the radar.
- Okay.
Will do.
[playfully tense music]
♪ ♪
I think it's time for
operation: Save the Turkey.
[opera music]
♪ ♪
- What...?
- Art is therapy.
- So, Sherlock...
- Sherloque,
simple pronunciation.
- We heard what you had to say
about not having a family.
- Right.
- And we here at Team Flash are
sort of a family, and you're
becoming part of that family,
so we would like to invite you
to celebrate
Thanksgiving with us.
- Caitlin, I'm afraid that
I must decline, all right?
Because I don't have a lot
of reason to celebrate,
and you of all people should
sympathize with that.
- Why should I sympathize?
- You lost your father, right?
And then you find him
only to discover that his body
is being possessed
by a icicle demon
who's trying to kill
all of Team Flash,
yourself included.
Not great, right?
- Okay, that's enough,
Debbie Downer.
Don't listen.
You know what?
Maybe you should lay off
the paint fumes.
- Do you know what,
young Ralph Macchio?
You have nothing
to celebrate either, right?
What your last year has been,
huh?
Let me recap for you.
First, heartbreak.
[imitates breaking heart,
sobs mockingly]
And then second,
Cicada crushes your powers
forcing you to fake
your own death,
also not great, and as for me,
multiple divorces have left me
with a mountain of debt
that's insurmountable.
So this past year, not been
very kind to any of us.
Pardon.
[operatic musical finish]
[soft, tense music]
♪ ♪
- She's had a few recent
outbursts,
and we don't allow
cursing here.
This type of behavior
cannot continue.
Anyway, that's the long
and short of it.
I'll give you two a moment.
[door opens]
- You called a kid
a rat bastard?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know
you can't go around
saying stuff like that?
- Why?
- Well, 'cause
then I get a phone call.
You know, I had to take off
work to come down here.
- You don't even like your job.
- What?
- You stay on the couch
all day,
and then when work calls
you curse and slam the door.
"Rat bastards."
- Look,
I get where you heard it.
All right, but you can't say
those words.
- Rat bastard!
- Hey, quit it.
- Stop.
- Rat bastards!
- Hey, listen to me!
I'm supposed to be
the parent here.
- No, you're not a parent!
Parents are supposed to make
the world better for their kids.
You make everything worse.
I hate you,
and you hate you too.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- You have to excuse
our dim lighting.
Today's storm out
at the power plant
knocked out our main generator,
So we're working off a backup
for the time being.
- So does that mean
you can't dampen
the meta prisoner's powers?
- Prison-wide dampeners
are down,
but we got every inmate
into meta cuffs incident free.
I hope you include that in your
article about our readiness.
After the corruption
of the last warden,
I am eager to assure the public
that their safety
is in good hands.
Now, our CSI's, which inmate
did you need to see?
- And he's been here all day?
- Never once out of our sight.
- There was a crime
committed today
with an MO similar
to Mardon's.
Can I take a look
at the security tapes?
- Anything for our friends
in the press.
- Well, this is a bust.
- Yeah, looks like you died
for nothing.
- Nora, hey, hey, look.
This has been a rough day
for you,
but you can't blame Iris
for what happened.
She's doing the best she can.
Besides,
we both decided on the plan.
- Oh, I know.
[metal shuddering]
- What the...?
[whooshing]
[all groan]
- Hey, don't mind me.
I'm just here to pick up
my dad.
- Did she say "dad"?
- Joslyn?
- [sighs]
It's Joss.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Bring me my father!
Now!
- Yeah, that's not
gonna happen.
- We'll see about that.
Bring my dad to Porter Plaza
in one hour,
or Central City is gonna
get wrecked.
♪ ♪
- I didn't know that Joslyn
was busting me out.
I didn't know she'd do
half the things she does.
I haven't spoken to her
in years.
- And you expect me
to believe she woke up
this morning and was like,
[high-pitched] "You know what?
I wanna break my dad
out of Iron Heights."
- [laughs]
I get it, but it's the truth.
Joss was born when me and her
mom were still in high school.
I never could work out
how to be with that woman.
Then when Joss came I thought
the best thing to do
was to focus on my career.
- Your criminal career?
- That's why I left her
with her mom.
Least until she ran away
because of some falling out.
- What happened with Joss
and her mom?
- The last time I spoke to her
she told me that her and Joss
are broken.
You know how it is.
Sometimes mothers
and daughters break
and there ain't no fixing 'em.
[wind whistling]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, watch your step.
And open your eyes.
- Whose house is this?
- It's my cousin Robbie's.
He doesn't live here anymore,
but he said
if I fix it up,
we could stay here.
- What's this?
- That is a dollhouse.
Or it can be
once we build it,
and, you know, you can...
Pick out furniture, and colors,
or wall paper,
decorate it how you want.
Hey...
I know we didn't get off
to the greatest start
these past few months.
Okay...
it was a lousy start.
But I want to fix all that.
Well, I was thinking that
while I work on this place,
we could work
on this one too... together.
Listen, you were right, kid.
I do hate me.
I don't really know
any other way to be,
but I want to do right by you,
Gracie.
I want to keep you safe,
and warm, fed...
You know, just...
give you all the things
a kid should have.
- Let's start with
the dollhouse.
- Okay.
Okay.
- How's Dad's interrogation
going?
- Well, we'll know in a minute.
Hopefully, he'll find something
that'll help us profile
Mardon's daughter.
- Okay, well, let me know.
- Nora, look, listen,
I know you're upset with me
for sending your dad
into that situation earlier,
and I just...
I wanted to say that I...
- Mom, it's okay.
I'm not upset with you.
- You're not?
- No, we're good.
I-I promise.
- Okay, cool.
- That's the other thing,
celebrating the decimation
of an indigenous culture
so a bunch of greedy colonizers
can get their turkey-lurkey on.
Do you know about this?
Do you know about the sham?
The sham we call
"Thanksgiving."
- Okay, I'm sorry,
am I missing something?
Since when did you guys become
anti-Thanksgiving?
- Since a bunch of guys wearing
hat-buckles
fed us some old bull,
wrapped in lies,
stuffed in propaganda.
It's a deception Turducken.
- Actually,
I think the hat-buckles
weren't real either.
- Don't encourage him.
- You get it.
- Okay.
Did you get anything
from Mardon?
- No, nothing that'll help us
find his daughter.
What about you guys?
What'd you dig up?
- Meet Joss Jackam.
She is a delinquent teen
turned amateur storm chaser.
A self-taught expert
in theoretical meteorology.
- How do we know
she's a storm chaser?
'Cause Helen Hunt
here has a blog.
- Mm-hmm. She lost her grant
from the Science Center
for doing too many dangerous
experiments on the weather.
- Well, look like she's way
beyond the experimental phase.
- Ooh, Weather Witch?
- I'll allow it.
- Dad, that weathervane,
doesn't it look a lot like...
- The staff she was carrying,
yeah.
Cisco, can you pull up
the security footage
from her attack
on Iron Heights?
- Sure can.
- It's infected
with a satellite shard.
She's got meta-tech.
- Like Spencer Young's phone.
- Look, she has instant
lightning on command.
There's no way
you're gonna be able
to get that staff from her.
She's gonna have
to give it up willingly.
- Okay, listen,
we got 20 minutes
before she destroys
the entire city,
so what is the plan?
- We only have one choice.
We give her what she wants.
- No Weather Witch in sight.
- Okay,
Singh cleared the perimeter,
so it's free of civilians.
- And our satellites
are on weather watch
for our Weather Witch.
Nothing yet.
- What?
I wouldn't say nothing.
My data leaves me to conclude
that there is
artificially-created
pressure system
of uncertain origin
headed rapidement
toward the downtown core.
- Listen, Galileo,
you can lick your finger
and stick it in the wind
all you want.
Why don't you leave
the actual calculations
to actual compu...
oh, for Christ's sake.
- And your exasperation
leads me also to conclude
that you have realized,
although late,
that once again I'm right.
I'm right. I'm right.
I'm right. I'm right...
[bangs keyboard]
- That's enough out of you.
[thunder booms]
- She's here.
So the rotten apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
- You're a poet.
Awesome.
Where's my dad?
[suspenseful music]
- All right, Joss, we held up
our end of the bargain.
You got your dad.
There's no reason
to hurt anybody...
- Ah, so boring. Come on.
We'll handle it from here.
Hey, baby girl.
- Dad.
- That's a pretty cool staff.
Would you just...how about
you just power
that thing off for a sec
and let your dad try.
- Try this.
[thunder booms]
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- Oh, no. [screams]
- Oh.
- [breathing harshly]
Oh, oh, don't feel bad.
He was a selfish dick
who abandoned his family.
Anyway, thanks for helping me
drop a truck on my dad.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [glitch stuttering]
Uh...guys?
What now?
I didn't see the hummer coming.
- I'm so pissed!
This city will drown,
crumble, burn,
because of you!
♪ ♪
- Thanks.
[groans]
I'm gonna follow her.
- Wait, are you serious
right now?
- What?
- You almost just died.
Again, and you don't
seem to care.
- Where is this coming from?
You know how dangerous
our job is.
- Yeah, but I don't want
to lose you again,
but you don't seem to give
a damn if you lose me,
and...and all for your job.
- Nora.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- How long you been holding
that one in?
- My best guess...
my whole life.
Growing up without you,
I was so angry...
but you were my hero, so...
it was easier to put my anger
for you not being around
on criminals
and meta-villains...
a lot of times on Mom.
But when I saw you die today
it reminded me that
I'm mad at someone else
about losing you...
you.
♪ ♪
- I get it.
It's not easy having a parent
who puts their life on the line
for others.
I remember feeling
the same way about Joe
being a cop when I was a kid.
- No, it's not the same thing.
Did he ever have to say
good-bye to you knowing
that he wasn't coming back?
You did...
and you're gonna do it again.
- Nora, you got to remember
you're talking about
a future that we might be able
to avoid.
We still have time to find
our way to a solution,
and we will.
- But there is a solution.
It's just one
that you don't want.
Give up being The Flash.
Come on.
It's the only way to guarantee
that you won't disappear again
in the future,
or any other time.
- Nora.
- Come on. Think about it.
You're not the only hero.
Let the others protect
the world.
You don't have to keep
sacrificing yourself.
You give your life
again and again.
How many times
does it have to be you?
It hurt so much
losing you
when I didn't even know you,
but now
after all of these months
getting to know you I just...
please, Dad, don't make me go
through it again.
I don't want to go through
it again.
[sobbing softly]
- Nora, people need The Flash.
- I need my dad.
♪ ♪
- This is the third ice cream
of the day, you know?
Something fishy's going
on here.
- Okay, you got me.
We're celebrating
because this is
a very special day.
One year ago today,
I made you a promise
that I would turn
my life around
and make things better for you.
I can honestly say
that my life
is a million times better
than what it was.
And it's all because of you,
Gracie.
So I got you something.
- It's the set I wanted.
- I thought your little
dollhouse could use a family.
I already have one.
- I love you, kiddo.
- Purple.
- You know, I think four
ice creams in a day
would be the...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
[explosions booming,
glass shattering]
[panicked screams]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Gracie, run.
Run. Run. Come on!
Go this way!
[debris whizzing]
[groans]
[overlapping shouting]
[raspy breathing]
Help me!
Help me, please!
- Sir.
- Somebody!
- [gasps]
- Save her, please.
- Get him on a table.
- [groaning]
- Move!
- [raspy voice] Gracie...
[groans]
Help her...
- On the eve of Thanksgiving,
reports of devastating
weather phenomena
are streaming in
from all over the city.
The exact cause of these
disturbances remains unknown.
- I can't believe
she's actually willing
to level the city
to kill one man.
- She doesn't know
where Mardon is.
It's overkill, but it's
the only option we've left her.
- Well, Caitlin's on radar,
and Cisco's trying
to juice the satellites,
but there's interference.
We can't locate Joss.
You okay?
Look, babe,
you're gonna find the words
to make her understand.
I know it.
- Not sure I have the words
to make myself understand.
She's got a point.
- [sighs]
[alarms blaring]
[dramatic music]
We got a hit on Joss.
She's at
Sheldon County Airport.
Barry, you got to move.
[electricity crackling]
[panicked screams]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
- You're good?
- Barry, do you have eyes
on Joss?
- No, she's damaged
the terminal so badly
the hangar's the
only safe place.
I'm evacuating everyone
trapped on the tarmac.
- I think I can bring
Frost out.
What can we do?
- Flood control
down at the Marina.
- Guys, how do we fight
weather?
- We fight weather
with weather.
- [snaps fingers]
Nora.
We still have
Mardon's weather wand.
I need you to get it
from the archives
and take it to Barry, okay?
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Mardon's wand?
- Cisco says you can use it
to counteract Joss's weather.
Where is she?
[lightning crackles]
- Last chance.
Where's my Dad?
- Joss, you know
we can't give him up.
- Then you know
what happens next.
- Joss, I deceived you, okay?
Not them.
You want make someone pay,
it's me.
- This is how you make
heroes pay!
[dramatic music]
[lightning crackling]
♪ ♪
- By the beard of Zeus,
she's making
a tornado out of lightning.
- Cisco, how do I use this wand
to stop this?
- You can attract
all the lightning to the wand.
That'll take down the tornado,
but all that energy
will go through your body.
You'll be a human
lightning rod.
- It's okay.
I know you have to go.
Run, Dad.
Run!
♪ ♪
- Back.
Everybody, back.
- [grunting]
- [screams]
[yells]
[thunder rumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
[ethereal music]
- Barry?
Nora, do you see him?
♪ ♪
- I, uh...
I...
- [breathing harshly]
- I see him.
He's still here.
[applause]
- We live in a world
full of meta-phones
and meta-weathervanes.
What's next?
My electric toothbrush?
- Till we figure out
how to remove those shards,
better safe than sorry.
- Yeah.
- Well, now that Mardon
and his daughter
are all tucked away
in Iron Heights.
What do you say we spend
some time with our own family?
- Well, might just be
us and Nora this year.
Caitlin and Cisco
are skipping Thanksgiving.
- What? Why?
- Don't even ask.
- What?
- A toast to...
- Mm-hmm.
- The thankless.
- The thankless!
- Allez-oop.
- Mm.
- [groans]
- Aw.
[opera music]
All right, boys,
I'm tapping in.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You two losers are sitting here
in what I can only assume is
the cantina of a starship,
drinking and eating
terrible food
when you could be drinking
and eating amazing food
with people who actually
care about you.
[both laugh]
- All right, all right, look.
both: When you put it
like that...
- She has a good point.
- You have a good point, yeah.
- And, by the way, I have the
least to celebrate this year
because I spent
most of it unconscious.
You nerds come to Thanksgiving,
or what?
[operatic musical finish]
["We Are Family"
by Sister Sledge]
- So it wasn't so much
the taste as it was the crunch.
- Wait, are you actually
saying...
- Yes, that was the year
I found out
why Grandma Esther's yams
tasted so good,
because she never cleaned
her favorite skillet.
[all groan]
- [indistinct]
- I take it this was
also the year
you stopped eating
Grandma Esther's yams?
- Uh-uh, I didn't say all that.
- [laughing]
Allow me to propose a toast.
Well, [speaking French]
first to clean dishware,
and also to...to family,
all right,
and to friends,
old and new.
And to the colonizers
who conquered this land...
- What?
- And...
the colonizers who grabbed...
- Remember...no...
- What they want,
they just take what they want.
- Yes, I know, but our...
- To taking what you...
- That's not...you know what?
Let's go.
Right now.
- Okay, you know what?
I think that it's time
to go carve the turkey.
- Great.
Nora. [clears throat]
Um, we didn't have a chance to
talk since the airport.
- Oh, Dad, I know
what you're gonna say,
and you don't have to.
I saw what it was like
when you hesitated
to save those people
because of me,
and I felt...
- Horrible?
- Yeah.
And I never want to feel
like that again.
I get it.
Sometimes you have to sacrifice
yourself to save others.
Even if it means leaving
your family behind.
- Not exactly.
Look, when I ran
into that storm I was thinking
I want to save everyone,
but...
the person I was thinking
about the most was you.
- [stammers] Me?
- Yeah.
I don't choose being The Flash
over being with my family.
I'm The Flash for my family,
and I don't have to run
to the future
to understand why
I sacrificed myself.
I'd do it to save you,
and your mom,
all the people I love.
- You know, maybe one day
if I train enough,
I'll be able to save you.
- I don't doubt it.
All right, come on.
- Okay.
- Ah, yes.
- All right.
- Hey, thank, God.
- Carve the turkey.
- Yeah, baby.
- Here we are.
Each person gets a turkey.
- No.
- Oh.
- We have the one for everyone.
- You all right?
- Just Dad with a knife,
it's a little...
- It's the most fun part.
- ♪ I got all
my sisters with me ♪
- Oh, you're very good
at that.
- Am I?
[music fades]
[distant sirens wailing]
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Orlin.
I told you it's too risky.
CCPD's already looking for you.
What are you doing here?
- It's Thanksgiving, Doc.
I'm here to be with my family.
- I want you to be optimistic,
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
As far as how long,
with all the brain hemorrhaging
she suffered,
you have to prepare yourself
for the possibility
that she may never wake.
- This is all my fault.
- No, it's these metas.
Wreacking havoc unchecked.
She didn't deserve this,
Mr. Dwyer,
and neither did you.
♪ ♪
- [breathes unevenly]
- This was the scene
Tuesday night as, once again,
The Flash saved Central City
from certain destruction.
After a world-wide
power outage
blanketed every country
in darkness,
a bizarre purple...
- [breathing shakily]
- The destructive phenomenon
emanated
from a satellite
that had fallen
into a decaying orbit.
Thankfully, before
the satellite could strike
the city and create
what scientists believe
would have been
"a catastrophic event,"
The Flash was able
to destroy it.
Once again, residents
of our proud city,
and perhaps the entire world
owe The Flash
and his allies...
[tray thudding]
[ominous music]
- A new meta was last seen
jumping off a building
in order to evade capture
after stealing jewels...
[whirring, metal clangs]
- It was reported that
he escaped Flash's grasp
after hijacking
an armored vehicle.
♪ ♪
- [breathing harshly]
I'm gonna make this right,
Gracie.
Every meta...
will die.
[dramatic music build-up]
♪ ♪
- Guys, this better be good.
- Yeah, we've got an
after-Thanksgiving tradition
called sleeping,
so what's up?
- It's good. Trust us.
Detective.
- Well,
it occurred to me that if you,
monsieur and madam West-Allen,
you want to spend this holiday
with your family.
Well, perhaps your meta-killer
does as well.
So I had monsieur Cisco hack
into the CCTV footage
of the hospital
and this what we got.
- Ever since Grace arrived,
only one man has come
to visit her.
Every day.
Including tonight.
- Team Flash,
I give you...
Orlin Dwyer,
also known as...
- Cicada.
[dramatic orchestral music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.