- Previously on
"The Flash"...
- We have a kid who defied
the laws of physics
to hang out with her parents.
- Melt.
- Killer Frost...
- Is gone.
- The only time you need
your mother
is when you're in trouble.
- My father's
death certificate.
- The M.E.
who signed off on it,
he doesn't exist.
- Now I know why she never
wants to leave
her dad's side
and never wants to be by mine.
- I just lost my speed.
- [groans]
- Sounds like an insect.
- Like a cicada.
- Who's Cicada?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- As a kid
there was a part
of the Flash Museum
that always scared me.
I guess it's normal
for children
to be afraid of monsters.
But this monster
was different.
No one knows where
he came from,
how he got his powers,
who he is.
All that's known is his alias,
and the last sound his
victim's hear.
- [heavy breathing]
- But that's not
what makes him scary.
What makes him scary is...
you never catch him.
- We never catch him?
- Supergirl, The Legends,
even The League tried,
but no one was successful.
- Probably 'cause he can dampen
everybody's powers
with that magic friggin'
dagger.
- Not all superpowers
are meta-humans though.
What about...
- Green Arrow?
Yeah, he tried too once,
but...
- So we're dealing with
a meta-human Jack the Ripper.
Amazing.
- [sighs]
What else do you know
about him?
- Just that he...
he's early.
- What do you mean he's early?
- In my history,
Cicada's first victim
was a meta-human named
Floyd Belkin.
And he never killed Gridlock
or Block.
They're completely different
victims.
- Because the timeline changed.
- Yeah,
and now they're both dead...
because of me.
- Okay, there's no telling
the ripple effect
of this change
or what kind of future Nora's
gonna return to.
We gotta catch this guy fast.
- You mean catch the guy
that future us can't catch?
Right, I thought beating
The Thinker was hard.
[electronic beeps]
- Guys, it's Joe.
CCPD needs help downtown.
- Okay, I got it.
- No, I'll...I'll do it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I got it.
You guys stay here
and deal with
the meta serial killer.
- Okay, guys, look,
we got this.
Let's just canvass
some crime scenes,
interview some witnesses,
and see if there's any
common acquaintances
between Gridlock and Block.
- I have a plan.
- You...you've got
a plan already?
- I know how to fix this.
♪ ♪
- Now nobody try nothing funny.
This baby is solar
with a zero carbon footprint.
I spent a week
in the sun charging
with U, V, A, B, and C!
So y'all stay put.
Hey. Hey!
I told you,
I brought my own bags.
- Sorry.
- Apology accepted.
- Don't forget
the other kind of greens.
- What the hell?
- Fear not, good citizens.
Elongated Man is here.
[laughter]
Why do I feel like
you're focusing
on the wrong thing?
I just saved you...
okay, if you're gonna...
just don't post...don't post...
I saw you post it.
- So your plan is
to contact Herr Wells?
- Yes, that's my plan.
I know in the future you guys
never bring in a Wells
to help you catch Cicada.
So if you want a different
result this time...
- I try something new.
It's a great idea.
- 'Cept it's not.
- What?
- It's a terrible idea.
If you're looking
for cooperation, trust me,
this is not your guy.
He is just an asshat.
- That's way harsh, Cisco.
- I'm sorry, I'm being harsh?
- Yes.
- Go ahead, call him.
See if you don't get
a steaming pile of side-eye.
- Okay.
- Yah?
[scoffs]
The Flash.
- [scoffs]
Wait for it,
- I love The Flash.
- What?
- Oh, you Barry Allen, yah?
With the zoom, zoom,
and the defy the physics laws
and gravity.
Always with some style
and grace, yah.
- Thanks, man.
- Das Kinder Flash.
Child of the Flash.
Obviously, you have
your father's moral fiber, yah.
And your mother's smarts,
and classic beauty.
- Oh, my God. Stop.
- Thank you, Herr Wells.
- [stammers]
No, don't thank him.
Don't fall for this ruse.
Clearly this guy
is putting on an act.
He's a charlatan.
- But you hurt me,
stab me in the back,
this guy who must be Cisco.
- You know who I am.
- Hey, don't be rude.
All right, look.
Hey, I'm sorry.
We need your help catching
a meta-human serial killer.
- Yeah,
I have heard of this Cicada.
Of course, the message already
from Kinder Flash.
Unfortunately,
I'm otherwise occupied,
unable to assist you
at this time.
- You can't?
- Nein.
But, I have done one better
and called someone who can.
This man is a legend,
this man is
the greatest detective
in all the Multiverse.
So I've attached
his coordinates
if you want to look at them.
- Okay.
- Yah, do you see it?
- Got 'em.
- Good.
- Cisco.
- Cisco what?
You want me to breach him here?
- Yeah.
- Hello? I just got Benihana'd.
Hurts a little bit.
- Sorry.
Why don't we just breach him
here the old fashioned way?
- Hey, man, thank you for this.
This is great.
- Privilege and an honor
to help The Flash, yah,
and Kinder Flash,
and Iris Flash, yah.
Bye, Kinder Flash.
- Bye, Herr Wells.
[giggles]
- Nice guy.
What are you talking about,
man?
He's awesome.
- He's not...
You know what?
Let's just turn on
the extrapolator
and get this master detective
out here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Well...
I imagine your Earth
would be colder.
Harrison Sherloque Wells
at your service.
I'm here to catch your killer.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- [quietly]
Barry, what is he doing?
- [whispers] I don't know.
Maybe it's some kind
of CSI kit?
- Voila.
- [whispers] Shh.
Just let him...
- Mmm.
That's the stuff.
And now we can begin.
- Tea?
- That's right.
- We've been watching you
for 20 minutes.
- You're welcome.
Cannot rush excellence.
- This is a waste of time.
Thank you very much for coming,
Cumberbatch.
- I'm sure you would like it
if I took my leave, right?
Could have more time to recover
from your recent heartbreak.
- What are you talking about?
- Subcutaneous
under-eye bruising,
which indicates
you've been crying.
Flaky skin,
which indicates dehydration,
probably from
alcohol consumption.
Alcohol plus crying
can only mean one thing.
You have been dumped.
- Wrong, detective.
I have not been dumped.
- Oh, no?
- It was a mutual decision,
okay?
Cynthia and I, we reached
a decision together as a team.
- Sure.
Of course.
- Okay, and I haven't been
sobbing.
In fact, I can't remember
the last time I cried about it.
Excuse me.
- [grunts]
[soft music]
You are the resident speedster,
I presume?
- How did you...
- Who favors stopping
on his right heel?
Can tell from the wear and tear
on your footwear.
It's uneven.
A trait that you have inherited
from your father.
Although you do share
a little bit more body language
with your mother,
who's been touching
her left shoulder
since I came around here.
What are you hiding from me?
- Excuse me?
I am not hiding anything.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, you are, but what?
You have touched it, like...
it's something there,
then gone again,
something removed.
A tattoo, right?
Yes, perhaps from
a former lover?
- Okay! [clears throat]
You know what?
I think that this Sherloque
has proven himself
and that we should start
finding Cicada.
- Excellent.
Let's find Cicada.
But first,
the question of my fee.
- You're charging us?
- This service is not free,
right?
I don't work for charity.
Can already tell
the young doctor here
is expecting to hire me
for another case.
I saw you glance at your purse,
and I'm happy to assist you
in that mystery.
But first,
I think we can all agree
that a villain
of Cicada's caliber...
will require a substantial fee.
- Yeah.
- [gasps]
Shrap, that's a lot of money
even from when I from.
- I'm very expensive,
but very worth it.
What do you think?
- I mean, we could sell off
some of Star Labs stock.
- Yes! We have an agreement.
- Yeah.
- Do you hear that?
[footsteps approaching]
Sounds of these frantic steps,
we're being approached
either by a tall,
sensitive man, or...
a frightened, baby giraffe.
- I got...I got a problem here,
guys, and I...
- Hey.
- Hello, baby giraffe.
- Harry, how are you?
- This is Sherloque Wells.
Loque.
Sherloque. "L-O-Q-U-E."
Sherloque.
I'm French.
- "Sher-lowk" here is...
- Loque.
- Is gonna help us find Cicada.
- Oh, cool,
so you're like a detective.
- Oh, detective, the fans.
Who should I make
the autograph out to?
Little baby giraffe.
- Uh, no, no, no.
I'm...I'm...listen.
I'm a detective as well.
- [speaking French]
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Ah, well...
[speaking French]
That's right, well,
you're a detective.
What...what have you solved
recently?
- Most recently?
I uncovered the case
of the stolen Chevy.
[clears throat]
Of Impala.
- Funny.
- Hmm.
- Very funny
from the looks of things.
- Well, okay, so I saved all
these hostages
and...and all anybody can talk
about is this picture,
and turned into a meme.
And...and...it's...
this is...I just...I don't think
anybody in this city
takes me seriously.
- Oh, there's 14 million people
in this city.
Only 500,000
have reposted this.
- Yeah.
- So, uh...Cicada?
- Cicada, yes.
I've reviewed your evidence
and I know
where to find your killer.
So, shall we, let's get this
done before dinner, right?
All right, allons-y.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not so fast, baby giraffe.
Two detectives
only complicates matters.
Especially when only one
is a master.
So why don't you stay put?
You can, bite the leaves.
Everyone else, come with em.
[speaking French]
- [clears throat]
- You okay?
- Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
I'm...[laughs]
Yeah, I'm...I'm great.
I just got shut down
by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
- You know Cicada's
not the only mystery
around here that needs solving.
- [sighs]
Yeah.
- Mom, I know it sounds crazy,
but we think someone forged
Dad's death certificate.
- Have you any proof?
- No, well, yes, sort of.
It's complicated, but
I just thought you should know.
- Unless I already knew.
- I didn't say that.
- It's why you're here,
isn't it?
If this is some elaborate,
possibly nefarious cover-up,
it must be mom's doing.
It's not like she's ever
had your best interests
at heart.
- You always do this.
I just want to know the truth.
I think I deserve to know that.
Is...
my dad even really...
- Caitlin, your father is dead.
And if you care about
my feelings at all,
you'll just let this be.
- Thanks, mom.
Pleasure as always.
- Don't become obsessed
with the past.
Your father had that flaw.
It nearly led to his ruin
even before his death.
I trust you know the way out.
- [sighs]
I'm sorry we came
all this way for no reason.
- No, I'm impressed.
Your mom is a really good liar.
- Yeah, I know she forged
this death certificate.
I just...
She's never gonna tell us why.
We've hit a brick wall.
- Ah, but where you see a wall
this detective sees
a brick door with no handle.
What I mean is I know exactly
how to get what we came for.
[electricity surges]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You sure he's in there?
- I'm certain.
Now, your evidence,
while slight,
was enough to build
a psychologic profile.
This is a man hiding
in the shadows.
This is someone
who's been pushed
to the peripheries of society,
and then now he sits alone
waiting for the moment
to strike.
All this,
plus the census data
cross-referenced with
the location of his attacks,
and the profile narrows
to one name...
David Hersch.
- Nora's plan might
actually work.
- Well, it will work.
- [sighs]
- Once inside, you should find
a small booby trap.
- I found it.
- I'm on it.
- Here is the critical part.
It's a decoy.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Sorry.
I got caught off-guard.
- [grunts]
- Not so tough without
your dagger, huh?
We got him.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[floor creaks]
- [heavy breathing]
- That's ridiculous!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't got anything on me!
- Well, he sounds angry.
- Yeah.
Forensics examined
Hersch's hideout
and they found evidence
linking him
to several anti-government
bombings.
He's been doing it for a while.
- So we got him.
- I don't know.
They didn't find
any sign of his dagger
or his mask.
- Dad, one CSI to another
look at the facts, okay?
Sherloque is the best detective
in the Multiverse.
His profile led us
to David Hersch,
and we found evidence
that David Hersch
is a mass murderer.
What are the chances
that this isn't our guy?
- I mean, maybe.
- Come on, we should celebrate.
Okay, I'm gonna gather
everyone up,
make some drinks,
and we can have our first party
in the new lounge.
- I don't know, Nora.
I...
[cicada chirpings]
Detective Joseph West.
- What do you want?
- To finish what I started.
The meta-human called Vibe.
Call him here now.
- I can't.
I don't even know him.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- You were saying?
- Yes, I mean, he helps CCPD,
but it's not like I have
a Vibe phone
so I can just call him up.
He's just a masked do-gooder
that shows up at crime scenes.
- This could be a crime scene.
♪ ♪
- When you said you had a plan,
Ralph,
I didn't mean you meant
breaking and entering
into my mother's company's
files.
[sighs]
Reinforced steel.
It's times like this
I really miss Killer Frost.
- Oh, don't you worry.
Ralphie's got it.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Yep.
Almost there.
Hang on.
Yeah, almost got it.
[gasps]
Oh, my God.
- What is it?
- Lasers.
Rooms filled with lasers!
Holy snakies.
Oh, my God.
It's like
a Rubik's Cube of pain.
- I don't know the code.
- Try something
that your mother would...[gasps]
Caitlin!
There's gotta be something.
- Got it.
- [sighs]
- You okay?
- Nothing a gallon of Aloe
won't fix.
- Ooh.
Look for the name
Thomas Snow.
[dramatic music]
- Jackpot.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
- What is that?
- It's a game my dad
and I used to play.
He would teach me
the periodic table, but...
he would let me make up
my own fictional compounds
and elements.
- Nerd-onium?
- He used to say it's
what made us so smart.
- [laughs softly]
- We used to have
so much fun together.
Catching bugs in the backyard,
looking at constellations
through a telescope we built.
He taught me so much
about science and life.
[soft dramatic music]
- Maybe he still has something
left to teach you.
♪ ♪
What is it?
- It's a letter from my dad.
Saying...
goodbye.
It's a suicide note.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music playing]
- Alcohol, thank you,
very much. Merci.
- There he is.
- Hey.
- Dad, we're all set
to celebrate...
- No, hey, um.
Actually, Hersch isn't Cicada.
- What?
He has to be.
- No, I checked Cicada's
boot print from
both the Block and Gridlock
crime scenes
and it's three sizes larger
than Hersch's.
It's not him.
- Well, of course it's him.
It's always Hersch.
Every time I capture Cicada
it's always the same man.
- Wait a minute,
you've caught this guy before?
- 37 times.
I've captured 37 Cicadas,
37 different Earths,
and every time I try
to capture him
trail always leads back
to that Earth's David Hersch.
- So this psychological profile
that you created,
you just made it up?
- Not, the first time.
Now the next 36,
then I just trot it out there.
You know,
to impress the client,
and then...[snaps]
Skip to the end.
- And here I thought you just
a bad detective,
but you're not a bad detective.
You're just a lazy one.
- [speaking French]
I'm not lazy.
I'm efficient, right?
Anyway, that's not the point!
- Ow!
- The point's simply
that there's no reason
for the Cicada of this Earth
to be anyone other
than David Hersch.
- Well,
there may be one reason.
- What's that?
- The timeline.
- Yes, since Nora got here
things have changed a bit.
Yeah.
- Oh, mais no, you must...
how can you not tell me this?
How am I expected to operate
when you don't give me
all the variables?
- I don't know,
but what we can expect
is a refund, so...
- Yeah.
- Oh, no, no, no.
That money is long gone.
- What do you mean "it's gone"?
You spent all that money
in one day?
- Right.
- On what.
- My ex-wife-ves..
Ex-wives.
Seven marriages.
Five wives.
Lots of alimony.
That's not the point!
The point is simply
this is not my fault.
It's your fault.
She is to blame.
Timeline variance.
- [scoffs]
- Dad.
[exhales]
You're not gonna
let Hersch off the hook
because of a boot print.
He's a meta.
How do we know
what this guy can do?
- That's the other thing.
Hersch has
no dark matter readings.
He's not a meta.
All right, remember.
From one CSI to another,
we have to look at the facts,
right?
We got the wrong guy.
- No, not this time.
You know what we should do?
We should throw him in
the pipeline for safe keeping
until he talks.
I'm gonna go get him.
- Hey, what are you...
no, you're not.
We're not gonna kidnap
a suspect in police custody.
If you don't see
what's wrong with that,
you can sit this one out.
[soft dramatic music]
- Well,
guess we're back to square one
with Cicada.
- Yeah.
Let's hope it's not too late
to save his next victim.
[suspenseful music]
[cicada chirpings]
♪ ♪
- You have a lovely family,
Detective West.
By not giving me what I want,
by putting your life in danger,
you're gambling
their future with you.
If you knew what I know,
you'd cherish them more.
- I'm not luring Vibe
into a death trap.
You can threaten me
all you want.
I'm not afraid.
- I believe you.
But you should be.
- [pained groaning]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Still swirling
around up there?
- I just don't get Nora.
I mean, I thought our training
was sinking in.
She defeated Block.
She was really making process.
And next thing I know,
she wants to break into CCPD
and kidnap a suspect
in police custody.
I mean, it's like she wants to
make Hersch Cicada.
- Barry, you really don't get
why she's obsessed?
- Wait. Should I?
- Think about it.
She's been hearing about
the ripple effects
on the timeline
since she got here
and at first they were
relatively small,
but now...
Cicada and...
- It's not so small.
- He's one of the worst
serial killers in history,
and now because of Nora...
he's here early.
And an entirely different
person.
- With an entirely different
set of victims.
- That is a huge weight
to bear for someone
who just wanted to spend time
with a dad she never knew.
She feels really guilty, Barry.
She wants to try
to fix her mistakes
whatever that takes.
Sounds like another speedster
I know actually.
- [scoffs]
[cell phone beeps]
Nora says there's an emergency
in the pipeline intake.
♪ ♪
Are you sure that...
- Sherloque.
- Yeah.
What happened?
- As far as I can tell
it looks like
he was in the wrong place
when this fusion cell
went critical.
I think it wasn't placed
in its cradle properly.
- Vaporized into ash.
- What a way to go.
- Shenanigans.
- Good grife!
- I call shenanigans.
You see,
these cells right here,
they run in a redundant
cascade circuit.
That's how they power
the pipeline,
in the first place,
so if one of them blew
they all would have blown.
- Yeah, the whole pipeline
would have exploded.
- Exactly right.
- Ugh.
- Mm.
- Darjeeling, oolong.
Tea leaves.
Barry, be a dear
and check the building
for a weasel in a pork pie hat,
about yay tall,
smells vaguely of poutine.
- [sighs]
- Whoa. Tell me...
who died?
- [clears throat]
- Found him with this.
- [grunts]
- Of course, you did.
So you thought you could
just leave
to another Earth
without paying us back?
- Worked on my fourth wife...
and my sixth.
Same woman.
- Oh.
- Okay, Cisco,
maybe it's time to have a talk
about a little place called
debtor's prison.
- Come with me.
- All right.
- You make me miss Herr Wells.
- Come with me.
- I'm...I'm taking you!
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
It's just...
for second I thought me
inviting Sherloque here
got him killed,
and I just, um...
least that's one thing
that's not my fault.
[scoffs]
- Hey, I wanted
to talk to you actually.
I think I understand
how you're feeling.
Sometimes our powers are
so extraordinary
it makes our mistakes
feel amplified,
especially guilt.
- Yeah,
but I should feel guilty.
[sighs]
I've never messed up
this badly before,
and I can't stop thinking
about it.
- That's just cause you care.
It's okay.
It's a good thing.
But...
[sighs]
Nora, if every time
you make a mistake
you just rush in to fix it
you're only gonna
make things worse.
Trust me,
I know that better than anyone.
You just gotta have
a little more patience.
Take a moment.
Think before you act.
Fix the problem the right way,
all right?
- Okay.
- Listen, Caitlin, I'm sorry.
- For what?
- For all of this.
Just I-I felt like
a complete joke
after that hostage thing,
and then...Sherloque shows up
and everybody swoons
over his so-called
"Master Detective-ness."
You were nice enough
to invite me along,
and I pushed you...
into that, and...
I'm really sorry.
- Ralph, this thing
you pushed me into
gave me something
I've never had before.
- Your first felony?
- [scoffs] No.
Closure.
It may not be pretty,
but I finally know the truth.
and that means everything.
So, for my book,
you're the best detective
a girl could ask for.
[soft dramatic music]
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
Hey, you never told me
what the code was
on your mom's Resident Evil
laser grid of death.
- It was my birthday.
[high-pitch whirring]
- [whimpers]
- [gasps]
- [groaning]
- All this
and not even a scream.
You've experienced pain before,
but not more than me.
- No, Cecile don't.
No.
That's what he wants.
- I didn't want to do this.
Not to a family man.
But I will.
Time to make a decision,
Detective West.
While there's still
some of you left.
[baby cries]
[beeping]
- No, no, no!
Leave her out of it!
- [groans]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- What's wrong?
- He took Cisco!
- Cicada took Cisco.
- What do you mean took him?
Took him where?
- I don't know.
They jumped into a breach right
when I got here.
- But a breach
could take them anywhere.
- Cisco, can you hear me?
- Guys, can you hear me?
[grunts]
- Cisco, where are you?
- I don't know.
My breach fritzed out
and spat us out in
a forest somewhere.
- Can you breach out?
- [groaning]
[breathing heavily]
It's not working.
[whirring]
[grunts]
- Cicada's dampening
his powers.
- Without a satellite
I can't pin point his location.
I mean, in this state alone
there's over
14 million acres of forest.
- All right, Black Forest
and Roanoke are closest.
I'll start there.
- We're not gonna find him
in time, are we?
- Well, before you give up,
what kind of trees?
- What?
In the forest,
what kind of trees, ask him.
- Cisco,
what kind of trees are they?
- I don't know!
I'm in a forest!
- What kind of trees,
little one?
- Pine trees, I think.
- Good.
- Some of them have
pointy leaves.
- Ah, pointy...
ash trees, of course.
All right, now I need
you to hold your breath.
- What? Why?
- Because I need
to hear the forest,
So, shh.
[insects chirping]
- [exhales sharply]
[indistinct fauna]
- Crickets.
You hear this?
Assuming that's field crickets.
They live in the soil.
Anyway, cross-reference
field crickets
with a high concentration
of pine trees, ash trees,
in an open field,
and you have...
- Kolins Woods.
- On my way!
- [gasping]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- Barry,
you got to get out of there!
We have to help him.
Barry?
[exciting music]
- It takes time
to hone your skills, Nora.
You can't just skip rungs
on the ladder
or jump right
to the big stuff,
that's not how it works.
Take a moment.
Think before you act.
Fix the problem the right way.
- I got it.
I can fix this.
I've thought this through.
I won't mess it up this time.
I promise.
- I trust you.
Go.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- All these years
in Central City
spent defending metas
instead of ending them.
Those days end now.
Starting with you.
♪ ♪
- [pained groan]
[exciting music]
- Use this!
- Hey, Michael Myers,
dampen this.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[EKG beeps]
- No. No. No. No.
Cisco's gone.
Oh, my God...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
- [groans]
[flatline]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco?
[thrums]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
He's alive.
- [laughs]
- He's alive.
♪ ♪
Hey.
- Hey.
Sorry.
[electricity thrums]
- Your daughter.
She remembered there's more
than one way to
open a breach.
- Figured Cicada
wouldn't give up
until Vibe was dead,
so we gave him what he wanted.
- Thanks, fangirl.
You saved my life.
- I did good?
- You did great.
[dramatic music]
- It's almost like
you're really dead.
- Yeah.
I almost really was.
[sighs]
[soft dramatic music]
How the hell are
we gonna catch this guy?
- Not with our powers.
We know that at least.
- We don't know
much else either.
Variations in the timeline,
they've...
shifted the elements,
complicated the equation.
Now...
- Not all those elements
are bad though.
You could be the new element
that saves us.
You could be the reason
we catch Cicada.
- I must admit,
Miss Nora here pulled
the rug right under
from Cicada.
Woof, alley-oop, huh?
Very impressive.
- Yeah, that's the only
fake death we're gonna see
around here
'cause you're sticking around
until you pay us back
every cent.
- Well, I have to say, prospect
of another mystery with Cicada
puts a little pep in my step.
Also, that breach device
you used to get
in and out of places,
I suppose
that's under lock and key
right now?
- That's at the bottom
of the ocean
as far as you're concerned.
- Well, then I'm staying!
Great!
- Course you are.
I'm watching you, Holmes.
- Yes. Yes. Yes.
Well, you'll learn a lot.
Good for you.
- Ow.
- All right, shall we,
sidekick.
- I'll sidekick your face.
- Something tells me
those two are gonna be
just great friends.
- [laughs softly]
- So...
You guys up for
a family dinner night?
[soft music]
- Sure.
- Yeah.
And then maybe after
we could help you
move into the loft.
I know you've been kind of
cooped up here,
and now that Sherloque
is gonna need a place to stay
I thought you could...
crash with us.
- I think it's a great idea,
Nora.
- Okay, thanks, yeah.
Thanks.
Let me get my purse.
- Okay.
- This will be good.
I think it could be
just the thing
to bring you two closer
together.
- I really hope so.
♪ ♪
[footsteps approaching]
- Hey.
Taking Cisco out
for some drinks
in memoriam of Vibe.
You wanna come?
- I'm okay, but thank you.
- Anything you want
to talk about?
- [sighs] My dad wasn't really
the letter writing type.
I feel like he would have found
some other way to tell me.
- No luck with his work notes?
- No, I mean,
these molecular models
are gibberish.
There's gaps everywhere
and some of these compounds
don't even exist.
It's like his mind
was the first to go.
But, maybe I should
just listen to my mom
and forget about the past.
- Well...
You left this behind.
Sometimes the past
is worth remembering.
- Thank you.
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
They don't exist
because they're not
supposed to.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
- So this is all
I could remember
about Cicada.
It's not much, but...
- No. No. No, this is...
this is great.
I mean,
every little bit we get
helps build a profile on him.
I will comb over this
in the morning.
You should go be
with Cecile right now.
Feel better.
- Wait. There's...
there's one more thing.
He made these comments
about family
and cherishing them.
And then the way he picked up
Jenna's blanket,
and I got this feeling
when I looked in his eyes.
- What...what kind of feeling?
- I think Cicada's a father.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[somber music]
[suspenseful music]
- Hello, Orlin.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Any progress?
- She's not coming out of it.
♪ ♪
Let me see it.
[buzzing]
It's not healing.
- Doesn't matter.
- You can't keep doing this.
You have to stop.
- Not until I'm finished.
♪ ♪
- Oh, hi.
I'm just looking for my purse.
I'm about to have dinner
with my parents.
- It's on the chair.
In the Cortex.
By the mannequin.
- Right.
Thanks.
Well, enjoy the couch.
- Nora.
[soft dramatic music]
Can you help me with something?
I've been wondering...
You. You've traveled back
into all these
great moments of your parent's
lives, right?
Some wonderful, some dangerous.
Most not as dangerous as...
punching a falling satellite,
right?
And yet...
that is the moment
when you made
the decision to act,
altering the course
of history forever.
That decision...
Did you come to it on your own?
♪ ♪
Of course you did!
Right?
No, of course you did.
You're Excess!
- [chuckles]
- The temptation...
was too much, I'm sure.
- It was.
[tense music]
- Well, please,
forgive me.
You have a dinner to go to.
Good night.
♪ ♪