- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- I didn't kill Clifford DeVoe.
- Tricked ya!
- Barry, they took a hostage.
- Well, who'd he take?
- Your dad.
- I'm ready for my supersuit.
- This tarp is your supersuit.
- What is this,
a puppy's raincoat?
[yelling]
- Nice job, rookie.
I won't be a fugitive.
If I'm convicted,
I'm not going to run.
- We find
the defendant guilty.
[tense music]
[indistinct yelling]
♪ ♪
- We're losing control
of the place,
drop grenades.
Deploy smoke grenades!
Backup, we need backup!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- They're back in.
Lock it down.
[dramatic music]
- Let's move.
Move out.
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
[police sirens blare]
- Fine, just tell us
what you want.
- I want you to back off,
or I will detonate this thing.
- Okay, calm down,
nobody needs to get hurt today.
- You just follow instructions,
and everybody here gets to live
to see the sunshine tomorrow.
Right?
And I'd better not see
The Flash, either.
All right, first, I want a car.
Something eco-friendly,
like a Prius.
- Okay, we can do that.
- Good. Uh, right.
Now second.
Uh, I want a plane, okay?
A private plane.
Okay, and a salad, all right?
I'm counting calories.
- Okay, it's going to take us
an hour to arrange that.
- You better hurry up,
because these hostages
don't have much time.
[playful music]
♪ ♪
- Should have gone
with a steak, pal.
'Cause it's the last decent
meal you're getting
for the next five to ten years.
- Who the hell are you?
- Your friendly
neighborhood superhero.
You can call me...
[stammering]
Mr...
[exhales]
One second.
Guys, this is
a huge moment for me.
What's my name?
- I was wondering
where you were going with that.
- Hey, hey,
where are my hostages?
- Uh, bathroom break.
They just couldn't
hold it anymore.
Don't worry, though,
they're totally safe.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get back, freak.
- Freak, oh, sticks and stones
may break my bones, buddy.
Well, they used to.
Not anymore.
- I'll blow this
whole city block.
- Uh, you do realize you're
a part of that block, right?
Come on, man, it's a weekday.
People just want
to get off work,
go home,
and watch the boob tube.
So why don't you
take off that vest and...
- No, don't touch me!
[screaming]
[air releasing]
- Ralph, are you okay?
- [belches]
Yeah.
Yeah, just, uh,
wicked heartburn.
Let this be a lesson
to all of you
would-be criminals
out there.
Catching you won't be
too much of a stretch.
- And so,
our streets are safe again,
thanks to Central City's
funniest new hero,
The Stretchy Man.
- Okay.
- Embarrassing.
- Cisco, next time
you're going with him.
- Iris, a chicken needs
to leave its roost
sooner or later,
especially when that chicken
insists on doing
his own solo mission.
- This is bad.
- This is really bad.
Stretchy Man,
that's a terrible name.
Also, now that I'm going
to be on TV all the time,
this grey suit, got to go.
- Hey, easy, chickadee.
- No, Ralph, I meant you, okay?
That bomb could have
torn you to shreds.
- Or Joe, or any
of the police outside.
- Relax, ladies, my cells are
completely polygamized.
- Polymerized?
- Yeah, that.
Which means they can stretch
and take a bomb blast.
- Oh, my God.
- Dibny is in-dib-structable.
- Okay, Ralph,
you are missing the point.
You need to be more cautious.
- No, no, no,
you are missing the point.
What I really need, guys,
is a new superhero name.
Ramon, you've had
all this time.
You can't
come up with anything?
- Patience, okay?
I'm getting to you.
I've just been
a little preoccupied,
what with Barry
being in prison and all.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- You find anything
that might prove
DeVoe framed Barry yet?
- My dad and Cecile are meeting
with Judge Hankerson tomorrow
to go over his appeal.
We've been pouring through the
evidence piece by piece, but...
- Don't worry, Iris,
we're going to get him out.
- Hey, has Barry
joined a gang yet?
I've got some friends
on the inside.
I can make some calls.
- Shut up, Ralph.
- Okay.
I will stop helping now.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
- You can watch the clock
all you want,
but it won't go any faster.
You're Barry Allen, right?
Henry Allen's kid?
I'm...
- Axel Walker.
You and your dad
kidnapped my dad once.
- Yeah, right.
Pudding?
Lunch lady gave me extra.
I think she has a crush on me.
- No.
- Hey, word on the block is,
you carved up some professor.
He give you
a bad grade or something?
- I didn't kill anybody.
- Yeah, sure.
Everyone's innocent in here.
Especially that guy.
Yeah, Big Sir.
He's really innocent.
This is grosser than usual.
Does pudding go bad?
- Axel, what do you
want from me?
- [chuckles]
To be murder buds.
You know,
we could share trade secrets.
I'd love to hear how you
carved up that college quack.
- I don't need any friends
in here.
- Oh, man, I do not feel good.
[groans]
- [grunts]
- Get him up.
You got mud
on my bright whites.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
- Sorry's right.
[gate opens]
- [clears throat]
[gate closes]
♪ ♪
- The first week
in Iron Heights
is often the hardest,
Mr. Allen.
You've already seen
what happens when a few inmates
try to revolt.
Acclimating to your new life
will take time.
Always does.
In the meantime,
do your best
to stay clean in here.
Oh, and Mr. Allen,
your 1:30 is waiting for you.
♪ ♪
- Hey, I'm so glad to see you.
- Me too.
How's it going?
- It's not as bad
as I thought it would be.
And hey, you're talking
to the newest member
of the Iron Heights
janitorial staff.
I'm the fastest mop alive.
[both laugh]
- Well, we've been surveilling
the DeVoes 24/7.
I mean, they must have made
a mistake somewhere, right?
And I've been pouring over
all of the evidence with Dad.
We are going to get you
out of there, Barry.
- I know you will.
How's the rest of the team?
I saw Ralph on TV.
- Ralph is getting
a little cocky.
- Yeah, I was when I
started too...it happens.
- Yeah.
- Iris, it's okay.
- I just can't believe
this is our new normal, Barry.
I don't want this
to be our lives.
- You're going
to find something.
I know it.
[buzzing]
- Closing time!
Wrap them up!
- I just wish I could
touch your hand again.
[sighs]
- You will.
I promise.
I'll see you tomorrow?
- Every tomorrow.
♪ ♪
- Walker here spewed
all over his cellmate.
Says he's got cramps.
- [groans]
- Who are you?
Where's Nurse Hill?
- Out sick.
Looks like he ate the pudding.
- Yeah, how do you know that?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Because I'm the one
who sent it.
Come on, Axel, let's go.
- Mom?
[both laugh]
- Walker and the nurse
used tranquilizers
on two more guards
on the way out.
- And nothing tipped you off
that this nurse
might be a criminal?
- Her background check
was clean.
She said her name
was Lindsay Fineheart.
She was sent over
by our staffing company.
- Well, I'm going
to need the hard drive
of the surveillance footage
from the security cameras
in the infirmary.
- Well, unfortunately, we're
still analog here in Gen Pop.
It will take a while
to dub the tapes.
In the meantime,
I'm having Fineheart's file
brought down for you.
- How's Barry doing?
- Model inmate,
just like his dad.
- Do you mind if I...?
- Let me check on that file.
- Bare.
- Joe, hey.
What are you doing here?
- Axel Walker escaped.
Some new nurse
helped him get out.
- [scoffs]
He was in here
because of the pudding.
- How do you know that?
- He was complaining
about the taste.
Hey, let me help
with this, all right?
- Barry...
- No.
Has Cisco having any luck
figuring out
how to bypass the system?
Because once he does that,
I could phase out of here.
I could help you track him.
- Barry, you need
to stay put for now.
Trickster is
just a messed-up kid.
We can handle him.
- No, I know, of course.
I just...I'm already tired
of feeling useless, you know?
- The only thing
you should focus on in here
is watching your back.
Pretty sure
cops can't touch inmates.
Otherwise, I'd give you a hug.
Stay strong, Bare.
- Mm-hmm.
- Detective?
- Sir.
- Well, this is her.
- This woman's name
isn't Lindsay Fineheart.
Her name is Zoey Clark.
- James Jesse had a girlfriend?
- Yeah, she called
herself Prank.
Back in the day, she was
Bonnie to Jesse's Clyde.
No matter what, whether it
was attempted murder,
arson, robbery,
she was always by his side.
[computer beeps]
- Man, what were people
wearing back then?
- Zoe Clark was the beneficiary
to Clark Toys empire.
- Not much of an empire.
All those stores
closed 20 years ago.
- Looks like she has
Bachelor's degrees
in arts and applied sciences,
as well as
a Master's in chemistry.
- Trickster and Prank
were responsible for a series
of terrorist attacks
across Central City,
including
the destruction of
the Gadzooka
Bubblegum company.
- Huh, I always wondered why
my favorite gum suddenly
disappeared in the 90's
- We have it on my Earth.
- You do not.
- I just said we did.
- We do.
- Anyway, after Jesse
was arrested,
she disappeared.
She's been
a fugitive ever since.
- Looks like Axel was born
nine months after
Zoey was last seen.
I bet she left to help to
take care of her son.
- And she came back
to bust him out of prison,
and pick up where she left off.
- Well, I'm digging
into CCPD files
to see if she had
any other known associates.
- I'll set the satellite
to do a search grid.
Ramon?
- Hey, how about you hook me up
with some of that gum?
- Why don't you
breach yourself?
- That sounds like an insult.
- Kind of was.
- Hey, Ralph, do you want
to go to your usual spots,
see if any of
your contacts have seen her?
- Sure, I need a chaperone.
Caitlin, you're up.
It's happy hour, you're buying.
- [groans]
- Come on,
use Killer Frost's credit card.
- No way, Jose.
- You think Ralphie's made
of money?
[suspenseful music]
- Where are you two hiding?
- Wow.
What is this place?
- It's all that remains
of Clarx Toys.
- Oh, it's cold in here.
Oh, awesome!
[laughs]
I made the news, ha!
- Not awesome.
Now the police
are looking for you.
As soon as night falls,
we're out of Central City.
- And then we'll go
meet up with Dad, right?
That's why you broke me out.
Because Dad wanted
to see me, right?
- Not exactly.
Axel, I wanted you
back in my life.
- Right, but what about Dad?
- Well, he broke out
a year ago,
and he hasn't
come looking for you.
[scoffs]
He doesn't care.
- Of course he does.
- Axel,
your dad's a deadbeat.
He doesn't want
to be a part of this family,
and he never did.
[solemn music]
- Don't talk
about him like that.
- Honey, I'm sorry,
it's just that
you just don't
know him like I do.
Do you know
what it was like for me
when you were growing up?
While you were
idolizing your dad?
I was the one
making your dinner.
While you were watching him
terrorize the city on TV,
I was the one
driving you to school.
I was the one making sure
you got your homework done.
I was the one packing
the lunches in the morning.
I was there for you.
- I know, I know, Mom!
Okay, now we can get him back.
- I don't want him back.
I want us to go
be free together.
I never wanted you
to end up like your father.
- Well, it's too late
for that, Mom.
♪ ♪
I just need
to get Dad's attention.
I'll show him
that someone in this family
still has a funny bone.
Mom.
[laughing]
♪ ♪
- Everyone walks away safe,
and so Central City
has a new,
sexier model of superhero.
- [laughs]
- Me...it's...I'm sexy.
- And I know
just how I'm going to do it.
- Sexy one.
Anyone want an autograph?
Autograph, anyone?
- [laughs]
- No, Axel.
Axel!
♪ ♪
- Heard you had
a little one-on-one time
with a badge this morning.
- [whispers]
Oh, God.
- First, you dirty up my shoes.
Now,
you're snitching to the cops?
You've had quite
the first week, haven't you?
- I don't want any trouble.
- Too late.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
This isn't over.
- Thanks.
- Hey, how's the search coming?
- Harry and I already set
all the parameters,
it's just got 300 square miles
to comb through, so.
Yeah.
[computers beep]
- That's not good.
- Hello, Central City!
It's been far, far too long
since my beautiful face
graced your screens.
[laughs]
- Whoo, this kid's
got a face for radio.
- Trickster's hijacking the
city's broadcasting signals.
- Today, we're going
to play a little game
I like to call
"what Does This Do?"
Looks like
a regular old bouncy ball.
But what does this do?
- Cisco.
- Tracing.
- Let's find out if and when
you throw it hard enough...
[cackling]
Kaboom!
[laughs]
- He's downtown,
corner of DeMeo and Bilson.
- Bring me the Stretchy Man,
or else you're
going to go "boom-boom."
- My first supervillain
thunderdome challenge.
This is awesome.
- Ralph,
you do not know this guy.
He's dangerous.
- He's throwing bouncy balls
and wearing
a bedazzled pea coat.
I got this.
Hmm.
- You still haven't
taken that off, huh?
- Oh, I sleep in this.
You mind breaching me there?
It's a lot faster.
[explosion]
- [laughing]
Where are you, Stretchy Man?
I've got plenty more
where that came from.
- Nice suit, Fall Out Boy.
- Yuck,
yours could use some work.
- Ooh,
look at that cutting wit.
You wanted me, here I am.
- Great, do you
want to play, uh, catch?
- You're really blowing
this supervillain fight.
- Well, it's my
Central City return party.
And your death
will make me a star.
[laughing]
- Child's play.
- Okay, all right,
this is what I call
the Hurty-Squirty Gun.
[gun beeps]
[laughing]
- [screaming]
- Tricked ya!
It's acid,
with a little ingredient X.
I call it "axid."
- [screaming]
- He's panicking, his heart
rate is off the charts.
- Ralph, are you okay?
- [yelling]
Help!
- Burn, Stretchy Man, burn!
- [yells]
- Oof.
- Not today, Satan.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
What the hell did he do to me?
[groans]
- [grunts]
What the hell was that stuff?
- Looks like Axel created
some sort of super acid.
- It's got a ph level
in the negative 50s,
and all it did
was burn through your skin?
- God, if it were anybody else,
it would melt
right through them
like xenomorph blood.
- Like in...
- "Alien."
- It's "Aliens."
- But you said my cells
were polymerized.
- Uh, no...
- You said nothing
could hurt them.
- Dibny, I didn't say that.
I said your cells were bonded
unlike anything I've ever seen.
I've never seen acid like this,
and so, cannot be responsible
for things I have never seen.
- It definitely hurts.
- Mm-hmm, of course.
- Well, now we know
what your kryptonite is.
- What the hell is kryptonite?
- What?
- Oh, come on.
- Think I'm gonna heal?
- Probably.
- Eventually.
- Probably?
- Well, you know.
- I thought
I was indestructible.
- [laughs]
So did we.
- Get out.
Okay, well, Caitlin,
you can treat the wound
and manage the pain, right?
- As needed.
- Okay, well, the most
important thing
is that you're safe.
- [grunts]
- Ralph, oh, my God,
I'm so sorry.
Um, Axel is still out there.
We should track him down.
Um, oh, my God.
- This might sting a little.
- [groans]
- Excuse me, my wife was
supposed to be here
a half hour ago.
Could you see if...
Cool.
Hey.
I was just wondering
why you helped me.
- Because your dad helped me.
- [giggling]
Oh, are you okay?
- No, Mom, I'm not.
Stretchy Man's still alive.
All Dad's going to see
is that I failed.
He won't want to see me.
[sighs]
Who am I kidding?
I'll never be like him.
- I think you can be
even better than him.
[laughs]
You don't see it, but I do.
You're the real Trickster,
boo-boo.
- What's gotten into you?
- Okay, I didn't take my meds.
[giggling]
- Mom, you did that for me?
- I would do anything
for you, boo-boo!
[both laugh]
- Would you kill with me?
- It's like riding a tricycle.
You never forget.
Let's paint the town red.
- I know whose blood
we should use.
We just need a new trick to
strong-arm Stretch Armstrong.
- [gasps], no.
- No?
- What we need
is something better.
Because if there's
one thing I've realized,
it's behind
every great trick...
is an even better Prank.
[both cackle]
- Hey, guys.
Any luck finding Trickster?
- Joe, geo-tracking
is an art form.
It takes precision, it
takes finesse, it takes grace...
- It requires
none of those things.
It's simply the fact
that he's not a meta-human.
Regular humans
are harder to track.
- Is there anything you can't
suck the fun out of?
- Leaf peeping.
[computer beeps]
- Trickster.
- Hello again, Central City.
It's time for
the exciting new game show,
"Wheel of Misfortune."
With prizes so amazing,
you'll think you died.
And if you play your
cards right, you just might.
Here's your host,
the murderous matriarch,
Prank!
[both laughing]
- What do we have
in store for tonight?
- Well, we have chills,
thrills, and plenty of kills.
- These guys are
absolutely nuts.
- So, why don't we meet
our first contestants?
Ta-da!
- Ta-da!
[both laughing]
- They've got hostages.
- Shocking prizes
are in store.
- Oh, Prank,
what about the grand prize?
- Oh, I'm so glad you asked.
[both laughing]
Because we have an axid shower.
[gasps]
- Oh, no!
- Sorry, Mr. Beebo.
- Oh-ho.
- Beebo loves getting clean.
♪ ♪
Beebo has an owie.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco.
- Triangulating their signal.
- We need a special VIP to
come down for our special show.
So, if you're watching,
Stretchy Man,
why don't you come on down
and spin the wheel?
You have one hour,
or these nice people die.
[giggles]
- There you are.
They're at the old
Clarx Toys factory
in Lawrence Hills.
- Tick-tock, Stretchy Man.
Time's a-wasting.
So, let's spin that wheel!
[both laugh]
[computer beeps]
- I'm going to have CCPD
create a perimeter
a few blocks away,
so they can't escape.
- Harry, how are you
coming with a solvent
for Trickster's axid?
- Well, slowly.
Very difficult to neutralize
a solvent that hasn't existed
until today.
- You've got 59 minutes.
- All I need is 58.
- Ralph, suit up.
[tense music]
- Well, you wanted a new suit,
didn't you?
I even made it pocket-sized.
- Is it axid-proof?
I can't do it, guys.
- These people need our help.
- Yeah, sorry,
but me getting melted?
That is a deal-breaker.
- Were you only doing this
because you thought
you couldn't get hurt?
- Yeah, why the hell else
would I do this?
- Ralph, last year, I thought
I was going to die, too.
But that didn't stop me.
- Okay, well, that's
the difference between us then.
I'm not that strong
in the face of danger.
I'm out.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Psst, Barry!
[stretching]
[groaning]
- Ralph,
what are you doing here?
- I'm breaking you out.
- I mean, come on,
you're a hero.
Slap on some tights,
go be heroic.
- Ralph, there are
cameras everywhere, okay?
They would know within minutes
that I vanished.
- So? A minute to us
is like hours to you.
Just vibrate through the walls,
go slap Trickster around,
and you'll be back before
whatever passes for dinner
in this place.
- Trickster attacked again?
- Yeah, he and his mommy
want to tussle with me,
but I have a rule against
fighting terrorists
with an Oedipus complex, so.
This looks like a job
for the F-L-A-S-H.
- I'm sorry,
why is this different?
You've done a good job
handling bad guys so far.
- [sighs]
I got hurt.
Axel created some kind of acid
that, we're guessing,
can probably kill me.
I'm not ready to die.
- [chuckles]
Look, this job,
it has a way
of making you feel invincible.
But every once in a while,
a little mortality check
shows up.
- I've been trying so hard
to ignore this feeling, but...
I'm not fearless like you are.
- [scoffs]
Ralph, I'm not fearless.
I mean, I wake up
every day in this cell,
and feel like there's nothing
I can do to help anyone.
And, I mean, that terrifies me.
I used to be
somebody who saved,
and now
I'm just Barry Allen.
Inmate number 3562.
- So let me spring you.
- That's not my point.
Having the ability to
help someone, but do nothing.
That is a far worse death
than anything
that Trickster has for you.
But rising above that fear
and saving those lives,
that's a greater life.
All right, so rise up.
I don't think
it's a stretch for you.
- [chuckles]
You really believe I can do it?
- Yes, you just need
to believe in yourself.
[whistle chirps]
[buzzing]
[tense music]
Hey, you know your way
out of here, right?
[gate buzzing]
- Yeah.
- You got one hour!
♪ ♪
- Scans are reading some kind
of container on the roof.
It looks new.
- Galvanized steel.
[zipper locks]
That's where
they're keeping the axid.
All right,
I will neutralize it.
And you two guys,
you get the hostages out.
Oh, we're gonna need
the ice queen.
- Oh, that's not how it works,
I can't just...
both: Lexi La Roche!
- It was her childhood bully.
There's a lot of
repressed anger in there.
Let's go!
[dramatic music]
- Oh, boy, here we go.
- Thank you.
Big Sir.
My dad saved your life
in here, didn't he?
That's why you helped me out.
How?
- I had stomach pains for days.
Your dad found me, figured my
appendix was about to burst.
Prison doctors were gone
for the night.
There's no way they could have
made it back in time.
But Doc Henry convinced
Warden Wolfe
to do the surgery.
He operated and saved my life.
- And that's why you owed him.
- Now, we're even.
♪ ♪
- Big Sir.
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Remember, anything in here that
looks fun is probably lethal.
- Just like me.
- Nice.
Okay, let's deliver these
delivery people to safety.
- Or we could just leave them
and kill Trickster and Prank.
- Remember that talk about
murdering your way
out of problems?
Yeah, we don't do that.
- Yet.
[tense music]
- We're going to
get you out of here.
- Ooh, Beebo hungry.
[giggles]
Beebo likes to play.
Beebo...
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
- Tricked ya!
- I'm guessing
the plan didn't work?
- Help!
- Harry, it's a trap.
They've got Caitlin and Cisco.
I'm on my way.
- No, you're not.
I am.
- Then you're
going to need this.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Groovy.
[muffled grunts]
[grunting continues]
[crowbar thudding]
- Hey!
Leave him alone.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I told you you'd be sorry.
You won't get lucky twice.
♪ ♪
[groans]
- Like father, like son, eh?
- Harry,
are you on the roof yet?
- Yes, and so is the axid.
All right.
♪ ♪
- You need
to neutralize the axid.
We're running out of time.
- Yep, thank you,
I'm aware of that.
[computers beep]
[both laugh]
- Uh-oh.
- Now, we asked for one hero.
But now, we've got two!
- Oh!
It's time for our
Showcase Showdown,
so let's spin that wheel,
and see what fun prize
awaits our new friends.
- [giggles]
- Harry, tell me you've got it.
[computer beeps]
- Don't got it.
- Hurry up, I haven't
killed anyone in years.
♪ ♪
- Oh, a tie.
Hmm, I guess they die together.
- [gasps]
- [claps]
♪ ♪
[window shatters]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
- Nice outfit.
- Thanks,
I've got a great tailor.
Now let everyone go,
pranksters,
and no one gets hurt.
- We thought you chickened out,
Stretchy Man.
- Actually, I did.
See, I thought I was
pretty much invincible
until you and your
oversized water pistol
put the fear of God in me.
- You're welcome.
- And I was ready
to throw in the towel.
But then I visited
a friend of mine.
And he helped me remember
that no one is fearless.
But real heroes, they find
a way to rise above that fear
and make a difference anyway.
Even if it kills them
in the process.
So, this is me, rising up.
Hopefully without
the dying part.
Now let my friends go.
[both applaud]
- First of all, great speech.
So inspired,
it melted my heart.
- Oh, thank you, I worked
on it on the way over.
- Now let's melt yours.
[both laughing]
Shoot him, boo-boo!
♪ ♪
- [yelling]
- Oh, boo-boo!
- I'd give up if I were you.
- How about I melt
your friends instead?
♪ ♪
- Harry, now.
- I don't got it.
- Harry?
- No!
♪ ♪
- Say good-bye
to your little friends!
- Harry!
- [yells]
[screaming]
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt!
[laughs]
I'm not dying!
Why am I not dying?
- Because I got it.
- Yes, nice work, guys!
♪ ♪
- I'm going to live, whoo!
Oh, don't even think
about running.
Any time.
Okay, uh...
you got scissors anywhere?
- You know what they say,
detective?
The family that slays together
stays together.
- Yeah, in prison.
- Hey, come on.
You can't keep a Trickster
behind bars for long.
- Oh, we'll see about that.
- You were amazing.
Can we do it again
in 10 to 15 years?
- Boo-boo.
I'm going to break us
out of here in two.
- Get in the damn car.
- [giggling]
[both cackling]
[reporters clamoring]
- Is it true that you took down
Trickster and Prank
single-handedly?
- How long have you been
a superhero?
- Are you single?
- Yes, about an hour,
oh, hell yes.
Do you like shrimp?
- No.
But I'm sure
the people of Central City
would love to thank you,
Stretchy Man.
- [sighs]
That's not my name.
- Then what should we call you?
I mean, you do stretch.
- No, I don't stretch,
I contort.
I elasticize,
I elongate, man.
- The Elongated Man?
It was just an expression.
- It has a certain...
- I don't know.
- "Je ne sais quoi" to it.
- I like it, too.
- Well, I hate it.
[all groan]
- Well, maybe you should have
let me do the naming.
- Exactly.
- Oh, don't worry,
you'll get your chance.
There's no way
this is going to stick.
both: Probably gonna stick.
- The Elongated Man?
Please, it's so literal.
You think Prince
would have settled
for "Shorty Guitar Man"?
- Hey.
- No way.
And like The Purple One,
I too need something
that hints at the true depth
of my sexy nature.
- Like The Flash.
- Exactly.
He's a fast operator,
gets the job done in seconds.
Or Killer Frost.
- What can I say?
When you got it, you got it.
- You got it.
- Eh.
Hey, Joe.
- Mmm?
- What should I do?
- Man, do whatever it takes
to keep the city safe.
Just like the rest of us.
- I could live with that.
- Guess I'll be looking out
for you a bit longer.
- I didn't get involved
because I wanted a favor,
I just wanted to help.
Piece of advice,
you want to survive in here,
find a friend.
- [laughs]
Your father would be
very proud of you.
- Thanks.
Did my dad call you Big Sir?
- No, he called me Dave.
- [chuckles]
- Allen, you've got a visitor.
- Well, whatever you said
to Ralph must have landed.
He risked his life
to save Caitlin and Cisco,
thanks to you.
- I just brought out what was
already inside of him.
- You seem to have that effect
on a lot of people.
- [scoffs]
- What?
- Just turns out being in here
isn't so different
from being out there.
[poignant music]
- Except we're not together.
And I can't touch you anymore.
♪ ♪
[vibrating]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- Coffee, that's all I get
for being a hero?
- What do you want, a cookie?
- Ooh, don't mind if I do.
Come on, man.
The thing about wearing a mask
is no one even knows
you're a good guy.
- Them's the breaks, kid.
Ah, yes, there's that
delicious nectar.
Hey, thanks for getting
this coffee, by the way.
- Who, me?
I'm broke.
- I didn't even bring my wallet
with me.
- I don't even own a wallet.
- Are you serious?
- Allen always pays.
- Oh, my God.
- No worries.
Uh, always pay it forward.
That's my motto, you know?
Because at any given moment,
one of us could need
a helping hand.
Like now,
you two total strangers,
you know, were short on cash,
and then someone just
steps out of the blue and helps
out in a totally random way,
am I right?
- Uh-huh.
- And you know,
it's more than just karma.
It's the principle
of infinite consequence
at work in our lives.
And it's always expanding.
Creating positive sums
on an infinite basis.
Isn't that amazing?
- Yes?
- You know what's amazing?
That shirt's pretty amazing.
- Yeah, thanks, yeah,
it's a classic.
"Oregon Trail,"
I love this game.
Have a great day.
Okay.
- A nice, beautiful girl,
and Ralph Dibny
doesn't offer her
a delicious crustacean buffet?
- Mmm, I think
she's too smart for me.
- Self awareness
from Ralph Dibny?
I think there's hope
for you yet.
- That's a stretch.
- Is that where
we freeze frame?
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.