Previously on The Flash...
The Flash is back!
How did you get your powers?
You're not gonna believe it.
And do you too wanna know
the best part?
I wasn't the only one.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes.
- This isn't goodbye.
- No.
Will I see you later?
He's right where you wanted him.
What do we do now?
We find the others.
Begin recording.
Observations on subject number two.
Name, Rebecca Sharpe,
or as she prefers...
- The plebeian sobriquet Becky.
- Hey, I'm Becky.
It's Becky with a "Y,"
not an "I-E" or an "E-E."
Just "Y." And you heard me
say no milk, right?
'Cause I am
severely lactose intolerant, like...
Subject was born in Sarasota, Florida.
The first indignity in a life
full of unfortunate circumstances.
That is definitely not soy.
Subject lives with her boyfriend.
Almost there, almost there,
almost there!
Kenny!
We are going to deal with this
in five to 10 minutes!
Correction.
Subject previously lived
with her boyfriend.
Subject's occupation,
blackjack dealer.
Or should I hit?
Subject's temperament.
I don't know, man, I think
you should just hit. Why don't you hit?
Defeatist.
- Okay, I'll hit.
- Great. Perfect.
- And...
- Twenty-one!
It is here.
Oh, wow.
- Here you go, sir, congratulations.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Here you go.
- Sure.
Oh, that's nice, thank you.
- Looks like I found my good luck charm.
- Hey!
My appletini!
Oh, no, oh, no.
Can I maybe just get
a reference, you think?
No?
Subject believes
no matter what she does,
the universe will conspire
to punish her.
Another job... Ow!
Or as she writes
on her Myspace page,
"I am jinxed."
Great! There goes another car!
It's okay, I'm fine.
Subject's low self-esteem suggests
she will be easily manipulated.
Wait! Wait!
Ow!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Come on! I'm here!
Hey! Yes, thank you, universe!
Finally, some good luck! Hi!
Okay.
Barry!
- Where are you?
- I don't know!
I lost Caitlin.
There's too many of them, man.
No, you can take them.
Just listen to me.
You just need to do one thing.
Run, Barry. Run!
Come on!
They got me.
You have failed this city.
For real, Chad? In the back?
Suck it, old man.
Oh...
Wait, did you guys die already?
- Well, Chad...
- He just told us...
Come on. Come on.
I don't know what's wrong with kids
these days. You're churlish.
You better watch yourself, Chad.
Come at me at the paintball field
next time, I'll kick your little a...
Mrs. McConell, how are you doing?
Chad's a treasure, he really is.
Pretzel for Caitlin...
Corndog for Iris.
Two franks for Cisco.
Yes, thank you.
Three burgers, five churros
and six funnel cakes for Barry.
Look at all of this junk.
Guys, I'm really sorry.
If the pipes in the house weren't
making this weird, annoying sound,
I would have just actually
had you all over for dinner.
Squeaky pipes at the West house,
what a surprise.
Really? You're familiar with this sound?
Oh, yeah, you mean the...
- Yeah.
- It's been doing that for 18 years?
Every house has a personality,
ours just likes to be heard.
Oh, my gosh, they broke up.
The Wexler-Waclawiks broke up.
- For real?
- Yes.
- Hell, yeah!
- Yes!
Who are the Wexler-Wa-claws-wilix,
and why are we happy
that their love is dead?
They are a couple that were
getting married at the Propizio
the weekend of the second,
which means now the venue is open.
That's amazing. What good luck.
Yeah, so, now, we just
have to put a deposit down.
- I'll run it over.
- No, already covered, babe.
Oh.
Oh, God. Breach alert, guys.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Uh...
Hey, Harry. Um, is Jesse not coming?
So, um...
I thought Jesse and I
were having date night.
Yeah, that's what you thought.
Let me just...
Okay.
Let's... Just let me...
- Okay, so...
- Ahem. Hey, Wally, it's me.
Good to see you.
So, I've been doing
some thinking, and...
You know, we've both been so busy...
Stupid hologram,
it's the darn Atlantean plastic.
It's really shoddy workmanship.
- Sorry about this.
- What is this thing?
Break... Breakup cube.
You don't have breakup cubes
on your Earth?
It's not good. Okay, okay.
A breakup cube is, uh...
Kind of what it sounds like.
You know,
you record a message
for the person you wanna...
The person,
and you pick a music setting,
and then there's...
A tissue pops out, if you need that.
You know, a breakup cube.
Jesse's breaking up with me
with a cube?
Seems like a really convenient way
to break somebody's heart.
Exactly.
What did she say in the message?
Well, you know, you heard.
"You're a great guy,"
I don't remember.
- Don't you have total recall?
- Yeah. No, no.
Don't. I did, I don't.
I did, but I don't.
Come on, don't make me...
She... You heard. She said that
you are a great, great guy,
and that she was busy on our Earth
and that you're busy here,
filling in for, you know...
On this Earth. And she just felt that
you guys were a little out of sync.
You know? And that she needed some time
to work on her stuff, you know?
"It's not you, it's me."
Not me. "Her" me. Her.
Not me, her. And she said, you know,
"I'll never forget you, Wally West,
because you're amazing," and then...
That you were her first.
And a bunch of other stuff,
not important.
So, the heeds talk,
you don't need that, right?
You're a tough guy, right, West?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Um...
Doesn't want a cube. I don't blame him.
211s at First National
and O'Sullivan Bank.
Could be a spree.
The Central City Bank's on
that avenue, too. I'll check it out.
- We're not done.
- What?
I'm sorry, I don't know why the app
crashed, but this one's on the house.
Oh.
Find a penny, pick it up,
then all day, you'll have good luck.
So true.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
It is a good afternoon,
Mr. Security Man.
Please, don't touch the oven, Mom.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Aw... You waited for me!
I see her.
She's getting away in a Prius.
Last time I checked,
the Flash is faster than a Prius.
Oh!
What the hell?
That's the least secure
security footage I've ever seen.
Yeah, that's not even
the strangest thing she made happen.
I mean,
I slipped on a barrel of marbles.
It was like I was in a cartoon.
That's some seriously bad luck.
Yeah, no such thing as luck.
Yeah? Tell that to my cousin, Hector.
He got jinxed by an ex,
hasn't been able to find
a mall parking spot for three years.
Hey, so, we ran the sketches you made
us through the CCPD database, and...
Her name's Becky Sharpe,
she's 24 years old.
- No priors.
- No priors?
Then why is she in the database?
Because in the last three years
she has lived in Central City,
she's been rear-ended four times,
her identity stolen twice.
A cat burglar literally burgled her cat.
Okay, you see, Harry,
that is bad juju.
Okay, Ramon, what you call juju,
I call quantum entanglement.
Discrete quantum particles
are connected and when triggered,
they simulate a synchronicity
that to the untrained eye, to the
common eye, could seem like luck.
So, if Becky can affect the particles
around her in a positive way,
then their connected particles
start spinning negatively.
So, when good things happen to her,
bad things happen all around her.
Great, she's got a good luck field.
- She's a meta.
- Well, except, she can't be,
I mean, she's only been in
Central City for three years.
Yeah, so,
there's no way she was affected
by the particle accelerator explosion.
Well, neither was Kilg%re.
We saw firsthand what he could do.
Not to sound like a broken record,
but where the hell are
all these new metas coming from?
You know what, maybe the scanners
in the suit picked something up.
You said you took all the tech out.
Okay, well, I left something in.
Okay? Sue me.
Cecile needs me at the house.
You guys let me know
what you find out, all right?
All right.
- There.
- Yeah, I see it, okay.
The suit definitely registered trace
amounts of dark matter on Becky.
So, if there was another
dark matter incident...
We need to figure out how and where
it happened, ASAP.
I'll calibrate your satellite to scan
for the same dark matter in the suit.
- No, you won't.
- Yeah, I will.
- Don't touch the satellite. Don't...
- I'll be touching it.
Oh, something just arrived for me
at the loft. I gotta go.
What?
You called the plumber?
Joe West, I cannot keep
living with that sound.
You know, this house is, uh...
- Bitchin'?
- No. It's in need of some work.
In my certified opinion,
you need all new piping.
It'll set you back $15 thou.
Mmm.
Okay. Thank you so much.
You've given us a lot to think about.
And I mean a whole lot.
Fifteen thousand.
My great uncle paid less
for this whole place.
I guess I'm gonna have to break open
the piggy bank.
Or, you know,
we could take that fifteen,
we could put it towards
a down payment on something new.
Ooh...
You're suggesting that
we sell my house?
Babe, I'm just saying,
you know, this is...
This is a really big place for
a couple of empty nesters like us,
and there's always gonna be something
that's gonna need replacing.
Let me think about it, okay?
- Think about it.
- I'll think about it.
Barry! Oh, my God, turn around!
- I did.
- Did you see?
- No, I didn't see!
- You saw!
I did see, but just for a second.
Which is like an eternity
for a speedster.
You know it's bad luck to see a bride
in her dress before the wedding day.
Too late.
- What happened?
- The Propizio called.
We're not gonna be able to
have our wedding there.
What? Why?
Well, the villa burned down,
I guess a crème brûlée competition
got a little heated.
Okay, well, thankfully,
we have our backup.
No, another couple booked it
this morning.
It's okay, though, it's okay.
If we can stop evil,
time-traveling speedsters
from destroying the planet,
we can find a wedding venue.
Barry, our wedding is in six weeks!
It'll work out, okay?
I would marry you anytime, anywhere.
Kobe beef, my favorite.
Becky! What are the chances
I'd run into you?
Is this your secretary?
Funny, you said she was haggard.
- No, I never said that.
- Let me get that for you.
I don't understand.
Your plan revolves around this dolt?
Who makes soup so hot?
As lusterless as Rebecca is, she may
be the most formidable of them all.
Then why don't we get her now?
The capricious nature of her powers
warrants further observation.
Oh, man, are those live lobsters?
- Gimme that.
- Stop hovering, okay?
- You're not holding it...
- I know how to read a dark matter...
- Not from where I see, you don't.
- Oh, yeah, good one.
Don't you have
somewhere else to be? Like,
maybe breaking
another speedster's heart?
- Have one...
- Sorry I'm late.
Iris and I just lost two wedding
venues in less than 24 hours.
- Bad juju.
- Gimme that, okay?
It's more of a test. All right.
Here we go and adjust...
- Sorry.
Here. Right here.
This was where Becky Sharpe
was exposed to dark matter.
- Here?
- Yes.
It can't be,
this is the middle of the street.
- It's not even an intersection.
- My scans are accurate.
- Accurate?
Explain how there's nothing
within miles of here
capable of even creating dark matter.
There was three weeks ago.
This is where I came out
of the Speed Force.
No, it isn't.
You came out in Ivy City.
No, I ran there after. I remember
now, this is where I came out.
This is where the portal opened.
And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
I can only imagine
how many meta-humans you created.
My best guess...
A busload.
We did it? We brought dark matter
into Central City?
When you pulled me out
of the Speed Force, yeah.
All the people on that bus,
we turned them into metas.
Every time we try to do something
right, it goes horribly wrong.
We're cursed.
Maybe we should burn some sage.
Guys, we're not cursed.
You're not cursed.
You should be cursed at.
Okay, why should we be "cursed at"?
You should be cursed at
because you opened the Speed Force
- without consulting me.
- Okay, I don't think we need to...
All right.
Okay, I did consult you,
and you were the one
who gave me the calculations
in the first place.
I told you not to use them
without consulting me.
I said, Ramon,
don't use the calculations
- without consulting me!
- Guys!
I heard you,
I didn't see the need for that.
And that's why
you should be cursed at.
- What does that even mean?
- What does that mean? It means...
Okay, you know what, this is
exactly why we didn't contact you.
'Cause the last thing
we need around here
is more of your salty-ass attitude!
If you don't need my salty attitude,
maybe you should carry on without me.
- I'll let myself out.
- You're going back to your Earth?
- I'll breach you there right now.
- "I'll breach you there right now!"
That's not what I sound like.
That was really high.
Listen, Cisco,
I know Harry could stand to work
- on his bedside manner, but...
- You know what, we don't need him.
What we need is to focus
on catching this meta, am I right?
Yeah, you're right.
But Becky doesn't seem like
one of our typical villains.
I think if we could track her down,
maybe we could get through to her.
Hey, Cecile.
What?
I'm on my way.
I need you to run me to the house.
- You said you...
- I need you to run me to the house.
Yes, sir.
Ah...
What happened?
The ceiling went
from clanking to howling, and then
it just started pouring
all of this stuff down.
- We need to turn the water off, stat.
- Yeah.
So, the water valve
is in the crawl space. Um...
Don't ever go into the crawl space.
I hear you, loud and clear.
Barry, thank you very much
for your help.
I'm gonna go check upstairs.
Man, why is this happening?
- Did that girl jinx us?
- No.
No. Nobody jinxed us.
This house is just...
- What's another word for old?
- Vintage.
- Cecile thinks I should sell it.
Yeah, what do you think?
I think she's got a point.
Life would be a hell of a lot easier
in a brand-new house.
Sounds like an easy decision.
It should be, but...
This house has got one thing
no other house will ever have.
Remember I measured you kids
every birthday?
Yeah, I outgrew Iris at 12.
She kept saying she'd catch up.
All of my memories of you kids
are tied into these walls.
- How can I give that up?
- You don't have to give that up, Joe.
You'll always have those memories
no matter where you live.
Trust me.
When I came to live here
after my mom died, I learned that
it doesn't matter where you live.
It only matters
that you have people that love you.
Hold on. What's up?
Great. Okay. I'll go there now.
Thank you.
We're not jinxed. If we were,
Cisco wouldn't have found Becky.
She's at Jitters, I'm going there now.
Winner, winner.
Another winner.
Becky? Hi, do you mind if I sit here?
Oh, today's my lucky day,
but you're not my type at all.
Can I sit?
Um...
Becky, you're probably wondering
how I know your name.
Mmm... It's written on my cup.
Right. Um...
But that's not how I... You see,
I work for the CCPD as a CSI.
I investigate very special people.
Celebrities?
No, not celebrities. Meta-humans,
which is what I think you are.
See, I think
you were exposed to dark matter
on a city bus three weeks ago.
I think I would know if I was
exposed to dark matter. That's weird.
Becky, I know, you've been having
a lot of luck lately.
And that you took some money
from the Central City Bank
that doesn't belong to you.
- How do you know all that?
- I just do.
Look, getting powers is overwhelming.
I'm sure you don't know how they work
or what you should do with them.
I have some idea.
Uh-uh-uh.
Do you really wanna test your luck?
Bad things happen to people
that get in my way.
Listen, CSI guy.
My entire life has been one piece
of crummy luck after the next.
Look, we all have ups and downs in life.
No, not Becky Sharpe.
I have only ever been dealt bad hands.
But I knew one day, the universe
would see it made a mistake.
And then I'd have the run of the table.
I got on that bus and Lady Luck
smiled on me.
Becky, this isn't some higher power
fixing a miscalculation.
You have powers and they're affecting
everyone around you,
making them feel as awful
as you used to feel.
I'm sorry about that.
But maybe it's just their turn.
Maybe for once, everyone else
can feel for a second,
how bad I felt my entire life.
Anyway, there is nothing you can do
to stop me.
Toodles.
So, what are we gonna do?
I don't know. I mean, I'm not sure yet.
I can't get close enough to her
without triggering bad luck.
Seriously, that girl's a hazard.
Hazard. That's the one.
Maybe that means the jinx is gone.
Her powers only work
in her immediate vicinity.
She didn't jinx us.
And the house
is still falling to pieces.
It's been falling apart for years,
just like, really slowly.
Plus, Jesse dumped me, too.
I know, dude. And, you know, that sucks.
And we're up against a meta
we can't even touch,
and we're the ones
who made her in the first place.
Guys, do you have any idea
how ridiculous you all sound?
We have not been jinxed,
or cursed, all right?
We make our own luck, right?
So, what do you say we focus,
and we figure this out?
Hey, Iris, you're where?
- Oh, come on. Hey.
- Hey.
Why did you want me to put on a shirt
and meet you at a funeral?
No, no, I wanted you
to meet me at this church.
- What?
- We're getting married.
Here, put this on.
- Excuse me?
- Barry,
we've had the worst luck, okay?
From the Dominators and Savitar,
to gorillas, and now, these bus metas.
And on top of everything else,
now, we're cursed.
Iris, we're not cursed.
Barry, look, you said that
you would marry me
- anytime, anywhere.
- Well, this is...
And I just feel if we don't get
married now, it's never gonna happen.
That's not true, okay? I mean...
Oh. Our turn. Our turn.
Go, go, go.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- Excuse me. Beautiful service.
- So sorry.
- I love this coffin...
Hey, that's...
- Hi.
- Hello.
Can I help you?
- Ah, yes, we would like to get married.
- Yes, we would.
- Right now.
- Oh.
Would you give us a moment
to reset the altar?
Oh, no, no, that won't be necessary.
Look, we'll just... Watch. Watch.
Hey? Okay.
She's excited, sorry.
Flip that around.
- Yes.
- You shouldn't have done that.
I know, it's fine.
Okay.
We are here today to join...
Um...
- That's you.
- Me? Bartholomew Henry Allen.
- And...
- Iris Ann West.
...in holy matrimony.
- Excuse me.
- You okay?
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
Kevin, did you use
the cinnamon incense?
You know he's allergic to it.
Shame on you!
- No need to shame the little boy.
- No, you're fine.
You're fine. Walk it off, Father.
It's fine.
- That did not just happen.
- You know, it was a...
- Very nice funeral.
- Really, Barry?
That was golden!
Don't shoot, okay?
I'm here to apologize.
I know you're trying to help us
fix our own colossal screw up.
- Yeah, like always.
- Yeah, I know.
I mean, I actually thought
you'd be at home by now,
but here you are, working away.
Well, things are a little complicated
on Earth-2.
Huh.
- Everything okay with Jesse?
- Yes.
I mean, yes. If you must know,
I spent the summer assembling
a support staff for her, so...
- Oh, like Team Quick.
- No.
- Team Jesse.
- Jesse and the Quicksters?
- They're not called that.
Well, they should be, that
sounds like an awesome team.
It is an awesome team
because I assembled it.
But then Jesse goes
and kicks me off the team, all right?
Apparently, I'm too much like me,
whatever that means.
I push too hard, you know? Too many
tests, too many training sessions.
And I don't allow the team enough
time for their personal bonding.
I don't understand Millennials.
Anyway, they took a vote.
I'm out. I don't even have
a home to return to now.
I can't even go back
to my own Earth.
I'm sure you can empathize,
right, Ramon?
'Cause you know what I'm like. Well,
you know what? We'll handle Sharpe.
And then I'll be out of your hair.
Guys, there are low probability
events happening all over the city.
- Becky's quantum field is expanding.
- Okay, that's not possible.
- Yeah, no, her powers were localized.
- Not anymore.
Babe, you in there?
The door's jammed.
One sec!
Guys, the quantum field
is getting higher.
My boss said you were
bad luck, sir, but I figured
what are the odds a pilot has
a goose fly into his engine twice?
Bird strike!
Mayday.
This is Flight 512 to tower. We lost
an engine and are coming down.
When did Hazard get so powerful?
Every action has an equal
and opposite reaction. So...
The more good luck she experiences,
the more bad luck she spreads.
She must be experiencing
an extreme level of good luck
for her quantum field
to be expanding like this.
- Where is she now?
- She went back to work.
Snake eyes!
For the 37th time.
Bringing your winnings to
- $1.2 million!
- ...million!
Give me those things.
Hi. Okay, here we go.
Come on, mama!
Guys, if Becky keeps winning,
then bad luck will keep spreading.
This could destroy the whole city.
- Okay, keep calm, all right?
- Okay, keep calm.
Nothing's going wrong here.
Guys, the particle accelerator
turned back on.
It's gonna explode.
Four minutes
to particle accelerator activation.
Harry, Cisco, status report?
Generators turned themselves on,
we gotta shut 'em down.
Flight 512 to tower,
we're attempting a water landing.
Cecile!
Damn it.
Barry, you've gotta find Hazard.
I'm almost at the casino.
Hazard's quantum field is increasing.
How much worse can it get?
Hello, my old friend.
Let's keep this winning streak
going, shall we?
Yes. Okay, cherry. Here we go, cherry.
Cherry, cherry, cherry,
cherry, cherry, cherry.
Cherry. Cherry! Cherry,
it's a cherry.
Gimme two, gimme two.
Cherry, cherry, cherry,
cherry, cherry, cherry.
How is that even possible?
Wait, no!
Starboard's fan blade
is just disintegrated.
We're not gonna make it to the water.
- Barry, what happened?
- Well...
She's playing the slots
and I cuffed myself.
- Oh, honey.
- I know. We need to get 'em off.
They're dampening my powers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm trying.
Hydrogen particle hatch.
We need to seal it.
Here we go.
Cherry, bang bang.
Cherry, bang bang. Cherry!
Cherry, bang bang, cherry.
Cherry, bang bang.
There's two cherries.
- Come on.
- Hey, look, it's the Flash!
No, hey, there's no fire.
It's not a fire!
Someone set off the alarm! Calm down!
- Babe, you okay?
- I think so.
Damn it, out back.
- Out back. Be careful.
- Okay. Okay.
- One minute to activation.
- Got it.
- Nope, don't got it.
- That just opened the electron hatch.
Yes, I am on fire, I know.
There's no fire!
Come on, cherry, pop.
Cherry, pop, cherry.
Damn!
Barry, I can't get the cuffs off.
Yeah, well, now, we have a sign
to get off of me, too.
Cherry number three.
Pop, cherry, pop.
Brakes, brakes, brakes!
Thirty seconds to activation.
Nope, nope.
- What're you doing? Come on.
- Wait, wait.
- Let it go.
- What?
- Let the accelerator turn on.
- Harry!
Let the accelerator turn on.
Trust me.
Ten seconds to activation.
This is it. Last one!
Five, four,
three, two.
Here we go.
Cherry, pop, cherry!
No. What? Star?
No, I don't understand. I lost?
The starboard thrusters are alive.
We're gonna make it.
Good.
What just happened?
The hydrogen electron collision
released a charge
that temporarily negated
Hazard's quantum field.
We did it.
You did it.
How did you know to do that?
Lucky guess.
Okay.
- Hi. Um...
- Hi.
Is there, like, any chance that
you're not gonna arrest me?
No?
- I understand. Sure.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Right this way.
- Yep.
Ramon.
I owe you an apology.
Okay.
- That was it.
- Okay, all right.
How about something like...
"I am sorry for blaming
everything on you"?
Or, "I am sorry for 'cursing' at you."
Yep, that's good.
That's good. That.
Pretend I said that.
Guess I'll take it where I can get it.
All right, good talk.
- Hey?
- Hmm.
You don't have to go back to Earth-2.
What?
You saved the day.
That's your get-out-of-jackass-jail
free card.
Plus, you're family.
You'll always have a home here.
Thank you...
I appreciate the sentiment,
it's just that...
- This is not my world.
- Oh, and Earth-2 is?
Did you make a bunch of friends
there that I don't know about?
Are they all tall, brooding dudes
with bad haircuts?
I have...
I have colleagues.
Work colleagues.
And some of them, I don't dislike.
Exactly my point. You've spent
so much time worrying about Jesse
and talking to dead people,
that you never even stopped
to make a life for yourself.
Wait a second, Ramon, are you
literally saying I don't have a life?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
You don't have a life.
But you can make one.
With us, right here. We'll help you.
'Cause God knows
you're gonna need that help.
- No, I don't think so.
- I don't think so, either.
Becky is locked up in the meta wing
at Iron Heights.
Something tells me our bad luck
streak has come to an end.
Good. We can't afford
to blow this place up a third time.
So, look at these heat scans taken
from the satellite three weeks ago.
That's the Central City bus.
- That's the bus?
- That's the bus.
Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
Twelve markers, twelve metas.
Now that we know how many there are,
we won't have to wait for them
to come to us.
- We can go right to them.
- Well, two down.
Yep, we got this.
Yeah, you do.
What's wrong, Wally?
You guys tell me. I mean,
the city was about to blow up,
no one realized I wasn't here?
Where did you go, Wall?
I went to Earth-2, I had to talk
to Jesse, hear it from her.
She told me she needs to focus
on herself, and I get it.
And I think I have to do
the same, right?
So, I'm leaving Central City.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go stay with a friend
in Blue Valley for a while.
Every hero has their own journey.
If yours is taking you on a new path,
you owe it to yourself to go.
Yeah.
Good luck.
Kid Flash.
I don't want anything more
than for you to find
what you're looking for.
But I've spent so much time
without you in my life.
I don't wanna lose you.
You'll never lose me, Dad.
Plus, I'm a speedster.
You need me and I'll come running.
I love you, son.
Yeah. Love you.
You sure?
Yeah.
Well, don't forget, Central City
will always be the home of Kid Flash.
I won't.
- Don't be a stranger.
- No.
- I love you.
- I love you more.
Okay.
West leaves.
Allen returns, West leaves.
Move, counter-move.
- What's your point?
- Simply that
a mysterious stranger comes to town
to seek out the Flash...
Causes us to open the Speed Force.
Which causes the creation
of a dozen new metas.
Right.
Hold on, you think the guy
behind the samurai robot...
Samuroid.
You think he wanted us to create
a busload of metas?
I think it's all connected.
Why would anyone wanna create metas?
I don't know.
Whoever they are, they've got
a seriously warped way of thinking.
They identified the targets
sooner than we planned.
Perhaps they're smarter
than you gave them credit.
Perhaps.
But I'm smarter.
Oh!
Just when I thought it was safe
to get back in the house.
Hey. I may not be a craftsman expert
such as yourself,
but I can handle plastering
a couple of holes in the wall.
Babe, you don't have to do this.
This is our home and it is
a disaster zone right now,
so, I'm doing my part to fix it up.
Oh... I appreciate that.
But, you know, Cecile...
- You were right.
- Hmm?
It's time for me to let this place go.
I... It took me a minute to get there,
I'm not good with change,
you know that, but once I did,
I realized that whatever house
I'm in with you,
I'm gonna love.
So, we might as well get one
with a dishwasher,
and a Jacuzzi.
Jacuzzi.
Oh...
- I love you.
- Funny thing, babe.
- Hmm?
I've actually had a change of heart.
- What?
- Hmm.
You wanna stay?
- Really?
- Yeah.
You told me that you couldn't have
asked for a better place
to raise your kids and
it made me look at this house
with new eyes.
Especially after I found out...
Joe...
I'm pregnant.
Joe?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::