[Cisco] Previously on The Flash...
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must
be Gypsy. It's nice to meet you.
- Who are you?
- Daddy!
[Breacher] You're a warrior who would
fight to protect the only person I love.
[Cisco]
I wanna take the cure.
[device whirring]
You're the person that
I want to run this team when I'm gone.
Sorry I went all ice-daggery on you.
I still don't like you.
Ramsey, don't do this.
[Ramsey] As long as I feed,
I could live forever.
[exhales]
So, this is where you've been hiding.
[Cisco] Sometimes the truth is
the hardest lie to see through.
And when you can't put your faith
in the truth,
all you have left... is yourself.
You're under arrest, Ramon.
- [guns cocking]
- [weapons charging]
[Iris West] Barry,
we don't have to do this.
[Barry] It's Tahiti, not Iron Heights.
I know, but we've got too much going on
right now to be taking a vacation.
Okay. Look, it's two days, all right?
Ramsey's been off the grid
for two weeks.
And Crisis is coming, no matter what.
Let me take you someplace special,
where we can have
fruity umbrella drinks,
and get sand between our toes.
I do like us.
And we're even better with mai tais.
Take a look. It's in a book.
[Cisco chuckling]
Hey, thought you guys
fathwoomed out of here.
Uh, we just wanted to make sure
you guys were okay
holding down the fort
while we were gone.
We're good. Rest easy, lovebirds.
"Team Leader" is my new middle name.
What was it before?
- Baracus.
- As in Barracas, Argentina?
No, as in Mr. T. What...
My mom was a big A-Team fan.
Wish mine was.
Could've been Hannibal Dibny.
Hannibal?
Please, you're Murdock on your best day.
You guys have fun.
I'm gonna hold it down with a little
help from my friend, the B.A.R.I.
- "The Barry"? I'm standing right here.
- Not you, Barry.
[computer chimes]
[Cisco] B.A.R.I.
Barry Allen Replicated Intelligence.
Aw.
It's my decision-making algorithm.
So, if there's a problem,
this is gonna tell us what to do?
Yes, and since it's based on
his past leadership choices,
it'll tell me how to handle
any situation exactly like he would.
I'm flattered... I think.
Huh. What is Barry's favorite thing
that I make him for breakfast?
Uh, banana.
[computer processing]
Oh.
Who's next?
Okay, computer,
what's Barry's favorite movie?
Empire.
[computer processing]
Oh, thank God. [sighs]
Actually, I mean, I love...
Loved Empire Strikes Back my whole life,
but now that I think about it...
Oh, God.
My favorite movie is Jurassic Park.
- There it is.
- [Barry] How does it do that?
Fuzzy logic and AI intuition, my guy.
With the B.A.R.I. by my side,
it'll be like you never left.
[Iris West] Well, okay.
I guess we should, uh, get going.
Yes, we should.
- Send me a postcard.
- Hey, look, remember.
I'm leaving you in charge.
I'll see you when you get back.
Bye.
[typing]
So, you got any marching orders,
boss?
[computer processing]
The B.A.R.I. wants me to stay here,
and you to go with Frost,
to stake out Ramsey's lab.
I love it when a plan comes together.
[Nash slurps]
[clicks tongue]
Just so you know...
I let you follow me here.
Ah. I'll let you think that.
Captain Joe West, C.C.P.D.
So, uh, what brings you down here?
People with your face
usually have something to hide,
so when my son Barry told me
that there was a new Wells,
I started keeping tabs on you.
I don't know how new a Wells I am,
and, second, "keeping tabs,"
if that's what you mean by spying on me
from that nondescript sedan
parked up on Lake Avenue?
Well observed. So, why are you...
digging holes in the city?
[sighs] Well, perfect stranger,
[clears throat]
the reason I'm digging holes
underneath the city is... Oh, wait.
- You couldn't possibly understand.
- Try me.
Nah.
- [power surging]
- [Joe] No, no, no!
[yells]
[Kamilla] You need some rest.
All those late nights
working on the B.A.R.I.,
- you've barely slept this week.
- Tonight, I'm gonna sleep like a child.
'Cause I got the B.A.R.I...
- [machine beeps]
- [Cisco] And I got my white noise,
and I got my boo.
[white noise humming]
[sighs] Good night.
[yells]
Babe, you okay?
No, not really.
I just almost went Sweeney Todd
on myself.
Why would I do that?
Maybe I was sleepwalking?
Yeah, that's, um...
That's kind of your new thing.
Huh?
Yeah, you woke me up last night, too.
I heard the front door shut,
and you were standing there
with your keys in your hand
and your shoes on.
I was half asleep,
so I just put you back to bed.
- Okay, why didn't you say anything?
- Well, I didn't think it was a big deal.
Just like a one-off,
'cause you're so exhausted.
Well, it is a big deal,
and it's not a one-off anymore, is it?
That's twice now that's happened.
Babe, relax. Okay, you just launched
the B.A.R.I. today.
You need time to rest
that sexy brain of yours.
My brain is the Ryan Gosling
of genius intellects.
Okay.
Will you please let me know
next time that happens?
- Yes.
- And hide those scissors from me.
- Okay.
- Good night, babe.
Good night.
I love... I look...
forward to spending time
with you tomorrow.
Uh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Yeah, okay. Good night.
[electricity crackling]
Oh, my God.
[Cisco] Uh.
It's okay. I know him.
He's my ex's dad.
Hey, Breacher,
long time no try to kill me.
What brings you to my bedroom... again?
Breacher?
Hey.
Josh.
It's Cynthia.
She's dead.
I can't believe she's gone.
And I never get to see her again.
Cynthia was tracking
a high-level hacker.
Goes by the name of, uh, Echo.
She mentioned him before.
Nobody's ever been able to figure out
who he really is, right?
We think Cynthia did.
How he got the jump on her,
we don't know.
I don't see her losing a fight
to anyone.
She won the fight.
Dying here just, uh...
triggered her Collector QT-net.
The quara-temporal containment barrier?
Gypsy once said these barriers
were like super-sized
vibe fields around a planet.
The collectors put them up
so a suspect can't breach away
to another world.
And only the Agency can lift it.
Meaning her killer is still here.
I'm going to avenge Cynthia's death.
And Vibe is gonna help me do it.
Cisco isn't Vibe anymore.
He decided to take the meta-human cure.
Weren't you worried
about breach psychosis?
It happens sometimes
when you suppress your powers.
It's really gnarly.
How gnarly?
Hallucinations, weird blackouts,
dry mouth.
My powers weren't suppressed.
They're gone.
Well, even without his meta-powers,
Cisco can still help you.
He's a genius.
[tablet processing]
What would Barry do?
[tablet chimes]
The B.A.R.I. wants us to go
to the crime scene.
Listen, you don't have to go back there.
I'll go.
I'll come with you.
Kamilla, this could be dangerous.
I mean, we're dealing
with a killer here.
I can't ask you to come with me.
You didn't. I volunteered.
I knew you wouldn't let me down.
[Nash and Joe coughing]
[Nash clears throat] Okay.
[both groan]
[cell phone beeps]
[Nash chuckles] You can dance around
with that thing all you want.
This place was a dead zone
long before that wall came down.
Well, it might eventually go through.
At least I'm trying to help.
What are you doing?
I'm getting us out of here,
that's what I'm doing. Stupid.
Well, I have a team
that could help us get out of here.
How? How are they gonna help us?
No one knows we're down here.
I am a precinct captain.
I have dozens of cops,
and a whole support staff
that depends on me 24/7.
If I don't show up for a couple
of hours, they're coming looking for me.
All right, somebody's overconfident.
You know what you don't have?
You don't have cell phone service.
You don't have Wi-Fi.
- You have no way of telling anyone...
- [weapon charging]
- What are you doing?
- That we're down here. Right?
- Put it away.
- This is our only option.
- I'm gonna get us out of here.
- What are you doing?
[both screaming]
[both] What is wrong with you?
Why did you not tell me
that this Earth's vibrational frequency
is calibrated at a molecular level?
- You're supposed to be the expert!
- Shush.
Shush me one more time,
we're gonna have a problem.
We already do.
It turns out that that fireball
sapped 80...
[device beeps]
87% of the oxygen in this chamber,
which means that you and I have
42 minutes left to breathe.
[sizzling]
You know, the idea was you'd call me
before he started killing people.
He showed up out of nowhere.
Rat and Pops tried to run for it.
They didn't get far.
Frost, that guy's next-level creepy.
I wouldn't go looking for him.
[door opens]
Smart move.
Especially without a partner.
[Killer Frost sighs]
How's business, Snake-shack?
Eh, had better days.
You mind giving us a minute?
Need to have a little chat with Frosty.
What are you doing here?
Looking for you. What happened
to staking out Ramsey's lab?
Norvok texted me.
He said he saw Ramsey here.
Frost, as your life coach,
going after Ramsey alone
is probably gonna put me out of a job.
This isn't a joke.
This is a fight, my fight,
so stay out of it.
We're a team. Your fights are my fights.
So, why don't you just take a breath
and try trusting a friend?
I knew from day one
not to trust this guy, but we did.
And now people are dead,
so I've gotta fix this.
Wasn't that long ago
that I felt the same.
Blamed myself.
Never asked anyone for help.
And you know where it got me?
Eyeball-deep in Gingold and self-pity.
So, believe me when I say
that life is better
if you have faith
in the people around you.
What?
I know who Ramsey has faith in.
I gotta go.
Did you hear anything I just said?
You can't go alone.
I know what I'm doing. And don't worry.
I won't be alone.
Listen, Kamilla,
there's something I've been wanting
to say to you.
I've been trying to figure out
how to say it,
but, I don't know, I think I should just
come right out and say it.
- Kamilla, I...
- Holy crap.
- [indistinct chattering]
- [computers processing]
I thought C.C.P.D.'s crime scenes
were serious.
Yeah.
Earth-19 Collector Agents take
investigations to a whole other level.
[Zak] Agent Zak Zeal.
Kamilla Hwang, Cisco Ramon.
Yeah, I heard you'd be coming.
I thought you'd be taller, you know,
from the way Gypsy talked about you.
Now that's funny.
She never mentioned you at all.
[Zak] Hmm.
Hey, make sure Walker's updating
the dimensional output report.
Thanks.
You gotta keep on them constantly
when you're in charge.
Breacher understands.
Where is he anyway?
He already saw everything
he needed to see.
We're here in his place.
Well, the Agency authorized you
to join this investigation,
so I guess I'll just have to let you.
Is there a time of death?
Due to multi-dimensional signal speed,
our best guess is that it happened
sometime between 2:30 and 4:30 a.m.
That's a pretty good guess.
Yeah, I know.
And we found this.
301-H energy cartridge.
Standard issue. No prints.
Combine it with the Sigma baryon residue
we also found, and it looks like...
Echo killed Gypsy
with a transonic-demolecularizer?
Show us.
Now.
Her body, clothes,
even her communicator,
were all vaporized.
[breath trembling]
Me being like this...
I don't want you to think I'm still
hung up over Cynthia or something.
Cisco, someone you cared about died.
I'd be worried if you weren't sad.
So, earlier, when we first got here,
you were gonna say something.
Kamilla...
- [Zak] We're locking down the area.
- For the love of God.
You two need to leave.
Ramon.
I just wanted to say again
how much I truly admired Gypsy.
I've got some big shoes to fill.
We're not seriously just gonna give up,
are we?
No, we're not.
Have you noticed he's the only one
who benefits from Cynthia's death?
So, what's the plan?
[tablet processing]
The B.A.R.I. suggests
a dual course of action.
First, we use the satellites to track
the weapon's unique signature.
- Can you...
- On it.
I've been paying attention. And second?
We're gonna have to do the impossible.
[rock clatters]
[breathing heavily]
Man, sit down, relax.
We may live longer.
What evidence do you have
that anyone, literally anyone,
is coming down here to rescue us?
- I don't have any.
- No?
- But I do have faith.
- Ha!
Well done, Captain.
At least you haven't lost
your sense of humor.
Whoa.
[grunts]
- Ouch.
- Uh-huh.
Got light-headed, didn't you?
No.
You selfishly don't believe in anything
or anybody.
I used to be like that.
When my ex-wife left me
and my daughter...
I was broken.
So much so that I went somewhere
where I almost never go.
Church.
I didn't go there to pray or anything.
I went there to yell at the universe
for destroying my life.
Next day, I'm at home,
I'm so hurt that I can't even
cook dinner for my...
For my daughter.
Doorbell rings, I open the door...
to what looked like my whole
neighborhood standing on my lawn,
with cooked food for us.
You can have faith in anything,
but it was then I realized that...
I have faith in people.
[Cisco] According to B.A.R.I.,
we can use low-level
delta-wave vibrations
to stimulate harmonic resonance
in my prefrontal cortex.
If I think of memories with Cynthia,
we'll be able to absorb
the residual vibe energy
from the object that killed her.
Can this machine restore my vibe powers?
No. We're not the generators
of the vibe,
but we will be the receptors of it.
But I'm gonna have to see Cynthia die,
won't I?
It's the only way we have
of finding out who killed her.
[sighs] My white noise machine
will stimulate our delta-wave patterns.
- [machine beeps]
- [white noise humming]
Add the shell casing as a trigger
and that'll do it.
B.A.R.I., initiate
artificial vibrational sequence.
[computer processing]
If we want this to work,
we have to make physical contact.
[weapon charging]
- You murdered my daughter!
- No.
- No, I didn't do it. I swear!
- [yells]
- Liar!
- You have to believe me!
[Kamilla] Leave him alone!
Where did you get that?
In Cisco's workshop.
I don't know how it got there.
I do. He just murdered
my daughter with it.
No, Breacher, I don't care
what you think you saw, okay?
You know Cisco.
You know how much he cared about Gypsy.
There's gotta be another explanation.
- Babe, please...
- [sputters] What about doppelgängers?
She's right. There's thousands
of other versions of me out there.
Yeah, and they're all pencil pushers.
None of them are scientists! Like you!
You had motive
and just enough guts to do this.
Breacher, I swear.
I don't know how this is possible.
Unless...
Unless breach psychosis.
Kamilla, what time did you find me
sleepwalking the other night?
I don't know. Maybe 4:00 a.m.
[grunts]
You're guilty!
[Cisco breathing heavily]
But you're not in your right mind.
I didn't just lose a daughter today,
I lost a son, because...
I still respect the man you were.
Now, I'm gonna give you an hour
to get all your affairs in order
and then turn yourself in,
or I will end you.
[Nash breathing heavily]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna blow this blockade sky-high.
You do that, this whole thing collapses,
we're dead.
I do nothing and we're dead anyway.
Uh, we still have time
for my team to show up.
Enough! Enough about your team and you!
You know where I stand.
How can you have such faith?
Because someone or something
called the Monitor
says my son is destined
to die in some kind of Crisis
and the only way
I can stomach any of that
is have faith that his continuing life
or his death is for the greater...
The greater... The greater good.
You've seen Mar Novu?
Captain.
[air hissing]
Hey. Hey, I got you, big guy.
You're all right.
Oh, you got my text.
No. I called C.C.P.D. with a Ramsey
update and nobody had seen you.
Ran your plates,
tracked your car to a block from here.
Your notes had this tunnel marked.
I'm guessing...
because of him.
[machine powering down]
Lone Ranger.
Hi.
[squelching]
I see you got my message.
Cait...
You know, it's a bit weird
seeing you like this.
- I guess both our looks are evolving.
- [Ramsey chuckles]
Yes, I did get your message.
It reminded me of when we both
used to work for your mom.
Way back when I was a resident.
You were like
the daughter Mum never had.
Do you know, at first, I was jealous?
Over time,
I came to see you less as a rival,
and more like a sister.
And that's why I'm offering you a chance
- to join me.
- You wanna kill me, too?
I'm offering you life, Cait.
I've learned to control it,
discovered its secret beauty.
This is my final masterpiece, Cait.
Life eternal.
Immortality?
You see? I'm no monster.
I'm a miracle.
You're talking about reversing nature.
Nature never meant for us to fly,
and yet we've touched the stars.
And not by being slaves
to the shackles of the natural order,
but by transcending them.
Take a look at your own life, Cait.
How many times have you had to say
goodbye to people?
How many more have you not even
had the chance to do so?
My mum should be here.
Your father should be here.
Your husband should be here.
Join me and this is the end of goodbyes.
No one you love will ever die again.
I've seen your version of life.
It's a nightmare.
But you can still be your mother's son.
She had so much faith in you,
and so do I.
You just need to have faith in yourself.
[gasps]
[choking]
Your words are madness.
[Killer Frost breathing heavily]
Next time won't be a choice.
Look, we have to face the facts.
And I have to own up
to whatever it is that I did.
You're gonna turn yourself in?
I have to. I can't trust myself anymore.
[Kamilla] Anymore?
You stopped trusting yourself
the moment Barry asked you
to take over as team leader.
I mean,
you've built this elaborate device
just so you wouldn't have to make
any decisions for yourself.
- That's...
- Let me make this decision for you.
You are innocent.
How can you be so sure?
Because I have faith in you.
The real question is, why don't
you have any faith in yourself?
Because Barry's gonna die!
What if I can't keep people safe
the way he does?
I'm not the Flash.
Babe...
Barry didn't choose you to be the Flash.
He chose you to be you.
All these doubts, they aren't you.
They're just noise in your head.
[machine beeps]
It's been in Wi-Fi mode this whole time.
[Kamilla] What is it?
[Cisco] This code,
it's turned my white noise machine
into a micro neural impulse disrupter.
It could go all Wreck-it Ralph
on my brainwaves.
Might even look like breach psychosis.
Who'd be smart enough to code like that?
Me.
Sometimes the truth is
the hardest lie to see through.
And when you can't put your faith
in the truth,
all you have left... is yourself.
- [guns cocking]
- [weapons charging]
You're under arrest, Ramon.
I surrender.
I'm guilty.
Suspect is in custody.
Initiate QT-net removal, so the prisoner
can be transferred to Earth-19.
- [man over earpiece] Copy that.
- [Cisco] Breacher,
that holo-cube will tell you
everything you need
to know about what happened to Cynthia.
- [man] QT-net is off.
- [device beeps]
QT-net's down, sir.
I'll cuff him.
I'm sorry it had to go down this way,
but I needed you to lift the net.
Re-engage the QT-net.
[man]
That'll take four minutes.
I don't care if it'll take four minutes.
Just get on with it!
[yells]
[force field crackling]
I hate force fields.
- I know.
- Cisco, you think I'm gonna let the man
that murdered my daughter escape?
No, sir. And neither am I.
[sighs]
I'm here.
There's no sign of him.
His breach portal energy puts him
at the east end of the warehouse.
[typing]
Game over, Echo.
[sarcastically] Oh, no, you found me.
How did you find me?
I tricked the collectors
into lifting the QT-net.
When they did, I knew you'd jump
at the chance to get out of here,
and try to open a breach.
I just had to track the portal energy.
Babe, just get him back here
so the agents can take him down.
You have approximately two minutes
before my ride out of here boots up.
I go bye-bye, and you take my place
in an Earth-19 collector jail.
But you're the one with the gun.
So...
do you have it in you to stop me?
[weapon charging]
I guess we'll find out, won't we?
You are an anomaly.
Makes me wonder
why it was so easy to frame you.
Don't you wanna know how I did it?
You might learn something.
No, I pretty much figured it all out.
After you got here, you killed
the top agent in the Collective,
but you still needed a way out.
So, you used your face to get
into S.T.A.R. Labs,
and plant this gun in my workshop.
- Is that right?
- So far so good.
But hacking my white noise machine
to make me sleepwalk...
[yells]
That's when you tipped your hand.
I'd recognize that coding anywhere.
And since I didn't hack it,
I knew it had to be
some other version of me.
I'm not just some other version of you.
I specialize in hacking
multi-versal databases
to create new identities.
I could change your world...
[snaps fingers]
in an instant.
You see, somewhere out there
is a Cisco Ramon
who isn't as lucky as you are.
Who doesn't have the job,
the mind, the life you have.
But if the price is right,
Echo can reverse those fortunes.
And you might just wake up tomorrow
living someone else's life.
[Cisco] Is that why you killed her?
So you could keep peddling
these fake identities to people?
I didn't kill Gypsy.
You did.
[laughing slyly]
I'll give her this.
She was a formidable fighter,
but not even the smartest
guy in the room
could beat her in hand-to-hand combat.
But it didn't matter. Even though
she'd been chasing me for years,
she never even knew what I looked like.
So, when she caught me
and she saw my face,
all it took was
one moment of her flinching,
and that gave me the second I needed
to use that gun, the same gun
that's in your hands right now.
Do you need me
to spell it out for you, genius?
Gypsy is dead because when she saw me,
- she saw you.
- Stop talking.
She didn't have to die,
but she couldn't let me go.
She breached me to this Earth,
and I vaporized her!
- No.
- [Echo] Yes.
[both grunt]
[weapon charging]
[Echo] Don't feel bad, Cisco.
You're just not wired like me.
[Cisco] You're right.
I'm a hell of a lot smarter.
I programmed that weapon to trigger
an anti-vibrational force field
around whoever fires it.
In this case...
that's you, genius.
Did you get my holo-cube message?
It took you long enough.
Echo is in an Earth-19 cell,
where he belongs.
I'm sorry I lost faith in you, Cisky.
You know what? It's okay.
Things were looking pretty bad there
for a second.
Yeah.
But what I don't get...
If she was dying, why come here?
Because she knew
you would bring Echo to justice.
She had to lure him here, to this Earth.
She never lost faith in you, Cisco.
Now that this is over with,
what am I gonna do?
[sighs] Same thing I have to do.
We start healing.
I wanna invite you
to Cynthia's remembrance ceremony
on Earth-19.
You, too.
I'd be honored.
Cynthia would have liked you.
I do, too.
What's not to love?
Awkward.
I have to go now.
[portal opens]
[portal closes]
Well, I... Yeah, I, um...
Well, we haven't said it.
Yeah, I know.
So... Yeah. I, um...
Me, too. Big time.
Oh, thank God.
[Kamilla chuckles]
Please tell me you went home
at some point.
I knew I smelled SPF 90.
- How was it?
- [Iris West] Amazing.
Fifteen beaches in 24 hours.
One of the many perks
of marrying a speedster.
- [chuckles]
- [computer beeps]
[Barry] Yo.
Chester's energy level's
already up to 87%?
Yeah. Yeah. The, uh, M.A.C.'s gonna
be done cooking them up any day now.
So, the B.A.R.I. was a success?
Actually, I had to get rid of it.
I did use it.
I tried to use it at first,
but over time, I finally realized...
And you already knew
that was gonna happen.
It's just more proof that you're
the right person to lead the team.
[Cisco] Mmm.
Cisco, we got your message.
I'm really sorry to hear about Gypsy.
Some things you never get over.
Well, her service is next week.
You want us to come with you?
- Yeah, I mean, we loved her, too.
- [Cisco] Thank you.
Uh, Kamilla's coming with me, so...
I'm very lucky to have her.
Is it wrong to feel that way?
I mean, with everything
that just happened.
It's like I'm moving on.
What kind of person does that?
Someone who is very much in love.
It's funny.
Cynthia wasn't the person
I ended up with.
But, um...
I think she taught me
how to be the person I needed to be...
for when the right person came along.
And for that, I will never forget her.
Your vitals are good, Joe.
[Dibny] You know, with all the hubbub
of saving your keisters,
I never got to ask
what the hell you were doing down there.
Hey, 1940s, no one says keisters.
Nash, if you would just tell us
what you're looking for down there,
we might be able to help you.
All right, tomorrow morning,
nine o'clock, tunnels.
Bring your whole fancy team.
- Why should we do that?
- [Nash] Because...
I know how to save Barry Allen.