Cleaned, corrected, dashes removed
and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
- by something impossible.
- Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed
to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
- Mom!
- And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
You opened your lab after
Nora Allen's murder.
Do you mind telling me what
you were doing
in Central City before that?
Here I thought we were
just two guys
having a friendly drink.
What?
I just noticed you don't
smile too much.
The explosion that put you
in a coma
also killed my fiancée.
Ronnie!
He was a hero.
I didn't want him to be
a hero.
I wanted him to be my husband.
Don't look for me again.
Everyone has a hero,
someone they look up to
or admire,
someone they just wish
they could be.
It's easy to believe in heroes.
What's hard is when our heroes
stop believing in us.
Oh, Barry, there's an
intersection coming up. Hurry!
This should slow 'em down.
Guys, which way?
- Left.
- Right.
Stop! You both hear you're
telling me two different things,
right?
Barry, listen up.
Listen carefully.
Here is what you're going to do.
Now, the Queen is trying to make
it to the bridge,
but I have a shortcut...
wait for it...
And left... left...
right...
I see her!
Make her go west
before Fremont.
- Okay, how?
- I'd recommend a detour.
Now, the King is headed for
the entrance to the interstate.
What entrance?
Atta boy.
Check...
Got the keys.
Mate.
Give me some!
Yeah!
Efficiently done, Mr. Allen.
- We need a picture.
- Pretty sure rule number one
of having a secret identity is
not taking pictures of yourself
in your super suit
without a mask on.
Oh, come on, please!
This is just for us.
This is to document all this.
Who knows? Maybe people
in the future
will want to know how
all this happened.
All right, well, if you want
the future to have
the whole story, then,
we all need to be in it.
First, let me put on
some makeup?
The future does not care
about your makeup.
Mm-mmm.
Okay.
Big smiles.
Three... two... one.
Ha!
Does that count as a selfie?
Absolutely.
Sick.
Came out good.
Thanks for talking me through
things out there.
My pleasure.
Well done.
I have to say it was a bit
of a rush feeling like a...
- A hero.
- Yeah.
You're pretty good at it.
- Hey.
You do realize the whole point
of moving out is
not being at home anymore,
right?
Ha-ha-ha.
I forgot a few things.
So... how is it living back
at the house?
- Hey, Bar?
- Yo.
Babe...
spaghetti a la me.
You sure you don't want
to stay for dinner?
Thanks, but Eddie is painting
all day
and I swore that I would help.
Although, I'm really just going
to do that thing
where I get a little paint
on my hair and on my nose.
Oh, hey,
someone from Central City
Picture News called you
the other day... I left the number
on the fridge.
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
Chill! Just did.
Hey, I heard that some members
of the Royal Flush Gang
are headed to prison.
Is that a good scream or
a bad scream?
Good! So good!
I just got offered a job
as a reporter
at Central City Picture News.
- That's awesome!
- The editor's a fan of my blog!
- That is amazing.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, God.
♪ ♪
Harrison Wells.
Hello?
We both know what you did.
It's time to pay the piper!
Come in.
Look, Joe, I apologize
for all of this.
It just... it really feels like a
case of so much for so little.
The police should not have
been called.
I got a prank call before
all this happened.
This feels like more than just
a prank, Doctor.
Well, there are those who feel
I did not suffer enough
for the particle accelerator
explosion of last year,
and some of them act on it.
Dr. Wells.
Dr. Wells, are you okay?
Dr. Snow, I'm... I'm fine.
A little chilly.
Otherwise, I'm fine.
Hello, Cisco.
Make yourselves at home
as best you can.
I'm gonna make
a hotel reservation.
Oh...
This place is so sick.
Yeah... hey, what took you guys
so long?
We got lost.
We've never been here before.
Really? Never?
He tends to keep his
private life private.
A precipice in front,
and wolves behind.
In other words, you're between
a rock and a hard place.
Check.
The King is dead.
Checkmate.
Dr. Wells?
There he is.
Hartley, allow me to introduce
you to Cisco Ramon.
Mr. Ramon here is one of the
finest mechanical engineers
I have ever seen.
Wow.
I can't believe Harrison Wells
said that about me.
I'm sure he'll prove to be an
invaluable member of your team.
- Trust me.
- You I trust.
I don't foresee myself
trusting someone
who showed up to his first day
of work
at a billion dollar
research facility
wearing a T-shirt that says
"Keep Calm and Han Shot First."
Huh... would you give us
a minute please, Cisco?
Yes, sir.
I realize you don't have to
explain your hiring decisions
to me, but maybe for the sake
of a fun exercise,
we could pretend you did.
I have a good feeling
about him.
Just as I did about you.
Oh...
Hartley...
You're still my guy.
And nothing and no one is ever
going to change that.
I canvassed the street.
No other reports of vandalism.
No strange cars.
Get this... Wells says he's right
there when it happened.
All that glass shattering down
around him and he can't walk?
And he didn't have a scratch
on him.
There's no point of impact.
No rock or bat or...
any solid object
went through these windows.
It's as if they just
shattered themselves.
This wasn't some teenage prank?
No, it wasn't.
But you don't want our help.
Why?
Because I already know
who did this.
Hartley Rathaway.
Who is Hartley Rathaway?
Hartley Rathaway is
the prodigal son.
And he has returned.
Hartley Rathaway possesses one
of the finest scientific minds
I've ever encountered.
Any ties to
Rathaway Industries?
His grandfather founded the
company, his father expanded it,
and Hartley here was set
to inherit the throne.
- What happened?
- He came out to his parents.
Old money, old values.
They were estranged
when we met,
but, brilliant.
I couldn't have built
the particle accelerator
without him.
You guys have never even
mentioned his name.
That's because Hartley had
a challenging personality.
What she means is he was
mostly a jerk.
But, every once in a while,
he could be a dick.
Let's just say that Hartley,
like many outliers,
had trouble relating to
his peers.
Yes, but he was always
your favorite.
The chosen one.
He referred to himself
like that.
So if you two were so close,
why would he target you?
Hartley left S.T.A.R. Labs
about a year ago
after we had a...
a disagreement.
About what?
Look, don't worry.
We'll stop him.
I won't let him hurt you...
any of you.
Let's get back to my lab,
all right?
I could've gone my whole life
without seeing that jerk again.
Yo. This place is so dope.
What a coincidence.
We were thinking of making
"Yo. This place is so dope"
our new slogan.
If you're so convinced
Dr. Wells made a mistake
in hiring me, why don't you try
proving it to him?
Magnetic flux is measured
by what?
Hall effect pick up.
The dual of a parallel
R-C circuit?
Series R-L circuit.
I can go all day, pal.
Hartley, it looks like you
have met your match.
I am Dr. Caitlin Snow.
It's very nice to meet you.
Cisco Ramon.
Nice to meet you.
And just ignore Hartley.
We all do.
Tell your boyfriend I need his
specs on the synchrotron
by end of day.
Actually, it is the end of
Ronnie's day.
We are leaving early.
My boyfriend is taking me
out of town
for our one-year anniversary.
- Aw. That's sweet.
- Thanks.
I'll see you guys on Monday.
See ya.
She seems nice.
You don't.
I give you a week.
Max.
Hi. I'm Iris West.
It's my first day.
I can see that.
Really? Does it show?
Uh, the fact that I've never
seen you before shows.
Mr. Bridge! Nice of you to
make an appearance
at a staff meeting.
I do love a good shmear.
Everyone, welcome Iris West,
our new cub.
Anyone want to volunteer to be
her mama bear?
Mason, you picked a bad day
to actually show up.
- I don't nanny.
- I lost the ability
to make a joke back in '05.
Today, you do.
Deadlines. All new stories
are due on my desk
at the end of the day.
Oh, actually, I had an idea
for a piece.
There's this program in Keystone
that helps battered women get
back on their feet.
Ah, that sounds really great,
West.
Actually, any thoughts on
a piece about The Flash,
something you haven't written
about yet, something new?
Um, no.
Not currently.
All right.
Sally forth, everyone.
Sally forth.
Everything has
a natural frequency.
And since sound is expressed
as a vibration, if the pitch
of the sound
matches the natural vibration
frequency of an object, then...
So, you're saying that can
happen to anything,
- not just glass?
- Oh, yeah.
I think that's absolutely what
happened to the windows
at Wells' house.
He's using some kind of
sonic technology.
I'm getting this feeling that
Wells is hiding something...
about what's going on with
this Rathaway character...
Don't touch that!
I mean, it sounds like this
Hartley guy was a pill
before he went all
super villain, so I...
I get why he never
mentioned him.
Like he never mentions his
girlfriend that got killed.
No.
How do you know about her?
He's taking up a big part
of our lives.
I wanted to know more about him.
I mean, if you want to know
more about him,
you could just ask me.
Sounds like you don't know him
as well as you think.
Joe. Multiple 911 calls.
Rathaway Industries
is under attack.
Sector cars are en route.
- Hey.
- Barry, it's Caitlin.
I think I know why
you're calling.
Get down on the ground!
It's over, Rathaway.
You know my name.
I know some names too.
Caitlin Snow.
Cisco Ramon.
Harrison Wells.
I can hear the radio waves
emanating from your suit.
About 1900 megahertz.
Is that them on the other end,
listening?
Are they gonna hear you die?
No. They're going to hear you
get your ass kicked.
Okay.
Looks like you're not as smart
as everyone says.
Smart enough to have
figured out
who Harrison Wells really is.
You see, I know his secret.
Being scooped up by a guy clad
in head-to-toe leather
is a long-time fantasy of mine,
so thanks.
Well, well, well,
the gang's all here.
You've lasted a lot longer than
I would've thought, Cisco.
And you didn't last
ten seconds against The Flash.
I was thinking of calling
myself Pied Piper.
Hey! I assign the nicknames
around here.
Although that one's not bad.
Caitlin...
Never did get
that wedding invite.
Shut the hell up!
Stay in front of me.
The scanner is detecting foreign
metallic objects in your ears.
- Take 'em out.
- I can't.
I suffered head trauma when
S.T.A.R. Labs exploded.
My hearing was severely damaged.
Without these, I'm in pain
you can't imagine.
We all lost something
that night.
Ha. Very clever re-purposing
the anti-proton cavities
into confinement cells.
Wells' idea, I'm sure.
It was mine, actually.
Hartley, don't make this more
difficult than it has to be.
Enough, Hartley.
Give us a minute.
See you soon, Cisco.
Doubt it!
God, I wish I'd taken
a language in high school.
How did you know we were
working with The Flash?
I wrote a hexagonal algorithm
tracking all of his sightings,
extrapolating a theoretical
exit trajectory.
In other words, every time he
ran from the scene of a crime,
he ran in this general
direction.
You are brilliant.
And... any anguish you have been
through because of me
was never my intent.
Not bad...
as far as
heartfelt apologies go.
Except that wasn't for
my benefit.
That was for you, Flash.
Feels good to have the great
Harrison Wells behind you,
doesn't it?
But one day,
this man will turn on you...
in a flash...
and even you won't
see it coming.
I only hope that he leaves you
in better shape than he left me.
If you're lucky,
you'll only be dead.
Because every day I have to live
with the agonizing,
piercing screaming in my ears.
I almost forgot...
I told your pet
I know your deep, dark secret,
Harrison.
Have fun letting him in
on that one.
I assume you were all
listening.
Well, Hartley was telling
the truth.
I have not been honest with you.
With any of you.
The accelerator...
Hartley warned me that there was
indeed a chance
that the accelerator
could explode.
His data did not show
100% certainty,
just that there was a risk,
but it was a real risk.
And yet I made the decision
that the reward... that...
everything we could learn and
everything we could achieve,
that all of that...
simply outweighed that risk.
I'm sorry.
Then the next time you choose
to put our lives,
and the lives of the people
that we love,
at risk,
I'll expect a heads up.
After the explosion,
when everyone else left you...
Caitlin and Cisco stood by you.
You owe them more than
an apology.
They might soon get more
than that what with Hartley
so intent on sending me
to the next world.
What are...
that wouldn't make it right
with them.
You broke their trust.
Our trust.
Oh! Hi, chief.
- Is that what people call you?
- Uh, no. Not really.
Listen, eyewitnesses say that
The Flash thwarted an attack
downtown today.
Look into it.
- Uh, yeah, sure.
- Great.
Mason, you're looking
particularly rumpled today.
Mm-hmm.
So, what are we working on?
I am following up on a lead
on corruption at the DWP.
You... well, I think you just got
your assignment from Larkin,
didn't you?
Look, I'm not stupid, okay?
I know that Larkin hired me
because he thinks
that I have some sort of in
with The Flash.
But I am serious about
being a journalist.
Why? Because you write a blog?
My mother writes a blog.
I may not have a lot of
experience, but I do have...
Spunk? Grit?
Gumption?
What is this,
a Chick-Lit novel?
No, no, no, I am having
the worst day ever.
We both can't be having
the worst day ever. Okay?
And I was really looking forward
to getting
some good complaining in.
Well, fire away.
Okay, well, turns out that
the real reason they hired me
is because they think I have
some sort of connection
to The Flash, which I don't.
Not anymore.
And I've been teamed up with
Mason Bridge,
who is a legend, who I admired,
before he told me
I was a worthless,
talentless millennial.
Well, the people we admire
aren't always
who we'd like them to be.
Well said.
So, I'm screwed.
No, look...
if this Mason guy doesn't see
what a talented journalist
you are, then he's probably
a lousy writer.
He won the Pulitzer.
Twice, I think.
Oh. Good for him.
Thanks, Barry.
Having someone believe in me,
it's, um...
a small... really,
really big thing.
- Yeah.
Where's Dr. Wells?
I'm not sure.
Barry was right.
Hartley was using sonic
resonance.
The intensity regulator's
measuring decibels.
But you know what's weird?
He had it set to
the lowest setting.
- What do you mean?
- Well...
He could've completely destroyed
his father's building
if he wanted to in one blast.
So, why not just do it
and leave?
I mean, why stick around and run
the risk of getting caught?
Unless he wanted to be caught.
Dr. Wells!
There's been a pipeline breach.
Hartley.
Stay here.
Ah! Not now.
Aah!
Cisco, can you hear me?
Ugh!
- Hey, what's up?
- Listen to me... Hartley escaped.
- He's loose in the facility.
- Okay.
Okay, your turn... why are you
having the worst day...
Tell me, Harrison.
Am I still your guy?
Hey! Are you okay?
Yeah, uh, Cisco and Dr. Wells.
He's gone.
Hey.
Welcome back, Mr. Ramon.
Ooh.
Oh, man.
- Caitlin?
- Hey.
She's fine.
You need to rest.
You have a concussion.
You're lucky.
Please tell me you got him.
I guess the attack on his
family's company was a fake out
- so we'd catch him.
- And give him...
- direct access to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Why?
I should've known he was
up to something.
This is my fault.
Hey, man.
This is on me, too.
I shouldn't have left before...
This is no one's fault
but mine.
I earned the blame... I'm not
interested in sharing it.
Hartley doesn't think I've paid
for my crimes.
And he's right.
He won't stop until I do.
Where are you going?
To earn back your trust.
Hmm... now what were you doing
in my accelerator?
Thought it was
our accelerator.
Because it will be our fault
if we turn this thing on
and blow a hole in Central City.
You are wagering the lives
of everyone in this building.
Everyone in this city.
If you don't have the courage
to admit you could be wrong,
I will do it for you.
Hartley Rathaway...
your position at S.T.A.R. Labs
is terminated.
If you think you can
shut me up...
Oh, I know I can, Hartley.
Because if you breathe one word
of any kind of
unsubstantiated accusation,
I will make sure the only job
you ever get in physics
is teaching it to
high school juniors.
What is going on here?
Press conference.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
And for those of you that read
the ten-volume report
issued by the Norris Commission,
well, I commend you on
your tenacity.
You already know, then,
the circumstances that led to
the explosion of the S.T.A.R.
Labs particle accelerator.
Or rather, you think you do.
Now, the Commission's finding
was that the catastrophe was
caused by a chain of events that
nobody could have predicted,
including myself.
The truth is...
I was warned there was a chance
the particle accelerator
might fail.
I was warned by
a former colleague...
a friend.
I chose to ignore the warning
and in so doing,
I let down all of you.
As a new friend pointed out...
I failed this city.
I failed this city and I failed
those who trusted me the most.
By coming forward today...
it's my hope I'm taking
the first step toward
regaining that trust.
And your trust as well.
Are there any questions?
Do you have any intention
of rebuilding
the particle accelerator?
Miss West, do you have
a question for me?
I don't believe you answered
my colleague's question,
Dr. Wells,
so I'll ask it again.
Do you have any intention
of rebuilding
the particle accelerator,
either now or in the future?
Of course not.
Thank you for your answer,
Doctor.
It's my pleasure.
No further questions.
Hey.
What was that?
Gumption.
Has Hartley made contact yet?
What makes you so sure
he will?
Because he's Hartley,
and he'll want to have
the last word.
Cisco, you should be resting.
The answer to why Hartley
fooled us into catching him
is in here,
and I'm gonna find it.
- You have nothing to prove.
- Not true.
Do you know why I hired you,
Cisco?
You said you saw something
in me... I know.
What I saw was humanity.
You and Hartley, Cisco,
you're both brilliant.
You both have mental...
sparks.
But his brilliance
subtracted from the experience
of working here,
whereas your brilliance,
your heart,
your warmth, your humor,
it just adds to it.
There is no chosen one,
Cisco.
No second or third favorite.
Never was.
It's just us.
What's that?
Nice gambit, Harrison.
But this isn't over.
Hartley, what do you want?
What do you want, Hartley?
I already gave my mea culpa
today.
The city already hated you.
You don't think I noticed
that press conference
was a pathetic bishop sacrifice?
No, no, no. I've played with you
too many times
to let you get away with that.
This is between you, me,
and The Flash.
You don't want to play
for those kind
of stakes with me, Hartley.
Actually, I really do.
What do you say?
One last game of chess?
You and I both know that
the winner of the game
is the one who makes
the next-to-last mistake,
and you clearly have
a move in mind.
You're right.
And I'm already at the board.
So why don't you move your
precious scarlet knight...
While I take out a few pawns.
All right. All right, Cisco,
where do I go?
I can't trace the signal. He could be
sending his messages from anywhere.
Cisco,
scan for seismic activity.
If Hartley's using sonic blast,
the vibrations could cause
tremors.
Look. Over here. Quake
activity but no fault line.
The Keystone Cleveland Dam.
Barry! Don't underestimate
him. He's brilliant.
Well, good thing I'll have you
in here.
Rook to knight four.
Aah!
Barry, you need to disarm
Hartley immediately.
Immediately! Do you hear me?
He is a master of distraction.
He is a master of hiding his
true endgame.
A-ha!
Uh-oh.
Aha what?
I figured out what Hartley
stole from S.T.A.R. Labs,
why he let himself get caught.
Which brings us to
the "uh-oh."
He has all the data on
Barry's molecular scans.
Why would he want that?
He can get Barry's frequency.
Barry, you need to get out of
there!
You need to get out of there
immediately!
It's over! You lose!
Amazing.
He replaced me with you?
Total moron.
I got you with
the same trick twice.
Ah!
Uhh!
I got the idea watching you
and Harrison chit-chat...
to use your suit's own speakers
to kill you.
Gah!
That feeling? That's your
organs shearing apart.
And you activated the frequency
when you disarmed me.
In chess, we call that
a discovered attack.
You don't see it
until it's too late.
Right, Harrison?
Aah!
Barry's vitals are
bottoming out.
We need to do something.
What are you doing?
Barry's on the travel road
of the dam, at rush hour,
surrounded by cars.
Many of those cars are going to
have satellite radio.
Satellite sends a signal to
the car,
song comes out the speaker...
Yes! I know
how satellite radio works!
How does that help?
Well, I'm gonna have the
satellite send something
other than a song.
Hartley is about to hear
something
he was not expecting...
a sound wave that will meet
the frequency of
and destroy his weapons.
You don't seem so special
anymore.
Given how easy it was to bring
you down,
I wonder if Harrison will
even miss you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no!
No!
Aah!
Checkmate.
Barry, can you hear me?
Sort of!
- Okay!
- How do you feel?
Fine! I mean there is
a little ringing in my ears,
but other than that I'm good,
so...
You're speaking very loudly.
- Sorry.
- It's okay, it'll pass.
- Nice moves.
- Thank you.
Anytime.
I think I'm gonna take my
doctor's advice
and go lie down.
What a great idea!
Man, I feel like I'm hung over
times ten.
I'm not surprised.
It's difficult for me...
to admit when I'm wrong.
Certainly, in front of
an entire city but also...
Also to my closest friends.
So I hope one day
to restore your trust
and faith in me.
That day was today.
Not every hero wears a mask.
Some heroes save the day in
the simplest of ways.
By just being there for us...
or letting us know
we're believed in.
If I'm any sort of hero today,
it's not because of my speed.
It's because I learned how from
the people in my life...
all of them.
Hey.
Man, that press conference today
was something else.
Dr. Wells...
took a lot of guts to do that.
I have to give him that.
He has his moments.
What's up?
Must have been hard for you.
What? To be this handsome?
Raising me.
Oh. No.
Well, a kid who loved
math and chemistry,
whose idea of
a fun afternoon was
doing experiments in the garage.
Couldn't have been easy.
As soon as I started AP classes,
you had
no clue how to help me
with my homework.
- No.
- You must have always felt like
you were competing with Richard
Dawkins and Neil Tyson and...
Henry Allen too.
But, look, none of them...
no one...
could ever replace you.
Not even Wells.
Aw.
All right,
I'll see you at home.
All right.
- Hey, Eddie.
- Hey, Barry.
Hey, what'd you find out?
I searched Wells' entire house
like you said.
There was nothing.
Are you sure you want to
do this...
Investigate Wells?
100%
Your evil hearing aids won't
help you escape this time.
So I'd get comfy.
You must be enjoying this,
Cisco.
- I am.
- Ah, well,
if that scares you,
I can't imagine
how you're gonna feel when you
open up these doors
and let me out of here.
Hmm...
maybe I'm going deaf,
'cause I could've sworn
you just said I'm gonna
let you out.
And very soon too.
Why would I ever do that?
Because I know where
Ronnie Raymond is.
I know what really happened
to him that night.
And I know how to save him.
Warning! Tachyon output
has passed acceptable
tolerance range.
Continued exposure is not
recommended.
Increase to maximum, Gideon.
Increasing to maximum,
Doctor.
Speed Force absorption
at 35% and rising.
I'm not stabilizing.
I can't hang on to my speed.
It comes and goes,
and I can not control it.
Gideon, for how much longer is
the Tachyonic device viable?
Calculations inconclusive.
- I'm sorry, Doctor.
- Oh, that's okay, Gideon.
This was only meant to be
a temporary fix.
The real endgame is almost here.
Greg, move your head!