Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created
the alternate timeline,
Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline
to how it was,
only to find
things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats
to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- I got hit
with the dark matter.
It must have affected me
somehow.
- We're going home.
- I went back in time
and created
an alternate timeline.
- Wally?
Aah.
Can you hear me?
- My name is Edward Clariss.
Rivals should know
each other's names.
- When I came back,
things weren't the same.
- I don't trust you,
and I don't like things
that I don't trust.
- You'll always be Barry,
and I'll always be Iris.
And we always find each other.
- [grunts]
Who are you?
- I am Alchemy.
- Alchemy!
- You failed, Clariss.
[clock ticking]
- Remember that feeling
you got as a kid
when you were so excited
about something
that you couldn't focus
on anything else?
That's me right now,
thinking about...
well, what I
always think about.
- Allen!
Enough with the knee.
[sprightly music]
Where are you going?
- I'm going on a date.
- Well, not yet, you're not.
- You know, you're not
actually my boss, Julian.
- But I am the senior lab tech,
and the last time I checked,
the hours were
10:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m.
Not 6:58.
Not 6:59.
[voice slowing down]
But se...
- Remember that other feeling
you got
when that thing
you were excited about
seemed to take forever
to arrive?
Imagine being a speedster.
Days seem like weeks.
Hours seem like days.
And seconds seem like...
you get the point.
- ...ven.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
[driving rock music]
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
- ♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
- It's too much?
Yeah, it's too much.
It's the heart, right?
It's too cheesy?
Hold on.
[whoosh]
Is that better?
That's...
That's worse?
We'll go back to the heart.
- No, Bare.
Wait, wait, wait.
It is so beautiful,
and you are so sweet,
but tonight,
I want to be with you.
Barry Allen.
Not the Flash.
- So...
- So no Flash talk.
No speed.
- No problem.
All right.
Starting now,
the Flash is officially
off-limits.
♪ ♪
- So, wow...
- Mm.
- Where are we going?
- It's a surprise.
- ♪ Electric love ♪
[Iris laughs]
♪ ♪
♪ Baby, you're electric ♪
- Are you planning
on donating a kidney
sometime in the near future
or...?
- A kidney?
- This place is...
- Oh, don't look at the prices.
Just get whatever you want.
So...
- Yeah, so...
- How was work?
- Yeah, super busy.
How about you?
- Well, Julian had me write up
a carbon dating report.
Then a DNA sequencing report.
A couple of chemical
compound reports.
So he pretty much just
gives me all the work
he doesn't want me to do, so...
- [yawns]
- Yeah, I know,
it's really boring.
- No, no.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Barry.
I'm just...
it's been a really long day.
- Yeah, I know.
Me too.
[siren wailing in distance]
What's going on?
- Apparently,
a robbery's in progress
across the street.
Excuse me.
- Go, go, go.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Yeah, use your speed.
Go.
- Okay.
[whooshes]
- [sighs]
- Uh, where were we?
- Um...
[phones ring and vibrate]
Cisco.
- We should go.
- Yeah.
[whoosh]
[tense music]
- What's going on?
- That.
- Yeah, why'd you open a breach?
- I didn't.
- What?
- That's why we called you.
- Well, can you close it?
- Once again,
wouldn't have called
if I could.
♪ ♪
- Somebody's coming through.
- Get back.
♪ ♪
- Allen.
- Wells.
- I need your help.
- With what?
♪ ♪
- With that.
- Hey, guys.
- Jesse.
You're a speedster?
- Yeah.
It's pretty cool, right?
[Caitlan:]  I mean
yeah, I would say so.
When did this happen?
- A few days ago.
- So, when I got
Allen his speed back,
Wally and Jesse were hit
with the dark matter.
Turns out she was affected.
She was totally affected.
- But I didn't get speed,
so could it have been
from something else?
- No...
I mean, I doubt it.
Dark matter affects
different people
in different ways
at different times...
sometimes not at all,
so be thankful,
but she was affected,
and I want to run some tests
and find out just how much.
- Well, then,
you've come to the right place.
Let's go to the Speed Lab.
both: Speed Lab?
[dramatic music]
- This is insane.
- Something tells me
you've never been
in this room before.
- Nope.
- Wait, you...
you nev...
Allen.
I suppose that means
you traveled back in time again.
- Yeah, but...
- How many times did I tell you
not to do that?
- You figured that out
pretty quickly, Harry.
- Yes, Ms. West,
it was easy
because we've never
been here either.
- Nope.
- Right.
Other Earths,
other timelines.
- Yes, exactly.
So when did you do it?
After we returned to Earth-2?
- Look, Harry,
only a couple things
are different.
- Oh, I'm sure.
Not.
- Really?
You guys are doing "not"
on Earth-2 now?
- Uh, no.
That's all him.
- Okay, let's just get Jesse
on the track
and see what she can do.
- Yeah, let's do it.
All right.
Check this out.
♪ ♪
- Damn.
She reallycan move.
- Yeah, she can.
Um...I got to go.
♪ ♪
- Wally.
Oh, man.
- I'll talk to him.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Joe.
Um...
Look, it's just...
itis better if he
doesn't have speed.
- Oh, you don't
have to convince me of that.
The last thing I want
is two of my kids
zipping around the city,
running into danger.
- 'Cause he looked
pretty disappointed.
- This is about
that other timeline, isn't it?
- No, I just...
I think you should
keep an eye out.
♪ ♪
[TV laughter]
- Where's dinner?
- It's almost ready, John.
- I work hard every day
to provide for this family,
and this is what greets me?
An empty table?
- Just five more minutes.
- I'm hungry now!
And you speak
when you're spoken to, girl.
You understand me?
I saved you
from the orphanage
and I provide for you
every day,
so keep your mouth shut,
Frankie, you got it?
- [whimpers]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Sorry, John.
Frankie's gone.
♪ ♪
- Hey!
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I was trying
to get some information
about the man who was attacked
by a lamppost last night.
- Hey...
Just come here for a second.
So, last night.
I know our first date
didn't shatter any records.
- I mean, it wasn't that bad.
- It was...
- Okay, yeah.
It wasn't that great,
either.
- It was just kind of...
- Boring?
- Boring, yeah.
Which feels like my fault.
Maybe I'm boring
without my powers.
- No, Barry, you are perfect
without your powers.
- That's nice, but I mean,
what do you think it is, then?
You don't think it's a sign
that we shouldn't...
- No!
[clears throat]
No.
- Good, I mean, 'cause I do...
I want to try this again,
as soon as possible,
but just with everything
that's going on...
this new case, and
Wells and Jesse showing up...
- Yeah.
No, Barry.
I totally get it.
I get it.
I should probably concentrate
on making my deadlines anyway,
so.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- All right.
All right, well, I'm gonna...
- Okay.
Yeah.
- Work.
- Yeah. Work.
Cool.
- Yeah. All right.
I'll see you later.
Oh.
- No, I was...
- Yeah, of course.
- Yeah.
All right.
- So this says you were
in the room when your father...
- Foster father.
John.
- Right.
Foster father.
You were in the room
when he was struck
by the street lamppost
that flew into the apartment?
- Yeah.
But I don't remember
any of that.
He came home
and yelled at Karen,
my foster mom,
to get him dinner.
- Mm.
Is that when you blacked out?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Has that happened before?
You blacking out?
[solemn music]
- Is John gonna be okay?
♪ ♪
- He's in Central City Hospital.
I...
He's pretty banged up.
♪ ♪
Frankie, can you excuse me
for a second?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thank you.
Bare.
- Yeah?
- What'd you find out?
- Okay, get this.
So, the outer layer
of the lamppost
is a half an inch thick,
but to bend
even a quarter-inch of steel
requires 177 tons
of tensile strength, so...
- So we're looking for
a meta with superstrength?
- Well, I'm not sure yet,
but that's as much
as I could find.
- What?
Why?
- Because I showed up.
- Yeah.
- Yes, the only problem
with Barry's little theory
is there were no fingerprints
found on the post.
- Again, Julian, not my theory,
and the meta
could've been wearing gloves.
- Yes, perhaps.
But the curvature on the post
suggests
that equal amounts
of pressure were applied
to the whole thing
at the same time.
So, unless our strong man has
a wingspan of over 20 feet...
- Something else caused it.
- Yes.
Who's that, sir?
- That's Frankie Kane,
the victim's foster kid.
That poor girl's been
in and out of homes for years.
Listen, she said
that she blacked out
during the incident.
- Blacked out?
- Yeah.
- Repressing memories
is a coping mechanism
for lots of foster kids.
- Hmm.
Is it?
- It is.
- It could be something else.
- What are you...
- What...
- Hello there.
- Hi.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Can I get you some more water?
- Yes, thank you.
- Sure.
- Gonna need another glass,
Detective.
- Follow him.
- Mm-hmm.
- See what you can get.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna finish this up
and convince my son
that he's not meant
to be a superhero.
- Good idea.
[whooshing]
- So, how'd I do?
- Blood pressure, heart rate,
metabolic rate all excellent.
And you've got
some serious speed, girl.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think you're good to go.
- Let's not
get ahead of ourselves.
I still want
to run a few more tests.
- Like what?
- Like more tests.
- Hey, so, is Wally here?
- No, not yet.
- Right.
Um...
Okay, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go grab some food.
I'm starving.
- Yeah, there's some PowerBars
in the workshop.
Help yourself.
- Cool.
- Harry?
- Mm-hmm?
- What're you doing?
- Being thorough.
- Yeah? 'Cause it seems
like you're stalling.
- Okay, fine.
I'm stalling.
So what?
- So what?
So why?
- So why?
Why?
Why? I got to explain myself
to you two?
Oh, I guess I do,
'cause you're not parents.
That's my daughter, okay?
And she spent months
on this very Earth
watching Barry Allen defeat
meta after meta after meta...
and Zoom...
and all of a sudden, bam!
She's got speed,
and now she wants
to be a hero
just like him.
And I think
that's a great idea.
Not!
- Harry, we can help her.
We can train her
just like we did with Barry.
- I don't want
you to train her.
I brought her here
for you to talk her out of it,
not talk her into it,
all right, Ramon?
You...you should talk to her.
You're a meta.
- Yeah, which makes me
the last person
she should talk to
about not using her powers.
- [stammering]
Okay, Snow...
Caitlin...
You and her,
you've always had
such a special relationship.
You talk to her.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah.
- And I don't know anything
about having powers,
so I'm the last person
you should talk to,
so don't ask me.
- Wait, I...
[sighs]
- Dad.
What's going on?
Why'd you want to see me?
- Oh, hey.
Uh...
Have a seat.
Look...
I know it's been
really hard for you,
seeing Jesse with speed.
- I just keep thinking of
what Harry said.
How sometimes it takes a while
for powers to manifest.
- Yeah, Harry also said
that they may never manifest.
- Yes, but I got hit
by that dark matter too,
just like Jesse.
Could still happen for me
somehow.
- Look, you weren't here
when the first particle
accelerator exploded.
That dark matter went
throughout the whole city.
Everybody got hit.
Me, your sister,
this whole precinct.
Do you know how many metas
there have been so far?
I know you want this
more than anything,
but you have to face the fact
that it might not happen.
- So you think,
just let it go?
Give up
on wanting to help people?
- You don't need powers
to do that.
Look, Barry was
coming to the rescue
as a CSI
long before he was the Flash.
He wanted to help people then
just like you want
to help people now.
So he studied.
He honed
that brilliant mind of his.
And you have
the same brilliant mind, Wall.
- Dad...
- No, I mean it, son.
Look,
a lot of people dream
about making the world
a better place.
With that mind of yours
and that engineering talent,
you literally could build
a better world.
[poignant music]
- So what?
I got to stay in school?
- Yeah, you got
to stay in school.
Just a couple more years.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
- I assumed you'd taken
a DNA sample before.
- Okay, yes.
I know what you're doing.
I mean,
why are you doing it?
- Are you looking
to steal another sample?
I've isolated an element
consistent in all five
of the husks that we've found,
including Edward Clariss's.
- You mean the Rival?
- Mm.
That's what
the papers are calling him, yes.
- What's the element?
- I don't know.
But it's not one that I've found
in any other meta-human samples
that I've studied.
- So you think that Frankie,
the girl downstairs,
has the same element in her DNA?
- Well,
I wouldn't be comparing samples
if it wasn't a possibility,
would I, Allen?
[tense music]
It's a good thing for both of us
I did.
Come on.
- What?
♪ ♪
- Where is she?
- Calm down, okay? Julian?
- You! You, girl!
Stop!
- Hey, ease up, Julian.
- Stop!
- Me?
- You did it, didn't you?
- What?
- The lamppost.
You did it, didn't you?
- What?
No, no, no, stop.
- You're a liar!
- Julian!
- You're a meta-human.
- Stop, no, stop!
- You put your foster father
in the hospital, didn't you?
- No, no!
- Didn't you?
Didn't you?
[dramatic music]
- Oh, I wanted to do
more than hurt him.
Now I'm gonna do
the same to you.
♪ ♪
- Frankie!
Frankie, stop!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
Frankie!
- No.
Frankie's gone.
My name is Magenta.
- You're like this
because of Alchemy.
He changed you,
didn't he?
This isn't you.
Just come with me.
♪ ♪
Tell me what happened.
I can help you.
- I don't need
any more help, Flash.
- I just don't want
anyone to get hurt.
- It's too late for that.
♪ ♪
- Frankie, don't!
- It's me...
or him.
- Come on.
- Aah!
♪ ♪
Her name's Frankie Kane,
but she's calling herself
Magenta.
- Meh.
- That Magenta is
a whole different person
than the scared, kind girl
I was interviewing.
- She's dissociative.
- You mean split-personality.
- According to
her medical records,
it's a condition
she's been dealing with
her entire life.
I'm sure
all the yelling at CCPD
is what triggered it.
- So Frankie is Jekyll.
Magenta is Hyde.
- Classic good versus evil.
- Or she's pulling
a "Primal Fear."
- She's faking it.
- No, she's not faking it.
I saw the struggle
going on inside of her.
Magenta's trying to
take over completely.
- You said she was raised
in the foster care system.
- Yep, all her life.
She went from home to home.
- Yeah, and maybe not good ones.
Her current foster father,
John...
the one who was hurt
in the attack...
yeah, he's got
a few disorderly conducts.
He might have some information
we can use.
I can follow up with him.
- There is something else.
She got her powers from Alchemy.
When I said his name,
she knew who he was,
so Magenta must have existed
in the other timeline too.
- Who's Alchemy?
- Well, Doctor Alchemy
is a magic man in a cloak
who can somehow restore
the powers that people had
in Flashpoint.
- Okay, and what's Flashpoint?
- That's what we're calling
the alternate timeline
that Barry created when he went
back in time and saved his mom.
- Oh.
So Magenta is
another side-effect
from your time trip.
Genius.
Not.
- I don't need to be reminded.
Thank you.
- Look, anybody
with those powers
and as angry as her
needs to be tracked down.
Fast.
- Well, great.
I mean, fast I can do.
Let me just go carb-load.
- He didn't...
that's...you don't...
Snow.
Please.
- Okay, Harry,
I'll talk to her,
but I don't know
what I'm gonna say.
- Hey, Joe?
Did you talk to Wally?
He still seems a little bummed.
- It's not
gonna fix itself overnight,
but it's all good.
He gets it.
- Okay.
- And I got to be honest,
it was one of my better
dad cop speeches.
- What's "dad cop"?
- There's good cop and bad cop
and dad cop.
Firm but reassuring.
Cuts to the point.
- I don't think I know that one.
- Yeah, I didn't use it on you.
Wally's different
than you, Barry.
You're like a second daughter.
You over-share your feelings.
Him, I got to be
a little more nuanced.
- Huh.
Cool.
- I'm messing with you.
I'll talk at you if I get
any leads on Frankie, all right?
- All right.
Second daughter?
What is he talking about?
- Hey!
- Hey.
Hey, sorry.
You guys were not kidding
when you said
speedsters were hungry
all the time.
- Yeah.
Listen, Jesse,
before you speed off
to find Frankie,
I just want to make sure
that you feel like you're ready.
- Why?
Is something wrong?
I mean, did the test results
say something?
- No, not at all.
All the test results
have come back fine so far.
It's just...
maybe you should
take it slow.
- Right.
This is because I'm a girl.
- What?
No, not at all.
Why?
- Well, I mean, Barry
didn't have to take things slow.
You know he was
stopping the criminals
the second he got his powers.
Why can't I do the same thing?
- Well, I mean,
I'm sure you think
that it's a great thing
to have powers,
but sometimes,
it's not so great.
Trust me.
I'm just saying
that if I had powers,
I would probably
take it slow.
- My dad put you up to this,
didn't he?
Yeah.
I mean, of course he did.
- Jesse...
- Hey.
You don't want
me to have this speed, do you?
I mean, that's why
we're here, right?
Not so you could test me,
but so you could get everyone
to talk me out of
using my powers.
- I just want you to be...
- To be safe, yeah.
Yeah, I know.
I've heard it my entire life.
- This is different.
This is way different.
- [scoffs]
Yeah, no, it is.
'Cause I'm not Barry, right?
- Right.
You're not Barry.
[tense music]
[sighs]
- Let me talk to her this time.
♪ ♪
- She's still here.
I can feel Frankie
trying to stay in control.
You said I could beat her.
- What I said was
I'd return to you
the power you had
to inflict your pain
upon others.
- But I need Frankie gone
to do that.
- Do you remember
why you came to me?
- I came to you
because you showed me a way
to stop him from hurting me.
- Show him
Magenta is in control.
And once you've done that,
Frankie will know it as well.
♪ ♪
- Here you are.
- Hey.
Hey, so, where...
where did you go yesterday?
- Wha...I...
I didn't want to
interrupt your training.
- Right.
Yeah, well, looks like
there won't be
much of that anymore,
now that my dad is getting
everyone to talk me out of
using my powers.
Wait, that...that's not
why you're here, right?
- No, no.
This is all me.
You all right?
- You know,
when this whole thing
happened to me,
you were...
you were actually the first
person I wanted to call.
Yeah, I was sort of hoping
it happened to you too.
- I dreamt about it,
believe me.
How did this all happen?
- I mean, it was crazy.
So, like, one day,
I was walking home
from a friend's house,
and this car ran a red light,
and it was speeding right at me,
and I just stood there, frozen,
basically waiting to be hit.
And then I looked around,
and everything around me
was frozen too.
It was peaceful and quiet,
but I felt this, like,
electricity running in me.
And so I ran out of the way.
I kept running and running,
and I...
I mean, now I don't
ever want to stop.
- So you basically
just jump-started your powers.
- I mean, I guess so, yeah.
Why?
[dramatic music]
- It's good to know.
[horn honking]
- Wally!
[tires screeching]
[dramatic music]
- What are you doing?
- Getting my speed.
Why would you do that?
- To save your life!
- It could've worked, Jesse!
- No, okay?
Look...
I don't think so.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
- Seriously,
what the hell
were you thinking?
You can't just go
stepping into the
street like that.
I mean you got
to use your head.
- Nothing happened, Barry.
Chill out.
- Didn't you talk to Joe
about this?
- Yeah, so?
- So it clearly didn't help.
What would you have done
if Jesse wasn't there, huh?
- I don't know, man.
- Because there's nothing
you could've done.
Because you don't have powers.
- Only room in our family
for one speedster, Barry?
- Please just stop trying
before you get yourself killed.
- You done?
- Do you have anything to say?
- No,
you pretty much covered it.
- This has got to stop.
- Stop yelling at me, okay?
I saved his life.
What did you want me to do?
- That's not the point.
That is not the...
- No, I know the point!
You don't want me
to use my powers.
- Right.
- Fine.
Fine, but I don't
need to stay here
and listen to this
anymore.
- No...Jess.
Jesse!
Don't...
[laughs softly]
What did you say to her?
- Me?
- Yeah.
You.
- Don't blame me for this.
I tried to help.
- Help her or help me?
- Listen, Harry.
Maybe the reason
she's shutting you out
is because
you're not trying to understand
what she's going through.
- I don't need to...
- Maybe if you helped her
navigate her powers
rather than just assuming
they'll destroy her,
she'd turn to you
rather than push you away.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Can't even bring myself
to take a lap around this thing.
- Why is that?
- I mean, you said it.
Everything's different here.
There's a guy
creating meta-humans...
innocent people...
'cause I changed the timeline.
It's on me.
- Yeah, I think
I know a thing or two
about what that feels like.
You know,
I keep making mistakes.
I make mistakes,
and then I want
to make up for my mistakes.
Then I just make more mistakes.
Next thing I know,
I have a daughter
that won't even speak to me.
- How do we keep
from messing things up
when all we want to do is help?
- I don't know.
But you did once tell me
that you have to trust it
in the long run
the decisions you make
are the right ones.
- [laughs softly]
- [sighs]
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- I was always too good
at forgiving myself, Allen.
You were never good enough.
♪ ♪
[siren wailing in distance]
- John James?
- Who's asking?
- Hi, I'm Iris West.
I'm a reporter for
Central City Picture News.
I wanted to ask you a couple
questions about Frankie Kane.
- [scoffs]
They find her yet?
- I don't believe so, no.
- Well,
what the hell's taking so long?
That damn meta-human freak
nearly killed me.
- I know.
I'm sorry.
- That's what I get for taking
Frankie in, huh? This?
God help me
if I ever see her again.
- What does that mean?
- It means
that she's gonna be the one
in the hospital.
- Tough love, John?
- Yeah, you're damn right.
- She was getting back at you
for hurting her.
And she's gonna try it again.
Nurse!
We need to get this man
to a safe location.
- Why?
[metallic scraping]
- What the hell's that?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Where are you taking me?
- Frankie is coming for you.
And as much as it pains me
to help an abusive dick
like you,
I can't let you die.
[alarm beeping]
- What kind of alarm is that?
- That's Iris's panic button.
- Her what?
- Her panic button.
We installed them
on everyone's phones.
'Cause we kept
getting kidnapped.
- At least something's
an improvement in this timeline.
- That's the hospital.
- Frankie's foster father's
there.
- Yeah,
and Iris went to see him.
- Looks like
she's not the only one.
- Is that a tanker?
- Th-th-that's a tanker, yeah.
- She's gonna kill him
and everyone else in there.
- I got to go.
- What are you gonna do?
You don't have superstrength.
- Start thinking.
♪ ♪
Guys...
There's not enough time
to get everybody
out of the hospital.
This thing's coming down.
- Barry, Iris is still in there.
♪ ♪
- What if...
what if I create a wind funnel?
- You won't be creating enough
updraft to keep that tanker up.
- No, no.
Not with my arms.
If I run.
- That could...
- Propeller.
- That could work.
Barry!
Run in a figure eight fashion.
You'll act like a propeller.
The wind will build
upon itself.
It'll create the supersonic
resistance we need.
Could work.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- Bye-bye, Daddy.
Flash!
♪ ♪
- Okay, well, that worked,
but now what?
He can't stop her
if he's up there.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
Cisco's right.
Go help him.
- Dad.
- You need
to get out there, now.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
I know you can do it.
You're more than fast enough.
Now, run, Jesse.
Run!
♪ ♪
- Hey, thought you could use
a little help.
I got this.
You go take care of her.
♪ ♪
- Magenta!
I got a little help.
So I could help you.
Okay, killing
your foster father
and everyone else
inside that hospital
isn't gonna give you
what you need.
- You have no idea
what I need!
It's not just John
that I want to get rid of.
I want them both gone.
♪ ♪
- Barry,
you got to stop her now.
That tanker's coming down!
- I know you're still in there,
Frankie.
Don't let John destroy the good
that's still inside you.
- He said I was weak.
That I was pathetic!
He said I was a horrible person.
- He's just blaming you
for all the bad things
he's caused in his life.
It's not your fault.
This isn't because of you.
- I just want him
to stop hurting me.
- This isn't the way.
Your foster father
never forgave himself
for his mistakes.
That's why he took
them out on you.
He couldn't face
who he really is.
He couldn't move forward.
♪ ♪
But you can.
- They did it.
- [laughs softly]
♪ ♪
- [crying]
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- [sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
- It's gonna be okay.
♪ ♪
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
- So no one else got hurt?
- Luckily, no.
You don't have to worry
about that.
- What about John?
- The DA's prosecuting him
for what he did to you.
So I think
he's gonna be serving time,
and he's not gonna ever be
anybody's foster father again.
- It's just so strange being
responsible for all of this
and not remembering
any of it.
- Whatdo you remember
about how you got your powers?
How this all began?
- Um...
I started having dreams,
at night, of Magenta.
- Dreams?
- They were more than dreams.
It was like I was living
another life or something.
And then I started getting them
all the time.
During the day.
And the more it happened,
the more painful they became.
Then I started hearing a voice.
- What voice?
- It was a man.
Named Alchemy.
He said he could
give me what I wanted
and make me powerful again.
I didn't understand.
I thought
I was going crazy.
- Trust me.
Magenta is not here
because of anything
that you did.
There may be
a darkness inside of you,
but if you face it,
it'll make it easier
for the good side of you to win.
- You're letting me go?
- None of this is your fault,
Frankie.
Caitlin found you
a good home in Keystone.
People that will never hurt you.
- But what if
Magenta tries to come back?
- Fight her.
And if you need help,
we'll be there.
We have faith in you, Frankie.
- Thank you.
- [laughs softly]
- Thank you all.
- Areyou okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I...
I just feel bad for her,
you know?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
No dad cop required.
- Oh!
You heard about that, huh?
- Yeah, I heard about that.
- [laughs]
[slow clapping]
- Hey.
- There she is.
You were tremendous
out there.
You really were.
I guess
that's your first victory...
as a superhero.
My daughter.
Jesse Quick.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, I mean,
I was only able to do it
'cause you believed in me,
so...
- No, I should've been that way
a long, long time ago,
but...
You know one day
you'll understand.
I don't expect you to now,
but I'm always gonna worry.
[poignant music]
I'm always going to be cautious.
♪ ♪
I'm always going to love you.
- Dad, I know.
I mean, of course I know.
♪ ♪
And I will always love you.
Even when you drive
me absolutely insane.
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
So...
- So.
- Are we going home or...
- I think we'll stay
for a few days,
run a few more tests,
and also to see
if this fits you.
♪ ♪
Cisco did the insignia.
Snow thought
this would help you,
and I agree.
♪ ♪
- You do?
- I do.
My...
My fear...
my guilt...
has kept both of us back
for far too long.
You know you've
always been my hero.
♪ ♪
But now...
it's time for me to let you
be one for everyone else.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
[romantic piano music]
- Hey.
- Hey, you just made it.
- Yeah, I had to make sure
Frankie was okay.
- So, are you ready
to try this again?
- Um...actually,
I had a thought
about why our last
date was so boring.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah...
♪ ♪
Here you go.
- [laughs softly]
- Um...
So, I know that you think
that I shouldn't use my powers,
and it's not that
I'm nothing without them,
but they are a part of me now,
you know?
They're part of you.
This is our life,
and I think,
last date, we were ignoring
that part of us.
We were trying to be
the people that we were
before I was the Flash,
and that's why
it wasn't working.
- Okay, so what are you saying?
[whoosh]
♪ ♪
- I'm saying we have to stop
denying who we really are.
- Well, yeah, I mean,
when you put it that way...
I agree.
We can't pretend like
none of this has happened.
♪ ♪
- I thought
you'd see it that way.
[phone vibrating]
- [laughs softly]
- Sorry.
It's Joe.
He needs me at the station.
- It's fine.
Go.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
This has already been
a really amazing date...
Flash.
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
[sighs]
[rousing music]
- Hey, what's going on?
- There you are.
Listen, Singh wanted me to
show you guys this.
This happened a few days ago
at Iron Heights.
They tried to
keep it under wraps
'cause they didn't want
anybody to think
there was a security issue,
but check it out.
- That's Clariss.
- Alchemy!
- Itwas Clariss.
- No! Aah!
No! Stop!
[screaming]
- Dead before he hit the ground.
- Alchemy.
- You ever heard
that name before?
Alchemy?
- No, I haven't.
- Maybe there's
an invisible meta.
- Maybe it's a ghost.
Do you believe in ghosts, Allen?
[tense music]
No?
♪ ♪
- Hey, do you think this thing
is part of the
Flashpoint timeline too?
- I have a feeling
a lot of things are these days.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.