1
00:01:00,060 --> 00:01:02,019
Just packed up
a real money load,

2
00:01:02,104 --> 00:01:03,104
and it's coming your way.

3
00:01:03,522 --> 00:01:05,481
Look for "Rodgers" on
the side of the truck.

4
00:01:05,649 --> 00:01:07,400
Don't forget my
share of the deal.

5
00:03:57,654 --> 00:03:58,738
Shit!

6
00:04:39,279 --> 00:04:41,489
Tuna on white,
no crust, right?

7
00:04:41,573 --> 00:04:43,532
I don't know.
How is it?

8
00:04:43,617 --> 00:04:45,242
Every day for
the last three weeks

9
00:04:45,327 --> 00:04:48,287
you've been coming in here
and you've been
asking me how the tuna is.

10
00:04:48,372 --> 00:04:51,958
Now, it was crappy yesterday,
it was crappy the day before.

11
00:04:52,042 --> 00:04:55,127
And guess what?
It hasn't changed.

12
00:04:55,212 --> 00:04:56,379
I'll have the tuna.

13
00:04:56,463 --> 00:04:58,381
No crust?
No crust.

14
00:05:22,614 --> 00:05:23,864
Thank you.

15
00:06:10,829 --> 00:06:11,954
Talk to me, Jesse.

16
00:06:12,039 --> 00:06:13,122
This ain't working, brother.

17
00:06:13,290 --> 00:06:15,916
It's your fuel map.
It's got a nasty hole.

18
00:06:16,168 --> 00:06:18,044
That's why you're
unloading in third.

19
00:06:18,128 --> 00:06:19,128
I told you it was third.

20
00:06:19,254 --> 00:06:20,963
Shut up.
I'd lengthen
the injector pulse

21
00:06:21,048 --> 00:06:22,173
another millisec,

22
00:06:22,257 --> 00:06:24,675
and just tune
the NOS timer,
you'll run nines.

23
00:06:32,350 --> 00:06:34,894
What's up with this fool?
What is he, sandwich crazy?

24
00:06:34,978 --> 00:06:36,645
No, V. He ain't
here for the food, dog.

25
00:06:36,730 --> 00:06:37,730
Chill out, bro.

26
00:06:37,814 --> 00:06:39,315
He's just slinging
parts for Harry, man.

27
00:06:39,441 --> 00:06:40,900
I know what he's slinging.

28
00:06:40,984 --> 00:06:43,069
He's trying to get
in Mia's pants, dog.

29
00:06:43,153 --> 00:06:44,111
What's up, guys?

30
00:06:44,196 --> 00:06:45,279
How you doing, Mia?

31
00:06:45,614 --> 00:06:47,156
How you living, girl?

32
00:06:47,365 --> 00:06:49,116
Hey!
Hey, Dom.

33
00:06:49,409 --> 00:06:51,243
You want something
to drink?

34
00:07:01,880 --> 00:07:03,881
He's beautiful.

35
00:07:03,965 --> 00:07:05,508
I like his haircut.

36
00:07:06,009 --> 00:07:07,009
Vince.

37
00:07:07,677 --> 00:07:08,677
Vince!

38
00:07:09,846 --> 00:07:10,888
What?

39
00:07:11,014 --> 00:07:12,098
Can I get you anything?

40
00:07:13,517 --> 00:07:14,809
You look good.

41
00:07:19,064 --> 00:07:21,398
Well, thanks a lot, Mia.
See you tomorrow.

42
00:07:21,483 --> 00:07:22,900
Sure.

43
00:07:24,569 --> 00:07:25,611
Tomorrow?

44
00:07:25,695 --> 00:07:26,862
I love this part.

45
00:07:27,989 --> 00:07:29,073
Yo!

46
00:07:31,243 --> 00:07:32,785
Try Fatburger
from now on.

47
00:07:32,869 --> 00:07:36,080
You can get
yourself a Double Cheese
with fries for $2.95, faggot.

48
00:07:36,164 --> 00:07:37,206
I like the tuna here.

49
00:07:37,290 --> 00:07:38,374
Bullshit, asshole.

50
00:07:38,542 --> 00:07:39,625
No one likes
the tuna here.

51
00:07:39,709 --> 00:07:41,043
Yeah, well, I do.

52
00:07:53,515 --> 00:07:54,640
Jesus Christ, Dom!

53
00:07:54,724 --> 00:07:55,766
Would you get
out there, please?

54
00:07:55,851 --> 00:07:57,226
I'm sick of this shit!

55
00:07:57,394 --> 00:07:59,728
I'm not kidding, Dom!
Get out there!

56
00:08:03,859 --> 00:08:05,109
What'd you put
in that sandwich?

57
00:08:05,193 --> 00:08:06,277
That's really funny.

58
00:08:06,361 --> 00:08:07,528
Dom!

59
00:08:08,196 --> 00:08:09,238
All right.

60
00:08:27,257 --> 00:08:28,424
Hey, man,
he was in my face.

61
00:08:28,592 --> 00:08:29,800
I'm in your face.

62
00:08:31,845 --> 00:08:34,930
Relax! Don't push it!
You embarrass me!

63
00:08:37,267 --> 00:08:38,601
Get over there!

64
00:08:38,810 --> 00:08:40,144
What are you doing?

65
00:08:40,228 --> 00:08:41,937
Jesse, give me the wallet.

66
00:08:44,941 --> 00:08:48,235
"Brian Earl Spilner."
Sounds like
a serial killer name.

67
00:08:48,320 --> 00:08:50,237
Is that what you are?
No, man.

68
00:08:50,322 --> 00:08:52,239
Don't come
around here again.

69
00:08:54,618 --> 00:08:56,785
Hey, man, you know
this is bullshit.

70
00:08:57,579 --> 00:08:58,996
You work for Harry, right?

71
00:08:59,122 --> 00:09:00,581
Yeah, I just started.

72
00:09:00,790 --> 00:09:02,291
You were just fired.

73
00:09:15,305 --> 00:09:18,224
Hey, Dominic,
I appreciate what
you did in a big way.

74
00:09:18,683 --> 00:09:20,226
Dominic, I owe you.

75
00:09:22,395 --> 00:09:25,064
Brian, you're messing
with my business.

76
00:09:25,148 --> 00:09:26,982
When Dominic drives,
he's golden.

77
00:09:27,484 --> 00:09:29,235
Kids pour in here,
they want everything he has,

78
00:09:29,319 --> 00:09:32,071
every performance part,
and they pay cash!

79
00:09:32,155 --> 00:09:33,405
What did Dominic say?

80
00:09:33,531 --> 00:09:34,782
You don't wanna know.

81
00:09:35,200 --> 00:09:36,325
What did Dominic say?

82
00:09:36,409 --> 00:09:37,743
He wants you
out of here.

83
00:09:38,662 --> 00:09:39,745
He wants me out of here?

84
00:09:39,829 --> 00:09:40,871
Yes!

85
00:09:40,956 --> 00:09:42,164
And what did you
say to Dom?

86
00:09:42,249 --> 00:09:43,540
What do you think
I said?

87
00:09:44,584 --> 00:09:46,877
I told him good help
is hard to find.

88
00:09:47,963 --> 00:09:49,004
Hey.

89
00:09:50,006 --> 00:09:51,173
Relax.

90
00:09:54,761 --> 00:09:57,513
I need NOS.
I need NOS.

91
00:09:58,056 --> 00:09:59,098
No.

92
00:09:59,182 --> 00:10:01,725
My car topped out
at a 140 miles
per hour this morning.

93
00:10:01,810 --> 00:10:03,686
Amateurs don't
use nitrous oxide.

94
00:10:03,770 --> 00:10:05,312
I've seen the way
you drive.

95
00:10:05,438 --> 00:10:06,939
You got a heavy foot.

96
00:10:07,023 --> 00:10:08,649
You'll blow
yourself to pieces.

97
00:10:08,733 --> 00:10:11,527
I need one of these.
One of the big ones.

98
00:10:11,778 --> 00:10:13,988
Actually, no,
let's make it two.

99
00:10:14,322 --> 00:10:16,532
And, Harry, I need it
by tonight.

100
00:11:28,396 --> 00:11:29,772
Player, hold up,
hold up.

101
00:11:29,898 --> 00:11:31,273
Look at this snowman
right here, man.

102
00:11:35,862 --> 00:11:37,404
Sweet ride.

103
00:11:37,530 --> 00:11:39,073
What you running
under there, man?

104
00:11:41,284 --> 00:11:42,701
You gonna make me
find out the hard way?

105
00:11:42,786 --> 00:11:44,119
Hell, yeah.

106
00:11:44,329 --> 00:11:47,373
You brave. You brave.
They call me Hector.

107
00:11:47,957 --> 00:11:50,709
I got a last name, too,
but I can't
pronounce it, so...

108
00:11:50,794 --> 00:11:52,127
Brian Spilner.

109
00:11:52,253 --> 00:11:53,545
Yeah, typical
white boy name.

110
00:11:53,630 --> 00:11:55,339
You know
what I'm saying?

111
00:11:57,801 --> 00:11:59,343
See that over there?

112
00:11:59,469 --> 00:12:01,053
That's mine.
It's my baby.

113
00:12:01,221 --> 00:12:02,763
But I ain't cutting
her loose tonight.

114
00:12:02,847 --> 00:12:04,765
Why not?
It's 'cause
I'm going legit, homie.

115
00:12:04,849 --> 00:12:06,433
Trying to get
on the NIRA circuit.

116
00:12:06,518 --> 00:12:08,310
You heard about that?
Hell, yeah.

117
00:12:08,395 --> 00:12:10,521
Yeah, yeah.
So, what's up
with you, man?

118
00:12:10,605 --> 00:12:12,356
I'm just waiting
for Toretto.

119
00:12:12,440 --> 00:12:15,275
Shit. Better get
in line. This yours?

120
00:12:16,152 --> 00:12:17,444
Yeah, I'm standing
next to it.

121
00:12:17,570 --> 00:12:18,821
That's funny.

122
00:12:18,905 --> 00:12:21,657
You know, Edwin happens
to know a few things.

123
00:12:21,741 --> 00:12:23,867
And one of the things
Edwin knows is

124
00:12:23,993 --> 00:12:26,120
it's not how you
stand by your car,

125
00:12:26,204 --> 00:12:27,621
it's how you race
your car.

126
00:12:27,747 --> 00:12:29,164
You better learn that.

127
00:12:35,380 --> 00:12:37,714
Shit. Here they come.
It's on.

128
00:12:54,732 --> 00:12:55,774
Marvin.

129
00:12:56,818 --> 00:12:58,569
Hey, Dom,
how you doing?
Hey, Gimel.

130
00:12:58,653 --> 00:13:00,571
What've you been
doing? Yoga?

131
00:13:04,993 --> 00:13:06,410
Oh, you did?
Of course, you did.

132
00:13:06,494 --> 00:13:08,370
Hey, I'm Monica.
Nice to meet you.
Monica.

133
00:13:10,582 --> 00:13:12,875
I smell skanks.

134
00:13:13,251 --> 00:13:15,210
Why don't you girls
just pack it up

135
00:13:15,378 --> 00:13:17,296
before I leave
tread marks on your face?

136
00:13:17,380 --> 00:13:18,547
Okay.

137
00:13:18,631 --> 00:13:19,631
Letty, I was just talking.

138
00:13:19,716 --> 00:13:20,883
Yeah, whatever.

139
00:13:21,759 --> 00:13:23,260
Okay. Hector.

140
00:13:23,386 --> 00:13:24,887
Yeah. What's up, man?

141
00:13:26,431 --> 00:13:27,764
Yo, what's up? Edwin.

142
00:13:27,891 --> 00:13:29,224
How we doing
this tonight?

143
00:13:29,684 --> 00:13:31,894
One race, $2,000 buy in.

144
00:13:31,978 --> 00:13:33,645
Winner takes all.

145
00:13:33,730 --> 00:13:34,897
Hector, you're gonna
hold the cash.

146
00:13:35,064 --> 00:13:36,231
Why Hector?

147
00:13:36,316 --> 00:13:39,276
'Cause he's too slow
to make away
with the money, man.

148
00:13:40,987 --> 00:13:42,237
Okay, good luck, guys.

149
00:13:42,363 --> 00:13:43,572
Hey, wait, hold up.

150
00:13:44,073 --> 00:13:48,035
I don't have any cash,
but I do have
the pink slip to my car.

151
00:13:48,119 --> 00:13:51,830
Hey, you just can't
climb in the ring with Ali,
'cause you think you box.

152
00:13:52,540 --> 00:13:54,208
He knows I can box.

153
00:13:54,334 --> 00:13:56,043
So check it out,
it's like this.

154
00:13:56,753 --> 00:14:00,047
I lose,
the winner takes my car,
clean and clear.

155
00:14:00,298 --> 00:14:04,051
But if I win,
I take the cash,
and I take the respect.

156
00:14:04,302 --> 00:14:05,594
Respect.

157
00:14:07,597 --> 00:14:09,389
To some people,
that's more important.

158
00:14:12,268 --> 00:14:13,810
That your car?

159
00:14:17,232 --> 00:14:18,857
I see
a cool air intake.

160
00:14:18,942 --> 00:14:22,236
It's got a NOS fogger system
and a T4 Turbo, Dominic.

161
00:14:22,320 --> 00:14:24,488
I see an AIC
control there.

162
00:14:24,572 --> 00:14:27,533
It has direct port
nitrous injection.

163
00:14:27,617 --> 00:14:30,619
Yeah, and a stand-alone
fuel management system.

164
00:14:31,204 --> 00:14:33,956
Not a bad way
to spend $10,000.

165
00:14:36,376 --> 00:14:37,793
You see that shit?

166
00:14:38,795 --> 00:14:41,046
He's got enough NOS in there
to blow himself up, period.

167
00:14:41,130 --> 00:14:42,214
Yeah.

168
00:14:42,632 --> 00:14:44,716
So, what do you say?
Am I worthy?

169
00:14:44,801 --> 00:14:46,468
We don't know yet.

170
00:14:46,636 --> 00:14:49,096
But you're in.
Let's go.

171
00:15:55,330 --> 00:15:57,331
What the hell's
going on around here?

172
00:15:57,874 --> 00:15:59,458
Street's closed, pizza boy.

173
00:15:59,584 --> 00:16:01,209
Find another way home.

174
00:16:01,544 --> 00:16:02,836
Goddamn street racers.

175
00:16:04,631 --> 00:16:06,298
Code 3. Tension is high.

176
00:16:06,382 --> 00:16:08,091
They've blocked the street.

177
00:16:53,930 --> 00:16:55,138
Edwin,

178
00:16:56,849 --> 00:17:00,268
this is yours,
whether you win or lose.

179
00:17:00,770 --> 00:17:03,897
But if you win,
you get her, too.

180
00:17:12,782 --> 00:17:14,116
You're gonna win.

181
00:17:15,785 --> 00:17:17,077
I'm gonna win.

182
00:18:01,706 --> 00:18:04,624
We got a reported homicide
187 at Barabian Liquors.

183
00:18:04,709 --> 00:18:06,585
I got a 187 in Glendale.

184
00:18:06,669 --> 00:18:08,712
Cops are all over it, man.
We're good to roll.

185
00:18:08,796 --> 00:18:09,880
I repeat, good to roll.

186
00:18:09,964 --> 00:18:11,381
All right.
Let's race!

187
00:18:11,466 --> 00:18:12,507
Right.

188
00:18:22,018 --> 00:18:23,059
Go!

189
00:18:36,699 --> 00:18:37,824
Hell, yeah!

190
00:18:54,091 --> 00:18:55,550
Damn, that guy's fast.

191
00:19:03,684 --> 00:19:06,728
Let's go! Ménage à!

192
00:19:33,297 --> 00:19:34,756
No!

193
00:19:35,049 --> 00:19:36,758
Monica!

194
00:19:51,774 --> 00:19:52,899
Shut up!

195
00:20:47,914 --> 00:20:49,080
Let's go now, baby!

196
00:20:49,206 --> 00:20:50,373
Yeah!

197
00:21:01,636 --> 00:21:03,178
Here's what you want,
right here.

198
00:21:03,304 --> 00:21:04,846
There you go.

199
00:21:09,310 --> 00:21:12,437
My sister holds
the money. Count it.

200
00:21:15,066 --> 00:21:16,608
Me and my trophy.

201
00:21:19,862 --> 00:21:21,821
Hey, hey, Monica.
What's up, baby?

202
00:21:21,906 --> 00:21:22,948
What's your problem, nigger?

203
00:21:23,032 --> 00:21:24,115
You didn't win.

204
00:21:26,702 --> 00:21:27,953
Fuck you, then!

205
00:21:41,092 --> 00:21:42,550
Was that fun?

206
00:21:42,885 --> 00:21:45,136
Got a problem there,
huh, buddy?

207
00:21:51,519 --> 00:21:52,978
What are you
smiling about?

208
00:21:53,104 --> 00:21:54,604
Dude, I almost had you.

209
00:21:57,566 --> 00:21:59,442
You almost had me?

210
00:21:59,735 --> 00:22:02,904
You never had me.
You never had your car.

211
00:22:05,825 --> 00:22:08,994
Granny shifting,
not double clutching
like you should.

212
00:22:10,037 --> 00:22:11,579
You're lucky
that 100 shot of NOS

213
00:22:11,747 --> 00:22:13,331
didn't blow the welds
on the intake.

214
00:22:13,416 --> 00:22:14,708
Nice job!

215
00:22:15,292 --> 00:22:16,751
Almost had me?

216
00:22:17,753 --> 00:22:19,254
I don't know, man.

217
00:22:19,338 --> 00:22:21,006
Get out of here.

218
00:22:21,090 --> 00:22:24,259
Now me and the mad scientist
gotta rip apart the block

219
00:22:24,343 --> 00:22:26,886
and replace
the piston rings you fried.

220
00:22:34,603 --> 00:22:36,730
Ask any racer,
any real racer.

221
00:22:37,314 --> 00:22:40,567
It don't matter if you win
by an inch or a mile.

222
00:22:40,651 --> 00:22:42,110
Winning's winning.

223
00:22:42,194 --> 00:22:43,778
Yeah!

224
00:22:49,160 --> 00:22:51,202
Any available
units, we have reported

225
00:22:51,287 --> 00:22:52,287
street racing
along Hawthorne...

226
00:22:52,371 --> 00:22:55,290
Oh, shit! We got cops,
cops, cops! Go!

227
00:23:07,344 --> 00:23:09,054
Dom, get in the car! Go!

228
00:24:33,472 --> 00:24:35,640
Toretto,
stop right there!

229
00:24:37,143 --> 00:24:38,434
Toretto!

230
00:24:53,325 --> 00:24:54,409
Get in!

231
00:25:41,290 --> 00:25:44,542
You're the last person
in the world I expected
to show up.

232
00:25:45,586 --> 00:25:47,670
Yeah, well, I thought
if I got in your good graces

233
00:25:47,755 --> 00:25:49,631
you might let me
keep my car.

234
00:25:49,882 --> 00:25:52,800
You are in my good graces,
but you ain't
keeping your car.

235
00:25:54,053 --> 00:25:55,762
You drive like
you've done this before.

236
00:25:55,846 --> 00:25:57,180
What are you,
a wheelman?

237
00:25:57,264 --> 00:25:58,264
No.

238
00:25:58,807 --> 00:26:00,099
You boost cars?

239
00:26:01,936 --> 00:26:03,144
No, never.

240
00:26:03,229 --> 00:26:04,812
Ever done time?

241
00:26:04,939 --> 00:26:06,481
A couple of overnighters.
No big deal.

242
00:26:07,608 --> 00:26:10,860
What about the two years
in juvie for boosting cars?

243
00:26:13,530 --> 00:26:14,864
Tucson, right?

244
00:26:15,783 --> 00:26:19,327
Yeah, I had Jesse
run a profile on you,
Brian Earl Spilner.

245
00:26:20,496 --> 00:26:23,665
He'll find anything
on the Web,
anything about anybody.

246
00:26:24,375 --> 00:26:25,750
So why bullshit?

247
00:26:27,461 --> 00:26:28,836
So what about you?

248
00:26:31,340 --> 00:26:32,882
Two years in Lompoc.

249
00:26:35,970 --> 00:26:37,762
I'll die before I go back.

250
00:26:43,852 --> 00:26:45,019
Oh, great.

251
00:26:45,521 --> 00:26:46,729
What?

252
00:26:48,816 --> 00:26:51,359
It's gonna be
a long-ass night,
that's what.

253
00:26:55,531 --> 00:26:56,614
Follow us.

254
00:27:47,416 --> 00:27:49,334
I thought
we had an agreement.

255
00:27:50,127 --> 00:27:52,211
You stay away,
I stay away.

256
00:27:53,422 --> 00:27:54,839
Everybody stays happy.

257
00:27:54,923 --> 00:27:56,007
We got lost, Johnny.

258
00:27:56,091 --> 00:27:57,258
What do you want me
to tell you?

259
00:27:57,426 --> 00:27:58,593
Who's "we"?

260
00:27:59,428 --> 00:28:02,513
My new mechanic.
Brian, meet Johnny Tran.

261
00:28:02,598 --> 00:28:05,558
The guy in
the snakeskin pants,
that's his cousin, Lance.

262
00:28:05,642 --> 00:28:09,270
So when are you
gonna give me a shot
at that Honda 2000 of yours?

263
00:28:09,605 --> 00:28:10,605
This your ride?

264
00:28:10,689 --> 00:28:11,939
It was. It's his now.

265
00:28:12,274 --> 00:28:14,650
No, it's not.
I haven't taken delivery.

266
00:28:16,945 --> 00:28:18,571
Then it's nobody's car.

267
00:28:19,573 --> 00:28:21,616
Somebody put in
the wrench time.

268
00:28:23,827 --> 00:28:25,578
What do you think, Lance?

269
00:28:26,372 --> 00:28:27,705
It's an amazing machine.

270
00:28:27,831 --> 00:28:29,207
Yes, indeed.

271
00:28:31,710 --> 00:28:32,835
Let's go.

272
00:28:35,381 --> 00:28:37,673
I'll see you in
the desert next month.

273
00:28:37,925 --> 00:28:39,884
Be ready to have
your ass handed to you.

274
00:28:39,968 --> 00:28:42,136
Yeah, you're gonna need more
than that crotch rocket.

275
00:28:42,221 --> 00:28:43,930
I got something for you.

276
00:28:57,694 --> 00:28:59,570
What the hell
was that all about?

277
00:28:59,655 --> 00:29:00,988
Long story.
I'll tell you later.

278
00:29:01,156 --> 00:29:02,490
Let's get out of here.

279
00:29:30,352 --> 00:29:31,561
NOS!

280
00:29:43,866 --> 00:29:46,284
So, what the hell
was that all about?

281
00:29:46,368 --> 00:29:47,910
It's a long story.

282
00:29:47,995 --> 00:29:50,204
Well, we got
a 20-mile hike.
Humor me.

283
00:29:50,998 --> 00:29:53,082
A business deal
that went sour.

284
00:29:53,876 --> 00:29:56,878
Plus, I made the mistake
of sleeping with his sister.

285
00:30:23,322 --> 00:30:24,530
Take care.

286
00:30:29,578 --> 00:30:30,786
Yo, Spilner.

287
00:30:32,581 --> 00:30:33,706
You want a beer?

288
00:30:33,832 --> 00:30:34,916
Yeah, sure.

289
00:30:35,918 --> 00:30:37,126
Oh, shit.

290
00:31:01,151 --> 00:31:02,568
You're all in, right?

291
00:31:02,694 --> 00:31:04,111
Wow, man,
she's hot.

292
00:31:04,530 --> 00:31:05,613
Which one of
you uses nitrous?

293
00:31:05,781 --> 00:31:06,906
Yo.

294
00:31:13,539 --> 00:31:15,081
Yo, Dom. Hey, man.
We were just about

295
00:31:15,207 --> 00:31:16,749
to go looking
for you, brother.

296
00:31:23,090 --> 00:31:24,298
Where were you?

297
00:31:24,466 --> 00:31:25,716
There were
mass cops there.

298
00:31:25,801 --> 00:31:27,134
They came in
from every direction.

299
00:31:27,261 --> 00:31:28,594
That shit was orchestrated.

300
00:31:28,679 --> 00:31:29,804
This your beer?

301
00:31:29,930 --> 00:31:31,013
Yeah, that's my beer.

302
00:31:34,184 --> 00:31:36,644
Yo, Einstein.
Take it upstairs.

303
00:31:37,312 --> 00:31:39,647
You can't detail a car
with the cover on.

304
00:31:40,691 --> 00:31:42,400
Can't even get that right.

305
00:31:42,484 --> 00:31:43,776
You all right?

306
00:31:45,821 --> 00:31:47,280
Am I all right?

307
00:31:47,406 --> 00:31:48,906
It was just
a question.

308
00:31:52,369 --> 00:31:55,496
Yo, Dom! Why'd you
bring the buster here?

309
00:31:55,581 --> 00:31:57,957
'Cause the buster
kept me out of handcuffs!

310
00:31:58,041 --> 00:32:00,251
He didn't just run
back to the fort!

311
00:32:00,460 --> 00:32:02,336
The buster brought me back.

312
00:32:07,926 --> 00:32:12,263
You can have any brew you want
as long as it's a Corona.

313
00:32:12,347 --> 00:32:13,306
Thanks, man.

314
00:32:13,390 --> 00:32:14,724
That's Vince's,
so enjoy it.

315
00:32:16,852 --> 00:32:18,102
You...

316
00:32:25,235 --> 00:32:27,278
Hey, bro,
you got a bathroom?

317
00:32:27,404 --> 00:32:29,447
Yeah, upstairs.
First door on the right.

318
00:32:45,714 --> 00:32:47,465
He's got no call
being up in here.

319
00:32:47,549 --> 00:32:49,050
You don't know
that fool for shit!

320
00:32:49,134 --> 00:32:50,635
Yeah, he's right, Dom.

321
00:32:50,719 --> 00:32:52,928
Vince, there was a time
when I didn't know you.

322
00:32:53,013 --> 00:32:54,722
That was
in the third grade!

323
00:32:55,015 --> 00:32:56,140
Yeah.

324
00:32:58,018 --> 00:32:59,685
Yeah, so,
what girls are here?

325
00:32:59,811 --> 00:33:01,479
You just name it.
You want mine?

326
00:33:01,563 --> 00:33:04,023
You need to shut the F...
You want two?

327
00:33:04,274 --> 00:33:05,399
You don't have anything?

328
00:33:05,525 --> 00:33:06,901
You look a bit tired.

329
00:33:06,985 --> 00:33:09,487
I think you should go upstairs
and give me a massage.

330
00:33:09,571 --> 00:33:10,738
Look at all our guests.

331
00:33:10,822 --> 00:33:13,699
How about we go upstairs
and you give me a massage?

332
00:33:16,536 --> 00:33:17,745
Crazy bitch.

333
00:33:22,501 --> 00:33:23,626
Yo.

334
00:33:25,420 --> 00:33:28,089
You know you owe me
a 10-second car, right?

335
00:33:29,633 --> 00:33:31,258
Ouch.

336
00:33:33,011 --> 00:33:34,178
Oh, shit.

337
00:33:39,810 --> 00:33:41,435
Did you wipe the seat?

338
00:33:44,773 --> 00:33:48,526
Jesus Christ! Would you
cut this shit already?
Come on!

339
00:33:50,445 --> 00:33:52,571
Come on, let's go
get me a drink.

340
00:33:52,989 --> 00:33:55,449
Come on, man.
We were just
about to get along.

341
00:33:55,534 --> 00:33:56,659
Yeah.

342
00:34:02,374 --> 00:34:03,541
So, what do you want?

343
00:34:03,625 --> 00:34:05,000
Anything,
long as it's cold.

344
00:34:07,254 --> 00:34:09,088
You know,
my brother likes you.

345
00:34:09,506 --> 00:34:10,923
He usually
doesn't like anybody.

346
00:34:11,049 --> 00:34:12,466
Yeah, he's
a complicated guy.

347
00:34:12,551 --> 00:34:14,593
Yeah? What about you?

348
00:34:17,222 --> 00:34:18,472
I'm simpler.

349
00:34:18,640 --> 00:34:19,890
You're a shitty liar.

350
00:34:21,476 --> 00:34:23,769
Well, I'll take
that as a compliment.

351
00:34:25,647 --> 00:34:26,772
There's a problem.

352
00:34:26,898 --> 00:34:27,982
What's that?

353
00:34:28,483 --> 00:34:30,484
You need
to get some sleep.

354
00:34:31,027 --> 00:34:34,822
And you definitely,
definitely need a shower.

355
00:34:35,949 --> 00:34:38,075
Come on,
I'll take you home.

356
00:35:00,390 --> 00:35:01,432
Show me your hands.

357
00:35:01,516 --> 00:35:03,017
Very good.
Now open the door.

358
00:35:03,643 --> 00:35:05,644
Put your hands on your head.

359
00:35:05,729 --> 00:35:06,937
Behind your head.

360
00:35:07,022 --> 00:35:08,230
Face the front
of the vehicle,

361
00:35:08,315 --> 00:35:09,982
walk backwards
towards the rear.

362
00:35:10,776 --> 00:35:12,693
Take two steps to your right.

363
00:35:13,278 --> 00:35:14,862
Stop right there.

364
00:35:17,365 --> 00:35:18,824
What'd I do?

365
00:35:18,909 --> 00:35:19,950
Shut up.

366
00:35:20,327 --> 00:35:21,702
He's clean, Sarge.

367
00:35:32,047 --> 00:35:34,215
Damn! Muse, will you
take these things off?

368
00:35:34,299 --> 00:35:36,175
I mean, shit,
you put them on so tight.

369
00:35:36,259 --> 00:35:37,760
I like realism.

370
00:35:38,011 --> 00:35:40,054
You never know
who's watching, Brian.

371
00:35:44,935 --> 00:35:46,310
Wow. Nice crib, Sergeant.

372
00:35:46,394 --> 00:35:48,562
It's a lot nicer
than that last place
you confiscated.

373
00:35:48,647 --> 00:35:50,815
Ain't it? You know,
Eddie Fisher built this house

374
00:35:50,899 --> 00:35:52,858
for Elizabeth Taylor
in the '50s.

375
00:35:52,943 --> 00:35:55,319
You see, even the cops
are Hollywood in Hollywood.

376
00:35:59,783 --> 00:36:01,283
Okay, here he is.

377
00:36:01,409 --> 00:36:02,952
Fresh from Toretto's
hot rod heaven.

378
00:36:03,036 --> 00:36:05,204
That was an $80,000
vehicle, officer.

379
00:36:05,288 --> 00:36:06,789
Wait a minute.
You tell him what happened?

380
00:36:06,873 --> 00:36:08,332
He knows what happened.
Hey, you know what?

381
00:36:08,416 --> 00:36:10,334
Why don't you send
the bill to Johnny Tran.
Brian.

382
00:36:10,418 --> 00:36:11,794
The kid's giving me attitude?

383
00:36:11,878 --> 00:36:14,588
That doesn't speak
very well for
police-FBI relations, Tanner.

384
00:36:14,673 --> 00:36:15,756
I mean, come on,
what is this?

385
00:36:15,841 --> 00:36:17,174
I walk in the door
and the guy's giving me...

386
00:36:17,259 --> 00:36:19,468
All right, all right,
all right. We'll talk, okay?

387
00:36:19,553 --> 00:36:20,553
Let's talk about it.

388
00:36:20,637 --> 00:36:23,931
Muse, why don't you
make us four iced
cappuccinos, please.

389
00:36:24,015 --> 00:36:25,140
Come on.

390
00:36:25,267 --> 00:36:26,433
Regular or decaf, Sarge?

391
00:36:28,103 --> 00:36:29,395
Decaf, I think.

392
00:36:29,813 --> 00:36:32,481
Four hijackings
in two months and we don't
have anything.

393
00:36:32,566 --> 00:36:35,359
DVD players and
digital cameras alone
are worth $1 .2 million,

394
00:36:35,443 --> 00:36:38,153
which brings the grand total
to $6 million plus.

395
00:36:38,488 --> 00:36:41,657
We're in
the political crosshairs
now, Brian.

396
00:36:42,033 --> 00:36:43,951
That's why
you're undercover.

397
00:36:44,202 --> 00:36:45,995
You want that
detective badge fast, kid.

398
00:36:46,121 --> 00:36:47,955
And you wanna
know something?

399
00:36:48,248 --> 00:36:51,166
The FBI can help,
if you come through for us.

400
00:36:52,335 --> 00:36:53,836
What does
the truck driver say?

401
00:36:53,962 --> 00:36:55,504
He gave us the same MO.

402
00:36:55,589 --> 00:36:57,756
Three Honda Civics,
precision driving,

403
00:36:57,841 --> 00:37:00,885
the same green neon glow
from under the chassis.

404
00:37:00,969 --> 00:37:03,721
Lab says the skid marks
came back the same.

405
00:37:03,805 --> 00:37:05,389
Mashimoto ZX tires.

406
00:37:05,473 --> 00:37:08,267
So we know that it's somebody
in the street racing world.

407
00:37:08,351 --> 00:37:09,810
We don't make
this case soon

408
00:37:09,895 --> 00:37:12,771
the truckers
will take matters
into their own hands.

409
00:37:12,856 --> 00:37:14,565
I told them we're close.

410
00:37:15,984 --> 00:37:17,318
You gonna make me a liar?

411
00:37:17,485 --> 00:37:18,861
Look, what do we know?

412
00:37:19,446 --> 00:37:21,906
We all know
this world revolves
around Toretto, right?

413
00:37:21,990 --> 00:37:23,782
Now, I'm not saying
that he's necessarily

414
00:37:23,867 --> 00:37:25,075
the one that's
popping these trucks,

415
00:37:25,160 --> 00:37:27,953
but I can guarantee
the both of you
that he knows who is.

416
00:37:28,038 --> 00:37:29,413
It's just a matter
of time until I win...

417
00:37:29,497 --> 00:37:31,665
You want time,
buy the magazine.

418
00:37:32,292 --> 00:37:33,751
We don't have time.

419
00:37:35,211 --> 00:37:37,254
Just get me
something I can use.

420
00:37:39,257 --> 00:37:40,591
Is Harry cooperating?

421
00:37:40,675 --> 00:37:42,676
Yeah, like a guy
that's gonna do
three to five

422
00:37:42,761 --> 00:37:44,553
for receiving stolen
property if he doesn't.

423
00:37:44,638 --> 00:37:46,430
What kind of vibe
is he getting from Toretto?

424
00:37:46,514 --> 00:37:47,556
He's scared
to death of him,

425
00:37:47,641 --> 00:37:50,142
but he doesn't think
he's jacking trucks
in his spare time, either.

426
00:37:50,226 --> 00:37:51,268
He's too controlled for that.

427
00:37:51,353 --> 00:37:52,436
Wait.

428
00:37:52,520 --> 00:37:55,522
Not that I want
to contradict Harry's
fine judge of character,

429
00:37:55,607 --> 00:37:59,276
but Toretto did
hard time for nearly
beating a guy to death.

430
00:37:59,361 --> 00:38:02,446
He's got nitrous oxide
in his blood and
a gas tank for a brain.

431
00:38:02,530 --> 00:38:04,406
Do not turn
your back on him.

432
00:38:04,783 --> 00:38:07,493
Hey, Tanner,
I'm gonna need another car.

433
00:38:11,414 --> 00:38:12,831
What about parts
and service?

434
00:38:12,916 --> 00:38:14,041
Hold off on that.

435
00:38:14,125 --> 00:38:16,001
Dom, I don't know
what to do with this.

436
00:38:20,048 --> 00:38:22,299
All right,
what the hell is this?

437
00:38:22,717 --> 00:38:24,301
What do you got there?

438
00:38:25,553 --> 00:38:26,637
This is your car.

439
00:38:26,763 --> 00:38:27,888
My car?

440
00:38:28,473 --> 00:38:31,517
I said, a 10-second car,
not a 10-minute car.

441
00:38:31,601 --> 00:38:35,562
You could push this
across the finish line,
or tow it.

442
00:38:36,773 --> 00:38:39,233
Couldn't even tow that
across the finish line.

443
00:38:40,402 --> 00:38:41,694
No faith.

444
00:38:41,778 --> 00:38:45,406
I have faith in you,
but this isn't a junkyard,
this is a garage.

445
00:38:45,490 --> 00:38:46,490
Hey, pop the hood.

446
00:38:46,616 --> 00:38:47,616
Pop the hood?

447
00:38:47,701 --> 00:38:49,118
Pop the hood.

448
00:38:51,162 --> 00:38:53,622
- 2JZ engine.
- No shit.

449
00:38:53,707 --> 00:38:54,748
Man, what did
I tell you?

450
00:38:54,833 --> 00:38:56,458
I retract my
previous statement.

451
00:38:56,543 --> 00:38:57,668
You know what?

452
00:38:57,752 --> 00:39:02,339
This will decimate
all after you put
about $15,000 in it

453
00:39:02,424 --> 00:39:06,260
or more if we have to
overnight parts from Japan.

454
00:39:06,594 --> 00:39:08,053
We'll put it on
my tab at Harry's.

455
00:39:08,138 --> 00:39:09,346
Yes!

456
00:39:09,639 --> 00:39:13,350
I gotta get you racing again
so I can make some
money off your ass.

457
00:39:14,102 --> 00:39:16,854
There's this showdown
in the desert
called Race Wars

458
00:39:16,938 --> 00:39:18,897
and that's
where you'll do it.

459
00:39:19,399 --> 00:39:21,525
I'll tell you what.
When you're not working
at Harry's,

460
00:39:21,609 --> 00:39:22,985
you're working here.

461
00:39:23,069 --> 00:39:26,822
If you can't
find the right tool
in this garage, Mr. Arizona,

462
00:39:27,157 --> 00:39:28,991
you don't belong
near a car.

463
00:39:33,163 --> 00:39:34,621
He owns you now.

464
00:40:00,065 --> 00:40:02,149
Tell me what
you think about this.

465
00:40:02,233 --> 00:40:03,317
Koni adjustables.

466
00:40:04,319 --> 00:40:06,612
They'll save us
about two pounds.

467
00:40:06,780 --> 00:40:11,075
And they're gonna
give us better traction
for the hole shot. All right?

468
00:40:12,202 --> 00:40:14,369
Okay, so this is
your basic layout
of the car,

469
00:40:14,454 --> 00:40:18,499
and that's pretty much
what it could look
like when it's finished.

470
00:40:19,042 --> 00:40:20,417
Red, green.

471
00:40:20,877 --> 00:40:23,253
Man, you should be going
to MIT or something.

472
00:40:23,338 --> 00:40:24,713
Yeah, right.

473
00:40:25,131 --> 00:40:26,548
No, I got that...

474
00:40:27,133 --> 00:40:28,509
What's it called?

475
00:40:29,177 --> 00:40:31,178
That attention disorder...

476
00:40:31,554 --> 00:40:35,599
ADD?
Yes, that shit. Yeah.

477
00:40:36,309 --> 00:40:40,145
You know,
I was good in algebra,
and like, math and shit.

478
00:40:40,939 --> 00:40:42,940
Everything else I failed.

479
00:40:43,525 --> 00:40:45,025
Dropped out of school.

480
00:40:45,693 --> 00:40:49,196
I don't know. There's just
something about engines

481
00:40:49,280 --> 00:40:52,366
that calms me down,
you know.

482
00:41:12,804 --> 00:41:13,887
I'm out of here.

483
00:41:14,013 --> 00:41:15,097
Come on, dog.

484
00:41:16,057 --> 00:41:17,099
Yo, Dom.

485
00:41:17,183 --> 00:41:18,642
Vince, get over here,
give us a hand.

486
00:41:18,726 --> 00:41:21,562
Looks like
you got all the help
you need, brother.

487
00:41:35,243 --> 00:41:37,327
Mia! The chicken's
dry already.

488
00:41:37,412 --> 00:41:39,246
All right already.
I'm coming out already.

489
00:41:39,414 --> 00:41:41,081
- How are you guys doing?
- Good.

490
00:41:41,166 --> 00:41:42,332
Come here.

491
00:41:47,255 --> 00:41:48,463
Wait, hold up.

492
00:41:49,090 --> 00:41:51,341
Because you were the first
out of everybody here

493
00:41:51,426 --> 00:41:54,469
to reach in
to get the chicken,
you say grace.

494
00:41:57,265 --> 00:41:58,432
Come on.

495
00:42:00,435 --> 00:42:02,019
Dear heavenly...

496
00:42:02,604 --> 00:42:03,812
Spirit.

497
00:42:04,522 --> 00:42:06,273
Spirit. Thank you.

498
00:42:07,066 --> 00:42:08,775
Thank you
for providing us

499
00:42:08,860 --> 00:42:12,779
with a direct port
nitrous injection,

500
00:42:13,156 --> 00:42:17,075
four core intercoolers
and ball-bearing turbos,

501
00:42:17,160 --> 00:42:20,954
and titanium valve springs.
Thank you.

502
00:42:21,164 --> 00:42:22,956
- Amen.
- Amen, all right.

503
00:42:23,041 --> 00:42:25,000
Not bad.
Amen.

504
00:42:25,126 --> 00:42:27,336
He was praying
to the car gods, man.

505
00:42:29,214 --> 00:42:30,547
If he's
not the best...

506
00:42:30,632 --> 00:42:32,174
What do you want?

507
00:42:32,300 --> 00:42:33,926
Practice.
Thank you, girl.

508
00:42:34,010 --> 00:42:37,554
Look who it is.
Old Coyotes 'R' Us.

509
00:42:38,014 --> 00:42:40,307
I thought you weren't
hungry, pumpkin.

510
00:42:40,725 --> 00:42:41,975
You know, I gotta eat.

511
00:42:42,143 --> 00:42:43,393
He's always hungry.

512
00:42:43,937 --> 00:42:45,437
All right, sit down.

513
00:42:53,029 --> 00:42:54,488
How you doing, Mia?

514
00:42:58,243 --> 00:42:59,618
Here you go, dog.

515
00:43:06,167 --> 00:43:07,459
Hey, Jesse,
hand me that chicken, bro.

516
00:43:07,543 --> 00:43:08,752
Let's eat some grub, man.

517
00:43:08,836 --> 00:43:09,795
Yeah.

518
00:43:09,879 --> 00:43:10,921
Want some
of that chicken?

519
00:43:11,005 --> 00:43:12,839
Where'd you go?
Rent a movie or something?

520
00:43:19,639 --> 00:43:21,431
Need a hand
with anything else?

521
00:43:21,516 --> 00:43:24,601
No, I'm good.
You can go join the boys
watching the movie.

522
00:43:25,186 --> 00:43:27,604
Well, you see,
the cook doesn't clean
where I come from.

523
00:43:27,689 --> 00:43:29,481
Yeah? I'd like
to go there.

524
00:43:34,070 --> 00:43:35,821
You know, I think
we should go out sometime.

525
00:43:35,905 --> 00:43:38,198
No, I don't date
my brother's friends.

526
00:43:39,117 --> 00:43:40,575
Wow, that sucks.

527
00:43:40,702 --> 00:43:42,202
I guess I'll have
to kick his ass then.

528
00:43:42,287 --> 00:43:44,121
I'd love to see
that one.

529
00:43:44,205 --> 00:43:45,289
No, I would.

530
00:43:45,373 --> 00:43:47,582
I would pay to see
that one, actually.

531
00:44:01,264 --> 00:44:02,973
Wash my car
when you get done.

532
00:44:03,057 --> 00:44:04,182
What was that?

533
00:44:04,267 --> 00:44:06,768
No, Mia. I'm talking
to the punk.

534
00:44:07,812 --> 00:44:09,938
And wear your favorite dress,
'cause when you're done

535
00:44:10,023 --> 00:44:12,691
I'm putting you on the street
where you belong, cutie.

536
00:44:16,571 --> 00:44:18,530
Is this thing broken?

537
00:44:18,656 --> 00:44:20,407
What's wrong
with this thing?
V.

538
00:44:21,743 --> 00:44:25,495
V, what was that
Cuban restaurant
you wanted to take me to?

539
00:44:25,913 --> 00:44:27,998
The one with
the picadillo and the...

540
00:44:28,082 --> 00:44:29,416
Little red candles,
wooden table?

541
00:44:29,500 --> 00:44:30,876
Yeah, the plantain, too.
Yeah.

542
00:44:30,960 --> 00:44:32,836
Food all over the place.
What was it called?

543
00:44:32,920 --> 00:44:34,755
Cha Cha Cha.
Yeah, that's it.

544
00:44:34,839 --> 00:44:36,715
Yeah.
Right.

545
00:44:36,799 --> 00:44:38,592
Well, you can
take me there.

546
00:44:39,093 --> 00:44:41,470
Friday night at 10:00.
ls that good for you?

547
00:44:42,305 --> 00:44:44,097
Yeah, it's perfect.
Good.

548
00:44:50,855 --> 00:44:52,606
There's no popcorn?

549
00:44:52,774 --> 00:44:54,524
Make your own
goddamn popcorn!

550
00:45:08,623 --> 00:45:10,791
All right.
Now, that's valet parking.

551
00:45:15,463 --> 00:45:16,963
Harry. What's up, dog?

552
00:45:17,632 --> 00:45:19,174
Excellent, brother.
Come on in, man.

553
00:45:19,258 --> 00:45:20,258
Check it, it's yours.

554
00:45:20,343 --> 00:45:22,386
Damn. What do we got here?

555
00:45:23,888 --> 00:45:24,930
Hired some new help, huh?

556
00:45:25,014 --> 00:45:26,014
Don't even think about it.

557
00:45:26,099 --> 00:45:27,682
All right, like that?
What's up, Hector?

558
00:45:27,767 --> 00:45:28,767
What's up, Brian?
How you feeling, man?

559
00:45:28,851 --> 00:45:29,851
Pretty good.

560
00:45:29,936 --> 00:45:31,311
So, what's up?
What do you need?

561
00:45:31,396 --> 00:45:33,230
What's up, man?
I need you to hook me up.

562
00:45:33,773 --> 00:45:35,941
Three of everything.
I made a list.

563
00:45:37,026 --> 00:45:38,944
Why don't you look
that over.

564
00:45:39,362 --> 00:45:40,737
When do you need
this stuff by?

565
00:45:40,863 --> 00:45:42,239
Tomorrow, today, now.

566
00:45:42,323 --> 00:45:43,407
Right.

567
00:45:43,491 --> 00:45:45,951
Come on, man,
white boys work fast,
don't they?

568
00:45:48,496 --> 00:45:49,704
That's right.

569
00:45:52,625 --> 00:45:54,543
Hey, you said you need
three of all this stuff?

570
00:45:54,627 --> 00:45:56,336
Yeah,
three of everything.

571
00:45:56,838 --> 00:45:58,046
What do you think
about that?

572
00:45:58,172 --> 00:45:59,423
Check this out.

573
00:48:07,552 --> 00:48:09,052
He moans like a cop.

574
00:48:18,479 --> 00:48:20,105
Brian, this is one
of those times

575
00:48:20,189 --> 00:48:23,024
when you need
to be very clear
about what you say.

576
00:48:23,526 --> 00:48:24,818
Nod if you understand me.

577
00:48:25,486 --> 00:48:26,820
Nod!

578
00:48:28,698 --> 00:48:29,823
Sit up.

579
00:48:36,455 --> 00:48:38,832
Tell me what the hell
you're doing down here.

580
00:48:38,916 --> 00:48:41,293
Oh, shit. What I'm doing?

581
00:48:44,213 --> 00:48:45,380
Dom,

582
00:48:46,799 --> 00:48:48,008
I don't...

583
00:48:48,092 --> 00:48:50,010
I owe you a 10-second car.

584
00:48:51,679 --> 00:48:53,388
And what this is about,

585
00:48:54,056 --> 00:48:55,765
this is about Race Wars.

586
00:48:58,477 --> 00:49:02,314
I just went in there,
and Hector is
gonna be running

587
00:49:02,857 --> 00:49:05,191
three Honda Civics
with Spoon engines.

588
00:49:05,484 --> 00:49:08,278
And on top of that,
he just came into Harry's

589
00:49:08,362 --> 00:49:12,949
and he ordered three
T66 turbos, with NOS,

590
00:49:14,327 --> 00:49:16,369
and a MoTeC system exhaust.

591
00:49:19,790 --> 00:49:21,499
So, what are you saying?

592
00:49:22,835 --> 00:49:25,629
You're gonna go
around and check
everybody's shit out,

593
00:49:25,713 --> 00:49:27,547
one garage after another?

594
00:49:30,217 --> 00:49:31,259
Yeah.

595
00:49:34,430 --> 00:49:36,222
Because, Dom, you know,

596
00:49:37,141 --> 00:49:38,725
I can't lose again.

597
00:49:40,311 --> 00:49:41,936
He's a cop.

598
00:49:44,065 --> 00:49:45,357
He's a cop!

599
00:49:48,527 --> 00:49:49,653
You a cop?

600
00:49:56,243 --> 00:49:58,078
Let's go
for a little ride.

601
00:50:01,207 --> 00:50:02,332
Walk!

602
00:50:21,769 --> 00:50:23,812
All right, kid,
you stand watch.

603
00:50:54,468 --> 00:50:55,844
Yo, Dominic.

604
00:50:57,930 --> 00:50:59,389
There's no engines.

605
00:51:00,850 --> 00:51:02,142
What are they planning
on racing with?

606
00:51:02,268 --> 00:51:03,518
Hopes and dreams?

607
00:51:03,602 --> 00:51:05,895
I don't know,
but I know
they're sneaky as shit

608
00:51:05,980 --> 00:51:08,440
and they got enough money
to buy anything.

609
00:51:13,988 --> 00:51:15,071
What, Jess?

610
00:51:23,330 --> 00:51:25,915
Dom, we got a wolf pack.

611
00:51:26,000 --> 00:51:29,502
It's Johnny Tran,
and he's coming
your way really fast!

612
00:51:29,879 --> 00:51:32,338
All right, we got
company. Spilner!

613
00:51:58,532 --> 00:51:59,657
Come on.

614
00:52:00,534 --> 00:52:01,576
Move!

615
00:52:01,660 --> 00:52:03,328
Let me ask you
a question, Ted.

616
00:52:04,789 --> 00:52:06,748
Do you see
anything wrong here?

617
00:52:07,583 --> 00:52:08,666
No.

618
00:52:11,921 --> 00:52:13,046
We got no engines,
do we?

619
00:52:13,172 --> 00:52:14,297
No!

620
00:52:14,381 --> 00:52:16,925
Do we?
No!

621
00:52:18,719 --> 00:52:21,346
A couple
of Nissan SR20 motors
will pull a premium

622
00:52:21,430 --> 00:52:22,722
one week before
Race Wars, huh?

623
00:52:22,848 --> 00:52:24,140
Yeah, probably.

624
00:52:24,809 --> 00:52:28,061
You're a smart fence, Ted.
Maybe too smart.

625
00:52:29,438 --> 00:52:31,272
What are you
feeling, Lance?

626
00:52:32,817 --> 00:52:34,108
40 weight?

627
00:52:34,777 --> 00:52:36,110
50 weight?

628
00:52:37,196 --> 00:52:39,280
40 weight sounds nice.

629
00:52:54,588 --> 00:52:57,382
Where are they, Ted?
Where are they?

630
00:52:57,466 --> 00:52:59,259
Enough!
Where are they?

631
00:52:59,718 --> 00:53:01,261
They're in a warehouse.

632
00:53:01,428 --> 00:53:03,012
They're in
a warehouse, man!

633
00:53:19,613 --> 00:53:22,031
Ted, kiss my shoes?

634
00:53:34,795 --> 00:53:36,796
Let's go get
our engines.

635
00:53:37,798 --> 00:53:40,466
My superiors are
flying in from D.C.
day after tomorrow.

636
00:53:40,551 --> 00:53:41,926
I want something to show.

637
00:53:42,011 --> 00:53:43,386
Now, we have
a top echelon fence

638
00:53:43,470 --> 00:53:45,471
with a lube hose
in his mouth,
automatic weapons,

639
00:53:45,556 --> 00:53:48,391
a jacket full of priors
on every one
of these Asian punks,

640
00:53:48,475 --> 00:53:51,561
a garage full of DVD players
and generally
psychotic behavior.

641
00:53:51,645 --> 00:53:54,022
Now, tell me why
we shouldn't move
on Johnny Tran right now

642
00:53:54,106 --> 00:53:55,398
and see where we are
when the dust settles.

643
00:53:55,482 --> 00:53:57,066
Because all
we have is behavior.

644
00:53:57,151 --> 00:53:58,484
Just let me get
some hard evidence,

645
00:53:58,569 --> 00:54:00,528
because what we have now
is just circumstantial...

646
00:54:00,613 --> 00:54:02,405
What we have is
probable cause.

647
00:54:02,489 --> 00:54:03,907
And truckers
arming themselves

648
00:54:03,991 --> 00:54:06,367
for some good old-fashioned
vigilante mayhem.

649
00:54:06,452 --> 00:54:08,244
Tell us about Hector, Brian.

650
00:54:08,329 --> 00:54:09,454
Oh, Latinos
with spear guns.

651
00:54:09,580 --> 00:54:10,747
Give me a break.

652
00:54:10,831 --> 00:54:12,332
No, Hector's still
working on the engines
for the cars,

653
00:54:12,416 --> 00:54:14,000
but the tires don't match.

654
00:54:14,209 --> 00:54:16,628
Will someone just
give me a cigarette?
Get him a cigarette.

655
00:54:16,712 --> 00:54:18,212
Don't get him
a cigarette.

656
00:54:18,380 --> 00:54:19,923
I thought you quit.
Yeah, I did quit.

657
00:54:20,007 --> 00:54:21,841
Just give me a cigarette.
Get him a cigarette.

658
00:54:21,926 --> 00:54:23,009
No!

659
00:54:25,387 --> 00:54:27,138
Tell me about Toretto.

660
00:54:27,222 --> 00:54:29,891
Well, I told you,
I think he's too
controlled for this.

661
00:54:29,975 --> 00:54:30,975
I mean, what?

662
00:54:31,060 --> 00:54:32,393
Going suicidal
on semi-trucks?
No way.

663
00:54:32,478 --> 00:54:33,770
I mean, maybe
his buddy, Vince,

664
00:54:33,854 --> 00:54:35,063
but he's too stupid
to pull it off.

665
00:54:35,147 --> 00:54:37,273
I think the kid
sister's blurring
your vision.

666
00:54:37,858 --> 00:54:39,734
What did you say?
I don't blame you.

667
00:54:39,818 --> 00:54:42,487
I'd get off on her
surveillance photos,
too, buddy.

668
00:54:45,157 --> 00:54:46,616
Knock it off!

669
00:54:47,534 --> 00:54:49,953
What, are you going
native on me, Brian?

670
00:54:54,875 --> 00:54:56,960
Have you read
Toretto's file lately?

671
00:54:57,044 --> 00:54:58,127
Yeah, I memorized
that file.

672
00:54:58,212 --> 00:54:59,671
Yeah, well read it again.

673
00:54:59,755 --> 00:55:01,547
No, better still,
take a look at these.

674
00:55:03,968 --> 00:55:06,803
Remember I told
you about the guy
he nearly beat to death?

675
00:55:07,638 --> 00:55:11,224
Toretto did
this with a three-quarter
inch torque wrench.

676
00:55:11,517 --> 00:55:13,726
He's a model
of self-control.

677
00:55:16,355 --> 00:55:22,652
I need a few more days.

678
00:55:24,905 --> 00:55:27,824
Got a TR7 here
with a ball-bearing upgrade.

679
00:55:27,908 --> 00:55:29,867
What it's gonna do is,
it's gonna...

680
00:55:29,994 --> 00:55:31,953
It's gonna spool
up really quick.

681
00:55:32,037 --> 00:55:33,871
I got this set up
for 24...

682
00:55:33,956 --> 00:55:35,415
Yeah.

683
00:55:37,710 --> 00:55:39,669
So, you got
big plans tonight?

684
00:55:41,797 --> 00:55:43,673
Yeah, we're going
out to dinner.

685
00:55:45,718 --> 00:55:47,719
You break her heart,
I'll break your neck.

686
00:55:48,846 --> 00:55:50,263
That's not gonna happen.

687
00:55:55,602 --> 00:55:57,311
I wanna show
you something.

688
00:56:07,489 --> 00:56:08,614
Wow.

689
00:56:11,660 --> 00:56:13,244
Me and my dad built her.

690
00:56:14,204 --> 00:56:16,914
Nine hundred horses
of Detroit muscle.

691
00:56:17,750 --> 00:56:19,000
It's a beast.

692
00:56:19,793 --> 00:56:21,169
Know what
she ran in Palmdale?

693
00:56:21,295 --> 00:56:22,712
No. What did she run?

694
00:56:22,796 --> 00:56:24,505
Nine seconds flat.

695
00:56:25,883 --> 00:56:26,883
God.

696
00:56:26,967 --> 00:56:28,009
My dad was driving.

697
00:56:28,385 --> 00:56:32,555
So much torque,
the chassis twisted
coming off the line.

698
00:56:33,724 --> 00:56:35,933
Barely kept her
on the track.

699
00:56:36,393 --> 00:56:37,810
So, what's
your best time?

700
00:56:37,978 --> 00:56:39,395
I've never driven her.

701
00:56:39,480 --> 00:56:40,730
Why not?

702
00:56:43,317 --> 00:56:45,151
It scares
the shit out of me.

703
00:56:47,613 --> 00:56:49,113
That's my dad.

704
00:56:50,616 --> 00:56:52,992
He was coming up
in the pro stock car circuit.

705
00:56:53,494 --> 00:56:55,203
Last race of the season.

706
00:56:56,371 --> 00:57:00,792
A guy named Kenny Linder
came up from inside
on the final turn.

707
00:57:01,376 --> 00:57:04,837
He clipped his bumper
and put him into
the wall at 120.

708
00:57:08,050 --> 00:57:10,593
I watched
my dad burn to death.

709
00:57:12,930 --> 00:57:15,306
I remembered
hearing him scream.

710
00:57:18,268 --> 00:57:20,478
But the people
that were there said

711
00:57:20,604 --> 00:57:22,814
that he had died
before the tanks blew.

712
00:57:28,862 --> 00:57:31,531
They said it was me
who was screaming.

713
00:57:35,035 --> 00:57:37,662
I saw Linder
about a week later.

714
00:57:38,747 --> 00:57:40,414
I had a wrench.

715
00:57:41,708 --> 00:57:44,460
And I hit him,
and I didn't intend
to keep hitting him,

716
00:57:44,545 --> 00:57:47,380
but by the time I was done,
I couldn't lift my arm.

717
00:57:52,761 --> 00:57:55,096
He's a janitor
at a high school.

718
00:57:56,223 --> 00:57:58,850
Has to take the bus
to work every day.

719
00:57:59,893 --> 00:58:02,854
And they banned me
from the tracks for life.

720
00:58:08,277 --> 00:58:10,987
I live my life
a quarter mile at a time.

721
00:58:12,656 --> 00:58:15,491
Nothing else matters,
not the mortgage,
not the store,

722
00:58:15,576 --> 00:58:18,119
not my team
and all their bullshit.

723
00:58:19,746 --> 00:58:22,748
For those 10 seconds
or less

724
00:58:23,709 --> 00:58:24,959
I'm free.

725
00:58:45,772 --> 00:58:48,983
So, how is it, anyways,
that the gang came to be?

726
00:58:49,067 --> 00:58:50,318
- The what?
- The gang.

727
00:58:50,402 --> 00:58:51,402
The gang?

728
00:58:51,486 --> 00:58:52,862
No, they don't call
themselves a gang.

729
00:58:52,946 --> 00:58:54,113
Well, what do they
call themselves then?

730
00:58:54,198 --> 00:58:55,198
They're a team.

731
00:58:55,282 --> 00:58:56,741
They call themselves
a team.

732
00:58:56,825 --> 00:58:59,827
All right, so how is it
that the team came to be?

733
00:58:59,912 --> 00:59:01,954
Well, that's
a whole lot of history.

734
00:59:03,457 --> 00:59:04,457
Well, I've got time.

735
00:59:04,583 --> 00:59:05,541
Okay.

736
00:59:05,626 --> 00:59:07,877
Vince grew up
with my brother.

737
00:59:07,961 --> 00:59:11,297
Actually, he didn't
ever actually grow up,
as you can tell,

738
00:59:11,673 --> 00:59:13,716
but they were
friends as kids.

739
00:59:13,800 --> 00:59:16,093
And Letty, she just...
She lived down the street.

740
00:59:16,511 --> 00:59:17,970
Always into cars, though.

741
00:59:18,138 --> 00:59:19,555
Ever since she was
like 10 years old.

742
00:59:19,640 --> 00:59:23,351
So, naturally, you know,
my brother always
had her attention.

743
00:59:23,977 --> 00:59:25,728
And then she turned 16...

744
00:59:25,854 --> 00:59:27,647
And then she had
Dom's attention.

745
00:59:27,856 --> 00:59:30,983
Yeah. Yeah, it's funny
how that works, isn't it?

746
00:59:31,652 --> 00:59:32,777
Yeah.

747
00:59:36,156 --> 00:59:38,491
How is it that Jesse fits
into the whole thing?

748
00:59:38,575 --> 00:59:39,575
Jesse?

749
00:59:39,660 --> 00:59:42,578
Well, Jesse and Leon
just sort of
showed up one night

750
00:59:42,663 --> 00:59:44,288
and never ever left.

751
00:59:44,373 --> 00:59:46,749
Well, it's just the way
my brother is, though,
you know?

752
00:59:46,833 --> 00:59:48,334
Dom's like...

753
00:59:49,461 --> 00:59:51,420
He's like gravity.

754
00:59:52,214 --> 00:59:54,674
You know,
everything just
gets pulled to him.

755
00:59:56,343 --> 00:59:57,593
Even you.

756
00:59:58,136 --> 00:59:59,387
Mmm-mmm.

757
01:00:00,013 --> 01:00:02,515
No.

758
01:00:03,058 --> 01:00:05,810
The only thing that
pulled me in was you.

759
01:00:06,144 --> 01:00:08,562
Being friends
with your brother
is just a bonus.

760
01:00:11,692 --> 01:00:13,317
That's good. That's...

761
01:00:15,153 --> 01:00:18,572
It's good.
It's nice to come first
every once in a while.

762
01:00:22,244 --> 01:00:23,828
Want to go for a drive?

763
01:01:02,075 --> 01:01:03,075
Yeah.

764
01:01:03,243 --> 01:01:04,243
The hijackers
have hit again.

765
01:01:04,328 --> 01:01:05,661
Bilkins has made
his decision.

766
01:01:05,746 --> 01:01:09,248
We're gonna
move on Johnny Tran
and his guys at 1700 hours.

767
01:01:09,499 --> 01:01:11,167
Unless you say otherwise.

768
01:01:11,293 --> 01:01:13,002
If you agree,
just say yes.

769
01:01:14,046 --> 01:01:15,838
Yeah.
Who is that?

770
01:01:17,966 --> 01:01:19,967
It's just a wrong number.

771
01:01:24,765 --> 01:01:26,140
Hi.

772
01:04:12,224 --> 01:04:14,308
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah. I know, but...

773
01:04:14,684 --> 01:04:17,144
Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Yes, sir.

774
01:04:17,395 --> 01:04:18,771
Yeah, I got it.

775
01:04:23,360 --> 01:04:25,277
The DVD players were
purchased legally.

776
01:04:25,362 --> 01:04:26,779
All we've got on
Tran and company

777
01:04:26,863 --> 01:04:28,614
are a couple of
low-rent weapons charges

778
01:04:28,698 --> 01:04:31,033
and some outstanding
speeding tickets.

779
01:04:31,117 --> 01:04:32,201
So, they're out.

780
01:04:32,285 --> 01:04:33,953
Yeah. Father bailed
them out.

781
01:04:35,622 --> 01:04:37,039
Is this the kind
of intelligence

782
01:04:37,123 --> 01:04:38,874
I can expect from you,
O'Conner?

783
01:04:44,339 --> 01:04:45,631
You're gonna put
this on me?

784
01:04:45,715 --> 01:04:47,383
I can put it on
whoever I want to, kid.

785
01:04:47,467 --> 01:04:48,551
Perks of the job.

786
01:04:48,635 --> 01:04:50,219
No, there's no way
you're gonna
put this on me...

787
01:04:50,303 --> 01:04:51,387
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.

788
01:04:51,471 --> 01:04:52,471
Let me tell you.

789
01:04:52,556 --> 01:04:54,557
I don't care if
you have to put a gun
to someone's head

790
01:04:54,641 --> 01:04:56,517
and blow your cover
to smithereens.

791
01:04:56,601 --> 01:04:59,144
You've got 36 hours
to crack this bastard

792
01:04:59,229 --> 01:05:01,981
or you might
want to be thinking
about another career.

793
01:05:13,451 --> 01:05:14,910
It's Toretto, Brian.

794
01:05:14,995 --> 01:05:16,537
It always has been Toretto.

795
01:05:18,206 --> 01:05:20,124
Tran and Hector are...

796
01:05:20,500 --> 01:05:22,001
They're just fumes.

797
01:05:25,547 --> 01:05:27,214
Well, I know
you've been lying to me.

798
01:05:27,299 --> 01:05:29,800
My question is this,
have you been
lying to yourself

799
01:05:29,884 --> 01:05:31,802
because you can't
see past Mia?

800
01:05:34,598 --> 01:05:36,307
He won't go back
to prison.

801
01:05:37,642 --> 01:05:40,477
Well, that's a choice
he's going to have to make.

802
01:05:44,524 --> 01:05:47,026
There's all kinds
of family, Brian.

803
01:05:48,486 --> 01:05:51,363
And that's a choice
you're gonna have to make.

804
01:06:09,257 --> 01:06:11,300
You ready
for this, Jumpy?

805
01:06:13,762 --> 01:06:14,887
Yeah!

806
01:06:37,577 --> 01:06:40,579
Nice car.
What's the retail
on one of those?

807
01:06:40,914 --> 01:06:43,749
More than you can
afford, pal. Ferrari.

808
01:06:49,839 --> 01:06:51,215
Smoke him.

809
01:07:46,062 --> 01:07:47,688
So, what's wrong, Brian?

810
01:07:48,940 --> 01:07:50,816
Nothing, man, I'm fine.

811
01:07:51,151 --> 01:07:54,361
Come on. Obviously,
something's off.

812
01:07:54,988 --> 01:07:57,364
Look, I have my good days
and I have my bad days,

813
01:07:57,449 --> 01:07:58,866
just like anybody else.

814
01:07:59,242 --> 01:08:00,993
Brian, don't lose
that cool of yours.

815
01:08:01,077 --> 01:08:02,953
That's your meal ticket.

816
01:08:04,664 --> 01:08:07,583
My meal ticket?
What, I can't pay
for my own shrimp?

817
01:08:07,667 --> 01:08:09,293
I got the shrimp.

818
01:08:09,711 --> 01:08:12,421
No, see, that's one
thing about me, Dom,
you don't understand.

819
01:08:12,505 --> 01:08:14,339
I don't need handouts.
I don't take handouts.

820
01:08:14,424 --> 01:08:16,508
I earn my way,
every step.

821
01:08:16,885 --> 01:08:19,428
Just gotta make
a little something extra
on the side, like you.

822
01:08:19,512 --> 01:08:21,096
What do you mean,
like me?

823
01:08:21,556 --> 01:08:22,765
What's that supposed
to mean?

824
01:08:22,849 --> 01:08:24,183
That's what I mean.

825
01:08:24,601 --> 01:08:25,768
What does that
mean "like me"?

826
01:08:25,852 --> 01:08:27,186
Don't try...

827
01:08:27,729 --> 01:08:30,939
I'm not stupid, all right?
I know that there's
no way in hell

828
01:08:31,024 --> 01:08:33,734
you paid for all that shit
you got under the hood...

829
01:08:33,818 --> 01:08:36,069
I know there's no way in hell
you paid for all that shit

830
01:08:36,154 --> 01:08:37,988
that's under the hood
of those cars,

831
01:08:38,072 --> 01:08:40,032
by doing tune-ups
and selling groceries.

832
01:08:41,242 --> 01:08:44,161
Now, whatever it is
you're in on,
I want in on it, too.

833
01:09:07,101 --> 01:09:08,143
Well, what is this?

834
01:09:08,269 --> 01:09:09,311
Read it.

835
01:09:09,729 --> 01:09:10,896
What is this for?

836
01:09:11,064 --> 01:09:12,231
It's directions

837
01:09:14,400 --> 01:09:15,651
to Race Wars.

838
01:09:16,402 --> 01:09:18,028
We'll see how you do,

839
01:09:19,447 --> 01:09:20,739
then we'll talk.

840
01:10:07,120 --> 01:10:08,871
How's it going, bro?
What's up, man?

841
01:10:08,955 --> 01:10:10,289
Welcome to Race Wars.

842
01:10:10,456 --> 01:10:11,832
Great. Thanks a lot.

843
01:10:34,731 --> 01:10:36,231
Baby. Hey, baby.

844
01:10:38,026 --> 01:10:39,610
You should be
watching from the side.

845
01:10:39,694 --> 01:10:41,945
I wouldn't want
to get any exhaust
on that pretty face.

846
01:10:42,030 --> 01:10:43,989
How about you put your money
where your mouth is?

847
01:10:44,073 --> 01:10:46,241
Well, how about I race you
for that sweet little ass?

848
01:10:46,326 --> 01:10:48,911
You want ass,
why don't you hit
Hollywood Boulevard?

849
01:10:48,995 --> 01:10:52,164
You want an adrenaline rush,
it'll be two large.

850
01:10:52,248 --> 01:10:55,042
Right here. Right now.
What's it gonna be?

851
01:10:57,837 --> 01:10:59,171
You got it.

852
01:11:19,192 --> 01:11:21,026
Another one bites the dust

853
01:11:24,530 --> 01:11:27,032
Come on. What do you got?
What you got?

854
01:11:27,367 --> 01:11:28,617
See ya.

855
01:12:04,696 --> 01:12:06,029
Hey, Bri, what's up?

856
01:12:06,155 --> 01:12:07,531
Hey, what's up, Jesse?

857
01:12:08,241 --> 01:12:09,574
What do you have
in your hand?

858
01:12:09,659 --> 01:12:11,743
Throwing down
the pink slip,
just like you.

859
01:12:12,328 --> 01:12:13,578
The pink slip to what?
The Jetta?

860
01:12:13,705 --> 01:12:14,955
Yeah.

861
01:12:15,039 --> 01:12:16,581
You can't bet
your dad's car.

862
01:12:16,666 --> 01:12:18,917
It's all right.
I ain't losing.

863
01:12:19,002 --> 01:12:22,587
This fool is running
a Honda 2000. I'll win.

864
01:12:22,672 --> 01:12:24,756
That way me
and my dad can
roll together

865
01:12:24,841 --> 01:12:26,883
when he gets out
of prison. It's all good.

866
01:12:26,968 --> 01:12:29,177
Well, they're gonna throw him
right back in prison
after he kills you.

867
01:12:29,262 --> 01:12:30,721
Oh, shit. I'm up.

868
01:12:38,563 --> 01:12:40,022
You visualize the win.

869
01:12:40,440 --> 01:12:42,232
Hey, visualize
the win, Jesse.

870
01:12:42,358 --> 01:12:44,109
I'm serious.
You gotta listen
to me, man.

871
01:12:44,318 --> 01:12:45,527
Who are you racing?

872
01:12:50,408 --> 01:12:52,409
Jesse, don't do it.

873
01:12:52,618 --> 01:12:54,786
I bet you he's got
more than a $100,000
under the hood of that car.

874
01:12:54,871 --> 01:12:55,871
Uh-huh.

875
01:13:19,479 --> 01:13:21,229
Too soon, Junior.

876
01:13:24,400 --> 01:13:25,442
No!

877
01:13:28,654 --> 01:13:29,780
Shit!

878
01:13:30,281 --> 01:13:31,490
Oh, God!

879
01:13:42,085 --> 01:13:43,877
Yo! Heads up, bro.

880
01:13:43,961 --> 01:13:45,337
We got problems.
What?

881
01:13:45,421 --> 01:13:46,588
Jesse.

882
01:13:48,257 --> 01:13:49,966
Where's Jesse going?

883
01:13:50,093 --> 01:13:51,843
He just raced Tran
for slips.

884
01:13:52,053 --> 01:13:53,845
Oh, shit.

885
01:14:05,566 --> 01:14:06,942
Where's he going?

886
01:14:07,068 --> 01:14:08,485
He went to the car wash.

887
01:14:08,736 --> 01:14:10,612
Whatever. Go fetch my car.

888
01:14:11,280 --> 01:14:12,781
Go fetch your car?

889
01:14:14,283 --> 01:14:15,951
We're not on
your block any more.

890
01:14:16,035 --> 01:14:17,702
You better watch who
you talk to like that.

891
01:14:18,871 --> 01:14:20,288
Toretto!
Okay, watch it.

892
01:14:20,373 --> 01:14:21,623
Toretto!

893
01:14:23,292 --> 01:14:25,335
SWAT came into my house,

894
01:14:26,129 --> 01:14:30,298
disrespected my whole family
because somebody
narked me out.

895
01:14:31,050 --> 01:14:33,468
And you know what?
It was you!

896
01:14:35,805 --> 01:14:37,222
Come on!

897
01:14:42,228 --> 01:14:43,687
Go! Get him!

898
01:14:45,148 --> 01:14:46,148
Go!

899
01:14:46,232 --> 01:14:47,274
Let him go!

900
01:14:56,117 --> 01:14:57,325
Dom!

901
01:14:57,827 --> 01:15:00,412
Get off of him!
Get off of him!

902
01:15:06,919 --> 01:15:08,211
You're gonna go!

903
01:15:09,338 --> 01:15:11,214
- Dom, chill out, man!
- Come on! Let's go!

904
01:15:11,299 --> 01:15:13,258
I never narked
on nobody!

905
01:15:13,384 --> 01:15:15,343
I never narked
on nobody!

906
01:15:16,846 --> 01:15:18,138
Let's go!

907
01:15:50,421 --> 01:15:51,504
Mia!

908
01:15:54,342 --> 01:15:55,425
Mia.

909
01:16:00,014 --> 01:16:02,849
I have respected you
and I haven't said shit.

910
01:16:02,934 --> 01:16:04,559
And now I'm asking you
not to go.

911
01:16:04,644 --> 01:16:06,186
Mia, I'm doing this
for both of us.

912
01:16:06,270 --> 01:16:07,604
No, don't give me
that crap.

913
01:16:07,730 --> 01:16:09,064
You're doing this
for you.

914
01:16:09,148 --> 01:16:11,024
Why are you insisting
on doing this?

915
01:16:11,108 --> 01:16:12,943
Dom, please, just don't.

916
01:16:25,373 --> 01:16:26,581
Mia,
what's going on?

917
01:16:26,666 --> 01:16:27,874
What?

918
01:16:27,959 --> 01:16:29,167
You know what
I'm talking about.

919
01:16:29,293 --> 01:16:30,460
No, I don't, Brian.

920
01:16:30,544 --> 01:16:32,087
Oh, so what?
You always have tears

921
01:16:32,171 --> 01:16:33,713
in your eyes when
Dom drives away?

922
01:16:33,798 --> 01:16:35,382
What is the matter
with you?

923
01:16:35,466 --> 01:16:36,508
Come on. What's
your brother racing off

924
01:16:36,592 --> 01:16:37,926
in the middle
of the night for?

925
01:16:38,010 --> 01:16:39,010
I'm talking
about the trucks.

926
01:16:39,095 --> 01:16:40,095
You know
about the trucks?

927
01:16:40,179 --> 01:16:42,847
No, Brian!
What trucks?
Jesus Christ.

928
01:16:43,641 --> 01:16:45,392
What?
Listen to me.

929
01:16:46,686 --> 01:16:48,103
Mia, I'm a cop.

930
01:16:49,188 --> 01:16:50,772
What are you
talking about, Brian?

931
01:16:50,856 --> 01:16:52,190
What is this?

932
01:16:52,275 --> 01:16:55,360
Ever since
the first time I met you,
I've been undercover.

933
01:16:56,946 --> 01:16:58,280
I'm a cop.

934
01:17:02,952 --> 01:17:04,536
Oh, you bastard.

935
01:17:07,790 --> 01:17:09,207
You bastard.

936
01:17:11,460 --> 01:17:13,336
Mia.
Get off of me, Brian!

937
01:17:13,421 --> 01:17:15,088
Mia! Listen to me!

938
01:17:16,382 --> 01:17:18,925
Everything I ever said
I felt about you was real.

939
01:17:19,010 --> 01:17:20,218
I swear to God.

940
01:17:20,303 --> 01:17:21,469
You have
to believe me, Mia.

941
01:17:21,554 --> 01:17:23,221
But right now
this isn't about
you and me.

942
01:17:23,306 --> 01:17:24,472
Your brother's out there,

943
01:17:24,557 --> 01:17:26,850
he's about to pull
a job and we're
running out of time.

944
01:17:26,934 --> 01:17:29,102
Those truckers,
they're not laying down
any more, you know.

945
01:17:29,186 --> 01:17:30,812
Maybe they'll make
it through tonight,

946
01:17:30,896 --> 01:17:32,772
but every single
law enforcement agency
in California's

947
01:17:32,857 --> 01:17:34,316
coming down on them.

948
01:17:34,400 --> 01:17:35,608
If you don't want
anything to happen

949
01:17:35,693 --> 01:17:37,819
to your brother,
to Letty, to Leon,
to Vince,

950
01:17:37,903 --> 01:17:39,487
you have to just get
in that car with me
right now.

951
01:17:39,572 --> 01:17:41,156
You have to help me.

952
01:17:42,241 --> 01:17:45,618
Mia, you are the only person
that can help me right now.

953
01:17:46,370 --> 01:17:49,372
Please, Mia.
Please help me.

954
01:18:01,260 --> 01:18:04,012
Civics are stashed
somewhere outside
of Thermal.

955
01:18:04,263 --> 01:18:06,014
And they wouldn't
double back.

956
01:18:06,098 --> 01:18:07,932
And Highway 10
is just way too
well patrolled.

957
01:18:08,017 --> 01:18:09,434
So, what does that
leave us with then?

958
01:18:09,518 --> 01:18:10,977
That leaves us
with all this.

959
01:18:19,820 --> 01:18:20,820
Nextel.

960
01:18:20,905 --> 01:18:22,781
Yeah, this is
Officer Brian O'Conner.

961
01:18:22,865 --> 01:18:25,492
Serial number 34762.

962
01:18:25,576 --> 01:18:27,202
I need a cell phone trace.

963
01:18:27,286 --> 01:18:29,037
Okay. What's the cell number?

964
01:18:29,121 --> 01:18:31,081
Mia, what's
his cell phone number?

965
01:18:32,458 --> 01:18:33,541
Come on, Mia.

966
01:18:33,626 --> 01:18:36,252
She needs Dom's
cell phone number now.

967
01:18:39,131 --> 01:18:43,259
3235556439.

968
01:18:44,720 --> 01:18:46,054
Thank you.

969
01:18:46,639 --> 01:18:47,931
Yeah, you get that?

970
01:19:13,666 --> 01:19:15,333
All right,
we're one man short.

971
01:19:15,418 --> 01:19:17,502
Letty, I need you
on the left side.

972
01:19:19,672 --> 01:19:21,923
Your sister's
right about this one.

973
01:19:22,007 --> 01:19:23,174
This don't feel good.

974
01:19:23,259 --> 01:19:24,509
Don't do that.

975
01:19:26,178 --> 01:19:28,138
Something's wrong.
Stop.

976
01:19:28,222 --> 01:19:30,432
We shouldn't be
doing this without Jesse.

977
01:19:31,517 --> 01:19:32,934
Look, this is
the mother lode.

978
01:19:33,060 --> 01:19:34,477
We've been on this
for three months.

979
01:19:34,562 --> 01:19:37,063
After this, it's a long
vacation for everyone.

980
01:19:37,148 --> 01:19:38,148
Let's go.

981
01:19:38,232 --> 01:19:39,274
I hope so.

982
01:19:42,695 --> 01:19:45,613
Listen, the other night
I had a dream

983
01:19:46,240 --> 01:19:48,658
that you and I were
on a beach in Mexico.

984
01:19:49,285 --> 01:19:51,077
Oh, really?
Really.

985
01:19:54,373 --> 01:19:56,207
Come on.
Let's make this happen.

986
01:19:59,795 --> 01:20:02,464
Leon, keep on
those scanners.

987
01:20:02,548 --> 01:20:03,882
Copy that.

988
01:20:07,636 --> 01:20:09,429
All right, let's go.

989
01:20:19,565 --> 01:20:20,607
Yeah.

990
01:20:20,691 --> 01:20:23,485
Okay,
we traced the number
to the northbound 86.

991
01:20:23,569 --> 01:20:25,612
Mile 114 outside Coachella.

992
01:20:25,696 --> 01:20:27,739
We'll keep
the trace open, officer.

993
01:20:28,449 --> 01:20:30,074
Let me see this.

994
01:20:34,413 --> 01:20:36,831
All right, I think
we're about 40 miles away.

995
01:20:37,208 --> 01:20:38,875
What are you gonna do?

996
01:20:40,085 --> 01:20:41,711
What are you gonna do?

997
01:21:14,620 --> 01:21:16,454
Okay! Go time!

998
01:21:32,221 --> 01:21:33,221
We're all good, man.

999
01:21:33,305 --> 01:21:35,598
I got nothing
on the scanners.
Keep going.

1000
01:21:50,322 --> 01:21:51,489
Vince!

1001
01:21:52,491 --> 01:21:54,492
Vince, don't!
Get back in!

1002
01:21:56,203 --> 01:21:57,412
Vince!

1003
01:22:03,043 --> 01:22:04,586
He's got
a damn shotgun! Leon!

1004
01:22:04,670 --> 01:22:06,963
Back off! Back off!
Get him off of there!

1005
01:22:21,562 --> 01:22:23,187
Get me off this thing!

1006
01:22:23,689 --> 01:22:24,814
Pull up.

1007
01:22:25,316 --> 01:22:27,859
Unhook! Unhook yourself!

1008
01:22:28,235 --> 01:22:29,402
Do it!

1009
01:22:29,695 --> 01:22:31,446
Do it!
I can't get...

1010
01:22:31,530 --> 01:22:33,072
You can do it!

1011
01:22:34,033 --> 01:22:35,617
Come on, Vince!

1012
01:22:42,958 --> 01:22:45,501
Dom! I'm pulling up
to distract him!

1013
01:22:53,177 --> 01:22:54,636
Come on, boy!

1014
01:22:55,387 --> 01:22:57,388
Shot doesn't get
better than this.

1015
01:23:02,686 --> 01:23:04,395
You son of a bitch!

1016
01:23:08,525 --> 01:23:09,734
Take me off here!

1017
01:23:09,902 --> 01:23:11,110
I'm gonna unhook the wire!

1018
01:23:11,195 --> 01:23:12,320
Try it again!

1019
01:23:12,404 --> 01:23:15,657
One, two, three!

1020
01:23:26,960 --> 01:23:29,587
Vince, unhook yourself!

1021
01:23:31,048 --> 01:23:33,049
I can't get my arm free!
My arm!

1022
01:23:33,133 --> 01:23:34,342
Vince, grab my hand.

1023
01:23:34,426 --> 01:23:35,718
My arm!

1024
01:23:35,844 --> 01:23:37,136
Listen, give me
your hand!

1025
01:23:37,721 --> 01:23:40,139
I'm gonna pull you
off the rig!

1026
01:23:50,234 --> 01:23:51,734
Dominic!

1027
01:23:55,781 --> 01:23:57,657
Dominic!
Shit!

1028
01:24:01,453 --> 01:24:02,453
Dominic!

1029
01:24:02,579 --> 01:24:03,621
Hang on!

1030
01:24:03,997 --> 01:24:05,915
Dom, move out of the way!

1031
01:24:05,999 --> 01:24:07,458
I'm coming to get him!

1032
01:24:32,234 --> 01:24:33,443
Letty!

1033
01:24:34,278 --> 01:24:35,737
Leon!
Yo!

1034
01:24:35,821 --> 01:24:37,822
Go back for Letty!
Get her out of there!

1035
01:24:37,906 --> 01:24:39,490
I'm on it! Go!

1036
01:24:48,667 --> 01:24:50,835
I've got her!
You get Vince
off that truck!

1037
01:24:56,759 --> 01:24:58,885
Letty! Come on, baby.

1038
01:24:59,178 --> 01:25:01,929
Letty. You okay?
Oh, shit.

1039
01:25:02,014 --> 01:25:03,431
Come on, girl,
you all right?

1040
01:25:03,557 --> 01:25:04,974
Come on, let me
look at you.

1041
01:25:05,058 --> 01:25:07,101
Come on.
We got to go.
Let's go.

1042
01:25:20,741 --> 01:25:22,325
Come on, Vince!

1043
01:25:27,080 --> 01:25:28,372
Dominic!
Vince!

1044
01:25:50,729 --> 01:25:51,854
Here, take the wheel.

1045
01:25:51,980 --> 01:25:53,105
What do you mean,
take the wheel?

1046
01:25:53,190 --> 01:25:55,441
Take the wheel!
Put your foot on the gas!

1047
01:25:55,526 --> 01:25:57,318
I'm gonna get him.
Put your foot on the gas!

1048
01:25:57,402 --> 01:25:58,569
Okay! Okay!

1049
01:26:02,282 --> 01:26:03,741
Come on,
keep it steady!

1050
01:26:04,785 --> 01:26:06,285
I got it!

1051
01:26:07,287 --> 01:26:08,538
All right, hold on, Vince!

1052
01:26:08,664 --> 01:26:09,914
Okay!

1053
01:26:10,207 --> 01:26:11,499
Hey, he's having
a hard time holding on!

1054
01:26:11,625 --> 01:26:12,959
Get me a little closer!

1055
01:26:13,043 --> 01:26:14,210
All right!

1056
01:26:14,711 --> 01:26:15,795
Closer!

1057
01:26:15,921 --> 01:26:17,088
I'm moving in!

1058
01:26:17,506 --> 01:26:19,131
Hold it right there!

1059
01:26:20,342 --> 01:26:21,425
No!

1060
01:26:23,011 --> 01:26:25,763
Vince! You got to hang
in here with me right now!

1061
01:26:25,848 --> 01:26:26,931
We're gonna get you
off this thing!

1062
01:26:27,057 --> 01:26:28,099
Give me your arm!

1063
01:26:28,183 --> 01:26:30,226
Vince, look at me!
Don't let go!

1064
01:26:34,231 --> 01:26:36,941
Come on, Vince!
Throw this arm around me!

1065
01:26:37,901 --> 01:26:39,694
Vince, don't let go!

1066
01:26:44,032 --> 01:26:45,950
Come on, Mia, get closer!

1067
01:26:51,623 --> 01:26:53,040
Mia, get closer! Come on!

1068
01:26:53,166 --> 01:26:54,625
Come on, Vince.
Here we go!

1069
01:27:21,987 --> 01:27:24,405
Brian!
Oh, shit.

1070
01:27:28,827 --> 01:27:31,662
It's gonna be okay, Letty.
I love you.

1071
01:27:35,334 --> 01:27:36,667
Watch her.
Yeah, I got her.

1072
01:27:38,003 --> 01:27:40,212
Come on, Vince!
Hang in there! Come on!

1073
01:27:44,635 --> 01:27:47,136
If we don't get
him to an ambulance
in 10 minutes, he's dead.

1074
01:27:47,220 --> 01:27:48,471
Hold this.
Hold the pressure.
Just like that.

1075
01:27:48,555 --> 01:27:49,555
I got it.

1076
01:27:49,640 --> 01:27:50,640
Don't let go.
Hold his arm up.

1077
01:27:50,724 --> 01:27:51,724
Vince.

1078
01:27:56,647 --> 01:27:59,523
Yeah. Yeah, this is
Officer Brian O'Conner.

1079
01:28:00,400 --> 01:28:02,318
I'm off-duty LAPD.

1080
01:28:02,444 --> 01:28:04,362
I need a Life Flight
roll out right away.

1081
01:28:06,031 --> 01:28:09,742
My 20 is a Highway 86,
mile marker 147.

1082
01:28:10,827 --> 01:28:14,038
I got one trauma victim,
about 24 years of age.

1083
01:28:14,247 --> 01:28:16,499
Six foot, maybe 200 pounds.

1084
01:28:16,625 --> 01:28:19,001
He's got a real
deep laceration
to his right arm,

1085
01:28:19,086 --> 01:28:20,461
with arterial bleeding.

1086
01:28:20,545 --> 01:28:22,755
And he's got
a shotgun wound,

1087
01:28:22,839 --> 01:28:24,840
close range
to his left flank.

1088
01:28:25,342 --> 01:28:28,260
Yeah. Yeah,
and he's going into shock!

1089
01:30:08,737 --> 01:30:10,821
Dom, put the gun
down now!

1090
01:30:13,325 --> 01:30:15,242
Move your car.
No. Bullshit!

1091
01:30:15,327 --> 01:30:17,661
Put it down now!
No more running!

1092
01:30:17,746 --> 01:30:19,663
I'm not running!

1093
01:30:22,459 --> 01:30:23,584
Where's Leon and Letty?

1094
01:30:23,668 --> 01:30:24,877
They're long gone!

1095
01:30:25,003 --> 01:30:28,047
Then it's over.
I didn't call the police
but don't push me!

1096
01:30:28,131 --> 01:30:29,965
Put the gun down!
I swear to God...

1097
01:30:30,050 --> 01:30:32,426
You are the cop!
You're a cop!

1098
01:30:34,179 --> 01:30:37,181
Brian, I gotta find
Jesse before they do!

1099
01:30:37,599 --> 01:30:38,891
I'm all the kid's got.

1100
01:30:38,975 --> 01:30:40,184
I'll call in the plates.

1101
01:30:40,560 --> 01:30:43,729
PD will pick him up
way before Johnny
even gets near him.

1102
01:30:44,147 --> 01:30:45,231
Move your car.

1103
01:30:45,315 --> 01:30:47,900
Dom, stop it!
It's over! Please!

1104
01:30:48,026 --> 01:30:49,693
Mia, stay out of it!

1105
01:30:50,112 --> 01:30:51,529
Move the...

1106
01:30:55,283 --> 01:30:58,202
Dominic, I am so sorry!

1107
01:30:58,745 --> 01:31:01,163
I don't know
what I'm doing, Dom!

1108
01:31:01,248 --> 01:31:03,541
I'm so scared right now!

1109
01:31:03,625 --> 01:31:05,459
I don't know
what's going on!

1110
01:31:05,544 --> 01:31:08,295
Jess! What were
you thinking, man?

1111
01:31:08,380 --> 01:31:10,881
I don't know!
I panicked! I'm sorry!

1112
01:31:11,049 --> 01:31:12,091
I'm scared!

1113
01:31:12,175 --> 01:31:13,592
I don't know
what I'm doing!

1114
01:31:13,718 --> 01:31:15,219
Will you please help me?

1115
01:31:20,392 --> 01:31:21,517
Dom!

1116
01:31:38,034 --> 01:31:39,201
Jesse!

1117
01:31:40,829 --> 01:31:43,539
Jesse! No, Jesse!

1118
01:31:58,346 --> 01:31:59,889
No. Dom, no!

1119
01:34:55,273 --> 01:34:57,941
Call 911 . You, call 911!

1120
01:35:33,269 --> 01:35:35,979
I used to drag here
back in high school.

1121
01:35:36,773 --> 01:35:38,148
That rail road
crossing up there

1122
01:35:38,233 --> 01:35:40,818
is exactly a quarter
mile away from here.

1123
01:35:42,112 --> 01:35:44,321
On green,
I'm going for it.

1124
01:38:08,675 --> 01:38:09,758
Dom!

1125
01:38:19,143 --> 01:38:21,395
That's not what
I had in mind.

1126
01:39:07,817 --> 01:39:09,693
You know what you're doing?

1127
01:39:10,361 --> 01:39:12,404
I owe you a 10-second car.

1128
01:46:26,255 --> 01:46:28,965
I live my life
a quarter mile at a time.

1129
01:46:30,634 --> 01:46:32,469
Nothing else matters.

1130
01:46:33,512 --> 01:46:35,889
For those 10 seconds
or less

1131
01:46:37,224 --> 01:46:38,308
I'm free.