My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats
and I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
Twelve markers, twelve metas.
They identified the target
sooner than we planned.
Perhaps.
There's nothing within miles of here
capable of even creating dark matter.
There was three weeks ago.
This is where I came
out of the Speed Force.
And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
You think the guy
behind the Samurai robots...
Samuroid.
He wanted us to create
a busload of metas.
I think it's all connected.
Hello, gorgeous.
You ready to get your schmoopy on?
Joe, I'm pregnant.
Look, I was thinking.
No, no, less thinking, more kissing.
Okay, but hold on a minute.
This thing we got going on,
this is real good.
- It's okay.
- What?
I'm just kidding, it's better than okay.
Yeah, that's right,
it's better than okay.
And because of that, I think
we're at a place in our relationship
where the guy says to his girl,
those three magic words.
What three words?
What's your name?
Um... Oh.
Well, that is technically four words.
Actually, technically, it's three words
'cause contractions are one word,
it's how grammar works.
That's not the point, though.
What's your name?
Gypsy. My name is Gypsy.
For real? You were born and somebody
was like, "I'm gonna name you Gypsy"?
Gypsy is what I like to be called.
It is mysterious and it's moody.
Hmm. Moody's right.
All right.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom,
and when I get back,
you better stop asking me my real name.
And be wearing less clothes.
I don't need to know your name.
This girl
She 'bout to rock your world
You're a dead man.
Those were collectibles!
Who are you?
Daddy!
Pleased to meet you, sir.
Is he gonna put me down?
You know, some of you may not realize,
but before I was mayor,
I was a cop in this very precinct.
And it's because of these men and women,
every family in Central City
can sleep comfortably at night.
What's happening?
Mayor Bellows is on his
reelection campaign.
...Detective Joe West.
Keep up the good work.
What do you say, Joe?
I'll do that.
And that's why he's not a politician.
I hate that.
Yeah? How about running against him?
Can you picture yourself
shaking hands and kissing babies?
What?
- Ain't nobody talking about babies.
- I was...
You said you had a lead
on this meta bus situation.
Yeah, I do.
Bellow for Bellows!
You took the photos down
from your mother's case.
Yeah, well, the case was solved.
This one isn't.
We got these two, Kilg%re and Hazard.
But that still leaves 10 meta-humans
that were created
when I came out of the Speed Force.
How hard can it be to track down
ten bus passengers?
Well, according to
the Department of Transportation,
over 900 people rode that bus that day.
What about the bus driver?
That's where things
get more interesting.
He's dead. Drowned. In his own bathtub.
That's not too suspicious.
Harry said it was all connected,
I think he's right.
The Samuroid pushing you guys
to bring me back,
and me not coming out at the place
that you thought I would,
the bus being at the exact right place
to be hit by dark matter...
- It was planned.
- Yeah, by somebody smart.
- We're pretty smart.
- Well, I think so.
Okay, let's look closer
into the bus driver's death,
it may give us a lead.
I'll have Iris pull up the autopsy
report from the coroner's office.
Sounds good.
What?
I don't know, this morning,
you're like...
Glowing.
What do you mean, "glowing"?
I just mean, like,
you got like a warmth about you,
like a Lite-Brite.
There's no warmth, no glow,
and I ain't no damn Lite-Brite.
You're wasting time. S.T.A.R. Labs.
Glowing and irritable.
How's Cecile?
Fine. Same. I mean, nothing's changed.
If something changes, I'll let you know.
All right.
This facility is poorly guarded.
Clearly.
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
Okay, power down, Buckaroo.
Good. You're both here.
Cisco, who is this?
This is Breacher, AKA Gypsy's father.
Oh.
Yeah, I can see the resemblance.
There is no resemblance.
So, you know how Gypsy's kind of
a big deal collector on Earth-19?
Well, her boss is her dad.
Who decided to pay us
a surprise visit at the perfect time,
which is why I decided
to show him around,
where I work, you know.
I'm Barry Allen.
Cisco's personal assistant.
His what?
And he is the best personal assistant
I've ever had,
stays late, starts early.
- One day, I'll be working for him.
- What are you doing?
I wanted to impress him,
and now, I can't stop.
Joe West.
A fellow law man.
You, I can respect.
And Harry Wells, back there.
You look like someone I once sent
my daughter to kill.
I get that a lot.
I thought maybe someone would
want to give him the old look-see.
Great idea, Allen, Detective West,
why don't you give Gypsy's father here
the nickel tour of the facilities?
Joe.
I've had to pee for, like, three hours.
- What is wrong with you?
- Have you seen his face.
The guy's killed people with that face.
I'm not even joking.
Gypsy said that literally happened.
- You want his approval, right?
- Yes, I want his approval.
He's my girlfriend's father.
Of course, Cisco, listen,
you're a fine upstanding, smart,
well-groomed young man.
Any father would be happy to have
you date his daughter except me.
Can't date my daughter, right?
Can't date Jesse, Jesse's off-limits.
Went for the compliment,
didn't stick the landing.
Just take him for coffee, okay?
Go for coffee,
get to know him a little bit better.
I bet
that you'll be pleasantly surprised
at how much you have in common, right?
You both have the same powers,
you're breachers,
you have ridiculous hair,
he has ridiculous hair.
- Okay, but...
- And you both love Gypsy.
Are you actually giving me
decent relationship advice right now?
I am. You'll be fine.
I don't want to be here anymore.
And we're leaving.
- Help me.
- Have fun storming the castle.
Why is the scariest person
I have ever seen roaming our halls?
Cisco.
Okay, so, I've got the coroner's report
for the death of the bus driver,
but it doesn't seem like
there's any signs of foul play.
Aside for him being the one guy
that could've told us
who else was on that bus.
They logged his personal effects,
let's see.
Credit cards, cash, receipts. Um...
Wait, go back.
- Ralph Dibny.
- I'll be damned.
Who is Ralph Dibny?
He used to be a cop.
Dirty cop. Got kicked off the force.
- For what?
- It's a long story.
- That's him.
- Oh.
He's handsome in a square-jawed,
Oliver Queen kind of way.
For real?
Babe, you know
I've only got eyes for you.
The IOU is dated the same day
that I came out of the Speed Force.
You think Dibny was on the bus that day?
Maybe he's a meta-human now?
Let's pay him a visit.
Hey, you seem... Something.
What's up with you and this Ralph guy?
It's like Joe said, it's a long story.
- Oliver Queen is hot.
- Amen and hallelujah.
I promised there wasn't
a single case I couldn't crack.
And a promise made is a promise kept.
Dibny detects.
Your husband didn't die
in that plane crash, Mrs. Broome.
He didn't? Then where is he?
Well, that brings us
to the difficult part.
Turns out he got remarried,
and moved to Minnesota.
Has two kids now, twins.
Twins in the Twin Cities.
Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey...
No, don't... Don't cry for that jerk.
He doesn't deserve it.
The sun still shines.
The birds, they still chirp.
Chirp, chirp.
Mrs. Broome,
you are a very attractive woman,
and you will find someone else.
Someone who will hold you,
someone who will wipe away those tears.
Do you like shrimp?
This is definitely his place.
Reconsidered, huh?
- Ralph.
- Joe West.
Barry Allen. Been a long time, rookie.
Well, I'm not a rookie anymore, Dibny.
You look healthy.
Yeah. Got the spare tire
out of the trunk. It happens.
Might even happen to you, too,
one day, Slim Jim.
So, what brings you boys
to Casa de Dibny?
Were you on the 405 bus
four weeks ago, around noon?
That's a very specific question.
We found your IOU
from the deceased
bus drivers' personal effects.
"Deceased"?
Hey. That's one less "U" I owe.
What's it to you two?
It's a simple question,
why don't you just answer it?
You walk into my office after
five years like nothing ever happened,
and ask me for a favor?
I smell a mystery.
It's not a favor, it's information.
And how much is this information worth?
Are you shaking us down?
I know something you don't.
And you need to know it badly.
Otherwise, you'd never
swallow your pride and face me
after what you did.
After what I did?
Ralph.
The people on that bus were exposed
to a dangerous substance.
"Dangerous"?
Dangerous like what? Like... Ebola?
Were you on the bus?
No.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey, I heard you shacked up
with that hot DA. She got a sister?
Okay.
Good luck. All the best.
So, what's it worth?
Ah, crap.
You don't wanna do this!
I know what you want!
Let's talk about this! Put me down!
Don't put me down! Don't put me down!
- That guy hasn't changed a bit.
- You really expect him to?
Guess he was on that bus.
Hey, guys, what the hell?
Yeah, yeah...
What's happened to me?
- Breathe, okay?
- I'm breathing.
Clearly, this guy is a bus meta.
This is interesting. The dark matter
polymerized Dibny's cells.
What the hell is dark matter
and why is it in my cells?
You're saying the walls of every cell
in his body have elasticized?
It seems they formed an unbreakable
bond at an atomic level,
and now, you can stretch these cells
and stretch these cells.
- Like Silly Putty.
- I'm Silly Putty?
- No.
- Kind of.
- I'm Silly Putty?
Ralph, who were the guys on the roof?
Is it really the issue right now?
Look at me!
Allen, you and your S.T.A.R. Labs
nerds better put me back together.
- We're trying to help you.
- You're not trying to help me.
Shut up! Oh, my God!
- Give him a second!
- Look at him!
- You're lucky, man. I would...
- Try me. Come on!
You can do this later,
I just need a sample of blood.
Oh... Is that my face?
Four years seeing this stuff,
I finally puked.
Can I plug in?
Daddy.
I know you love me and I love you.
I really like Cisco,
and I need you two to get along.
So, do you think
that you can try to do that?
I'll do anything for you, petal.
Ah! Three coffees.
How about you, huh?
Ready for some hot java?
We don't have coffee on my Earth.
Crops were destroyed,
my world was attacked, invaded,
by the worst,
most evil creatures in the multi-verse.
I'll never drink coffee again.
- Two for me.
- It's okay.
Daddy, why don't I get you a tea?
- Like a relaxing tea?
- Yeah.
- Please. Thanks.
- Okay.
Ah...
I know from a friend
who is also a father,
how important his daughter is to him
and I just wanted to let you know
how important your daughter is to me.
And that after you and I
get to know each other a little,
maybe we might find that...
We're not so different.
I'm going to hunt you.
You're not worthy of her.
Isn't that for her to decide?
Ten.
Also, I could've sworn you said
you were gonna hunt me.
What, like a deer?
I've hunted some of the worst
breach criminals in history.
Maaldor, the Darklord,
Solumga of the Sheeda,
the Sand People of Quarrm.
You will be easy prey.
Nine.
Listen, I have tried
to be polite with you,
but this is going a little too far.
I get that you're overprotective.
- Eight.
- Are you counting?
In the next 24 hours,
I will be hunting you
throughout this city.
We'll not use our powers,
but when it's over,
my daughter will be free of you.
Seven.
Do you do this with all her boyfriends?
I hunted her last one, yes.
Where is he now?
- I don't know.
- He got away.
I don't know where you go when you die.
- Five.
- You just skipped six.
I know. Four.
And don't try to breach.
I'll know it if you do.
You can't hide from me.
So, if I were you...
I would start running.
Cisky.
Three, two, one.
Damn. He's hunting him.
I finally calmed him down.
It's amazing what 50 milligrams
of Lorazepam can do
when you get it in aerosol form.
Is there anything you can do
to put him back together?
Please, my stomach can't take much more.
I think I could stabilize his cells
if I had a sample of his DNA
from prior to when he was exposed
to the dark matter on the bus.
Why?
So, he can go out and start hurting
people like our other friends here?
I think we should lock him up
in the Pipeline.
He hasn't done anything.
Yet.
Trust me, I know this guy.
He's a bad guy.
Barry, I took an oath to help people.
I'm a doctor. I can't just
leave him in there like spaghetti.
"Villains"?
Yeah.
Every person that was on that bus
is now a thousand times
more dangerous than they were before.
Dibny included.
- What if he's changed?
- People don't change.
I did. When I became Killer Frost,
you still believed in me.
You're a good person.
He's...
Not.
Barry, how about you and I
go to Dibny's office,
find a DNA sample for Caitlin?
Dad, you go back to CCPD,
see what you can dig up on Dibny.
Yes, boss.
Looks like someone tossed this place.
Yeah.
Probably the same guys
that hung Dibny off the roof.
Why do you think?
I don't know, guy like that,
probably has a long list of people
that want to toss him off rooftops.
Why do you want to?
No, seriously.
What happened between the two of you?
It was one of my first cases
when I was a junior CSI.
Dibny was the lead detective.
What case?
A woman named Judy Gimlin
was stabbed to death.
Her husband, Reagan,
was the prime suspect.
But there was no evidence.
Nothing to tie him to the crime scene.
And then, Dibny
miraculously found a knife
with the husband's fingerprints.
Case closed. Dibny was a hero.
I don't know, maybe because my mom
was stabbed, I wanted to be sure.
So, I analyzed the knife.
The serrations on the blade
did not match the wound on the vic.
So, Dibny planted the knife.
Yeah.
And then he lied about it, under oath.
And you busted him?
I mean,
he didn't just bend the rules, Iris,
he committed perjury,
evidence tampering.
He was thrown off the force.
Point is, he was crooked then,
he's crooked now.
Hey, how much DNA
do you think Caitlin needs?
Not much.
Okay.
Oh... Think this'll work?
Hmm.
Barry!
I guess someone hates him
more than you do.
And that's what it feels like
to vibrate through solid matter.
I'm just glad that you two weren't hurt.
No thanks to your new buddy in there.
He's not my buddy, he's my patient.
Caitlin, I just don't understand
why you're defending him.
Because I know what it's like
to suddenly find yourself
with extraordinary powers
and be totally freaked out by it.
And so do you, for that matter.
You and I both woke up in this lab once
knowing that our lives
would never be the same.
So, how about you give the guy
a little sympathy?
- Hey.
- Guys.
I pulled the LUDS on Dibny's phone,
there were 15 phone calls
between him and the mayor's office.
What is Mayor Bellows doing
talking to Ralph Dibny?
Look, it's my good buddy, Barry Allen.
Someone just blew up your office.
Sweet. Insurance claim.
My fiancée and I almost died.
You landed West's daughter?
- Well...
- Wow.
Everything's coming up Allen.
The job, the girl.
Who's trying to kill you, Dibny?
Do you know how many people
I have pissed off
in the last five years?
Angry husbands, angry wives.
Not exactly dealing with high society
taking photos of cheating spouses.
Then why are you talking to the Mayor?
- Who says I am?
- Your phone records.
Did...
Did you get a warrant for that
'cause I know you're all by the book.
What's your business with Mayor Bellows?
Nothing.
Just call and tell him
what a swell job I think he is doing.
Fifteen times.
Twelve of those were butt dials.
All right, look, whatever.
We'll go talk to the Mayor ourselves.
He's a huge fan of Joe's.
- Yeah, you go do that.
- All right.
I'm gonna stay here.
Stretch my legs.
Ramon, do you think it's wise
to be sneaking around
a technologically weaponized facility?
It's a lot safer than what
I'm up against out there. So...
Coffee didn't go well, I take it.
Well...
Gypsy's dad wants to hunt me
for 24 hours
to see if I'm worthy of his daughter.
No powers.
So, don't know what the hell
I'm supposed to do about that.
Fight back.
I swear,
it's like you're trying to listen,
but you just nod while you're
thinking of something else.
You're doing it right now.
Fight back, Ramon. What did you say?
You said no powers?
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, in addition to being Vibe,
you have another superpower.
You're smart, in here, all right?
Outwardly, you're weak, all right?
Too much.
But use your outwardly weak
appearance to your advantage.
He's gonna anticipate a pathetic target.
Well, you're pathetic...
You're pathetic, you're weak.
Not helping, just hurting.
All I'm saying is set a trap, okay?
Beat him at his own game, set a trap.
- Set a trap.
- That's right, a trap.
A trap, I can do.
'Cause he may be the Predator,
but I'm the Schwarzenegger.
Where is he?
He was here.
Yeah, he went that way.
I farted.
I'm not sure everything is still
where it's supposed to be down there.
- Drink this.
- What is it?
I don't just drink stuff.
My body is a temple.
Clearly. Drink it.
I want to know what it is.
It's 17% alcohol.
You should've led with that, sister.
Oh!
What was that?
It's a serum of sulfur, zinc oxide,
and steric acid
to cross-link your polymerized cells.
In English.
It's gonna fix you.
You did it! I'm cured!
Well, not cured.
All I did was introduce
a stabilizing enzyme
to reset your body to default shape
through vulcanization.
It's like muscle memory.
Muscle memory, huh? Huh...
How far back memory, you think?
I don't know.
Think about the shape you wanna be
and just be it.
I'm back. I look like a Hemsworth.
- Joseph.
- Thank you for meeting us.
Quick stop on my way to a hospital
ribbon cutting, no problem.
What's with you? You're glowing.
No.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
Well, how can I help you, gentlemen?
I got a lot on my schedule today.
We won't take up
much of your time, Mr. Mayor.
Do you know a man named Ralph Dibny?
Doesn't ring a bell. Who is he?
He is a former cop
turned private investigator.
I don't think so.
Really? He called your office
over a dozen times.
Oh, I'm gonna have to check
with my secretary.
Anthony, you used to be a cop.
We're not talking to the Mayor here,
it's three cops talking.
Whatever cops say to each other,
they don't say to anybody else.
What's going on with you and Dibny?
I...
- Made a mistake.
- "Mistake"?
You mean, like,
the kind of mistake you make
with a woman who's not your wife?
It was only that one time, Joe.
I regretted it the moment I did it
and I broke it off right away.
And then, Dibny shows up,
and he's got pictures of us.
And he threatens to show them
to my wife unless I pay him.
- How much?
- Not enough.
All those phone calls,
it was him negotiating
for a bigger price.
I love my family, Joe.
Just let me pay him
and I'll be done with it.
No, Mr. Mayor,
you're not gonna have to do that.
We're gonna take care of it.
Joe, Barry, thank you.
So much for Dibny changing.
Dibny's alive and talking. Find him.
- I want those pictures and his head.
- And the cops?
What do I care about the cops?
Waste them.
- Your vitals are fantastic.
- Good.
You're blackmailing the Mayor?
Classic Barry Allen, enters the room
and accuses wildly.
We know about the photos, Ralph.
Bellows told us everything.
Hey, I'm not the one who told him
to step out on his wife.
That's your defense? It's his fault
that you're extorting him.
Isn't that a little easy for you to say?
Your fancy lab, your good job,
and your hot girlfriend.
People like me are just trying
to get from one bill to the next.
And I wouldn't
have to be living like that
if you hadn't cost me my job.
You got yourself fired.
You tampered with evidence,
you framed that guy.
Because he was guilty.
And he was gonna get away
with killing his wife,
and then you let him go.
I was a good cop,
I was a good detective.
I lost everything.
Mayor's got plenty of money,
he can afford to spare a little.
Consider it the pension you cost me.
Good people don't destroy lives
and call it noble.
You were dirty then, you're dirty now.
Live with that.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Get off me.
Are you kidding me?
Thanks for ruining my life twice, Allen.
Cisky.
Show yourself.
No one can avoid me forever.
I'm not going to.
Are you kidding me?
Say goodbye, my little enemy.
What the Sheol?
Guess who's got a hologram?
Ho, ho, ho.
Bet you're wondering
what this is.
This is an anti-vibrational force field
with an oscillating power grid.
Good enough for the Reverse-Flash.
Good enough for you.
So, you might as well
wave your white flag
'cause you aren't
getting out of this thing
until the clock strikes Cisco's victory.
Oh, victory.
Feels good.
I pulled this from the body
of an Earth-48 hunter-killer.
You can't trap a trapper.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
I just needed to cool off.
I figured.
Dibny seemed to have
gotten under your skin.
Why is it so important
to you that he be the bad guy?
When I first started at CCPD,
all I cared about was the rules.
But, you know, these last few years,
we've locked up meta-humans
without a trial,
played with time and space,
messed with other worlds.
Yeah, but what does that
have to do with Dibny?
Just that everything we've done, we did
because we were trying to help people,
keep them safe.
Hmm.
Is that all Dibny was
trying to do back then?
"Good people don't destroy lives
and call it noble."
Did I make a mistake back then?
Did I cost a good man his life?
I don't know, Barr.
He did break the law, cross the line.
You didn't make him do that.
And you didn't make him
blackmail the Mayor.
But maybe Caitlin was right.
Everyone who has gone through
what you and her
and now Dibny has gone through...
Maybe he deserves a second chance.
I got it.
Allen.
Detective West.
Aren't you two on the Mayor's detail?
Sorry to bother you at home,
but dispatch just radioed.
Captain Singh needs you
down at the station ASAP.
All right, let me get my jacket.
Barr!
That never gets old.
Those two work for the Mayor.
- They just tried to kill us.
- Dibny's next.
Cisky, Cisky, Cisky.
Cisky.
Come out.
Come out and meet your end.
Plastoid.
You creatures destroyed my planet.
Now, I will kill every last one of you.
Guys! Anyone there?
Barry, I'm here, it's me!
What's up?
I need you to activate the tracker
I put on Dibny.
You put a tracker on Ralph?
Plastoid.
Cisco, do you know where he is?
He's at City Hall.
You lost weight.
Lap-band surgery.
Since killing you didn't work out...
What we agreed upon, 200K.
Let me have the photographs.
Here's the pictures.
- Keep the money.
- What?
I take it back.
"Take it back"?
I take my blackmail back.
Is this some kind of a trick?
I'm not dirty.
And I don't want
any part in this anymore.
And don't you forget.
I can tie you to that bomb you had
your goons plant in my office,
so, if you don't walk away,
I will go to the cops.
That's still blackmail.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
You're telling me
if I don't give you this money,
you won't go to the cops.
Okay, fine.
I am blackmailing you
into not being blackmailed.
So, we're good, then?
Yeah, we're good.
Bullet booger. Super gross.
Sorry, Mr. Mayor...
It's over.
Die, Plastoid, die!
You will not infest this world
as you did mine, Plastoid!
Plastoid? What? Is he talking to me?
Breacher, stop.
Okay.
He dies, speedster.
Joe, get in there, Joe.
- You're coming with me, come on.
- Flash!
Look, you don't have to do this.
Yes, I do!
Leave him alone.
This guy didn't invade your planet,
he didn't do anything wrong.
He's like this 'cause of me and my team.
So, if you've got a problem
with him and his powers,
then you deal with me.
Hey, are we good here?
Because I definitely
got to change my drawers.
The Mayor took Joe.
I can't run fast enough right now.
I'll never have enough speed
to jump off a building.
Can you breach me up there?
There's no way, the event horizon would
rip the helicopter apart.
We got to save Joe.
What do we do?
You can get me up there.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- How?
- You can stretch, grab it!
Are you crazy? I can't do that.
Yes, you can. All right?
I know that you have it inside you
to help someone other than yourself.
I know you, Ralph.
How could you possibly know me?
Dude, are you kidding me?
You're the Flash?
Everyone else gets
struck by lightning and dies,
- and you get superpowers?
- Yeah, that's right.
Your assistant's a speedster?
I liked the Flash,
now I have to hate the Flash.
Ralph, focus. I need you to do this.
Joe needs you to do this, please.
Show me I was wrong about you.
You said you were a good cop,
be one, right now.
What the hell?
I got it!
Whoa-whoa!
- Help!
- Hold on, Ralph.
Cecile's pregnant.
Well, we've reached the end of our road.
We had some stumbles along the way,
but we pulled it together,
we made it home.
I hate you.
Wow, really thought that one would work.
But I respect you.
You're a steadfast warrior
who would fight the fiercest
of enemies to protect your friend,
and the only person I love.
With my dying breath, sir.
I know that, but I still hate you.
I have never seen him gush like that.
That's gushing?
I'm terrified
to experience him loving me.
- Well, that's my job.
- That's right. It is.
I feel a code-17 breach in progress.
We have to leave now, Cynthia.
Cynthia? Cynthia?
What's your dad's name?
Josh.
Cynthia and Josh!
That's great.
Not so scary now, Cynthia.
Keep calling me that, see what happens.
All right.
See you around, Gypsy.
- I fixed up your office.
- Sweet fancy Moses!
Thanks for screwing up
my insurance claim.
No payout, no Mayor money,
I got to pick up a case soon.
What if I had a job for you?
I want to laugh really hard right now,
but I'm afraid my face
will fall off again.
I can't change what has happened
between us in the past,
but I can offer you a chance
to change what happens in our future.
How?
Let my team and I study your powers,
figure out how to improve them,
see what your limitations are.
And let me train you.
Train me? For what?
To do what I do.
To be a detective again, Ralph.
A real one.
Look, it's not gonna be easy,
I'm gonna push you to your limit.
It's safe to say some days,
you're gonna hate me.
Allen, it's safe to say
that I always hate you.
Do I get a cool superhero name?
What do you think about Plastic Man?
I think that's the dumbest name
I've ever heard.
It's Cisco who comes up with the names.
Yeah, it's better that way.
What do you say?
There's just one thing I got to ask you.
What made you look into Mayor Bellows
in the first place?
It was a client who
asked me to follow the Mayor.
Never met him, though,
he did everything over the phone.
Who was it?
Only gave me his last name.
DeVoe.
You and I have been
enemies for years.
You've had others, of course.
There's Thawne, Zoom, DeVoe.
This is where we came up
with the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
What's wrong?
The name "DeVoe" mean something to you?
I smell a mystery.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::