[Black Lightning] Injustice?
Damn.
Look, Barry, those protocols
are a one-way trip, and a bad one.
- I know that.
- All right.
All right.
- Just take a deep breath.
- [breathing heavily]
Tell me what happened.
In the last 24 hours,
I've lost my job, my home base.
[breathing heavily]
I started having blackouts.
I destroyed my apartment at super speed.
I attacked my team, my family.
Jefferson, I attacked innocent people.
Dozens of them.
And I don't remember doing it.
I'm out of control!
Easy.
In my experience, there's almost
nothing that can't be undone.
But I'm gonna need you
to calm down for a minute.
[yelling] Calm down? I'm losing my mind.
Look, you know the contingency plan.
The Injustice Protocols were put
into place for a reason.
To protect the world
when one of us goes rogue.
It's happening, Jefferson.
You have to take away my powers.
- We need to call in the others.
- We don't have time.
No, Kara, J'onn, Sara.
We all designed this plan together
after Faust.
We all made the same promise!
If anyone ever lost control,
a designated teammate would step in.
For me, that's you.
And I don't carry that weight lightly.
What if this is all temporary?
What if your mind starts healing?
It's not going to heal.
It's only gonna get worse.
How can you say that for sure?
I forgot Joe died.
The man who raised me.
He passed away six months ago
and I can't remember it... at all.
Look, I know you have questions,
but I'm losing myself.
You took an oath.
If I ever said the word "injustice,"
you'd listen.
Please... we have to do this now.
My father had a saying.
One that I even teach my students today.
"Where's the future? Right here.
Whose life is this? Mine.
And what are you going do with it?
Live it, by any means necessary."
So don't worry. I will honor my promise.
I will do whatever is necessary
to keep folks alive.
But remember...
when we take away your powers,
they are gone...
permanently.
[intense music playing]
[Human Despero] It's happening again.
Another world lost.
Another failure.
Armageddon waits for no man.
And it won't wait
for me to find you, Flash.
[Chester] You think Despero was right,
that Barry's gonna destroy
the world or something?
No. Hey, what Barry did today was scary.
And the things that he said,
they really, really hurt.
But someone that we love
is going through a mental health crisis,
so I don't care what he may
or may not do ten years from now.
We need to take care of him today,
just like he did for me.
Okay, we'll follow your lead.
What do you want to do?
Okay. I've been sensing Despero all day.
He's using his mind's eye
to scan the city.
Now, he hasn't found him yet,
but if Barry's not thinking clearly...
What if he's the only one
thinking clearly?
Boss, what are you talking about?
Look, I know how this is gonna sound,
but when Despero showed up,
he said that Barry would suffer tragedy.
And then on cue, he lost his job,
he lost S.T.A.R. Labs, and now...
he's lost his mind.
Doesn't that seem like
a big coincidence?
A little too big?
But Despero's from the future.
Wouldn't he know what happened?
But what if he didn't know that
someone secretly caused it to happen?
You think he's being framed?
[Cecile] Iris.
He forgot about Joe.
Nobody was framing him then.
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
Look, when Dad died, C.C.P.D said
that his death was an accident,
that he fell on the tracks
at Scott Railway.
Kramer left me with the evidence,
but for the last six months,
I haven't been able to look at it.
But then I thought about
what Barry said,
that we have to investigate
what happened.
- So I finally started looking...
- [laptop beeps]
...and this is what I found.
Joe.
Why are you showing us this?
Just trust me.
See, one second he's there
and the next, he's gone.
I haven't figured this all out yet,
but if somebody framed Barry,
then he doesn't cause Armageddon,
and, Cecile, Dad could be alive.
No, no, it's impossible.
Is it?
I mean, what if a meta-human
abducted him at the last second
or he got swapped
with like, a Mirror clone?
I saw them bury his body.
So did Barry, and so did you.
Okay, guys, how about we take five?
I'm not trying to upset you.
Then what are you trying to do?
I'm trying to find out
if my dad is still alive.
I'm trying to prove
my husband's innocence.
It does not matter if he is innocent,
if we can't find him,
which is what we have been trying to do
while you have been living
in a fantasy world.
Hey.
Iris has trusted Barry
against the odds before,
like, when Bloodwork infected him
and she was right.
If there's even a chance
that this could be real,
I can't give up
and you wouldn't want me to.
Is that what you think?
You think I gave up?
My God, do you think I don't wake up
alone every morning in our bed,
praying to God that all of this
was nothing but a bad dream?
Iris, I have done everything that I can
to just keep moving forward
since I lost Joe,
I did it so that
I could be there for you,
and for Jenna, for this team.
And you come in here and you want
to shove his death in my face?
He was the father of my child!
And my father!
Fine.
If you insist on pursuing this lie,
then we will save Barry without you.
Fine... You save him your way.
I'll save him mine.
[exhales]
Okay, Cecile. What do you want to do?
We find Barry before Despero does first.
No matter what it takes.
[Caitlin] How are we
supposed to find Barry now?
Okay. This is gonna sound wild,
but Despero's scanning the whole world
for Barry's brainwaves, right?
Like a needle in a haystack.
I know him better than almost anyone.
So you should be able to pinpoint
Barry's mind faster than he can.
Only Despero's psychic radius
is exponentially higher than yours.
Alex Danvers says he gets a power boost
from his power source of...
...Flame of Py'tar.
Okay, I just need
a boost of my own, right?
So you can build something,
something that can amplify
my psychic powers.
You want me to build a Cerebro
out of the trash in my garage?
Oh, frack, yeah, I can do that.
Okay. There's still one problem.
Kalanorians like Despero
have four hemispheres to their brain.
The human brain only has two.
So even if we amplify
your empathic radius,
you'd still be at a disadvantage.
Then we're gonna need
some more brain power...
and I know just who to call.
[Allegra] So, things got
a little intense back there. You okay?
[Iris West] Yeah. Look,
I don't want to hurt Cecile,
but if someone's framing Barry
and my dad might be okay,
then I have to figure out the truth.
I'm just glad
I don't have to do it alone.
Team Citizen forever, boss.
So what are we looking for?
Signs of a meta-abduction?
What the hell?
What is it?
I'm not sure. Do you see anything?
No, I'm not picking up anything
on the electro-magnetic spectrum,
but your time sickness
makes you see stuff sometimes, right?
Could it be acting up?
Must be.
Deon's treatments are probably
wearing off.
I'm supposed to see him tonight.
You know what I did see?
The fiber optic aura for these cameras
leads to a security booth inside.
So if someone wanted to alter
the footage of Joe's accident,
to make it seem like he died...
That'd be where they'd start.
I'll never forget that day.
People were screaming, "Someone fell."
I tried calling the emergency line,
but it was too late.
What about before it happened?
Did you see anyone suspicious
on the platform?
It was pretty empty when Mr. West died.
The Red Line came in 15 minutes early.
Hang on.
Iris West-Allen.
Were you his daughter?
I still am.
What about after?
Was there anyone there who had access
to the scene before C.C.P.D. arrived?
Ma'am...
your father took a bad step.
It happens sometimes.
Well, the reason
I'm asking is because
the video files that you sent over
to C.C.P.D.
were missing some very important frames
from the moment of incident.
That doesn't just happen,
unless you're saying
someone got into your system.
Or because we're on the same power grid
as Sharks Stadium.
Whenever there's a game,
like there was that day,
our automatic CCTV upload
gets interrupted
and we end up losing chunks of data.
It's a good thing
we back up our files locally.
- Is this the only angle?
- No, it's okay.
I was wrong. It was just an accident.
- [rock music playing in background]
- [balls clanking]
So, who wants next game, boys?
Think you can end up on top?
[Cecile] I think you're done for today.
[sighing]
Horton, I'm surprised you showed.
Figured you'd still be crying
over your boyfriend somewhere.
You should have heard the cheers at
Iron Heights when that news broke out.
Well, that's funny, because I figured
you'd already be running
Scudder's entire criminal enterprise,
not hustling morons in a dive bar.
I guess you probably shouldn't
have sold them out after all.
Fine.
Aw.
That means you're available.
For what? Got a job for me,
Ms. Meta-Attorney?
Look, I need help.
Psychic help.
Someone that I care about is missing.
Let me guess. He runs real fast.
It's all over the news.
Flash went bad.
It's the feel-good story of the year.
And even if I did want to help
return the scarlet speedster
to the side of angels,
during our last go-around,
you messed with my head.
I don't know if I can trust you.
Can you trust me to help
get your parole restrictions lifted?
Quid pro quo, huh?
When do we start?
Damn it, I can't get this last conduit.
You know what? Sometimes,
I like to work with a little music on.
Yeah.
["Blue Monk" playing]
Monk?
Okay, trying to impress me.
I kind of grew up on this stuff.
Joe always had something
spinning on the turntable.
Miles Davis, Johnny Hartman,
Ella Fitzgerald...
It's his favorite.
Was his favorite.
[breathing deeply]
Yeah, I lost someone, too, a while back.
Bill Henderson.
Actually, he was a cop,
like your old man.
We had our ups and downs,
but... through it all,
he was my best friend... brother.
Bill died saving my life...
so I could get home
to Lynn and the girls.
Yeah, he made that sacrifice...
just like you sacrificing
a big part of yourself here today.
You know, if Joe was here,
I think he'd be real proud
of the hero you've been...
all along.
It's been you all along, Flash.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, that was the last conduit.
Now, when your suit materializes, you'll
be able to generate enough voltage
to disrupt my Speed Force connection.
All right. Giving Gambi
a run for his money, huh?
Well, all right.
Let's go blow this fuse.
[tense music playing]
[sighs] I'm ready.
This is gonna hurt.
Mm-hmm.
[electricity crackling]
[screaming]
[groaning]
Boss, you gotta see this.
Okay, do you remember
what the security chief said,
that the day Joe died,
the Red Line was running early?
Well, back in my car-thief days,
I'd take the Red Line home
from the chop shop,
and it was never early.
It was always late.
So, my dad was just unlucky?
Well, that's an understatement.
The train that hit Joe passed a routine
inspection two days before the accident.
Yet, somehow the hydraulics failed?
Iris, there are dozens and dozens
of coincidences like this.
Do you know what the odds are
that they all happened at once?
A million-to-one.
The events that led to Joe's accident,
they line up perfectly.
Too perfectly.
So, what are you saying?
That you're right.
That someone was pulling the strings.
Barry's not crazy. And your dad...
Look, Allegra, I was wrong...
about everything.
These last six months have been
the worst six months of my life.
Look, I get it.
I do.
When Esperanza died...
I lost hope, too,
but... what saved me from the darkness
was remembering the words of a hero.
"As long as we keep the loved ones
we've lost in our hearts,
there's always hope."
Are you seeing this?
Seeing what?
I have to get back to the station.
- I thought that was a dead end.
- It's not.
We just couldn't see all the evidence.
Ladies, may I present the solution
to all of our Flash-finding problems,
the Neural Conjoiner.
Both of you have the natural ability
to access brainwaves like an antenna.
Cecile is an empath,
and Rosa is a psychic who can spin
people's emotions out of control.
So with the telepathic crown
as an amplifier,
we'll be able to conjoin
your psychic powers
and pick up way more brainwaves
than you'd ever be able
to pick up on your own,
like, all over the continent.
Now, all you need to do
is focus on the Flash's brainwaves,
and the N.C. will transmit them here,
while I use the visual data
to triangulate his location with this.
I'm sorry, but does that TV
have rabbit ears on it?
Yeah. Because it's my grandma's,
which means
we'll have to be done by 7:00,
because she doesn't
want to miss her stories.
You ready?
[overlapping mind voices]
[groaning]
[panicking] It's too much.
It's too much! It's too much! I can't!
- Chuck, turn it off.
- No. We can do this.
[gasps]
So many minds to reach and touch.
- [frantically] can't, I can't.
- [breathing heavily]
- It's too many. I can't do this.
- No, there aren't.
Horton, listen to me.
Together, we are strong enough
to handle this,
but you're letting your own feelings
hold you back. Now, focus!
[gasping]
Horton! You're letting
your own emotions bring you down.
That sadness you got, get over it.
- You want to find your hero?
- Yes.
Then, lose the weakness,
just like I lost those gushy feelings
for Scudder.
Forget about your grief,
your guilt, your sadness.
Forget about your damn dead boyfriend.
Bury it!
[breathing heavily]
[overlapping mind voices continue]
[The Flash] I still have
some of my speed.
The connections not fully severed.
I found him.
Keep it going. Keep it going.
We almost have a clear signal.
[both groan]
- What happened?
- You overloaded the crown.
Damn, Horton. I knew I was good, but...
color me impressed.
Okay, if the amplifier's busted, then
maybe we should try a different way.
No, Chester, you can fix it, right?
You can fix it.
Well, I need about an hour
to recalibrate,
but then, we should be good to go.
Do it. We finally made some progress.
We're not gonna stop now.
[Human Despero] Those humans.
Their emotions blind them to reason
yet give them power.
They'll find Flash first.
And I'll be right behind them.
You forget we had
an appointment in the books
'cause, usually,
we meet in the Speed Lab.
Then again, I am a force god. So...
I can work with this, too.
Ready for your treatment?
I didn't forget we had an appointment.
I wanted you to find me here.
Why?
This is where your dad died.
I can sense him walking
through here, six months ago.
I came here earlier today
and I saw these particles
near the tracks where my dad fell.
And then I saw them again when I was
going through evidence from his death.
This is a sign that there's
something wrong with my dad's death.
Proof that someone is...
altering reality
and leaving particles behind.
But nobody's screwed with the timeline,
or I would've sensed that.
Then, someone's hiding something.
I need you to undo my treatments,
all of them.
- You can't be serious.
- Deon, please.
Whatever's happening,
its connected to these particles.
If I absorb all of that
temporal matter out of you,
and that sickness you got
starts spreading too fast,
you're gonna start moving
in and out of timelines again.
- Or worse.
- I'm not afraid of that.
Well, I am.
Look, if there's a chance that I can
save my husband and bring my dad back,
I'll risk it.
My God, what are they?
[Deon] Temporal isotopes.
They're decaying instead of growing.
That's why I couldn't sense them before.
Oh, damn.
Someone tapped into the Negative
Still Force to rewrite the timeline.
Your dad wasn't supposed to die.
But someone changed the past
to make sure that he did.
[Caitlin] Cecile, we need to talk
about Dillon.
Look, I know. I get it, okay?
Dillon can be a little intense,
but we're trying to beat Despero here.
She wants you to forget about Joe.
It's more than a little intense.
And... honestly, it's not the first time
I've seen you repress your feelings.
You have no idea
what it's been like for me. None.
Actually, I do, because
it's what I went through with Ronnie.
After the particle accelerator exploded,
I was so traumatized by his death
that even thinking about him
would send me spiraling.
Rather than facing my grief,
I started fearing it. I just...
I can't help thinking
you're heading down the same path.
Okay, no. I know I don't talk about Joe.
It's because I think about him
every second of every hour of every day.
And it's not just my grief
that I have to feel,
Caitlin. Barry,
and Iris and little Jenna...
because of my powers, whenever they're
near me, I feel all of their grief, too.
It's everything that I can do
to push it all down just so that
I can keep moving forward,
because if I don't, I will drown...
and that cannot happen again.
I know it's hard,
but your strength as an empath,
it doesn't come
from burying your emotions.
It comes from feeling the feelings...
even the hard ones.
- [beeping]
- Let me guess. Dinner's ready.
Oh!
Sweet Joseph Winters. Okay.
My phone is still plugged into
the S.T.A.R. Labs emergency sensors.
Someone just turned on
the particle accelerator.
- [alarm sounding]
- What the hell's going on?
The power's spiking, sir.
Impossible.
It's like the particle accelerator
turned itself on.
[Human Despero] Not exactly.
I may have given it a little push.
[agent] Susan?
[grunts]
Susan, what in the world...
Checkmate.
- [bone cracking]
- [gagging]
[man groans]
[electrical buzzing]
And with this power...
no mind will shut its doors on me!
[manic yelling]
Why would Despero
turn on the particle accelerator?
He's into alternative energy. Who cares?
Guys, look, she is right.
We need to do this.
Okay.
Remember what we did last time.
Remember that power.
[overlapping mind voices]
Come on.
Where are you?
I can see Flash.
He's with Jefferson Pierce.
Where are they?
Let me try and find out.
I can feel your grief again, Horton.
I told you to bury it.
Cecile, you don't have to listen to her.
You know your powers
better than she does.
Hell yes.
It's like meta-juicing,
only ten times better.
[Cecile gasps]
You should be proud of the power
you displayed here.
Now...
open your minds to me...
and show me the Flash.
Leave us alone.
Guys... Who are they talking to?
Despero. He must be here.
Dillon, what are you doing?
Causing a little vertigo.
It's an oldie but a goodie.
Okay, big boy.
How about a little quid pro quo?
I let you inside my mind,
show you where the Flash is...
and then you and I go kill him together.
What makes you think
I came here to bargain?
Okay.
How about I let you peek inside my mind
for free and we'll call it even?
[groans and screams]
Dillon!
[Cecile] Dillon!
I can't feel her anymore.
- What did you do?
- I looked inside her mind,
but I could only partly reconstruct
the Flash's location.
The other half must be in yours.
Don't be afraid.
It's a necessity.
I am trying to save the world.
By killing us? And Barry?
A few lives to spare billions.
That's the trade I'm willing to make,
but one that you won't even stomach.
Your mind's strong for a human empath,
but it's kindling
compared to the Flame of Py'tar.
[screaming]
Stop fighting me
and show me where he is.
You have no allies left,
you're weak and you're alone.
You're wrong.
I am not alone.
[gasps]
[groans softly]
Hey.
- [Cecile] Hey, you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
She's alive, but barely.
Despero, he attacked us.
How did you survive?
I thought about Joe.
[device beeps]
Hey, wait, wait, wait. I found Barry.
He's at the Hall.
- [whispers] What?
- [Cecile] Guys, guys,
Despero was in my head.
That means he knows where Barry is, too.
- [electricity crackling]
- [The Flash screams]
[Black Lightning] All right,
maybe we should take a break.
No, we have to finish
before Despero finds me.
Who the hell is Despero?
[sighs]
If you're keeping something important
from me,
I suggest you remedy it.
He's from the future.
He says that ten years from now,
I'm going to destroy the world.
You believe him?
Do you remember what we said
when we first met during Crisis?
We're not quitters.
You can change your future,
just like you did back then...
That's what I'm trying to do.
If I get rid of my speed, I can
keep Despero's future from happening.
What will this Despero do if you don't?
He's going to kill me.
You didn't think that was important
to mention?
I knew if I told you,
you'd want to go after Despero,
but I need you to follow
the Injustice Protocols.
I'm not acting out of fear,
I'm trying to do the right thing.
Yeah, I thought I was too, but I wasn't,
and you weren't, either.
You're just...
afraid of becoming this man
that Despero says you are.
I've already hurt people!
- I'm already a liability!
- No, what you are is a hero.
Doesn't that mean something?
I've seen what happens.
What I end up doing.
It's going to happen.
Getting rid of my speed
is the only way to save the world.
[yells] Damn it, Jefferson,
it's the only way
to save your family, too!
I suggest you keep my family
out of this.
After everything we've done today,
everything I've told you,
you're just giving up.
[Black Lightning] Barry...
you need to think
very carefully right now.
I'm asking you to save
the world and you won't even listen!
You're gonna hear me now...
'cause one way or the other,
you're going to help me finish this.
[The Flash] Look at what I just did!
The damage I can still cause.
You made a promise to keep
this world safe.
[Black Lightning]
I am keeping the world safe!
By saving one of its protectors!
Fine. You wanna ignore the protocols?
Now imagine millions dead...
all because of me!
It's your lightning, you keep it.
[groans]
How about we stop this insanity? Huh?
You remember why we call
our safety plan "Injustice"?
Because if one of us goes rogue,
the rest of the world
doesn't stand a chance.
[electricity crackling]
[glass breaking]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs wearily]
[Black Lightning] You think this is...
what he would have wanted?
[Black Lightning groans]
You told me that before... Crisis,
Oliver went to the Monitor,
to trade his life for yours.
Now, I never met the man,
so you tell me.
Why'd he do that?
Because he was afraid?
No.
A man like him...
lays down his life for a man like you...
for one reason.
Because you are the best of us.
Oliver Queen wasn't a quitter.
He'd never quit on you.
So don't you dare quit on yourself.
Jefferson, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Just tell me this.
Where's the future?
[subdued laugh]
It's right here.
Whose life is this?
Mine.
So what are you gonna do with it?
Live it...
by any means necessary.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
I told you, Flash.
If I found any trace
of your true nature,
I'd end your existence.
Leave him alone. He's innocent.
Someone changed the timeline to kill
my father and make Barry seem insane.
You really believe
you're telling the truth.
How tragic.
[screaming]
Hurry, I'll hold him off.
[groans]
You need to go and figure out
who is trying to frame you.
I need to go to the future,
to see who really causes Armageddon.
I can't hold him much longer.
I'm not gonna make it there.
I don't have enough Speed Force left.
How about some Still Force?
My isotopes will pull you
toward any weird temporal activity.
Run, Barry! Run!
You all just killed this world.
[intense music playing]
[Eobard] If I could have
everyone's attention for a moment.
I have been waiting
for this moment for a very,
very long time.
When you find...
...the love of your life,
it's like electricity
pulsing through your veins,
giving you a shock that you absolutely
never want to end.
Because...
because now...
now you're a part of something greater.
A part of something wonderful,
and frankly, surprising,
because you never know...
what face fate will be wearing
when she shows up to knock on your door
and change your life... forever.
But when it does,
for you, my wish is that,
that face...
is as beautiful as the one
standing next to me. To Iris West...
the love of my life.
And to our future together.
What the hell is he doing here?