(SCREECHING)
Reloading.
Argh!
-David!
-(GROANS)
Back door, the captain's down.
Go, go, go, go.
Down, down, down, get down.
(CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHOUTING STOPS)
IRIS: Some people are calling it
"The Metapocalypse,"
the days when Central City was overrun
by an army with powers beyond imagination.
But in these dark times,
we must never forget our own strength,
our own power to fight back.
That it is only in the blackest of nights
that we can truly see the light,
and know, for sure, we are not alone.
We are never, ever alone.
We usually take these guys down
one at a time, not 100 at a time.
And yet, you don't seem overwhelmed.
I know we can do it. (CHUCKLES)
Guys, you have to come see this.
Cisco, what are you... Caitlin?
She's in shock.
A little dehydrated and malnourished,
but I think she'll be fine.
I'm okay.
What happened? How did you get away?
(SHAKILY) He let me go.
I didn't think he would,
I thought it was a trap.
But he told me you were dead.
I'm not. I'm right here.
We're all here. Together.
HARRISON: Snow,
Jay's not here. You're safe.
(SHAKILY) He's gonna overrun the city,
you can't stop him.
Yes, we can.
Listen to me, he's not going to succeed.
We've got this. This is our Earth.
You don't know that.
You don't know what he is capable of.
I know from being in the Speed Force
that the universe is with us, not Zoom.
And if the Universe is with us,
how could we possibly lose? Right, guys?
Yeah, yeah, right.
You've been through a lot.
You should get some rest, come on.
You were in the Speed Force?
I... (SIGHS) When you were gone,
it's hard to explain,
but we tried to get my powers back,
and the dark matter lightning
I was inside...
Okay, I'm gonna say it.
Um, we don't think he's just being
a little too...
-Overconfident?
-(SCOFFS) Yeah.
Yeah, maybe it was his time
in the Speed Force.
I mean, he's acting
like he's invincible now or something.
Yeah, like nothing fazes him anymore,
which isn't...
Realistic, no.
Somebody needs to talk to him before
letting his guard down gets him hurt,
or worse.
I mean, he did bring me out of my coma.
That's bound to make someone
a little overly chipper.
Well, like I said,
somebody needs to talk to him.
DR. McGEE: Amazing job, Anupam.
This is exactly
the kind of groundbreaking thinking
I built this company for.
Well done.
(SCREECHING)
(RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE MURMURING INDISTINCTLY)
Everyone, evacuate! Now!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Hurry!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING AND CLAMORING)
Hey.
She's out like a light, huh?
Yeah. Jay really did a number on her.
(SCOFFS) It's not like he exactly used
kid gloves on the rest of us.
She'll be okay, she just needs time.
And for us to finally bring Zoom down.
Which we will.
Yeah, because the Universe
is with us, right?
Listen, man...
(BIRD CHIRPING)
BARRY: Cisco? Hey, are you okay?
-You just vibe?
-Yeah.
What'd you see?
I saw a bird. Like, a dead bird.
(COMPUTER ALARM BEEPING)
Mercury Labs.
-It's under attack.
-All right.
MAN: Come on!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Ah!
(RUMBLING)
Thank you, Mr. Allen.
I'm not stupid.
(CHUCKLES)
Boom.
So, how did you know?
-Your real identity?
-Yeah.
Come on, Barry, I'm a scientist.
We're paid to be perceptive.
And you're always
a little too well-informed
-when things go pear-shaped in this city.
-(CHUCKLES)
But I don't believe we've ever met before.
Dr. Christina McGee.
Dr. Henry Allen. I'm Barry's father.
Okay, now that the cat's out of the bag,
did you happen to see who it was
that caused your building to collapse?
I didn't see anything,
it happened so fast.
Maybe the security cameras
caught something?
Can we access them?
Mercury Labs does have
a crash-survivable memory unit.
A what?
Virtually, a blackbox for buildings.
It will have stored
all the security footage
right up until the building collapsed.
Okay, great, I'll go find it.
This wasn't some random meta-human.
Whenever Mercury Labs has been targeted
in the past,
there's always been a specific reason.
Yeah, someone's after something.
Yes, and that someone is probably Zoom.
-Mmm-hmm.
-There may be one more possibility.
A few months ago, I saw
Harrison Wells running out of my facility.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm certain it was him.
Is there any way
he could have anything to do with this?
A few months ago? Sure.
Now? No.
Yeah, there are a few more things
that we could catch you up on, Dr. McGee.
Hey, my purse!
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
-(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
-(GROANS)
-That ain't yours, punk.
Big mistake.
You picked a bad time to play hero.
(GRUNTING, SCREAMING)
(MAN GRUNTS, GROANS)
Dad?
(GASPING)
(GROANING)
Wally? What the hell were you doing?
That guy just jacked a bunch of people,
so I had to go after him.
You could've got yourself killed!
I'm not just gonna let these guys
get away with this.
-I have to do something.
-Wally, these are not just guys!
These are meta-humans!
Leave this to the cops and The Flash!
The Flash can't be everywhere at once.
I... I have to do what I can to help.
I have to show him
I was worth being saved.
(SCOFFS)
Wally.
You are worth it.
Really? Am I?
'Cause last time I checked,
I'm the guy
who avoided his dying mother for weeks.
I'm the guy who shamed
a bunch of other guys
and illegally took their cars from them.
I'm the guy who caused The Flash
to lose his powers
and start this whole damn Metapocalypse
in the first place.
-Wally...
-Last time I checked,
I have a whole lot to make up for.
That's what I intend to do.
Damn it.
-HARRISON: Snow.
-Oh.
-I didn't know you were here.
-What are you doing?
Jesse asked me to run some tests to see
if her genetic structure had changed.
Why did you ask Dr. Snow
to run tests on you again?
Because I got hit
with the dark matter, okay?
I mean,
that must have affected me somehow.
(WHISPERS) You're not a meta-human.
(NORMAL VOICE) What you are
is a young woman with genius-level IQ
that we could use in our fight
against this new wave of meta-humans.
Okay. All right, fine.
Fine.
(GASPS)
Snow.
You all right?
Yeah, fine.
-Is this it?
-DR. McGEE: That's the one.
All right, great.
Dad, Dr. McGee, Cisco,
why don't you guys crack this open,
-see what you can find?
-Sure.
We'll go see what kind of meta-human
powers can take down a building like that,
-and how to stop it.
-Great.
Sounds like fun.
All right, I'm gonna go see
if Joe needs any help in the streets.
Everybody cool here?
Should be a piece of cake, right?
HENRY: Hey, slugger.
-Hey.
-Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure. What's up?
Well, I know you said
that what happened to you
in the Speed Force
changed the way you see things.
-Yeah.
-But you seem very optimistic,
you know, with a lot of meta-humans
running around, tearing up the city.
What, did you see the future in there?
(CHUCKLES) Um...
Not this time. No, I... Look,
what I was shown in the Speed Force,
it didn't just change my mind,
it changed me.
I don't know, I mean,
what you're seeing as optimism is...
For the first time,
I'm just not afraid anymore.
Great. That's...
But you know
you still have to be careful, right?
-What do you mean?
-Well...
I don't... Why are you trying
to take something from me
that I've fought so hard to get to?
Barry.
(STUTTERS) You don't know everything
that I've been through, Dad.
You haven't been here long enough to know.
I didn't mean...
I'm sorry, I don't know why I said that.
I think I do.
I haven't been around.
To teach you how to drive
or take you to look at colleges,
but I've done everything in my power
to know who you are.
Barry, I don't want to take anything
from you, I believe in you.
This isn't about my not believing in you.
I know that. And I'm fine, okay?
Thank you.
Thank you very much for worrying about me.
I love you,
but I'm fine.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Come on.
What is that?
It's C.C.P.D.
Zoom.
Barry, don't do it.
JAY: You know I never saw the crime photos
of my mother's murder.
Although I guess I didn't need to.
I had a ringside seat
while you got whisked away.
Too delicate, I suppose.
Not just a hologram after all,
are you, Flash?
Interesting.
I know you didn't call me up here
just to banter.
Let's finish this right now.
Actually, I did.
I called you up here to tell you
you can't keep running
from one meta to the next.
Around and around,
like a dog chasing its tail.
I'll do whatever it takes to stop you.
JAY: If only that were good enough.
'Cause here's the thing. I know you.
I know you,
I know what's holding you back.
You and me,
we're really just the same person.
Yeah, you keep saying that,
but it's not gonna make it true.
You'll see. We are.
Same tragic background,
same reason for running,
same desire to be the fastest,
to be the best.
The difference?
You think your anger is dirty somehow.
You want to be seen as pure, the hero.
Doesn't it get exhausting?
Doesn't it get exhausting, Barry?
It was exhausting playing Jay, believe me.
I'm not pretending.
(RUMBLING)
Now, if it were me,
I'd let that building tumble
without a second thought. But you?
You'll never let that happen, will you?
That's why I'm gonna beat you, Barry.
Because you always have to be the hero.
And while you're playing
the good little boy,
I'll be busy winning.
BARRY: We can't let Zoom
destroy another building.
We need to take him down. Now.
And how do you propose we do that
with an army of meta-humans
laying waste to Central City?
We couldn't stop Zoom on my Earth.
What makes us different?
We're a team.
We start with the meta-humans,
they're his armor.
We take them down first,
then Zoom's more vulnerable.
Barry, we don't know even know
how many of his minions there are.
There could be hundreds, a thousand.
And all of them,
they're all working with different powers.
It could take weeks to track 'em all down.
Guys, we don't have weeks.
So what we need to do is come up
with a way to stop them all at once.
Again, how?
(SIGHS) Cisco.
Your goggles, your camera,
they didn't work on Earth-2, right?
Yeah, it was all a different frequency.
And the way you took down
the Time Wraiths?
That was based on frequency.
Hartley's entire schtick...
I think I'm smelling
what you're stepping in.
-Yeah.
-So, basically,
we create some vibrational tech
that could take down the Earth-2 metas.
-Basically.
-I like it.
-Me, too.
-I'll help.
Okay.
I'll let you know
if I hear anything from CCPN.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You guys,
we got this.
-Barry, can I talk to you for a second?
-Yeah.
(BIRDS CAWING)
(GLASS BREAKING)
Birds. Why?
It's like a Hitchcock movie in my head.
BARRY: What's up?
Man, it's Wally.
-Is he okay?
-Not really.
Earlier, he thought
it would be a good idea
if he used himself as bait
against a meta-human psycho.
Thought he could do things
the way The Flash would.
Joe, I mean, he did tell me
that he wasn't gonna waste
the opportunity The Flash gave him.
I don't know if you can stop him.
I'm gonna have to
or he's gonna get himself killed.
Look, he ain't you, Barry.
He can't just go Mach 50...
(CHUCKLES) Mach 50 isn't a real thing.
Point is, thinking you're invincible
isn't any kind of armor.
Now, Wally's already at a higher risk
than I'm comfortable with,
and him throwing caution to the wind
on top of all of that? No.
We gotta keep him safe.
So, can The Flash talk to him?
Again.
Yeah, I'll talk to him.
I'll try, I promise.
-Yeah?
-Mmm-hmm.
(EXHALES) Thank you.
I thought throwing things was Harry's
preferred method of dealing with stress.
That is how frustrated I am right now.
I'm just running out of ideas
as to how to make this work.
Where's Barry? I need a taste
of that Walking on Sunshine thing
he's got going on right now.
(GASPS)
(GASPING) No, no.
-(GASPING, WHIMPERING)
-Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's me.
Okay? Breathe. Breathe.
You're okay, right? You're shaking.
I... I thought I saw him.
Zoom, I thought I saw him right there.
It's just me, okay?
Look at me, he's not here. He's not here.
(EXHALES)
I see him everywhere.
Look, you literally just escaped
a psychopath who kidnapped you. All right?
So I think it's normal for you
to have a severe reaction like this.
This is so much worse than that.
I'm afraid all the time.
I don't think I can ever move forward.
(SCOFFS) You will.
When? Jay took everything from me.
My confidence, my trust, my sanity.
I don't think I'll ever be whole again.
(SCOFFS)
Of course, you will.
Promise.
OFFICER 1: (ON RADIO) Copy that, en route,
ETA four minutes, send backup, 442.
OFFICER 2: (ON RADIO)
Yes, code 50 on that 11-81.
We're gonna need 1013, backup for...
THE FLASH: Stealing is illegal, you know.
(CHUCKLES)
Detective West tells me
that you've been fighting Zoom's army
on your own.
Yeah, I wanna help.
I admire what you're trying to do,
but the best way to help
is to just leave this to the police.
Like you did?
I do have powers, Wally,
it is a little different.
(CHUCKLES)
This isn't your fight, it's mine.
No, it's all of ours.
This is my city, too, now,
and it's up to all of us to protect it.
Barry, we got a major meta-human alert
at Fifth and Main. Get there.
Fifth and Main, got it.
We'll continue this later.
(SIGHS) Why is it always so difficult
to choose?
-CISCO: Barry, what is it?
-It's...
Laurel Lance.
Laurel.
(LAUGHING)
Laurel Lance is dead.
On this Earth, anyway.
Poor Black Canary. Bye, bye, Birdie.
Earth-2 Laurel.
You knew her doppelgänger?
We didn't just know her, we loved her.
So, what do I call you?
You can call me Black Siren.
Zoom mentioned
that you might be showing up.
Well, if he told you what I can do,
you should look more afraid.
And so should you.
Tell me,
why did you take down Mercury Labs?
Because I like to watch things
crumble and fall.
Guess what.
You're next, Red.
(SCREECHING)
(FEEDBACK RINGING)
(GROANING)
CAITLIN: Barry?
-Are you okay, Barry?
-(EXHALES)
Look. Anything over 200 decibels
will kill a human.
-(FEEDBACK RINGING)
-(GROANING)
Was that too loud?
Perhaps, we should
quiet things down a bit.
(GRUNTING)
(THE FLASH GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
You know, the sad thing is,
I think Zoom's actually afraid of you.
I didn't think that he feared anything.
(BLACK SIREN CHUCKLES)
And you, you're hardly worth the chills.
How many metas did he send
to try and kill you?
Well, it's too bad,
he should have just sent me,
because that way,
you would have already been...
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
-(GASPS)
-Get in!
-(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
-Thought you might need a lift.
-Yeah, thanks.
You're welcome.
Why do so many villains
that we go up against
use sound as a weapon?
-What?
-Nothing.
-You're gonna be fine.
-Thanks.
So Wally just drove on up
into the thick of it?
Mmm-hmm.
Must have been some conversation
you two had.
Seeing as though he did
literally the opposite of what we wanted.
This I can hear.
It's not funny.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm in no laughing mood.
Look, Joe, I tried.
I told you I would try, right? I...
Wally's a determined kid.
Yeah, determined to get himself killed.
Or determined to help people.
And be glad or, you know,
I would not be standing here right now.
Well, he was lucky tonight.
I don't want to see the day when he isn't.
Yeah, we got more than luck
on our side, Joe.
You know you're not invincible, right?
Yes, of course, I know this.
(SIGHS) Joe's being overprotective,
but I get it.
Yeah, but it's like you think
that nothing can touch you.
Like nothing bad can get in your way.
That's not true for any of us.
What are you saying?
Look, I know that you had an experience
in the Speed Force.
And I'm happy that you think
that we're gonna win the day.
But I think a little fear
can be a healthy thing.
It helps you determine
which risks are worth taking.
I think that's something for both
you and Wally to take to heart.
BLACK SIREN: I met your little red friend
tonight.
Aren't you gonna ask me if I killed him?
You didn't.
You're good, but not that good.
And yet, I seem to be the only one
of your top lieutenants still standing.
Like I said, you're good.
So why don't you go knock down
a few more buildings? Like I ordered.
What's the point?
The point is so that it seems random.
That way, The Flash and his merry band
won't realize what I'm up to
until it's too late.
What are you up to?
No good.
-Ow!
-CISCO: Sorry.
-(BEEPING)
-Ow!
-(CHUCKLES) There we go.
-Are you kidding me with this?
-Hey, at least it works.
-Tremendous.
What is it, exactly?
It's just a small source of joy.
But more importantly,
it's how we're gonna stop Zoom's army.
By giving them all electro-shock therapy?
By giving them all
dimensional-shock therapy.
This is where I play stupid
and you explain the science.
Okay, fair enough. So, all matter vibrates
at its own unique frequency, right?
You disrupt that frequency,
you disrupt the matter.
Like how an opera singer shatters glass
with her voice.
Exactly. So, we found out
that all Earth-2 people vibrate
at their own, more erratic frequency.
HARRISON: Higher frequency.
-Different frequency.
-Higher.
-Higher frequency than we do.
-Right.
So, I ran this all past Hartley, right?
And he postulated that we could create
a sort of dimensional tuning fork. Voilà!
Okay, you didn't do it yourself.
-Just let me have this one, okay?
-HARRISON: All right, have it.
Thank you. So, if you run around the city
fast enough to create a refracting field,
the device can send out a pulse
that will bounce off of it, split apart,
and collide with itself over and over.
Amplifying it to an erratic frequency
on the Earth-2...
-Higher. Higher frequency.
-Higher frequency on the Earth-2 spectrum.
And when that pulse hits anyone
from Earth-2...
It'll disrupt their nervous system.
Earth-2 metas go night-night.
-Even Zoom?
-Even Zoom.
Harry and Jesse are from Earth-2.
How do we keep the pulse
from hurting them?
Detective, I didn't know you cared.
Yes, you did.
(CHUCKLES) Well, we designed these
headphones to protect us from the pulse.
-Beats By Wells.
-(HARRISON CHUCKLES)
(BEEPING)
Cisco, it's your meta-human alert app.
That's the high-rise development
on the west side.
Hundreds of people live there.
Ramon, we're up. Let's go.
Set that pulse off right now.
Allen, you need to start generating
that refracting field right now.
Black Siren could take down this building
at any point.
(STUTTERS) All those people, Wells...
How many more people are gonna die
while we wait?
(SIGHS)
Guys, which is it?
I think I just got
the worst idea of all time.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't think I've taken down
so many buildings at once.
WOMAN: Maybe you're not as powerful
as you think!
What are you two doing here?
Why should you have all the fun?
I thought you two were dead.
Zoom thinks that, too.
And we'd like to keep it that way.
For now.
You think you two can pull one over
on Zoom?
Well, enjoy being dead.
I told you.
Give her a chance.
What chance?
She's not ready.
BLACK SIREN: Excuse me.
Do you know what I'm capable of doing?
Try it and I'll shatter
your entire nervous system
without breaking a sweat.
Wow, you really think
you can take on Zoom.
We can.
You don't even know how powerful you are.
With a single call,
you can take down a building.
I'd call that impressive.
But why stop there?
Why serve a master
when you can be a master,
when you can be a god?
We could be gods.
-All right.
All right, we're synced up
with whatever the heck that thing is.
Finally, something we're both baffled by.
I'm kidding.
That, my friend, is a 75-KTSB,
40,000 watt reverberating sound amplifier,
designed to single out
the operating frequency
of every single Earth-2 being
on this planet,
which, when contained and magnified
by The Flash creating
a sound pressure wall around the city,
will render
all of us Earth-2 beings unconscious.
Hence, the safety precautions.
I'm baffled by it.
(CHUCKLES) Are we ready?
Yes, we are.
All right.
Here we go.
(BEEPING)
If I were interested
in forming an alliance with you two,
what's your plan, exactly?
We ambush Zoom at C.C.P.D.
With our three powers combined,
he'll be no match for us.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I like the sound of that.
Great. Then let's go.
There's just one more thing.
Reverb, catch.
(CHUCKLES)
You know, all doppelgängers,
they're mirror images of themselves.
But you two, you didn't know that,
did you?
Reverb is left-handed.
Well, I just... I just happened to
catch it with my right... Run!
(BEEPING)
Oh, no. What are we gonna do?
I don't think
that there's anything you can do.
What the what?
-(PANTS) I don't know.
-Well, do it again!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Cisco?
We're a go.
(VIBRATION RUMBLING)
There is nothing on this Earth
that can stop us!
(HIGH-PITCHED BEEPING)
It's working.
Ah!
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
Dad? Dad, it hurts.
(GASPING, CRYING)
-No, no, no, don't! (CRYING)
-It's okay. It's okay, honey.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)
-(GASPS)
(JESSE CRYING)
Turn it off, turn it off, it worked.
It's okay, it's okay.
We'll take care of him.
It's okay, Jesse, he's gonna be okay.
Barry, we did it. Bring them all in.
Copy that. I'm on cleanup.
What's that? I can't... I can't hear you
through the double-paned soundproof glass.
It's... It's kind of hard to make out
what you're saying.
So, should we tell Sara and Captain Lance
about her?
No. I've seen what interacting
with your family's doppelgängers can do,
and that's not even Laurel.
Nope, it's just a poor imitation.
Speaking of, that was a pretty good
Killer Frost you did back there.
Guess I was just in the right headspace
to play a cold, vicious killer.
How you doing? Are you okay?
No.
But I think I'm gonna be.
Being out there with you guys,
fighting meta-humans, and saving people?
It's the first time I felt normal
in a long time.
-Come here.
-(CAITLIN EXHALES)
This is a group hug moment.
-Yeah, get in.
-It is.
(LAUGHS)
So, all of Zoom's meta-humans
are locked up in Iron Heights?
Most of 'em. Some are somewhere else.
-I don't want to know.
-No, you don't.
And Zoom?
The metas we spoke to said Zoom
created a breach and escaped.
And how did he do that again?
Who knows? But he's back on Earth-2 now.
CAPTAIN: Earth-2?
Is that something else
I don't wanna know about?
-No.
All right. Well, Flash, thanks.
The man who saved Central City once again.
No, we're all just part of the same team.
Speaking of teams,
where the hell is Allen?
(GRUNTS) Sorry, man. Sorry.
Hey, heard my name.
-Uh, what's up?
-Good.
Well, you've got about 100 meta-criminal
cases to get through,
so I would get to cracking if I were you.
I will get right on that.
Captain.
-(SNICKERING) Well done.
-Thanks.
Listen, uh, I've been thinking
about Wally some more.
Are you gonna talk to him again?
-No, I'm not.
-Why not?
Because he's your son, Joe.
I know he's my son.
Look, no, what I mean is,
he's got your values.
He's got your inner drive
to help people do what's right.
We're supposed to think we're something
we're not until we become that thing.
That's the path that Wally's on.
I'm not gonna stop him from being the hero
that he's gonna become.
I really don't think you should, either.
I can't wait till you have kids
and they torture you.
-I'm gonna laugh in your face.
-(LAUGHS)
All right, gramps.
-Poppa.
-What?
My grandkid's gonna call me Poppa.
(LAUGHING) All right.
What in the world?
-What is this?
-CISCO: Blame Iris.
Okay, I just figured that since Henry
is officially back for good,
we should celebrate.
And since Zoom is gone
and the city is quiet right now.
I appreciate it, Iris. Thank you.
-Hi, Tina.
-DR. McGEE: Hello, Henry.
-Jesse. Hi.
-Hi.
-Good to see you.
-Good to see you, too.
-You look great.
-Thank you.
I hope you don't mind
that I invited Dr. McGee.
Seems like somebody's glad you did.
-Mmm-hmm.
-(CHUCKLES)
So, I guess you are invincible.
-Told you. The Speed Force is with us.
-Mmm. (CHUCKLES)
Since I'm feeling extra invincible lately,
what do you say you and I
give this a shot?
Yeah, I would like that.
So, is it true?
You saved The Flash's life?
Oh, I mean, I was just in the right place
at the right time.
Proud of you, Wally. You did good.
Thanks, Dad.
-(CHUCKLES)
-What?
Uh, I'm just... I'm proud of you, too.
-Soup's on.
-CISCO: Hey!
Taking out a city full of monsters
makes a man hungry.
First,
a toast.
-To family.
-ALL: To family.
That's my kind of toast, short and sweet,
let's eat.
(LAUGHING)
Oh. You guys. Great.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
It's Earth-2.
Cisco, what, what is it?
What'd you see?
What do you mean, see?
Cisco gets visions.
-I don't understand.
-What, Cisco?
Earth-2 splitting in half,
straight down through the poles.
Tell me I didn't just vibe the future.
Please, tell me I did not just see
the end of the world.
Our story continues, Flash.
-DR. McGEE: Henry!
-Oh, my God!
Dad? Dad?
(GASPS)
It's poetic,
returning to your childhood home.
Jay, don't do this.
All right? I'm begging you.
I'm begging you!
-Take me. Kill me.
-No!
You still won't believe me
that you and I are the same.
Come on, come on.
Barry, look at me, son. Look at me.
So, I'm gonna have to make you believe me.
Whatever happens,
you have made me the happiest father.
-Dad.
-This time,
you're gonna watch your parent die,
just like I did.
-No! No!
-And this is what's gonna make you
just like me.
-Your mother and I love...
-Jay!
No!