My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
...but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
Ronnie was vaporized
in the accelerator when it went critical.
Ronnie's alive. I saw him, Cisco.
Firestorm.
I wanted to talk to you about Firestorm.
We had some success
with our stage-one testing.
- Professor Stein...
- Professor Martin Stein?
He was our team leader.
I know what really happened to him.
In the mass of energy. Looks like...
Ronnie.
- And Professor Stein.
- The dark matter merged them together.
So how does a superhero
get ready for a date?
Same as everybody else.
All right.
Everyone tells you to just be yourself.
But who is that really?
You change one more time,
I'm gonna shoot you.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Punctual.
Ye... Yeah, that is what my
friends call me. Mr. Punctual.
Is that lonely-looking flower for me?
Is this dumb?
I thought about getting a full bouquet,
but I thought that was weird.
No.
It's awesome.
All right.
Mm.
Yes!
Victory.
I told you these were the spiciest tacos
in Central City.
- I thought you were bluffing.
- I never bluff.
Just say it.
I am the champion of all things spicy.
You are the spice champion of Central City.
Well, this requires soap and water.
- I'll be right back.
- Mm-hm.
H9)'-
Robbery at the convenient store
on Brand and Paulson.
Oh, man, come on.
I'm kind of on a date.
Can't the cops get this one?
Fine. But when you read
in the paper tomorrow...
...about that poor little old lady
getting robbed...
- How do you know it's a little old lady?
- Please. It's always a little old lady.
Okay. All right.
No little old lady.
Your move, Allen.
What's next?
So, what's wrong with you?
Why hasn't someone snatched you up yet?
Uh, it's work. Just a sec.
H9)'-
- Hello.
- Hey, I know you're on a date...
...but we got a jumper on 52nd and Waid.
Sir, please, you have
everything to live for.
No, I don't.
- Are you gonna let me go back up there?
- No.
Well...
"thanks.
Yeah.
- What was that for?
- To see if I wanted a second date.
And?
Let me see one more time.
Definitely.
Quentin Quale.
Can I help you, young man?
Haven't been called that
in quite some time.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
We went to school together.
- You're one of my students.
- No.
Classmates.
University of Chicago, class of '74.
We protested the war.
"Make love, not napalm." Remember?
Look, I don't know
if this is some kind of practical joke.
I know about your brother.
- The truth is, he committed suicide.
- What?
You found the body.
- I never told anyone about that.
- You've told one person.
Martin?
I need you to help me.
Dude, you're a crime-fighting,
lady-slaying machine.
Oh, God, it was so cool.
She was so cool.
- We're going on another date tonight.
- Tonight, really?
Aren't you worried about moving too fast?
No. What do you mean?
It's a second date.
No, no, no, I meant going too fast.
Hurrying?
Look, you're fast,
but there's fast, and then there's fast.
- Am I being subtle?
- Really not.
Cisc0's right. With your increased
blood flow and heart rate...
...theoretically,
your speed can cause you to...
You're gonna need to think
about a lot of dead puppies.
Like we're talking a whole kennel.
And baseball. Cold showers.
You know what? Nuns.
- It is just a second date.
- A second date?
With Who?
Uh, with Linda Park, the sports reporter.
- Hello.
- That's great.
Linda seems great, and you're great.
So great. Heh.
- Great.
- Hey, I gotta go. I gotta help out a friend.
- Everything okay? We just got here.
- Yeah. I'll see you later.
Quale was attacked near
his lab at Concordance Research last night.
There were several
unsubstantiated reports...
...of the so-called Burning Man in the area
following the attack.
Burning Man?
Caitlin, weren't you asking about him
a few weeks ago?
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
- Thanks for meeting me.
- Sure.
What exactly are we doing here?
That's Barry's old house.
Where his mother was murdered?
I have a theory about who might've
been involved in his mother's death.
Thought you and I
could re-examine the scene.
You could apply your expertise,
and help me prove who did it.
We should get Dr. Wells and Caitlin in
on this.
No, we should keep this between us. if too
many people know, Barry will find out.
I don't wanna involve him
until we know something definitive.
Hello, ma'am. I'm Detective West.
This is Cisco Ramon.
Please, it's Sherry. Like the drink.
- What can I do for you, detective?
- I don't know if you're aware...
...but there was a homicide
in this residence 15 years ago.
- Oh, I know.
- We've re-opened the investigation.
Do you mind if we come in
and take another look around?
Not at all.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hm.
- You live alone?
- Yes, I'm divorced.
Well, it appears letting Ronnie roam free
is no longer an option.
He's not even Ronnie anymore.
He's Martin Stein
walking around in Ronnie's body.
Like a vampire.
Is there a reason Stein's brain is in control
of Ronnie's body, not the other way around?
Simple Darwinism, I suspect.
A brand new organism will select the strongest
parts of itself in order to survive.
Survival of the fittest.
In this case, Ronnie's body, Stein's mind.
But any event, he badly hurt an innocent man
and we have hunted meta-humans for less.
Caitlin...
...we need to know that you're on board
with what needs to be done here.
How do we find him?
Quentin Quale...
...the scientist that Ronnie attacked
is a former colleague of Martin Stein.
If Martin is indeed in control
of Ronnie's body...
...he may be trying to figure out
what's happening to him.
What do we know about him?
I don't even know what Stein looks like.
Martin Stein.
- That's Stein?
- It is.
- I've seen him before.
- When?
On the train,
the day the accelerator exploded.
Super cool, isn't it?
Uh, S.T.A.R. Labs, I mean.
Yes, it's super cool.
Trust Harrison Wells to build
a particle accelerator with a bit of style.
Most scientists don't have an appreciation
for the value of aesthetics.
Albert Einstein said,
"Once you can accept the universe...
...as being something expanding into
an infinite nothing which is something..."
"Wearing stripes with plaid
comes easy."
I thought people your age didn't read
actual books anymore.
- I'm the only one.
- Oh.
Physics. Hobby or endeavor?
Both, actually.
I'm a CSI. I work for the
Central City Police Department.
Really? You look too young for that.
That is what they tell me.
Are you gonna watch the accelerator
turn on tonight?
I wouldn't miss it.
They say it's gonna change the world.
I hope so.
Carson Station. Carson Station.
This is my stop.
- It was nice talking to you.
- You too.
Maybe I will see you there tonight.
Excuse me.
I'm taking a girlfriend-Not my girlfriend.
She's just, uh...
Sorry.
She's a female friend.
Who I'm not dating. Yet.
- The doors are about to close.
- Yeah.
Bye.
Don't turn it on!
Don't turn it on! Don't turn...
Caitlin, whatever happens...
Of course I've heard of S.T.A.R Labs.
Martin was always vocal
about the competition.
S.T.A.R. Labs is helping
the C.C.P.D. looking...
...into your husband's disappearance,
Mrs. Stein.
Oh, please, call me Clarissa.
The Conway Prize
for Scientific Advancement.
Martin was very proud of that one.
Well, I always hoped to win
one of these myself.
Oh, and look at that,
he won it three times.
Takes a special kind of person
to make Dr. Wells jealous.
Martin had a talent
for making people jealous.
Even me.
I sometimes think Martin loved his theorems
and experiments...
...more than he did me.
I'm sure that's not true.
And you haven't heard from your husband
since he disappeared?
No.
Mrs. Stein, could I show you a photograph?
Have you seen this person before?
Yes, I have.
Who is he?
Um...
He's a person of interest
in your husband's case.
When did you see him?
I started getting the feeling
that someone was watching me.
Sometimes I still do.
And about a month
after Martin disappeared...
...that young man showed up here.
What happened to me?
It's a month...
Clarissa.
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
The loose stone,
you leave a key for me there.
I'm always losing my keys.
Losing my mind.
- I'm going to call the police.
- This isn't my body.
Where's my body?
I see my life but I can't reach it.
Please send someone.
There's an intruder in my house.
It appears Martin Stein and Ronnie Raymond
have something in common...
...besides sharing a body.
They both feel the need to protect
the women they love.
Clarissa said she feels like
she's being watched.
Well, then...
...this has all the makings of a stakeout.
But Barry's got a date tonight.
- I'll cancel.
- No. No, go.
If we need you here, something tells me
you can get back in a hurry.
I'm not picking up anything.
Not even with the super light.
Super light?
It's a multispectrum ultraviolet laser
enhanced scanner...
...that detects molecular schisms
in the 600-megavolt range...
...but I figured "super light"
was easier to say.
But what does it tell you?
Nothing we didn't already know
about that night.
Okay, keep looking.
Ahem. Uh, can I get you boys
something to drink?
Water? Soda?
Wine?
We're fine. Thank you.
Well, if you change your mind, I've been
told my strawberry daiquiris are sinful.
- I will not judge you.
- Okay...
Barry's mother's body was found here.
Knife beside her.
Blood spatter on the wall
belonged to Nora.
Joe, I think...
I just think maybe it's been too long.
And everything's different.
Except that mirror.
Sherry must've bought
it at the estate sale.
Oh, my God.
Silver nitrate.
The compound used in photography.
It was often used to back vintage mirrors.
If there were two speedsters there
that night...
...the sparks from their movement
would've generated enough flashes...
...to actually expose images
onto the silver nitrate.
- Are you saying what I think your saying?
- This mirror might contain photographs...
...of what actually happened that night.
Hey, you look great.
Well, I have a big date tonight
and I kind of wanted to impress the guy.
I think I can speak for that guy
and say that he is super impressed.
So this is your place?
It's awesome.
Yeah. Well, not entirely. I grew up here.
- Is it really lame, that I live at home?
- Mm, not at all.
- I still live with my parents.
- Really?
No. That would be so lame.
Ha, ha. All right, so here's the plan:
First, a dinner reservation at Paper Clip.
Then a round of mini golf.
Followed by Mal Duncan,
who's playing at an underground jazz club.
But my foster dad has connections there
so he hooked us up.
And if you're not sick of me by then,
we can get Froyo.
Or...
Want some of my fries?
No, thanks. Why would he come back here?
Because this is his home.
I don't mean the actual house.
I mean Clarissa. She's his home.
And we all wanna go home again.
Where we feel safe.
Where we feel loved.
Ronnie's your home.
Not anymore.
Remember what I told you on your first day
at S.T.A.R. Labs?
"A scientist's work is never finished."
His work is never finished. My work did
this to Ronnie, did this to Martin Stein.
But it's not finished, and it won't be...
...until we bring them both home.
So I'm assuming you have Barry
on speed dial?
Mm. Wow.
What's wrong? That felt amazing.
I just got a little excited.
- I would hope so.
- Sorry, Linda, I'm just, urn...
...a little worried about, urn...
...moving too fast.
It's okay. I hate slow.
Denying every tear
I'm sorry, I should check
just in case it's an emergency. Aah!
Okay.
I'm so sorry. It's important.
Not that this isn't important.
It's just that, um...
...this other thing is time-sensitive.
But otherwise there's no way
that I would be leaving you.
No one in their right mind would leave you.
Um, your shirt's on backwards.
Yeah, I got it. Okay.
I will text you, all right?
No, I'll call you. I'll call you.
Why don't I just... I'll just
do both, okay? I'll do both.
I'm so sorry.
Professor Stein.
Hey, I'm not here to hurt you.
And I know you don't wanna hurt
anyone else.
So if you could just not...
...flame on.
No!
Well, that was terrifying.
I sent Sherry to the movies.
Trust me, the best show in town
is gonna be in here tonight.
So you can get actual photographs
from this thing?
The science is solid.
It works exactly like an old film camera.
I developed the mirror backing,
and fortunately for us...
...the lightning went off
about 10 times that night.
- Multiple exposures.
- Now you're getting it.
I went ahead and enhanced them digitally,
and just for kicks...
...decided to extrapolate a 3D hologram
from the original 2D.
- Cisco.
- Lights...
...camera, action.
Wow.
Can you play it again, slower?
There, there. You see that?
Next frame.
This wallpaper is new.
Oh, man.
Is that blood?
We had a husband holding
the same weapon that killed his wife.
We weren't looking for any other suspects.
That blood belongs to one of the two
speedsters that was here that night.
Maybe the one that killed Nora.
I'll get a sample kit.
L 90'! you.
- That's great.
- Linda.
_H6Y-
- So I hope it's cool that I came by.
- Yeah, of course.
I was just writing a column
on the Combines.
Oh, sweet, how are they doing?
Well, they were up two goals to none
last night, but then they blew it.
Wait, we're not talking about
hockey anymore, are we?
No, we're not.
Look, I'm so, so sorry
that I left you like that.
I'm not that kind of guy.
Well, let me tell you
what kind of girl I am.
I work in a hard business
and I work hard in it...
...and so I'm very picky about who I choose
to spend my free time with.
I chose to spend some of it with you...
...so tell me, Barry Allen,
did I make the right choice?
Yeah, you did, it's just that
something important came up.
Not more important than you, just sort of an
equal-level-of-importance type situation.
And usually I can do both...
...but it's just that I have to, um...
I have to go to work. I'm so sorry.
It's a police emergency.
Can we talk later tonight?
I'm not going anywhere, yet.
Okay, thanks.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Sorry, gotta go. Uh, hey, what's up?
Bye. Ha, ha.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
- Yeah, sure.
- So...
...you and Barry are like BFFs, right?
The best of BFFs.
Has he ever actually dated anyone before?
Because he's simultaneously surprisingly
good at it, and really, really bad at it.
I don't know. He's Barry.
What was his last girlfriend like?
You know, he hasn't really had a girlfriend
in a while.
I don't know, maybe he's
just not ready yet.
What do you mean?
You know, I mean, he was into someone,
an unrequited-love thing.
You know, he had feelings for someone...
...and they weren't really
reciprocated, so...
Yeah, maybe just give him time.
Sure.
There he is. Looks like the tracker
Barry placed on him worked.
Professor Stein?
- I told you to stay away from me.
- And I will...
...but there's someone else
who wants to talk to you.
Martin?
Do you know who I am?
Clarissa?
- Is it really you?
- I don't know.
I hear the other inside of me,
and he wants to go home to her.
But we can't.
I just want to be me again.
Martin.
What's my favorite color?
You could... You could never decide.
So you chose stripes.
You shouldn't see me like this.
I see you.
I see you, Martin.
These people can help you.
They say they can.
Please, let them.
Please, help us.
Well, we got him... Them. Now what?
Stein clearly thinks he can separate himself
from Ronnie's body using nuclear fission.
- What do you think?
- What do I think?
Is it possible? Theoretically.
Splitting an atom and splitting a man
are two very different things.
I don't suppose it's necessary
to point out you're all staring.
Our apologies.
It is remarkable.
I feel clearer than I
have since the accident.
- What did you give me?
- A cocktail of antipsychotics.
Depressants, mood stabilizers.
The same formula used to treat
dissociative identity disorder.
I assume this was your idea?
Very clever, Cait.
Don't call me that, please.
I apologize.
We'd like to run some tests on you,
if you don't mind.
Of course, Dr. Snow.
Hey, I'm so sorry
I had to run out like that again.
I had police business.
That's funny. I just called the station. They
said that you'd taken some personal time.
I'm not mad, Barry, I swear.
- But I do think that we should call it.
- Wait, can we talk about this?
- What do you mean?
- I know how hard and weird it is...
...to date someone new
when you're still not over someone.
- What are you talking about?
- You and Iris.
Me and Iris? We're not...
Who told you that I was hung up on Iris?
- Hey. Um...
- Hey, what's up?
Why would you tell Linda
that I had feelings for you?
I did not say that. Wait, did I?
Okay, Iris, this isn't funny.
I like this girl.
- I know and I am happy for you.
- Really?
Because, I mean, right now,
it sort of feels like...
...you don't want to be with me, and you
don't want anyone else to be with me either.
I've wanted nothing more than
for you to meet someone amazing.
And I did, and you went out of your way
to convince her that I was unavailable.
Look, I'm really sorry.
- Great.
- Do you want me to talk to her?
No, no, no. Absolutely not. Don't talk
to her. I'll figure this out on my own.
I just need you to know that I don't
have those feelings for you anymore.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Yes, yes, yes.
See, we got two different blood samples.
- One for each speedster.
- That's right.
One is A-positive, and the other one's
AB-negative. Super rare.
I'll run them both through the C.C.P.D.
criminal database, see if I get a match.
Can you run them against a specific person?
Yeah, sure, if we have something
to match it to. Who are we looking at?
Dr. Harrison Wells.
I thought we were trying to solve
Barry's mom's murder.
We are.
And I'm asking you to keep this between us.
You think Dr. Wells killed Barry's mom?
No way. He didn't even know Barry then.
Why would he kill his mom?
I don't know yet.
But I do know that Wells keeps secrets.
And this may be one of them.
Dr. Wells is a great man.
I was nothing when he gave me a job,
a chance to change my life.
He has helped so many people.
He's not a murderer.
Cisco.
I'm a cop. I'm good at reading people.
So I know I can trust
you with my suspicion.
When I go talk to the family and friends
of a murder suspect...
...somebody I know is guilty...
...and I tell them the person they love
is a killer...
...guess what they all say.
"That's not the person I know."
I think I'm done being a cop for today.
Are you comfortable?
A little warm.
Ronnie used to always run warm.
Not that warm.
Can I talk to him?
Sorry, my dear,
I'm not sure it works like that.
I can feel him, though.
I have these memories.
Memories that I know aren't my own.
One is particularly strong.
Piedmont State Park,
it's famous for the Hudson Falls.
I know that I've never been, but I can
remember those waterfalls perfectly.
That's where Ronnie proposed to me.
He loves you very much.
That, I can feel.
Dr. Snow, can we see you for a minute?
Excuse me.
- You okay?
- Yeah, it's just confusing.
What isn't confusing
is what's happening to him now.
Ronnie's body is rejecting Stein's atoms
like a host rejecting a parasite.
The resulting instability
is causing an exothermic reaction.
I worry, if his temperature
continues to rise...
...it'll set off a chain reaction.
And then what happens?
He could go nuclear.
Ronnie.
Not Ronnie.
- Martin Stein.
- Cisco Ramon.
Your colleagues are in the next room,
not so subtly discussing my condition.
That's not freaky at all.
It seems Ronnie's fight with the Flash
has exacerbated the Firestorm matrix.
It's unstable.
It's exponentially increasing the rate
of fission inside his body.
How long does he have?
If his temperature keeps rising
at the current pace...
...no more than a couple of hours.
But you can fix it, right? I mean,
you can separate them before it's too late?
Any attempt we make to separate
the two of them could be catastrophic.
A nuclear explosion.
And a nuclear explosion of this magnitude
would level this entire city.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless the host body
were no longer functional.
You wanna kill Ronnie?
No, I don't wanna kill Ronnie.
But in this scenario,
Ronnie is the host body.
If you kill Ronnie, you kill Stein.
That's two people.
I don't know how else to stop it.
And my guess is
that if Ronnie and Professor Stein...
...knew the consequences that
we were all facing...
...they would make the same decision.
It's two lives for millions.
Can you give us a minute?
Caitlin...
I've already lost Ronnie once.
I'm not gonna do it again.
You said we have a couple of hours.
Use them.
Dr. Wells, you don't really
think we should kill Ronnie, do you?
Stay here, Cisco.
Hey.
Sorry.
Can I get you anything, or...?
A glass of Chateau Haut-Brion
Pessac-Leognan 1982 might be nice.
Or maybe it wouldn't.
This body's taste buds
would obviously be different from my own.
Perhaps I'm now a light beer man.
There are worse things to be.
You mean like a living nuclear bomb?
You know.
Unstable nuclear fission was always a
danger in the transmutation process.
Plus, you all argue very loudly.
I'm sorry.
But my friends are gonna figure out
how to fix this, I promise.
I remember meeting you, Mr. Allen,
on the train.
You were headed to S.T.A.R. Labs
with a girl, but not your girlfriend.
Yeah.
I'm not sure that I have any girlfriend.
You know, Einstein was
not only brilliant...
...he had a great sense of humor.
How did it go?
"Any man who drives safely
while kissing a pretty girl...
...is not giving the pretty girl
the attention she deserves."
If I learned anything this past year...
...life's too short not to live.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I gave you an out.
- I don't want an out.
I won't date someone who's
into someone else.
I'm not into anyone else.
I'll prove it to you.
This is a naga jolokia,
or the ghost pepper.
It is the world's hottest pepper, measuring
401.5 times hotter than Tabasco sauce.
If you do not agree
to go on another date with me...
...I will eat it, right here, right now.
You're bluffing.
I never bluff.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine, yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hm.
Yes, yes, I'll go out with you.
- That pepper could've killed you, nerd.
- Thanks. Mm.
Ugh. Thank you.
Okay, I won't let my job...
...or how bad my mouth is burning right now
come between us.
My Spice Champion of Central City. Ha, ha.
A crude weapon, if I may say so, Dr. Wells.
I couldn't agree more, Gideon.
But it Will do the job.
Gideon...
...can the tachyon prototype be converted
into a quantum splicer?
Theoretically,
but I must warn you, Dr. Wells...
...converting the tachyon prototype
will delay your timetable.
There's not gonna be a timetable if Central
City goes up in a mushroom cloud.
Hey, anything?
I have an idea. It's a bit of a Hail Mary,
but Cisco and I are gonna give it a try.
- Thank you.
- I'll get Professor Stein.
Looking for the professor?
Yeah, he's gone.
- You guys almost done?
- Hang on, hang on.
I found Stein. He's in the Badlands.
The middle of nowhere,
30 miles outside of Central City.
Minimum safe distance.
He's sacrificing himself.
How much time does he have left?
Twelve minutes.
And we're done.
- What is it?
- This is a quantum splicer.
- Will it work to separate them?
- We'll know in 12 minutes.
Now, Barry, even you
can't outrun a nuclear blast...
...so you get this device to Professor Stein
and you get out of there as fast as you can.
- What are you doing?
- Going with you.
- No, you're not.
- It's too dangerous.
Barry doesn't know how
to operate the splicer.
- Cisco's gonna talk me through it.
- There's not enough time. Let's go.
Go.
What was that?
Uh, comm system's on the fritz.
I'll be right back.
- Cisco.
- I'm not proud of it but I ran the samples.
- One wasn't identified. The other had a match.
- Cisco, you're hesitating.
- Was it Wells?
- No, it's not Dr. Wells.
I told you, he has nothing to do with this.
But I know whose blood it is.
It's Barry's.
We already know
Barry was there that night.
No, no, no, you don't understand.
The sample had high levels of P-16, a protein
that builds up in the blood as we get older.
And these levels were way too high
for an 11-year-old.
This sample was from Barry as an adult.
Professor Stein!
What are you doing here? You can't be here!
Get her out of here now!
Please, look,
Ronnie's still in there somewhere.
All those people.
Clarissa, I won't let them die.
It's better I end this now.
We can separate you!
We can stop the explosion.
- How?
- A quantum splicer.
It's a fission device
designed to bombard your atoms...
...with as much energy as they experienced
in the particle accelerator explosion.
It should be enough to separate you.
Please, professor,
you have nothing left to lose.
Ronnie, if you're in there...
...I love you.
That was from him.
I look forward to meeting you
in person, professor.
It's not working.
- He's not gonna make it. He's gonna blow.
- Get out of there. Barry, get out of there now.
- Oh, no. No, no!
- Caitlin, we have to go.
Run!
No!
Sir, we have a thermonuclear detonation...
...approximately 30 miles northeast
of Central City.
Deploy the Rapid Response Team, sergeant.
Bring me Firestorm.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org