CAITLIN: Previously on The Flash...
Four years from now,
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
This is the Speed Force bazooka.
And that's gonna trap Savitar?
I know what you are.
You're a Time Remnant.
You all shunned me
because I wasn't the true Barry Allen.
I was an aberration.
How did you become Savitar?
I was broken and alone.
God feels no pain.
All I had to do was become one.
Iris?
You know what I'd love right now?
Anything you want.
Caviar.
- Caviar?
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay. Well, it's just a little late,
so it might be hard for me
to find a place that's open that has it.
But I'll find an assortment.
Thank you.
Just stay with me, okay?
The whole team's working on this.
And we can accomplish a lot in 24 hours.
I know we can.
I'm fine, Barry. Really.
Get some caviar.
Okay.
Hi, Barry.
Um...
There's something
that I need to say to you.
Hey, Cisco.
What?
Where?
All right, I'll come pick you up.
- What is it?
- Uh...
Really good news.
BARRY: Lyla.
CISCO: Hey.
Gentlemen.
- It's a wee bit chilly.
- Yeah.
Want to take this inside?
Every square inch
of that building is bugged.
- Figured it was better to talk out here.
- Okay.
- I love the breeze on days like this.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So I got your message,
but you're gonna have to run me
- through exactly what you need again.
- Yeah.
- So we're building a cannon...
- Right.
Bazooka thing. It's a sort of trap.
In order to turn it to on,
we need something to power it,
something extremely powerful
and regenerative.
Okay.
Yeah, so I tasked our satellite to look
for anything that might have
our specific power requirements.
And wouldn't you know it,
we found something
that has exactly what we'll need,
and it's right there
in that building.
Crazy, huh?
I really don't think
you should be spying on me, Cisco.
Is it spying if we're friends?
But he's right, isn't he?
You have something, don't you?
It's a piece
of the Dominators' technology.
LYLA: We got it from the ship
that crashed in Central City.
- That's great.
- You can't have it, Barry.
What?
Lyla, we've searched everywhere.
This tech is the only thing
that we can use.
I can't do it.
Is this because of Baby Sara?
Look, I'll admit.
It's been hard not to wonder
what it would've been like
to have a daughter instead of a son,
but this is less about what happened
than why it happened.
- I made a big mistake.
- Exactly my concern.
Barry, this is the kind of tech
that wars are fought over.
If something happens, and it gets
into the wrong hands, people could die.
Millions.
And, frankly, I don't know
if I can trust you to have it.
GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL: Director Michaels?
I've got to go.
Lyla, if we don't use this,
Iris is going to die.
Tonight.
I'm sorry, Barry.
I can't help you this time.
You'll have to find another way.
JOE: Are you serious?
BARRY: Yeah.
Yeah, if Lyla won't let us have
the Dominators' tech,
then we're gonna break into A.R.G.U.S.,
and we're gonna steal it.
Wally and I will phase through the walls.
We'll be in and out of there
before anyone even gets off a shot.
Uh, hello? No, you won't.
- Yeah, we...
- What is that?
CISCO: That is
a meta-human power dampener,
and it's all over the building,
so you can't use your powers inside.
Can we use anything else
to power this Speed Force gun?
- "Speed Force bazooka."
- Bazooka.
Nothing else.
Manipulating extra-dimensional energy
requires, well,
ridiculous amount of energy.
And the Dominator tech's
the only thing that can do that.
Yeah, I have an idea, gang.
What if we just put you, put Iris, on
a plane to Paris or somewhere far away?
No, there's nowhere on Earth
that Savitar wouldn't find her.
Guys, stealing this Dominators' tech
is our only option, all right?
Barry, A.R.G.U.S. is more secure
than the Pentagon.
If your powers don't work in there,
how are you going get past security?
Okay, this is what we're dealing with.
- Surveillance cameras. Eye scans.
- I'm out. No.
- Palm prints. Heat sensors.
- Oh!
H.R.: What?
CISCO: Laser sensors.
They really thought of everything,
didn't they?
- That's just the first floor.
- So you're saying
this is the most fortified structure
in the history of fortified structures.
They can't use their superpowers,
and we have less than 14 hours
to steal the thing.
And none of us are master thieves.
No.
No, we're not.
Hello, Flash!
I need your help.
Barry Allen, the hero of Central City.
This is Siberia in the year 1892.
We're a little out of your jurisdiction.
Yeah, hear me out.
I want to recruit you for a mission.
I'm already helping
a bunch of idiot do-gooders.
Sorry, I'm up to my fuzzy hood
in teamwork.
Would it help if I said please?
No. And you already have a bunch
of superhero types in your life.
Why ask me?
Well, you have a particular set of skills.
Great movie.
Last time we tried to be buddy-buddy,
it didn't work out so well for you.
Why trust me now?
Spit it out,
or I'm going to step onto that ship
and pretend like this conversation
never happened.
Iris.
- Oh, girlfriend.
- Fiancé.
Mazel tov.
What about her?
If you don't help me, she's gonna die.
True love. That's your pitch?
It's all I've got.
And I assume saving your girlfriend
requires us doing something
less than lawful?
We need to break into A.R.G.U.S.
and steal an alien power source.
The Flash, a thief.
That's my kind of mission. One condition.
My rules.
Your rules.
H.R.: I know we don't have a plane.
We steal a plane, okay?
We'll put it back, all right?
And we parachute out of the plane.
We land on the roof.
Got to land on the right roof, all right?
And then...
Right down the air ducts,
Mission: Improbable style.
- Easy.
- Easy?
- Yes.
- What about the counterterrorism missiles?
- What?
- Yeah.
Hello, Joe, Cisco, Iris.
I love the ice. Sparkly.
Captain Cold?
Snart, what the hell are you doing here?
Snart's going to help me break
into A.R.G.U.S., get the power source.
Huh?
Awkward. I can see
you all have a lot to talk about.
I'll be down in your lab,
getting everything ready.
Barry, are you out of your mind?
- I thought he was with the Legends.
- He is.
- No, he dead.
- Well, I...
- You time-traveled again?
- Yeah.
That's what got us
in this mess in the first place.
I thought you said
you would never do that again.
I also said I would do whatever it takes
to save you.
That hasn't changed.
And I'm pretty sure you all feel
the same way, too. Right?
Look, I'm not changing time.
I will put him back right where I found
him, after we get what we need.
Fine. You say we need Snart's help,
we need his help.
So what's the plan?
What are you doing?
Flash damaged my suit in our fight.
Pretty badass. Very godlike.
Well, dress for the job you want.
We're a team, right?
Barry and Caitlin at it again.
You're not Caitlin.
And I'm not Barry.
FROST: You sure
you're gonna go through with this?
- What?
- Killing Iris.
You're gonna take her to lnfantino Street
and ram a metal spear through her back?
Well, it's either her or me.
If she doesn't die, I'm never born.
Right. But behind
that pretty little face of yours,
you still remember
everything that Barry does.
So you remember growing up with Iris,
falling in love with her, kissing her.
You sure you're ready to end her life?
What I remember
is being created as a disposable life.
Something to be thrown away
when Barry Allen was done with me.
He didn't care about me.
Why should I care about his love?
You're not having second thoughts,
are you?
Good.
Because you know what you need to do.
And when the time comes,
I expect you be ready.
What is it?
Barry went back in time
to get Snart's help
with stealing the power source
from A.R.G.U.S.
Power source? For what?
Uh...
It doesn't matter.
- Well, should I stop them?
- SAVITAR: No.
Let them take it.
No speed gun can stop a god.
My guess is the power source
is most likely here.
Why there?
Because it's the deepest part
of the facility.
And if it's as valuable as you say it is,
then the deepest recesses of any facility
are usually the most secure.
- Mmm. Smart, Snart.
- "Smart, Snart."
I'm gonna keep hacking away
and find out for sure.
Do you have any idea
what else might be down there?
Doesn't matter. There are only four rules
you need to remember.
Make the plan. Execute the plan.
Expect the plan to go off the rails.
Throw away the plan.
Follow my lead, and you'll be fine.
I'm trusting you.
We all are.
Just don't sit me at the singles table
at the wedding reception.
JOE: Just out of curiosity,
you have a plan for getting in there?
I've got that covered.
Oh! Hold that for a second, yeah? Okay?
Okay. And don't look.
- What?
- Hey!
Flash, superhero cowl on, please?
We've got civilians in the house.
It's okay, H.R.
We're trusting Tracy with our lives.
- We can trust her with this.
- Good point.
Yeah.
- Okay. I'll put my hands down now.
- Okay.
Oh!
- Totally should have figured that out.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Carry on.
- All right.
Okay.
All right, Joe, I need you to take Iris
someplace far away from here.
- Far away from me.
- Barry...
I can't know where.
If I know, then Savitar knows.
I'll get Wally. We'll keep her safe.
Don't worry.
So here we are.
This is not goodbye.
Yeah.
Look, I know you're gonna do
whatever it takes to save me.
But don't lose yourself
in the process, okay?
- Hello.
- Harry.
HARRISON: Kid, Joe, Iris.
What brings you folk
to this section of the multi-verse?
- What's that?
- It's how much time we have left.
Before what?
Before we lose.
We're prepping the chopper
for San Francisco now.
Copy that, sir.
Director Michaels, I thought you were
en route to San Francisco.
Plan's changed. I received
an unexpected gift from the Flash.
- Captain Cold.
- Always nice to meet a fan.
- I'm taking the prisoner to lockup.
- Of course. We'll just need your ID.
Spent so much time
on that A.R.G.U.S. fake ID.
The thing's a masterpiece.
And your eye scan?
You boys really dot the I's
and cross the T's.
Finally, Director Michaels,
"Elvis. Banana."
- What the hell?
- Search me.
"Elvis. Banana." It's word association.
Barry must have to come up with
the next correct words in the sequence.
- Peanut butter. Bacon.
- Yeah, Kevin Bacon.
TRACY: Mellow yellow.
H.R.: James Brown. Split.
Okay! Barry, you're gonna have to stall.
I repeat, ma'am. "Elvis. Banana."
My, my, my.
Getting rather violent in your young age.
Yeah, what were you doing?
- Magic.
- Neat trick.
It was a neat trick yourself.
Transmogrifier from H.R.'s Earth.
Here you go.
Cisco, where to next?
Okay, you will take the... East elevator?
They should take the west elevator.
- I agree with Tracy.
- Barry, take the west elevator.
I used to watch you do that as a kid.
I thought you were so cool.
What'd I tell you?
Guns aren't cool.
They're just for protection.
Right.
Dad, look, I know
this is hard for everyone,
but I feel like it's hardest for you.
Dad, can I tell you something?
Yep.
When I was 16, um,
Barry and I switched rooms
so that I could sneak out of the window
past curfew.
- It's true.
- Wait a minute.
You...
You told me that it was because Barry
didn't like the noise from the street.
Yeah, no.
But, in my defense,
my curfew was 8:00 p.m.
- Yeah, I was a little strict.
- A little?
Okay, since...
Since we're confessing,
remember when I told you guys
that we couldn't eat out for a month
because I was saving money for yours
and Barry's college tuition?
Yeah?
I took some of that money,
and I went on a blues cruise.
Junior Walker was playing.
It was just for three days.
- Dad.
- Mmm.
Oh, that reminds me. What, um...
What was that song
you used to sing all the time?
You don't remember?
I don't remember.
♪ What Does It Take! ♪
♪ What Does It Take. ♪
♪ I tried, I tried, I tried, I tried ♪
♪ - In every way I could ♪
♪ To make you see how much I love you ♪
♪ I hope you understood ♪
- I love you.
- I love you too, Dad.
Take this for me, please.
Just in case.
Make sure you give it back to Barry.
Okay.
Who's Grodd?
Telepathic gorilla.
Spared his life on another Earth
so he could invade Central City.
That's what mercy gets you.
This must be
where Waller kept her Suicide Squad.
I think this is it. Come on.
Cisco, we found it.
CISCO:
Barry? Barry, can you hear me?
Cisco?
Barry, are you talking? Barry?
Hey, Cisco, can you read me?
Loud and clear.
Hey, uh, so we found it.
Jackpot!
But there seems to be some kind of signal
interference at the end of the hall.
And the lock is the Montgomery 3000.
- Montgomery 3000.
- What, is that bad?
Well, we're looking at a 25-ton door
that can withstand
a 30-megaton nuclear blast.
And aside from being
completely bomb-proof,
the Montgomery 3000 can only be
unlocked by a voice recognition system
necessitating three different pass codes
from three different people.
And as if that weren't already enough,
the thing costs $10 million to build.
Thirty-seven seconds.
I must be out of practice.
Well, A.R.G.U.S. should ask
for their money back.
Wait! Make the plan. Execute the plan.
Expect the plan to go off the rails.
Seen a lot of things,
but a half-man, half-shark takes the cake.
I can't believe A.R.G.U.S. turned
King Shark into a guard dog.
"King Shark." That's adorable.
- Give me your Cold Gun.
- So you can do what exactly?
Snart, there's only one way
that tech's getting out of here.
Oh, I see.
You didn't just recruit me for my skills
as a thief, did you?
You wanted a partner who wouldn't mind
if you got all murdery.
I told you what I'm up against, all right?
Give me the gun.
Open the door.
Open the door!
LEONARD: Have you seen Shark Week, Barry?
Me, I can't get enough of it.
Good thing the Waverider has cable.
What's your point?
Most sharks are cold-blooded,
but the great white shark,
like our friend in there,
is partially warm-blooded.
He's susceptible to cold.
Never strays into water colder
than 53.6 degrees Fahrenheit.
If we lower the temperature
in that room to 53.5 degrees,
King Shark should fall asleep
like a little baby.
Or you can go ahead and kill him
and prove what a badass you are.
Your choice.
Throw away the plan.
Tracy Brand. You know,
it's moments like this I'm reminded
that S.T.A.R. Labs is so much more
than a haven for beautiful minds. It's...
- It's a miniature Jitters.
- It's a... Oh, yeah!
Raspberry and coriander.
Mmm.
- Yes, it is. It's a home, is what it is.
- Yeah.
You know what? It's my home.
It's my... It's my family, although I...
You know what? I will say, it...
I have to tell you that
I haven't always felt I belong completely.
- What?
- Yeah.
I'm lacking a clear sense
of purpose sometimes.
- But then you arrived.
- I did? Oh, yeah, I did.
No, yeah, you did. Here you are, yeah.
And with you here,
I understand my purpose.
It's us. You and me,
that meeting of the mind that we have,
it's just so powerful...
- But H.R., you're from another Earth.
- Yeah, it's...
And I'm an unemployed
former grad student who...
Come work at S.T.A.R. Labs with me, okay?
I mean, it doesn't pay much.
- How much?
- It pays next to nothing.
But you know what? It wouldn't matter.
We'd be together.
Imagine, me inspiring you,
and you applying that inspiration,
and us changing the world together
and drinking so much coffee.
Tracy Brand, will you do me the honor
of joining Team Flash?
With you? I'd love to.
By all means, you first.
Thanks.
Reminds me of Jaws.
They didn't show the shark because
they couldn't afford to make it look good.
How long do you think he'll stay asleep?
I like Shark Week.
I'm not a marine biologist.
Move!
- Snart!
- Barry!
This place is going to be crawling with
A.R.G.U.S. agents in the next two minutes.
Look on the bright side, Barry.
This is your chance
to show how ruthless you really are.
Sometimes, you've got to make
a tough call, Barry.
Cisco!
We need your help!
BARRY: I have the energy source,
but Snart's trapped inside the cell
with King Shark.
You've got to open the door.
I can't hack through the mainframe!
Hurry, all right?
Cisco's working on it.
Whatever you do, don't look behind you.
If Cisco saves my life, tell him
I'll put in a good word with my sister.
Come on.
CISCO: Bam!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
- I got you!
- Barry!
- I got you! I got you!
Hang on.
Slam the door, Cisco, now! Close it!
Ouch.
Been there.
Okay.
Flash!
Let's get out of here.
BARRY: Lyla.
Barry.
- I told you I couldn't give this to you.
- Yeah.
- And you snuck in here anyway?
- To save Iris's life, Lyla.
Yeah, I'll do anything.
Not anything.
I saw the whole thing
on the security monitors.
You could've left Snart to die.
But you risked your freedom
and iris's life to save him.
You're just gonna let me have it?
I couldn't let Iris die, knowing that
that could save her.
And I know you'd do the same thing for me
if it were John's life on the line.
Thank you.
Now go. Do it.
And get this guy back
to wherever he belongs.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Tell me, Snart, did you think
I had it in me to leave you behind?
I wasn't sure.
I've always known you had the potential
to be as ruthless as they come.
Your history made sure of that,
same as mine.
Who knows? Maybe that's why we get along.
You see the good in me.
I see the bad in you.
Maybe.
Piece of advice. Stop trying
to beat Savitar at his own game.
Your goodness is your strength.
Call me sentimental.
I think the Flash should remain a hero.
Take care of yourself, Snart.
No strings on me.
We did it. We got the Dominator tech.
- Yes! Yes!
- Where's Iris?
Uh, Iris, safely stashed away
on Earth-2 with old Harry Wells.
No.
Barry! Savitar knows where Iris is!
Savitar's coming.
- What?
- HARRISON: Now, Joe.
Iris, stay behind me. He gets to you
through my dead body. Harry, Wally!
Yeah.
I got him.
Oh, god, it's really true.
Yes, it is.
Aim that gun at me, and I'll kill you.
Listen to me.
- You were my son once.
- Oh.
Whatever I did to make you feel this way,
I'm sorry.
Please, Barry.
No.
That's not my name.
- Barry...
- That's not my name!
IRIS WEST: Please, stop, okay?
I will go with you.
Just, please, do not kill them.
I'm not gonna kill them now.
They need to watch you die first.
- Baby, no.
- Dad, it's okay.
Oh, look, Joe, she's accepted her fate.
You should, too.
He took her.
He...
- I'm sorry, Barry. I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
No, it's not. It's not okay, Barry.
I should have been there for her.
I should have protected her.
You did everything you could, all right?
You trusted me, and I let you down.
- Listen to me. Listen to me.
- I let you down.
There is no way
you could ever let me down.
You've become the hero
I always knew you could be.
I'm gonna go get our girl back, all right?
Thanks.
- B.A., I'm so sorry. I screwed up.
- It's okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- So what now?
Now we go to Infantino Street.
We know exactly where Savitar
is gonna be and when.
Is the bazooka ready?
I've loaded the power source
into the device,
which should deliver
the necessary amount of energy
to trap Savitar in the Speed Force.
I'll be on standby in case it fails.
It won't fail. It won't fail. It's ready.
We didn't have that the last time.
So we have the upper hand now.
All right,
you guys figure out what your plan is.
I can't be here to know any of it.
You know where I'll be.
Gauntlets, check. Goggles, check.
Superpowers, check.
Locked and loaded.
- Don't stress. Tracy's bazooka.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna work.
- Tracy's bazooka.
- Yeah, you helped.
- I didn't... I didn't...
- I didn't help.
- Yes, you did! You inspired her.
I didn't inspire her.
I didn't do anything inspiring.
You know what's inspiring? Barry.
A hero among heroes. You're all heroes,
and you've all given me so...
So much, you know?
You've given me a home.
You've given me a purpose.
Now, you've lead me
to the woman that I adore,
that I want to spend my future with.
And through it all, what have I done?
What have I done?
What have I contributed, except...
Some fair-to-middling drumming
and lead Savitar directly to Iris?
- That's not fair.
- It's not fair?
It's not fair for you to say.
Savitar tricked us.
"Us"? Me.
I'm the one who opened his big fat mouth,
and now we're all in trouble,
and especially Iris
- 'cause I couldn't keep my mouth shut!
- Hey!
That could've happened to me, okay?
Easy. I mean it.
That could've happened to me.
That could've happened to any of us.
H.R.
- You're gonna hold down the fort?
- Yeah.
CISCO: Of course you are.
'Cause that's what you do.
You show up. You're ready,
dependable when we need you the most.
- You hear me?
- I hear you.
- All right.
- Till next time.
Oh, Cisco, time for a little chat.
Cisco?
- I just had a vibe.
- What? What did you see?
Killer Frost. I saw this coming.
What are you talking about?
Ever since Caitlin got powers,
I've had vibes of us fighting in a forest.
This whole time, I've been fighting it.
I didn't want to face the fact
that, one day, she'd be this far gone.
Then go now,
keep her from making
the biggest mistake of her life.
And what about you?
You're gonna need my help.
Savitar won't be with her right now.
This our best chance to help her.
Go save Caitlin. I'll save Iris.
NEWSCASTER: In other legal news,
the highly publicized
trial of Jared Morillo, a.k.a. Plunder,
comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty of grand theft
and aggravated assault
after he was caught by Kid Flash
robbing the Central City Museum
earlier this year.
Please don't fail. Please don't fail.
Everybody, stay on alert.
Here we go.
I know you're here!
Come out and face me like a woman!
FROST: I didn't think you'd actually show.
That's 'cause you don't know
anything about me
or Caitlin, for that matter.
Savitar's right.
In order to join him as a god,
I have to cure myself of Caitlin.
This has to happen.
I don't want to fight you.
I don't wanna fight you, either.
I want to kill you.
SAVITAR: Flash, this is it.
Now the moment is upon us,
my ascension to become a god.
Not tonight.
Show me you're the hero.
Let's see what happens.
I'm gonna stop you.
It's working.
Why didn't...
It didn't work.
Why didn't it work?
I spent an eternity
in a trap just like that.
You think I didn't know how to prevent it
from happening again?
The Philosopher's Stone.
It's made of calcified Speed Force energy.
And you gave it to me.
- Guys! Guys!
- I failed.
Joe!
You stuck me in the Speed Force
for an eternity of hell.
Now, welcome to yours.
No! Don't do this.
Don't do this.
Now, finally, I am free of you.
- Barry!
- I'm begging you. Just...
- You lose, Barry.
No!
IRIS WEST: Hi, Barry. Um...
There's something
that I need to say to you.
I love you.
And if something happens,
I need you to hear this.
I, Iris Ann West,
take you, Bartholomew Henry Allen,
to be my lawfully wedded husband,
to have and to hold from this day forward
in sickness and in health,
to love and to cherish
until death do us part.
THE FLASH: No!
Iris. Iris.
Iris.