Dad?
Nora?
How are you...
Don't worry, Dad.
I know we've been through a lot,
but everything's gonna work out
like it's supposed to.
I promise.
It's really you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
We've missed you so much.
Iris, hey.
This is gonna sound crazy, but...
I think we're pregnant.
This must be why
you're feeling so sick. You know?
And since meta-DNA signatures
can misrepresent hCG levels,
I gotta...
Hey, do you know where my keys are?
I gotta drive these samples
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Otherwise, the chemical integrity
could be compromised.
Of course. Right here.
I'll call you
as soon as I know the test results.
- Cecile. Hey, what are you doing here?
- Oh, hey.
I have a file that Iris needed
for the Kord case. Is she in?
No, she is... at work already.
Isn't that her work computer
right there?
Yes, it is.
But she's been more of a pen and
paper kind of reporter lately.
You know, old-school.
You're feeling very nervous.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
You're feeling nervous and excited.
Ecstatic, even.
Barry, what's going on?
I'm just running late for work.
It makes me kind of nervous and ecstatic
'cause I love my job.
So... And I'll make sure she gets this,
and I'll see you later.
Hey, I thought
we were having lunch today.
- Us?
- Yeah.
Oh, uh...
Our monthly Tuesday lunch date.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
No, I'm really looking forward to that.
As always.
This is just a bag of protein bars.
Speedster metabolism.
I'm always hungry. So...
- See you later. Bye.
- Okay, I...
Clink your glasses
Melt the eyes like ice
Raise your glasses
Melt the thighs like ice
Clink your glasses
Hot flashes
You weren't ready for it to...
Girl, you getting your art mojo on.
I can dig it.
Ooh. Okay, well, my bad.
I did not mean to disturb
the artist at work,
but a friend of yours
is out and about.
Who, Mark?
Yeah, and I just figured
it was something you should see.
Why? What do you know?
Caity told you everything, didn't she?
No, I just remembered you two fought
at that bar the night you got arrested.
Yeah, and again
the night of the Force Storm.
Well, says here that he handed in
state's evidence and got parole.
So maybe he's turning
over a new leaf.
Like Captain Cold.
Uh-uh. I don't buy it. Not for a second.
I'm just waiting
till he shows his true colors,
and then I'm gonna kick his butt
right back to Iron Heights.
Sounds kind of like
you're gonna stalk him or something.
You know, like watch his every step.
That would be crazy.
Great idea, Chester.
Wait, what?
No, I said that sounds like it's crazy.
I said "crazy," right?
You're a damn good detective.
You dug up more on Operation Griffin
in one week than I did in years.
And I hit the same dead end.
So, the last we saw your perp,
Warrant Officer Adam Creyke,
was on a security camera
stealing five M18 Claymore mines
from the barracks armory.
Which he used to eliminate my unit.
One thing I don't get...
The explosive output and close proximity
of five Claymores?
That would have been lethal.
Creyke would've known that.
How did you survive?
Honestly, I have asked myself
that same question over and over.
Well, what exactly do you remember
about the attack?
Fragments.
Just screams, mostly.
The heat of the explosion.
Adam's eyes.
Somehow I could tell
he knew he'd survive.
Thanks to whatever
his damn meta ability is.
Creyke was like
a brother to you. What...
What drove him?
Adam and I are both
Wet'suwet'en First Nations.
Adam loved open waters.
He wanted to join the Navy
but followed me into the Army.
Said he didn't trust anyone else
to look out for me.
I had an uncle who used to take me
fishing every summer on a schooner.
Sailors take naming their vessels
as seriously as they
name their firstborn.
Did Adam have a callsign?
- Yeah. Rasputin.
- Rasputin.
Yo. A schooner named Rasputin
is registered in Midway City
six weeks after Operation Griffin.
He's been a few hours away
this whole time.
There's no way in hell
I'm letting him get away again.
Kramer.
What are you gonna do when you find him?
This has to be about justice.
If this is gonna be about vengeance,
you can do this by yourself.
Lead the way.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Did you drive here?
What's up, party person?
Yo!
So, why's the Flash driving a car?
Oh, wait, do you have a Flashmobile?
No. It just isn't safe
to zoop these samples.
Samples for what?
Blood and urine.
For my annual physical with Caitlin.
Who's my GP.
Right. Isn't it kind of weird
to have a teammate as your doctor?
No.
I mean, it was at first,
but it's cool now.
I should get to the med lab.
Hey, good luck, 'cause Caitlin's in
there running a medical consult with...
Ultraviolet.
- Oh.
- I guess she accidentally
double-booked your appointments.
Yeah.
- Catch you later.
- Not if I catch you first.
- I get it. 'Cause you're fast, right?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
- That's... Yeah.
Iris, Caitlin's in the med lab,
and we don't want anyone to know yet
until we're sure.
Yeah, you're right.
My lab at C.C.P.D. has everything I need
to create a neutralizing
meta-gene variant
that'll track your hCG levels.
All right, Thanks. Love you, too. Bye.
What did they do to me?
Black Hole introduced
a deliberate irregularity
into your vascular system.
One that creates a 40% decrease
in your body's ability
to maintain oxygen intake.
They made it so the mask
keeps her alive to ensure her loyalty.
Actually, the mask is hiding
the real damage.
Implantation circuitry
grafted to your vocal cords.
Okay.
How do we help my cousin?
So, the software in the chip requires
regular software updates,
just like your smartphone.
But no Black Hole means
no more software updates.
So, pretty soon it'll stop working,
and I won't be able to repair it.
Caitlin thinks she has
a way to fix this. Permanently.
Right. It's risky,
but I think I can repair the damage.
It doesn't matter. I won't do it.
I'll leave you two alone.
Esperanza.
Why won't you let Caitlin operate?
Will you trust me?
I know this team.
I've fought with them,
suffered losses alongside them.
They're good people.
So, if Caitlin thinks
she can help you, let her.
I don't need help.
Unlike you, I don't fear dying.
Maybe so.
Look, I get it.
Surgery is how this nightmare
started for you.
But Caitlin isn't Black Hole.
It's my life, not yours.
Then why am I the only one
who gives a damn about it?
Don't you get it?
This isn't about saving Ultraviolet.
It's about saving Esperanza Garcia.
Mi familia.
You boys really know how to throw
a welcome home party.
Yeah, well, the only rats welcome here
are the ones in the kitchen.
That's funny
coming from you, punk.
Leave.
Now.
Snowflake.
As always,
you have perfect timing.
So what happened?
Came to ask your old boss
for your job back?
- Didn't go so well?
- That...
plus something about,
"snitches get stitches."
Ah. No one's buying this whole
"turned over a new leaf" crap.
Look...
You ready for that dinner date yet?
I mean...
I should probably be a gentleman
and change first.
Whoa, whoa.
Come on.
I'm taking you to Danville General.
No.
They're probably still pretty upset
about the CAT scan machine
that I sabotaged a few years back.
Okay, fine. Leawood Med, then.
I kinda blew up their bio-chem lab.
Okay, um...
Fine. There is a shady vet
down on Fairview. He won't ask...
Dr. Haley.
Yeah, I love that guy.
He's wanted to kill me
ever since Tijuana, though.
It's actually a really funny story
for some other time.
I can't believe I'm about to say this.
I will take you to S.T.A.R. Labs
and have Caity fix you.
But if you step out of line,
I will let you bleed out.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
Is that urine?
Hey. Um... Is it lunch already, or...
Yes, and I'm starving.
Please tell me you're not still
the middle of something.
No. Um...
Yeah, I'm just waiting to see if this
chemical compound reacts and turns blue.
Oh. Cool.
What does blue mean?
- Barry.
- Cecile.
Are you and Iris...
No. No, no, no, we're not...
You all right?
It was Godspeed?
He must have broken out of Iron Heights.
Either that, or there's another clone
in Central City.
Great.
But why would they attack downtown?
I thought they wanted
to steal your speed.
The last one did.
When Rathaway and I took him down,
he said whoever sent him
wants infinite velocity.
Well, now it looks like
he wants infinite chaos.
Oh, man.
I just picked up
two different reports in progress.
One has Godspeed causing
a multi-car collision near City Hall.
And the other one has him
at a gas station,
like, three miles away.
Man, he's fast.
Even you can't be in two places at once.
Neither can he. There's two of them.
- Frost, if I run you downtown...
- I'm already ahead of you.
All right, I'm gonna take
the gas station.
Wait.
Where'd they go?
Satellites aren't picking up anything.
They're just gone.
Okay, maybe Iris
can rally Team Citizen.
They can canvass the sites,
- find out what they were looking for.
- No.
What I mean is, there's two of them.
So that means
they have the advantage now.
So anybody that's not a speedster
should stay put where it's safe.
And since Iris is already
home sick anyway,
so she's already in
the safest place possible.
Okay.
What are we supposed to do?
I've been thinking about that.
A cryptographic algorithm.
Might help us decode their modem-speak
and figure out why they're back.
All right. Do it. Yeah.
I'm gonna search the city.
So, here's a question.
Confidentially speaking, I mean...
what is your sister into?
Is it horror movies, Westerns,
single malt, blended...
"Cardigan" or "Blinding Lights"? Go.
- Confidentially speaking...
- Uh-huh.
You can't handle her.
Rest up.
Hey, what's with our sonic booms?
Oh... Don't mind me.
Let's play a guessing game, shall we?
Let's see, a sonic boom
at ground level...
And with this being Central City,
aka meta heaven,
I am guessing a speedster's behind it.
And since there's been one, two...
That's math.
Five Godspeeds
running around Central City
in the last year and a half alone,
I'm also guessing another one
just showed up to the party.
I hate you.
There's two more.
Yep. You heroic types
have quite the dilemma.
How are we gonna stop
both of them at the same time?
That's a good question.
We aren't doing anything.
You need to focus
on Ultraviolet's surgery.
Who's Ultraviolet? Is...
- Will you just be quiet?
- Shut up.
Stay here.
I've got a job to do.
Do you need any help?
I could stay, you know.
Come on, put me in, Coach.
You just got patched up.
You're benched.
Right.
You, Caitlin, and whoever else is part
of your S.T.A.R. Labs posse
think you get to just sit up here
in your ivory tower
judging who's good and who's bad.
But guess what?
Life isn't binary.
It's everything in between.
Now, you don't trust me?
That's fine.
But you cannot decide
who someone's gonna
be today based on
what they did yesterday.
And you should know that
better than anybody else...
Killer Frost.
I'm sorry. I just want to help you.
No.
Okay.
Is this really necessary?
Great.
She's gonna be okay, right?
Of course. Hey...
She's in good hands.
They're back, aren't they?
One of the Godspeed clones is attacking
the Central City Power Plant.
If he takes it out
like he did with the gas station,
the blast radius will be
over 40 square miles.
All right.
You should take
Allegra and Frost with you.
No, if the other Godspeed attacks,
they're our last line of defense.
Look, I know you're not
the real Godspeed,
but I won't let you harm
this city anymore,
so why don't you
just tell me who sent you?
Barry, my algorithm is
translating what Godspeed said.
What is it?
"I have him."
Oh, frak, it's a trap!
Get out of there!
Barry, get out of there!
Chester, initiate Babel Protocols!
But Barry, if I drop the force field,
you'll be locked out.
Do it now!
So, what, they couldn't phase through,
so now they're trying to punch through?
How long will the force field hold?
At the rate they're going,
an hour, maybe?
Wait. What are you going to do?
Get reinforcements.
Maybe.
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just thinking
I'm glad Iris is home and not here.
At least she's safe there.
I still put the rest of you in danger.
Hey, man...
Look, we're Team Flash.
Hey, we can handle this.
Plus, look at it this way. With all
the clones here, the city's safe.
Wait, Chester, is there a way
to evacuate
without raising the force field?
Even if there was, Caitlin's mid-surgery
with Ultraviolet right now.
So, if she stops,
Allegra's cousin might die.
- All right, we need a new plan. Fast.
- Yeah, on it.
I'm gonna check in with Iris.
Hey, Iris, you must still be resting.
That's good.
Um...
I'd come check on you in person,
only it's kind of turned into
a hell of a day here at the old office.
Anyway, um...
I know it's supposed to be
one of the happiest days of our lives,
and I don't want you to worry,
just rest.
But know that whatever happens,
I'm gonna do everything I can
to keep you and the baby safe.
I knew it! You're having a baby!
I'll check in with you later. Love you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Chester,
but we haven't told anybody yet,
so if you could
please help me keep it that way...
Oh, no, I got you. I got you.
- Consider it locked and zipped.
- Okay.
Whoa. Little baby speedster.
Maybe his first steps
will be a fathwoom.
It's a girl, not a boy.
Wait, have you already met this kid?
Is this like
a Back to the Future-type thing?
Not exactly.
Then how do you know the gender?
'Cause relatively speaking,
you just knowing
you have a kid
introduces a whole new set
of temporal variables,
all of which can have an effect
on present and future timelines,
and change what was once
predetermined outcomes.
I guess I don't know for sure.
I mean, I have seen so many
different versions of our future.
Just like the Godspeeds...
If it looks like those clones
are gonna break through,
I want you to hide in the Time Vault.
Cisco turned it
into a panic room before he left.
Just in case
I ever went Dark Flash again.
Nothing can get inside.
Oh, snap, I completely forgot
why I came here.
I have a plan.
So remember that trap from earlier?
- Yeah.
- That was the Godspeed clones
creating a set of variables
designed to predict a fixed outcome,
that you'd come to save the power plant.
But they didn't predict
that you'd get away.
Which means that our best defense
against them would be...
The unpredictable.
How much longer?
Allegra, honey, she's gonna be fine.
Okay, but...
how can you do that
with all hell breaking loose out there?
I don't have a choice.
Oh, like you're really surprised.
Well, that's getting worse.
Guess those two Godspeeds
need a place to crash.
Can't be good.
There's six of them now.
And if they get in here,
they could kill us all.
You brought Derek and Nancy?
It's worse than I thought.
First, I need you to promise me
that if I give these to you,
you won't stab me in the back
at the first chance you get.
I'm serious, Mark.
Today, you need to be a good guy.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because I'm not a good guy.
I mean, you know that.
It's why you're attracted to me.
Please, can we not do that right now?
Fair enough.
But if you really want my help,
then you need to at least try
to speak to me in a way
that someone like me can understand.
'Cause I'm no hero.
I'm never gonna be.
Fair enough.
If those six speedsters get in here,
we're screwed.
So, I need all the backup I can get.
'Cause I don't wanna die,
and I'm pretty sure you don't, either.
All right.
I'm in.
It takes a lot to gain my trust.
Break it? You won't get it back.
So what's the plan?
So, here's the plan.
You know how those Godspeed clones use
that modem-speak to communicate?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, I can take audio of it.
Then I can transmit that sound
through C.C.P.D.'s
Emergency Alert System.
Like this.
Yeah, okay. Now, imagine
one of these staticky clone voices
coming through
every speaker, every radio,
and every cell phone in Central City.
It'd be like trying to talk
to a friend over a loud dance floor.
Impossible, right? And...
They wouldn't be able
to predict where to go first.
And in the confusion,
Frost, Mark and I would have a chance
to take them down one at a time.
And I can boost the signal loud enough
to scramble their brains like eggs
for good measure.
But first, I gotta prep
the C.C.P.D. server
by uploading the signal.
- How long will that take?
- Five minutes.
Make it four.
Got it.
Is that supposed to be happening?
No. Whatever Black Hole did
removing the chip
has caused some sort
of systemic neural trauma.
I don't understand.
The anesthesia should be working.
She's hurting, you have to do something.
What I have to do
is finish this and close the wound.
Okay, hey, Caitlin,
can I try something?
Her reaction's stabilizing.
What did you do?
The only thing I could.
I can share my feelings with others now.
So I gave Esperanza the peace
that I feel knowing that you and Caitlin
and the rest of Team Flash are out there
saving the world one day at a time.
Barry, we have a big problem.
Brute force and phasing
didn't work, so now...
They figured out something better.
Draining energy from
the force field itself
like they would with my speed.
We have a perimeter breach.
He's calling the others.
Chester, get out of here.
Gideon... Gideon, secure the room!
Tachyon nullifiers activated,
Chester P. Runk.
Time Vault secured.
- Can I change my mind about helping?
- Too late.
Chester P. Runk,
multiple Godspeeds
are assaulting S.T.A.R. Labs.
Do you need assistance
formulating a plan?
I already had one, Gideon!
I was gonna pipe their clone-speak
into C.C.P.D.'s systems
and confuse the hell out of them.
But, you know...
stuck in a room...
Would you like
to play the signal
through S.T.A.R. Labs'
intercom system instead?
Yes, Gideon! Yes, I would!
And hopefully this'll give
Barry and the others
the distraction that they need.
Okay, Gideon!
Pipe audio file number 2808
into every room in this facility.
And crank it. I mean, P-Funk loud.
Of course.
Yo, I used to check out lyrics
Upon the formats
Built with skill with technique
Computer ADAT
My lyrical form is clouds
On your brainstorm
I get hyped, think, thought
Flow, acrobat
Sync the track, pump the track
Dance missions clubs like spores
React by strobe visions
And hurrying more reflects
On the dance floor
Blowing up
And having mad people showing up
Packing crowds, jam packed venues
Needles collapse
While atmosphere continues
Sprinkle that, win it like that
Move it like that
Hitting like that, the melody is phat
Yo, I'm on the energy source
The cosmic boss with Prodigy
Flipping astrology
My intellects devour, with diesel power
Blows your mind
Drastically, fantastically
Mono 7-0-6, 8-0-7-3
4-21
Robot-sonic
Blows your mind
Drastically, fantastically
Oh, crap.
Come on!
What the hell?
Ultraviolet's recovering,
but she's gonna be okay.
Good.
Thanks. Both of you.
Without that chip, she's free.
Now I just have
to help her adjust back to...
you know, normal.
Yeah, well, with you in her corner,
that'll be easy-peasy.
Thanks, Chuck.
'Cause with everything that's going on,
we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
Allegra's right.
How do we stop a dozen Godspeeds?
Oh, yeah, Barry, how much
of your speed did they steal?
Barely any.
The other clones attacked the first ones
before they could do any real damage.
But why fight each other?
Yeah, and why would any Godspeed
wanna protect the Flash?
I don't think they wanted to help me.
I just think
they were trying to kill the other six.
Speedsters fighting speedsters?
Yeah, that ain't
no regular bad guy battle.
Whatever it is,
we're stuck in the middle of it.
All this time, we assumed
the Godspeeds were aligned,
but if they're not...
It's a civil war.
You know, technically,
we didn't win.
But we are alive.
Something I didn't think
would be the case an hour ago.
That is cause for celebration.
So now I guess that you're done with me,
you're not gonna let me spend the night.
Uh...
No one's kicking you out.
Not yet.
Wow.
One little near-death experience...
Are we becoming friends?
You tell me.
Well, you gotta admit,
we do have explosive chemistry.
It's kind of like sucrose
and potassium chlorate with heat.
What a nerd.
You know,
when those two Godspeeds had us pinned,
I really thought that was it.
But somehow, I was okay with it.
I'll tell you why?
It was because you were with me.
And somehow, knowing that you would be
the last face that I would see
or the last voice that I'd hear,
just made everything okay.
Everything.
I didn't think
we were gonna make it, either.
But we did.
What are you thinking about now, Mark?
You, Snowflake.
What the hell was that?
Sucrose and potassium chlorate, my ass.
Mark?
- Barry.
- Hm?
Stop worrying.
You're gonna be a great dad.
We all know it.
Thanks, Cecile.
I just...
wish Iris was feeling better
and could be here.
I know, I know.
But you're gonna call her
as soon as we're done.
Yeah.
Okay, what is it?
I was just thinking.
I hope our child has Iris' heart
and her fearlessness.
Aww. She will.
It's negative.
I don't...
I mean, my dream...
Nora said everything was gonna work out.
It will, honey.
- I know it will.
- How?
If this isn't the future
for me and Iris...
what is?
Creyke hasn't shown up all day.
Maybe he moved on.
No, he'll be here.
I can feel it.
It's strange, being so close
to almost closing this case.
Are you worried
about arresting an old friend?
After we joined the service,
I went into intelligence.
Adam ended up in Special Forces.
Turns out he had a knack for killing,
one the Army used to great effect.
Something changed in him, West.
And I didn't see it.
And since you two grew up so much alike,
now you're worried that
whatever broke him might break you, too?
All our lives we had each other's backs.
Until he stabbed me in mine.
Left me for dead.
What can change a person enough
to do that?
What the hell is that?
Get out of the car!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::