Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created
the alternate timeline,
Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline
to how it was,
only to find
things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats
to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
- Previously
on "The Flash"...
- We have to think
about getting back to our Earth.
We've been here
long enough.
A whole multiverse
of Harrison Wells out there.
You want one?
Let's go get one.
- [laughs]
- Wells with a sense of humor.
- Harrison.
- Call me H.R.
- Out with the old,
in with the new.
- What are you doing here?
"Julian Albert,
meta-human CSI specialist."
- I don't trust you, and I don't
like things that I don't trust.
- How have I worked
with this guy for the past year?
- You say that
all the time.
- Do you maybe want to grab
some dinner tonight?
- I got movie night with my kids
tonight. Rain check?
- You were the only one
who wasn't affected
when I messed
with the timeline.
[dramatic music]
women: ♪ Express ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Express ♪
- ♪ You don't ever need no help
from no one else ♪
- Yo!
- You know you don't
need to do this
every morning, right?
- Oh, come on,
it's the least I can do.
I mean, I love Joe,
but at some point,
man needs his own space,
and until I find my own space,
that means your space.
So as a token
of my appreciation,
two eggs over easy,
bacon, toast...
I can't remember, do you
like it buttered or not?
- Barry, sometimes a man just
wants to butter his own bread.
- Okay, sorry.
I was just...
Yeah, no,
you're right, I...
- Look, don't get it
twisted, okay?
I love having you here.
You're a great guest.
I'm not sure how I feel
about our other visitor, though.
- Wells?
- "Please, call me H.R."
- So you don't like him?
- Oh, it's not so much
that I don't like him.
I just...the way he says things,
there's something about him.
I don't know what it is.
- Dude, he's only been here
a few days; let him settle in.
I know we've had
our Wells issues in the past,
but you can't just
stop trusting everybody
or giving them chances.
You know?
You can't live like that.
- This is true.
Wise words from a wise man.
- Joe Knowledge.
- I'm gonna take this to go.
- Okay. All right.
- Uh, I'll see you there.
- Yeah.
Oh, I can take you.
- No. No.
I'm gonna drive myself
today.
- Yeah, cool.
Cool.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Can I help you?
- I'm here to see
Dr. Tannhauser.
- Do you have
an appointment?
- No, but I'm pretty sure
she'll see me.
You can just tell her
Caitlin Snow is here.
- Dr. Tannhauser's
a very busy woman.
I'm sure you can
understand.
- I appreciate
the diligence, Jackie,
but Caitlin's
always welcome here,
even if I wish
she'd call first.
- Nice to see you too, Mom.
- So what brings you here?
I didn't forget
your birthday, did I?
I'm pretty sure
I sent a card.
- You did...
in April.
- Thank you.
- Look, I read your new paper
on applications
in cryo-medicine, and I think
you might be able to help.
- I had no idea you
kept up on the literature
over at S.T.A.R. Labs.
That's still what
it's called, right?
- Yes, and I have a patient
who could use your help.
- Well, if you want
to send over the file,
I'll be happy to take a look
when I have a chance,
but right now, I have
a shareholder meeting
to prepare for and...
- Mom!
[ice crackling]
♪ ♪
I'm the patient.
- Cancel my appointments,
and have Nigel meet me
in the bio-lab.
We have work to do.
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Here we go ♪
- ♪ So fall in love and... ♪
- Sumptuous day.
Oh, no, on this Earth,
I believe you say...
- Good morning.
And it is, isn't it?
I mean...
♪ ♪
The music on your Earth,
well, it strikes a chord,
no pun intended.
Please, help yourself.
I find a crew
works best
when it's well-fed
and well-rested.
- Are those coffees
for us too?
- Yes indeed, Miss West.
[chuckles]
I took the liberty of reading
through your ledgers last night.
A lot of information to absorb,
but let's see how I did.
Skim milk chai latte.
- Okay.
And an iced Americano
with two...no,
three shots of espresso.
- Boom.
- That happened, Walter.
- Wally.
Now, for my fleet-of-foot
friend...
oh, you'd best
stick to decaf.
- [chuckles]
Probably for the best, yeah.
- San Francisco.
I have "prepar-ed"
a French roast
with a touch of creamer.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
[chuckles]
Did you know, on my Earth,
coffee crop was
wiped out by blight?
I mean, that's one more reason
to stay on this Earth,
for the coffee alone.
- Yeah, though
that's if you stay.
- If I stay.
Time is of the essence.
Here's what I propose, a series
of team-building exercises.
Now, I've hidden
a series of clues
all around the facility.
What I propose is,
we break into
two groups all right,
and you can pick
a partner. You're...
- Okay, okay.
[laughs]
I have to stop you, H.R.
I am not feeling this.
- It's the roast, isn't it?
I should have gone with a dark...
- No, it's not the roast.
The roast is fine.
Our trust isn't something
that you can just build
with games.
Okay?
- No.
- This is something
that goes back three years.
It's something
that's been forged in fire,
sometimes literally,
so maybe you should
just step back
and observe,
see what we do here,
how we operate.
Did you get that?
- Excellent note.
I'm gonna run with that.
- Where's Caitlin, by the way?
Have you...
- Yes. So she was here.
- She was?
- All right, yeah, you know,
we talked, and she...
- What?
- Knocked back
a triple-shot latte,
and she left you a message,
so I'm gonna...
Uh, I...yeah, let me just
play it for you.
This is not the same
as my Earth's.
This is a different...
There it is.
- Hey, it's me.
I've got some things
I need to take care of.
I shouldn't be gone
more than a few days.
See if you can
get along without me.
Make sure Cisco doesn't touch
my pizza pockets.
- Wasn't labeled.
- Okay, you know what, guys?
I got to go to work.
I'm running late.
- Ooh, yeah.
I got to do that too.
- Yeah, let's go.
- I got to bail.
- Oh.
You know, we'll do
the team-building
exercises another...
I'll leave the clues
hidden in the facility.
- Cool. How do you guys say
"see you later" over there?
- Ah.
"Until next communion."
- All right, see you later.
- See you later.
- So weird.
- Come.
- Hey, sorry I'm late.
I had to meet somebody and...
- You can add tardiness
to the list, Captain.
- Allen, it's been brought
to my attention
that you've been giving yourself
unauthorized access
to your colleagues'
case files.
- Excuse me?
- Along with multiple
infractions,
repeated absences,
disappearing
throughout the day,
phone call interruptions,
guests in the lab.
The list is pretty extensive,
Captain.
- I'm sorry,
with all due respect,
I do my job here.
- You do good work here,
Allen.
Don't put that in jeopardy
by thinking
the rules
don't apply to you.
Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- [scoffs]
Sorry, Captain, that's it?
Sir, I document
eight different...
- Nine.
- Nine different violations
of regulations,
and he gets
a 15-second talking-to?
Must be nice.
- We are done here.
You can go.
- Captain.
- Were you really
just being a tattletale?
That's bush league, man.
- You know what? You're right.
Silly me to think the rules
actually apply
to the golden boy
of CCPD's crime lab.
Detective.
- He's unbelievable.
- You know what?
I wish you two could be
a little less oil and water
and a little bit more
oil and vinegar.
You guys have been
at each other's throats
for a year now.
- That's just it.
From my perspective,
it's been two weeks.
- So you're saying
that before two weeks ago,
you weren't Julian's enemy?
- I'm saying
before two weeks ago,
Julian didn't even exist.
- It's because
of your Flashpoint.
- I know it's
because of the Flashpoint.
[cell phone buzzing]
Cisco.
Hey, is this important?
- I don't know;
does 30 hits downtown
on the meta-human app
count?
- What are we looking at?
- Well, nothing really.
Every traffic cam
in a ten-block radius
suddenly went down,
so we're flying blind,
and the hits are
all over the map.
- All right, well,
there's one way to see
what's going on.
I got to go.
- Most of the chatter's coming
from the harbor district.
- All right, I'm here.
It's a bad scene, man.
[people screaming]
- You should be
right on top of it, Barry.
What is it?
- It's a...monster?
- [roars]
[people screaming]
- Guys, did you hear me?
There is a monster
in Central City.
- What are we talking?
Yao Ming size
or Andre the Giant?
- No, it's, like,
an actual monster.
- What even makes that?
- I don't even know that.
- S.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
show me something.
Whoa.
You ever see anything
like that on Earth-19?
- You want me to observe.
I'll just observe.
[dramatic music]
- [growls]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
[people yelling]
- Iris, what are you
doing here?
- Working on a story,
and last time I checked,
you don't need
super-speed and a red suit
to help people.
[both grunting]
- All right,
get out of here.
I'm gonna try
to stop that thing.
- Come on, come on,
come on.
- Cisco,
where'd it go?
- Can't track it
if I can't see it.
- Know what you could do?
Could use your ears.
- My ears?
[car alarm blaring outside]
- What's that sound?
- It's a car alarm;
I can use the car alarms
to track the direction
the monster's heading in.
We got him.
Head north three blocks.
[computer beeps]
I lost him.
- Yeah, me too.
- I don't get it.
I don't get it.
- Every meta-human
we've encountered
has been exactly that,
meta-human,
so where did this thing
come from?
- I don't know
where it came from, man.
I just...it just vanished.
That's all I know. It was gone.
- Yeah, but in my experience,
things are always different.
- What?
- Than they appear.
There must be a reason
the darn thing
can just disappear
like that.
Maybe the darn thing's got
some kind of cloaking mechanism.
- That's a good idea,
but right now, I would settle
for "how can we stop it?"
- Yes, obviously.
- Just how?
- I don't know.
- We don't have
a magic monster lasso.
- But you know
what we could...
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
I'm just...I'm just observing.
- No, H.R., please.
We're open to any idea
right now.
- On my Earth, we have ropes
made out of carbon fiber.
They are ultralight
but strong enough
to pull a battleship;
we could restrain it with that.
Right?
What do you think?
- Okay, I think it's...
- Okay.
- I think it's worth a shot;
we can spin it
down in my workshop.
- Yes. Good.
- Yeah, there was something else
that was weird, though.
I-I saw a transformer explode
as this thing passed by it.
- That is weird.
- What's weird about that?
- Monster didn't even
lay a finger on it.
It exploded
before it got to it.
- Kind of reminds me
of that Hitchcock movie
where the extra covers his ears
before the gun goes off.
- You have Hitchcock
on this Earth?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, brilliant.
"Murder on the Titanic"!
"Who did it? Who cares?
We're drowning."
The beast must emit
some kind of electrical pulse.
Is there a way I could get
a look at that transformer?
- No. It's...the whole place
is a crime scene now
with Julian
in charge of it.
- Ah, Julian.
Who's that?
That's the CSI guy
you don't like, right?
- I mean...
- Yeah, all right.
- [whispering]
He's great.
- Sorry, cold hands.
- I didn't even notice.
- I'm Nigel,
by the way.
- Nice to meet you.
- We're gonna help you
figure this out, Caitlin.
Let's get you to the lab.
- What's this?
- It's to test how your ability
affects molecular motion.
That shaft
is solid tungsten,
and it's heated to
over 2,000 degrees centigrade.
I want you to cool it down,
and when we determine
how you can do that,
we can figure out
the best way to help you.
Best we could do
in such little time.
- So this is where you've been
for the last hour.
- I had to reschedule my day
for this, Caitlin.
A lot of things around here
require my attention.
- I remember.
- [sighs]
Whenever you're ready.
[dramatic music]
Don't hold back.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Julian.
- Hmm.
You seen this?
It's bad enough we have
the metas destroying the city.
Now we have this thing
to worry about.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is there any point
in me asking where you've been
for the last hour?
Or should I just assume
the rules
still don't apply
to you?
- I was...I...
- Yes, okay.
- Look, hey, man,
so I know that...
you and I, we got off
on the wrong foot.
We never managed to find
the right one,
and I'll take that.
That's probably my fault,
but I just...
I don't want things to be
like that anymore, you know?
I-I'd...like it
if things changed.
- It's funny,
'cause I remember you saying
something similar to that
right before you stole
the case
from underneath me.
Do you have idea
what it's like
to work side by side
with someone
with such little regard
for the rules?
You may very well be
contaminating my work.
- That's exactly why I want
to learn from you.
- I don't follow.
- I just...you know,
whenever I read your reports,
it's clear that your
evidence collection techniques
are far superior to mine.
[clears throat]
- [scoffs]
Go on.
- I don't know; I mean,
if I could just shadow you
for a day,
maybe ask a few questions,
I think that you could
really help bring my skills
up to...snuff.
What do you say?
- [scoffs]
Sorry.
- What if I gave up the lab?
There's a storeroom downstairs
that I could convert,
so if you let me follow you
on this case, lab's yours.
- Lab's mine?
Okay. Deal.
You can't slow me down, though.
- I would never.
- All right. I'll call you.
- How long have you had
these abilities?
- They started manifesting
a few months ago,
but I'm assuming
I got them when
the particle
accelerator exploded,
just like
all the other metas.
- And you haven't
told anyone?
- Just you.
- I told you, you never
should have taken
that job at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You could have stayed here,
had access
to world-class facilities.
- And have all of my work be
in the shadow
of your reputation.
- Of course, the only time
you need your mother
is when you're in trouble.
- What's that
supposed to mean?
- Oh, come on, darling.
You ran off to Central City
to play scientist
with that disgraced quack.
- I was trying to make
a name for myself.
- For three years,
barely a word,
until trouble hits,
and then here you come,
walking through the door
and expecting Mommy
to drop everything in her life
to try to fix it.
- You have no idea
what I've been through...
- Dr. Tannhauser,
look at this.
- She's absorbed
all that energy?
How?
- I'm not sure yet,
but if we can figure that out,
this could change
everything we're doing here.
♪ ♪
- So then The Flash...my Flash,
again, not your Flash...
we hatched a plan to gather
all the remaining meta-humans
into one place
for a final showdown.
They called it "World War M."
It was glorious.
Two forces on opposing sides
of the stadium.
The tension built. No.
It was like that movie
where the gladiator
was the lead gladiator.
What was that called?
- "Gladiator."
- That's better;
on my Earth,
it was called "Sweaty Men,"
and that didn't take.
So the two forces charge
into battle, and when they do...
- I need to take a five.
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
Let's take a break.
- By myself.
- Yeah, you go ahead.
I'll keep working on this.
[sighs]
[device beeps]
So entry AAA:2.
Plan is proceeding.
Characters are in place.
Nobody seems the wiser
as to why I'm here.
- Hey.
- I had to give
a witness report
on the attack,
and I thought I would
make it a lunch date.
- Yeah, cool.
Clear a spot.
Let's do this. Ahh.
- Yeah.
Are things any better
with Julian?
- Oh, my God,
it's like, every time
I try to get to know the guy,
he does something
that makes it
really hard to.
All I know now is that
he dislikes meta-humans
about as much
as he dislikes me.
- Maybe you should try and
see things from his perspective.
He might have a reason
to dislike both of you
that you don't know
anything about.
- Did you just hit me
with a Joe-ism?
- Well, sometimes he's right.
Sometimes he's not.
- Yeah.
- Oh, speaking of which,
I just saw him downstairs,
and he was talking
to the DA.
He blew off a date
with her.
- I saw him do the same thing
last week.
I don't know.
Maybe he's not into her.
- No, he's into her.
I mean, when I asked him
about her,
he basically told me
to buzz off.
- You're not too good
at buzzing off, are you?
- Nope.
When it comes to my dad, no.
[cell phone buzzes]
- [groans]
Well, look who it is.
Looks like I have an opportunity
to see things
from Julian's perspective...
- Hmm.
- Right now.
Sorry about lunch.
I got to go.
- Mm.
- See you later.
Oh, I need that.
- If you don't stop squirming,
I'll never find a vein.
- What exactly are you
testing for now?
- Any polymorphism
that could help us understand
how you're able to absorb
that much energy
from molecules
to create gelid surroundings.
- You realize I've run
all of these tests already?
- Then what was the point
of coming here?
- Seriously, Mom?
I'm terrified
of what I'm becoming.
You realize you haven't
asked me once how I'm feeling?
- I'm trying to keep
emotion out of this.
Believe me, it's for your
benefit as much as it is mine.
- Right, because that's
your specialty, isn't it?
Being cold,
just like after...
- After what?
- After Dad died.
- I did everything I could
to save your father.
- Well, you lost your daughter
at the same time.
- You're the one
who went away, Caitlin.
- Because I had to.
You realize you never acted
like my mother again
after Dad got sick?
You would barely even
look at me.
- I...couldn't handle
the pain.
My work got me through it.
Losing someone like that,
you have no idea
what that feels like.
- Actually, I do.
My husband died
over a year ago.
- I'm sorry.
- [sighs]
Okay.
What do you got?
- I said get here quick,
but that was...
quicker than I expected.
- Oh, no, yeah,
it was a...
crazy Uber driver.
- Hmm.
Well, the blast pattern
and the scoring
on the insulation suggests
that it was a power surge
that blew it out.
- So it's a coincidence?
- I highly doubt it.
But I'll figure it out.
Someone in this city has to do
something about these metas.
- What do you mean?
We have a whole police force
working to stop
these metas.
- No, you have The Flash.
- So it's not just bad metas
you don't like.
It's all the metas.
- I'm just saying
that because of him,
the police department
has got lethargic.
I mean, why do anything at all
if The Flash is gonna
save the day every time?
It's a bit like you
with rule breaking...
a momentary fix,
and now you're lazy, sloppy.
- Cool. Thanks.
I think The Flash
is actually
a source of inspiration
for the city.
I think he kind of
provides hope.
- Yes, well, that's one
of many things
that we'll have
to disagree on, Allen.
- What?
You see something?
- A pattern.
The creature's movements,
they seemed random at first,
but they were contained
to a prescribed area.
You know, like the creature was
stuck in an invisible fence.
- Traffic cameras
were down, right?
Maybe it was being watched
or controlled by somebody
that needed to keep it
in visual range the entire time?
- Constricting the creature's
movements to the line of sight.
That actually makes sense.
Maybe there is a brain in there
after all, Allen.
[wire snapping,
car alarm blaring]
[intense music]
Dispatch, this is CSI.
I'm requesting
immediate backup.
The monster has been sighted
by the harbor.
- Hey, maybe we should split up.
- That's a terrible idea.
- Yeah, but we got to do
something, right? Whoa.
- Don't worry, I have four
years' training in the military.
- Uh, even still, since when
does a CSI carry a gun?
- Since there were monsters
in our city.
- All right, Jul...
- [roars]
♪ ♪
- Cheers.
- You're leaving us?
- Yeah.
Things between
my mother and me are...
complicated.
- We can help you.
- I don't need your help
with the science.
I can do that on my own.
I came here to get something
from my mother
that I realize now
I'll never get.
[door clicks shut]
What are you doing?
- Sorry, Frosty,
but you're not going
anywhere.
- Let me out of here.
Open these doors.
- I said no!
I am sick of working
day after day,
night after night, only to have
my work benefit your mother.
With the information
I can get from you,
I can finally
get out of this place,
so you're gonna stay here
until I get everything
that I need.
- You are not
going to test me.
- Yes, I am.
- No, Nigel.
You are not going to test me,
now or ever.
- Wait, let go!
Let go! Ah!
- Caitlin! Don't do this!
This isn't you!
- You don't know anything
about me, Mother.
- I-I know I wasn't
much of a mother,
and I know I have
a lot to make up for,
but I know I didn't
raise a killer.
For whatever it's worth,
I am so sorry.
- It's worth a lot.
- Now go.
- What about...
- I-I'll take care of him.
No one will ever know
about this. I promise.
- Thank you.
- Just go.
- Every time there's been
a sighting of the monster,
multiple transformers
have blown.
- Hmm, so it's definitely
feeding off electricity.
- Mm-hmm, and see,
I mapped out
all the streets
that it's been spotted around.
Never leaves
a ten-block radius.
- You know, this is exactly
what I was talking about.
Some meta's been gifted
this incredible power,
and this is the very best thing
they can do with it...
terrorize a city.
It's pathetic.
- Why exactly do you
hate metas so much?
- If you think
I'm gonna break down now
and tell you that
one killed my parents
and that's why
I have to do this job,
I'm not, okay?
I don't need a deep, personal
reason to hate metas, Allen.
I just need to see
person after person transformed,
given these
extraordinary abilities,
and watch them
be squandered.
Robbing banks, hurting people,
spreading fear.
It's just...
well, it's not just a crime.
It's an absolute waste.
I mean, can you imagine
what it would be like
to have those powers?
I mean, I would be
helping people.
I would be improving
the world.
I guess I wasn't one
of the chosen few, was I?
- That's it?
You're mad at them
because you weren't chosen?
Sorry, I mean,
I'm just saying,
it can't be easy
being a meta-human,
having your life...their lives
change in ways that,
you know, neither one of us
could possibly imagine.
It's got to take
some adjusting.
- Right.
So now you're defending them?
- Well, no, I mean, I'm...
I don't think that...
- This internship thing
we're doing is completely over.
- Whatever.
Transformers are the key.
- No, I agree...
- Anytime the monster's
shown up,
any nearby have exploded.
- They blow up.
- Car alarms keep
malfunctioning too.
- Car alarms, transformers.
What is the connection?
Yeah, we'll get there, fellas.
We'll get there.
We just got to keep trying.
- Maybe someone's pulling power
out of the transformers
and using it
to power the monster.
- Power...
yes, the monster.
That's...ah, you just beat me
to it, San Francisco.
- [chuckles]
See, that can't be it, H.R.
- Can't be it...
- 'Cause we would have detected
a surge in the power grid.
- We did not.
- Not if it was
broadcast power
or something
like a portable Tesla tower.
- A portable Tesla power.
- Tower.
- Tower. That's what it is.
Nice. Mm, mm.
Teamwork, hmm?
So PS, where I'm from,
on my Earth,
we call that a problem solved.
I'm gonna go for coffee.
On my Earth, the coffee
was wiped out by blight.
- Blight, yeah.
- Can you imagine?
- He didn't really do
anything, did he?
- Thank you.
Took me a while
to realize it,
but he's just resaying
everything
that we're saying
in a different way.
- No, he did have
the idea for the rope.
- Ah, ah, reverse inception.
He made you think he had
the idea for the rope,
but he didn't even tell us
how to use it.
- Okay, well, we're not gonna be
caught off guard again.
We should vibe him.
- It'd be my pleasure.
- Hey-oh.
- Hey, baby girl.
- Hey.
- You've been hanging out here
a lot lately.
- Yeah, well, there's
a lot of scared people
with this monster
running around the city.
- Oh, we'll get him.
We always do.
- Oh, yeah? Is that a quote
I can use for my article?
- No.
- All right.
It was worth a try.
Dad, you know Wally and I
are all right, right?
- What is that
supposed to mean?
- We just don't want you
to not do things because of us.
You know, we just want you
to...find someone.
- I'm not having
this conversation with you.
- Dad, that DA
is totally into you.
You should go out
with her.
- Iris, I don't need you
to be Cupid.
I got my job.
I got you, Barry, Wally.
I'm good.
- I know Dad and
that's great. I just...
Now that I'm falling in love
with someone,
I just want you to have
the same thing.
- Joe? Alert every task force
and sniper unit.
Tell 'em to load up.
- I should get
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- What's up?
- Albert thinks
he's figured out
the creature's next target.
- Well, if there's ever
an opportunity
for a 40-foot monster
to wreak havoc,
it's gonna be where people
like to gather.
2nd Street Promenade.
- Well, let's end this.
- That's what I intend
to do, Detective.
- Where'd he go?
- Doesn't matter.
I don't need him.
- What do you mean?
What do you...hey, dude.
Come on, you can't just go
through his stuff; that's not...
- [scoffs] I'm not
going through his stuff.
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
What even is this?
[device beeps]
- Now I seem to have won
most of the team's trust,
except Francisco's.
- Those are my things.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Who are you really?
We know you're hiding
something.
- You've been burned,
twice...
by a man
with the same face as me.
I imagine it's hard to trust
after something like that.
- You think?
- I do think.
So play...
the rest of it.
I've read his journals.
I found nothing
that can tell me
why Francisco feels
the way he does,
but I do hope I can change
his opinion of Harrison Wells
and the two of us can
rebuild that friendship.
What a fantastic C-story
to weave within the narrative.
[device beeps]
- What?
- What narrative?
- Narrative.
I'm writing a novel.
"The Tales of H.R. Wells."
Catchy, I know.
[laughs]
- Wait, I'm sorry, you're
a scientist and a novelist?
- Yes.
- Wow. That's perfect.
- Thank you.
That's exactly right.
I'm a scientist and a novelist;
I run S.T.A.R. Labs,
and also I'm an author
of science-romance.
That's my niche.
Write what you know.
And I thought,
"Well, what better opportunity
"than to come
to another Earth and pen
yet another best seller
about my adventures here?"
- Why didn't you just tell us
this in the first place?
- I guess it didn't
seem relevant,
and also,
I didn't think
you guys were gonna
rifle through my belongings.
That's all it is.
I'm a scientist
and a novelist.
Do you think you can
trust me now,
or is that not something
that you have
on this Earth, trust?
- Trust?
- Oh! [laughs]
You scared
the dickens out of...
- Trust who?
[cell phone buzzing,
computer beeping]
- It's the app.
- It's the monster.
It's back.
- Monster?
- Yeah, you've missed a lot.
I'll explain upstairs.
- Well, I'll just
stay here, then.
- Come on.
We need you.
[people screaming]
- All right, guys.
I'm here.
- Tell us everything
that you see right now.
- Mayhem.
- [roars]
- And the monster.
- Okay, so what's the plan?
- Great question,
Miss West.
So we fashioned
just a carbon fiber rope,
but correct me
if I'm wrong,
we never actually
discussed
how he was gonna use
that rope, did we?
- Guys.
- Barry, we're gonna
do "Empire."
"Empire of the Sun,"
Barry.
- What? "Empire Strikes Back."
- What?
- "Empire Strikes Back," Barry.
- Just take it down
like it was an AT-AT.
- Just like an AT-AT.
- "Bigger they are,
the harder they fall."
Even I've seen "Empire."
- I like that.
- I like you.
[people yelling]
- All right, here we go.
I always wanted
to be a Jedi.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Guys? Rope went
right through it.
It's a hologram.
- That explains everything...
the ten-block radius,
the transformers.
It takes that much power
to render.
- Wait, CCPD sent
snipers there.
- If it's not real...
- Then the bullets will
pass right through it.
- Guys, it's gone.
Where is it?
- Hold on.
Give me a sec, Bar.
- Okay, we don't have
a second!
- H.R., triangulate the signal
being sent to the monster.
We have to disrupt it
before anyone gets hurt.
- Okay, let's do that now.
Let's...let's just triangulate.
The computer
doesn't triangulate...
- What?
- The signal the way...
not the way I'm used to...
this is
a different size
computer for...
- Oh, my God. I knew it.
- What?
- You're a fake.
- This whole time, he's been
acting like he can help us,
but he can't because
he doesn't now how, does he?
- How?
Triangulate!
- Guys, which way?
- Get the...
- All right, you take over.
- Found it.
It's at 2nd and Fulton.
- [roars]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
- I have a lock
on the target.
- Fire when ready.
♪ ♪
- Stop!
Stop firing!
It's a hologram!
- Hold your fire!
Hold your fire!
- A hologram?
Where'd it go?
- Detective West,
where's Julian?
- He was here!
- Cisco, I need
that location.
- Hamilton building,
25th floor.
There's more power
going there
than anywhere else
in the building combined.
- Line of sight
to all the attacks.
That's where he is.
- I said
put your hands up!
This is CCPD!
Freeze!
Stop what you're doing!
I said put your hands up!
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- You're just a kid.
- Yeah, a kid
you almost killed!
You're gonna pay for that one,
buddy. You're gonna...
- Yeah, I don't think so, man;
I think you're the one
that's gonna be paying
for all the damage you did
to this city...
for a very long time.
- [groans]
[whimpering]
- Hey, Flash.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- [panting]
- Do you realize
how many innocent people
could have been hurt,
or worse?
What made you do
something like this?
- I just wanted to feel
powerful for a change.
- And that did it?
Scaring people?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, it did.
You know, the kids at my school,
they tease me every day.
I'm a weirdo there.
And I'm just sick of feeling
scared all the time.
I just wanted someone else
to feel that way for a change.
- Look,
I know sometimes
things are hard
at your age.
But trust me,
it does get better.
- So what happens now?
- Well, there are severe
consequences for what you did,
and you're just gonna
have to accept that,
but listen,
you're young.
You can turn
all of this around.
All right.
Come on.
- You were named
Entrepreneur of the Decade
by "Tech Magazine"?
- That's right.
- Is any of what's on here true?
- All of it.
- How?
You can barely turn on
a computer.
- There are two parts
to every idea.
There is the inception
and the execution.
I provide the former.
- So you come up
with the ideas?
- Yeah, I don't know
how to implement them.
I'm the idea man.
- So you didn't actually solve
the cryptogram that we sent you?
- No, that was my partner
at S.T.A.R. Labs on my Earth.
I'm the face
of the company.
I'm more of the inspiration
behind the company.
Then I was exposed.
Well, people thought
that I was something
that I-I guess I wasn't.
Anyway, it...it kind of all
fell apart for me.
But then I got
your message.
My partner brought me
I realized he's bringing me
an opportunity
to come to this Earth
to write this book.
- So many planets
in the multiverse,
and we happen to pick
the one Wells
who's not a scientist.
- You're right.
I wasn't completely honest
with you...
with all of you.
I feel badly about that.
I regret that.
But let me ask you a question.
Has there been none amongst you
that has ever shaded the truth
for what you believe to be
the greater good?
- It sounds to me
like you're a con man.
all: Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Was I a con man
when I showed
San Francisco here
how to track the beast
using car alarms?
Was I a con man
when I showed him
how to fashion a rope
using carbon fiber?
- I came up with those ideas!
- You were prompted
by my suggestions.
- Oh.
- That is how ideas work!
People, you need a muse!
I can be your muse.
- What about stopping
all the metas on your Earth?
- More of an advisory role
for me, but I was there.
I remembered how we...you don't
think that's something?
Let me present you
with a scenario.
You're confronted
with something,
a threat that
you've never seen before.
You don't know how to stop it.
Who does?
That's value to you.
Let me prove my worth to you.
If I fail, I will "pfft"
right back to my Earth,
but if I succeed,
I will have succeeded
not just in redeeming myself
but also...
will have done some good
with my life.
- You know, you're lucky
we're pretty big
on redemption
and doing good here,
so I think you can...
I don't know...
stay for a few weeks,
try to prove yourself,
but if not, "fyoo,"
back to your Earth.
- Thank you.
- Hey,
no more repackaging.
- Word is bond.
- That...just no more that.
- All right, H.R.
- Okay.
- Where you been?
- I actually went
to visit my mother.
- Your mother?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, boy.
Why?
- To see if we could work
through some of our issues.
And I think we might actually be
on the road to recovery.
- When it comes to family,
you got to do whatever it takes,
'cause one day, you might not
be able to do that anymore.
Glad you're back.
- This is home.
- I nearly killed
a kid tonight.
The monster
we were chasing,
it turns out it was
just a hologram,
operated by a
15-year-old boy.
Flash came to save
the day.
And he saved me
from doing something...
- I heard.
- You know what's sad?
That kid, he's just acting
'cause he's scared, you know?
He wants everyone
to be terrified
and to run away from the monster
so he can feel powerful.
I know what that's like.
- How do you mean?
- I come from a pretty
wealthy family...
[laughs]
Back in England.
It's a long line
of generations of old money,
tradition...
nonsense, really.
And I was the heir.
I was their firstborn son.
I was supposed
to inherit the lot.
But I was the odd duck...
[laughs]
Who would rather
go in the garden
and collect samples
of insects...
[laughs]
Rather than learn how to tie
a Windsor knot
or which fork
to use first at dinner.
Yeah. No, I wanted more.
You know?
I came here to do
the one thing
that they couldn't
stop me from doing:
becoming a scientist...
becoming a great scientist.
And then just as I got
to the top of my field,
poof. The world
changes overnight.
Meta-humans.
I don't know a single thing
about meta-humans.
I don't know how they talk.
I don't know how they walk.
I certainly don't know
the first thing
about stopping them, so...
rendered useless.
I suppose that's the monster
that I'm running from now:
just feeling powerless.
- Yeah, I feel the same way
some days, Julian.
I lost my mom
when I was a kid.
Lost my dad recently.
It's a scary world.
People die.
Trusts are betrayed.
Things change.
But change can be
a good thing, you know?
It can bring new experiences,
new opportunities, people.
You can treat 'em
like a potential enemy
or like a new friend.
Just trust that everything's
gonna be okay.
- Yeah, maybe you're right.
[chuckles]
You can stop.
You can stay.
I was really wrong
about The Flash,
so I could be wrong
about you too.
Good night, mate.
- Julian?
You want to get a drink?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
- All right.
Let's do it.
- Caitlin, I've been going
over the data we collected,
and I found
some disconcerting results.
Your body's chemistry
is changing in ways
that I don't fully understand,
but one thing is clear.
These powers you have,
the more you use them,
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
I'm sorry, honey,
but listen to me.
You must not use these powers
under any circumstances.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.