[thunder cracks and echoes]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oracle, it's Huntress.
Come in.
- Huntress, the comms
are barely functional.
- Barbara, can you hear me?
- I need more time.
- The wave's coming
too quickly.
You're gonna have
to evac right now.
- I'm sending all relevant
data before the wave hits.
- Oracle?
Oracle, please answer me.
- Sending all relevant data...
[anti-matter cracks and thrums]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
- We have only located four
of the seven Paragons
needed to save the multiverse.
- We could find the last
three if...[clears throat]
- Hey, it's uh...repairing
a Paragon Detector, okay?
It's complex stuff.
[breach whooshes]
- Someone call for backup?
- Iris.
- Cisco, thank goodness.
I need another
genius intellect, stat.
- That's why I'm here.
And that
is a super doppelganger,
which is super weird.
- Holy all-star squadron.
Hi, hi, how are ya?
Ralph Dibny, Elongated Man.
Ready to help kick butt.
[chuckles]
- Ignore him.
It's his first crossover.
- Listen, the antimatter wave
is still ripping its way
across the multiverse.
We have to get everyone we can
to safety.
- Calculations still show
that Earth-1
will be the last place
for the wave to hit.
- I just heard from
Alex and Brainy on Earth-1.
Everyone we saved from Earth-38
is still accounted for.
- Then we should bring as many
people to Earth-1 as we can
in the time being.
- Let's get
a rescue team together,
save who we can
across the multiverse.
I can use my psychic abilities
to stay in connection
with the Waverider.
- And I'll go as well.
- Well, parallel Earth Rory
still has Jonathan,
so I'll run comms
and keep everyone updated.
- Supergirl?
- I'll stay here.
We have to find a way
to get our world back.
[computer chimes]
- Hey, I think we did it.
I think we fixed it.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Guys,
we already know all this.
- It's buffering,
so maybe a little patience.
[computer chimes]
- Huh.
Why am I not surprised?
- That's new.
- Uh, who the hell is that guy?
- Dr. Ryan Choi,
physics professor
at Ivy Town University
on our Earth.
- Well, I guess
we know our next stop.
Ray, Ralph?
- Ivy Town.
It's my old stomping grounds.
Let's go.
- With all
the Paragons identified,
our next priority
is determining
how to stop
the antimatter wave.
- [clears throat]
Sorry to interrupt,
but Mr. Diggle has arrived.
- How could you let
this happen, Sara?
You, of all people?
- It's complicated.
- It's not complicated.
I wasn't there
when he needed me.
- Dig, we are working
on bringing him back
the same way that
he brought me back, remember?
- You're talking about
a trip to Purgatory.
- Yes.
- Fine, count me in.
- And there's...[exhales deeply]
There's something else.
Dig, it's Lyla.
She's...
she's gone missing.
- What?
- Nobody saw her leave.
She was there one minute
and gone the next.
- But she has the ability
to teleport,
so she...
- So there are now
infinite possibilities
for Lyla's location.
- You.
Listen to me.
I am not losing
Oliver and Lyla.
So cut the crap and tell me
how the hell do I find my wife?
- You heard him.
Where is she?
- Harbinger could very well
be with my adversary...
[dramatic orchestral music]
The Anti-Monitor.
♪ ♪
- The Anti-Monitor...
is that, uh, set in stone,
or can we workshop that
a little bit?
- This is why I have been
preparing all of you...
testing and pushing you
to your limits.
I needed your courage,
your honor,
your strength of will,
even the truth
of your convictions...
everything that makes you
the greatest heroes
on this Earth or any other,
because that's
what it will take
to defeat our opponent.
- And what exactly
does this guy want?
- To eliminate the multiverse
and replace it
with another universe.
- One that he can control...
just like every other
megalomaniac.
- I should've foreseen
my connection with Harbinger
could be perverted to his ends.
- Should have?
Just tell us
how to get her back.
- I want to find her just
as much as the rest of you,
but I cannot rewrite
what has already been written.
I can only attempt
to save what remains.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- You know what to do
to get Oliver's soul back.
I'll watch over his body
and I promise you I will
keep you updated on Harbinger.
- Copy that.
[tablet chimes]
- Cisco, maybe you should
call Kamilla back?
- No, no, no.
That wasn't a phone call.
I'm triangulating
anti-matter wave particles
on the Earth that are left.
- Why?
- I'm trying to locate
the source of the wave
and according to this,
it's hidden
in a subterranean region
right in our own backyard.
Meet me in the cargo bay
in five.
- Cisco Ramon.
- [exclaims]
[dramatic music]
Didn't I just leave you?
- You are not a Paragon,
but you do have a purpose.
Vibe must live again.
- No.
No, my powers are gone
and there's a reason for that.
- You must answer the call
whether you wish to or not.
- Okay, maybe
you didn't hear me
under those voluminous
mutton chops of yours.
♪ ♪
- Now go.
Serve your higher purpose.
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- Are you still sure
you want me to go?
- Yeah.
Go find Ryan Choi
and hurry back.
♪ ♪
[breach whooshes]
- Where did Barry race off to?
- Perimeter search...
make sure this isn't a trap
set up by the Anti-Monitor.
[groans]
That name makes me wanna barf.
- Nice to have you back, Vibe.
- Let's just get
to Nash's work site.
- Right this way.
Huh.
That's new.
- We gotta get in there.
[breach whooshes]
Who's there?
- Nash, is that you?
- [whispering]
I am no longer Nash, I am...
Pariah.
And I'm here to bear witness.
- To what?
- Tragedy.
- Mm-hmm, new name,
new suit...
guess no one's consulting me
anymore, huh?
- Wait, what exactly happened?
- I searched these tunnels
as Nash for Mar Novu
to kill him,
expose him as a false god,
and now I'm being
controlled by another god.
- And that's the...
[clears throat]
Anti-Monitor?
- He laid a perfect trail
for me to follow,
but all along,
he was manipulating me
so that he could gain
a foothold in this universe.
- Why didn't you resist him?
- His will was too strong
and now I am forced
to bear witness
as he destroys
world after world.
- That's why
we're gonna stop him.
Now can you open that door?
- I cannot.
My memories as Nash
are somehow lost to me
as Pariah, but you can.
- By vibing those memories?
- Yes.
[slow dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[mysterious energetic music]
[glyphs tinkling]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- What did you see?
- A way in.
- You think the book can bring
back the destroyed Earths?
[laughs]
Oh, too good.
- We don't have time for this.
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- Tell us how to use the book
or lose an arm...your choice.
- Do the strong-arm tactics
work in Gotham City?
- [grunts]
- [gasps and groans]
The book channels
ancient and endless power.
It takes immense willpower
and focus to make it work.
- What did you focus on?
- His hatred for Superman.
- Got it in one.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
But that was easy
for the book to provide.
You try to use it on the scale
that you're talking about,
and it could drive you mad.
Like Deegan.
♪ ♪
[force field whooshes]
- Kara, there's no telling
what kind of ripple effect
this could have.
- I'm supposed to be the
Paragon of Hope, right?
Maybe this is my role,
to bring back my Earth and...
and Argo and all the others.
I have to find a way
to fix this.
♪ ♪
- See you soon.
[thumping electronic music]
- So why did we take a detour
to another parallel Earth?
- So many Earths
are already gone.
The pillars of magic
are crumbling,
leaving me the worse for wear,
so I can't get us
into Purgatory.
But don't worry, squire.
Luckily, I know a guy.
- Oh, you're gonna love her.
She's pretty much
up for everything.
- Always a pleasure
to see you, Lucy.
- [scoffs]
- It's time.
- Excuse me, ladies.
Seems like you're not the only
ones who want a piece of me.
I'll see you later.
Johnny.
[chuckles]
I'd like to say it's a pleasure
to see you on my Earth
outside my club.
It's not.
[chuckles]
Hello.
Don't believe we've met.
Lucifer Morningstar.
- Lucifer Morningstar,
as in...
- The devil.
Yes, exactly.
So tell me.
What is it you desire?
- I...
I, uh...
I desire to get my father back.
- [chuckles]
Daddy issues.
Why didn't you say so?
- Look, I don't know
if you have an Oliver Queen
on your world,
but ours has, uh,
shuffled off this mortal coil.
- A soul retrieval, blah, blah,
blah, the worlds are ending.
It's all very Biblical, John.
[inhales deeply]
Okay, okay.
I'm only doing this
'cause I owe you for Maz.
- Yeah, you do.
- You remind me
of my brother, by the way...
tall, dark, annoyed by me.
- You gonna help us or not?
- Oh, flirt.
The devil always sees through
on a deal.
Take this card.
You'll have a limited time
once inside Purgatory,
and once the picture
completely fades...
- Our souls will be decimated,
blah, blah, blah.
- And trapped
in eternity forever,
so I don't recommend it.
Consider us even,
John Constan-tine.
- [chuckles]
Constantine.
- [chuckling] Is it?
I don't care.
Always a pleasure
doing business with mortals.
Eh?
- He forgot to tell us
what to do.
- Did he, now?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Ah.
Welcome to Purgatory.
- Looks a lot like Lian Yu.
- Which is Mandarin
for "purgatory."
- Lovely little
coincidence, eh?
- Any idea why Dad's soul
would choose to come here?
- Souls choose their prisons.
This place must be
what Oliver thinks about
when being trapped
for all eternity.
It's a funny thing too,
considering his memories
are probably missing.
- What are you talking about?
- The second that
Oliver's soul landed here,
his memories would've been...
how can I put it?
Squeegeed.
- So we'll have
to make him remember us.
- Bollocks.
We'll have
to get a move on as well.
This card is already
beginning to fade.
Well, when you work
with the devil
you never know
quite what you're getting.
- No pressure there, right?
- [whooshes]
Perimeter's clear.
There's no sign of any
Quantum Tower on Earth-1.
What are you doing here,
Pariah?
- Behind this wall...
his domain.
- What Mr. Green Jeans
is trying to say
is once we get inside,
we can actually stop
the anti-matter wave
right at the source.
- All right, let's do it.
[soft suspenseful music]
[glyphs tinkling]
♪ ♪
[stones scraping]
- Whoa.
This place has some
crazy vibrational frequency
surging through it.
- This place is the nexus
between the anti-matter
universe and your own.
Behold, Anti-Matter Cannon...
this is the source of the wave.
- Guys, I think
this blur is alive.
- Let me check it out.
- No!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[energy cracks]
- [grunts]
- Barry!
- What happened?
- It's a force field.
I couldn't get through.
It's the Flash from Earth-90.
He's trapped on that treadmill.
- That's Barry Allen
from Earth-90?
- How did he get there?
- The Monitor sent him away.
- You will not do to this
Earth what you did to mine.
[whooshes]
- He wound up
in the Netherverse
where the Anti-Monitor
found him,
corralled his speed,
used it to build
his Anti-Matter Cannon,
test-fired it...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Destroying Earth-2.
- Harry's gone?
- Jesse.
- Pariah,
how do we stop the cannon?
- The force field that contains
this is anti-matter based.
As such,
anything made of positive
matter cannot penetrate it.
- We have to get the Flash
off that treadmill.
The Monitor said
Vibe had to live...
that he had a purpose.
Maybe this is it.
♪ ♪
- Here goes nothing.
- [grunts and groans]
♪ ♪
- Thank you for the reprieve.
[breathes heavily]
But you gotta
put me back on it.
[energy booms and crackles]
- Guys.
- The Anti-Monitor designed
that treadmill with a failsafe
so that if I ever got off
of it, it would erupt,
destroying all remaining
Earths at once.
We only have a few minutes.
- Pariah, how do...
Pariah?
Where'd he go?
♪ ♪
- Amanda, please.
I know the red skies
are freaky, honey,
but I'm sure
it's just atmospheric...
- [clears throat]
Dr. Ryan Choi?
- Disturbance.
Babe, I gotta go.
Wow, is that really you?
Dr. Ray Palmer?
Oh. Emm. Gosh.
I'm Ryan Choi.
It's so wonderful to meet you.
Your second paper on
subatomic density manipulation
was the foundation for my work
on miniaturization.
- Wow, thank you.
You know, I...
- Okay, Dr. Choi,
we need you to come
with us right now.
- Look, you've seen
the red skies outside?
The world is ending.
- Dr. Palmer,
who are these people?
- [exhales deeply]
We are superheroes,
and Ryan,
we need your help.
- [laughs]
Sure, Dr. Palmer.
Good one.
And next you're gonna tell me
I've been nominated
for the Breakthrough Prize
in Fundamental Physics?
- Okay, we don't have time
for this.
- Seeing is believing, right?
[rousing music]
Tissue?
- You're Elongated Man?
♪ ♪
Are...are you superheroes, too?
- I know
this sounds cuckoo, pal,
but you're what's called
a Paragon,
which is a fancy word
for saying,
"We need your help
to save the universe."
- Dr. Choi.
- If the world's ending,
I need to go home.
- Please, Ryan.
We really need your help.
- No, you don't.
I'm no hero.
I'm a husband.
And if this is the end, I have
to be with my wife and kid.
I'm sorry.
[computer chimes]
[ominous music]
- Another Earth is gone.
- There's only seven left
in the multiverse.
It's ironic.
I'm watching
the biggest event in history,
the destruction of every Earth,
and no one will ever
read the story.
- These Earths are not
the only worlds destroyed.
My world died.
My family.
[soft dramatic music]
- What were they like?
- Mm.
♪ ♪
So full of life.
[chuckles]
They were everything to me.
If only I'd cared
as much for them
as I did my work.
[indistinct]
♪ ♪
I now understand why
you are such a good reporter,
Miss Lane.
[breach whooshes]
- [grunts and shouts]
- Clark?
- [breathing heavily]
I couldn't save them.
- You wanna take a minute?
Looks like you could
use a breather.
- Put this on,
this crest...
I made a promise
to keep fighting
no matter what.
- Hey, why'd you
add black to it?
♪ ♪
- Because, Lois,
even in the darkest times,
hope cuts through.
Hope is the light that lifts us
out of darkness.
I must go back.
[sighs]
[breach whooshes]
- Guy never quits no matter
what Earth he's from, huh?
Now you're just talking
to yourself.
[structure rumbling]
- It's getting worse.
- Put me back
on that treadmill.
- No, all right?
We'll find another way.
[thunder cracks and echoes]
[electricity crackling]
[dramatic music]
- Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Send me back to Freeland now!
[electricity crackles]
- Calm down, Electric Guy.
- The name is Black Lightning.
[energy bolts crackle]
♪ ♪
[both groan]
- Enough!
I did not bring you here,
Jefferson, to fight.
I brought you here
to save lives.
- Who the hell are you people?
- I am Pariah.
This is Jefferson Pierce.
On his Earth...
an educator,
a father, and a hero.
- What do you mean, my Earth?
- There are multiple Earths,
Jefferson...
many Earths like this one.
Your Earth...
♪ ♪
Has just been destroyed
by a wave of anti-matter.
- So...so...
Lynn, my girls?
- They're gone.
I transported you here
to help us save humanity.
- [growls]
You should've saved
my family, not me!
Not me!
- Jefferson.
I'm so sorry.
Right now we need your help
to stop this anti-matter wave.
I can't imagine
how you're feeling,
but I do know how it feels
to lose your family.
♪ ♪
What would they want you
to do right now?
- Please.
All worlds could die.
♪ ♪
- What do you need from me?
- That machine behind you
is the source
of the anti-matter wave.
- We have to disable it,
but we can't get near it.
Can you contain
that much energy?
♪ ♪
[energy thrumming]
- Let's find out.
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
[grunts]
- Don't.
You open that book, and you
do not know what will happen.
Do you?
To all of the Earths
you're trying to save?
- I have to, Kate.
Those people?
They need help.
- And we are doing our best
to help who we can.
That is not the answer.
- Then what am I
supposed to do?
Just be okay with
all those people dying?
Like Bruce?
Believe that if life's
supposed to end, just let it?
- No, of course not,
but if you open that book,
it will destroy you.
- I have to do this.
- [inhales deeply]
Then I have to stop you.
[tense music]
- You won't be able to.
♪ ♪
- You'd be surprised.
I wish things
were different, Kara.
I wish I was hopeful like you.
But one thing I do know is if
you take a chance on that book
and it doesn't work
and something happens to you,
we're all doomed.
♪ ♪
[exhales]
- [groans loudly]
Tick, tock, people.
- Black Lightning
is gonna kill himself
if we don't solve this soon.
- Then we need more time.
[energy crackling]
Every second that we waste here
another Earth dies.
That wave gets closer
to my wife.
- I was married once, too.
Tina always said
that keeping me running
was her purpose in life,
so as someone who's
been running for 30 years,
let me tell you.
Sometimes,
in order to find
your purpose as a hero,
you gotta take
a couple steps back.
Reverse the way
you see the situation
and see a bigger picture.
- That's it.
[dramatic music]
I know how to stop the cannon.
This is what The Monitor meant
that day in the Time Vault.
This is what I've been running
towards all these years.
It's time for Flash
to vanish in Crisis.
[dramatic music]
- Reversing the treadmill's
directional velocity
could make the
anti-matter wave recede
and funnel back into
the speed cannon...
- Destroying the machine
and the wave...
- Ending this once
and for all...
- Freeing me from
the Anti-Monitor's control.
- [grunts and groans loudly]
Where's the future?
Right here.
Whose life is this?
Mine.
What are you gonna do with it?
Live it
by any means necessary.
- It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna find him.
- You don't know that.
Dad's soul
could be lost forever.
- Family's everything to Oliver.
He'll come back to us.
- [growls]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, Oliver, Oliver!
Oliver, wait, man.
Listen to me.
I see you, man,
and I'm so sorry
that I wasn't there
to have your back during
Crisis, but I'm here now.
I need you to come back to us.
You're my brother.
[soft dramatic music]
I can't lose you, man.
♪ ♪
I can't lose you.
- [panting]
- Hey, John.
♪ ♪
- Mia, you came.
- Of course I did.
♪ ♪
- They're beautiful.
I didn't get to introduce
myself earlier, Dr. Choi.
I'm Iris West-Allen
from Central City.
- Are you a superhero, too?
- No, I'm just like you.
Look, I know this
is a lot to ask
and you're right to want
to be with your family
when things go bad.
- [sighs]
What about you?
You clearly have someone
in your life you care about.
Don't you want to die holding
them when the world ends?
- My husband's not like us.
He goes out there
as a superhero day after day
and faces whatever he has to
to keep his city safe.
- That's really brave, Iris,
but that's not me.
See, I'm nothing
like your husband.
- No, no, you're not.
[soft dramatic music]
You're human,
and we have a purpose too.
We remind superheroes
what they're fighting for.
- My wife, Amanda and I,
just had a baby six months ago.
Simone.
I might not get
to see her grow up.
- Don't you want to hold her
knowing that
you had a hand
in making the world safer?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I need to go tell my wife
I'm gonna be late for dinner.
- [exhales deeply]
- Just got word from Lois.
Six more Earths are gone.
This is the only Earth left.
- At least now we have Ryan.
- Yeah.
- How'd you know
what to say to him?
♪ ♪
- Iris.
- Hey, what is it?
- What if this is it?
What if
stopping the wave
is my purpose as a Paragon?
I mean, what if it's
the sacrifice I have to make?
- Well, if this is it,
then I don't want you
to die without me, Barry.
I don't want you to be alone.
I'll come with you.
- No.
You can't come, Iris.
I may be the one
with superpowers,
but your intelligence,
your resourcefulness,
your heart...
that's your superpower and
that's what's gonna help you
convince Ryan Choi
to be the hero he needs to be.
- Barry, I don't want
to live this life without you.
I don't...
I don't want to say goodbye.
- When I put this ring
on your finger,
I promised I'd always
come running home to you.
[tender music]
And if we're apart,
for however long,
know that wherever I go,
I will be running home to you.
♪ ♪
- Are you still sure
you want me to go?
- Yeah.
Go find Ryan Choi
and hurry back.
- I'll see you soon.
[sniffles]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Caitlin.
- I don't wanna say goodbye.
- You two were there
the first time
I opened my eyes
as the Flash.
I couldn't be the hero I am
without you guys.
♪ ♪
Tell Joe and Iris I love them.
- We will.
- Sorry, kid,
but this has to happen.
[energy crackles]
- Barry, what are you doing?
- I'm momentarily
stealing your speed.
You play the speedster game
long enough,
you learn some neat tricks.
- Wait, why are you doing this?
- Novu said the Flash
must die in Crisis.
He never said which one.
♪ ♪
[lightning crackling]
- [groans]
[electricity booms
and whooshes]
[groans]
- You're a true hero,
Jefferson.
I can't thank you enough.
♪ ♪
Open the breach.
I need to get
in that force field.
- No.
- Do you want
your friend to die?
Let me do this.
Let me save you all.
- Cisco, don't.
♪ ♪
[groans]
Cisco, come on.
♪ ♪
[breach whooshes]
- Thank you.
Keep riding the lightning, son.
I know you'll make us
all proud.
[breach whooshes]
- [grunts]
Barry!
He's gonna die, Cisco!
- You made me team leader,
and sometimes,
the leader has to make
the tough choices.
♪ ♪
- We can't stay here.
- Let's go.
- No.
- No, I'm not done...
- Barry, let's go!
- I'm not going!
- Come on!
♪ ♪
- [panting]
I have faith in you, Tina.
- Well, the truth is,
I have faith in you, too.
♪ ♪
- [bellows]
[anti-matter sizzles and snaps]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
- I hate to break up
the reunion,
but this really is our cue
to make like a tree
and get Oliver's soul back
to his body.
- Oliver Queen.
[soft dramatic music]
- Who are you?
- Jim Corrigan.
- Another one I know.
- But I'm also someone else.
I'm something else...
a spectre.
[mysterious energies whisper]
- Take a hike, crazy eyes.
- In another life, I was
a decorated police officer,
a hero in my own right,
but then I was called
to a higher purpose.
It's your turn now, Oliver.
[tense music]
Only you can light
the spark, Oliver.
It is your destiny.
- What is my destiny?
- To save everyone.
Otherwise, all universes...
all the people you love
will perish.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, but I have to.
- Dad, no.
- It's gonna be okay.
[dramatic music]
It's going to be okay.
♪ ♪
What now?
- Dad, wait.
I love...
[energies whooshing]
♪ ♪
- What happened?
- Dad wouldn't
come back with us.
- I'm sorry, Sara.
- The others fare any better?
- Barry's team stopped
the anti-matter wave
with one Earth left.
- I need a drink.
- I appreciate you
helping us, Jefferson.
I know what you've lost.
- My world...
I lost the love of my life,
my two daughters.
Nothing will ever
be okay again.
- I know.
That Flash,
the Flash from Earth-90...
he looked just like my dad,
Henry Allen.
He was a resilient man.
He spent years in prison
for the murder of my mom,
a crime one of my enemies
committed and framed him for.
Through all that,
he never lost his light.
[soft dramatic music]
Times like this,
I try and do the same.
- My father, uh,
Alvin Pierce...
he was a good man, too.
Reporter.
Spent his life giving
a voice to the voiceless.
♪ ♪
He was murdered when I was 12.
But I still carry the lessons
he taught me to this day.
I passed them along
to my girls.
[takes deep breath]
My girls.
♪ ♪
[sniffs]
Anyway, I get it.
[sniffles, clears throat]
Look.
I don't think Henry or Alvin
raised any quitters,
so we should
honor their memory...
and rage...
against the dying of the light.
- Dylan Thomas.
- Well, all right then, Flash.
- It's Barry.
Barry Allen.
[music building]
- Jefferson Pierce.
- Hey, Kara.
Listen, I...I get you wanted
to bring those people back.
You have the biggest heart
of anyone that I've ever met.
I just don't want
to see you get hurt.
- [scoffs]
You know, I gotta say.
For someone who was unsure
that they were
the Paragon of Courage,
took a lot of guts
to do what you did.
- Maybe.
But I have hope that
there's a better way.
[soft dramatic music]
Which is why...
which is why I wanted
to give you this.
♪ ♪
- Kryptonite.
Why do you have that?
- It was Bruce Wayne's.
He lost hope and I never will.
♪ ♪
- Keep it.
I have the courage that
you'll never have to use it.
♪ ♪
- Attention.
Iris, Ralph, and Raymond
have returned with Dr. Choi.
[tender piano music]
- Iris.
I told you I'd come
running home to you.
♪ ♪
- It wasn't you, then?
- It was the Barry Allen
from Earth-90.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Everyone,
this is Jefferson Pierce.
We wouldn't have been able
to stop the anti-matter wave
without him.
- Wait, so...
so the Superman thing is real?
Oh, damn.
After all these years.
- And this is your Paragon
of Humanity, Ryan Choi...
scientist, super brain,
and ready to help
save the universe.
- How do you guys plan
on doing that, exactly?
- Well, Kara decided not
to use the Book of Destiny.
- It was too risky.
- And Harbinger, unlike me,
can travel anywhere she wants.
So how do we find her?
- By whatever means necessary.
♪ ♪
- Well, we can start by trying
to re-task the Waverider's
satellite search grid.
♪ ♪
[energy whooshes]
- Lyla.
- Johnny.
- You okay?
- I'm sorry.
I tried to get word to you that
I was doing recon on Earth-1,
but the deaths
of the other Earths
is affecting my abilities.
- Where were you on Earth-1?
- I...
I can't remember.
- It's okay.
I thought I lost you, Lyla.
- Not that easy.
I just...
wish I could remember
what happened.
[takes deep breath]
- We'll figure this out.
- [whispering]
What if the Anti-Monitor
wanted Harbinger
back on the ship?
- [whispering]
He's been controlling her
the entire Crisis.
- And controlling you,
only allowing you to appear
when he wants you to see...
- A great tragedy.
[suspenseful music]
[normally] Lyla?
- Lyla.
[energies whooshing]
[grunts]
- No!
[dramatic music]
- [Anti-Monitor's voice]
It is time
to end the age of heroes
and everything you hold close.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Lyla.
- That is no longer your wife,
John Diggle.
She has been taken by...
- The Anti-Monitor.
- Murderer!
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
- This is for my girls.
[energy reverberates]
[tense dramatic music]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
- Lyla!
You have to fight him, Lyla!
- The fate of all humanity
lies with you now, Pariah.
- What can I do?
- You will know
when the moment arrives.
[energy beams whooshing]
♪ ♪
[energy beams crackling]
- [in Anti-Monitor's voice]
Pathetic.
It was foolish
to try to stop me, Novu.
- No, Mobius.
[breathes heavily]
It was foolish to allow your
creation in the first place.
- Goodbye.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[computer chimes]
- [gasps softly]
- Alert.
Earth-1 is gone.
- We're all that's left?
- It is done.
The infinite Earths are gone.
Soon only the anti-matter
universe will remain.
[warning chimes]
- Warning.
The anti-matter wave will hit
the ship in 28 seconds.
- I know what I must do.
[energy whooshing]
♪ ♪
- What's happening?
- Iris.
- Everyone to the bridge.
Now.
- Where did you send them?
- Somewhere
you can't touch 'em.
- Wherever they are,
they're gonna fight you.
- By any means necessary.
- To their very last breath.
♪ ♪
- What the hell just happened?
- Where are we?
[soft dramatic music]
- This is the Vanishing Point.
[KATE]
- What does that mean?
- It's a point outside
of time and space.
- What happened to the
Waverider and the others?
- The Anti-Monitor...
he used Harbinger to attack us.
Pariah must have
sent us here knowing
that the Anti-Monitor
couldn't follow.
- Well, we have to go back.
We have to go back right now!
- Barry, we can't.
They're gone.
♪ ♪
[quavering]
No.
[energy ringing out]
- [strained] Something's wrong.
- [Kara] Kal?
Kal?
- Something's wrong.
[grunts]
- Hey, hey, hey!
- I can't...
- Come on.
Please.
Fix it.
- [gasps]
What do I do?
[energy rings out loudly]
- [groans]
- No, no!
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, I am so happy
that worked.
- Lex, what did you do?
- Well, I held
the Book of Destiny
and I saw you seven Paragons
due to be stranded
at the Vanishing Point,
and I thought destiny
could use
a little rewrite.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So...
what do we do now?
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.