[MAN &amp; WOMAN LAUGHING]
MAN: Farooq!
-It's not safe. Come down.
Farooq, I'm serious. It's gonna rain.
Y'all are tripping.
This is the best seat in the house. Whoo!
You know, when I said we should watch
the particle accelerator turn on...
...I just meant we should get naked
and howl at the moon.
[LAUGHING]
It's already on. Consider me unimpressed.
Whoo! Yeah, baby!
-Oh, my God. This is awesome.
-Are you seeing this?
-Oh, man. I think I am tripping.
WOMAN: Ha, ha, ha.
MAN:
Oh, man.
Get in the car! Get in the car!
[GRUNTING]
Farooq!
-Oh, my God, Farooq!
-Farooq!
Argh!
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
-Good day, Dr. Wells.
-One can always hope, Gideon.
-Bring up my log, would you?
-Certainly.
-Go ahead, doctor.
-New entry.
It has now been 311 days
since lightning struck.
Subject has begun relying
on his speed in everyday life.
Using his extraordinary powers...
...to solve ordinary problems.
[ALARM BUZZING]
I'm late.
WELLS:
Accomplish ordinary tasks.
Unfortunately, his penchant
for the heroic persists.
I hate it when they let the new guy
train during the morning rush.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
WELLS: The fact is...
-Don't try nothing.
-...he can be a bit of a show-off.
-Wallet. Now.
Oh, this is awesome.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Hold on, okay? I'm gonna set this down.
Heh, heh. This is crazy. There are hundreds
of thousands of people in Central City.
Out of everyone you could
have picked to rob, you pick me. Heh, heh.
What are you, sick? Money. Now.
You're really gonna
be kicking yourself, man.
I mean, if there was an Olympics
for bad luck, you didn't just medal, pal.
You Michael Phelps-ed.
I'm gonna count to three,
then I'm gonna shoot you.
-One...
-Yeah.
...two...
WELLS: And while his desire
to help others is commendable...
...it is impeding him from realizing
the full scope of his abilities.
But...
...there's still time.
As the future remains intact.
-Where's Barry? He's late.
-Late is kind of his signature move.
Hey, you guys wanna see
my signature move?
Sorry, guys. I got a little held up.
You had to be there.
I'm gonna need a moment
or two alone with Barry.
Ooh, you're in trouble.
WELLS:
Now, may I remind you, Mr. Allen...
...we had an agreement that we would help
with your heroics...
...while you would help us research
and develop your abilities in here. Right?
Yeah. No, I know.
I guess I've just gotten a little caught up
with being able to help people.
Put bad guys away. Feels good.
Imagine how good it would feel to cure
diseases, stop aging, reverse paralysis.
All good causes.
So how can I help you do that?
You need more MRIs? More blood?
I need more speed.
-Okay.
-Speed is the key to progress.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
You need to kick it up a notch.
There was a homicide.
I'm sorry. I've gotta go.
This is not just about you.
Remember that, Barry.
Yeah.
-I hope you both skipped your breakfast.
-Whoa.
What the hell could do that?
Two thousand four hundred degrees,
give or take.
This area is filled with combustibles.
How come nothing else burned up?
Where you going?
See the soot on the ground
where the cement is burnt?
JOE: Yeah.
-That's evidence of arc blasts.
Happens when high amperage currents
travel or arc through the air.
There's no live wires.
There's no utility poles.
So how was this guy electrocuted?
The first thing we need to do is ID him.
BARRY:
Yeah.
His face is melted off.
How's that picture gonna help ID him?
-I've got mad skills
-Please don't ever say that again.
All right.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine. Why?
I don't know. You seem a little off.
No, I'm fine.
All right.
CISCO:
Facial reconstructive software.
It was designed for archeologists,
and it should help us ID your crispy corpse.
BARRY:
How did he get fried in the first place?
Is there a metahuman
that can control electricity?
It'd take a serious electrostatic discharge
to cause that tissue damage.
Guys, according to the software...
...there's an 82 percent chance
your victim looked like this.
-Eighty-two?
-It was zero when you walked in here, pal.
Cross reference with the DMV database?
Get a name?
Absolutely.
This software can do just about anything.
Now that Felicity reprogrammed it.
Casey Donahue. No wife, no kids. Used to
work at the Petersburg electrical substation.
That can't be a coincidence.
That's weird. Someone just used his ID
to enter the substation.
The Petersburg grid is experiencing
a power drain right now.
Barry be...
...careful.
I'm pretty sure this is a restricted area.
Easy there, zappy.
I have to feed.
[GRUNTING]
Whoa, what was that?
More of that.
I need more.
Barry, what's happening?
[GRUNTING]
FAROOQ:
Too much.
WELLS:
Get out of there.
[PANTING]
Run, Barry.
I can't.
My speed...
...is gone.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
-He runs slow even for a normal person.
BARRY: Unh.
You can't just lose your powers. Okay?
Your DNA was transformed
by the particle accelerator blast.
There's no way to untransform DNA.
Yeah? Tell that to the Uber driver
who charged me 65 bucks to take me here.
Had to say I was coming
from a cosplay party.
So we were wrong. This metahuman doesn't
electrocute people. He siphons electricity...
...thereby removing your power.
All right, do we think this is temporary or...?
We have to run tests.
Yeah.
I've gotta warn Joe.
WELLS: Barry, we will find a way
to restore your speed.
I promise you that.
-You didn't catch it.
-I loved that mug.
What part of "a metahuman stole
my speed" didn't you understand?
Barry, there's no part of anything
you can do that I ever understand.
-What does Dr. Wells say?
-He's working on it.
Barry, you have to get your speed back.
The people in this city need protecting.
If you don't get your speed,
how the hell are we gonna keep them safe?
The meta who stole my speed, he burned
up the body we saw in the alley today.
Tell the police not to confront him.
He's dangerous.
IRIS: Who's dangerous?
-No one.
-Just some thief.
-Well, criminals better watch out.
Cops in Central City are the best there are.
And if you can't protect this city, Dad,
I know the Flash will.
What if he can't? What if he's gone?
Gone?
Or maybe he's just done.
Or maybe whatever he could do before,
he can't do anymore.
Don't you have some place to be?
Yeah. I'm going.
Aw. Barry loved that mug.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
That's a quality timepiece, young man.
Oh. Um, thanks.
They took mine.
All of them.
Guess you shouldn't have done
whatever it is you did.
-Gideon, show me the future.
GIDEON: Certainly, doctor.
[GASPS]
Run a complete search.
Show any references to the Flash.
-Zero references to the Flash.
-Look again.
Zero references.
-Show any references to Barry Allen.
-Zero references to Barry Allen.
-Look again.
-I've searched 3452 times, Dr. Wells.
There's nothing.
-You think I'll ever wear it again?
-I hope so.
I didn't have my speed for very long.
But now that it's gone,
it feels like part of me is gone too.
With or without your speed,
you're still you, Barry.
But I'm not.
I'm not the best version of me.
I love being the Flash.
[BARRY CHUCKLES]
I love everything about it.
The feeling of running
hundreds of miles per hour.
Wind and power just rushing past my face.
Being able to help people.
I'm not sure I can live without it, Caitlin.
CISCO:
Farooq Gibran.
BARRY: Who?
-The powers vampire who jacked your speed.
I hacked into surveillance footage from
the substation. It was easy to find a match.
BARRY: He climbed an electrical tower
the night of the accelerator explosion.
No surprise where his powers came from.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
This is not happening.
Dr. Harrison Wells, I need to see you!
Come on. I know you're inside.
Open the door.
I just wanna talk, Dr. Wells.
Wells, let me in!
Joe.
Hello, Iris.
I am out. I need you to cover for me
until the shift change.
Only one headline. Prison transfer.
William Tockman.
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
[GUNSHOT AND ALL GASP]
Guns on the floor.
It should take you
less than three seconds...
...to discard any thought
of rebellion and comply.
[MAN GRUNTS]
I take it I don't need to count out loud.
[GUNSHOT AND ALL GASP]
Hm. Hm.
Striking resemblance.
He's inside.
[SIREN WAILING]
Captain, Tockman has at least 10 hostages.
Two officers down.
-Copy that. When is the power back?
MAN: We're on gennies for now.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Not now.
BARRY: Wait.
Capt. Singh, I've been trying to get in touch
with Joe or anyone at the precinct.
There's a hostage situation, Barry.
Joe's inside, so is his daughter.
-I'll call you when I know more.
-Wait.
[LINE CLICKS]
Joe and Iris are in trouble.
I need my powers back now.
I have a theory. It's untested.
-I'm willing to roll the dice.
-Okay. You've lost your speed. Yes.
But nothing has changed
inside you on a subatomic level.
-Your cells are still primed.
-They just need a jump-start.
Okay, how do we jump-start me?
Replicate the initial jolt to your system.
But that would mean a peak current
of at least 20,000 kiloamps.
That's more electricity than they
give to people in the electric chair.
Caitlin, with Farooq in the building,
we're looking at a death sentence.
CISCO:
The spare generator's offline.
If we reboot it,
we could get a charge that big.
We need something
that can transmit the load...
...from the generator to Barry
without shorting out.
The treadmill.
My baby could take the charge.
-What if Barry can't?
WELLS: Well, that's up to Mr. Allen.
CAITLIN:
Where are you going?
I'm gonna talk to him.
-Nope. Nope.
BARRY: Okay...
...you didn't see him at the substation.
He needed to feed.
I got super speed
out of the particle accelerator blast.
But his best friends died.
He woke up with a disease.
Earlier today, you worked a crime scene...
...where this metahuman
electrocuted an innocent man.
He's a murderer.
And you are powerless
to defend yourself against him.
He may just need help like I did.
I don't need my powers to offer him that.
I have to try.
Tockman.
I am presently in control
of eight of Central City's finest...
...three underpaid assistants,
and one very brave civilian girl.
You've got demands. I wanna hear them.
But first, let the civilians go.
Would you prefer
I sent them out alive or dead?
Please be more specific.
One helicopter.
One vegetarian takeout meal.
One laptop with eight gigabytes of RAM
will be delivered on this roof...
...at exactly 53 minutes
and 27 seconds from now...
...or I shoot a hostage.
There is a citywide blackout.
I'm gonna need more time.
Captain, you may delay, but time will not.
Benjamin Franklin.
Very good, detective.
Hey, whoa. Whoa, easy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
[SCOFFS]
You can't hurt me.
Where is Harrison Wells?
Look, I know what happened to you.
The night of the accelerator explosion,
it changed you.
It changed me too.
You were the one in the red suit.
I fed from you.
-I have to keep feeding.
-Right. I know this has to be terrifying.
That's why I wanna help you.
Okay?
The night of the explosion
when the light hit me, it stopped my heart.
-Jake and Darya.
-They were your friends.
I woke up and they were beside me, dead.
They tried to give me CPR.
They were touching me and...
...I electrocuted them.
This is not your fault.
I know.
Wells did this to me.
Farooq, you need to listen to me.
[BARRY GRUNTING]
-Not sure how long that'll hold.
-Done being noble, Mr. Allen?
Caitlin, get him to the treadmill.
Cisco, bring the generator online.
Make sure Barry gets the charge.
What? You're not coming with me?
I am not leaving you.
Listen to me.
Of everything I've done in my life...
...of everything I have invented,
my most important creation is the Flash.
Barry Allen must have a future. Now, go.
Go.
[FAROOQ GRUNTING]
End this now, and I'll talk to the DA.
It was your district attorney
that denied me furlough...
...so I could visit my dying sister
one last time.
Say goodbye to her in person.
Time I'll never get back!
So however long I have in this life...
...I promise not one second more...
...will be spent in a prison cell.
-Unh!
-Got him.
IRIS:
Eddie!
Eddie. Eddie.
An officer was just shot 9.2 seconds ago.
I'd pick up the pace
in meeting my demands, captain.
[BARRY GRUNTING]
I'm not healing fast anymore.
-That's unfortunate.
-Don't worry.
When Dr. Wells has a theory,
he's usually right.
What if something happens
to Joe and Iris first?
[CLATTERING]
Come to check on your pet?
Why don't you just kill me, huh?
Get it over with.
Quid pro quo.
That's Latin, Mr. Woodward.
You've heard of Latin?
Quid pro quo means
"something for something."
And in this case
that something is your freedom.
I'm prepared to grant it to you.
How do you know I won't kill you?
A calculated risk. One I'm willing to take.
-Really?
-That's right.
-Why would you do that?
-Because...
...there is another metahuman
loose in this facility.
And I want you to kill him.
FAROOQ: Did you know the human body
generates electricity?
The average person gives off 342 watts.
And I can smell it coming from you.
Turn on the treadmill.
-You're still hurt.
-We don't have time.
Been dying to punch somebody.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Ouch.
-Caitlin.
-I can't.
-We don't have a choice.
-If I turn this on, it could kill you.
If you don't, we could all die.
I already lost someone I cared about
in this building. I can't do it again.
[SIGHS]
Listen.
Someone once told me that I was
struck by that lightning for a reason.
That it chose me.
I'm not sure I believe it.
Right now, it doesn't matter what I believe.
What do you believe?
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
Unh!
My God. You okay?
Did you feel anything?
It didn't work.
[THUMP]
Please. He's bleeding.
You have to let us get him some help.
You'll stay where you are.
While you're killing time,
he's bleeding out.
[TOCKMAN CHUCKLES]
"As if you could kill time
without wounding eternity."
Henry David Thoreau.
Good.
-Little battlefield trick.
-Eddie.
[EDDIE SCREAMING]
If he lives long enough
to receive medical treatment...
...they'll know the exact time
the tourniquet was applied.
[GRUNTING]
What? No "thank you"? Heh, heh.
They call you the Clock King, right?
A somewhat florid appellation,
but I've grown to see the humor in it.
-You're going back to prison.
-Really? Heh, heh.
-And how do you reckon?
-Because the Flash is coming.
Oh.
Where are you?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING
AND TONY GRUNTS]
AND TONY GRUNTING]
Tony. Tony, what are you doing?
TONY:
Come on. You know me, Allen.
I never run from a fight.
All right. Well, stay with me. Okay?
You're good.
Run. Unh.
What?
Hey.
Tony.
No.
Barry.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Early.
You ever see the city at night by helicopter?
It's quite spectacular.
[BARRY PANTING]
CISCO:
You're winded. That's not good.
I need to take your blood
and figure out what happened.
I can't believe he's dead.
Dr. Wells?
BARRY:
No. No. Tony Woodward.
-He escaped the Pipeline.
-He must've got out when the blackout hit.
Not possible. The Pipeline was designed
to withstand power outage.
Someone had to have let him go.
WELLS:
I did.
I released him.
Why?
To divert our intruder's attention
while we worked to restore your speed.
You used him as a distraction?
An unnecessary one as it turns out,
it seems the plan has failed.
I have his blood on me.
How could you do that?
You're showing sentiment
for a man who tormented you as a child.
Tony might've been a bully then and now,
but he didn't deserve to die.
Does Caitlin, or Cisco, or me, or you?
I had a choice to make, him or us.
I chose us without a second thought.
Well, all your talk about miracle cures
and scientific breakthroughs...
...but you don't care about people at all.
Maybe you care too much.
Being a hero is important to you.
I respect your ideals.
I don't have the luxury of sharing them.
I forgot. Your game's chess.
We're all just pawns to you. Right?
So, what's your move, doctor?
Which one of us gets sacrificed next?
We have to get out.
We just left him on D-level.
We'll never make the main entrance
from here.
What about the garage?
The mobile lab van?
WELLS:
It's my move, Mr. Allen.
And I say we make a run for it.
CAITLIN:
Oh, my God. Barry, look.
Your cells are rapidly regenerating.
-I still don't have my speed.
-It must be mental.
Not physical.
-Ho-ho. You have the yips.
-The whats?
When a second baseman
all of a sudden can't throw to first...
...or a golfer tries to putt,
and they get all embarrassed and upset.
That makes the yips worse, and it's a hot
mess. They feel like even more of a failure.
That's not helping.
You asked if I believed you were struck by
lightning for a reason, if you were chosen.
I believe.
You should too.
[THUMPING]
Let's move.
Tockman, no. No. Don't do this.
Not her. Take me. Please.
Something tells me you will not
be a docile passenger. She will.
-Dad. Dad.
-Wait. Wait. Let her say goodbye.
This is her boyfriend lying here dying.
I think you and me both know
that he probably won't make it.
It's wrong you didn't get to
say goodbye to your sister.
Give them what you deserved.
You have 20 seconds.
Eddie. Eddie.
-Sorry, babe.
-No. Please.
You have to hang on for me. Okay?
I'm gonna be right back.
EDDIE [WHISPERS]:
Ankle holster.
TOCKMAN:
Let's go.
Second van. Keys are inside.
BARRY:
Come on.
Get in. Come on.
[ENGINE SPUTTERS]
[ENGINE STALLING]
Come on.
He's here.
BARRY:
Unh!
CAITLIN: Barry.
TOCKMAN: Quickly.
"Time and tide wait for no man."
-Wait. Let her say goodbye.
-You have 20 seconds.
Ankle holster.
-[GUNSHOT]
-Iris!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
-Did he hit you?
BARRY: Yeah. I'm okay.
-Guys.
-Oh, my God.
-Oh, my God. No. Please.
WELLS: Hey.
You're here for me.
Finally, you show your face.
Well, I wasn't exactly eager to be killed.
Neither were my friends.
I know.
I hurt a lot of people that night.
People? You don't even know their names.
Jake Davenport.
Darya Kim.
Ralph Dibney. Al Rothstein. Grant Emerson.
Will Everett. Bea De Costa.
Ronnie Raymond.
I know the names of every person
who died that night. They mattered.
And the fact that the world
is now deprived of their potential...
...is something I have to live
with every day, but these people...
These people have done nothing wrong.
You wanna punish me? Fine.
Let's do that.
But let these people live.
You died that night too.
No!
You just didn't know it till today.
[FLASH GRUNTING]
[FLASH SCREAMING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Iris.
-We could've called him Blackout.
-He had a name, Cisco.
BARRY:
I'm still not sure what happened.
Why didn't he just siphon
all my powers like before?
Because you finally stopped thinking about
your powers and just connected to them.
Look. This is a sample of your blood
from just after you were struck by lightning.
Now your cells are generating
more energy than ever before.
It was more energy
than the meta could safely handle.
It's almost like he choked on you.
-What does that mean?
-I think it means you kicked it up a notch.
Dr. Wells.
What I said about
how you don't care about people...
Mm. No. Look, Barry.
There is a reason
that my biography describes me as...
...arrogant, prickly, brusque.
"At times, contemptuous."
-I read it twice.
-You were right.
I don't care much for people.
I find them misinformed.
Shortsighted.
So why do you do what you do?
Why get up in the morning?
Because I believe in a better future.
One that I very much want to see.
One that you are a part of.
I might not much care for people, Barry,
but I care about you.
-Hey, Allen.
-Hey, Eddie.
Flowers?
That's so nice. Heh, heh, heh.
Where were you all night?
Home. Tried to eat all the ice cream
before it melted.
I love ice cream. Ha, ha, ha.
He is on pain meds.
Lots of them, but he's gonna be okay.
It's been some night.
I am gonna get some coffee. I'll be back.
Do it.
Awesome.
I guess you're feeling better.
Oh, yeah.
Did you guys see that?
You're just high, partner.
Right. I forgot. Ha, ha, ha.
[MACHINE CLANKING]
Oh, now you show up.
FLASH:
I'm sorry I wasn't there for you tonight.
It couldn't be helped.
It's okay. A girl's gotta be her own hero
every now and again.
I promise I'll never be late again.
My best friend is always saying that,
and he is always late.
You're worth being on time for.
Honey, you all right?
Yeah. Why?
You forgot your coffee.
Oh. Heh.
[BLEEPING]
GIDEON:
Good day, Dr. Wells.
Yes it is, Gideon. Bring up my log, please.
New entry.
It has now been 312 days
since lightning struck.
In the past 24 hours,
subject has taken a great leap forward...
...causing me to revise my initial thesis.
I thought...
Well, I thought
his attachment to people...
...was a distraction
slowing down his progress.
Now I realize the opposite is true.
Barry's attachment to people...
...people he cares about...
...is actually the key
to getting him up to speed.
In the meantime, good news.
The future remains intact.
WELLS:
You're early.
Yeah. I know. It feels weird to me too.
I thought after yesterday,
you'd wanna sleep in.
Can't. There's too much work to do.
I'm ready to do it. I wanna push myself.
Find out how fast I can really go.
You were right.
This is not just about me.
Let's get to work.
[TREADMILL WHIRRING]
Now, you...
...had the ability to steal
the Flash's powers, and I...
...would love to know...
...how you did that.