[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [breathing heavily]
[footfalls approaching]
♪ ♪
- IRIS:Surprise, babe.
- Yeah, wow.
This is not a banana.
- I know Valentine's Day
isn't for a couple of days,
but I thought why not?
Let me surprise my hubby
before some crazy
meta-of-the-week strikes.
- Here, wait, I got it.
How's your arm?
- Oh, um,
I mean, it stings,
but it's a bit better.
- Yeah?
- You know, if you really want
a banana,
I could always go
in the kitchen...
- No, no.
No, I don't need a banana.
This all looks awesome.
I mean, the pancakes
are really...
round.
Excited to taste 'em
with my mouth.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
When did you learn to...
I mean, these are really good.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Is this fresh-squeezed?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, um...
we may or may not now own
a very expensive juicer.
- Gotta say, you're full
of surprises this morning.
- Well, the day is young.
- Mm-hmm.
Wait, how did you have time
to get a spread like this
together?
I mean, it sounded
like yesterday was insane.
- Yeah, it was,
which is why Team Citizen
is regrouping
before we go after
Carver again.
And as for all this,
thank God for 24-hour
grocery stores.
- Amen.
[Alexa chimes]
- This is your reminder.
You have a reservation
at Giovanni's
February 14th at 7:00 p.m.
- You know what?
If we also made a reservation
for tonight,
we could up our chances
of having an emergency-free
Valentine's Day dinner.
- Well, I don't care
when we have dinner,
as long as we're together.
- Alexa, set a reminder
to call Giovanni's
today at noon.
- Okay, I'll remind you.
- Great.
You finish eating.
- I will.
- I'm gonna go take a shower.
- Okay.
You're amazing.
- Son of a motherless goat.
You do not want to test me.
- Ah, thank God it's just you.
- You're out of tape.
- Did you just let yourself in?
- Relax.
I'm not some whack job
meta-killer
with crazy good aim
and ulterior motives.
Anymore.
- Another house call
from Dr. Light would suck,
but I was actually talking
about Nash.
He's a total stage-one clinger.
Didn't you get shot yesterday?
Shouldn't you be soaking
in a tub of frozen peas
or something?
- And miss out on my first
Valentine's Day?
No way!
- I hate Valentine's Day,
and I have a lot of work to do,
so...
- You know,
it's my understanding
that there are two kinds
of people
who hate Valentine's Day.
One, those who think
it's a made-up holiday
by Big Candy,
or two,
those with a broken heart.
I think you're the second one.
- No.
I'm not.
- Really?
I think actually you are.
And I think
Mr. Emerson Fairweather
is the emo dope
who's responsible.
- We met after a gig
his band played.
- Mm-hmm.
- Anyway, it didn't work out.
- "Another Valentine's Day
waiting for love.
"Let the drinking begin.
#CoffeeNotCocktails."
Ugh!
Look, you're perfect
for each other.
You have something in common.
You're both miserable.
- [scoffs]
Thanks for the reminder.
- You know, maybe you
and Mr. Fall Out Boy
can go off and be mopey
together,
and then you wouldn't hate
Valentine's Day.
- I'm sorry, have we met?
- Look, says here
he's gonna be back
at Jitters tomorrow.
And you know what?
So are we.
'Cause I'm gonna get
the two of you back together
for some V-Day love.
Cupid demands it.
- What?
- BARRY:I'm glad we decided
to do dinner tonight.
It's awesome celebrating
Valentine's together,
even if it's early.
- Yeah.
No Crisis, no dark future
looming over us.
- Feels nice.
- It really does.
- Buonasera.
[speaking Italian]
- I'm so sorry.
We don't speak Italian.
- [speaking Italian]
And can we just get
another minute?
Grazie.
- Uh...
- What?
- What...
do you speak Italian?
- Oh, well...
you know that story
that I was writing
a few months ago
on Little Italy?
Well, I picked up
a phrase or two.
Likeporca miseria.
It's a curse word,
but it literally means
"pig misery."
Yeah, weird, right?
[glass shattering]
[dramatic music]
- Roses are red,
violets are blue,
step forward, Saul Frankel,
or I'll kill all of you.
♪ ♪
Ah.
And they say chivalry is dead.
Hand over the case, Love.
- You know what will happen
if you take this.
- I know what will happen
to you
if I don't.
[grunts]
[humming]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Darlings!
Long time no see.
Did I interrupt date night?
- CCPD.
Amunet Black,
I'm placing you under arrest
for robbery
and aggravated assault.
- So very official, Mr. Allen.
But aren't you just a CSI?
- I'm still a cop
who can arrest you.
- Oh, okay.
Well, by all means,
let me help you
with the first bit.
[clears throat]
I have the right
to remain silent,
which will come in handy
if you don't want me letting
that little secret identity cat
out of its flashy red bag.
So why don't we just
call this a warning.
I'll be on my way.
No harm.
No cowl.
- I'm supposed to just
let you leave?
- Bloody right.
Don't think of coming after me,
'cause if I see you,
or your onesie,
or any one of
your frigid or bendy
superhero friends,
I will hold it against
all of you
and tell the world
your real identities.
Savvy?
Hmm?
That's right.
Because behind every great man
is a woman
rolling her eyes.
[laughs, snorts]
Ta-ta, sweethearts!
[crowd muttering]
- So much for date night.
- Pig misery.
- There's no trace of Amunet?
- It's like she vanished.
- Yeah, she does that.
- Were there any rumblings
that she was back in town?
- None, but Captain West
has all officers searching
on high alert.
- All right, thanks, Korber.
- Barry, Amunet has been
off the grid for so long
that if she's back,
it must be for something
big and bad,
and I'm pretty sure it involves
that device that she stole.
- I know.
- Hey, don't worry.
We're gonna find her.
- I just...I can't believe
I just stood there
and let her walk out.
- Barry, it's not your fault.
We knew that her
knowing your identity
would come back to bite us.
- All right, well,
time to fight her
the old-fashioned way.
I'm gonna run some sweeps
of the city.
- Whoa, whoa,
she said no onesies.
- Please don't call it that.
- What I'm trying to say is
we can't risk her
putting Team Flash on blast.
- Okay, but we also
can't do nothing.
- Well, we won't.
If you want to figure out
a criminal's plan,
visit their playground.
[upbeat indie pop music]
- This is a bad idea.
- Challenging an entire
drug cartel to a knife fight,
that's a bad idea.
Fun, though.
This, this is nothing.
Just go over there
and talk to him.
- He really does
look miserable.
- I'm sure he's over there
working on some sad sack song
to perform tomorrow night.
Trust your awesome life coach,
and just get over there.
- Well, what do I even say?
- I don't know.
You said you could be yourself
around him,
so go do that.
- You're right.
♪ ♪
- Don't worry.
I'm sure they're just
good friends.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
- A really good friend.
- [sighs]
- Allegra...
- I knew this was a bad idea.
Next time you want to play
life coach, don't.
- Uh...
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- BARRY:I still think it's
better  if I go.
- Babe, this is a known spot
that Amunet used
to recruit her crew.
Besides, a cop can't just
waltz in there.
- Okay, but it's mostly
criminals in there.
- It's really dangerous.
- Barry, it's my job
to get
information out of people.
Amunet's not gonna be there,
but if someone knows
where she's headed next,
I can get them to talk.
It's what I do.
Besides, if things get dicey,
we have our code word.
- Banana.
- You hear that,
you come fathwooming.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, fine.
Just be safe, please.
- Scout's honor.
[overlapping chatter]
[rock music playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Mother your prodigal's
come in ♪
- Whiskey, rocks.
- You look familiar.
- He must read the "Citizen."
Get out.
BARRY:Get out.
Get out of there, Iris.
- Maybe I have
one of those faces.
I'm looking for Amunet Black.
[music stops]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- You don't seem like her type.
- Got a problem, Lars?
[grunts]
[crowd oohs]
- Banana.
Banana.
Banana!
[glass clinks]
Banana, banana.
Banana, Iris!
- Now do I seem like her type?
- Seems like I need
a new bouncer.
[rock music resumes]
You interested?
- I'll keep it in mind.
Now for the last time,
where is Amunet?
- Last I heard,
she was heisting
some specialized tech
from this spot.
- ♪ 'Cause we like it hard ♪
♪ Oh lord lost and found ♪
♪ Give my soul
and I'll take the crown ♪
♪ Oh lord on my side ♪
- Thanks for the drink.
- Hey, what happened?
I heard glass breaking.
- Nothing. I broke a bottle
over some loser's head.
- You what?
- Barry, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
I was playing a role
to get information.
- Okay, well, that was maybe
crossing a line.
- I'm sure they have
some sort of mob doctor
in there somewhere.
- Okay, but, I mean,
it was reckless,
and it could've backfired.
- But it didn't, because
I knew what I was doing.
And we got this.
- Is this Amunet's next target?
- Let's go get her.
[tense music]
[loud boom]
- Ooh, I do love loud noises.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
For the lady
who has everything.
[soft whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Well, your source
at the bar was right.
She's here.
- Yeah, but what is she doing?
Any idea what that tech is?
- No.
But I'm betting it's connected
to the first device she stole.
We have to figure out
how to stop her,
before things get...
[door slams]
[chains jingling]
♪ ♪
Worse.
- Just what I was looking for.
- Goldface is working
with Amunet?
- Well, they did used to date.
- You're too late, Keith.
- Oh, Leslie.
You know I can't let you leave
with that.
- I don't think
they're working together.
- BARRY: No.
This is a gang war.
♪ ♪
- I suppose you're here
to steal what's mine.
Typical.
- What's yours?
Baby, that device
belongs to me.
- Oh, here we go again
with the possessive man
routine.
The vinyl records were mine,
Keith.
- Since when did you
like Radiohead?
I had "OK Computer"
on 180 gram vinyl
with a triple gatefold sleeve!
- [coughing]
Overrated.
- You skipped out with my
"Straight Outta Compton"
soundtrack!
- Oh, please, like you even
knew who N.W.A were
before you met me!
- Security, freeze!
Don't anybody move.
- Took some doing
setting up that deal,
and you just stroll out
of Giovanni's with my score?
- Sorry not sorry.
- Baby.
- I said freeze!
- You know I'm not letting it
go down like that.
[intense music]
[grunts]
- [yelps]
- Oh, come on.
- Looks like somebody's lost
their touch.
- I said put your hands
in the air!
- Really?
Looks to me like somebody's
lost their gym membership.
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- Barry.
- What?
- It'll be bad if Amunet knows
the Flash is here.
- Yeah, but that guard might
get really hurt.
I have to do something.
- [stammers, groans]
♪ ♪
- GOLDFACE: Yeah, well,
no amount of gym time
could help me lift
all your baggage!
♪ ♪
Still strong enough
to lift this though.
- You okay?
You okay?
- Bye, Felicia.
- [groans]
- How did you lift that?
- Uh...adrenaline.
Stay here, okay?
You'll be okay.
[whispering]
Probably.
Where are they?
- Gone.
- What?
Well, let's go after them.
We have to get the case.
- Who needs the case
when you've got what's inside?
♪ ♪
[electricity zaps]
- Ah.
Oh, my God.
- Hey.
Did you find anything?
- Uh-uh.
- Why are you so tired?
- I don't know, I mean...
I mean, to keep Amunet
and Goldface from seeing me,
I had to run so fast
I was practically invisible,
but it's getting bad out there.
I mean, their gangs
are just trading attacks.
It's like both sides think
that the other
has the second device.
- Yeah.
I called my dad.
He said that Amunet
and Goldface
are sticking
to criminal targets
like each other's
stash houses, but...
I don't know, I think
they're trying to hurt
each other,
not just their businesses.
- Okay.
All right.
Well, until we know
what they're after,
I guess I'll just keep
patrolling at super speed.
I'm just worried
some innocent people
are gonna get caught
in their crossfire
while we wait for this thing
to blow over.
- I don't think it will, Barry.
When Amunet and Goldface
were arguing at Ivo,
they used each other's
real names.
They argued about
an old record collection.
That's personal.
Personal doesn't just
blow over.
- But what's personal
about stealing tech?
- Okay, so I called Ryan Choi.
The first item
that Amunet stole?
A specialized UV projector.
The second item was a biome
simulated storage unit.
If you combine the two,
it can be used
to transport delicate,
plant-based life.
- They're after a plant?
Why?
- [scoffs]
I don't know.
But if those two are after it,
it's probably dangerous.
- Yeah.
- So a botanist source I used
from an old story
is looking into it,
but I think there's
a faster way
to figure this out.
We give Amunet what she wants.
- What?
- Yeah.
We use the leverage we have,
we get close to Amunet,
and we solve this thing
from the inside.
- No.
I mean,
that's way too dangerous.
I mean, Amunet knows
both of us.
- So?
- So we stay put.
- You mean I stay put
while you patrol.
- Well, I mean...
- You're the Flash.
You know best, right?
- What?
Iris, come on.
I mean, look at the facts...
- Screw facts, Barry.
I trust my intuition.
My intuition, by the way,
that saved my life
from an assassin
while you were on some island.
- What?
What's...okay,
what's going on?
It feels like ever since
you came back home
the other night,
you've been acting
kind of different.
I mean, the pancakes
and the bottle smashing...
- Do you hear yourself
right now, Barry?
Seriously?
My New Year's resolution?
Learn how to make pancakes.
And I told you
that I was playing a role.
Come on, Barry.
You know what?
Actually,
I didn't forget my files
at the office last night.
I was following up on a lead,
so there.
- You were following a lead
in the middle of the night?
I mean, something
could have happened to you.
- That, Barry.
That right there.
That's why I didn't tell you.
I don't need you to save me.
I can handle myself.
I even have my own team now,
Team Citizen.
- I know.
- And you know what?
While you were preoccupied
with Crisis,
I was planning to start a life
without you,
and it was the hardest thing
that I ever had to do,
but I did it
because you asked me to, Barry.
I would do anything for you,
and you know that,
but I can't be your damsel
in distress anymore,
and I cannot be the voice
inside your cowl
cheering you on.
I'm a reporter, Barry,
and I'm a damn good one,
and risky or not,
I deserve to be in that field
just as much as you do.
- I know that.
It just feels like...
I mean...it doesn't feel
like we're connecting lately.
- I've grown, Barry.
And I'm really proud
of the person that I am today.
I just wish that you felt
the same way too.
- Come on, I...
Iris.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
- Oh.
It's just you.
Yeah, I thought, you know,
maybe it might be the...
you know, the girl, the...
what's her name?
Abbondanza.
- Allegra?
- Yeah, Allegra.
That's her.
- Why are you looking for her?
- She's...she's...this...
nano-dimensional bucket auger,
it's hers,
and she wanted...
I was bucket augering,
but now she wants
to bucket auger,
so I was like...
anyway, what are you doing?
Sitting here drinking
by yourself?
- Yes, Valentine's Day drinking
to celebrate
what a screw-up I am.
- What is that?
- Naltorian mead,
left to us
by one of the previous Wells.
You know, back when there were
other Wells in the multiverse.
Sorry.
Nash, I didn't...
- It's fine.
It's fine.
- See what I mean?
Everything I touch
turns out sucking.
I mean, how do I explain
to Ralph
that he's wasted
the last five months
trying to teach me
how to be a better person?
'Cause doesn't matter
how much litter I pick up,
how many sick kids I read to,
I still don't get people.
I really thought
I could help Allegra
fall back in love
with her ex,
but instead, I just made
a mess of everything.
- You know, you got lost.
Now you just get back
on the highway,
and find new inroads
with this Allegra.
Easy-peasy.
You know, I don't know her
very well,
but perhaps
she's one of those people
that just sees things
in absolutes, right?
Black and white.
Missions fail or succeed.
Right?
You know what you need to do?
You need to get back in there
with her.
Open her up and show her
that things aren't just black
and white, you know?
Black and white,
that's just for...
death and taxes.
Everything else,
everything else happens
in the grays.
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
Ehh!
- [laughs]
- Wow.
Someone's not a fan.
- Mrs. Flash?
However did you find
your way here?
- Well, there is
a very charming bartender
that is giving out tips
rather than collecting them,
so...
- Lars.
I'll have to kill him.
Hmm.
Ladies first.
- Ah, wait.
I know what you're after.
♪ ♪
And I want in.
- Hmm?
♪ ♪
- So let me get this straight.
Iris West-Allen,
a skyrocketing
news media force,
daughter of the police captain,
devoted spouse
of the Scarlet Speedster,
all of that,
and I'm supposed to believe
you're willing
to give me an invaluable piece
of stolen tech?
Why, exactly?
- Rappaccini's Daughter.
A rare orchid recently shipped
for study
at CC Arboretum.
- And why on this
great big blue marble
do you think that I would be
interested in that?
- Well, because
what makes it rare
isn't that it blooms
every 25 years.
It's the flower's pollen.
When adequately heated,
it can be synthesized
into a telepathic narcotic.
If you can read minds,
it would be much easier
to gain access to PIN numbers
to big, fat bank accounts.
- Bravo!
Well done!
[giggles]
But you didn't answer
the most important question.
[dramatic music]
Why the bloody hell
should I believe you?
- Because I want to use
the pollen.
- For what?
- Well, as you know,
I am married to the Flash,
and he's a man who has a lot
on his mind.
- Mm-hmm.
- And lately,
that hasn't been me.
And to tell you the truth,
I'm afraid that
all this superhero-ing
is ruining my marriage.
But if I could use the pollen,
then I could read his mind.
- Oh, why didn't you just
say so?
That I can believe!
Girl, I am no stranger
to roguish means for love.
- You mean you and Goldface.
- Men.
They're all idiots.
Who needs them?
[squeals]
This could be the start
of a beautiful friendship!
[laughs]
Come along.
We're going flower shopping.
♪ ♪
- Goldface's gang
is throwing Molotov cocktails
at one of Amunet's warehouses.
They are retaliating
by sinking
their latest delivery boat.
I mean, I know it's criminal
on criminal attacks right now,
but if we don't stop it,
I mean,
it could be
a Valentine's Day massacre
where civilians get hurt.
- Yeah, no,
I'll keep doing sweeps.
I'll help wherever I can.
- Mm.
Well, I might have to roll out
a special meta taskforce.
Can you pull together
Team Flash?
- No, I can't.
I mean, she knows them all.
I have to protect
their identities too.
You know what, Joe,
there's something not right
about this Amunet-Goldface
thing, and...
Iris thinks there's
something personal going on.
- Well, I mean, I do wish
they were still a couple.
I mean, things were a lot
quieter out there and safer.
- Some Valentine's Day, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
Barry.
You've been looking down a lot.
My floor's not that
interesting, so what's up?
- [sighs]
It's Iris.
I mean, she...I don't know,
it's just something
that's suddenly off between us,
or at least it feels
sudden to me.
- And what'd she say
about that?
- She's grown,
and I haven't accepted it.
- Mm, I don't know
about that second part,
but that first part?
She has grown.
She took down
a Black Hole assassin.
- And she led the charge
to find Ryan Choi
during Crisis.
- And she was the only one
who knew that Rosso hadn't
completely taken you over.
I mean, what does that
sound like to you?
- [sighs]
I know.
I mean, she has grown,
and I guess she was right.
I mean, I didn't notice
because I was consumed
with Crisis.
We're just not clicking
like usual though.
Do you think maybe
she's grown apart?
- Barry, no.
No.
Neither one of you
are ever gonna stop growing.
I mean,
marriage is like a tree.
I mean, bear with me.
Look, the branches,
they grow from the center.
They grow farther and farther
away from the center,
but what you have to remember
is underneath,
the roots?
They're mirroring the branches.
They're growing just as much.
So you're growing
your foundation.
Now of course,
you gotta tend to the soil,
communicate with each other,
take care of each other,
look out for each other, but...
as the branches grow,
so does your foundation.
So you grow together.
♪ ♪
- Art therapy.
Been there.
- Look, I'm sorry
about Jitters.
I know you meant well.
- No, I'm sorry.
Look, my life coach
made my life better.
I was just trying
to pay it forward.
I probably should've gotten
the whole story
about your breakup
before trying to intervene.
- I guess I haven't exactly
been an open book.
- Why don't you start
from page one?
- After I got out
of Iron Heights,
I wanted to take a shot
at living a normal,
non-meta life.
That's when I met Emerson.
We became friends.
Then we went on a few dates.
Had some laughs.
But it ran its course,
so I dropped it.
- You ghosted him.
- Kind of.
- Why?
♪ ♪
You didn't want him to find out
you're a meta.
- Back then, I could barely
deal with my powers.
How could I expect
someone else to?
Anyway, it was never
gonna work between us.
- You don't know that.
I mean, you never gave him
a chance
to find out who you really are.
- It doesn't matter now.
He probably hates me
for ghosting him.
- Are you sure?
'Cause maybe he's been looking
for you every day since.
Or maybe he forgot you existed.
Whatever it is, you don't know
because you've been
filling in the blanks
without the facts.
Coming clean to Emerson
might actually make you feel
a lot better.
And who knows?
Maybe you'll get a friend
out of it.
But you can't assume
that life happens
in black and white,
because life happens
in the gray,
and you need to get out there
and live in it.
♪ ♪
- Keith and I
were like fireworks
when we were together.
We shared the same ambitions,
and it ignited us both.
We inspired each other.
Rappaccini's Daughter was meant
to be our greatest score ever.
- Even though it only blooms
every 25 years?
- What can I say?
We were optimists,
making plans for the future.
We knew that it was set
to bloom this year,
and once we had our hands
on its mindreading powers,
no one would be able
to stop us.
We would run this town
together.
I felt like I could be myself
when I was with him.
He's the only one who ever saw
beyond all this.
He saw me for me.
- So what went wrong?
- Hmm, as business boomed,
our relationship didn't.
Our passion wilted
and died.
- I don't know, Amunet.
The way you two were trying
to kill each other...
- It's a fine line
between love and hate, my dear.
- Thank you.
Why don't you just tell him
how you feel?
Talk to him.
- No.
I'm better off without him.
And when I get my hands
on that flower,
I'll run this town myself.
Come, my lovelies.
♪ ♪
Hello, lover.
- That case.
It looks like a larger version
of the tech that you stole.
- This orchid
is a lot like love.
It can only survive
in a carefully tended
environment.
That glass device you gave me
is a miniature biome simulator.
The UV projector
provides a nurturing light.
Together,
l'amour.
♪ ♪
- Flowers.
You shouldn't have.
♪ ♪
- Seeing that you got the means
to transport the flower,
I figured I'd take them both
from you at once.
Consider it a Valentine's gift.
- And here I thought we weren't
exchanging gifts this year.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Happy Valentine's Day.
[groans softly]
[lasers blasting]
[electricity zapping]
- Barry, what are you doing?
Amunet can't see
the Flash here.
- I'm done playing her game,
and I'll risk anything
to save you.
Look, after piecing together
the leads that you dug up,
it wasn't hard to figure out
that they were after
Rappaccini's Daughter.
They're gonna destroy
each other.
- Not if they both accept
that they still
have feelings for each other.
- Joe did say things were
better when they were together.
- My life got better
without you.
You're dead weight.
- You were the biggest mistake
I ever made!
- [shouting]
You always had this one
really bad habit.
Breathing!
You are nothing but a cheap,
bald Mr. T.
- I'm gonna stop
their crossfire.
[electricity zapping]
- I'd rather date Norvock
than you.
- That makes two of us!
Your American accent sucks!
- So does yours!
[grunts]
- I'm from Connecticut.
I went to Yale.
- Okay, stop.
Just stop this.
You guys were happy together
once, right?
Why'd you break up?
- I thought I said...
- She stopped listening to me.
I needed her support
when things went bad,
not her cold shoulder.
- I got tired of him always
celebrating with his posse
and only coming to me to whine
about his failures.
It got old!
- Okay, see?
I mean, you guys
are talking now.
This is great, right?
- I said no onesie.
- Okay, why does everybody
keep calling it that?
- Whatever you call it,
there's an awful lot of gold
in there, Flash.
- Whoa.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Oh, God.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- [giggles]
- Now, where were we?
- I was just about to tell you
when I told you
I liked your dog?
I lied!
I'm a cat person.
- The mud mask you use at night
smells rank.
Real mud smells better.
- [grunts]
Ow!
Oh, that didn't feel great.
Okay, it's no use.
There's no fixing them.
- I have an idea,
but it might be reckless.
- What's the plan?
- Burn the flower.
♪ ♪
- AMUNET: There you go again,
twirling your shiny spaghetti.
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
[gentle music]
[Pat Benatar's
"Love Is a Battlefield"]
- I'd hold you forever,
but it still wouldn't be
enough time together.
- The sight of your eyes
fills my heart with gold.
- Did it work?
- The stars at night
can only dream
they'd ever shine
as bright as you.
- I was always so proud
of the work you did at Yale.
- Your natural mud mask
works wonders.
- You complete me.
- What's happening?
- I missed you.
- I missed you too.
- ♪ Whoa ♪
♪ We are strong ♪
♪ No one can tell us
we're wrong ♪
♪ Searching our hearts
for so long ♪
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I should take off my gauntlet.
- GOLDFACE: Leave it on, girl.
Daddy likes the metal.
- I can't unsee this.
- Well, at least
it's less violent
than a gang war?
[giggling and moaning]
[metal clanging]
Barely. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- AMUNET: More nicks
than I remember.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
[laughs]
- ♪ Love is a battlefield ♪
- How'd it go?
- Better than I thought.
I said sorry for ghosting him.
Told him why.
He accepted my apology.
- So he's fine with you
being a meta?
- Yeah.
Turns out his new drummer
is bioluminescent.
Emerson and I
are gonna be friends again.
And you know what?
I think that's what I was
really missing this whole time.
Him too,
he actually wants me to go
take a look at his new lyrics
before he goes on stage.
- Look at you.
Back to being a muse.
- Yeah.
So, thanks
for your help
with all the gray life stuff.
It's exactly what I needed
to hear.
- You're welcome.
Although I can't take
all the credit.
A friend of mine did give me
some advice.
- Well, tell them thanks too.
They may not know me,
but they get me.
- [sighs]
Frost.
I mean...
you.
Got your message.
What's so important?
- I thought you'd want to know
that Allegra was here
so you could give her
your tool thingy.
- The...are you kidding?
Really?
You bring me to a crappy
Valentine's Day open mic night
for that?
- Well,
also so I could tell you
that I owe you one.
The advice you gave,
it really helped me
get through to Allegra.
It was very insightful.
Almost parental.
[dramatic music]
- You going somewhere
with that?
- I'm just saying,
if you ever want to talk,
like I said, I owe you one.
And I'm a very good listener.
♪ ♪
[dramatic musical flourish]
- Hell of a Valentine's Day,
huh?
- Next year, we lock ourselves
in the Time Vault
and don't come out
till morning.
Listen,
I'm really sorry
that I made you feel
like I wasn't seeing all
your success in a larger way.
- Babe, it's fine.
- No, it's not.
You've made a name
for yourself,
and this city looks to you
and the "Citizen"
for the truth
about what's going on.
And I am so proud
of who you are
and all of your
accomplishments.
I just...
for a moment today,
I felt like...
maybe we were growing apart.
- That will never happen.
- I get that now.
- And babe, just remember
that no matter what changes,
you're always gonna be
my lightning rod too.
- Iris West-Allen?
- Hmm?
- Will you be my Valentine?
- You read my mind.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic musical flourish]
- Get away from him!
Barry!
That's not me!
She's not me!
Barry!
- Greg, move your head.
[electricity zapping]