My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Just one more bus meta out there.
Edwin Gauss.
We better find him before DeVoe does.
This is an intelligence booster.
You're talking about intense
amounts of dark energy
going right into that cap.
I'm gonna help you finish
the thinking cap
without using dark matter.
Fine.
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
How can I be of service?
Hello, Gideon.
Good ol' CCTA bus number 405,
where I was gifted with pretty much
the best powers ever.
If it wasn't for this old girl,
I'd still have to leave the couch
when I need to use the bathroom.
- You know, because I can...
- Yes, I know.
All right, this might be
our last chance
to find any clues
on the final bus meta
- before DeVoe catches him.
- Yeah, we know what happens next.
What do we know about this meta?
Other than his name, Edwin Gauss?
Nothing, it's like he disappeared.
Well, that explains the brand-new
beepy flashy schmancies.
Cisco designed these scanners
to look for dark matter anomalies,
so anything that looks
weird, all right?
Waves, ripples, whatever, log it.
Oh!
- I got something.
- What?
My Big Belly punch card.
Only five away
from a free kids' meal.
If I even live long enough to use it.
Man, don't even joke like that,
we're gonna get DeVoe.
Throw him in the Pipeline,
long before he gets to you.
Right, if that doesn't work, we'll
just take him out the other way.
What other way?
We'll put him down with a shovel.
Give him his harp and wings,
send him to visit
Grandma Thinker in the sky.
Ralph, you think
we're gonna kill DeVoe?
The way that you're saying that
makes me think
I'm supposed to say no?
Okay, look.
I've taught you a lot
about being a hero, right?
You ready for what's
probably the most important lesson?
We never have to kill.
For people with our abilities,
there's just always another way.
You understand?
Allen, you complete me.
- Bring it in.
- I'm good.
- Thank you.
- Just a little bit.
Come on. Okay.
What's this?
Wait a second.
I talked to the guy
who was sitting there.
I remember 'cause I paid his fare.
Uh... U-oh.
I think I may have left my wallet
in my other pants.
Look, buddy, either pay the fare,
or you hit the sidewalk.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Mr. Bus Driver, dude.
Allow me to pay his fare.
Who are we to be the gatekeepers
of whatever path
this fellow traveler is on?
Have a seat.
Uh... Thanks.
Namaste, hermano.
Namaste in the back of the bus.
You're a funny fat dude.
This is crazy, his residual
dark matter reads as if
he was here one second
and the next, vanished.
It's Harry, he wants us back
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Says he got something important
to show everyone.
Well, now so do we.
Yeah, right, come on.
THE FLASH
That's the big news?
You're taking a sculpture class
at the community college?
It's not art.
It's science! And as such,
it is the thing that
is going to help us defeat...
DeVoe.
Recall, if you will, the one thing
that we've seen, nay, heard,
that can actually harm DeVoe.
Izzy Bowin's sound wave powers.
No, Izzy was killed by DeVoe,
so whatever power she had
is in his hands now.
And now, Joe, they're in ours.
Watch this.
So...
Maybe you should
take a couple of steps back
if you value your internal organs.
I know how that feels.
One strike
incapacitates The Thinker. Two strikes,
no more Thinker.
I call it a Sonic Scepter.
Okay, points for alliteration.
Basically just a big tuning fork.
My goodness.
It's not just any tuning fork.
This might be the most powerful
tuning fork in the multiverse.
You must've laser shaved
this thing down to the nano.
Shaved it right down to the last
angstrom as a matter of fact,
child's play for me
and my thinking cap.
The Sonic Scepter mimics
Izzy Bowin's sonic frequencies,
so we can penetrate
a heretofore impenetrable
force field of DeVoe.
And here's the best part.
Because there's no tech involved...
It's Kilg%re proof.
- Yes.
- Nice.
So, now we just need to figure out
where DeVoe is gonna appear next.
As a matter of fact,
before you got here,
I've scripted a subroutine
on the pocket dimension predictor
and it's gonna give us
a massive head start.
DeVoe's next location, thank you.
Yesterday, I thought you said
that was impossible.
That's right, Snow,
I did say that yesterday,
but today...
Is a new day.
I've got a million new ideas.
The cap and I are...
Firing on all cylinders.
Onward and upward.
Okay, let's get to it.
Cisco, can you integrate
Harry's algorithm
- into the predictor?
- Can do.
Okay.
Hey.
Harry's really loving
that thinking cap, huh?
Oh, my God, it's like
the best friend he never had.
I mean, he wears this thing
everywhere, I'm pretty sure
I saw him step out
of the shower with it.
I wanna know what kind of problem
he was trying to solve in there.
No, no, I don't wanna know.
What are you working on?
My brain. Or brains.
I think I've finally figured out
the science behind what
activates Killer Frost.
So, in fight or flight,
the adrenal glands flood the body
with catecholamines,
AKA the stress hormone,
and guess where the highest
concentration of dark matter is
in my body?
In your adrenal glands?
Exactly. So,
if adrenaline is what activates
Killer Frost, then all I need...
Is a shot of epinephrine?
No more Harry and Cisco traumatizing
me to get Killer Frost to show up.
Can't wait to tell her.
Wait, you guys talk now?
Sort of. We leave each other notes.
"Thanks for the badass new jacket,
I got some blood on it.
"Don't worry, it's not ours."
I guess her humor
is sort of an acquired taste.
Uh-oh.
Pocket dimension is about to open.
It's DeVoe, get that pen ready.
Okay, stay ready.
Edwin Gauss?
What?
All right, guys, say hello
to our last known bus meta,
Edwin Gauss. As we know,
there's not much on him.
No college history,
no known addresses,
just a couple of backpacking photos
on an old message board.
Old? Flip phones are old,
this site is from the age
of dial-up. Try prehistoric.
No digital fingerprint,
everything this guy owns
is strapped to his back.
He was off-grid before
he was even a meta.
That and his powers are
the reason that we couldn't find him.
And why there were
12 heat signatures
on the bus, including the driver.
Cisco, the way he appeared
and disappeared.
Pocket dimension.
What, like the DeVoe kind?
No, like the Edwin Gauss kind.
You see, pocket dimensions
like the one you see here
are unique to their users.
Just like DeVoe can only enter
or exit his,
Gauss, too, is limited
to his own pocket dimension.
So, why does DeVoe need him?
Well, DeVoe uses his chair
to create pocket dimensions.
If he has Edwin Gauss' powers,
he won't need it anymore.
Then we need to catch Gauss first.
And we will.
Little late, just tweaking
the cap. Now, listen,
locating this meta is not a task
that we have to accomplish.
"Why is that, Harry?"
I'll tell you why,
it's because we already have.
Now, this is the map that we constructed
of all the pocket dimension activity
throughout Central City.
Right, but that's when we thought
all the pocket dimensions
belong to DeVoe, now we don't know
whether they belong to him
- or to Gauss.
- And figuring out
those distinctions, sorry,
but that's too big even
- for your britches, Harry.
- My britches are plenty big.
Okay? I fill my britches,
watch this, okay.
By simply tracking the
trillions of identifiers,
cross-referencing the fluctuation
migration patterns
and the temporal displacement
and energy...
And...
I give you Edwin Gauss'
pocket dimension activity.
"Ah! Harry, it's amazing."
Yeah, let's all just split up
and search each one
for Edwin Gauss.
Barry you take Caitlin and Ralph,
and I'll go with Cisco
and my dad, Harry.
- I'll go with you.
- No, I was thinking that
you could just stay here
and hold down the fort.
Okay, I'll tweak the cap.
Detective, are you not going
after Gauss?
I'm on my way out,
I just wanted to see
if you needed anything
before we left.
If I need? No, I'm good.
Holding that thinking cap real close.
Never know when you might need it.
You only need it for
DeVoe-related problems, right?
DeVoe-related problems,
science problems.
Making the perfect omelet.
You make omelets with that cap?
Yeah.
Pretty darn good omelet.
I bet. Hey.
- Do you mind if I borrow the cap?
- No, I don't think so.
- Not a good idea.
- Why not?
It seems pretty easy to use.
Detective, this "easy-to-use"
thing is actually
a delicate scientific instrument
that directly alters
the brain wave of the user,
so I don't think so.
Hmm.
- So, it's dangerous?
- Yeah, it's very dangerous.
And yet you risked using it
to make breakfast?
All right. Okay, you're good, Detective.
How much do you wear that cap?
I'm not overusing it
if that's what you're asking.
Overusing is one way of putting it,
addiction is another.
I'm not addicted to...
Your concerns are well-founded.
Ramon had the same concern.
I told him...
No, I promised him
I would not use this thinking cap
with dark matter.
- Hmm. And that's a promise you kept?
- Yes.
I don't mean to be paranoid.
Sometimes it's just hard
to turn off the cop brain.
I get it. No worries.
Good luck finding Gauss.
Guys.
Where are we?
Looks like some
sort of hippie commune.
Yeah. Smells like one too.
I think I figured out DeVoe's plan.
He means to suffocate us
with B.O. and incense.
Well, this is the last pocket
dimension hot spot on our list.
So just... Do you see Gauss anywhere?
Unwashed flower child.
Have you seen this man?
No.
I've seen the soul that belongs
to this man.
Dude's aura is a trip.
Wait, so you know Edwin Gauss?
Sure do.
Around here, we call him
"The Folded Man."
- Folded man?
- He's everywhere.
And nowhere.
But mostly he's around here.
Time for the reflection hike,
everyone, don't forget to leash
your spirit animals.
Literally already smells better.
Okay, let's just search for Gauss
and stay in touch over the comms.
Yeah, I will leash my inner
penguin spirit animal
and head south.
Be careful.
Don't touch anybody.
Okay, remember
if we find Gauss first,
we might be able
to put an end to DeVoe's plans.
Speaking of ending DeVoe...
- It's not what I said.
- Allen, I'm just saying
DeVoe has been ahead of us
at every turn, his backup plans
have backup plans. On the off chance
that we can't capture him,
shouldn't we be willing to do
whatever it takes?
- We know that he is.
- I am willing to do
whatever it takes, except kill DeVoe.
- Even in self-defense?
- It's not self-defense
if you're already thinking about it.
Look.
I've been down this road,
I know you're scared,
I understand the temptation,
but you have to hear me when
I say there's always another way.
I really hope you're right, rookie.
Guys, I've got eyes on Gauss!
He's fast for a non-speedster.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Easy narcs, hey.
- I give up.
- We're not cops.
But you are in danger,
we are here to protect you.
Oh. Righteous.
Is that why you brought
your ninja buddy?
What?
Caitlin.
Meet us at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You can't stop me, Mr. Dibny.
I'll cut through all of Team Flash
to get what I want.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I mean the wound started
healing before I even woke up.
You frosted out for a sec
when we got here,
- it probably helped.
- Yeah.
Hey, shouldn't you rest?
Honestly, I'm fine.
If anything, this has just made
me more determined
to get DeVoe. I'm gonna
go help Cisco with that
pocket dimension predictor.
Well, it could've gone worse.
Yeah, all things considered,
we got pretty lucky.
Yeah.
Lucky? Are you two serious?
Am I the only one
who's paying attention here?
Ralph, the mission was successful.
Caitlin's okay and Edwin
agreed to stay in the Pipeline.
Edwin will be safe in there.
Safe. Because DeVoe
has never successfully attacked
metas in a maximum security
facility before.
Wait, he did exactly that.
- Watch it, Ralph.
- I have been watching.
Watching DeVoe ahead of us
at every turn,
watching Caitlin get skewered,
watching the metas drop
like flies one by one,
because we can't save them.
And why? Because we won't make
the tough call and end DeVoe
- when we get the chance.
- Look, I'm not doing this.
Okay, Ralph, I get where
you're coming from.
But that is not the tough call,
that is the wrong one.
Mr. and Mrs. S.T.A.R. Labs agree.
I swear, if I was running this team...
- But you're not!
- Okay, all right. That's enough.
We don't have time for this, okay?
We need to focus
and stick to the game plan.
Find DeVoe, hit him with the scepter
and put him in the Pipeline.
No one has to die.
Same plan again.
And you wonder
why he's always ahead of us.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Yo.
Magnum, P.I.
I am digging this
tiny padded room, bro.
It's like an eggshell for my body.
Which is the eggshell for my soul.
Which contains the universe
on this...
Zesty Ranch.
Right on.
You strike me
as a munchies kind of guy.
Guilty. Wait, wait,
not actually guilty,
it's not like I'm on anything.
You guys said you aren't cops, right?
- Nope.
- All right.
But apparently we have to follow
more rules than they do.
Well, whatever rules protect me
from the evil genius dude,
I shall heed.
Even his name is creepy.
The Ponderer.
It's Thinker.
Yeah, sure is a thinker.
Make me think about my journey,
like first time I folded,
I was in this white space for days,
and then another time,
I tumbled down this ramp
in this space-agey room
with blue lights and there was
this bald dude and a professor,
exploding chair with tubes coming out
of his noggin,
and there was this lady
in a white lab coat,
with such a hot accent. Ah!
Wait, wait, wait,
Edwin, do you remember anything else
from there? Anything at all?
This is important.
I don't know if this detail
is relevant,
but he had one of those
robot samurai dudes.
You were in DeVoe's lair.
But how can that be?
Cisco said that a pocket dimension
can only be accessed by
a specific user.
I mean, I don't know...
Some places are harder
to get to than others,
but if you set your mind
to a high enough plane,
you can go anywhere.
My mind gets really high.
Edwin, can you get us back there?
For sure.
Come on.
I got more.
I cannot do it any faster, Captain.
If I apply any more hobby glue,
this ship is gonna blow!
Wow!
This glue is really something else.
I should probably wear a respirator.
Where is it?
Where is what? The exit?
It's right behind you.
- Please and thank you.
- Can't find my thinking cap.
Hey, I don't have it,
Captain Caveman.
I never said you did.
So, why would you volunteer
that information unless
you do have it.
- Get out.
- I know what this is about.
You never wanted me to build
this sucker in the first place.
'Cause you never wanted
me to be smarter than you,
well, guess what, that's funny,
'cause I already am.
What the hell are you talking about?
- What the hell are you doing?
- Give me my cap!
- Hey.
- Give it to me.
- It's mine, it's my cap!
- Cut it out.
- It's mine!
- Stop!
Harry!
He didn't take it.
I didn't take it.
You definitely have a problem, man.
- Joe, this is fine.
- Be quiet.
Just listen.
I've seen these signs before
with my late wife Francine.
Back then, I didn't intervene
so quickly because I said to myself
I needed to be sure.
But I was sure.
I just didn't want to see those signs
in somebody I cared about.
I can't make you stop using this,
that's up to you.
All I will ask is that you take
a long hard look at what
it's doing to you.
And how it's making you treat people
you care about.
Ramon.
Uh... Where are we going again?
You are gonna open up
a pocket dimension into DeVoe's lair.
And I'm gonna stop him for good.
No, you're not.
Cisco installed motion detectors
in the Pipeline intake.
I thought it was DeVoe
coming for Edwin.
And I kind of wish it was.
Edwin can get me into DeVoe's lair,
I can end this.
All you have to do is let me go.
I can't let you do that.
Um...
Listen, I don't really
do confrontation,
so can I just go back
to my glass cage?
We're both leaving in a second.
Okay.
Just give me the scepter.
You know I can take it away
from you if I have to.
Yeah?
Well, you're going
to have to take it out of me.
Whoa! Bro, okay, I'm actually glad
I stayed for that.
That was trippy.
- Don't do this.
- Do what?
This?
I'm sorry, Ralph.
Olive branch?
You don't want to have
a drink with your buddy?
Is that what you call someone
who just went all
Thor, son of Odin on you?
- You can take it.
- Yeah.
Look.
I know you're worried about DeVoe.
About what he might do to you.
But there are some
lines we can't cross.
Wow.
You really don't know as much
as you think you do, rookie.
I know what killing DeVoe
would do to you.
You would be throwing away
everything you've done
to become a better man,
to become a hero.
You gotta realize that.
You
are a moron.
- Ralph...
- I am not afraid of DeVoe
or what he might do to me.
I am afraid of what
he might do to you.
And Iris and Caitlin and Cisco.
Joe, Harry, Cecile.
DeVoe has taken out
everyone who has gotten in his way.
And Team Flash...
They will always be in his way.
This was never about
protecting yourself.
I know that killing DeVoe
would mean throwing away
everything I've done
to become a hero.
But aside from my mom,
this team is the only family
that I have ever had.
And I would throw myself
into a furnace
to keep them safe.
DeVoe cannot have them.
They are mine.
What about what we want?
You may not care about
losing who you've become,
but we do.
We like hero Ralph.
Please don't take him away from us.
Well, Ralph was misguided,
but he had a half-good idea.
- Which half?
- We use Edwin Gauss' powers
to create a pocket dimension
to DeVoe's lair.
Yeah, that's the half
I was afraid of.
It doesn't get more
dangerous than this.
So, if we go, everybody
needs to sign off.
Look, you two have led this team
through every danger there is,
so if you think this will stop
DeVoe from claiming
any more lives, then...
Let's go get that bastard.
I mean, damn, Joe, you put it
all John McClane like that,
of course, I'm in.
- I'm in.
- I don't even need to ask
Killer Frost how she votes,
we're in, too.
So, it's settled.
Tonight, we take on The Thinker.
- Open it.
- You got it, mega-fast dude.
Open it again in 15 minutes.
If we don't come out with DeVoe
in cuffs,
close it, don't open it again.
It didn't work.
Why would it?
Sound has no effect on a hologram.
If DeVoe's not here, then...
Now, my love,
the real battle begins.
What's happening?
Someone's taken over our systems.
He sealed us in.
The second pocket dimension
opened in S.T.A.R. Labs at the exact
same time as ours.
It's DeVoe, he used
that first opening
to conceal his own entrance.
That's why our sensors
didn't register.
This is all a part of his plan,
the Samuroid attack,
us getting Edwin, using him
to attack DeVoe's lair.
- He wanted us divided.
- Where did Edwin go?
He's back locked in his cell,
and we've got DeVoe's
pocket dimension energy
coming from the Cortex.
That must be where his chair is.
I mean, if we can get to it,
we can use it to get our team back.
First, we gotta get ourselves
out of here.
Harry, can you unhack his code?
Trying, but it's too complex.
If only I had my quantum
encryption keys, I could do it,
but they're stuck in
Cisco's workshop.
But we're not stuck in here.
- What are you gonna do?
- It's a little worst case scenario
that I had Cisco whip up.
Get back, get back.
Harry.
- Go, get your...
- I'm going to hack the computers.
Yeah. Iris, get to that chair.
- Dad, you can't...
- Go.
I heard all the commotion
and I thought,
"If DeVoe was here.
"Where would he be going?"
Hmm.
A simple deduction for a simple man.
Though I assure you,
you are no threat
for an intellect of my magnitude.
Please.
Everyone I fight is smarter than me.
No bad guy has beaten me yet.
Well, I'm afraid an old friend
requests a re-match.
I really hate sequels.
Ah!
Mrs. West-Allen.
I was hoping we'd meet again.
You might change your mind
about that pretty soon.
Ah...
There's that passion for
our chat in the courthouse.
But I do remember warning you
that it could easily be destroyed.
And I remember you asking me
what I was willing to do
for my husband.
How about I show you?
Gideon.
Yes, Dr. Wells?
Increase the thinking cap's
dark matter feed.
More.
Warning, safe zone parameters
will be exceeded.
- Recommend...
- Maximum capacity, now!
Ah!
Come on.
A little closer. Little closer.
Warning, fists in Pipeline
are larger than they appear.
No.
God!
Even gray matter as un-evolved
as yours understands
the pain of psychic attacks.
You were born for me, Mr. Dibny.
And now...
You will die.
For me.
Yeah? You first!
What's that?
Big old fork to shove up your...
One more strike and you're dead.
I have been waiting
for this a long time,
you and me alone
so I can make the hard choice
that no one else will.
Perhaps you are willing to do
what it takes.
But it seems my love
is stronger than yours.
Get out of my office.
Where is he?
- Iris.
- I'm okay.
I'm okay, the others are
still out there
fighting DeVoe and a Samuroid.
Actually, now it's just DeVoe.
- Iris.
- I'm okay,
- we just need to get DeVoe.
- Breach us to him, I'm ready
- to get blood on this jacket.
- The blowback in the lair
knocked down my breaching.
I'll find him.
Did you just...
Beat the Thinker? Yeah, I did.
You just got out-thunk, punk.
And I see you went
with the same plan as always.
Yeah.
Do you remember when
I visited you in prison?
You said that I can have
a greater life if I just
rise up?
Well, I'm ready for that life.
And for the first time,
I might even deserve it.
Yes.
It appears I have been bested.
However, a tip if I may.
Before you cuff a meta,
make sure the light
is the right color.
Ralph!
Ms. Petty never understood
the full magnitude of her powers.
You're currently
the same gravimetric weight
as a cement truck, Mr. Allen.
That should hold you long enough
to bear witness.
Ralph, just fight it, all right,
fight it. I'll save you.
You already did, Barry.
No.
No!
Ralph.
Stay back.
Melt.
All the training.
All the lessons you've taught
Mr. Dibny to help him
reach his full potential.
This body will be
the greatest gift of all.
Thank you, Mr. Allen.
You were an excellent teacher.
We were supposed to save them.
We tried.
We failed.
I know this isn't the ending
we were expecting,
so...
If anyone wants to talk.
Should I track him down?
No.
I think I know where he is going.
Cisco.
Hey, uh, weather says rain's coming,
you mind helping me?
Can you get Harry?
I think something's wrong with me.
- All your vitals seem okay.
- Blood pressure,
respiratory rate
seems normal as well.
You're gonna have
to run the test again.
There was some feeling,
I don't know what it was, but...
You touched DeVoe.
Hand me the dark matter scanner.
The dark matter.
I'll get it.
- Focus, Harry.
- Gotta focus.
There's no trace of dark matter
anywhere in your body.
He must've used Melting Point's
powers to entangle your meta-DNA.
- So, Killer Frost...
- Is gone?
Thought I might find you
at the other office.
Yeah, well...
Without Ralph being around
to dodge rent,
it's only a matter of time
before the landlord
closes this place up.
I know there are some things in here
Ralph wouldn't want anybody finding.
You know, you could just
"whoosh" around
and you could pack up a lot faster.
Yeah, I know.
Barry, look, I just wanna...
Iris, I've...
I know that you're...
You're here for me
and that I can talk to you.
And I love you for that, but...
Right now, I just need to pack up.
That's all.
Okay, yeah.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll keep them safe.
To our overwhelming success.
Yes.
In more ways than one.
- What do you mean?
- Not only is my new host
body immune to the ravages
of my ever-expanding mind,
it also holds an ancillary benefit.
Clifford!
I'm nothing without you.
And now all of me
is with you once more.
But we must temper our celebration
with conviction.
Our plans have yet
to reach their apex.
- What is that?
- Dark matter,
siphoned from the room where
Dr. Wells was charging
his counterfeit cap.
As I predicted,
his hubris was his undoing.
And so now, the fire that burns down
Team Flash,
will also light the path
to the enlightenment.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::