- Previously, on "The Flash"...
- Four years from now,
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar
in the Speed Force.
- This is the Speed Force
bazooka.
- And that's gonna
trap Savitar?
- I know what you are.
You're a time remnant.
- You all shunned me
because I wasn't
the true Barry Allen.
I was an aberration.
- How did you become Savitar?
- I was broken and alone.
God feels no pain.
All I had to do was
become one.
[Aurora's "Murder Song"]
[melancholy acoustic
music]
♪ ♪
♪ Five, four, three
two, one ♪
♪ Five, four,
three, two, one ♪
♪ He holds ♪
♪ The gun ♪
♪ Against my head ♪
♪ I close ♪
♪ My eyes ♪
♪ And bang ♪
♪ I am dead ♪
♪ I know
he knows ♪
♪ That he's
killing me for mercy ♪
♪ And here I go ♪
- ♪ Go ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh-oh,
♪ Oh, oh, oh-oh ♪
- [inhales deeply]
[exhales]
- Iris.
- You know what I'd
love right now?
- Anything
you want.
- Caviar.
[sad music]
- Caviar?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay. Well, it's just
a little late,
so it might be hard
for me to find a place
that's open that has it.
[inhales deeply]
But I'll find an assortment.
- Thank you.
- Just stay with me,
okay?
The whole team's working
on this.
And we can accomplish
a lot in 24 hours.
- I know we can.
I'm fine, Barry.
Really.
- [chuckles]
[exhales]
Get some caviar...
[sighs]
[blazes away]
♪ ♪
[steady,
measured music]
♪ ♪
- [breathes deeply]
[phone chimes]
- Hi, Barry.
Um...
there's something that
I need to say to you.
♪ ♪
[phone vibrates]
- Hey, Cisco.
What?
Where?
All right, I'll come
pick you up.
- What is it?
- Ah...
Really good news.
- Lyla.
- Hey.
- Gentlemen.
- Ah...
- It's a wee bit chilly.
[both chuckle]
- Wanna take this inside?
- Every square inch
of that building is bugged.
Figured it was
better to talk out here.
- Okay. Yeah,
I love the breeze.
- Yeah.
- On days like this.
- So, I got your message.
But, you're gonna
have to run me through
exactly what
you need again.
- Yeah...
- So, we're building a cannon.
- Right.
- Bazooka... thing.
It's a sort of trap.
- In order to turn it on,
we need something to power it.
Something extremely powerful
and regenerative.
- Okay.
- Yeah, so, I tasked
our satellite to look for
anything that might have
our specific power requirements,
and...wouldn't you know it...
we found something that has
exactly what we need.
[laughs] And it's right there
in that building.
Crazy, huh?
- I really don't think you
should be spying on me, Cisco.
- Is it spying if we're friends?
- But he's right, isn't he?
You have something, don't you?
- It's a piece of
the Dominators' technology.
We got it from the ship
that crashed in Central City.
- That's great.
- You can't have it, Barry.
- What?
- Lyla...
We've searched everywhere.
This tech is the only thing
that we can use.
- I can't do it.
- Is this because
of Baby Sara?
- Look... I'll admit,
it's been hard not to wonder
what it would have been like
to have a daughter instead of
a son, but this
is less about what happened
than why it happened.
- I made a big mistake.
- Exactly my concern.
Barry, this is the kind of tech
that wars are fought over.
If something happens and
it gets into the wrong hands,
people could die.
Millions.
And frankly, I don't know
if I can trust you to have it.
- Director Michaels.
- I gotta go.
- Lyla, if we don't use this,
Iris is going to die.
Tonight.
- I'm sorry, Barry.
I can't help you this time.
You'll have to find
another way.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Yeah, if Lyla won't let us
have the Dominators' tech,
then we are gonna break
into ARGUS,
and we're gonna steal it.
Wally and I will phase
through the walls.
We'll be in and out
of there before
anyone even gets
off a shot.
- Uh, hello?
No, you won't.
- Yeah, we...
- What is that?
- That is a meta-human
power dampener.
And it's all over the building,
so you can't use
your powers inside.
- Can we use anything else
to power this Speed Force gun?
- Speed Force bazooka.
- Bazooka.
- Nothing else.
Manipulating extra-dimensional
energy requires,
well, a ridiculous of energy,
and the Dominator tech's
the only thing that can do that.
- Hey, I have...
I have an idea, gang.
What if we just put you...
put Iris on a plane to Paris,
or somewhere far away?
- No. There's nowhere on Earth
that Savitar wouldn't find her.
Guys. Stealing
this Dominators' tech
is our only option,
all right?
- Barry. ARGUS is more
secure than the pentagon.
If your powers don't work
in there, how are you gonna
get past security?
- Okay. [inhales deeply]
This is what we're dealing with:
surveillance cameras.
- I'm out.
- Eye scans.
- Nope.
- Palm prints.
- Whoa!
- Heat sensors.
- What?
- Laser sensors.
- They really thought of
everything, didn't they?
- That's just the first floor.
- So, you're saying this is
the most fortified structure
in the history of
fortified structures,
they can't use
their superpowers,
and we have less than 14
hours to steal the thing.
- And none of us
are master thieves.
- No. No, we're not.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[gun charges]
- Hello, Flash.
♪ ♪
- I need your help.
- Barry Allen.
The hero
of Central City.
This is Siberia
in the year 1892.
We're a little
out of your jurisdiction.
- Yeah, hear me out.
I wanna recruit you,
for a mission.
- I'm already helping
a bunch
of idiot do-gooders.
Sorry. I'm up to
my fuzzy hood in teamwork.
- Would it help if
I said please?
- No. And you
already have a bunch of
superhero types in your life.
Why ask me?
- Well, you have a...
particular set of skills.
- Great movie.
Last time we tried
to be buddy-buddy, it didn't
work out so well...
for you.
Why trust me now?
Spit it out, or I'm gonna
step onto that ship
and pretend like this
conversation never happened.
- Iris.
- Oy. The girlfriend.
- Fiancée.
- Mazel tov.
What about her?
- If you don't help me,
she's gonna die.
- True love. That's your pitch.
- It's all I've got.
- And I assume saving
your girlfriend
requires us doing
something less than lawful?
- We need to break into ARGUS
and steal an alien power source.
- The Flash, a thief?
That's my kind of mission.
One condition:
my rules.
- Your rules.
- I know we don't
have a plane.
We steal a plane, okay?
We'll put it back. All right?
And we parachute out of the
plane, and land on the roof...
gotta land on the right roof,
all right? And then...
[imitates air whooshing]
Right down the air ducts.
Mission: Improbable style.
- Easy.
- Easy?
- Yes.
- What about
the counterterrorism missiles?
- What?
- Yeah.
- Hello, Joe! Cisco.
Iris!
Love the ice. Sparkly.
- Captain Cold.
- Snart, what the hell
are you doing here?
- Snart's gonna help me
break into ARGUS...
get the power source.
[H.R. splutters]
Huh?
- Awkward.
I can see you all
have a lot to talk about.
I'll be down in your lab,
getting everything ready.
- Barry, are you out of
your mind?
- I thought he was
with the Legends.
- He is.
- No, he dead.
- Well...
- You time travelled again?
- Yeah.
- That's what got us
in this mess in
the first place.
- I thought you said you
would never do that again.
- I also said I would do
whatever it takes
to save you.
That hasn't changed.
And I'm pretty sure you all
feel the same way, too. Right?
[sighs] Look, I'm not
changing time.
I will put him back,
right where I found him.
After we get what we need.
- Fine. You say we need
Snart's help, we need his help.
So what's the plan?
- [sighs]
[power drill whirrs]
- What are you doing?
- [sighs] Flash...
damaged my suit
in our fight.
- Pretty badass.
Very godlike.
- [scoffs] Well,
dress for the job you want.
- We're a team, right?
Barry and Caitlin,
at it again.
[ominous music]
- You're not Caitlin.
And I'm not Barry.
♪ ♪
- You sure you're gonna
go through with this?
- What?
- Killing Iris.
You're gonna take her
to Infantino Street,
and ram a metal spear
through her back?
- Well, it's either
her or me.
If she doesn't die,
I'm never born.
- Right, but...
behind that pretty little face
of yours, you still remember
everything that Barry does.
So you remember
growing up with Iris,
falling in love with her,
kissing her.
You sure you're ready
to end her life?
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
What I remember...
Is being created as
a disposable life.
Something to be...
thrown away
when Barry Allen
was done with me.
He didn't care about me.
Why should I care
about his love?
You're not having second
thoughts, are you?
Good. Because you know
what you need to do,
and when the time comes,
I expect you to be ready.
♪ ♪
[loud ringing]
- What is it?
- [exhales]
[laughs]
Barry went back in time
to get Snart's help
with stealing
the power source from ARGUS.
- Power source? For what?
- Oh... it doesn't matter.
- Well, should I stop them?
- No. Let them take it.
No speed gun can stop a god.
- My guess is the power source
is most likely here.
- Why there?
- Because it's the deepest part
of the facility, and if it's
as valuable as you say it is,
then the deepest recesses
of any facility
are usually the most secure.
- Hm. Smart, Snart.
[chuckles] "Smart, Snart."
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm gonna keep hackin' away
and find out for sure.
- [exhales] Do you have any idea
what else might be down there?
- Don't matter. There are only
four rules you need to remember.
Make the plan,
execute the plan,
expect the plan to go
off the rails...
throw away the plan.
Follow my lead
and you'll be fine.
- I'm trusting you.
- We all are.
- Just don't sit me
at the single's table
at the
wedding reception.
- Just out of curiosity,
you have a plan
for getting in there?
- I've got that covered.
- Oh, ah...here, hold that
for a second. Yeah, okay,
and...kay...
and don't look.
Hey, Flash.
Superhero.
Cowl on, please?
We got civilians in the house.
- It's okay. H.R.,
we're trusting Tracy
with our lives.
We can trust her with this.
- Good point. Yeah. Okay,
I'll put my hands down now.
- Okay.
- Oh! [laughs]
Totally should've
figured that out. What...
- Well, carry on.
- All right.
- All right, Joe.
I need you to take Iris
some place far away from here.
Far away from me.
- Barry.
- I can't know where.
If I know,
then Savitar knows.
- I'll get Wally.
We'll keep her safe,
don't worry.
- [sighs]
- So here we are.
- This is not good-bye.
- Yeah.
[sad music]
Look...
I know you're gonna do whatever
it takes to save me,
but don't lose yourself
in the process, okay?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[train rushes past]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[breach whirrs open]
[all breathe heavily]
- Hello.
- Harry.
- Kid, Joe.
Iris.
What brings you folk to
this section of the multiverse?
[dramatic music]
[watch beeps]
- What's that?
- It's how much time
we have left.
- Before what?
- [exhales] Before we lose.
♪ ♪
- We're prepping the chopper
for San Francisco now.
Copy that, sir...
♪ ♪
- Director Michaels.
I thought you were en route
to San Francisco.
- Plans changed. I received
an unexpected gift
from the Flash.
- Captain Cold?
- Always nice
to meet a fan.
- I'm taking the prisoner
to lock-up.
- Of course. We'll just need
your ID.
[tense music]
[computer beeps]
- Spent so much time on
that ARGUS fake ID.
That thing's
a masterpiece.
[computer chimes]
- Your eye scan?
[scanner whirrs]
♪ ♪
[computer beeps]
- You boys really dot the "I"s
and cross the "T"s.
- And finally,
Director Michaels:
Elvis, banana.
[suspenseful music]
- What the hell?
- Search me.
Elvis, banana...[gasps]
it's word association.
Barry must have to come up
with the next correct words
in the sequence.
- Like "peanut butter, bacon."
- Yeah, Kevin Bacon.
- Mellow, yellow.
- James Brown, split.
- Okay.
Barry, you're gonna have
to stall.
- I repeat, ma'am.
Elvis, banana.
[dramatic music]
[thwack]
- [grunting]
[thud]
- [grunts in pain]
♪ ♪
[transmogrifier buzzes
and whirrs]
- My, my, my.
Getting rather violent
in your young age.
- Yeah, what were you doing?
[handcuffs click]
- Magic.
- Neat trick.
- Was a neat trick, yourself.
- Transmogrifier
from H.R.'s Earth.
Here you go.
Cisco, where to next?
- Okay, you will take the...
East elevator?
- They should do
the west elevator.
- I agree with Tracy.
- Barry, take the west elevator.
[train rushes by]
- [sighs] I used to watch you
do that as a kid.
[inhales deeply]
I thought you were so cool.
- What'd I tell you?
Guns aren't cool,
they're just for protection.
- Right.
Dad, look, I know this is
hard for everyone,
but I feel like
it's hardest for you.
Dad, can I tell
you something?
- Yep.
- When I was 16, um...
Barry and I switched rooms,
so that I could sneak out
of the window past curfew.
- [laughing]
- It's true.
- [laughing] Wait a minute.
You...
[laughs, clears throat]...
You told me that
it was because
Barry didn't like
the noise
from the street.
- Yeah, no.
But in my defense,
my curfew was 8:00 p.m.
- Yeah, I was a little strict.
- A little?
- Okay, since...
since we're confessing,
remember, um,
when I told you guys
that we couldn't eat
out for a month,
because I was saving money
for yours and Barry's
college tuition?
- Yeah.
- I took some of that money,
and I went on a blues cruise.
Junior Walker was playing.
It was just for three days.
- Dad.
- Hm.
- [laughs] Oh, that reminds me.
What, um... [snaps fingers]
What was that song you used
to sing all the time?
- You don't remember?
- I don't remember.
- "What Does It Take."
- "What Does It Take"!
- [claps] ♪ I tried,
I tried ♪
[together]
♪ I tried, I tried ♪
- ♪ In every way I could ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ To make you see how much
I love you ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ I hope you understood ♪
[both laugh]
[sad music]
- I love you.
- I love you too, Dad.
[exhales heavily]
♪ ♪
Take this for me, please.
Just in case.
Make sure you give it
back to Barry.
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply] Okay.
Okay. [inhales deeply]
♪ ♪
[animal roars]
- Who's Grodd?
- Telepathic gorilla.
Spared his life on
another Earth,
so he could invade
Central City.
That's what mercy gets you.
♪ ♪
This must be where Waller
kept her suicide squad.
[music swells]
- I think this is it.
Come on.
[tech hums
and buzzes faintly]
Cisco, we found it.
[garbled electronic noises]
Cisco?
Hey, Cisco, can you read me?
- Loud and clear.
- Hey. Uh, so,
we found it.
- Jackpot!
- But there seems to be some
kind of signal interference
at the end of the hall,
and the lock
is the Montgomery 3000.
- [sighs exasperatedly]
The Montgomery 3000.
- Wait, is that bad?
- Well, we're looking at
a 25-ton door that can withstand
a 30-megaton nuclear blast.
And aside from being
completely bombproof,
the Montgomery 3000
can only be unlocked
by a voice-recognition
system necessitating
three different passcodes
from three different people,
and as if that weren't
already enough,
the thing costs
$10 million to build.
[door unlocks]
- 37 seconds.
I must be out
of practice.
- Well, ARGUS should ask
for their money back.
[tense music]
- Wait!
Make the plan,
execute the plan.
♪ ♪
- [snarling]
[King Shark slams the door
and growls]
- Expect the plan to go
off the rails.
[growling]
[King Shark stomps]
- Seen a lot of things,
but a half-man, half-shark
takes the cake.
- I can't believe ARGUS turned
King Shark into a guard dog.
- King Shark.
That's adorable.
- Give me your cold gun.
- So you can do what,
exactly?
- Snart, there's only one way
that tech's getting out of here.
- [chuckles] Oh, I see.
You didn't just recruit me
for my skills
as a thief, did you?
You wanted a partner
who wouldn't mind
if you got all murder-y.
- I told you
what I'm up
against. All right?
Give me the gun.
[cold gun charges]
♪ ♪
- Open the door.
Open the door!
- Have you seen
"Shark Week," Barry?
Me, I can't get enough of it.
Good thing the Waverider
has cable.
- [growls quietly]
- [gasps]
- What's your point?
- Most sharks
are cold-blooded,
but the great white shark,
like our friend in there,
is partially
warm-blooded.
- He's susceptible to cold.
- Never strays into water
colder than
53.6 degrees Fahrenheit.
If we lower the temperature
in that room to 53.5 degrees,
King Shark should fall asleep
like a little baby.
Or, you can go ahead
and kill him, and prove
what a badass you are.
Your choice.
[thoughtful music]
♪ ♪
[freon cartridge
pops out of gun]
[whispering]
Throw away the plan.
[swelling music]
[cartridge hisses]
[milk froths]
- Ho-ho-ho. [claps]
Tracy Brand, you know,
it's moments like this
I'm reminded that S.T.A.R. Labs
is so much more than a haven
for beautiful minds, it's...
- It's a miniature Jitters.
- Isn't it...ohh, wow. Mmm!
[slurps drink]
- Raspberry and coriander.
- Mmm!
[laughs appreciatively]
Yes it is...it's a home...
- Yeah.
- ... is what it is.
You know what? It's my home.
It's my...
It's my family.
Although, I...you know what,
I will say...
I have to tell you,
I haven't always felt
I belong completely.
- What?
- Yeah, lacking a clear sense
of purpose sometimes.
But then you arrived.
- I did?
Oh, yeah, I did.
- Oh, yeah, you did.
Here you are. Yeah.
And with you here,
I understand my purpose.
It's us. You and me.
That meeting of the mind
that we have,
it's just so powerful...
- But H.R., you're
from another Earth...
- Yeah, I...yeah...
- I'm a unemployed,
former grad student,
who...
- Come work at S.T.A.R. Labs
with me.
Okay? I mean,
it doesn't pay much.
- How much?
- Ah, it pays next to nothing.
But you know what?
It wouldn't matter.
We'd be together.
Imagine: me inspiring you,
and you applying
that inspiration,
and us changing
the world together.
And drinking
so much coffee!
- [laughs]
[gasps]
- Tracy Brand.
- [gasps]
Will you do me the honor
of joining Team Flash?
- With you? I'd love to.
[both laugh]
[snarling]
- [roars]
[thuds
to the ground]
[circuitry explodes]
- By all means,
you first.
- Thanks.
[dramatic music]
[snarling]
- Reminds me of "Jaws."
They didn't show the shark
because they couldn't afford
to make it look good.
♪ ♪
[King Shark snarls]
- [exhales shakily]
♪ ♪
How long do you think he'll
stay asleep?
- I like "Shark Week."
I'm not a marine biologist.
♪ ♪
[tech grates
against chamber]
[door begins
to slide shut]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
- Snart!
- Barry!
[alarms blare]
- This place is
gonna be crawling
with ARGUS agents
in the next two minutes.
Look on the bright
side, Barry. This is
your chance to show
how ruthless you really are.
Sometimes you gotta make
a tough call, Barry.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco?
We need your help.
I have the energy source,
but Snart's trapped inside
the cell with King Shark.
You gotta open the door.
- I can't hack into
the mainframe.
- Hurry, all right?
- Cisco's working on it.
Whatever you do,
don't look behind you.
[intense music]
- If Cisco saves my life,
tell him I'll...
put in a good word
with my sister.
- Come on...
[keys clack,
computer beeps]
Bam!
- Come on, come on!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
- I got you!
- Barry!
- I got you, I got you!
- I got you!
[skin squelches]
Hang on!
- Now, Cisco, now!
Close it!
[door slams shut]
[both panting]
- Ouch. Been there.
[skin squelches]
- [growling] Flash!
- Let's get out
of here.
Lyla.
- Barry.
I told you I couldn't
give this to you.
- Yeah.
- And you snuck in here anyway?
- To save Iris' life, Lyla.
Yeah. I'll do anything.
- Not anything. I saw
the whole thing
on the security monitors.
You could have left
Snart to die.
But you risked your freedom
and Iris' life to save him.
- [sighs]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- You're just gonna
let me have it?
- I couldn't let Iris die
knowing that
that could save her.
And I know you'd do
the same thing for me
if it were John's
life on the line.
- Thank you.
- Now go. Do it.
And get this guy back
to wherever he belongs.
- Took the words
right out of my mouth.
♪ ♪
- Tell me, Snart,
did you think I had it in me?
To leave you behind?
- I wasn't sure.
Always known you had
the potential to be
as ruthless
as they come.
Your history made sure
of that, same as mine.
Who knows, maybe that's
why we get along.
You see the good in me.
I see the bad in you.
- Maybe.
- Piece of advice:
stop trying to beat Savitar
at his own game.
Your goodness
is your strength.
[hopeful music]
And call me sentimental...
I think the Flash
should remain a hero.
♪ ♪
- Take care
of yourself, Snart.
- No strings on me.
[whoosh]
No strings on me...
[whooshing]
- We did it!
We got the Dominator tech.
- Yes, yes!
- Where's Iris?
- Ah, Iris...
safely stashed away on Earth-2
with ole Harry Wells.
[terrifying music]
♪ ♪
[H.R. gasps]
[whoosh]
- Barry! Savitar knows
where Iris is.
- [exhales]
[device beeps rapidly]
- Savitar's coming.
- What?
- Now. Joe.
- Iris, stay behind me.
- Dad.
- He gets to you through
my dead body. Harry, Wally.
- Yeah.
[loud whooshing]
[tense music]
- I got him.
[whoosh]
[electricity sizzles]
[swooshing]
[electricity zaps]
♪ ♪
[thud]
[circuits crackle]
[bones snap]
- [screams]
[electricity snaps]
[thud]
[guns fire]
[bullets ricochet
off of suit]
[suit groans mechanically]
[mechanic whirring
and clanking]
[Iris yelps]
[dramatic music]
- Oh, God.
It's really true.
- Yes, it is.
Aim that gun at me
and I'll kill you.
♪ ♪
- Listen to me.
You were my son once.
- Oh.
- Whatever I did to make you
feel this way...
I'm sorry.
- [chuckles scornfully]
- Please, Barry.
- No. That's not my name.
- Barry.
- That's not my name!
- Please! Stop, okay?
I will go with you,
just please, do not kill them.
- [chuckles] I'm not gonna
kill them now.
They...need to watch
you die first.
- Baby, no.
- Dad, it's okay.
- Oh, look, Joe.
She's accepted her fate.
[electricity snaps loudly]
You should too.
[whoosh]
-[groaning
in pain]
[whoosh]
♪ ♪
- He took her.
- He...
[breathes heavily]
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, Barry.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
It's not okay, Barry.
I should have been there
for her. I should have
protected her...
- You did everything
you could, all right?
- You trusted me,
and I let you down.
- Listen to me.
Listen to me!
There's no way you could
ever let me down.
You've become the hero
I always knew you could be.
- [exhales shakily]
- I'm gonna go get our girl
back, all right?
- [sniffs tearfully]
[door slams]
- B.A., I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- I screwed up.
I'm so sorry.
- So, what now?
- [sigh]
Now we go to Infantino Street.
We know exactly where
Savitar's gonna be and when.
- Is the bazooka ready?
- I've loaded the power source
into the device, which should
deliver the necessary amount
of energy to trap Savitar
in the speed force.
We'll be on standby
in case it fails.
- It won't fail.
It won't fail. It's ready.
- You didn't have that
the last time,
so we have the
upper hand now.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
You guys figure out
what your plan is.
I can't be here to know
any of it.
You know where I'll be.
[exhales deeply]
[items rustling]
- Gauntlets, check.
Goggles, check.
Super powers?
[inhales] Check.
Locked and loaded.
[case zips]
Don't stress.
Tracy's bazooka...
- [sighs]
- It's gonna work.
- Tracy's bazooka?
- Yeah, you helped.
- [huffs] I didn't...
[object clatters to ground]
I didn't help.
- Yes, you did.
You inspired her.
- I didn't inspire her.
I...I didn't do
anything inspiring.
You know what's inspiring?
Barry.
A hero among heroes.
You're all heroes.
And you've all given me
so, so much, you know?
You've given me a home,
you've given me a purpose.
Now you've led me
to the woman that I adore,
that I wanna spend
my future with,
and through it all,
what have I done?
What have I done?
What have I contributed except...
[drums on hat]
Some fair-to-middling drumming,
and lead Savitar
directly to Iris.
- That's not fair.
- It's not fair?
- It's not fair
for you to say.
Savitar tricked us.
- Us? Me.
I'm the one who
opened his big, fat mouth,
and now we're all in trouble,
and especially Iris,
'cause I couldn't keep
my mouth shut!
- Hey! That coulda
happened to me, okay?
Easy. I mean it.
That coulda happened to me,
that could happen
to any of us.
♪ ♪
H.R...
You gonna hold down the fort?
- [punches hat lightly]
Yeah. [chuckling]
- Of course you are.
'cause that's what you do.
You show up.
You're ready.
Dependable when we need
you the most.
You hear me?
- I hear you.
[both chuckle]
- All right.
- [clears throat]
Till next time.
♪ ♪
[warping sound]
[terrifying music]
- Oh, Cisco.
Time for a little chat.
[electricity zaps]
- Cisco?
- I just had a vibe.
- What? What'd you see?
- Killer Frost.
I saw this coming.
- What are you
talking about?
- Ever since Caitlin
got powers,
I've had vibes of us
fighting in a forest.
This whole time I've
been fighting it.
I didn't wanna face
the fact that one day,
she'd be
this far gone.
- Then go now.
Keep her from making
the biggest mistake
of her life.
- What about you?
You're gonna need my help.
- Savitar won't be
with her right now.
This is our best chance
to help her.
Go save Caitlin.
I'll save Iris.
news announcer:
In other legal news,
the highly publicized trial
of Jared Morillo, AKA Plunder,
comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty
of grand theft
and aggravated assault after
he was caught by Kid Flash
robbing the Central City Museum
earlier this year.
- Please don't fail,
please don't fail.
- Everybody,
stay on alert.
- Here we go.
- [exhales]
[clock ticks]
- I know you're here!
Come out and face
me like a woman.
- I didn't think
you'd actually show.
- That's 'cause you don't know
anything about me.
Or Caitlin,
for that matter.
- Savitar's right.
In order to join him as a god,
I have to cure myself
of Caitlin.
This has to happen.
- I don't wanna fight you.
- I don't wanna
fight you, either.
I wanna kill you.
[icicles shoot
through air]
[sonic wave
rushes forward]
[whooshing]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[panting]
♪ ♪
- [exhales nervously]
[whoosh]
- Flash.
This is it.
Now the moment
is upon us.
My ascension to
become a god.
- Not tonight.
- Show me you're the hero.
- [gasps]
- Let's see what happens.
- I'm gonna stop you.
[whoosh]
[gun shoots]
- [grunting]
[whooshing]
[electric humming]
- [grunts]
[electric zaps]
Ha!
[energy trap whirrs
and crackles]
[Flash grunts
with effort]
- It's working.
- [panting]
[electricity zaps]
[suit hums mechanically]
♪ ♪
What?
- It didn't work.
- What... what? [panting]
Why didn't it work?
- I spent an eternity
in a trap just like that.
You think I didn't know
how to prevent it
from happening again?
- The philosopher's stone.
- It's made of calcified
Speed Force energy,
and you gave it to me.
- No... guys... guys!
- I failed.
- Joe!
- You stuck me with Speed Force
for an eternity of hell.
Now, welcome
to yours.
- No. Don't do this.
Don't do this!
- Now, finally,
I am free of you.
- Barry.
- I'm begging you, just...
- Barry!
- You lose, Barry.
[spear unsheaths]
- [wailing] No!
[Aurora's "Murder Song"]
- Hi, Barry. Um...
there's something that
I need to say to you.
I love you.
And if something happens,
I need you to hear this.
♪ ♪
I, Iris Ann West,
take you,
Bartholomew Henry Allen,
to be my lawfully
wedded husband.
To have and to hold,
from this day forward.
In sickness and in health.
To love and to cherish.
- ♪ My eyes ♪
- Until death do us part.
- ♪ And bang ♪
♪ I am dead ♪
[spear rushes]
♪ I know ♪
- [panting] Iris. Iris.
- ♪ He knows ♪
- Iris!
- ♪ That he's killing me
for mercy ♪
♪ Five, four,
three, two ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Five, four ♪
♪ Three, two ♪
♪ One ♪
- Greg, move your head.