BARRY: Previously on
The Flash and Supergirl...
THE FLASH: What just happened to him?
Wally has taken my place
in the Speed Force.
THE FLASH: It's okay. We're going home.
BARRY: What Wally saw,
it's gonna haunt him for a while.
I proposed
because I thought it would save you.
What does that mean?
I think we need some space.
I owe you the truth. My name is Mon-El.
I'm the former Prince of Daxam.
I deserve better than being lied to.
I've been looking for you.
Toodles!
I told you. Everything's better in song.
When you speak, it's just words,
but when you sing, you open up your soul
and let who you really are shine through.
Thanks, Mom.
- I love you, my beautiful boy.
- I love you, too.
This?
Again?
What, are you gonna spend
the rest of your life
- sitting around on the couch? Come on.
- No...
You've been doing this for days.
Let's do something.
- Let's go out.
- No, man, I'm sorry. I'm...
I don't feel like going out.
What is it with you
and musicals these days, anyhow?
Everything's better in song.
Listen, dude, I know you've been going
through a tough time
since Iris broke off the engagement,
- or I guess...
- What?
Technically, since you
broke off the engagement.
Whoever broke off the engagement,
it doesn't matter.
I just... I don't know, man. I wanna help.
Nothing you can really do.
Really? I guess I'm just gonna
have to let Mr. Gene Kelly take over
'cause, Lord knows,
I can't do anything about that!
It's H.R.
Yeah.
B.A., someone's coming through.
Could be Gypsy.
Yeah, could be, or could be...
Supergirl?
Kara.
- What happened to her?
- We don't know,
but whoever did it has come to this world.
Her vitals are low.
- How long has she been like this?
- A few hours.
Okay, we need to find
whoever did this to Kara
and punch him repeatedly until he
reverses whatever spell he put on her.
And I get to punch him first.
Who are you, exactly?
My name is Mon-El. I'm Kara's...
Friend.
Her more-than-friend?
We've been kissing a lot.
Oh! She never mentioned
she had a boyfriend.
It's a recent thing, so...
I thought you two broke up.
I tell you what. I know enough not
to mention the breakup between Barry and...
- H.R.
- H.R.: Sorry.
Look, hey, whatever's going on
between me and Kara,
I cannot leave her like this, okay?
I need to get her back.
We will, I promise.
So what happened to her?
An alien prisoner escaped our custody.
He did something to her.
Put her in some kind of a coma.
Then he disappeared.
We tracked him here and followed.
Okay, but why would he come to this Earth?
Well, we believe, for you.
- Me, why?
- We don't know.
But his last words before he disappeared
were about finding the fastest man alive.
Okay, well, clearly,
we're talking about a breacher here.
And if there's one thing I can do,
it's find breachers.
So what else can you
tell us about this guy?
Not much. It's like he just
materialized out of thin air.
You mean like this clown just did?
I'm gonna go.
Wallace.
I understand what you've been through.
Stuck in the Speed Force,
the things you saw, I get it.
I also know that sometimes
the old adage is true.
When you get bucked from the horse,
best thing you can do,
get right back on the damn thing
and ride, Wallace. Ride!
Hello, Barry Allen.
- How do you...
- Know your name?
I know a lot of things,
and I can do a lot of things, too.
Wally West made it here, too.
This is exciting.
It's good of you to join the party,
Kid Flash. I'm happy to have you.
What do you want with Supergirl?
The same thing that I want
with both of you.
To teach you all a lesson.
Is that all you got, Kid Flash?
I mean, you look a little scared.
And you're too slow.
Nighty-night, Flash.
What the hell?
KARA:
♪ Moon River ♪
♪ Wider than a mile ♪
♪ I'm crossing you ♪
Kara?
♪ In style someday ♪
♪ Oh, dream maker ♪
♪ You heartbreaker ♪
♪ Wherever you're going ♪
♪ I'm going your way ♪
♪ Two drifters ♪
♪ Off to see the world ♪
♪ There's such a lot of world ♪
♪ To see ♪
♪ We're after ♪
♪ The same rainbow's end ♪
♪ Waiting round the bend ♪
♪ My huckleberry friend ♪
♪ Moon River ♪
♪ And me ♪
- What a singer, huh?
- Yeah.
You know her?
Yeah, I do.
- Barry?
- Hey!
Barry, it's you. Thank Rao!
- Wait, it's really you, right?
- Yeah, this is me. Yeah.
- Good.
- What is...
- Where the hell are we? What's going on?
- I was hoping you could tell me,
or maybe explain to me
why I just pulled an Audrey Hepburn
and sang at a nightclub.
- Maybe we're dreaming?
- The same dream?
Yeah, that's... What's the last thing
you remember before you got here?
I was at the DEO.
They had just brought in
an alien prisoner. He got loose and...
- It was really weird. He had this red...
- Pocket handkerchief?
- Yes.
- I saw you on my Earth.
You were in a coma.
Your boyfriend brought you to us.
He is not my boyfriend.
He's just a boy who is not my friend.
- He's my nothing.
- Okay.
All right. Well, whoever he is
said that this guy whammied you,
and then he escaped to my Earth.
He showed up at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I went after him to try to get him
to wake you up...
- And then you got whammied.
- Yeah.
- So where are we?
- I don't know.
I mean, it could be a parallel dimension,
or maybe just some elaborate illusion.
We just need to figure a way out.
I guess I could
click my heels together three times?
- Yeah.
- I was kidding.
Okay, all right, well...
Come on, let's...
- You're a really good singer, by the way.
- Hey, thanks.
My sister says
I put the "Kara" in "karaoke."
MALCOLM: There you are!
Merlyn.
"Who?
Malcolm Merlyn, former head
of the League of Assassins?
The what of the what?
What the hell are you talking about, kid?
My name's Cutter Moran. I own this club,
and both of you work for me.
- We what now?
I pay you to sing,
not pepper me with questions.
And I hope you got
something better in your songbook
than what you were
belting out up there, blondie.
- Hey! Don't call me "blondie"!
- Now, look, I don't know who you are...
But obviously you're someone
who's quick with a knife.
You'll have to excuse my friend.
He doesn't think before he talks.
Yeah, I had a cousin like that.
I had to slit his throat, too.
Oh...
Grady, get these two set up!
And nothing I've heard before.
I want something original.
Barry, I don't have my powers.
Me neither.
Winn?
Winn, you're here, too?
Who's Winn? The name is Grady.
I tickle the keys around here.
Say, you realize how he got
the nickname "Cutter," don't you?
- No.
- Because he likes to cut people.
You ask me,
I think he's all talk.
Cisco. Not Cisco. Hello.
I pray that one day you do not find out
how very, very wrong you are, Pablo.
- Now, go do your job.
- All right.
You see, Grady doesn't know this,
but one day I'm gonna be somebody.
I'm gonna be somebody, and it's gonna
happen right there on that stage.
You'll see. I just need my one shot.
- It's just curiouser and curiouser.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's like The Wizard of Oz!
"And you were there, and you were there..."
Except it's not really them.
They're all playing characters
- in a musical.
- Musical.
Barry, where are we?
I don't know.
MUSIC MEISTER: Well,
you know what they say.
The show must go on.
Ah!
Supergirl, I loved your rendition
of Moon River, such a beautiful song.
You were a little flat in places,
but I'm willing to let it slide
just because you're so cute.
Hold on. What did you do to us?
Oh, nothing much.
Just put a little song in your heart.
"Put a little..."
Why did you bring us here?
I didn't bring you anywhere.
We're inside your heads.
You created this world.
And we got lucky because it could've been
a war movie or a space opera,
but thanks to your love of musicals,
what with the countless times
you watched, um, Wizard of Oz
- with your adoptive parents.
- How did you know that?
And you, all those rainy nights watching
Fred Astaire and Frank Sinatra with mom.
Well, where else would we be?
All right, all right.
Whoa! Swing and a miss.
I didn't tell you. I'm not really here.
See, I'm out there in the real world.
Central City's mine for the taking.
- Huh. We're gonna stop you.
- Yeah.
You're welcome to try that
if you can get out of here.
How do we get out of here?
You're in a movie musical,
so all you have to do is just follow the...
The Yellow Brick Road?
- No, the script.
- Oh. Yeah.
Reach the end of the plot,
and, presto change-o, you get to go home.
One little detail, though,
I should mention.
If you die in here, you die out there.
Lovely.
I've reached my limit with magical creeps.
In the meantime, I hope you're both ready
to get the rust off those pipes of yours.
- We're not singing for you.
- No.
- Uh. Anymore, I mean.
- Anymore.
Come on, now, maybe just one
little fun opening number, just to...
Leave your jacket on.
- Kick things off!
- Where'd it go?
♪Think of your fellow man ♪
- Stop that.
- It's not happening.
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪
- It's not gonna work.
- BARRY: We're not singing.
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ You see, it's getting late ♪
♪ Oh, please don't hesitate ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world will be a better place ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ And me ♪
♪ You just wait ♪
♪ And see ♪
♪ If you want the world to know ♪
♪ We won't let hatred grow ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world will be a better place ♪
♪ - For you.
- For you ♪
♪ - And me.
- And me ♪
♪ You just wait ♪
♪ And see ♪
♪ You better take a good look around ♪
♪ Oh, if you're looking down ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ And the world will be a better place ♪
♪ All the world will be a better place ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ - And me.
- And me ♪
♪ You just wait and see ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ Put a little love
Put a little love ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
♪ Put a little love ♪
♪ Come on
And put a little love in your heart ♪
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
Come on, let's find him. Huh?
KARA: He's gone.
BARRY: Yup.
- So what do we do now?
- I don't know.
I mean, I guess we just...
We do what he says, right?
We have to figure out what the plot
of the musical is and follow the story.
Okay. Uh...
So what do we know so far?
We're singers.
And apparently, we work for a gangster.
Yes, who wants us to perform for him.
I mean, honestly,
it's pretty straightforward.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Oh. Hello.
- Hi. I miss being bulletproof.
- You're coming with us.
- Says who?
Says me.
- KARA: Barry, are you okay?
- Oh...
Please stop yelling.
I'm not yelling.
Wait. Where are we?
I don't know.
All right, well,
I'm sure everybody at S.T.A.R. Labs
is working on getting us out of this.
Yeah, I'm glad they brought me
to your Earth.
Mon-El seems like
he really cares about you.
Mon-El only cares about himself.
He lied to me about
who he really is for nine months.
- Mmm.
- I can't shake it.
I thought
it was gonna be something special
like what you have with Iris.
That is off track.
I'm sorry.
I asked her to marry me.
You did? That's great.
- Did she not say yes?
- No, she said yes,
but I guess I did it
for the wrong reason, and...
I mean, I love her,
but I was trying to change the future.
Then I pushed her away
so I could focus on saving her,
and it's just a mess now.
Mmm...
Everything's so simple when I'm running.
Or flying-
Shut up! Both of you.
Stein?
Who's Stein?
Right.
This them?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Do you know who I am?
Not Joe West, I'm guessing.
Digsy. Digsy Foss. I run this town.
So you're the Mayor?
The mayor may have gotten the vote,
but I got the power.
I got a situation
that you two are gonna help me with.
We would love to help you with it.
Really love to.
My daughter, Millie, she's missing.
The last she was seen, she was
heading into Cutter Moran's place.
Have you seen her in there?
- "Millie," did you say?
- Yeah. Why?
- We haven't seen her. I haven't see her.
- I haven't see her.
- Yeah, we haven't...
- She's the only thing that is good
and decent about my life.
If anything happened to her,
this town will run red with blood.
Starting with yours.
We wouldn't want that now. Right?
So, um, how can we help you?
You two sing for Cutter?
- We sure do.
- Yes, we do.
You could poke around
and see if you can find her.
BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
So are you gonna do this for me?
- What do we do?
- Follow the script.
- DIGSY: Hey!
- Hey.
- We're gonna find her, sir.
- KARA: Mmm-hmm.
Good.
Okay. This is the place. Apartment 4B.
This is where we can find Iris?
- Millie.
- Millie. Right.
Yeah, she's in there, all right.
Now, you two listen to me.
Don't you go telling anyone
I showed you this.
No. Yeah, we promise.
Word to the wise,
you go digging around in this dirt,
you might not like what you find.
Okay.
Okay, so, remember, she might
look like Iris, but she is not Iris.
- I know. This is gonna be weird.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
I'm glad we haven't seen someone
that looked like Mon-El.
I'd probably just punch him
in the face for the fun of it.
WOMAN: Oh, my God!
That's her. Sounds like she's in trouble.
Here. Stand back.
I'm gonna kick the door in.
No, you stand back. I'll kick the door in.
I didn't mean it like a gender thing.
I just wanted to kick it in...
- Barry.
- All right, together. All right?
- One, two...
- Three!
What the hell is going on?
All right, you caught us.
We're in love.
Gross.
Guys, we have a problem.
Well, another problem.
The Speed Force levels in Barry's cells
have been severely depleted,
as has the amount
of solar radiation in Kara's body.
What exactly does that mean?
They're being drained.
The guy who did this to them,
I think he's stealing their powers.
Power up.
We've got to bring him in.
No, not "we." Me.
I'm the reason Barry got whammied.
We win and we lose as a team.
I'm coming with you.
I'm coming, too.
Look, J'onn, I respect this whole
special-agent situation you got going on,
but this problem right here
needs someone with...
Green skin and a sick-ass cape.
Call me the Martian Manhunter.
Think you'll find that J'onn's a lot more
than just a pretty face.
Guys. Hello. Uh...
Also, Barry and Kara's vitals
are all over the place.
Let's go.
All right.
Hello, friends.
Kid Flash, oh, I'm so glad
you could join the party.
I'm such a huge fan of your work.
But I have to say,
recently, your work's been a bit off.
You know what I'm talking about?
I think maybe
it's just that you're a little scared
from what happened in the Speed Force.
Is that it?
No, and I'm not afraid of anything.
Prove it.
Uh, Cisco, they're heading towards
4th and Aspen.
Got it. This way.
All right, J'onn, how do you feel
about a little one-two combo?
I'm gonna open a breach. You be ready to
hit something really hard on the B-side.
Hitting hard, I can do.
Wally, get ready to do
the same thing on the ground level.
Copy.
Now!
Nighty-night.
Who are you? Your names, now.
I'm Kara. This is Barry.
We're singers at your dad's nightclub.
Yeah. Uh, Millie, your dad thinks
you've been kidnapped.
Well, clearly, he's mistaken.
He really wants you to come home.
- Listen, I am never going back there.
- Mmm-mmm.
Why not? There's no place like home.
Tommy Moran is my home.
And besides, if our geezers
ever caught wind of this,
they'd go to war.
It'd be the end of more than just us, huh?
MILLIE: Yeah, Tommy's right.
Our fathers hate each other.
Our love is forbidden.
This is just like West Side Story.
I was thinking more of Fantasticks, but...
MILLIE: Look, the point is,
we ain't telling nobody nothing,
and neither are you, capisce?
Capisce.
- Can you give us a second?
- Oh, um...
MILLIE: Sure.
Okay, look, he says
we need to follow the script.
We're in a musical, so I think
if we convince them to tell their fathers
that they're in love,
maybe that'll get us out of here.
And back home to being single.
- Yay!
- At least we'll be single together.
Saying that never made anyone feel better.
Debatable.
Okay, so, look...
your fathers aren't perfect, right?
Love isn't perfect.
No, but you can't let
your love for somebody
cause you to be afraid
of what might happen.
You've got to take the good with the bad,
- no matter what.
- Right.
And that includes telling your fathers
how you two feel about each other.
All right, you make a convincing argument.
- You do.
- We'll do it!
MILLIE: We'll tell them about us, right?
TOMMY: Well, we should go now.
- Okay!
- Gee, thanks, kid.
TOMMY: Here you go.
MILLIE: Thank you.
Wow.
Okay. Uh. Convincing people in musicals is
- really easy.
- Yeah.
Let's hope getting out of one
is just as easy.
Digsy, she's back!
- Oh!
- MILLIE: Mmm.
DIGSY: Thank God you're safe.
Well, of course I'm safe.
Barry and Kara told me
that you sent them to find me.
We were concerned.
Dads, there's no reason to be concerned.
"Dads"?
- You got a problem with that?
No. I love musicals, so...
Okay.
Look, Dads, there's something
that I need to tell you.
Hmm?
I'm in love!
Who is the, uh... The lucky boy?
Um...
Tommy Moran.
Oh... You mean, Cutter Moran's kid?
Dad, look, we're in love.
- The hell you are.
- He's a hooligan.
- His father's a hooligan. His mother is...
- Hey!
Not in front of the girl.
And you're not loving that boy.
Have you lost your mind?
She is the daughter of my enemy!
Digsy Foss is a dirty rotten scoundrel,
and the apple
doesn't fall far from the tree.
- Dad, if you'd just let me explain...
- There's nothing to explain, Tommy!
I knew you were keeping something from me.
I never imagined
it was something like this!
She isn't your little girl anymore.
Well, she isn't.
She's an incredibly brave, strong woman.
One look, and you can see that.
And she wants to be with him.
No matter how scared she was to tell you,
no matter how dangerous it is
to be with him,
all that matters is they're together.
And when you find a love like that,
well, you've got to hold on to it,
no matter who's trying to stop you.
That's clear to me now.
I think you're being
a little tough on your son.
Excuse me?
Well, it's obvious why
he didn't tell you right away.
I mean, look at the way you're reacting.
Maybe if you just listen
and hear his reasons
and try to see things
from his point of view...
Maybe...
Maybe you'd understand
why he didn't tell you before now.
Baby doll, it's just...
You'll never understand
what it means to be a father.
Millie, my darling,
we've always taken care of you.
We just want you to be happy.
♪ Velvet, I can wish you ♪
♪ For the collar of your coat ♪
♪ And fortune smiling all along your way ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love this day ♪
♪ Mansions, I can wish you ♪
♪ Seven footmen all in red ♪
♪ And calling cards upon a silver tray ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love this day ♪
♪ Standing there ♪
♪ Gazing at you ♪
♪ With a sheep's eye ♪
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪
♪ Music, I can wish you ♪
♪ Merry music while you're young ♪
♪ And wisdom
When your hair has turned to gray ♪
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪
♪ Your own true love this day ♪
♪ With a sheep's eye ♪
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪
♪ And the strong arms to carry you away ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ And the strong arms ♪
♪ To carry you ♪
♪ Away ♪
Thanks for telling us the truth, baby.
I love you both so much.
BOTH: We love you.
Thanks.
Okay.
So what do you wanna do?
Uh...
Gather up the boys. We're going to war.
I had a feeling.
I appreciate your honesty, son.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Come here.
Get the boys. We are going to war.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the two people
I was hoping would visit me the most.
Fix them, now.
I'm sorry. I can't.
If you ever wanna get out of that cell,
that's exactly what you're gonna do.
You don't get it.
You don't understand, big guy.
That's just not how it works.
My powers don't work that way.
What do you mean?
You're the one who did this to them.
Yes, but they're the only ones that are
in control of what happens to them now,
as are the two of you.
Us? What does that mean?
How much do you love him, Iris?
And, you, Mon-El,
how much do you love her?
So the question is,
is that strong enough to save them?
You want Kara and Barry
back from the world they're in?
You can go get them yourselves.
You have that power.
- How?
Ah. I can't tell you. Sorry.
You've got to figure it out yourself.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna just chill
in this wonderfully decorated
little cell of yours.
Bye, guys. Good luck.
Love will find a way. You can do it.
The power of love, and all that.
What do we do now? We got...
We got Millie and Tommy to tell
their fathers that they're in love.
Which I know we're
in a musical and everything,
but seeing Mon-El
in love with someone else was...
It was hard to watch, I know.
Anyway, I mean,
what are we supposed to do?
What do you think this
Music Meister needs us to do now?
Uh...
Ah! There you are. You two ready?
Ready for...
For rehearsal, you dolt.
Mr. Moran told me that you got
more songs in your repertoire.
- Ah. Yeah.
- We have to finish the musical.
Uh, do you happen
to know anything original?
As a matter of fact, I've been
working on something all day.
Wow.
Things really are easier in musicals.
Yeah.
All right.
♪ At times like these
When life is getting me down ♪
♪ And the world seems
Like it's gonna end-ship ♪
♪ There's at least one power
That we both still have ♪
♪ And that's the power of ♪
♪ Friendship ♪
Yeah, that's exactly what I was gonna say.
Yeah, it's an easy rhyme.
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Your super friend ♪
♪ I'll be there in the nick of time ♪
♪ If you're ever in a spot ♪
♪ And if you're not there in time
You can just go back in time ♪
♪ And give it another shot ♪
I'm actually not supposed
to do that anymore.
Oh. Okay.
Sing!
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Super friend ♪
♪ When you need a compliment ♪
♪ I can rattle off a dozen ♪
♪ For instance, I have to say
I'm not impressed ♪
♪ By your more famous cousin ♪
Thank you! No one ever says that.
Oh, he's all like, "I'm Superman."
- That's a really good impression.
- Thanks!
♪ I'm your super friend ♪
♪ Super friend ♪
♪ When it comes to buddies
Pal, you're the best ♪
♪ I love you more than the lightning bolt
I wear on my chest ♪
♪ If you're ever sad
I'll bring you flowers ♪
♪ And you can list soprano
As one of your powers ♪
♪ If you're ever broke ♪
♪ I've got the cash ♪
♪ On my couch ♪
♪ You're welcome to crash ♪
♪ And if you ever need a hand ♪
♪ I'll be there in a flash ♪
- Barry.
- That was funny.
♪ I'm your super
That has a double meaning ♪
♪ Friend ♪
Hello, my friend.
It will be a cold day in hell
before our daughter
marries any son of yours.
Like he said, a cold, cold day.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
Come on.
Stop!
Barry!
Oh, my God.
- What's wrong?
- I think we're losing them.
Can you stop it?
Not if I don't know why.
Then what are we gonna do?
Um...
We need to go
to whatever world they're in.
How are we gonna do that?
Look, he said, if we loved them enough,
that we could save them wherever they are.
Cisco, you can vibe us there.
I don't think it works that way.
You sent me into the Speed Force.
You sent Barry and Wally into the future.
- You can do this, too.
- What is she talking about?
- What's a vibe?
- CISCO: I'll explain later.
Come on, just grab on to my shoulders.
Let's hope this works.
Barry... Barry.
Kara.
- Barry!
- Kara!
Hey. It's me. It's Iris. I'm here, hon.
Hi.
MON-EL: Stay with me.
I'm gonna get you out.
There's no time.
We have to go. We have to get them out.
Come on, Barry. Barry!
No.
I'm so sorry I lied to you.
I forgive you.
I love you.
No, Barry... Barry, you're gonna be okay.
Barry, no!
I love you.
Iris?
Mon-El.
Hi.
They're back!
Bravo! Round of applause. Standing O.
That was so good!
I loved it. That was a hell of a show.
And you two, I guess your love
really was strong enough after all.
Beautiful.
Man, how did you get out of the cell?
Cisco, do you really think that cell
is gonna just, like, hold me?
No, I'm sorry. What's going on?
Why did you do this to us?
I did it because
I believe in the good guys.
I told you when we first met,
it was to teach all of you a lesson.
'Cause I see everything,
and I saw two people
with two broken hearts.
So the lesson was...
Love, Supergirl.
Love is about letting yourself be saved.
It's not just about saving other people,
even if you are superheroes.
Anyway, I'm sorry that I had to, like,
mess with you a little bit.
I was just trying to get you
to play the game, do the song and dance.
Are you from another, uh, Earth,
multi-verse, universe, or something?
Yeah, you wouldn't even
understand where I come from.
Uh...
Wait. I'm sorry. That's it?
You're just gonna teach
somebody else a lesson?
- Yeah, it's exactly what I'm gonna do.
- Oh.
♪ Think of your fellow man ♪
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪
Wait.
So let me get this straight.
You got whammied by some guy named...
Music Meister.
Damn, Barr, I'd have paid good money
to see you singing and dancing.
No!
Uh. Well, he's holding out on you
because Barry has an amazing voice.
- He does.
- Uh-uh.
I've actually seen him sing.
What, you have?
How have we not made a GIF of that?
Well, technically, I'm not even
the only one here who can sing.
Thank you, B.A.
Well, I was talking about Kara.
Oh. You, too?
Kara. Of course Kara can sing.
Well, her name is Supergirl.
It's kind of implied, right?
Well, we better be getting going.
We promised Kara's sister
we'd get her back in one piece.
We couldn't have done this without you.
Thank you.
- How you guys doing?
- Yeah, I think we'll be okay.
Although, if you lie to me again,
I will drop a mountain on you.
Wow. You mean, figuratively?
- No, I mean, geologically.
- Okay.
What about you guys?
We'll see.
You didn't change anything
when I moved in with Cisco.
I, um, couldn't bring myself to do it.
You know, we've been through a lot
these last three years,
but getting stuck in a musical?
BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
Music Meister said that, you know,
it could have been anything,
that I created that world because...
You were watching them, because of us.
My mom used to always say
that musicals have the power
to make everything better.
Did it work?
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪
♪ Can't change what the future may hold ♪
♪ But I want you in it
Every hour, every minute ♪
♪ This world can race by far too fast ♪
♪ Hard to see while it's all flying past ♪
♪ But it's clear now
When you're standing here now ♪
♪ I am meant to be
Wherever you are next to me ♪
♪ All I wanna do ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And all my life, I promise to ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And I could see it right from the start
Right from the start ♪
♪ That you would be ♪
♪ Be my light in the dark
Light in the dark ♪
♪ Oh, you gave me no other choice ♪
♪ But to love you ♪
♪ All I wanna do ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪
♪ And all my life, I promise to ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home ♪
♪ Home to you ♪
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪
♪ Can't change what the future may hold ♪
♪ But I want you in it ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪
Iris West, will you marry me?
Yes.