- Previously on
"The Flash"...
We just beat Zoom.
Why does it feel like
I just lost?
I feel more broken
than I've ever felt.
- Wherever you need to go,
whatever you need
to do, do it.
I'll be here.
[whooshing]
- [grunts]
- You're safe.
- So what should we call
this brave new world?
I was thinking Flashpoint.
- My name is Edward Clariss.
Rivals should know
each other's names.
[gunshot]
- It's like I'll be
thinking of a moment
from my past
and it vanishes.
- This isn't your home, Barry.
It's a mirage.
Things are back
to how they should be.
Well, for me, anyway.
For you?
I guess you'll just
have to wait and find out.
- Where's Iris?
- You know Iris isn't here.
They don't talk, Barry.
- Oh, God.
What did I do?
I made a big mistake.
I just couldn't
take it anymore, you know?
What happened with Zoom,
my dad dying,
my mother's death,
me becoming The Flash.
All of it.
I wanted a new life.
I wanted to start over.
And that's what I did.
But somehow
I-I made things worse.
[dramatic music]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- No.
- So I reset everything.
I put everything back to the way
that it was before.
Except some things
weren't the same anymore.
Not even a little bit.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
Take a breath.
[inhales, exhales deeply]
You were talking
way too fast.
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- I really screwed up,
Felicity.
And this time I don't know
if I can fix it.
- Okay, let me
get this straight.
You ran back in time?
- Yeah.
- Stopped Reverse-Flash
from killing your mom
and then lived in
an alternate reality
where both your parents
were alive?
- Yeah.
- And then you
restored the timeline,
came back
to the moment you left,
and noticed
that things were different?
- Exactly.
- Does that just happen
when you travel through time?
Do things just
change like that?
- No, I mean,
not like this.
Not on...I don't know.
I don't know Felicity.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
- Okay, why don't you just run
me through...
walk me through
what happened?
And we'll, uh,
we'll try and figure it out.
So what changed?
[motorcycle engine roars,
tires screech]
- I knew once I got back
last night
some things had changed,
but before
I could figure out
exactly how much,
I had to deal
with someone this morning.
♪ ♪
[whooshing, metal clanking]
You are not gonna
get too far
on that thing anymore,
are you?
I will be taking these back
to the jewelry store
you stole them from.
[siren wailing]
But, uh, you can keep these
if you'd like.
[bullets clinking]
Good luck with that.
[clicks tongue]
[whooshing]
After he was taken care of,
I went to S.T.A.R. Labs,
and that's when
I found out
a lot more had changed
than I realized.
What kind of idiot
still thinks
I can't outrun bullets?
- That guy should be
the criminal poster boy
for what not to do
against The Flash.
- So what are we
gonna call him?
- You mean like a nickname?
- Yeah.
Cisco does it for all of them,
he's like the master of it.
Can't just call him
Suspect on a Motorcycle,
Right?
What do you think?
- I don't know.
- I'll take this one.
Uh, The Crook.
Lame?
A Five-Finger...
- How about Thief?
He robs stuff.
Let's just call him Thief.
Gotta get to the gym.
Excuse me.
- The gym? Is he...is he,
like, working out now or...
- You know, Barry,
sometimes your jokes
just aren't very funny.
- I should...I should
get back to the paper.
- It's okay.
I was just leaving.
- Hey, guys...hey, Joe.
Look, hey, I'm sorry.
Look, I just, I know you guys
aren't speaking
to each other right now,
but I was just thinking
maybe we could talk about
why that is for a minute.
I...
- No.
- Dude.
- No, we can't.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
I just...look.
I'm sorry, I just thought,
I don't know,
maybe it would be good
for you guys just to...
hear it said out loud.
- This is because
of what he did, Barry,
not me.
- Iris.
- What?
What could you possibly
have to say?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- I'll just see you
at the station, all right?
Nice job with, uh,
Thief.
- Uh, give me a lift to CCU?
- Sure.
- So you're still taking
engineering classes.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, cool.
All right, well, good...
good luck with that.
- What is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
- Are you trying to make me
as mad at you as I am at him?
- No, no, look, I'm...
I'm sorry, I...
I guess I don't fully understand
why you're so upset at him.
- [sighs]
Then maybe you shouldn't
bring it up again.
- Yeah.
- How about we talk
about us instead?
- Us?
You...you mean you and me,
like, trying this?
- I just thought
with everything
that's happened lately
and everything
that you've been through,
I wanted to make sure
that you still felt the same.
- Well, Iris,
I did what you said.
I went where
I needed to go,
I did what
I needed to do,
and I'm ready.
- I never told you
to do that.
- Yeah, no, you did...
on the porch,
right after we beat Zoom,
right before you...
- Wow, you kissed Iris.
- Well, not anymore.
I've kissed Iris West twice,
and I have managed
to erase both times
from existence.
- Man, I hate it
when that happens.
- That's just the least
of my problems today.
Joe, hey...hey, man,
um, can we talk for a second?
- Yeah, I just gotta
drop this off for Singh.
- Oh, Captain Singh's back?
That's just terrific.
- Yeah, why,
did he go somewhere?
- Uh, no...maybe.
I don't know, I...
- Is that cowl cutting off
all the oxygen in your brain?
- What? No, I'm fine.
Why? Why?
- Because you've been
acting real odd lately.
Asking why Iris wasn't
at the house last night.
And that stunt you pulled
at S.T.A.R. Labs this morning.
You know damn well
why she's not talking to me.
- Of course.
Uh, because sh...
- Because I should have told her
her mother was alive
but I didn't.
- Yeah, but she forgave you
for that.
Ah...one would think
that she would have.
- I don't know
if she ever will or not,
but you sticking your nose
into it isn't helping, Bar.
Good intentions and all.
- I was...okay.
- We found another husk
this morning.
- Husk?
- Singh wants this processed
ASAP.
- Yes, the skin husks
we've been finding around
the city are the ones we think
are attached to the meta-humans.
This is now the fourth one.
- Well, let's figure out
what's happening
before there's a fifth.
- Yes, sir.
- [stammers]
- Deep breaths.
- Um, hello?
- Yes.
Hello, Mr. Allen.
I can still see you're there
and no,
I don't want your help,
thank you.
- What are you doing here,
Julian Albert,
meta-human CSI Specialist?
- I did tell you
the meta-human conference
was only for two days.
- Okay, but this is...
- Still our lab...
unfortunately.
Yes, County forgot to mention
that significant detail
before assigning me,
but here we are.
Looks like you and I
get to be roomies
for a little longer
than we'd hoped.
- Roomies.
- There's a whole new guy
at work
that you didn't even know about?
- Yeah.
And he's worked there
for almost a year.
And he doesn't like me
very much, apparently.
- Well, that's impossible.
Everybody likes Barry Allen.
You're like pudding.
Everybody likes pudding.
- Not everyone.
37.
- I hated that we never spoke.
I think the thing that haunts
me the most is the fact
that I never told him
I loved him.
Or that I idolized him.
I have memories of Dante
all the time.
But they don't
feel like gifts.
They feel like reminders...
of what I did wrong,
and how I'll never make
another memory with Dante again.
♪ ♪
Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
Oh, wait a second.
Now you wanna be there for me?
- I'm just trying
to understand.
- My brother's dead.
There's nothing to understand.
Exit's that way.
- So you altered the timeline,
Joe and Iris
don't talk anymore,
there's a guy at work...
a new guy...
who doesn't like you,
you never kissed Iris,
and Cisco's brother is dead.
Admittedly, that is an issue.
- And what if there's more?
- Well, has anything here
changed?
- [sighs] No, I don't know.
I mean,
everything seems the same,
I think.
- Good.
- Can I use...hold on.
- Uh...
- I'll be real careful.
I got it, don't worry.
I got it.
[keyboard clacking rapidly]
♪ ♪
Yeah, I don't know...
I mean, everything looks okay.
Wait.
Who's that young boy
with Dig?
- No way.
He didn't have kid before?
- No, he had a kid.
He has...he has a kid.
Yeah, it was baby Sara.
- Baby John.
- No. Are you...
- Oh, my God.
It really can affect us.
- Okay, you know what?
I don't wanna know anymore.
- Okay, I know this is
a lot of pressure,
but everything's gonna be
all right.
- I screwed up everyone's life.
- Yeah, well, maybe
you should tell them.
- I'm not gonna tell them.
I mean, how is that gonna help?
That's just
gonna make everything worse.
I mean...I don't know
how to fix this.
- Okay, well,
you're gonna figure it out.
If there's one thing
I've learned from you,
is that with you,
anything is possible.
- Why?
'Cause I'm The Flash?
- No.
Because you are Barry Allen.
And sweet, loving,
kind Barry Allen
that everybody likes,
the Barry Allen
who's just like pudding,
can fix this.
So go and fix this.
- Yeah.
Okay, you're right.
Yeah.
- Now!
- Right now?
- Yes!
- Okay, all right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[deep whooshing]
- Stop!
- Find me.
- Who?
Who?
[scraping on glass]
♪ ♪
[monastic chanting]
- I am Alchemy.
- I have visions...
of another life.
Please, make them stop.
- Is that what
you really want?
To make the visions stop?
Or do you want them
to come true?
To be fast again?
To have speed?
- Yes.
- Do you want
that other life?
- That's what I want.
- Once again,
you will have power.
And no man will be
your rival.
- [chuckles]
[dramatic music]
[cameras clicking]
♪ ♪
- Julian, I thought you could
use some help on this one.
You know, the two heads thing
and all.
- I don't need any help,
Detective.
Especially from him.
- What is that?
- Another epidermal husk, Allen.
A fully intact human pelt,
comprised of nothing
but the stratum corneum.
You see what I mean?
- Do we have any theories
as to what's causing them?
- Well, I'll take
a wild guess at it and say
it's the same thing that created
the last four husks.
- Spalling could be caused
from toxic epidermal necrolysis,
or maybe some kind
of moist desquamation
from intense radiation exposure.
We've had a lot of...
- Radioactive metas.
Yes, thank you, Allen.
I've read all the case studies.
I'll tell you what,
when I figure it out,
I'll enlighten you then,
shall I?
- Thanks.
How have I worked
with this guy for the past year?
- Yeah, you say that
all the time.
- I'm sure I do.
- Julian?
Are you certain
that Barry can't
take a sample or something
to speed things along?
- [sighs]
I'm sure, Detective.
Quite sure.
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
- You might wanna get that
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- You know, there's really
not that much here.
- Yeah, no, I know.
It's basically touch DNA.
I had to steal the sample
because our meta-human expert
wouldn't let me take one.
- Oh, you mean Julian Albert?
- [sighs]
Yeah, you know him?
- Yeah, we've known him
for a while.
He's the best.
Um, you need me?
- No, I think I got this.
But thank you.
- Okay.
- Cisco told me
you showed up
to his bereavement group
last night.
- Yeah, I did.
He also tell you
it didn't go so well?
- It's only been a few months
since Dante
was killed
by that drunk driver.
I'm sure he just needs
a little bit more time.
- Wait, why is he
so mad at me?
- Oh, no.
I'm staying out of that.
- Kate, he'll...
he'll barely look at me
unless other people
are in the room.
- Maybe it's just easier
when the rest of us are around.
- [sighs]
Do you think maybe
you could convince him
to come with you to my house
for dinner tonight?
- Why?
- So I can try to fix things
between us, maybe
between Joe and Iris, too.
Just all of us together again
in one room
and try to work this out
once and for all.
Think you can do that?
- Okay.
But how are you gonna
get Joe and Iris there?
- Joe?
Hey, Joe.
Um, so I talked to Iris
and she just has
a few things that she wants
to say to you.
- Bar, I thought I told you
to stay out of this.
- Oh, no, no, no.
This was all her, I swear.
- So she just,
out of the blue,
decided now she wants
to talk to me?
- [claps hands softly]
[whooshing]
Hey, um, so Joe said
that he'd give you
what you need about
the husks for a story.
- Hi.
- Uh, what? He just decided,
out of the blue, to tell me?
No one at the precinct
will say anything.
Even Julian.
- Oh, I hate that guy.
- Yeah, you always say that.
Um, when does he
want to do it?
- Uh, tonight,
at the house.
He said he's making
your favorite.
- Okay, he's out of his mind.
He knows I will not
go back there,
even if he does make one of
Grandma Esther's recipes, so...
[whooshing, papers falling]
- When?
- Uh, tonight.
Tonight, yeah.
Um, at the house.
- At the house?
- Yeah.
- She vowed she'd never
set foot in the house again.
- Unless you made dinner.
- [chuckles] Dinner?
- Yeah, like old times.
So, one of her favorites,
like Grandma Esther's recipes,
maybe.
- Okay. I suppose
I can make something.
Which dish?
[whooshing]
- He said he'd make
the chicken.
- I hate the chicken.
I like the noodles.
- Oh, noodles, okay.
- Why are you out of breath?
- I'm not out of breath.
Uh, Joe also thought
maybe just to take some pressure
off that he'd invite
Caitlin and Cisco.
- Okay, um, what time?
- Uh, 7:00.
- All right.
[whooshing]
- Um, 7:00 will work,
by the way.
- Okay, but which dish?
- I mean, I was thinking
maybe to take some pressure off,
you could invite
Caitlin and Cisco.
- That's a good idea,
'cause if we're gonna do this,
I gotta get started.
- Yeah, I got it.
No problem, yeah.
- Bar?
- Yeah?
- Which dish?
- Noodle dish.
Yeah, noodle dish.
[whimsical music]
♪ ♪
This hits the spot, huh?
- You can thank Grandma Esther.
- No, I mean, it's good.
I just meant, um...
all of us, actually,
just here, together.
I was actually thinking,
um, that maybe it'd be fun
if we all went away together
for a few days.
Just like a little
Team Flash vacay.
- And do what?
- Bond. [gulps]
Reconnect.
- You mean like a retreat?
- Nah.
- With trust exercises?
- Epic fail, party of six.
- I just...I just feel like
we're not the team
that we were or can be.
[sighs]
No one?
- I'd be down for it.
- Okay.
So other than Wally,
I'm the only one
that thinks that's a good idea?
- I don't think The Flash
really takes vacations.
- Especially with all these
husks showing up all over town.
- Speaking of husks,
I'm glad you're finally ready
to open up about them.
- Iris, I already told you,
I can't tell you
anything about this case.
- Oh, really?
Because that's not
what I was told.
- Strange.
I was under the impression
you had some things
to say to me, too.
Isn't that right, Bar?
- Told you. Epic fail.
- Okay, look, yeah.
I arranged this.
I put all this together.
I'm sorry, guys.
Look, I just...
we're not acting like a team,
and I just wanted things
back to how they were.
Just fixed.
- If you wanted things fixed,
maybe you should have
gone back in time
and stopped my brother
from dying.
[somber music]
- You want me to change
the timeline to save Dante?
- Why would you do that?
It's not like he's your brother.
♪ ♪
[cell phones beep, vibrate]
Meta-human app.
We gotta go.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Remember me, Flash?
- Clariss?
[dramatic music]
- Oh, you do remember, Flash?
Good, yeah.
Because I remember
everything, too.
- How are you here?
- It doesn't matter.
You see, what does matter
is that I know
your little secret.
You changed the timeline.
Because if I recall correctly,
the only Speedsters
in my other life
were me and that
smartass Kid Flash,
until you showed up
and stole everything from me!
- I didn't steal anything
from you, Clariss.
I-I was just trying
to put things back
to the way
they're supposed to be.
- This is how my life
is supposed to be!
For years, I felt like
something was missing.
And now I know why.
- Well, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to do this to you.
- Yeah, well, you did.
And here I am.
Your Rival, back again.
♪ ♪
Believe me, Flash,
this time,
you're not gonna
steal my life so easily.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
[thud]
- [grunting]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- We finally get rid of Zoom,
and there's another
evil Speedster?
- Who is this guy, now?
- I can help you with that.
I finally got the results back
from the test I ran
on the husk
that Barry gave me
this morning.
And it's weird,
because there's
no traces of dark matter,
but there are traces
of the Speed Force.
- And that's the husk
from this Speedster?
- Appears so.
His name is...
- Edward Clariss.
- And somehow Barry
is exactly right.
- Can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- S.T.A.R. Labs
isn't the only one
with access to the city's
security cams.
It's pretty obvious
that this guy knows you.
You want to tell me what
that's about?
This is why you've been
acting so weird lately...
trying to get me and my dad
talking again,
tricking all of us
into dinner tonight...
because you're keeping
something from us.
You need to tell me
what is going on, Barry.
Right now.
And if you lie to me...
this thing between us,
it cannot happen.
- You're right,
and, uh, I'm sorry, I...
I did this.
All of this.
It's my fault and I've been
trying to fix it.
But I think that there's only
one way to do that now.
I'm sorry, Iris.
[whooshing]
[thrilling music]
♪ ♪
[grunts, panting]
Flash?
- Flash.
Here, put these on.
We need to talk.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Call you up
in the middle of the night ♪
♪ Like a firefly
without a light ♪
- Where are we?
- Motorcar Diner
in Central City.
- Yeah, I meant what year?
- 1998.
- ♪ Runaway train
never going back ♪
- Care to get
something to eat?
'Cause I'm starved.
The corn beef hash here
is the best I've ever had.
- This is why you pulled me
out of the Speed Force?
Buy me a meal?
- Because you were
about to reset
the timeline again
after screwing it all up.
Oh, yeah,
I know about that.
- How did you...
- After your
not-so-subtle reaction
when you first met me...
Harry told me all that happened
with Zoom and your mom
and your dad, so I decided
I'd keep my eye on you
for a bit.
- He tell you anything else?
- He did.
I'm your father's
doppelganger.
Sorry about that.
- It's just...
really weird.
- And really sad, too...
I'm sure.
Having a loss like that
in your life,
I see why
you'd wanna erase it.
Who wouldn't try
to save their parents?
I understand that, Barry,
completely.
But the thing is,
there are consequences
to time travel.
- I have heard
all of this before.
- Not from me you haven't.
I'm not some Doctor
with a theory, Barry.
I'm a Speedster, like you,
who's travelled in time,
and made these same mistakes
you are making right now.
Here, let me
show you something.
- Okay, you know what?
- Humor me, kid.
This coffee cup right here.
- All right, yeah.
- Think of it
as the space-time continuum.
Whenever you go
back in time it breaks.
[vibrates rapidly and shatters]
- For real? I mean...
- Now...
you can reset the timeline,
you can try to fix it,
but no matter how hard
you try...
it's never gonna be
exactly how it was.
- Look, I've learned
all this stuff
that I didn't know before, okay?
I'm not gonna make the same...
both: Mistakes.
- Yeah, what you just said
right there?
That is the paradox
of time travel,
and also the paradox of life.
I mean, if I only knew then
what I know now.
- Why have these powers
if I can't go back
and fix what I broke?
- We're not gods,
we're men,
who, for whatever reason,
have been given
extraordinary abilities.
The question you need
to ask yourself is,
what kind of hero
are you gonna be?
Are you just gonna
take a do-over
every time you make a mistake?
Or will you live with them
and move forward?
♪ ♪
[pensive music]
- Where's Barry?
[whooshing]
- I need to tell
you all something.
The truth.
- The truth about what?
- [sighs] Okay, um...
after Zoom killed my dad,
after we defeated him, um...
I wasn't in a great space,
and I felt like the only way
I could fix that was
to run back in time
and save my mom.
- You stopped the Reverse-Flash
from killing your mom?
- Yeah.
- Wait, so, is she alive?
- She was.
For a few months.
I lived with her and my dad.
I had a completely
different life.
I wasn't even The Flash
for most of it.
- I don't understand.
You created
a whole other existence.
How is that possible?
- [sighs]
Okay, um...
I'll do the...
this is the timeline.
This is the point
that we exist on it right now.
This past point
is where my mom was murdered.
So when I saved her,
I created a new reality.
A new timeline.
I was living in...
- A mirror universe.
- It's called a Flashpoint,
apparently.
- But you decided
to leave it. Why?
- That life started
to spin out of control.
This guy, Clariss,
he was a Speedster there, too.
He was known as the Rival.
He caused a lot of problems.
So, um...
I decided to run back in time
again and let things happen
as they were supposed to,
in hopes of...
resetting the timeline, but...
- But what?
- But, um,
when I came back,
things weren't the same.
- You mean people.
Like us.
- Yeah, yeah.
Um, I created another timeline.
Uh, it's the one
we're living in now.
It's not as different
as the last one.
Not in large ways,
but in some ways,
in smaller ways,
and, uh, meaningful ways
for all of you or anybody
that's close to me.
And I can't ever really
put it back together.
♪ ♪
- Barry, that's a lot
to take in.
- Yeah, it is.
- We got along
in that other life,
my dad and I, didn't we?
That's why you've been
working so hard
to get us talking again.
- Okay, here's the thing.
Um, I will tell you
what's different, all of you,
if you wanna know.
But you have to live
with those differences
because I can't change it again.
But at least you'll know.
And you all deserve that choice.
- So you decided
it was okay to change things
when someone
in your family dies,
but when it's someone
in my family...
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna go talk to him.
Hey.
♪ ♪
What are you working on?
- These are the gauntlets
for my suit.
And you probably
know nothing about that.
Do you?
- I'm really trying here, Cisco.
- Barry, I'm the one
who's been trying.
I've been trying
this whole time
to get you to do
this one thing for me,
but you kept saying,
"No, Cisco.
I can't, Cisco.
I would never do that, Cisco."
And now you're telling me
you went and did it
for yourself.
- Were you listening?
It...it went bad.
It went really bad.
- I don't care!
At least I'd have
my brother back.
- Yeah, you would
have him back,
but because of it,
somebody might have something
happen to them
that's just as awful
as what happened to Dante,
and trust me,
you don't want that
on your conscience.
It's a heavy burden to bear.
♪ ♪
And I don't know how many times
I've said this, but...
I'm really sorry
about Dante, man.
♪ ♪
- Sorry doesn't change anything.
- No, it doesn't,
but I can't go back.
I can't change it.
All I can do is move forward.
♪ ♪
I really hope you can, too.
Hey, um, I need your help.
- It's the four words
I seem to hear you
most often say, Barry.
That and,
"I hate that guy."
Which, the feeling's
mutual, so...
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, um,
this is gonna be
hard for you,
but I just,
for a second,
need you to imagine
that we're actually friends.
- Can't do it.
- Friendly.
- Equally as challenging, Barry.
- Hmm.
- But I'll give it a whirl.
What are you after?
- I need to read your report
on one of the husks.
- Which one?
- The one from this morning.
Edward Clariss.
- Edward Clariss?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- May help me figure out
a case I'm working on.
- Well, the nutshell is, uh,
the hyaluronic acids
were found to be above normal.
Uh, androgen degradation
atypically low.
- Mm-hmm.
- Cellular regeneration
seemed to occur
at a staggering rate.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's quite a bit different
from the previous husks
that we found.
That's about it.
- Could I...
could I maybe just
take a peek at it?
I'm sorry, it's just something
I need to see
to know what I'm looking for.
- [scoffs]
Sure.
- Great, thank you.
Wait, why does this say
the body's place of discovery
was Williamson when it was found
on the waterfront in Leawood?
- The body ended up
in Leawood.
There was a strong current
this morning,
so chances are that it
originated from Williamson.
Somewhere near the old
Prescott sawmill.
You done?
- Yeah, uh, yes.
Thank you.
[whooshing]
- You found me again, Flash.
I wondered how long
it'd take you this time
to figure it out.
- Wasn't too hard.
- I see you didn't bring
your little sidekick
with you, though.
- Nope.
Just me.
- That's too bad.
I brought one.
[beam blasting]
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, and Flash?
A little, uh,
quaking in your boots
wouldn't be inappropriate.
♪ ♪
- So?
- He changed our lives, Iris.
And he kept that secret from us.
You really just want us
to just be okay with that?
- All I'm saying, Wally,
is that he made a mistake.
- Yeah, he did.
- Cisco, we all make mistakes
to protect the people
that we love.
I mean, you told Captain Cold
that Barry was The Flash
in order to protect
your brother.
- Okay.
Not my finest moment.
- That's my point.
It was one decision
made in one moment.
One very
heart-wrenching moment.
Look, guys,
we're like a family here, okay?
And sometimes families
get mad at each other
for screwing up.
I know that all too well.
But they also forgive.
Because after a while,
it just seems silly
when you stop
and think about it.
[sentimental music]
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Guys, Iris is right.
We all have secrets.
We've all screwed up,
but this is Barry
we're talking about.
[computer beeping]
Who apparently is in trouble.
[dramatic music]
[beam blasting]
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- And who are you?
- I am Alchemy.
- Okay, well,
what do you want?
- To help people achieve
their true potential...
such as he has.
- And why are you doing this?
- Because I'm preparing
this world.
[whooshing]
- [grunting]
- Remember what happened here
last time, Flash?
It's where I died.
- [grunting]
- And I'm not gonna waste this
second chance I've been given.
This time, I'm gonna show you
who's the fastest man alive.
- [grunts]
[metal clangs]
[computer beeping rapidly]
- Barry? Barry!
- His coms aren't working.
- He's at the Prescott Mill.
- That's right around
the corner.
- We gotta do something.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- [grunting]
- Having fun yet, Flash?
'Cause I'm having a blast.
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
Ah!
♪ ♪
[grunting]
Ah!
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Time to look
for a new rival.
[laser beam blasts]
♪ ♪
- Stay away from my friend.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
[both grunting]
[glasses beep]
♪ ♪
Thank you.
- Sorry it took so long.
- You were just in time.
♪ ♪
- Nothing.
No mention
of Alchemy anywhere.
No mask-wearing monk metas.
Not even close.
- I didn't find
any known aliases in any
of the records at CCPD.
And Clariss
won't say anything either.
- All right, well, keep at him.
Alchemy is the one that gave
Clariss back his speed.
- He's kinda like a doctor,
that way, don't you think?
Come on, don't pretend
like "Doctor Alchemy"
doesn't have
a nice ring to it.
- Okay, well, that explains why
he didn't have
any traces of dark matter
in his cells.
He didn't get his powers
from the particle accelerator,
he got them from Alchemy.
- What was that?
- Doctor Alchemy.
- [laughs]
How could he do that?
- I don't know,
but we need to figure it out.
There's gonna be more.
Alchemy...Doctor Alchemy
said that he is
preparing this world.
- Preparing the world?
- Mm-hmm.
- For what? Like,
the second coming or something?
- I think that everyone
that had powers in Flashpoint
is gonna get them back.
- Well, we already found
four other husks,
which means
there's at least that many
running around
Central City right now.
- We need to find him
before he changes
more people's lives.
- Speaking of changing lives,
we all talked about it, Barry,
and we don't want to know
what our lives were like
in Flashpoint.
- You sure?
- To quote the wise words
of Harry,
"What's the point, Allen?"
- I gotta get
to the precinct.
- Uh, stop by Jitters
on the way?
- Yeah, it's on me.
- Oh, good.
Then I'm coming, too.
[sentimental music]
- Yo, um, I've just been
thinking that it was pretty cool
having someone out there
with me last night.
And, I don't know,
maybe we could
make that a thing
every once in a while.
- I-I got some things
to work on
before I start doing that.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
- Maybe someday.
It'd be pretty bitchin'.
♪ ♪
- Glad to see everything's
starting to
get back to the way it was.
- Yeah. I mean...
mostly.
You have nothing
to worry about, Cait.
I think out of everyone,
actually, you're the only one
that wasn't really affected
when I messed with the timeline.
I mean, unless you're
secretly moonlighting
as an ophthalmologist.
- A what?
- Kidding, nothing.
Just a Flashpoint joke.
I'll see you later.
[suspenseful music]
[ice crackling]
♪ ♪
- What's that?
- That's the finished
Edward Clariss report.
Or should I say The Rival?
At least, that's what
The Flash called him
last night when he took him
into Iron Heights.
- Huh.
- I thought you might
want to see it.
You know, to do with
your other case.
- Actually it turns out
there was no connection.
- Hm.
You know,
I have to ask you.
- Hm?
- How did you know his name?
- What?
- Yesterday, you came in
and you asked
for Edward Clariss' report,
but I didn't tell you
who that husk belonged to,
so that means
you stole a sample when you
showed up to my crime scene.
How did you do that?
- I...
- [laughs] Oh, wow.
You've really got this good guy
routine thing down, haven't you?
And everyone just buys it.
There is something
not right about you, Allen.
They don't see it...
but I do.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
[chuckles] You know why I don't
actually like you, don't you?
- [exhales]
- I don't trust you.
And I don't like things
that I don't trust.
♪ ♪
- See you tomorrow, roomie.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I was hoping you'd be here.
- Yeah.
Dad and I just polished off
Grandma Esther's noodle dish.
- Oh, did you leave me some?
- Too slow, Flash.
- Ooh.
[both laugh]
So you guys are...?
- We're good.
- Are you sure you don't wanna
know about the other timeline?
- No, I guess, in my mind,
wherever you go,
you'll always be Barry,
and I'll always be Iris.
♪ ♪
And we always find each other.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- You failed.
♪ ♪
You failed, Clariss.
- I'm sorry.
Please...
let me try again.
Alchemy!
[faint electrical crackling]
No, no, no, no, no.
[rumbling, booming]
No!
[screams]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.