Last season on "The Flash"...
Iris West,
- will you marry me?
- Yes.
I'm not Caitlin anymore.
- You're not Killer Frost.
- I'm not.
I'm something else,
and I need to figure out
what that is on my own.
Cecile Horton,
I love you.
That is definitely not a breach.
The Speed Force is unbalanced.
- This is Speed Force Prison.
- Without a prisoner...
- It goes unstable.
- How do we stop this?
My name is Iris West,
and I was supposed to marry
the fastest man alive,
but six months ago, he left.
Barry, it's time.
Barry.
This isn't fair. We were supposed
to have our happy ending.
I'm ready to be Iris West-Allen.
And you always will be.
But you have to keep
living your life, okay?
Keep running, for me.
Promise me you'll run, Iris.
I promise.
I promised him I'd run, so that's what
I've been doing these last six months,
running as fast as I can.
I can't find her, Cisco.
Well, I gotta work out more.
She's really stepped up her game.
Then let's turn up ours. I
don't have eyes on her.
- Iris?
- Copy, I'm on it.
Looking...
Got her. - And?
- Duck!
- I don't see no duck.
Peekaboo.
Your only warning, boys.
Stay back.
- She meant the other duck.
- Yeah, I cannot believe
you actually thought
she meant a duck duck.
Where is she, Iris?
She's headed for the Keystone Bridge.
If she gets out of the city,
we're gonna lose her for good.
You guys have to stop her now.
Oh, I'ma catch her this time.
I hate teleporters.
Three...
She jumps every third rooftop.
Cisco, she's gonna jump
to the Broome Tower.
When she lands, stop her. - On it.
Dad, meet them at the bottom. - Copy.
- Wally...
- I know what to do.
Whoa.
Come on.
Peekaboo-yah!
Dead bang, fellas.
Look at that.
We got her.
- sync and corrections by Mr. C -
- www.addic7ed.com -
I'm so proud of us.
That was a good hustle
out there, Team Vibe.
It's Team Kid Flash, but thank you.
Okay, not your finest hour, gentlemen.
What are you looking at me for?
I was the one to put her down.
And Wally and I helped him out
with the assist. Classic maneuver.
Yeah, it actually went
exactly as we planned.
Exactly as we planned.
You don't believe us, ask Joe.
Joe, go ahead and tell her how
this went exactly as we planned.
Peek-a-Boo fell right into our trap.
- I'm not doing that.
- And we aren't exactly
catching bad guys at our old rate.
One out of every three
metas that we've fought
in the last six months has escaped.
Temporarily, yes,
but Team Kid Flash is on the case.
Son, I love you,
but ain't nobody feeling Team Kid Flash.
It's, like, too many syllables.
Okay, guys, maybe a little
less fooling around
and a little more taking
things seriously.
It's up to us to protect
this city, right?
Because there is no one else.
Wally, why don't you, um,
go to the Speed Lab?
I've programmed a new
training simulation for you.
- It should only take four hours.
- Four... what?
No, what about family dinner tonight?
You know what, training sounds amazing.
Okay. See ya at home, boss.
Cisco, you wanna...
share what you're thinking?
I'm thinking it would
be a lot better off
if we weren't one man down.
I only have a couple more
boxes to bring over.
We have no more room
in the garage or the basement.
Right... or, we could just get
rid of some more of your stuff.
- Like what?
- Like, babe, do you really need
all the smelly old records in there?
- Oh, Cecile...
- Records?
You mean my vintage
jazz LP collection...
- Mm-hmm.
- That I painstakingly
and carefully collected
over the last 30 years?
- Really?
- Those are my loves, babe.
They're going in the
coffin with me when I die.
Okay, maybe we could bury them now,
and you can just join
them at a later date.
- Oh, you got jokes?
- Yeah.
You lucky I already gave you the key,
because I'm starting to rethink
this whole move-in thing.
- No, you're not.
- No, I'm not.
No, you're not...
'Cause you love me.
Um...
Why don't I go make some coffee?
Obvious.
Okay, so,
ever since Julian moved back to London,
they have been short-staffed
in the crime lab at CCPD,
and I've been stalling Singh
with this whole story of
Barry being on sabbatical
in the Czech Republic...
And they wanna hire
someone to replace him.
Yeah, they should. They need the help.
- Barry's not coming back, so...
- You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
Sweetheart...
I'm very proud of you
for taking the lead
with Wally and Cisco at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and I let you have your space,
so that you'd have time to
deal with what happened.
Dad, I'm fine, okay?
I'm not. We lost him, Iris.
My son, your everything.
Dad, what do you want me to do?
Curl up in a ball and cry all day?
I can't do that.
Barry told me to be strong.
I'm being strong.
When H.R. died, we had a funeral.
We spoke about his life.
Maybe we should do the
same thing for Barry,
give us all permission to grieve.
And what are we gonna bury, Dad?
An empty suit in the lab?
You know what, thank Cecile for dinner.
I'm gonna get going, okay?
Wally? Cisco?
We're up.
Guys? What are we looking at?
Holy Ronin.
It's a Samurai.
Anybody speak Japanese?
_
Tell me he did not just speak Japanese.
I can do things.
_
The Flash.
Yeah, you're looking at him, pal.
You're not The Flash.
You're not the best.
Bring me The Flash...
I'm sensing an "or else."
Or else your city falls.
The Flash ain't coming.
Furthermore, Mifune,
we're gonna need you
to sheath that sword
before somebody gets hurt,
somebody like you, for instance,
'cause you're up against
some bad hombres,
and what do you think
you're gonna do against us
with a sword?
You guys okay?
What the hell kinda sword is that?
You have one day.
If The Flash does not face me,
Central City dies.
The Flash hasn't been
seen in almost 6 months,
leaving us to speculate
what can save us from
this newest threat.
There are other
superheroes in this town.
Yeah, and your boy, Kurosawa, over there
blew us away like ragdolls
performing his reverse Excalibur.
We haven't faced anything
like this before.
Why do you think he
only wanted The Flash?
He said he wants to fight the best.
He's threatening to destroy the city.
- Do we think he can do it?
- I say yes.
Then he has to fight The Flash.
Who isn't here?
What if he was?
Iris, you said it yourself.
Just us trying to keep the city safe,
we're barely getting it done.
And this guy, he's no joke.
If we don't offer up The Flash,
there's gonna be serious damage.
People are gonne die, and
that's gonna be on us.
We need to bring Barry back.
Cisco, we can't.
If Barry comes out, the
Speed Force Prison goes...
It becomes unstable.
It could destroy the
city, the whole world.
Which is exactly what
we're trying to prevent.
What if I can solve that?
- In the next 24 hours?
- Yes!
Guys, I've been working on this.
For how long?
Since the night he left.
- Cisco?
- I've had help.
I've consulted with Harry and...
and Tina
and Tracy and Felicity and Curtis,
and I'm pretty sure I figured out a way
to stabilize the Speed Force
Prison and free Barry
without unleashing another
lightning storm on the city.
I just need a couple more things.
- Maybe we should.
- No.
You've been working on this for how long
and you never told us?
I didn't wanna say anything
until I was certain.
Are you certain that the Speed Force
won't take Wally in his place?
Are you certain that
you can even close it
before it rips Central City in two?
Are you certain that Barry
is even still alive?
He's gotta be.
Iris, you, of all people,
how can you not be in on this?
Because Barry is gone.
That is the only thing any
of us can be certain about.
Now, let's do what we can
do to come up with a plan
to take out this Samurai.
Okay?
- Okay?
- Okay...
But I'm gonna need some coffee.
♪ Coming over the mountain
Hello.
My, what a selection.
You got any recommendations?
Yeah, drink somewhere else.
What can I get you?
Let's go with something sweet
but deceptively strong
with lots of ice.
Shirley Temple, coming right up.
What is a nice girl with
two doctorates and a PHD
doing in a rat's nest like this one?
Working. How'd you find me?
'Cause I'm great with computers,
and I have my own satellite.
You do the math.
- You Vibed me.
- I Vibed you, yes.
You're looking a lot less frosty
than the last time I saw you.
You said you weren't her, but
you weren't Caitlin either.
It's just me, Cisco. I'm just Caitlin.
How'd you do it?
What do you want?
Well, a stiffer drink, for starters.
If you're back to
normal, I have to know,
why didn't you come back to us?
Okay, I get it. That's fine.
I'm not gonna make you answer that.
But we really could've used you.
Barry's still stuck in the Speed Force?
You knew about that?
I'm gonna get him out,
but I need your help.
Everything okay?
- Everything's fine.
- Yeah, everything's great, pal.
Do you mind? I'm talking to the lady.
I'm sure there's someone
else you can find in here
to commiserate with
over poor life choices.
Thank you.
Look, I figured out how to save Barry,
but I can't do it without you.
Did you see that Samurai
that showed up today?
Yes.
He's threatening to blow up the city,
and we need Barry to stop him.
So help us out, please?
Caitlin?
My shift's over in an hour.
Girl, I got time.
Oh, this is good.
Is there anything you can't do?
Move on, apparently.
Hang tight. You're coming home, buddy.
Hey, Cisco, can you pull up
the Mockingbird satellite?
We're tracking down this Samurai.
Cisco?
Wally?
Mr. West, Mr. West.
So, what are we doing out here, Cisco?
It seemed an appropriate venue.
- We've had good luck here before.
- Why do we need good luck?
Because we're bringing Barry back.
Cisco, Iris said...
I know what Iris said, Joe.
I also know Barry said
everyone would look to me
after he was gone.
So look to me.
Four of us, we can do this.
What do you mean the four of us?
- Hi, Joe.
- It's okay.
She's Caitlin again, our Caitlin.
She's here to help us.
So, what do you say?
You better be right.
I am.
Joe, I know that I can never make up
for the things that I
did to you, to Cecile.
I just hope...
I just hope that one day
you can forgive me.
Come here.
Let's bring everybody home today, okay?
- You got it.
- So how are we gonna bring
Barry back without blowing
a hole in the, uh, world?
Ha! In the spirit of
bringing back old friends,
may I present the Speed Force bazooka.
Ah...
I made a few slight modifications,
as Captain Solo would say.
Caitlin and I spent all of last night
working out some kinks,
fine-tuning the Quark Sphere.
- What?
- The Quark Sphere,
filled with Barry's
unique genetic marker,
and programmed to track
his specific DNA,
using the electrical current
of the Speed Force.
Once we track Barry and we pull him out,
the Quark Sphere will
trick the Speed Force
- into thinking he's still there.
- Hey, Wally,
can you put that on the center pylon?
- Ready.
- Let's bring our boy home.
Quark Matter scanning
electrical current.
Triangulating Quark
Matter on his location.
I've got a lock on something.
It's him.
It's him!
Now, Cisco!
I can't believe you did
this behind my back.
You would've tried to stop us.
Because it was a waste of time.
I don't understand.
This should've worked.
Or you could've killed us all.
I don't know, Iris. I think
we were pretty close.
I'm sorry, "we"?
Where have you been the
last six months again?
- She was only trying to help.
- Look, guys,
we need to concentrate
on stopping this Samurai
who's trying to destroy
the city, not on Barry.
Dude, what is your deal?
It's like you don't even want him back.
Hey, hey, hey!
Cecile, can I call you back in a minute?
We're in the middle of something here.
What?
State police picked him up on the 112
- outside of Ivy City.
- That's 300 miles away.
Yeah, one of the cops is a Keystone vet.
- Recognized him.
- I knew it would work.
I knew it.
You should prepare yourselves.
Barry?
Barry...
Nora shouldn't be here.
Your mom isn't here, Barry. It's...
it's me, Iris.
You're home.
Your Honor, I'm innocent.
I didn't do this. I didn't kill anyone.
Can you hear the stars singing?
Rhyming, chiming, timing
every hour, every minute.
You said the city was safe,
that there was no residual danger,
but that's not true.
What really happened that night...
The city is safe.
You saved it. You saved us all.
Stars melting
like ice cream,
dream, gleam.
Nothing seems...
Nora shouldn't be here.
I'm guessing this isn't just shock.
Shock results from a
drop in blood pressure.
This is neurological.
It's a whole new way
of looking at physics.
It will change the way that we think
about everything,
from a single atom
to an entire galaxy.
God!
Stars so loud.
Loud, cloud, proud.
Dad and I are both okay.
We're gonna be fine.
I'm just not sure I'm like you, Oliver.
We need to get him back to S.T.A.R.
Labs now.
What's the diagnosis?
Does he have brain damage or something?
He's actually scary healthy.
His neurotransmitters are functioning at
five times the normal speed.
- Then what's wrong?
- I have two theories.
One is that he's suffering
from a form of schizophasia.
That's where you assign the
wrong definitions to words.
So, from his perspective,
all that nonsense he's
saying makes sense?
It's too bad we don't have a translator.
No, but we can make one.
If his brain's schizophastic
and these symbols represent
different words,
he could be sending us a message,
and we just need the right
algorithm to decrypt it.
You said you had two theories.
What's the other one?
We know that the Speed Force
exists beyond space and time.
To us, Barry was only in
there for six months,
but to him, it could've
been 10,000 years.
All that time in isolation,
it could've caused dementia.
That may be all of him that's left.
So how do we find out which one it is?
I could decrease the
sedative, wake him up.
I think I've got the
perfect song for that.
Are you sure this is appropriate?
Yeah. It's a good luck charm.
I mean, it worked before.
Last time, he was in a coma,
not a pan-temporal extra dimension.
Well, waking up to Gaga
shouldn't seem too freaky.
Hey, Barry.
Hey.
It's me, Cisco,
AKA Vibe,
BKA your BFF.
Yeah. Hey, buddy.
Hey.
While you were gone, I
made you a new suit.
Do you wanna take it out for a spin?
The stars are raining.
Draining.
Paining. Too soon.
I think maybe later.
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.
He didn't do those things.
He didn't hurt my mom. I
was there that night.
There was a man, plan.
No plan.
We're gonna need more diapers.
Diapers.
You keep drawing, buddy.
You keep drawing. I'm
gonna figure this out.
- Caitlin...
- I don't know.
Guys, can I get the room for a second?
♪ 77
Barry...
I don't know
if you can hear me,
or if you're trying to
send us a message somehow.
Hey, I did what you told me to.
I kept running, I kept moving forward,
because I knew that if I
stopped to look back,
then I would remember that you
weren't behind me anymore.
And it's been so hard.
And when Cisco said that
he could bring you back,
you know, I didn't know what to think.
What if it didn't work?
What if you were dead?
I mean, I thought it would be
like losing you all over again.
I never imagined this, though.
I don't know what I would do if
this is all that's left of you,
if this is all that's left of
the amazing man that I know
and love.
Please come back to me.
Tell me you're still my Barry.
Guys?
Barry! Barry, stop!
Breach him to the pipeline!
He's too fast!
Expecting someone else?
We need to get him in a containment cell
before he does that again.
Samurai's back.
More like Samurai jackass.
Nope, that's a rough draft.
It hasn't even been a full day yet.
He said he'd level the city if
we didn't bring in The Flash.
Well, let's give him what he asked for.
You wanted me...
Here I am.
You're not The Flash.
Wally!
If I don't get the real
Flash by nightfall,
this city comes down.
How long till I can get back out there?
Wally, he sliced right
through your fibula.
If you weren't a speedster, I'd
be amputating your leg right now.
Okay, how long?
Four to five hours?
We don't have that kinda time.
You know what, I'm fine.
Son... son, son...
You've done everything you can do.
Relax.
- Any luck?
- No, not yet.
The computer keeps telling
me it's random gibberish.
- Maybe it is.
- No, it's not.
Barry's trying to send us a message.
I know it.
I mean, he spent all this
time in the Speed Force.
Maybe now he knows the answers to
life, the universe, and everything.
So you think all this crazy writing
is Barry's way of telling us 42?
Yes, exactly.
Have I mentioned how much
I miss having you around?
I'm gonna keep working on this....
Unless
you have any ideas.
Nope, it's all Greek to me.
Great Caesar's Ghost.
This analysis is based on
a monoalphabetic substitution cipher,
but what if it's polyalphabetic?
What if it's... it's like Greek?
Like the symbols are unique alphabet?
Excelsior!
- What is it?
- Cisco figured it out.
He figured out how to
crack Barry's code.
- You did? What does it say?
- Hold on one sec.
It's loading. Come on...
Loading, loading, loading, loading...
and it says...
"This house is bitchin'."
"This house is bitchin'"?
- That doesn't sound like Barry.
- No.
No. No, it doesn't.
That's 'cause it's not.
Whoa.
Don't tell me you have
Frankenstein under there.
It's Barry's new suit,
although right now, I'm
having trouble seeing it
as anything other than a waste of time.
- Cisco...
- I know.
I should've listened to you.
Barry was never
trying to communicate with us,
but I believed it.
I really did.
Sometimes, I feel like if I believe in
something hard enough,
that'll make it real.
You know what the worst part is?
I didn't do it to save the city.
I did it because it...
gave me an excuse to bring him back.
I did it because I missed my friend.
Much better.
You said it yourself.
She goes looking for danger.
I thought cleaning him up
would make me feel better, but...
Yeah.
The more he looks like himself,
the more it reminds you how lost he is.
You have to believe that
things can get better.
There is an answer for every question.
I don't think I know
how to anymore, Dad.
I know that feeling. I was
struggling with it too.
But I figured it out.
- How?
- Church.
You haven't gone to
church since I was a kid.
I know.
Cecile suggested it,
thought it would help.
But I swear,
one of the priest's homilies,
it was like... it was
like he wrote it for me.
"Strength means nothing
without faith"...
And I started realizing
that my strength
didn't stop me from thinking
I lost you to Savitar,
or that we'd never see Barry again.
Cecile reminded me to have faith...
And I believed.
And here you two are.
You got strength, baby girl.
You just need a little faith.
Joe, Samurai's 24 hours are up.
Gotta go.
Come get me.
I don't see The Flash.
I'm afraid you're gonna
have to make do with us.
Iris! Hold your fire.
You want The Flash? Take me.
Why?
Because he'll come for me.
And how...
do you know this?
I believe.
Iris!
Hey! Samurai's got Iris.
- She gave herself up to him.
- What?
Why would she do that?
How do we get her back?
Barry! Iris is in trouble.
She needs your help.
I doubt restraint is how you got to be
the man you are today,
play, way, no way!
Highway, byway!
Please, son. Please!
I wanna help you with
all this, and I will,
but right now she needs our help,
or she's gonna die.
Barry, did you hear what I said?
Iris is gonna die!
Barry's gone.
You know what else is gone?
The new suit.
What's happening?
The Flash is back!
Do you see how fast he's running?
- I've never gone that fast.
- No one has.
Where is this Samurai taking Iris?
They're already way past Danville,
and the only thing out there
is the flatlands and...
And what?
Come on, Barry, catch her.
The Flash,
welcome home.
Barry...
You came back to me.
Always.
Pupils are equally reactive to light.
I mean, your vitals are amazing.
You're in perfect health, even for you.
I... I'd like a urine
sample, just to confirm,
but everything looks great.
Man, you love urine.
You love the... the testing of urine.
The testing of the urine.
You know what I meant.
Why do you have to ruin science?
It's good to have you back.
Right back at ya.
- How you feeling?
- I feel great.
Yeah, I feel incredible.
I don't know, it feels
like I've been reborn.
- Mm.
- Well, okay, speedy Jesus.
Seriously, though.
I mean, it hurts me to admit it,
but you may be the
fastest speedster ever.
I mean, you were in the
Speed Force for six months.
Maybe you were soaking up its energy?
Maybe.
How was everything while I was gone?
Oh, yeah, it was... it was really cool.
Team Kid Flash had everything
under control, so...
That's not our name.
But still, we have some
mysteries left to solve,
like our flying Samurai robot...
Android Samurai.
Samur-oid.
Oh-ho-ho, we back, baby!
Yeah, someone created this,
and it must be for a reason.
Does the phrase, "This
house is bitchin'"
mean anything to you?
No?
- Should it?
- No.
Just know that when you were in
your "Beautiful Mind" phase,
you were talking straight-up nonsense.
I don't remember any of that.
Last thing I remember was going
into the Speed Force with my mom
and then saving Iris.
So how'd you know Iris was in trouble?
I don't know.
Hm.
Well, thanks for bringing me home.
You're very welcome.
Hey, Cisco,
thanks for believing when I couldn't.
- We'll see you tomorrow, boss.
- Yeah.
I know we left some
questions unanswered,
but I have to know,
are we gonna see you tomorrow?
Yeah, you will.
We back, baby.
- Where have you been?
- Doesn't matter.
Really?
Tell Amunet I'm out.
You wanna quit, Snow?
Doesn't work that way.
You do what Amunet says for
as long as she tells you.
Not anymore.
Now leave me alone.
You don't tell us what to do.
Don't make me frosty.
You wouldn't like me when I'm frosty.
What's the matter? Brain freeze?
Touch my hand again, and
I'll freeze yours off,
maybe some other parts too.
Tell Amunet I'm done.
Don't let your beer get warm.
Time to have some fun.
Not yet.
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Not again.
Are you tired? Do you
want to get some sleep?
No, I feel like I've
been asleep for months.
I, um... I couldn't bring myself
to sleep in our bed alone.
I couldn't even look at that.
It's been really hard, Barry.
Hey, well, I'm back,
and I'm never going anywhere ever again.
I tried to keep going,
to keep fighting, to keep
running, like you said.
You did.
You kept everyone together.
I'm so proud of you, okay?
Look, it sounds funny,
but... maybe this was a blessing.
You being gone for six
months was a blessing?
I just... I... I can't
tell you how I feel, Iris.
It's like, everything that
was wrong in my life,
the pain of my past, my mistakes,
it's all just washed away,
and all I see is you and us
and our future together.
Iris, it's gonna be great.
Central City needs The Flash.
I'll be right back, I promise.
The Samurai served its purpose.
As in 12th century feudal Japan,
a time when the military
class was powerful,
the execution methodical,
like ours.
Well, it worked.
The Flash is back in Central City.
It appears things are going as planned.
As if there were any doubt.
What's our next step?
I'm thinking.