I'm almost at the goal line.
[sighs]
Look, I know I've been stable
for a few months, and I'm not due
for another treatment quite yet,
but I appreciate you checking.
Hey, got to check yourself
before you wreck yourself.
[chuckles nervously]
All right, well,
you're all good now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, it's... It's just that...
Um...
Lately, I've been forgetting things.
For instance, there was this dinner
at my dad's and I...
Dad.
Weren't you just upstairs?
Yeah,
and then I went to the garage
because you asked me to get the files
from the old Scarpola case.
Remember?
Um...
Yeah. I must have just...
Checked out or something
for a couple of minutes.
And then I have this hazy memory
of... of a train station,
and for some reason, I feel
like you were there.
[Deon] You forget we had
an appointment in the books...
You're gonna start moving
in and out of timelines again.
It's news to me 'cause I'd remember
something like that. [chuckling]
Yeah, yeah, no, of course.
Hey, um...
How does someone catch
a "time sickness" anyway?
No idea. But I intend to find out.
Whoa, hold up now.
What is it?
I'm picking up mutations.
Ones I've never seen before.
Well, that sounds bad.
Actually, it could mean a lot of things.
Might even be a side effect
of my treatments.
Tell you what, I'm going to go hit up
my Force sibs to see if they can
help me figure this out.
Well, what do I tell Barry?
Nothing. I don't know what this is yet.
So for now, just chill.
Trust me.
All right? As soon as I find out
what's up, I'll come find you.
Wherever you are.
[sighs]
This case gives dead ends a bad name.
At least no one else has been hurt.
Yet.
Barr, what's wrong?
I just can't shake the feeling
that there's something we missed.
Look, I'm gonna dig into the evidence
you gave me
from last week's crime scene.
All right. Thanks.
Hey, where's Caitlin?
We need all the help we can get.
Ever since she decided
to go all-in with Marcus,
it's open season
on spontaneous getaways.
So one minute, they're listening to show
tunes, getting all weepy on the couch,
and then the next, they got
last-minute tickets
to Dear Evan Hansen in Metropolis.
Well, good for her.
But where does that leave us?
[Chester] One step closer
to the truth, y'all.
Okay, so I stayed up all night
building this cold fusion
alarm module for our satellites...
- [Cecile] Chester?
- Uh...
You all right?
Yeah. Sorry. Sorry, uh...
This all-nighter's got me zoning out.
Here's the deal. So, we know that
this meta's fire powers are cryokinetic,
meaning that their power output
would read as extreme cold pockets.
So, this alarm I just finished building?
It's going to alert us
as soon as there's any rapid drops
and barometric anomalies
anywhere in the city.
Only downside is we won't know
where our baddie actually is
until "flames on."
Or someone else gets burned up.
No, the moment we get a hit, I'll be
fast enough to get there in time,
and we can end this
before anyone else gets hurt.
[Allegra] Sue Dearbon.
Loving the non-catsuit look.
Why the change?
I got restless. So, here I am.
Iris?
Hi, you good?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm great. Um...
Yeah. So what brings you
back to Central City?
Oh, well, now that Black Hole is gone
and my parents
are in white-collar prison,
I am in charge of revitalizing
the family business,
so I'm just here showing face
at all the business holdings
and reassure everyone personally
that things are gonna be different.
And added bonus,
I get to pop in on my favorite tenants.
Well, we are eternally grateful
for your help in expanding our office.
Hey, you guys are the ones
doing all the work.
All right.
I have got to jet to Coast City.
We own a string of luxury hotels
I have to go inspect.
- Sounds fun.
- No. No, it's boring as hell.
Yeah. But if I'm lucky, maybe I'll catch
a glimpse of the C.C.P. while I'm there.
Oh. You guys haven't heard. Apparently,
there's been multiple sightings
of someone walking through walls.
It's popping up on socials as
#CoastCityPhantom.
[Allegra] Yeah, sounds like a new meta.
But I wonder how they got
their powers on the west coast.
Actually, I have run into
quite a few metas around the world.
Turns out there's folks all over
the place with latent meta genes.
All it takes is the right set
of circumstances
for their powers to manifest.
Maybe that's what happened
in Coast City.
Yeah, giving them their first meta.
Iris, this could be a great story.
Yeah. You should come with me.
I would love the company.
You don't mind staying in posh
five-star hotel suites, do you?
Um, I'll go.
You will?
Yeah. Allegra can cover things
while I'm gone.
I can?
Yeah, don't you have a blossoming
media empire to run?
Well, I can run things remotely.
And besides, Allegra's right.
I mean, this is a huge scoop.
And if this story pops, it could lay the
groundwork to a west coast expansion.
I am sold.
Great! That's that. Road trip.
Oh.
Let's go.
Okay.
[alarm sounding]
Is that a cold spot?
Our fire meta just turned up
at 138 South Devon Road.
What the hell?
[whooshes]
Flash, did you find him?
Barry, what's happening?
I'm too late.
Black fire?
Yeah, it was like nothing
I've ever encountered.
And it put itself out.
How's that even possible?
I don't know. But I'm telling you, man.
I mean, it was there one second,
the next, nothing.
So, what else do we know?
The vic's name, Parker DeStefano.
She teaches classes here at the studio.
Hey, are you seeing this?
Look.
Holy Fahrenheit 451.
Okay. We need a way to preserve it.
Maybe we could try using
the micro-catalyzed containment unit.
- The what?
- Ray Palmer and I designed it together
in collaboration with the foundation
that he named after my dad.
The M.C.C.U. preserves
the vaporized integrity of gases,
but it's back at my workshop.
What does it look like?
It's like an eight inch vacuum-sealed
borosilicate canister
with an ionic-fused base and cap.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah, okay, that's going
to take some time to get used to.
Is this it?
Yeah, yes, yeah. [chuckles softly]
Okay.
Okay, try to determine
its molecular properties,
- then reprogram our satellite module...
- To detect whatever meta-data I find.
Yeah. Then match it to
a city-wide search.
That way, if we're lucky...
We can catch this murderer
before they kill again.
[Iris West] I triangulated the last few
Coast City Phantom sightings
posted to social media,
and all of them occurred downtown.
[Sue] Wow. You're really pulling out
all the stops.
So, how's tricks?
Everything okay at work?
Yeah, better than ever.
I mean, CCC Media is evolving.
How about you and Barry? You guys
still the couple of the century?
[scoffs] You say that
like it's a bad thing.
Lady, it is the best thing.
Agreed.
Uh, yeah, no, Barry is leveling up
and firing on all cylinders
with Team Flash
and... Hold on.
What's with all the prying?
It's nothing.
I mean, I get it. Life's grand
and you're busy as all get-out.
But with all that going on,
you're still really eager
to help this new meta become
The Streak part two.
And Allegra could have handled
this story
and taken some of this off your plate.
Is there anything you want to share?
- [device beeping]
- [Iris West] Oh!
Oh, look at that. We got a hit.
Let's go.
Okay. Not them.
Could be either one.
- We should probably get closer.
- Uh-uh
Give it a minute.
Yahtzee.
Hi. I am Iris West-Allen
with the Central City Citizen Media.
Never heard of it.
- Fair enough. And this is...
- Her landlord.
Yeah. Still not caring.
So, if you don't mind...
Okay. Well, we were hoping
that you could help us
with a story that we're researching.
Not interested.
It's about the Coast City Phantom.
You ever heard of him?
Or her?
Look, we don't want
to cause you any trouble, okay?
We really just want to talk to you
and see if
there's any way that we can help you.
What's your name?
I'm not telling you that.
Order for Tinya.
Oh. Tinya.
Triple espresso.
That's a lot of caffeine for a teen.
Okay, I'm gonna be honest. When we heard
that there was a possibility of a meta
- in Coast City...
- What's a meta?
People like you, with powers.
And what?
You think I'm your next headline?
No, no, it's not like that.
It's just in Central City,
we have experience working with metas.
To do what?
Well, to help others.
Have you heard of The Flash?
Okay. Well, eight years ago,
I was the reporter
that helped break his story.
And if you let me,
I can help do the same for you.
How'd you guys find me anyway?
Well, metas like you are made up
of dark matter,
and this app helps us find just that.
Really?
[electricity crackling]
Well, good luck finding me now.
[sarcastically] Yeah, that went well.
I've triple-checked
the Who's Who binder.
Nothing on a Tales from the Crypt meta
who can conjure up black fire.
With no chemical signatures
to program into our satellites,
we're still flying pretty blind.
[sighs]
All right. Keep working the science.
I'm gonna pay Kramer a visit.
Now that she's part of the team,
she needs to know
what we're really dealing with.
Plus, maybe she can help us find
a connection between all three victims.
Just call me if you find anything.
- Yeah...
- [whooshing]
No problemo.
Just me and the scary black flame.
Nothing weird about that.
- [rumbling]
- [distorted voice warbling]
[breathing heavily]
Okay. Relax, Chester P.
Relax.
[exhales] You got this.
No, no, no, no, no...
No!
Hey, hey, there's fire!
There's fire! Help! Help me!
Fire! Help!
[yells in panic]
[Allegra] Chuck? Chuck.
[breath trembling]
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just us.
You were shouting in your sleep.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I just...
It's just a bad dream.
Must've been a doozy.
[Cecile] Hey, are you sure that's it?
I can feel how frightened you still are.
No, no, no.
I'm good. I'm good. Really.
I've just been working
way too much lately.
Maybe I just need some coffee
to power up the old mental hard drive.
[clears throat] I'm sorry.
Okay, I can feel him struggling.
Anybody else notice that he's
been having a hard time lately?
Yeah, I definitely have.
If something's bothering him,
why wouldn't he say so?
I mean, he's the most
touchy-feely person I know.
Must be super personal, then.
To keep us out? Team Flash?
Then that's just wrong.
He'll talk to me.
Since your phone's toast, I'm
downloading Chester's dark matter app.
Only seven hours and nine minutes to go.
Okay, I really need to upgrade
my service. I can afford it.
No, Sue, we don't have
that kind of time.
I mean, Tinya can walk through walls.
I mean, she could be anywhere.
Well, until this downloads,
we have the rest of the day
to come up with a better idea.
And this looks like
the perfect place to strategize.
Okay, well, we need to narrow down
all the places that we think
that she might be and search them.
Great. And we can talk about
the real problem while we're doing it.
Come on, Iris.
What are you really doing here?
[scoffs]
It's... It's far out, so...
Try me.
Last year, I started feeling...
weird.
And so, the Still Force
took a look at me
and discovered that I had
contracted a time sickness.
Now, what that means
and how I got it is still a mystery.
But I don't know.
Recently, I feel like...
I'm starting to lose time.
Okay. Okay. I see why you're freaking.
Yeah. And then this morning,
I checked in with Deon
and he found something
that he had never seen before.
And even though he told me to relax
while he looks into it,
I mean, I can't help but feeling
that something is really wrong.
And that's why you threw yourself
into this story?
Yeah, I needed a distraction.
Believe me, I understand.
I did the same thing
when I found out that my parents
volunteered to work for Black Hole.
At first, I was so mad,
I just looked the other way.
I mean, seriously, I did everything
to avoid facing
the consequences of their actions.
But I had to stop running away
and face my parents.
And, Iris, you have to do the same thing
about this fear
around this time sickness thing.
[sighs] Yeah, but I mean, what if Deon
shows up tomorrow with bad news?
Yeah, that could happen.
You could also be fine.
Either way, you have to stop running
from the fear of the unknown.
It's... It's a race you can't win.
- What?
- Tinya.
What if I'm not the only one running?
I think I know where to find her.
Got enough for a second cup?
Yeah, yeah. Definitely.
I'm not going to lie.
You look more stressed now
than you did during
the "Trials of Gyntarri" campaign.
Yeah. That was a tough one.
Wow. Even D&D talk
isn't going to perk you up.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little out of it.
I know this new fire meta case
is pretty intense.
And as our resident science guru,
you're in it pretty deep,
I mean, you have to examine victims
and run tests on bodies.
That's a lot of pressure.
I guess what I'm saying is,
you're not alone.
I mean,
we're all in this together, right?
So, if you need to talk
about something, anything...
[suspenseful music playing]
It's happening again.
How'd it get out?
It didn't, trust me.
I know you're not really here.
This is just another dream.
No, it's not.
Doesn't S.T.A.R. Labs have a fire
suppression system or something?
This fire is cold fusion.
It doesn't produce carbon dioxide.
Our sensors wouldn't pick it up
as real fire.
Please, please. Not like this.
It's here.
I can't put out these flames.
All right, just stay behind me.
I don't get it. First, Chuck has a dream
about this weird fire.
And then, the meta
who created it attacks us.
And why would anyone
want to hurt Chuck anyway?
I don't know.
But we're going to
keep you safe, I promise.
Thanks.
Chester, what about
your barometric-detection thingy?
Why didn't it go off?
When I programmed the search parameters,
I used the default setting
that establishes a tracking grid
outside of S.T.A.R Labs.
Right. Maybe you should fix that.
Yeah, I just did.
I also double-checked to make sure
that S.T.A.R Labs was clear, too.
It's like this black fire meta can
appear and disappear at random.
Plus their fire leaves no trace.
Like a ghost.
I gotta get some air.
He's hurting really bad inside.
Can you blame him? First, two bodies
show up at O'Shaughnessy's.
Then the yoga instructor,
DeStefano, this morning.
Yeah, and now the same person
is hunting Chuck,
a guy who would never hurt anyone.
It doesn't make any sense.
If this meta can get
inside S.T.A.R. Labs undetected,
they could be anywhere.
What if they're
controlling the flames remotely?
The shape that we saw in the fire
had no face.
No identifying marks.
Maybe it was some kind of projection.
I mean, it could explain
why you haven't been able to catch them.
The killer's never actually been
at any of the crime scenes.
But that doesn't explain
why our black fire meta
is going after Chester.
Put S.T.A.R. Labs on lockdown.
Nobody, except for me gets in or out,
till we figure out what's going on.
Where are you going?
If somebody
is controlling the fire remotely,
I'm going to search this city
until I find them.
Stay on comms.
On it.
[Iris West] She's not here.
How did you get...
I don't know how you found me,
but I'm out of here.
How about you stay?
Right. You do know that I can
walk through walls, right?
Well, we have friends at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And when I told them that we had
a ghost meta on our hands,
they gave me this.
It's called a molecular
destabilizing matrix.
Apparently, all I have to do
is turn it on
and it destabilizes any folks like you.
Within a three-block radius.
What do you say we give it a try?
Yeah, I thought you two helped people.
[Sue] Oh, she does.
Me, it depends on my mood.
So... Why don't you relax?
Let's hear Iris out.
Why do you even care?
We know that you're looking
for your mother.
It was your backpack, at Jitters.
It looked like your whole life
was jammed inside of it.
I started looking through Coast City's
missing persons database.
And that's when I found out
that you had run away from foster care.
And that your birth mother
worked at that Jitters.
And that this apartment
was her last known address.
Yeah, she's a damn good reporter.
Okay, well, then you also know that my
real mom abandoned me when I was born.
And hasn't tried
to contact me since. Not once.
Not to see how I'm doing
or if I even survived.
But I did.
And it's been hell recently.
But now that I suddenly have
these new powers,
I have a chance to be somebody.
So you wanted to show your mom
what you've become.
Yeah, because maybe she'll think
that I'm something special.
And take me back.
Latent meta powers,
manifested by intense emotion. Check.
Let us help you find her.
[Sue] Eh, it's just a paperweight.
Like I said, Iris is a great reporter.
And if there's anyone
that can help you find your mom,
it's her.
If you'll trust me.
[Allegra] We're gonna find out
what's behind all this.
And you're gonna be fine.
I'm starting to wonder
if that's still possible.
[Allegra] We've got your back.
Trust me, you're more than
just a part of this team.
You are a part of my life,
and I'm not letting you go anytime soon.
Got it?
Allegra, I...
Never mind.
It's just...
You're just a really good friend.
So are you. The best.
Which is why I gotta tell you this.
That person in the fire?
I know who it was.
And it wasn't some new fire meta.
It was a ghost.
You seriously think
you're being haunted?
For real?
By my father.
That's who was in the fire.
And I know that
because that's how he died.
But for some reason he's...
He's come back.
But... I was there,
and whatever it was,
it didn't have a face.
It was just a shape.
No, no, no. It was more than that.
I wasn't with my dad
when he died, okay?
But when that fire appeared,
that thing inside of it
made me feel like I was.
Right there on the road,
where it happened 24 years ago.
It's almost like
I could see the wreckage.
And feel the heat
from the engine burning.
And then I could
hear my dad shouting for help.
But no one came.
Allegra, no one came.
He just...
No one came. He just...
He died alone.
I don't know what you saw.
But that wasn't your father.
- It couldn't have been.
- Yes, it was! It was!
Chuck, you told me what happened.
Last year, when you met.
How much he loved you, what a great dad
he turned out to be. All this time.
Chester...
A good father
would not do something like this.
It had to be. Look, Allegra,
I can feel it.
Okay? I can feel it. Like I was
right there at the crash site.
I can...
You said, "Quincy P. Runk loved his son
more than anything else."
Which means,
whatever you felt, or thought you saw,
it was a lie.
Allegra...
I hated him my whole life.
What if this is some kind of like...
Some kind of
messed up afterlife payback?
No! I don't believe in ghosts.
And neither do you.
Which is why we have to figure out
what's really going on.
[alarm ringing]
[stammers] He's back, isn't he?
If so, he's gonna
have to go through me first. Let's go.
- [Allegra] What's going on?
- [Frost] We're not sure yet.
We've got cold fires on multiple levels,
and it's spreading.
And they're all headed our way.
[alarm beeping]
If it's cold fire,
how come it's getting hotter in here?
His flames form in a sub-zero state,
but they still give off
high levels of kinetic energy.
Which means they can still
burn the hell out of us.
[crashing]
That was a router junction.
They're in the walls, too.
He's after me. This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
Chuck, you need to concentrate.
Okay? We're gonna
need your help to survive this.
No, I can't. The fire's already burning
through our structural supports.
Once they're done...
Every volatile resource
in S.T.A.R. Labs
will melt down
and contaminate Central City.
So, what do we do?
Chester... I know this is hard
right now,
but we need your help to stop this.
That means we need you
to initiate a search protocol.
Look for anything that could create
cold-catalyzed reactions.
We'll buy you as much time as we can.
Okay, I'm on it.
[breathing heavily]
Tracking muon-catalyzed
heat signatures, and...
Barry, the flames
are converging on the Speed Lab.
I don't know why.
But maybe there's some sort of
epicenter forming there, or something.
Let's do this.
[electricity crackling]
- Frost...
- I'm on it.
[Frost grunts]
- Our heat index is off the charts...
- [Cecile] Chester.
I just felt a massive wave of despair.
I told you, I can't do this.
He thinks he is being haunted,
by his dad, and that's the reason
all of this is happening.
[gasps heavily]
That's not the reason. Chester!
The despair that I'm sensing,
it's not just from you.
It's like I can feel the pain
of thousands of people, maybe more.
[screaming]
- What the hell is this?
- Cecile?
All right, listen to me. You guys
need to evacuate while you still can.
No, we're not leaving you behind.
- [exploding]
- [gasps]
It's here.
All that pain and sadness.
[inhales]
All that grief.
Dad?
Take my hand.
It's time to come home, Chester.
I'm so sorry I couldn't save you.
Chuck, that's not your dad.
It's true.
Chester, all of the sadness
that I'm feeling is...
It's coming from that thing.
Allegra's right. That's not your father.
Chester, we belong together.
No... no. Chester.
Everything that's inside of you,
is just moving
from you... into it.
It's... becoming a part of it.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
It's feeding on your grief.
Chester, you have to let it go.
I love you, son.
It's lying. No, no, that thing is lying!
It's lying to you, honey.
It wants you to stay trapped
inside of your sadness. Because it's...
Hungry! Chester, honey,
you have to let it go.
I can't. I can't.
Chuck, listen to me.
Think about
the last time you saw your dad.
And what you remember most about him.
That's what you have to hold on to.
Okay? Yeah,
'cause if your real dad was here,
he would be the first to say,
"Remember how much I love you."
Hold on to that, Chuck.
That's what matters.
Take my hand.
My dad.
He would never ask me
to turn my back on my life here.
I know he would love the life
that I've built here.
Yes.
No.
He'd freak...
if he saw my workshop.
And he'd love that I'm working
with an actual superhero,
helping him save the world every day.
No, my dad...
he'd be proud of his son.
And the man that I've become.
I said, "Take my hand."
No.
No, I'm gonna stay here.
For my friends, because they...
They're my real family.
And you're not my dad.
So, why don't you just go to hell!
[screaming]
Chester, the cold flames are gone.
What happened?
I sent him packing.
With a little help from my friends.
[Allegra chuckles]
[Joe] Chester, seems like
you had a pretty close call, huh?
You, too, Barr.
[Barry] Yeah, thankfully,
I was able to phase myself
and Frost long enough
for Chester to do the rest.
[Chester] Ah, it wasn't all me.
If it wasn't for Allegra and Cecile,
I'd be just another
burnt corpse right about now.
Hey, what about the other three victims?
Joe, did you find anything?
I did some digging.
Called in a few favors.
Uh, turns out, our first victim,
Stan Mullen,
recently lost
all his belongings to foreclosure.
Then, Donna Winters?
Her sister died last week.
Let me guess, our yoga vic
was suffering some loss, too.
Fiancé and childhood sweetheart
to cancer.
It's a grief pattern.
Which fits
with where I've been at, lately.
So, this new meta, whoever he is,
eats grief and sorrow to survive.
Yeah, that's not terrifying.
[Chester] It gets scarier.
We thought we were looking for
a meta serial killer.
Someone that was
controlling the black flames,
like the figure I saw in the fire.
But the fire created that.
And when I spoke to it, it heard me,
like it could understand or something.
[Cecile] Chester is right.
With all of that sorrow that I felt
coming out of that thing,
I also felt other emotions.
Determination, passion, desire.
It's almost like,
whatever that thing is,
it's got a mind of its own.
So, we're not looking
for a separate fire meta.
No. The will to seek out victims
to kill?
The need to satisfy its hunger
at all costs...
The flames have a survival instinct.
Which means, the flames
aren't being used by the killer.
They are the killer.
Because they're alive.
[footsteps approaching]
We're not interrupting, are we?
No, no, no, it's good.
Just trying to
wrap my head around all this.
You know, every member of this team
has dealt with grief.
Me, with my own mom, back in Houston.
- Nash, and Esperanza.
- [Cecile] And Barry.
All that he's dealt with,
and with both of his parents.
That's right. But I guess,
dealing with loss is just...
another thing that makes us human.
When we help each other deal with it...
It's what makes us family.
Yeah.
So, I have some filing I need to do...
Back at my office.
- Right now?
- [Cecile] Yep.
You guys stay. I'll see you tomorrow.
[both chuckle]
Hey, I know we have,
like, D&D plans for tonight.
But honestly, I just... I can't.
Yeah, I'll text Marco and the gang.
Maybe we can
pull an all-nighter this Saturday.
- I'd like that. A lot. [chuckles]
- Me, too.
And, Chuck...
You know I'll always be there for you,
- right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
And, for the record,
you're a very big part of my life, too.
- [Barry] How's Sue?
- [Iris West] A life-saver, as always.
And, it turns out that
the Dearbon Corporation
owns an entire city block
in downtown Coast City.
- Oh, she "rich" rich.
- Yeah, and you forget about it.
Until she puts all three of us
in a place like this, and you're like,
"Yeah, billionaire."
So, Tinya is there, too?
Uh, yeah, she's sleeping
in the suite next door.
She has no place else to go, Barry. I...
I really wanna help her.
Yeah, that's what I love about you.
You make a real difference
in people's lives,
with everything you do.
Yeah, you, too.
Speaking of, I was thinking
that with powers like hers,
she could be a hero, too.
Like The Streak?
I mean, why not? That worked out.
Yeah... Yeah.
- Babe, what is it?
- No, I'm...
I'm glad you decided
to stay in Coast City a little longer.
The black fires?
Yeah, it's just...
It's not safe here right now.
Um, okay, I mean,
is there anything that we can do?
No, it's okay. I mean,
we don't even know how to locate it,
let alone stop it,
If anything happened to you...
Yeah. No, I get it.
- Okay, well, I love you.
- I love you, too.
- [Iris West] Get some rest, okay?
- Yeah, you, too.
[whooshes]
You found out what's wrong with me.
And it ain't good news.