- Mother is better now, Mayor.
And thanks again.
I know family emergencies
are never convenient.
[zips]
But after some
personal reflection,
I realized
I have to be with her.
[suspenseful music]
Everything I am
started with her.
- You sure you
weren't followed?
- Yes.
- Good.
- You've changed
your appearance.
- The suit is necessary.
The properties inside of it
help me continue
my acclimation process
when I'm outside the
reflection modulation chamber.
Now...
It's time to get rid
of my husband.
We begin by dismantling
everything that protects him.
You know where to start.
- Success is assured.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[exciting music]
- Guys, shouldn't it be
all hands on deck
with Iris, Kamilla, and Singh
stuck in the Mirrorverse?
- Hey, you're just
as important.
- Uh, Ms. Caitlin?
Or Frost?
- Uh, they're going
to the Arctic, not Ozz-fest.
How are you so bad
at everything?
- Caity keeps our heavy coats
in the back closet.
- I'll check on it.
- Right.
That makes more sense.
You're so good
at this kind of stuff...
so mad at me.
- Little bit.
Mm.
- Nash, Allegra will come
around eventually.
You just have to be there
when she does.
Trust the process.
- Pretty wise for a popsicle.
- Thanks.
Got a Dib-ploma to prove it.
- [laughs]
- Ba-dum-bum.
- Uh...cool.
Can I borrow this?
- Sure.
- I'm really gonna miss you.
- Me too.
- Hmm?
[soft music]
- I mean, all...we all are.
- Aww.
There's hope for you yet.
- Enough.
Okay.
You stay frosty.
♪ ♪
[echolocation ringing]
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not.
And honey, it's okay.
I promise you
you can handle anything.
You just gotta remember.
She's your mom too.
- Of course I am.
[dramatic music]
Hi, Killer Frost.
- Uh...
it's just Frost now.
Hi.
- Okay, um.
[clears throat]
We're gonna leave
you two alone.
Give us a call when you get
settled in the north.
[whimpers]
- Give 'em hell.
- [sighs]
So...
I, um, I think I should run
a few tests before we leave.
Check your baseline
for any ribonucleic anomalies.
- Great.
- Eva's been missing
for over 24 hours.
Where are we
with facial recognition?
- Satellites have
turned up zilch.
- The Artificial Speed Force
isn't finished yet,
so I still can't do
my usual sweeps of the city.
- Right.
Uh, why are we meeting here?
- I have a backlog of cases.
I can't lose my CSI job
along with everything else.
A job...
[poignant music]
Eva said that she
had unfinished business.
Is there any way that
she meant that literally?
- Oh, if she wants
to get McCulloch back,
she does have to deal
with Black Hole.
- So find Black Hole,
find Eva.
- Mm-hmm.
- Any idea where to start?
- Actually, no.
- Maybe.
- Ralph.
- Where'd you get that?
- Sue gave it to me.
- She gave you that?
- She gave that to you?
- She gave that to me.
And it turns out
that Black Hole's logo
is embedded inside.
- Dude, there's serious UV
energy coming off that thing.
Can I?
Huh.
[activates, whirrs]
- Oh, yeah.
This is a Triangulation
Cartograph.
It's a treasure map.
- Allegra.
Aim it over this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
The center's at 42nd and Darby.
- Hang on.
42nd and Darby...
Holy heck.
- What?
- Well, it turns out
that is a ginormous warehouse
with five subterranean levels.
- Ralph and I
will check it out.
You two take comms.
- N...
[sighs]
- Let me just...excuse me.
♪ ♪
- [blowing]
Could be a long night.
I made us a couple of coffees.
- I hate coffee.
- No coffee.
- Barry:Guys, we're in.
- Nash:All right.
Be careful. Place like that
could have a guard or two.
- More like five.
- They were all stabbed.
- By a mirror-bayonet,
I'm guessing.
[whistles]
That is a lot of bad-guy stuff.
- It's Black Hole's
depository.
- Sue said that Carver
was blackmailing her parents.
This is bank statements,
investment records.
This must be everything
that Carver has on them.
I'm taking this.
- All right.
[liquid trickling]
It smells like gasoline
in here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Singh.
- I don't wanna hurt
anyone else.
- Tell that to those guards
you killed.
- They left me no choice.
I have to assure Eva's success.
- Just put down the flare gun.
Help us bring Carver
to justice.
- [chuckles]
Mother's not interested
in your brand of justice.
- Singh.
Singh!
This isn't you.
- You still don't get it,
do you?
[crash]
Carver was there that night.
[explodes, mirror whirring]
He let the mirror keep her.
He never tried to rescue her.
Instead, he sold her tech
to the highest bidder.
For weapons,
blackmail, or worse.
And that is why Carver
is a dead man.
[flames whooshing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Uh, not working.
[radio crackling]
- Guys?
- Nash:Allen, Dibny,
are you guys there?
- Barely.
What do we do now?
- The only thing we can.
Protect Carver.
♪ ♪
- And our guy knows
to destroy anything
that could tie me
to the warehouse?
- Yes, but there's
nothing left to destroy.
Everything we had
was incinerated.
- Replace the items.
Quickly and quietly.
Don't use The Three.
They can't know
they're off leash.
If someone is coming after me,
I'll need their protection.
Hello.
Officer Allen.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Please.
You're not here to slap me,
are you?
[laughs]
Captain West went
for the left side.
How is he, by the way?
- Look, there's no easy way
to say this, so...
Your wife wants to kill you.
But CCPD can't keep you safe.
- My wife is dead.
- Eva's been trapped
in another dimension
for the last six years.
Place called the Mirrorverse.
But you already knew that.
- If Eva did escape
that wretched place, I'd know.
This is about your wife,
isn't it?
[dramatic music]
I came across this footage
from my wife's office
a couple of weeks ago.
- You knew Iris was abducted?
- Your wife was a problem.
Her disappearance
was fortuitous.
- What happened to my wife?
- The same thing
that happened to my Eva.
She's gone.
They both are.
- No.
There has to be a way
to get her back.
- I used to think that too.
But if Iris
is still alive in there,
there's probably nothing
left of her to save.
I had the most brilliant minds
in the world study that...
Mirrorverse.
You know what they found?
It's incompatible
with the human brain.
That place warps the mind
until the person
is no longer recognizable.
Your Iris
is long gone.
I suggest you accept that
and move on.
♪ ♪
Oh, so one more thing.
How do you know
Eva's coming after me?
- Who else would've burnt down
your warehouse?
42nd and Darby, right?
- I'd never buy
on that side of town.
And I don't need protecting.
- Mm.
[chuckles]
- You give Captain West
my best.
- Without the satellites,
finding Chief Singh
feels impossible.
- I know.
- We'll have to go find him
ourselves.
- [sighs]
Every time I interact
with this place,
the neural dissonance
gets worse.
And what if Eva comes back?
Then what?
Look.
Things in this place
may be backwards,
but everything works.
We just...we just
have to figure out how.
[neural dissonance ringing]
[exclaiming]
Did you see the map
of the city?
- You just said looking
at those was too dangerous.
- No, I didn't mean to,
but I was thinking
about finding David,
and the map came into view.
There...there was thermal energy
coming from a specific place.
I'm not sure where,
but that has to be David.
There was like a...a radius,
almost like a beacon.
I...I feel like
if I could just focus,
I could...I can
find his location.
- No, Iris.
Come on, look at you!
- No, I'm acclimating
to this place, Kamilla.
That's why I can see the map
and you can't.
I can find David.
[dramatic music]
[knocking]
- Mrs. Dearbon.
- Hi.
- Mr. Dearbon, so great
to see you again.
I have fantastic news.
So it turns out that s...
- Oh.
So you are the person
that my parents
employed to find me.
It's so good to meet you.
[chuckles]
- [chuckles]
Hi.
- And please forgive me.
I...I never meant
to cause a stir.
I read "Eat, Pray, Love,"
and I took the pray part just
a little bit too seriously.
- [chuckles angrily]
- Our Susie joined
a mindfulness retreat in India.
- I meant to stay for a month
and then lost track
of the weeks, months.
Oh, well.
Happens, right?
- Mr. Dibny,
while we're delighted
to have our Susie back,
we realize how much
trouble you went to.
[laughs]
Do you have a pen?
- Uh...
Oh, heck.
Wouldn't you know?
I'm fresh out.
Let me just check
that hallway closet.
Ms. Dearbon, could you
help me look for a pen?
- Of course.
- We'll be right back.
You need a legal pad
or anything?
- Why would you call
my parents?
- So that diamond that
you gave me, it turns out
that it has a map
for Black Hole's stash house.
I did some recon.
- Ohh!
I thought breaking and entering
was a line Elongated Man
didn't cross.
- Will you...
inside voices please.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Look.
Carver had files with your
parents names on them.
Those files
contain the evidence
he was using to extort them.
- What do you mean "had"?
- Well...
[laughs]
Things got toasty,
and Carver's blackmail arsenal
got cooked.
- You torched the place?
- No.
I...no.
Okay.
How do I say this?
There's a Mirrorverse
dimension.
There's these pod people
running around.
They're claiming
innocent lives.
It's very
"Invasion of the Body S-"
You know what?
Why don't we just forget
about that part?
The point is
your parents are safe.
- Yeah.
I already knew that.
- Well, you're welcome.
It was really no...
Wait.
What?
- Yeah, Carver called
last week.
Said he had a change of heart.
- Guys like Carver
don't have hearts to change.
- Agreed.
But my parents are safe,
and I can finally go home.
- I don't understand.
If we agreed...
- Enough, slick.
You really wanna help me?
Leave us in peace.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[speaking foreign language]
- Did he say who wants
his head on a pike now?
[mirror shimmering]
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[photon rifle
activates, whirrs]
- Who's there?
- Hello, Kimiyo.
Shall we do this
the easy way...
Or the hard way?
[photon rifle fires]
[glass shimmers]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Sunshine?
♪ ♪
Hoshi?
Ultraviolet?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I'm glad Carver
turned you down.
After what he did
to my cousin, Joe, Iris,
he deserves what he gets.
- He doesn't deserve to die.
What if he's telling the truth
about the Mirrorverse
affecting minds?
- Or he's lying.
He's not exactly
the paragon of truth.
- I don't think he's lying.
I think it could be
neural dissonance.
I came across this Earth
on my travels
where any visitor to that
Earth immediately suffers
a traumatic
psychological state.
Neural dissonance.
This could be that.
- I'm glad someone believes me.
I need your help
after all, Allen.
Federal Protection.
The full Joe West treatment.
- What happened
to your killer minions?
- Eva got to them first,
didn't she?
- You gonna help me or not?
- [scoffs]
- Look, get me into protection,
and Joe can get out of it.
One call from me
and he's sleeping
in his own bed tonight.
- [scoffs]
You're a real piece of work.
You know that?
- That sounded
like a yes to me.
[tablet beeps]
- Huh, that's interesting.
The stoichiometric ratio
is manifesting
in a way that's abnormal.
[sighs]
It'd be so much easier
if Caitlin were here
to help analyze.
- I could help.
- Oh, I'm...I'm sorry.
I just...I just meant
that I could use
an expert in meta-DNA.
[sighs]
I forgot.
- I figured.
Probably because
every time you look at me,
you just see Thomas
and the monster he became.
- You're not a monster.
[emotional music]
♪ ♪
You protected Caitlin
from her father and then some,
which is a hell of a lot more
than I ever did.
- You know, to be honest,
I always kind of felt
like a third wheel.
- I'm sorry you felt that way.
No.
It must have been horrible.
Then again, I've...
made so many mistakes
in my life.
Maybe...maybe I'm the one
who needs fixing.
- You're a brilliant scientist
who runs the most
successful lab on the planet.
I don't think you need fixing.
'Cause from where I'm standing,
you're a pretty awesome
human being.
One I'd like to get
to know a lot better.
- I'd like that too.
♪ ♪
- What is taking so long?
- Uh, federal agents
will be here any minute
to take you into custody.
[elevator dings]
[dramatic music]
- Officer.
Mr. Carver.
When your paperwork
came across my desk,
I thought a VIP
such as yourself
shouldn't have to ride
in a two-bit government van.
So I'm here to escort you
personally into custody.
Allen, a word?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Let me walk out of here
with Carver,
and Mother will give you Iris.
- [scoffs]
- Eva is not interesting
in a fight with you
or with your friends.
- You knew we were
in that warehouse
when you set it on fire.
That feels like a fight to me.
- Let me have him, Barry.
He's a bad man.
Bring Iris home.
Get your life back.
- Are we doing this or what?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- On my six!
- What the hell?
[flash]
- Will someone please tell me
what the hell is going on?
- I saved you.
That's what's going on.
- Nash.
- What?
♪ ♪
- The Barry Allen I know
would never, never
have considered that deal.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[mirror crackling]
- I knew Eva was ambitious,
but Mirror Duplicates.
- Eva's more powerful
than you thought.
- I don't get it.
Why doesn't she just come
after you herself?
- Well, Eva's still
technically missing,
so she can't be seen in public.
- That's why she took Singh.
The chief of police
could get close to you.
- [sighs]
Fortunately, Mr. Wells
teleported us to safety.
- You're welcome.
- What is that device?
And how much
do you want for it?
- It's not for sale, dirtbag.
- [laughs]
Oh, please.
Everyone has a price.
- Hey, listen.
We just saved your keister.
So why don't you
put a sock in it
till we can figure out
what to do with you?
- So guess we're stuck
with our new guest for a while.
- It's only a matter of time
before Eva shows up here.
- Right.
Any mirrored surface
inside S.T.A.R. labs
is a door for her
to walk through.
- McCulloch security system
can protect us.
I have a panic room
Eva doesn't know about.
- No offense, but extra guards
and a locked den
aren't gonna help us out here.
- I have a biogenic
ionization field
that can be activated
around the entire facility.
Anything breaking in would
be atomized in a second.
We just have to get there.
- We could take
the sewer system.
Pop over underneath R and D?
I break into things.
- Mm.
No time like the present?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Allen.
I wanna ask you a question.
You knew that Carver
was in mortal danger, right,
as soon as Mirror-Singh
stepped off that elevator.
Why didn't you get him
out of there?
- I couldn't exactly run him
out of there as Barry Allen.
- Or he offered you a deal.
That's the other thing.
I have all these Wells
in my head, and they all...
they're all screaming
the same thing,
that the Barry Allen they knew
would never have hesitated.
You did.
You were considering
the deal.
You were considering trading
Carver's life to save Iris.
- It's more complicated
than that.
- It's more complicated...
- Yeah.
- Is it complicated
like in the way you almost
killed Eobard Thawne
and me along with him?
- No. That was different.
- How is that different?
- Iris is my wife.
I have to save her.
How do you not understand that?
- I do.
But what do you think
Iris will say
when you tell her
you traded another
person's life to save hers?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[door mechanically unlocking]
[lights whooshing]
- A.R.G.U.S. will be here in an
hour to take you into custody.
[tense music]
Wait, this isn't safe.
- Relax.
After I saw what happened
to your wife,
I had it coated
with protective nanites.
- I thought Palmer Tech
and McCulloch were rivals.
- [scoffs]
Let's just say what Palmer Tech
doesn't know won't hurt them.
[beeps]
And this is my panic room.
Concrete walls
and not a mirror in sight.
Even if my outer field fails,
Eva can't get in here.
- Well, once
the building's clear,
you can engage your ion field.
[keys clacking]
- Then tell your people
to speed up the evacuation.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
- You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
- Allegra, here.
Take this.
Just in case.
All right?
Any trouble,
you should blast it
with one of your UV Rays.
All right?
Provide a welcome distraction.
- When are you
gonna stop trying?
- Never.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What the hell?
[electronic whirring]
[scoffs]
I knew you were lying.
- You really can't take a hint.
- You're not here
to rob the place.
And Carver didn't have a change
of heart on your parents.
You...you offered to take
their place in Black Hole.
- Carver agrees.
I'm more valuable
than my parents.
- [inhales deeply]
Sue, you...
you don't have to do this.
- Yes, I do.
I've been trying to collect
leverage on Carver
for over a year.
He's untouchable.
- Untouchable unless
you have one of those
handy-dandy Black Hole pins.
You joined Black Hole
to get close to Carver.
Because you're gonna kill him.
That's why you're here,
isn't it?
- Carver's never gonna
let my parents go.
- Sue, damn it...
- It's the only way it ends.
- You gotta listen to me.
There...there is always
another way.
Do you understand what happens
if you kill Carver?
Every time you look
in the mirror,
you won't recognize
the person looking back.
You'll lose yourself.
- Why do you care?
- Because I believe in you!
And I know there's
still good in you.
I can see it.
- I'm sorry about this, slick.
[sprays breath spray]
- [sniffing erratically]
Oh, come on.
[thuds]
- Allegra:All clear down here.
Ready for the force field
when you are.
[computer beeps, activates]
- The ion field's
up and running.
- Now all that's left to do
is sit and wait.
Cheers.
- [coughing]
[lights click off,
power shuts down]
[dramatic music]
- [sighs]
That's not good.
[computer beeping]
- Guys, the force field
isn't working anymore.
Can we find out what happened
to the power source?
- We know what happened.
♪ ♪
- Carver's angels invited
themselves to the party.
[both speaking Spanish]
- Something Carver never did.
- We're no longer
under his thumb.
Neither is Eva.
- Whatever she is paying you,
I will double it.
- This isn't about a paycheck.
- It's about payback.
[photon rifle activates]
- Eva's coming for you, Carver.
And we're gonna make sure
no one gets in her way.
♪ ♪
[all grunting]
[photon rifle blasting,
lights spark]
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Nice family reunion!
[fighting playing
over TV monitor]
- Eva's gonna be here
any minute.
We have to get
your ion field back up.
Is there an alternate
power source?
- The sub-basement.
There's remote access
to a secondary generator.
- Guys, hold them off
as long as you can.
I'm gonna get
the power back on.
- You do that.
I know how to handle traitors.
[phone beeping]
[photon rifle blasting,
lights sparking]
[all grunting]
- Drop your weapons!
♪ ♪
- Singh.
You don't wanna do this.
This isn't your will.
- Eva's will is my will.
♪ ♪
[groans]
[glass shattering]
[laser canon blasts]
- [thuds]
♪ ♪
- Success is assured.
[dynamic music]
[all grunting]
♪ ♪
[men screaming]
[photon rifle blasting,
lights sparking]
[all grunting, screaming]
♪ ♪
- I thought Sunshine
was solar-powered!
- How the frak
is she frying people at night?
- Those bracelets
aren't fashion.
They're fuel.
They're solar energy
battery packs.
- Well, how do we get them off?
- We just gotta increase
the internal temperature,
overload the cells.
Allegra, if you...
- Already on it.
- She's good.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
I'm making it up as I go.
[photon rifle blasting]
[photon rifle blasts]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[both speaking Spanish]
[photon rifle blasting,
lights sparking]
[all grunting]
- Fine.
Do it.
You think you're the only one
that feels that way?
The only one that feels alone?
Get in line!
[triumphant music]
- [grunts]
- Okay.
Remember when I told you
if things go sideways,
zap the stone?
- Yeah.
- I'd zap the stone.
[UV light beam blasts]
- [distorted screaming]
- [whimpering]
- [grunts]
[phone rifle whirring]
[grunting]
- You came back.
- Couldn't let you
have all the fun.
- Fun must mean something
entirely different
when you're rich.
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[fighting playing
over TV monitor]
[TV shuts off]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Honey...
I'm home.
[both grunting]
- Guess somebody forgot
to spike the punch.
- [exhales]
[mirror shimmers]
[tense music]
[glass shatters]
- Oh!
Let's talk about this.
[laser cannon
activates, whirrs]
- [chuckles]
About what?
How you weaponized
my technology?
Extorted charitable donors?
Kidnapped and blackmailed
innocent meta-humans
like Kimiyo,
Esperanza, and Millie?
This is me talking.
- I did what I had to do.
[laser cannon deactivates]
- [sighs]
Then I'll do what I have to do.
Good-bye, Joseph.
[mirrors shimmer]
- No, Eva!
Wait!
- [grunts]
- [yelps]
- No!
What don't you understand?
He's not worth saving!
- [strained]
Maybe...
But it's not your decision.
- Oh, yes, it is.
- [screams]
- [coughs]
- My husband...
let me rot in that world
for years!
He does not get to live
in this one.
- [grunting]
You're not my wife.
[choking]
My wife died
in the particle
accelerator explosion.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Well...
I've never felt more alive.
- You're not...
even...
human.
- No.
No.
- I'm sorry
you had to see that.
- [groans]
Ahh!
God!
- [labored breathing]
- What are you doing here?
- I'm making this up as I go.
- Right.
- Flash.
Barry.
You and I are not enemies.
We never have been.
- [groans]
You just killed him
in cold blood.
- Your wife
set out to catch a bad man.
She couldn't.
But together, we could.
We're on the same side.
- No.
- Just remember that.
- All right, on three,
everybody go crazy.
- Got it.
- That seems like bad advice.
- Song title.
No, I like it.
It'll be good.
All right.
One, two...
- Eva:Stand down.
Joseph is dead.
- Well...
I didn't see that coming.
- You're gonna let us go?
- Of course.
I've achieved my goal
for today.
- We'll never stop
coming after you.
[labored breathing]
- You'll fail.
This building, this company...
It's all mine.
- [groans]
- And you and your little
friends are trespassing, so...
run along now, Barry,
before I have to call
the police.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Mrs. McCulloch, where have
you been all this time?
- Well,
over the past six years,
I have been held hostage
by an international
crime syndicate.
Forced to watch
as they stole my technology
and used it to create
deadly weapons.
[camera shutter clicking]
- How did you escape?
- My husband, Joseph.
He worked tirelessly
to try to find me.
And, um,
he succeeded...
only to be murdered moments
after we were reunited.
[camera shutter clicking]
Words cannot express my sorrow.
But know that I am working
with the CCPD
to try to find
my husband's murderer.
And as for
McCulloch Technologies,
I will be resuming
my position as CEO,
effective immediately.
It's what Joseph
would have wanted.
Thank you.
[knocking]
- Ralph: Going somewhere?
- Carver's dead,
which means my parents
are finally free.
And so am I.
I'm going home.
- Sue, I'm not sure you can.
[intriguing music]
Eva framed you...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
For Carver's murder.
- Barry, we've been through
stuff like this before.
Don't worry.
You're gonna find
a way to stop Eva
and get Iris back.
- I can't even
be frustrated without...
[sighs]
Without losing more of it.
- Maybe instead of focusing
on what you've lost,
you should try remembering
what you'll never lose.
The reason you've beat
Zoom, Godspeed, Thawne?
It's because speed
isn't what drives you.
It's love.
That's your true force,
and there is nothing
artificial about that.
So as long as you
stay true to yourself,
you will always find a way
to beat the bad guys.
And gals.
[emotional music]
- I'm gonna miss you.
- I'll be back
before you know it.
[door opens]
- All set?
Car's downstairs.
I promise I'll get these two
back to you and your team
as soon as possible.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Hey, um...
Frost can hear me, too, right?
- As long as she's awake.
- Frost:I'm awake.
Really.
- Go ahead.
- Just get better.
And hurry back.
We still have a whitewater
rafting trip to take.
- I'm holding you to that.
- She says she can't wait.
♪ ♪
Tell the team
I miss them already?
- I will.
♪ ♪
- Well, well.
This is a little quieter.
- Yeah.
- Hey, look.
I know that I'm...
not your favorite person,
but if ever you need anything,
if you ever need my coffee.
What...what happened
to, "I don't like coffee"?
- [laughing]
Okay.
- Thanks.
- For what?
- For this.
- Of course.
- What did it do to her?
My cousin?
- It made her relive
her worst memory.
You know what?
You hang on to it.
Just in case you need it again.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
- Iris and the others,
they're still Eva's prisoners.
- We're gonna get them back.
And remember, we still have
one thing that Eva doesn't.
Hope.
- We also have reinforcements.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Oh.
- Joe.
♪ ♪
How are you here?
- Well, it turns out that
when the guy that's trying
to kill you kicks the bucket,
they lift
the protection detail.
- That makes sense.
- Nash.
- Hey, man.
Yeah.
- Hey.
- And just in time.
Team needs you now
more than ever.
- Well, let's go save
some people we love.
♪ ♪
- You have been at this
for hours.
- Barry wouldn't give up.
And the woman that he married
wouldn't either.
[computer beeping]
I found him!
David's at
Central City Hospital.
I can't believe
I just did that.
- Holy frak.
Iris, you can
control this place.
[mirrors shimmering]
[neural dissonance whirring]
Iris?
Iris, stay with me!
- [screaming]
- Iris!
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.