- Previously
on "Crisis on Earth-X"...
- To Barry and Iris.
all: To Barry and Iris.
- Are you asking me
to marry you?
- I am.
- Just forget about it.
- Felicity.
- I don't want to marry you!
- I just called off
my engagement.
- To making things go away.
- Does anyone have just cause
why these two should not
be married?
- Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
- Nazis?
- Why would Nazis want
to crash my wedding?
- There's a 53rd earth
called Earth-X.
Basically our Earth
with one difference.
The Nazis won the war.
- I call it
"Calm After the Firestorm."
- No powers for either of us?
- The other archer
and flying woman
are Oliver and Kara
of Earth-X,
and Thawne is working
with them.
- The general is dying.
- All we need is a new heart.
And we found
the perfect donor.
- I don't think
this is our Earth.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[dogs barking]
[man yelling indistinctly]
- [crying softly]
- Eyes front!
- So this crap-hole's Earth-X.
- Wells was right.
- He usually is.
- It's hard to believe a place
like this actually exists
on any Earth.
- I wish I shared
your sentiment,
but in all my travels
to distant times,
one thing which sadly remains
constant is men's ability
to feel hatred for other men.
- Keep moving.
Move!
Man over PA:All prisoners,
stay away from the gate.
- Stars and triangles...
- Badges used to identify
purported crimes these people
have "committed"
to land in here.
- What's the pink triangle for?
What did you do?
- I loved the wrong person.
♪ ♪
- We got to get out
of these things.
Transmute us out.
- With pleasure.
- I can't vibrate
through them either.
- Power-dampening collars.
- Well, why are we
wearing them, then?
- Doesn't matter.
There's too many guards
here anyways.
- They're gonna kill
my sister.
- Look, we're not gonna
let that happen,
Alex, I promise you.
- We're gonna get back
to our Earth before then.
- How? We don't even know
how we got here.
- No, we don't.
We're gonna figure it out.
Then we're gonna find a way
to get out of this place,
and we're gonna get back
to the people we love.
- I hope everyone else is okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[ball bouncing]
- Oh!
- Rip Van Ramon awakens.
- This doesn't look like
a wedding.
- [muted yelling]
- You missed quite a bit,
Cisco.
- All you need to know
is that you are locked
in one of your fabulous
anti-meta-human cells
with the rest of us.
We can't escape.
- Of course we can't.
That's what I designed
them for, genius.
- Good command of the obvious.
- Boys.
- Is that a ball?
- Why? Is it bothering you?
- Yes.
God. Hey!
[ball thumping on wall]
- Are they gonna do that
the whole time we're in here?
Cisco: Ow!
- Probably.
- It hurts! Cut it out!
- Cut what out?
- [sighs] S.T.A.R. Labs.
It feels like old times,
doesn't it?
You know, I, uh...
I built this place...
with my own hands
and called it home
for 15 years,
and do you know what?
I hated every minute of it.
- Where are my friends?
- Your friends,
they're on Earth-X.
I wouldn't worry about your
friends too much because...
they're not going
to be alive much longer.
- [grunts]
- [chuckles] Oh, honey.
It's because
of the red sunlight.
And trust me,
it'll make you weaker
than you can possibly imagine.
- [panting]
- [breathes unevenly]
- You did all this just...
just to get me?
Do you know how many
innocent people you killed?
- Their lives to save mine?
Well, they should feel honored.
- [grunting]
- [laughs menacingly]
It's a strange sensation,
isn't it...
feeling vulnerable?
- And it's just
gonna get worse
because this red sunlight,
it's softening you up
until pretty soon,
I'm gonna crack you open
like a walnut.
Then I'm gonna take
your healthy heart.
I'm gonna put it in her.
Which means we should
probably get you going.
- Good.
That'll give me time
to talk to...
myself.
[suspenseful music]
- [panting] Did you hear that?
Everyone else is on Earth-X.
- And Kara only has a few hours
before they go full Mengele
on her.
- We gotta stop them.
- Got any ideas?
- I don't know.
Give me some time to think.
- Iris, I'm all for girl power
and everything,
but how are you and I gonna
stop the meaner, Nazi version
of my whatever he is right now
and...
[whispering]
People with superpowers?
- We don't have to.
We just need to get
to the pipeline and get Cisco.
He could turn off
all the power to the building
and breach us out of here.
- Do you know how to get
to the pipeline from here?
- [breathes deeply]
I think so.
- Lead the way, McClane.
Guard: Move!
[alarms ringing]
[whistles blowing]
Move!
- I don't like
the looks of this.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
- Keep moving!
- What are we doing?
- It's roundup time.
- Roundup for what?
- Move!
- In line, now.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- So these are...
the heroes.
- Yes, Sturmbannfuehrer.
[woman vocalizing eerily]
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
Blonde hair...
blue eyes...
this is Nordic perfection.
Why would you align yourself
with the unpure?
- Because I like men
and I like women.
- [huffs]
You know, I had a daughter
who looked just like you,
with similar compulsions.
♪ ♪
And I expunged thatfilth
from my family line forever.
Bring them all.
And him!
- Move! Now!
[guns cocking]
Go!
[whistle blows]
- Not to be an alarmist, but if
we don't have an escape plan,
I suggest we get one
immediately.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[device whines]
[electricity crackling]
[all groaning]
- Up!
♪ ♪
Go.
Turn around.
I know you are not him,
but I cannot stomach
the sight regardless.
Ready!
- I'm sorry, Kara.
- Aim!
[guns cocking]
[blaster fires]
- I hate "fire."
all: Snart?
- About time!
- Kill them all!
[gunfire]
- Take cover!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[gunfire]
- Hey, you're cutting it close.
- I thought that was
great timing.
I really enjoyed the pun.
- So you're Leonard Snart's
doppelganger.
- No, I'm Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Leo.
That is a fantastic outfit.
Did you make that?
- Leo.
- Right.
Time to make you shine, buddy.
- Uh, you, uh...
you might want
to close your eyes.
- Why?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Well, I believe he just
answered your question.
♪ ♪
- Come on, let's go.
- Where are we going?
- To our base.
- Your base?
- And...and who are you?
- I was thinking exactly
the same thing about you all.
[guards shouting]
- You might have to tell us
on the way.
[gunfire]
- [grunts]
- You're looking more human.
Scared, helpless, pathetic...
inferior.
- We're not
that different from them.
- Oh, please. We're everything
they want to be:
blonde, white.
Aryan perfection.
- I'm not like you.
I don't think I'm better
than everyone else.
- You should.
You are.
You're a god to them.
You could have been living
like one.
- [chuckles softly]
Like you?
- Yes, like me.
They want someone to bow to,
to worship, to lead.
- What you're doing
is not leading.
It's ruling.
- Yes, it is.
They're like ants, Kara.
- They shouldn't fear us
for what we can do.
They should rely on us
when they need us.
- Oh, spare me
the Good Samaritan crap.
- I'm not gonna
take advantage of anyone
just because I can.
- The world isn't made better
by protecting the weak.
It's made better
by getting rid of them.
You really are pathetic.
You know, I saw you
at the wedding.
By yourself.
Poor, lonely little Kara.
Can't even find a date
to a wedding. [laughs]
- You don't know
what you're talking about.
- It's written all over
that pouty little face
of yours.
You spend so much time
on your planet
taking care of everyone
but yourself.
No wonder you seem
so utterly miserable.
- It's not going to work.
You're not gonna get
what you want.
- Really?
Why do you care
if I take your heart?
You're not using it.
- At least I have one.
- We're almost ready.
- [panting]
Clear.
- I know bad guys
have inopportune timing,
but this is, like,
the worst timing ever.
- Yeah, tell me about it,
sister.
Barry and I were just about
to get married.
- At least you guys left
on good terms.
The last thing I said
to Oliver was, "I don't want
to marry you," and now
he's stuck in Nazi world.
I mean, what if we never
see them again?
[gunfire]
- Stop!
Hands in the air!
[dramatic music]
[guards scream]
- [groans]
- That was extremely badass.
- Same to you.
Cisco.
Felicity:Cisco?
- Hey!
Guys, we're trapped in here!
- We're gonna get you of here!
[pounding]
- Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
- What?
- I can't open the blast door.
- You mean they're trapped?
I'll send an SOS
to the Legends.
- How long will it take
for them to get it?
- Depends where they are
in time.
- We can't wait that long.
[computer beeping]
It's up to us to save Kara.
[thunder rumbling]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I guess we're in Earth-X's
Star City.
- I have to say,
that's one hell of a story.
You're a speedster.
- Yeah.
- Okay, you two
turn into the burning man.
- Yup.
- And you're the good
doppelganger of the Fuehrer.
- "Good" might be
an oversimplification.
- You still haven't told us
which Earth you're from.
Clearly, it's not this one.
- We're from Earth-1.
- Earth-1? Well...
golly.
- Am I missing something here?
- I'm from Earth-1 too.
- If you're from our Earth,
then you know how we got here,
don't you?
- Yeah, I have
a pretty good idea.
I think you guys...
came through this.
- A temporal gateway?
- Same physics as a breach,
just more stable and larger.
- Yeah, much larger.
- So we have a way to get back.
- So where is this thing?
- It's actually
not too far from here.
- 22.3 kilometers,
to be exact.
- Well, we'd drive there.
- Good.
- So take us to it.
- Can't do that.
- Why?
- Because the gateway's
in a facility guarded
by a not-so-small army
of Nazis.
- Yeah, well,
we've faced worse, so...
- Look, it's our only way home.
We're going through it.
- Nobody's going through
anything.
Because we're blowing it
the hell up.
♪ ♪
- Winn?
- Please,
Freedom Fighter General Schott.
- General Schott?
- Yeah, and who are you?
- New friends from Earth-1.
- They're on our side.
- Except for the part
where you guys
want to blow up
our only way home.
- We don't exactly want to.
- Everyone we care about
is on the other side
of that gateway,
imprisoned by Nazis.
- The Nazis that want
to cut open my sister.
We have to get back.
- Eliminate that facility,
and you eliminate
our only chance
of saving our friends
from your enemies.
- I'm sorry,
but we've been waiting
for an opportunity
like this for years.
We cannot wait any longer.
This is our only chance
to separate the Fuehrer
from his army.
We are trying
to turn this war around.
- You are gonna leave
our Earth at the mercy
of the three psychopaths
who have ravaged yours.
- Wait, why does
this man look exactly
like the Fuehrer
I am trying to kill?
- Look, fingerless gloves,
all we are asking
is for a little bit of time.
Let us get into the facility
and through that gateway.
- The gateway is guarded
by 30 Panzer XIIs,
50 Sturmtigers,
and 100 Schutzstaffel officers.
Not the best odds, maybe.
- I'll take them.
- No, you will not.
We are blowing up
that gateway right now.
Final order.
- Sorry he's a little rough
around the edges.
But he is the general,
and he's issued his commands.
- Hey, hey, hey.
You won't change his mind.
No one does.
- Look, on my Earth,
he and I are like family.
And he would do anything
to help my sister.
- Ray, let her try.
- You don't seem to know
how to take an order.
- That's because
I'm used to giving them.
You can't do this, Winn.
- General Schott.
Look, I don't know where
the hell you think you are,
but this planet has been
at war for generations.
We are tired.
There are men dying
for the same causes
their grandfathers did.
[scoffs]
- We're not asking you
to surrender.
Hey, just...just let us
get back home
before you destroy
that thing.
I-I'm just asking
for a little time.
- Time is what
I can't give you.
They have a weapon...
a doomsday weapon
powerful enough
to affect other worlds.
It has to be eliminated.
- Winn.
Please.
- [sighs]
- The Fuehrer on your Earth,
the people that you hate,
they're going to kill
my sister
if you don't let me
get back to save her.
On my Earth, my sister
is your closest friend.
She's saved you
countless times.
You would do anything
to help her.
to help each other,
no matter the risk,
without question.
So all I'm asking for
is a chance.
Please.
- I am sorry
about your sister
and about your Earth.
I truly am.
But today I have the chance
to protect my people,
my Earth.
My decision stands.
- Winn.
- Jefferson?
- Uh, Grey, I'm busy, man.
- Yes, I can see that,
but I was hoping
you might take a moment away
from your ruminations
on dystopian alternative history
to accept my apology.
I may be a learned man,
but I am not always
an astute one.
I think I was just so thrilled
with the reality
of my imminent departure
that I neglected
to consider your feelings.
- Look, man, I'm not trying to
take you away from your family
or nothing...
- You are my family.
Long before I unexpectedly
found myself with a daughter,
I found myself unexpectedly
with a son.
- Yeah, I know. I ju...
- You know.
You know, do you?
Look around you.
We're standing in one of the...
darkest places imaginable.
Yet somehow I'm optimistic.
Do you know why?
- 'Cause you're
a crazy old man.
- Yes. No!
- [laughs]
- Because I'm standing here
with you.
You are a better son than
I could have ever hoped for.
And no length
of time or distance
will ever change that.
- A'ight. Apology accepted.
Come here. [chuckles]
- What are you doing?
- Looking for a gun...
or knife...anything.
Okay, I don't care
how many Sturmtigers
they have out there.
I'm gonna go save Kara,
with or without the help
of these people.
- No, you're not.
- I'm a government agent
certified in over 30
military weapons.
- And you're impressive,
I'll give you that.
But you still
can't fight your way
through an army of Nazis
alone and scared.
- I'm not scared.
- No, not for you.
For your sister.
- I should've done more.
I mean, if I hadn't gotten
so...distracted.
- Well, sorry to be
a distraction.
- You don't understand.
I can't lose her.
- I understand
more than you think.
- [sighs]
- I lost my sister.
The anger and guilt
that I felt
for not being able
to save her
took me down a dark path.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
- How could you?
I mean, the only thing
we know about each other is...
what we look like
with clothes off.
Beautiful, by the way.
You also don't know
that I protect my team,
and you, Danvers,
you're on my team.
And I promise you,
we're not gonna let
what happened to my sister
happen to yours.
- I'm sorry.
I just want to...
I want to save Kara,
and I want to get back
to Maggie.
- Maggie is?
- Complicated.
- Yeah. I had a Maggie too.
And I think about
going back to her...
all the time.
Look, Alex.
You seem like
a pretty thoughtful person.
And if you thought
it wasn't gonna work out
and had to end it,
I'm sure that reason was valid.
Trust your instincts.
- Ray, please,
let's talk to him.
- Look, you said
to let Alex try.
I let her try.
She didn't succeed.
- So that's that?
We just let these poor
strangely dressed individuals
lose their one way home?
- Look, it's what Winn ordered,
and I am not in the habit of
defying generals on any Earth.
- And what about your family
back on Earth-1?
- What about them?
- You'd be giving up any chance
of ever seeing them again.
- Leo...
why are you pushing this?
- Pardon?
- We have fought
and bled and sacrificed
for this war.
And then these strangers
show up
and you're willing to throw
everything away for them?
The fate of the world
is at stake.
- So are the lives
of their loved ones.
- Come on.
- Tease me all you want
for being sentimental.
These heroes
would risk everything
for the people they love,
just like I would...
for you.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- [chuckles softly]
You know I can't say no
when you look at me like that.
- That is why
I look at you like that.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- We talked to the general,
and after a lot of arguing,
he agreed, so...
- We're gonna help you out.
♪ ♪
- Now, you referenced
100 guards.
I assume most of them
are around the perimeter?
- Correct.
- All right.
We fight through them
outside.
We access the main corridor.
What is security like
inside the hangar?
- I'll do some recon.
So the entire facility
has meta-human dampeners.
- Okay, we can't take
that hangar with no powers, man.
- These satellites indicate
a control room off the hangar.
That must be where
the dampener is.
- Okay, well,
we definitely can't take
the main control room
with no powers.
It's not like we blend in here.
- [exhales]
[exciting music]
I think I know how to get in.
- I'm allowing this mission
against my better judgment.
You have one hour.
- [exhales] I appreciate it.
We all do.
- Yeah, I know.
I know what you're thinking.
- If you don't make it
through the gateway,
I am not giving you more time.
I will blow that place
to kingdom come.
- Red light saturation...
is complete.
- [groans]
- She's cooked.
- And you will wake up
stronger than you've ever been.
- I love you.
- [whispering] I love you.
- Unfortunately, Miss Danvers,
we need you awake
for this procedure.
- My...my cousin...
he'll find you.
- Your cousin.
Really?
Fun tidbit.
I fought your cousin once.
In the future.
He is fast.
I'm faster.
[saw whirring loudly]
♪ ♪
- They're starting the surgery.
- I'm working on it, and...
[saw continues whirring]
[electricity powers down]
[alarms blaring]
- Just have backup power,
and it's not enough.
- Well, everyone in the building
has been accounted for.
Where might people be hiding?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[women grunt]
- Take that you, Nazi mother...
- Whoo!
Hey, hey, hey.
Come with me
if you want to live.
- Get me to the sun.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
- I got her, I got her.
- Okay.
- We gotta go.
[elevator whirs]
[electricity zapping]
- I don't believe Mr. Thawne
is done with you yet.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Your papers, Sturmmann.
- We don't have papers.
This is a special visit.
- Your papers. Now.
- Suit yourself, but, uh,
I think you better
talk to our boss.
- As you were.
- Mein gott.
My apologies, sir.
Let them through!
[gate buzzes]
- Let them through!
- Thank you,mein Fuehrer.
♪ ♪
all: Hail, Fuehrer.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
Mein Fuehrer, we were...
we were not expecting you.
- Nor was I anticipating
being back so soon.
Thanks to your incompetence,
the Earth-1 doppelgangers...
[raising voice]
My doppelganger...
[softly]
Escaped his execution.
- Yes, he did.
- And?
- We are exhausting
every possible means
to locate them.
- Good.
- Would you like us to delay
deployment until we do so?
- Deployment?
- She is inbound and ready.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Oliver:The doomsday device.
- The Wellenreiter
is fully operational
and at the ready,mein Fuehrer.
Shall we send her through?
- As scheduled.
- Begin!
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- The Wellenreiter
is on its way.
Hail, victory!
all: Hail, victory!
- Hail, victory.
♪ ♪
- Report.
- Good news.
The Wellenreiter's made
the transition to this Earth.
- Kara is all that matters.
- That red sunlight
we're flooding her with,
that's burning off.
So pretty soon, her cells
will be so desaturated,
we cannot perform the surgery.
- Fix it.
- I can't.
- This is your city.
This is your facility.
So turn the power back on.
- I can't because the system
has been encrypted.
- By who?
- By Miss Smoak.
♪ ♪
- Is there anything else
I can help you with?
- No, that'll be all.
- Very well.
Before I go, I have something
for you,mein Fuehrer.
A gift...
to celebrate your return.
Guard!
Well, I know how much you enjoy
executing rule breakers,
and this one has broken
many of them.
We discovered
this Jewess
handing her rations
to the work camp children.
Strictly against camp rules,
of course.
- Those children were starving.
- [scoffs]
- [sighs]
- Well, this must be hard.
I hear your doppelganger
on Earth-1
loved a woman who looks
just like this.
♪ ♪
[gun clicks]
[laughs]
[guns cocking]
[chuckles]
Did you really think I would
hand you a loaded weapon...
[raising voice]
Before verifying who you are?
[grunting]
[gunfire]
[men yelling]
♪ ♪
- Hey, hey, hey,
you're okay.
No, no, no, you're fine.
You're fine.
Just take this and go.
- Why are you doing this?
- It's the strong's duty
to protect the weak.
Take it and go.
Go!
[dramatic music]
Clear.
- How did it...
Oh.
- Barry, we have a problem.
The gateway control's
been damaged.
- We can't turn it on?
- We can't turn it on here,
but there should be a manual
override at the platform.
- [sighs]
All right, we're gonna have
to fight our way through.
- What do you mean?
Call it back!
- Too late.
It's been programmed.
There's no changing
course now.
- You said we'd have an hour.
- Yeah, well,
I changed my mind.
- The team hasn't gone
through the breach yet.
- That team has nothing to do
with us or saving our planet.
And everyone
who can threaten it
is on the other side
of that breach.
They are not coming
back through.
- General!
- Leo, enough!
I'm not risking any more time.
We are blowing it up.
- Guys, we have a problem.
- What kind of problem?
Snart:A weapon is heading
to blow up the facility.
- A weapon?
You mean a missile?
- Not exactly.
♪ ♪
- Felicity Smoak.
Turn the power back on.
- He said...
- [breathing raggedly]
- Felicity!
- [coughs]
- "Turn the power back on."
- Sorry, Eobard.
Eobard?
- Eobard.
My God, the future
sounds weird.
- That's funny.
Sometimes we think
we're more clever than we are.
Because where I come from,
the history books
are filled with stories
of this Age of Heroes:
Green Arrow,
Black Canary,
The Flash.
And yet no one...
no one has ever heard
of Felicity Smoak.
- Stop!
Stop. Stop.
You came here for me,
so just take me, please.
Please don't hurt anyone else.
Give them the code.
- If I do, they'll kill you.
- It's fine.
Nobody's gonna die
because of me.
- Latte, Ada, Jonas,
1-1-9-0-0.
- Latte?
Cute.
- [sobbing softly]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Let's go.
- In ten minutes, Red Tornado's
gonna bring down
this entire facility,
and there's nothing we can do
to stop that robot.
- Then we need
to reopen the gateway
before that happens.
Barry, Ray...
- We know.
Stop a flying robot somehow.
- Good. The rest of us
will open the breach.
- That's the whole plan?
- Well, as the Snart we know
used to say,
"Make a plan. Execute the plan.
"Expect the plan
to go off the rails.
Throw away the plan."
- Wow. That is...
that is terrible advice.
I always have a plan,
down to the second,
so nothing
ever goes wrong.
- No, no, no,
the only plan now
is not to leave this Earth...
without me.
- Okay.
- Right.
Ready for Tornado watch.
- Let's do it.
- I thought it'd be fun
if we put on our costumes.
- Where'd you get
the bow and quiver?
- The general collects weapons.
- Let's go to war.
- No one gets to the gateway!
No one!
[guns cocking]
[explosion]
[men grunting]
♪ ♪
[guards yelling indistinctly]
Soldier: Move! Move!
[both grunting]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[train horn blowing]
- Here we go.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[train horn blowing]
♪ ♪
- Okay, we're Nazi-free.
Let's go.
- Hold on.
That's an automated power cell.
We need to activate it before
using the control console.
- I can hot-wire it, no problem.
- Then I'll turn on
the console.
- You want to split up?
You sure?
- It's our most favorable odds.
Let's kick some ass, Jefferson.
♪ ♪
- Grey, we got power.
[gunfire]
- Whoa! Hey!
Ray!
A little help here!
♪ ♪
[yelling]
[both grunt]
both: Oh, crap.
[gunfire]
- Well, that's not very fair.
- I'm pinned down!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
- [gasps]
- Grey! No!
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.