The Great Wall has stood for centuries
as one of mankind's
most enduring wonders.
It spans over 5500 miles
and took more than 1700 years to build.
It protected from many dangers.
Some are known. Some are legend.
This is one of the legends.
THE GREAT WALL
All Commanders to the Great Hall!
All Commanders report to the General!
Make way! Make way!
All Commanders to the Great Hall!
Make way!
Commander Lin is needed immediately!
Calling Commander Lin!
He says two days ride
north, in the mountains.
They claim to have killed it.
-Two days?
Earlier than we expected.
Strategist Wang.
I'm listening, General.
-The two of them killed it?
He claims to have killed it alone.
-By himself? -Impossible.
Guards!
Commander Lin. Wait.
General. They claim to be
traders who were ambushed.
These barbarians are liars.
-Perhaps not.
They brought the claw here.
The wound is fresh.
There is green blood on his sword.
Those prove his story.
To protect our secret,
we must kill them.
Eliminate the possibility of trouble.
-I agree.
We should kill them!
General, until we find the truth,
I advise we keep them alive.
-Alert!
General, signals from the smoke towers!
We are under attack!
Take them to stockade.
All stations on full alert!
-All stations on full alert!
What's happening here, amigo?
Is this bitch going to kill us?
Hurry! -I'm sorry, sir.
I cannot find the key.
Forget it. Bring them to the Wall.
Keep an eye on them!
General. It's finally happening.
-Yes.
Sixty years preparing for this moment.
Stop! Stop!
Go! Go!
Inside!
Stand still!
Get down! Get down!
Catch it!
Long distance weapons!
-Yes!
Drums signal long distance weapons!
Grab it!
Light it!
Aim for the eyes! Aim for the eyes!
Crane Corps attack!
General, there is the Queen!
She commands them!
Attack the Queen!
Close combat!
-Yes! Close combat!
Drums signal close combat!
You fought well today.
Take them to the barracks.
They need rest. -Yes.
Thank you for saving my life.
Commandeer Lin. You grew
up in the Nameless Order.
I've taught you many things...
And you have been learning,
but they have been learning also.
Strategist Wang warned they are evolving.
No one listened.
The enemies we're facing today
are more intelligent
than sixty years ago.
Watch the foreigners closely.
They can never leave.
We must protect the secrets of the Wall.
-Yes, sir!
General.
I couldn't help wondering,
why would such an accomplished archer,
use such a primitive bow.
He claims his weapon
is second to none.
Let him show us.
Give him some space!
Unless he is afraid.
It's a large audience.
Men are too heavy.
Do you think we can pull him up?
Trust.
Xin ren.
Stay vigilant!
The next attack is coming.
Strategist Wang requests your presence.
Troops unaccounted
for at the West Tower!
Why did they leave the bodies?
Dismount!
Formation!
Advance!
Stop!
Commander Lin.
General...
They led us into a trap.
We underestimated their intelligence.
The Nameless Order
is yours to command.
-General...
Commanders, this is my final order.
From this day forward,
Commander Lin will lead you.
The soldiers of Nameless Order
will stand firm.
The Wall must not fall!
We will defeat the Tao Tei!
Rest in peace!
-Rest in peace!
This is 900-year-old battle report.
-A 900-year-old battle report.
How to prove it?
He wants to try.
He wants to catch one.
Use a spear, hook them.
So we can catch them.
He claims to have seen it done it Spain.
The mixture must be strong
to put the creatures to sleep.
Spread it on evenly.
-Yes, Commander.
Snap out of it!
Useless idiot! Report to the kitchen
where you belong! -Yes, Commander!
Go!
Death Squad ready!
-Yes! Death Squad go!
Blades ready!
Blades forward!
-Attack! -Go!
Left! Right!
Harpoons! -Harpoons, now!
-Yes! Harpoons, fire!
Fire!
There! -Move!
-It's the last one!
Pull!
Hold!
Let him run!
Ring of fire!
-Yes! Ring of fire!
Screaming arrows!
-Yes! Screaming arrows!
Aim inside the circle.
Blanket the whole area.
Fire!
Pull!
Prepare black powder weapons!
-Prepare black powder weapons!
Prepare to light the fuses!
Yes! Prepare to light the fuses!
Xin ren.
Excellent. Send it to the
capital immediately. -No!
We need to study it here. -If Tao Tei is
captured alive, it must be sent to the Emperor.
This is Imperial Order.
Tao Tei movement!
All troops to the Wall!
General, it goes all the way through.
Tao Tei have breached the Wall.
They're smarter than we thought.
Summon my commanders immediately!
-Yes, General.
All of the attacks have been a diversion,
while they dug this tunnel.
They have breached the Wall. Once they reach
the capital, nothing in the world can stop them.
At a full gallop,
it's 2 days to the capital.
There is no way we can catch them.
-The wind is strong now.
It blows from the north all day
tomorrow. We have to use the balloons.
If it works, how long to Bianliang?
-Six hours if the wind holds.
If we make it alive.
General, none of the tests have worked.
Get ready!
THE CAPITAL
BIANLIANG
How did you capture it?
-Your Excellency.
It's the magnet!
It keeps the beast under the control.
This is the most important discovery
in the history of the Tao Tei.
We will investigate immediately.
-Bring him here!
Liar!
General.
-Speak up!
I was there when it happened.
I saw him try to stop them.
Are you sure?
If you're lying, I'll have your head!
I swear on my vow to the Nameless Order!
Lock him up. Send the cavalry. Go after
the two that got away. -Yes, General.
Keep it steady! -Yes, General.
-Watch the powder! -Yes, General!
Strategist Wang!
Please take me with you.
Distance is the key. The magnet is
only effective when close to the beast.
Therefore, the effect weakens
as it gets further away.
You see I have it
under complete control.
Write down nine feet.
Steer to the rear of the palace.
-Yes. To the rear of the palace!
Light a grenade!
-Yes, sir!
State your purpose!
General Lin Mae of the Nameless Order.
At your service!
What took you so long?
The Tao Tei have overrun the city!
Thousands of soldiers and
innocents are dead. You're too late!
Your Majesty, where is
the captured Tao Tei?
In the dungeon!
-We need to kill the Queen.
Once she is dead,
the Tao Tei cannot function.
Without her signal, their
whole army will freeze.