I was sifting through Sadoc's old book.
Harfoots must've journeyed this way
a long time ago.
[Brânk] The Istar will surrender to me,
because if he doesn't,
I will slaughter
the halflings he calls friends.
[bell tolling]
[Kilta grunts]
[in Quenya] ...Túlielde Yallo!
[Poppy and Nori screaming]
[in English] Nori!
[Estrid] Were you headed
for the ridgeline?
The survivors will be waiting for us
where we made camp.
-My father, too.
-I think you may have missed them.
-[Isildur] You hoping to find kin as well?
-[Estrid] My betrothed.
If he's even half as strong as you,
I'm certain of it.
[Estrid] I'm not so strong as you think.
[screams]
[Theo] Anything you were to me,
is ashes now.
So for my part,
we don't ever need to speak again.
-[Berek whinnies]
-[Estrid grunts]
-[grunts]
-[Berek whinnies]
[Theo] D'you really want your horse back?
-You know where he is?
-Meet me here. Tonight.
[Hagen] What are you doin' out here
in the dark, boy?
[Wildman grunts]
It's an ambush!
[Theo screams]
[Glüg] Preparations are nearly complete,
Lord-father.
Must we go to war again?
We'll never truly be safe,
until we've made certain
Sauron is no more.
[Galadriel] Since the wearing
of this Ring, I have perceived
glimpses of the unseen world...
-[Celebrimbor grunts]
-[screams]
[Galadriel] Our letters to Celebrimbor
have all gone unanswered.
I fear Sauron may be in Eregion.
The High King has consented
to send me and a small party there,
to ensure Celebrimbor
and his city are safe.
Elrond's task is not to join your company.
But to lead it.
[opening theme music playing]
[birds chirping]
[indistinct shouting]
[Galadriel] Still no word
from Celebrimbor...
If we take the Axa Bridge,
Eregion is just under 150 leagues.
We shall need an archer, two swordsmen.
I trust you can recommend a set.
Trust? Me?
Are you certain that's wise, commander?
At the High King's urging, I agreed
to appointment you as first lieutenant.
But if you deem that duty beneath you,
I will choose another.
-Yes.
-"Yes" what?
Yes, I can recommend
an archer and two swordsmen.
Who else shall we take with us, commander?
[captivating music playing]
[ominous music playing]
Lightning?
No earthly force could do this.
This is the work of Sauron.
Camnir. What other paths might we take?
To circumvent it,
we shall either have to turn due north,
adding two weeks to our journey...
Or?
We go south,
through the Hills of Tyrn Gorthad.
-[Voice on the Wind whispering]
-[ringing]
[Camnir, muffled] Which will get us
to Eregion much faster.
[hisses]
There is evil in those hills.
Ancient, and filled with malice.
Sauron means for us to go that way.
We must go another.
The Enemy is doubtless
watching both roads.
This collapse makes it more critical
than ever to reach Celebrimbor at speed.
[Galadriel] We won't reach anywhere
at speed if we walk into a trap.
We go south.
Commander, I must protest.
[Elrond] Your opinion on the matter
has been heard.
Elrond.
Opinion heard, lieutenant.
We go south. [shouts in Sindarin]
[in English] This company will not take
counsel from that trinket, nor will you.
If you cannot abide by those terms,
you will leave now and return to Lindon.
-I should like to.
-Then why do you not?
Because I do not wish to see
any of this company slain.
Including you.
[Stranger yelling] Nori!
[somber music playing]
[goats bleating]
Nori! Poppy!
[goat farmer humming]
[grunts]
Uh...
Um, uh...
Pardon me. I don't suppose you've seen
a pair of halflings come this way?
[goat farmer sighs]
See you found the goat.
[brays]
It wasn't...
quite what I was searching for.
Well, there's what you're searchin' for
and there's what you find, now,
isn't there?
[singing] Hey dol, merry dol
Ring a dong dillow...
Sandflies in the grass
Bees around the willow
There are some stars above your hill.
Stars above most 'ills.
But my friends and I
were looking for these stars.
-I had hoped that...
-[whooshes]
Oh... [grunts]
My apologies, j-just a moment...
[singing] Of sun, stars
Moon and mist
[Stranger grunts]
Rain and cloudy weather
[amusing music playing]
[Stranger grunting and groaning]
[sighs]
The branch... of course...
Yes.
It must be.
[branch creaking]
[grunting]
[rumbling]
[exclaims]
[yells]
[speaking in Quenya]
[grunting]
[wind whistling]
-[insects trilling]
-[bird squawking]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[in English] Poppy!
[Poppy groans]
Get up!
[coughs]
[gags]
[groans]
-[Nori] D'you see him?
-Who? [grunts]
Who d'you think?
Our friend, the bleedin' Stranger.
Never mind where's he, where are we?
-[horse whinnies]
-Nori! Run!
[gasps]
[both grunting]
[both panting and groaning]
I think, I think we lost them.
[Merimac] Where'd you lot come from?
Us?
Where'd you come from?
Oh, my head.
Uh...
-Live here.
-Harfoots live here?
What's an Harfoot?
[chuckles] Well, you are...
Who are you, exactly?
I'm Nobody.
Well, you can't be "Nobody."
Well... That's what everybody calls me.
If everybody calls you Nobody,
doesn't anybody call you somebody?
Well, my mum calls me Merimac.
I'm Poppy.
Hmm.
I'm Nori.
Where'd you get that water from?
-Keep your voice down.
-[Poppy] You stole it, didn't you?
You stole it from that well.
From the big folk.
[gasps]
[grunting]
-But... Where are you going?
-[Merimac] Uh, nowhere.
Take us with ya.
Uh, sorry, no outsiders in the village.
Village? What village?
No village! There's no village.
Listen here, Nobody.
-[exclaims]
-Either we're coming with you
or I will turn you in myself
this moment, water-thief.
[Merimac] You're about to meet The Gund,
our dwell-leader.
And if you want her to even think
about takin' you in, there's four rules.
One, never look her in the eye.
B, always stand three steps back.
Four, don't, ever, ever, no matter what,
call her "The Gund."
-Got it.
Was that three rules or four?
[Poppy] I wasn't really paying attention.
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
[female Stoor villager 1]
Off you go, have fun now.
[female Stoor villager 2]
Come on. Over there.
That's 'cause it's had the sunshine on it.
[female Stoor villager 3] You're there.
[female Stoor villager 4] Nice,
fresh batch, ready to peel.
-Big hat, like mine!
-[child] Like Dad's!
Harfoots, livin' in holes?
It doesn't seem natural.
[Gundabale]
That's 'cause we're not Harfoots.
We're Stoors.
Stoors?
[Gundabale] What were you thinkin',
bringin' 'em here?
-Nobody's that stupid.
-[scoffs]
They needed a place to hide.
What, with half the devils
in the desert searchin' for them?
Boy, if we put your brains in a vulture,
it'd fly backwards.
Be nicer to him.
Are you talkin' back-sass to me?
Oh, that was the fourth rule.
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't
feed you leg, limb, and joint
to those Gaudrim hunting you out there.
Go on, plead your case.
I have walked across rivers,
and mountains,
and deserts to help my friend
find his destiny,
one the fate of the world may well
depend on, yours included...
I said one good reason.
This friend of yours, who is he, anyways?
-He's a giant.
-A giant?
-What, like an Elf?
-Bigger than that.
So he's a great big Grand-Elf.
He's not an Elf.
He's a wizard.
[villagers exclaiming]
[murmuring]
Well, the only wizard under these skies
is the Dark Wizard.
And the last friend we need
is a friend of his.
Tie 'em up.
[Poppy] What?
What? No.
What? Let her go. What Dark Wizard?
[Brânk] The Istar is already much more
powerful than we had anticipated.
He conjured a sandstorm from thin air
that killed two of my men,
He makes his way north now.
Towards... the hermit.
[Dark Wizard] And what of the halflings?
[Brânk] We are scouring the desert
even now.
They will not evade us for long.
I swear my life on it.
You are either very foolish, Gaudrim,
or very brave.
Let the Harfoots be your sole concern.
I will see to the Istar myself.
[Old Man Ironwood growling]
[Tom] Let him out again.
You should not be wakin'.
Eat earth. Dig deep.
Drink water, hmm?
Go to sleep.
[grunts]
[shushes]
-[Old Man Ironwood growling]
-[shushes]
Who... Who are you?
Been awhile since I've been
called much of anythin',
but back in the Withywindle,
folk used to call me Bombadil.
Tom Bombadil.
[singing] Down west sinks the sun
Soon you will be gropin'
Don't be bashful now, Goldberry...
[Goldberry singing]
When the night-shadows fall
[both] Then the door will open
[object clattering]
I've done such as I can
with your filthy robe.
Well, clean your hands, wash your face,
then come join me by the fire.
Is, uh... Is somebody out there with you?
I thought I heard a woman singing.
Woman? What woman?
Is no one else here with you?
You're here.
That is, I think you are. Are you?
Uh... Yes?
[laughs]
[Tom humming]
Now, what was it that you were hopin'
to find under those stars of yours, huh?
Certainly not old Tom.
I was hoping to find my friends.
Shows what stars know, doesn't it?
Newcomers, that's what they are.
One year, it's dark.
The next, you look up,
there's a sea of tiny eyes
lookin' down at ya, a-watching.
Now, they think they know everythin',
but newcomers. Hmm?
Still newcomers.
[gasps] Wha...
What are you?
Don't you know my name yet?
That's the only answer.
Tell me, who are you,
alone, yourself, and nameless?
But you are young, and I am old.
Eldest, that's what I am.
What do you mean, "Eldest"?
Eldest.
Mark my words, friend,
Tom was there
before the river and the trees.
Tom remembers the first raindrop
and the first acorn.
He knew the dark under the stars
when it was fearless.
This whole place used to be green.
Now, it's all sand.
I had to come see for myself
to believe it.
Even the birdsong isn't wholly untouched.
Even your tree out there.
Old Man Ironwood.
-I thought it...
-Uh...
He... might be able to, lend me a branch.
Oh, well you should've tried askin' him.
[yawns]
[bleats]
Easy, Iarwain. Easy.
-[bleats]
-[Tom grunts]
I know.
This... magic. Can you teach it to me?
Teach you? What's to learn way out 'ere?
You wield power over trees,
over wind and fire.
You wield it, as if it belongs to you.
All things belong each to themselves.
Just as you belong to yourself.
Then, might you teach me
how to wield a staff?
A wizard's staff is like a name.
It's yours to wield already,
if you prove yourself worthy of it.
You showed today that you're not. Yet.
Whether you can become so,
well, we shall soon discover.
I was never meant to find a staff
under these stars.
I was meant to find you. Wasn't I?
[chuckles softly]
[horse whinnies]
What is it?
We're not alone.
[horse whinnies]
[sinister music playing]
[Stranger] Who are they?
Why do they hunt me, and my friends?
You are not the first Istar
who's eaten honey by my fire.
Years ago, there was another.
The Dark Wizard.
What became of him?
Once, he sought to control magic,
like you.
Now, he controls much of Rhûn.
But still, he hungers for more.
You believe his evil will spread?
Not without an ally
far more powerful even than himself.
Sauron.
If these two flames combine into one,
there will be no end to burnin',
till all Middle-earth is ashes.
Can you stop it?
Old Tom's a wanderer, not a warrior.
Great deeds are left
to the hands they were placed in.
And I shall gather lilies,
while yet they grow.
You mean...
You mean my hands.
Is it my task to stop the fire?
Is it my task to face Sauron?
Your task... is to face them both.
[rustling]
[Voice on the Wind whispering]
I am waiting for you.
[Daemor] What is this place?
Tyrn Gorthad.
Known to Men as the Barrow-downs.
In ancient days, this was where
they laid their lords and kings to rest.
I feel no rest here.
Even the trees seem ill at ease.
[Vorohil] Fear not.
Dead Men are no threat.
[Elrond] Keep moving.
[Voices on the Wind whispering]
Cold be hand and heart and bone
And cold be sleep under stone
[intense music playing]
[Voices on the Wind whispering]
-[twig snaps]
-[grunts]
[eerie music playing]
For a moment, I thought I heard...
Heard?
What did you hear?
It was almost like a song.
Or the memory of a song.
Galadriel.
Their barding is from Lindon.
The King sent a dispatch
to warn Celebrimbor.
This dispatch?
We must go from this place.
-[whooshing]
-[grunting]
-Daemor!
-Hold on to me.
Don't let go!
[both grunting]
-[Daemor screams]
-[Voice on the Wind growling]
[all panting]
[crunching and squelching]
[Voices on the Wind] Cold old be hand
and heart and bone
And cold be sleep under stone
Never more to wake on stony bed
Never, till the Sun fails
and the Moon is dead
[rustling]
In the black wind the stars shall die
Prepare yourselves.
What are they?
Barrow-wights.
[Barrow-wights growling]
[in Elvish] Attack!
[grunts]
[screams]
[clanking]
Still your arrows!
[speaking Sindarin]
[Barrow-wight hisses]
[Camnir in English] They're impervious
to our weapons.
[hisses]
Hold fast. Come with me.
Where are you going?
-Help me open it.
-[Camnir] What?
[in Sindarin] Hurry!
[both grunting]
[hisses]
[grunts]
[in English] Lieutenant!
[grunting]
[shrieks]
Take it.
[growls]
-[grunts]
-[shrieks]
[Rían] How?
According to lore,
only the blades with which they were
buried will return such creatures to rest.
But the Men buried here have been entombed
for over a thousand years.
I think it is safe to say
that something has awoken them.
No.
Someone.
Awakening evil.
Across all of Middle-earth.
[Isildur] Theo! Theo!
-[female Southlander 1] Theo!
-[male Southlander 1] Theo!
-Theo!
-[male Southlander 2] Theo!
-[male Southlander 3] Theo!
-Theo!
[male Southlander 4] Theo!
[male Southlander 5] Theo!
-[male Southlander 6] Theo!
-[female Southlander 2] Theo!
[eerie music playing]
They left all their weapons.
To a Wildman, an axe-head
is worth more than gold.
Strange, they did not take it with them.
Come, all of you. We move on.
This way. Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
Do not torture yourself, Númenórean.
Theo has survived far worse.
He will weather this.
[male Southlander 1] Theo!
[female Southlander] Theo!
[male Southlander 2] Theo!
You there. This way.
[birds screeching, cawing]
[man] I say we raid their camps.
[Isildur] We'd be starting a war.
-We're already at war, Sea-folk.
-[people assenting]
What I saw,
I do not believe was done by mortal Men.
They're not Men. They're animals.
They'd eat human flesh if they had to.
Every minute we waste
is another Theo's still out there.
We've got to keep searching.
We could canvass Eastfield Glen.
Whispers are, Wildmen camp there.
[female Southlander] That's a good idea.
You'd do better to look north.
Why north?
I've spent weeks searching these lands,
lookin' for loved ones.
That part of the forest is old.
Promise you, there are Wildmen there,
and worse.
[murmuring]
[female Southlander] You might be right.
Arondir.
[Arondir] Let's not waste any daylight.
Gather water and provisions.
[male Southlander] Let's get a move on.
-[creaking]
-[Estrid and Isildur grunting]
Oh!
[chuckles]
There you go.
You missed a spot.
[Isildur] Thanks.
Fancy you never want
for water on your island.
No. In Númenor,
we have water in most of our homes.
I'd like to see that.
I wager your betrothed would too.
We ought to keep moving.
In a moment.
You say you spent time
among the Wildmen, Estrid.
How much?
Uh, I wasn't exactly among them.
I was hidin'.
-Did they ever do you harm?
-Arondir, what are you...
I ask because I noticed
a wound on your neck.
Looks to be recent.
No. That was my fault.
I, um... fell asleep by the fire.
I should've put it out,
but the night was cold.
It was foolish of me.
We all do foolish things sometimes.
Especially in moments of hopelessness.
[both grunting]
[both breathing heavily]
[grunting]
Estrid, what is this?
Self-burn.
The Wildmen do it
to hide the Mark of Adar.
We would have caught her at the gate
had she not come in with you.
She's a Wildman?
She's one of them.
And she's going to lead us
to all the others.
[Isildur] What was your plan?
Stab me? Take my horse?
Was that it? No?
Then you saw I was a Númenórean.
Had a better idea, didn't you?
[scoffs]
You were using me all along.
Wager you don't even have a betrothed.
-Would you rather I died in Mordor?
-I don't know.
Let me think.
What is it?
Be still.
[speaks Sindarin]
[in English]
Come quickly.
Theo was not taken by Men at all.
-[sinister music playing]
-[creature groaning]
[wood creaking]
[breathing heavily]
-[Hagen] Look.
-[gasps]
Well-fed's awake.
[Wildman 1 coughing]
-[rumbling]
-[prisoners shouting]
[Wildman 2] Help!
[creature groaning]
What's out there?
Don't know yet.
But whatever they are, they're big.
[Arondir] Watch your step.
[both grunting]
[panting]
Might be easier to balance
if I had use of my hands.
And easier to escape.
[sighs in exasperation]
No one could escape in this.
Come on, unlock me.
[Isildur grunts]
It's all right.
[grunts]
Be still.
I said it's all right.
[grunts]
Give me your hand.
-[bubbling]
-Help!
[both grunting]
[bubbling]
Lift me up.
I'm going down.
[both grunting]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[hisses]
[gasps]
[shrieking]
What was that?
There are nameless things
in the deep places of this world.
This one...
we shall call "supper."
[laughs]
[Gundabale] Right, I've conferred
with the village elders.
You two are to be cast out at sunrise.
Sorry, but Stoors must come first.
Truth is, he was in your place...
Sadoc likely would've done the same thing.
Sadoc?
Our trail-finder.
He was called Sadoc Burrows.
Sadoc Burrows was your leader's name?
Just so's we're both working
with a full bushel, I don't believe you.
I'm only showin' you this
to make good and sure.
Sure of what?
Story goes, in ancient days,
there was a Stoor.
Wasn't like the rest of us.
They say he dreamed one night of a place,
with endless streams of cold water
and rollin' hills so soft,
a family could dig a hole
and live in it in less than a month.
He called it "the Sûzat."
Struck out one year
with a caravan of followers to find it.
Promised, when he did,
he'd send someone back
to gather the rest of us.
But that was the last any of us
ever heard of Rorimas Burrows.
Poppy's walkin' song.
Harfoots have been here before.
Your kind's home, where you come from,
does it look like this?
Have you come back here
to lead us all to the Sûzat?
I think, um...
Rorimas never found the Sûzat.
And after a while...
we just kept wanderin'.
We don't have a home.
[indistinct shouting]
The riders sighted. Big folk.
Comin' this way.
[ominous music playing]
To what do we owe the pleasure of...
[villagers exclaim]
[Brânk] The Harfoots, where are they?
The only halflings we know about
in this desert are Stoors.
[Brânk] Do you know
why we wear these masks?
Defy the Dark Wizard
and, when we return with him,
you will find out for yourselves.
[Galadriel] I know you believe this Ring
is deceiving me.
But I believe it is guiding me,
and that following it
may be our only path to victory.
Is there no point at which
the cost of victory becomes too great?
I have yet to reach that point.
How does that not terrify you?
Because the suffering
of a world ruled by Sauron
terrifies me more.
I have always felt it.
But with this Ring, I can see it.
Everything we stand to lose
if we fail in the task before us.
My father foresaw that, one day,
Celebrimbor's life would be in my hands.
I will choose the path I must to give me
the best hope of protecting it.
Protecting that which is most fragile,
most dear,
is a task entrusted to all Elves.
And one that is not yet complete.
And I promise you,
there will be more painful sacrifices.
-[sinister music playing]
-[screaming]
Galadriel?
Promise me, Elrond,
you will put opposing Sauron
above all other considerations.
Even my life.
I will make no promise
whose asking is borne of that Ring.
But I swear to you...
defeating Sauron will come first.
Even before you.
[footsteps approaching]
Forgive me, commander, we heard drums.
[dramatic music playing]
Is that the key to the manacles?
Believe he meant for you
to decide whether or not to use it.
I'm sorry.
So am I.
No. Isildur, y'see...
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
Forgiveness doesn't come to folk like me.
Sooner or later, they'll cast me out,
you know they will.
[bowstring tightens]
I won't let them.
I won't let them cast you out.
Put down the sword.
[rumbling]
[thudding]
Estrid, drop the sword!
[grunts]
Estrid!
[in Sindarin] Stop!
[in English] I am Arondir,
of the Greenwood.
Hast thou ever touched axe to wooded life?
To my great pain, I have, but...
[Winterbloom wailing]
[in Sindarin] Listen to me!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[in English] It is not for felling trees.
What does it fell?
Orcs.
[whispers] Stay back.
There was an...
an army of them.
Maiming and murdering as they marched.
We saw what they did.
Is that why you're here?
Why you're so angry?
The spilling sap and burning branch
called to us from afar.
But... we were too late.
An army? How long ago was this?
Winterbloom nourished many of those trees
from seed and sprout.
-Do not ask her to speak more of it.
-[Winterbloom sobs]
[Winterbloom]
They are no different from them!
Disemboweling, and uprooting,
branch-breakers and trunk-splitters, all!
[in Sindarin] We would seek...
[groans softly]
your forgiveness...
for the injury...
...we have done.
[in English] Forgiveness takes an age.
Rain washing clear
the long memory of soil.
New bark, covering old scars.
And in all that time, I promise,
we will see to it that the trees
of this wood are left in peace.
Think they know what peace is?
It is what comes after the night storms,
when the dawn is silent,
and the birds awaken.
We have tended this forest
since before the mountains
rose up and divided it.
When the only sound here
was the light upon the moss...
Theo?
And the breathing of the leaves.
Yes. We know peace.
Estrid? It's me.
-[rain pattering]
-[grunts]
Estrid? Estrid.
Hagen?
-What... I thought you...
-So did I.
[Estrid] I can't believe you're here.
Look at you.
[footsteps thudding]
Thank you for coming for me.
I made a promise.
Thank you for keepin' it.
Now I must keep another.
Orcs are on the move.
I must follow the trail where it leads.
Perhaps have another chance
to confront Adar.
You can come with me, if you wish.
I have promises of my own to keep.
Then mae glenno. Lord of Pelargir.
[sinister music playing]
[snarling]
[indistinct chanting]
Orc-treachery.
That trail.
I gather it leads to...
Eregion, my liege.
We came in search of Sauron.
And instead, we find Adar?
Could they
be in league with each other or...
Perhaps at war.
A legion of Orcs
have marched into Elvish lands.
We are all of us at war.
Word of this must reach the High King
before our host sails for Mordor.
[Orc] There!
-[arrows thudding]
-[horse whinnies]
[in Elvish] Hold!
[Snaghûl, in English]
But that's our supper gettin' away!
-[grunts]
-[horse whinnies]
[Snaghûl] Come on!
Back in line!
[snarls]
[Snaghûl] Who is it?
Keep looking. [laughs]
[groaning and choking]
[snarls]
[sniffs]
[chuckles]
-[coughs]
-[Snaghûl] They're nearby. Keep lookin'.
[muffled whimpering]
[Snaghûl] Who is it? What was that?
[Borzag] Came from over here.
[Snaghûl] I can smell an Elf.
[Camnir, muffled whimpering]
[in Sindarin] Amazing.
[Borzag, in English]
Leave no stone unturned. Go!
Get to Lindon.
I will occupy them as long as I am able.
[Borzag] Keep looking.
Take it.
Take it, Elrond.
Over there.
[Orcs laughing]
Where's the rest?
I stand alone.
Cut off her right thumb.
Tell us where the others are,
I'll let you keep the left.
-[all laughing]
-[grunts]
[all grunting]
[Orcs screaming]
[grunts]
-[Orcs snarling]
-[horse whinnies]
[grunts]
[Orcs screaming]
[panting]
She sacrificed herself to save us all.
No, you are mistaken, Camnir.
[in Sindarin]
She did not do it to save us.
What?
She did it to save the ring.
[in English] Hurry.
[horse whinnies]
These are Elven lands.
[Orcs snarling]
Go back to the shadow.
[grunts]
[in Quenya] A star shines on the hour
of our meeting...
Lady Galadriel.
[in English] Now let the song begin
Let us sing together
Of sun, stars, moon and mist,
Rain and cloudy weather
Light on the budding leaf
Dew on the feather
Wind on the open hill
Bells on the heather
O slender as a willow-wand
O clearer than clear water
O reed by the living pool
Fair River-daughter
O springtime and summertime
And spring again after
O wind on the waterfall
And the leaves' laughter
Old Tom Bombadil
Is a merry fellow
Bright blue his jacket is
And his boots are yellow
Reeds by the shady pool
Lilies on the water
Old Tom Bombadil
And the River-daughter
O slender as a willow-wand
O clearer than clear water
O reed by the living pool
Fair River-daughter
O springtime and summertime
And spring again after
O wind on the waterfall
And the leaves' laughter