Cleaned, corrected, re-synced,
dashes removed and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother
Killed by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly I use my speed
To fight crime
and find others like me,
And one day I'll find
who killed my mother...
- Mom!
- And get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on the Flash...
Iris West.
I hear you've been
writing about me.
I've been
collecting internet posts
About the Streak sightings.
Baby, there's no Streak.
I saw him, Barry.
He wears a red suit.
I finally diagnosed why Iris
is writing about the Streak.
She's doing it for me.
I'm gonna find out
who really killed Laura,
And I'm going
to get you out of here.
Whoever this Streak is,
I am not stopping until the rest
of the world believes in him.
Maybe we shouldn't
see each other for a while.
To understand
what I'm about to tell you,
You need to do something first.
You need to believe
in the impossible.
Can you do that?
Good, because all of us,
We have forgotten
what miracles look like.
Maybe because they haven't made
much of an appearance lately.
Our lives have become ordinary,
But there is someone out there
who is truly extraordinary.
I don't know
where you came from.
I don't know your name,
But I have seen
you do the impossible
To protect the city I love.
So for those of us who believe
in you and what you're doing,
I just want to say thank you.
Hmm.
You're welcome.
How did you...
I literally just hit send.
Speed reading.
It's crazy
what you can do to your voice.
You need to stop
writing your blog.
People need to know
that you exist.
What else can you do?
- This is not an interview.
- Come on.
You got to give me something.
Hobbies, pet peeves,
favorite color?
Wait, scratch that last one.
Red, duh, obviously.
- You're not hearing me.
- My hearing is fine.
It's just selective.
What should I call you?
Anything but the Streak.
Fine. Suggestions?
You said you were writing
about me to bring hope
To someone you care about.
How would he feel if doing
that put you in harm's way?
He and I aren't exactly
on the same page these days.
Besides, you're giving hope
to a lot of people,
So I'm doing this for them.
To be continued.
Gotta run.
Hey!
You can't just leave me up...
here.
Whoa.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
What kind of a tool
steals a yellow humvee?
What kind of tool
buys a yellow humvee?
Get these people back.
I need everybody back!
Son!
Out of the way!
What the hell?
Eddie!
Yeah!
Step out of the vehicle!
If you say so.
Uh-oh.
Unh!
Looks like you were born
to take a beating.
Check the math.
Your dispersal models
don't correlate.
Uh, they do if you factor
in the seasonal fluctuations
In reproduction cycles.
What exactly are we debating?
The average number of bugs
Barry swallows
in a day of running.
I look forward to seeing
you accept your Nobel.
Barry?
Are you okay?
13 fractures.
That's a new record,
and that's just in your hand.
You also have a concussion,
three cracked ribs,
And a bruised spleen.
Even with your powers,
you'll need a few hours to heal.
What exactly did you hit?
A man.
A big, bad man.
His skin changed when I hit him.
Like, it turned to metal.
Interesting.
A man of steel.
So you went after
a meta-human alone?
Dude, why didn't you call us?
I didn't know what he was.
Besides, I was off-duty.
Hmm.
You're lucky
he didn't knock out your teeth.
Those puppies
don't grow back.
The strange thing is
I feel like I knew him.
What do you mean?
He said something
that was familiar,
But he's gonna hurt someone
if we don't stop him.
So how do I fight a guy
that's made of steel?
We will find a way.
Tonight, you heal.
Yeah.
There was lightning
in my house.
Yellow and red lightning.
There was a man in yellow,
then I was on the street.
I don't know how I got there.
Please, you have to
believe me!
Hey.
What happened to you
last night?
Got beat up
by a steel-plated sociopath.
Good times.
- So he is a meta-human?
- Yeah.
That particle accelerator's
the gift that keeps on giving.
You okay?
Relatively.
Any idea who he is?
Eddie's taking point
while I run down a lead.
I need you to work with him
until I get back.
Wait, why me?
Because he saw something
impossible
That he's got questions about,
questions that I can't answer.
In other words,
make up some science-y stuff
To throw him off?
Exactly.
He stole the humvee
and evaded capture.
So pleased you could join us,
Mr. Allen.
Rough night?
Uh, just a little beat, sir.
As I was saying,
Our perp yanked three ATMs
after he boosted the vehicle.
ATM security cameras
caught him on video.
We got a hit in the database.
Tony Woodward.
He's got a history
of violence, petty theft,
Assault, going way back
to juvie.
Dropped off the radar
ten months ago.
Looks like he's back.
Increased pressure
produces increased heat,
And if you don't release it,
you get combustion.
I don't know how you
remember all this stuff, Barry.
Because he's a little freak,
just like his old man.
Don't talk about my dad.
Or what?
Is he gonna murder me, too?
Looks like you were born
to take a beating, Allen.
Allen.
- Hey, Allen.
- Hey.
You okay?
Hey, yeah.
Sorry, Eddie.
Listen,
I saw something last night
I just can't get my head around.
Uh-huh.
I fired a dozen rounds
at our car thief,
And it was
like they sparked off of him.
Huh, well, I mean,
He must have been
wearing some kind of body armor.
On his face?
- Um...
- hey.
Barry.
Hi, Babe, I saw the news.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine,
Which you would know
if you checked your messages.
I tried you three times.
Sorry.
I had to work late.
Um, so I heard
that the Streak saved a kid.
Any comment, Detective?
All I know is our perp
got away,
But Barry here is gonna
help me find him.
- Yeah.
- Fine.
I have other sources.
I will see you tonight.
- Bye.
What is going on with you two?
What do you mean?
Nothing, it's fine.
It's... sorry, it's fine.
I don't know.
Okay.
Dr. Wells.
I guess you heard about
Barry's incident last night.
If you're looking for him
I think he's at the station.
I actually came here
to see you.
I need your help
solving an old case of mine.
What case is that?
The murder of Barry's mother.
Your childhood nemesis is now
an unstoppable meta-human.
That is seriously messed up.
I had a childhood nemesis.
Lexi la Roche.
She used to put gum
in my hair.
Jake Puckett.
If I didn't let him
copy my homework
He'd give me a swirly.
Now that we've established
that we're all uber-nerds,
What are we gonna do
about Tony?
Glad you asked.
We're gonna train you, man.
Karate kid style.
Behold!
I call him girder.
For the record, not my idea.
Fighting is physics.
It's not about strength.
It's not about size.
It's about energy and power.
Channel your speed the right way
And you can totally take
this bad boy down.
Now obviously your girder
is a moving target.
So...
I have ice
and bandages standing by.
I'm pretty sure
I just dislocated my shoulder.
Okay, not gonna lie.
This is gonna be quick
but extremely painful.
Oh, speaking of pain.
Eddie, hey.
Allen, we found the stolen
humvee in the alley
At Fremont and Lawrence.
Need you down here
to do your thing.
Great.
I'll see you in a sec.
Okay.
Let's do this.
So Barry, when you said
you were off-duty last night,
You weren't
visiting Iris again.
You know, in disguise?
'Cause that would be reckless
and a little creepy.
No.
Good.
Allen, you really need a car.
I usually
manage on foot okay.
What do we got?
The rig Tony Woodward
boosted last night.
No sign of the stolen ATMs.
Probably got
those where he's holed up,
Though he's gonna have one hell
of a time breaking 'em open.
I wouldn't be so sure.
So, about you and Iris...
Look, Eddie, we had a fight,
And I just don't really
feel comfortable
Talking about it with you.
I get that, and I get that
you two go way back.
To be honest, I was a little
threatened by you at first.
You were threatened by me?
Sure.
I mean, I've seen
how close you two are,
But you seem like a good guy,
And Iris, I just
want her to be happy.
From my experience,
good friends are hard to find.
Detective.
Excuse me.
Sir, we ran the plates
on that humvee...
Come on, Barry!
You can do it!
Barr, focus!
I am!
Son, son, son.
You're getting frustrated.
You need to learn
how to control your emotions.
Iris, come here, sweetie.
You want me to hit a girl?
He wants you to try.
Relax, Barry.
I've had her in gloves
since she was six.
She's tougher than she looks.
Sorry, Barry.
Son...
Sometimes the best way to
win a fight is not to start one,
But if you do
come up against somebody
You know
you can't beat, be smart.
It's okay to run
the other way.
All right?
So what do you think?
Judging by the mud and kegs
I'd say he got hammered,
Stole a big-ass truck,
And went joyriding.
I bet the kegs are stolen, too.
Rusty iron ale, it's a micro
brewed right over in...
Keystone, I know the place.
- Let's check it out.
- Yeah.
Barry described a tornado
of red and yellow lightning
Inside a man in yellow.
Then, bam.
He's blocks away on the street.
Doesn't know how he got there.
When I arrived,
the place was a wreck.
Nora Allen is dead.
Single stab wound
to the heart.
Henry Allen
covered in her blood.
And despite all the evidence
that Henry Allen is guilty,
Now you believe this... what,
man in yellow is responsible?
Last night, I saw Barry
Rescue a young boy
from being run over,
And it looked exactly like what
Barry described happened to him.
It got me thinking,
What if somebody with Barry's
abilities killed Nora?
There's one flaw with
your theory though, Detective,
And is that all of this
happened 14 years ago,
Which is long before...
Your machine gave Barry
his powers.
An accident gave Barry
Do you think it is possible
That somebody
with Barry's super-speed
Could have existed
before the explosion?
Detective, I deal
in probabilities as a scientist,
And in this case...
It's highly unlikely.
Gentlemen, CCPD.
Any chance
some of your merchandise
Was stolen last night?
No, I don't think so.
How about this guy?
You seen him?
You know Tony, don't you?
Hey.
Allen, come on!
Allen, you okay?
- Oh, never better.
- Get up.
I didn't do nothing, man!
So why'd you run?
- Look, it was an accident!
- What was?
Tony falling, okay?
But I swear to god,
we didn't kill him!
Keep talking.
About ten months ago,
Keystone Ironworks.
Boss is handing out pink slips.
Tony gets his,
and he just snapped.
He started beating the crap
out of the guy.
We pulled him off,
and then the lights went out.
Some kind of power surge.
And then Tony
Went over the railing right
into a vat of molten scrap.
Just gone.
Lucky for you
he's still alive.
What?
How'd you get in front of us?
Shortcut.
♪ When I was just a boy,
my mama... ♪
I've been meaning to ask you,
where's your shadow?
What shadow?
Barry.
He hasn't been in all week.
Getting his fix
somewhere else.
Too bad.
He's cute, I kind of miss
having him around.
Iris?
Long time no see.
I got to say,
Iris, you look amazing.
Thanks, Tony.
Um, you too.
Oh, yeah.
I keep in shape.
I got a gym at my place.
Been living out in Keystone
on the west side,
And you should, uh...
you should stop by sometime.
So, uh,
can I get you a drink?
No, I came to see you.
How did you know I was here?
I've been reading up
on the Streak.
Found your little blog.
Why are you writing
about this guy?
People say that he's a hero.
I say he's a coward,
And I happen to know that he
took a beating last night
And ran off like a little girl.
You should write about that.
Do you have any idea
Who leather boy is?
No clue.
So, um,
if you don't want a drink
I should probably
get back to work.
Actually I'd prefer to buy you
a drink.
What time you off?
Thanks, Tony,
But I don't think
my boyfriend would approve.
He's a cop, like my dad.
I never really did like cops
too much.
Iris!
Well he's picking me up
for the policeman's ball.
Wall-to-wall cops.
Can't swing a cat.
I should probably call
him to see where he is...
Give me the phone, Iris.
Now!
I'm sorry.
Uh, for the damage.
We'll pick this up
some other time.
Barry!
Check it out!
The gravel
you pulled from Tony's ride?
It contains 76.8% hematite.
Consistent with the mines
at Keystone Ironworks.
Which closed
down ten months ago.
It's the perfect hideout.
Barry, do you mind telling me
about this?
"I have info about someone
you're looking for.
"He was here.
You know where to find me."
Now who could she be
talking to?
I guess you got my message.
Are you okay?
Cop's daughter.
I can handle myself.
Not with this guy.
I knew him when we were kids.
He didn't want to hurt me.
He wanted to impress me,
But he is fixated on you,
and not in a good way.
Do you know where he went?
He said he had a place
out in West Keystone.
Bragged about how big it was,
but I have no idea where.
- I do.
- Wait, there's something else.
His hand.
It transformed
like an iron fist.
He's like you, isn't he?
Yes, and writing about me
is what brought him to you.
I know,
but maybe I could talk...
No!
He's too dangerous.
Damn, that's my ride.
Eddie insisted on a detail.
I have to... go.
Barry, talk to us.
What are you doing?
Dude, don't run angry.
We don't know
how to defeat him yet.
This is definitely the place.
You're trespassing, freak!
There's nowhere left to run.
- Barry?
- Barry, where are you?
Caitlin, over here!
Barry?
Please, say something!
Say something
so we know you're okay.
- Ow.
- Get him out of there!
What were you thinking?
I told you
that we would figure out a way
- to deal with him.
- I'll heal.
You can't heal
when you're dead.
He could have killed you.
I know, all right?
I know!
In the past 36 hours
I've had my ass
Handed to me twice by the guy
that tortured me as a kid.
I couldn't stop him then,
and I can't stop him now!
Even with my powers
I'm still powerless against him.
Not necessarily.
Cisco?
Any material,
If struck at a high enough
velocity can be compromised.
We ran an analysis on
the metal in Tony's footprint.
Based on its density
and atomic structure,
If you impact it
at just the right angle,
At just the right speed, you
could do some serious damage.
How fast would I have to go?
Factoring in the metal's
tensile strength,
Estimated dermal thickness,
atmospheric pressure, air temp,
You'd have to hit him
at approximately...
Mach 1.1.
You want Barry to hit
something at 800 miles an hour?
837, actually.
That's faster than the speed
of sound.
I know.
He would create a sonic boom,
Which, as I've said before,
would be awesome.
I've never gone that fast.
Yet.
I can't believe we're actually
entertaining this idea.
I mean, he'd need
a straight shot from miles away
Yeah, 5.3 miles,
theoretically.
Do it right,
you'll take him down.
Do it wrong,
You'll shatter every bone
in your body.
Barry.
Joe, I've been
beaten up enough for one day.
- I gotta...
- Hey, wait.
An anonymous tip led us
to Tony Woodward's hideout.
The place was trashed.
What happened?
He shows up at jitters
to see Iris.
I had to go after him.
Iris, where is she?
She's fine, she's fine.
Eddie put a detail
on her to be safe.
I thought I could
handle him this time.
I tried.
Look, I know what this punk
put you through,
But you can't let emotion
cloud your judgment.
The tollbooth camera
got a shot of Woodward.
Stolen car headed out of town.
State police are taking over.
- We lost him.
- Don't worry, Eddie.
They'll get him.
I wanted
to take this guy down.
Not half as much as I did.
Let's go, Allen.
Go where?
Blow off some steam.
- I need to hit something.
- What?
I don't think he meant
hit you.
Go.
So I heard you and this
Woodward guy have a history.
Hey, Allen.
It's okay.
Trust me.
I had my fair share of bullies
at school.
Yeah, somehow I find
that hard to believe.
I was short, fat,
and the son of a politician
Who closed the factory
in my school district,
So not so popular.
So what'd you do about it?
I got my ass kicked.
A lot, until my gym coach
took pity on me.
She said the key
to fighting is patience.
Here.
A lot of guys waste energy
trying to land the most punches.
All it takes is one,
but you got to make it count.
Choose your spot
and drive through it,
Like it's six inches
behind the target.
Harder.
Harder!
The seam
was starting to split.
Appreciate you coming down.
Hmm, well these days
it's rare to find someone
Happy to have a drink with me.
Well, our conversation
yesterday got me thinking.
You said, as a scientist,
you look for the probable?
That's right.
And we both recently
have seen things
That have redefined
what is possible.
Yes, we have,
and we both know
The direct cause
of those things.
Your accelerator explosion.
Evolutionary leaps follow the
creation of new technologies.
It's that simple.
Like the Roomba.
Yes, like the Roomba.
So humor me here.
Hmm?
If we know that meta-humans
were created
By the particle accelerator
and testimony shows
That a meta-human may have been
involved in the murder
Of Barry Allen's mother 14 years
ago, it seems to me that...
Way back then
there must have been
Another particle accelerator.
- Another particle accelerator?
- Hmm.
I can assure you that's
extremely unlikely, Detective,
And if they were I don't recall
any dark matter lightning storms
Before I moved to town.
Do you?
No, no, I don't.
When did you move to town,
Dr. Wells?
Something tells me
that you already know the answer
To that question, Detective.
This whole "help me solve
the murder of Nora Allen,"
You were never
looking for my help, were you?
You opened your lab a month
after Nora Allen's murder.
Would you mind telling me
what you were doing
In Central City before that?
I was starting over.
Starting what over?
Here I thought
we were just two guys
Having a friendly drink.
You want answers, Detective?
Tess Morgan, look her up.
Unit 52, this is dispatch.
Requesting status update
on the west house.
Unh!
Hey, Iris.
- Nice, Allen.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Okay.
Hey, next time
work on your speed.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Thawne, Allen.
The unit watching Joe's
daughter, they've been attacked.
Iris is missing.
Go, all right?
I'll call Joe.
Let's adjust the impact angle
by .2 degrees,
Up the speed to 838.
Bam.
- Ouch.
- Ouch?
Guys, you there?
Yeah, man, what's up?
Tony took Iris.
I need you to do whatever you
can to help me find her.
All right?
Satellites, security cameras.
- Hack 'em all.
- We're on it.
What's wrong?
Remember this place, Iris?
So what's the plan here,
Tony?
You finally gonna
go for that G.E.D?
You want a plan?
How's this?
You used to write
about the Streak, right?
Now you're gonna write
about me.
You just abducted me, Tony.
Why would I do that?
Because the Streak is dead.
No.
Squashed like a little bug
by me.
So if you don't want
the same thing to happen to you,
You're gonna
tell the whole world
That there's a new big man
on campus!
And I'm just getting started.
You could have
anybody write about you, Tony.
Why me?
'Cause I like you, Iris.
Always have.
You should have said
something.
You try anything
like that again
And I'm gonna leave
more than a bruise!
Eddie, anything yet?
We have roadblocks
on every major artery.
Units are searching.
We will find Iris, Joe.
You don't think
he'll hurt her, do you?
Sir, sir, we got a fire alarm
call at Carmichael elementary.
Dispatch the fire department.
We'll send backup when we can.
That's the school
you and Iris went to.
- And Tony.
- Go.
Tony, turn yourself
in before things get worse.
It's not too late.
Yeah, it is.
Cops are already looking for me,
So get ready to cover
the showdown of a lifetime
'cause I'm not going out
without a fight.
Good,
'cause you just found one.
You just won't stay dead.
Come to save
your little fan girl?
This is between us.
Let her go.
Oh, I could,
but I'd rather make her watch
While I break every bone
in your body.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
Too slow, tin man.
- Aah!
- I've known guys like you.
Peaked in high school.
Never got over it.
All these powers,
and look at you!
Bully then, bully now.
- He's hurt.
- No!
If you do come up
against somebody you know you
Can't beat, be smart.
It's okay to run the other way.
There goes your hero.
He made it out.
Barely.
Why did he stop?
He's miles away.
5.3 miles away.
- Barry, wait!
- No way.
He's gonna do it!
Go, man, go!
Unh!
Supersonic punch, baby!
Whoo!
Nice cross.
- Yeah, I think I broke my hand.
- Oh, me too.
Hey!
What is this?
Where the hell am I?
Somewhere you'll never
hurt anyone ever again.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
You know who I am.
Allen?
The thing
that happened to you, Tony,
It happened to me too,
But it didn't just
give us abilities.
It made us more of who we are.
You got strong.
I got fast.
Fast enough to beat you.
You used your gift
to hurt people.
Not anymore.
Allen.
Allen, don't walk away from me,
Allen!
Hey!
Come back here!
Allen!
Dude, that had to feel great.
- You have no idea.
- Almost as good
As proving me wrong
about the supersonic punch?
Actually, that part hurt.
Like, a lot.
But I couldn't have
done it without you guys.
All I want to know
is which childhood bully
Are we gonna take down next?
- Mine or Caitlin's?
- Okay, yeah.
I vote mine.
What?
Guys, this is not a joke.
Doctor.
Detective.
Are you here to make
more accusations?
I'm here to make amends.
I looked up Tess Morgan.
I'm sorry for your loss.
You two were research partners
in Maryland?
Yes, we were.
We were...
Married to the work
as much as to each other.
After the car accident...
I could not go back to the work.
Could not go back to our lab.
So you moved here.
Where no one knew me.
Where no one could remind me
of what I had lost,
And, um...
I...
I found it difficult,
Starting over,
Rebuilding,
And what took me 14 years
Tess could have done in 4,
Believe me,
she... she...
At the time
of Nora Allen's murder,
The particle accelerator that I
would eventually create
Was...
but a notion,
Much less a reality,
And so whomever or whatever is
responsible for her death,
It did not originate
from me or from my work.
I'm sorry I doubted you,
But I hope I can still
count on your help.
You don't give up, do you?
Nope.
Not till I get my man.
I owe that to Barry
and to Henry.
Barry is lucky
to have you on his side, Joe.
Hi.
Oh, I thought
that you were someone else.
So Joe told me what happened.
How's the hand?
Not broken,
so that's something.
- I should have believed...
- I'm sorry I said...
I've missed you.
Yeah, I've missed you too.
When I heard
Tony took you, I...
I just...
I don't know what I would do
If anything happened to you.
Well, my guardian angel's
looking out for me.
Do you want to hang out
and catch up?
Yeah.
I would like that, yeah.
I promise not to talk
about the Streak tonight.
No, I want you to.
No, I mean, I want... you can...
I want you to talk
About whatever you'd want
to talk about.
I know it's important to you.
Good because it's not
just the Streak.
There are others out there
that are like him.
I've gotten scattered posts
about this guy that's on fire,
Except that he doesn't burn up.
Okay, so wait.
Wait.
You're trying to find
the burning man now too?
Yeah, why not?
I mean, a lot can happen
In a week,
especially with the Streak.
Heh.
I've been trying to
get answers from him.
Where does he come from?
How does he do what he does?
But he dodges everything.
Literally,
with this super-speed power.
When he moves, Barry,
you don't even see him.
He comes and goes
in the blink of an eye,
- In a...
- Flash?
In a flash.
Yeah.
Today, I was saved by
the impossible.
A mystery man.
The fastest man alive.
Then a friend gave me an idea
for a new name,
And something tells me
it's gonna catch on.
Greg, move your head.