Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough
to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
- Previously
on "The Flash."
- I'm free!
- Who are you?
- I am the future Flash.
- I can't spend
the rest of my life
wondering if I'm gonna
become Killer Frost.
- I understand
the real reason
that you invited me
on this team.
You just want
your own meta-human specialist
to try and find you a cure.
- That's not
the only reason.
- I wish I could
believe that.
- I'm Cisco, by the way.
You must be Gypsy.
You're into me.
- Even if I was,
you couldn't handle me.
- I'll marry that woman.
- Iris West,
will you marry me?
- Yes.
[both laughing]
- Looks like we may need
to find a new job.
Heard Stagg Industries may be
getting bought out.
- By who?
- Doesn't really matter now,
does it?
All I know is we got
millions of dollars of tech...
like whatever that thing is...
that no one's using.
- Then surely you gentlemen
won't mind
if I abscond
with some of it.
This piece in particular.
- How did you get in here?
- Believe me, that's the least
impressive of my tricks.
- Hands up, pal.
Do it now, or I'll shoot.
Stop!
- How the hell did he
do that?
[alarm blaring]
- Maybe you can figure out
how I did it,
but...I doubt
you'll have time.
[dramatic music]
[both screaming]
♪ ♪
[upbeat pop music]
- It's just beautiful.
You know what, it matches
the sparkle in your eyes.
- Aw, thank you.
- Barry,
your grandfather had
really good taste in jewelry.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, he did.
- Okay, so, break it down.
How did it happen?
- Um...we were
at the apartment,
and, um, Barry sang to me.
- [gasps]
- And then he proposed.
- Oh, my God,
that's so romantic.
You sing?
- Not as good as Joe.
- Shut up, Barry.
- Well, okay,
that reminds me,
My sister has four tickets
that she can't use...
to "Hamilton."
- "Hamilton"?
- On the house.
I thought that maybe
we could make it a double
if you guys were interested?
- Uh, yeah, we're interested.
When?
- First weekend in July.
[tense music]
- Um, July.
- Y...does that not work
for you guys?
- Um...
- No, that works great.
We'll be there,
all of us.
Don't!
Don't do this!
Please?
I'm begging you! Just...
- Barry!
- You lose, Barry.
- No!
[dramatic music]
- [sighs]
Well, everything's the same.
The future has not changed.
- All right.
Well, we have two months
to make sure that it does.
- Okay, well,
we should approach this
the same way we approach
any other problem...
start with what we know.
Problem can't be solved
if it's not understood.
- Therein lies the rub.
I feel like we can't understand
any of this
until it actually happens.
It's like Savitar's prophecies.
- Precisely, and just like
the newspaper headlines.
Well, all bar one.
[phone ringing]
- It's a crime scene.
We gotta go.
- Stagg Industries?
- All right, no.
- Hey, Julian,
before you go,
there was an envelope
delivered for you
from the Central City Opera.
- Yes, you'd mentioned that
you'd never gone before, so...
well, I got them for us
a while back, but now...
just go with whoever
you'd like.
- Huh.
Looks like things
between you and Julian
are a little frosty, huh?
It's too soon
for the cold puns?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Thought so.
- He still doesn't trust me
after I lied
about taking a piece
of the Philosopher's Stone.
- You did what you felt
you needed to do
to get rid of your powers.
- I know that and
you know that, but he...
- He'll come around.
Watch.
- I don't know that
he will, Cisco.
[camera clicking]
- Hey, Bar.
Anything?
- [clears throat]
Nothing yet.
- How the hell did this thing
get filled with water
and those poor dudes
get trapped in here?
- Beats me.
There's no water access
in the entire wing.
Instead of sprinklers,
every floor uses
a halon gas system that
absorbs all the oxygen
if there's a fire.
[sighs]
What about the security cams?
- None of them either.
Apparently, the Stagg geniuses
don't want any of their
"secrets" to get out.
Julian, please tell me
you found something.
- Nothing yet, Detective.
No fingerprints,
no DNA,
just two rather plump
looking corpses.
- What about the stolen tech?
- Nothing.
No one's saying a thing.
Everyone is incredibly
tight-lipped about it.
- Of course they are. Look,
I'll make some phone calls,
see if I can pry
those lips open, all right?
- Okay.
I'll keep working on it.
- This is the last thing we need
to be dealing with right now.
- I feel the same way,
but we can't just do nothing.
Iris ain't gonna let us
get away with that.
- I know, Joe,
but we're running out of time.
- That's why you and me need
to solve this case fast.
- Yeah.
- Sometimes...I wish you hadn't
told me what was gonna happen.
[phone buzzing]
- Yeah, I know.
Hold on.
Hey, what's up?
- Looks like we got
a robbery in progress
over at Kord Industries.
- Great, thanks.
Now Kord Industries.
That's two in one day.
- That's two
in under 12 hours.
- Yeah, I'm gonna make sure
it's the last one.
[speeds away]
[alarm blaring]
[Flash arriving]
- I don't think
that's yours, pal.
- Flash.
- You didn't think I'd want
to come meet
the newest resident
of Iron Heights?
- No, I assumed
that you'd show.
I just didn't expect you
to be so young,
Barry...Allen.
- Now, how do you know
who I am?
- I'm from the future.
You don't believe me?
Let's see, uh, 2017.
Hmm. How are things going
with your doomed love,
Iris West?
Or your greatest foe, Savitar?
- You know Savitar.
- I know everything about him,
and you.
[dramatic music]
- What the...
[groans]
- [panting]
Gypsy.
Still seeking revenge,
I see.
- I'm gonna get it
this time.
- We'll see.
- No!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- He calls himself
Abra Kadabra.
- As in hocus pocus?
- He's certainly got
a lot of tricks.
- Yeah, we think he has
some sort of nanotechnology
built into his body...
allows him to do
some extraordinary feats.
Teleportation, telekinesis,
you name it,
and believe me,
I have seen it all.
- So that card trick
he played on Barry,
the water tank at Stagg,
that's all some futuristic tech
that he's masking as magic?
- Well, it's Arthur C. Clarke's
third law.
"Any sufficiently advanced
technology is"...
both:
"Indistinguishable from magic."
- Before you showed up,
he said he was from the future.
- The future?
- He is, 64th Century.
- Great, another criminal
from the future.
Haven't we had our fill
of those guys?
- 64th Century.
What exactly are you
after him for?
- He's at the top
of the collectors'
most wanted list.
Showed up on my Earth
a few years back,
did a string of robberies
that ended
with a lot of people
losing their lives.
Showed up again
a couple weeks ago,
looted some tech companies,
came here.
- To do the same thing?
Why?
- He must have needed
our Earth's tech for something.
- Well, whatever it is,
we can definitely help you
figure it out, 'cause
I don't know about you guys,
but ever since last time
you were here,
I've been looking forward
to some Gypsy vibe action.
- That's way too much.
- Embarrassing.
- Yeah, I just want to catch him
so I can bring his ass
back to Earth-19
and put him down.
- Don't worry.
We can help you do that.
- We should check and see
if Julian's gotten anything.
- I'll go ask him.
- In the meantime,
we can figure out
where this guy
disappeared off to.
Lend me a hand?
- Stupid.
- I know that look.
What is going on
inside that head of yours?
- [sighs]
This guy knew
what was going on
with you and me
and Savitar.
- If he knows something
about Savitar, then...
- He might be the key
to saving you.
- This is the first real lead
we've gotten.
- But, guys,
what about Gypsy?
I mean, if she gets
ahold of him,
she's gonna take him
back to Earth-19.
- We can
figure that out later.
Right now,
we just need to find him.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I got nothing.
Why can't I find you?
- I told you,
this guy is smart.
You can't just vibe
Kadabra's location.
Whatever he's doing,
it renders him invisible to us.
- Okay, well,
if we can't vibe him,
then I guess we'll have to
find him another way, right?
- [sighs]
- What are you doing?
- I'm putting
some search parameters
into the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
to see if anybody vibrates
at a different frequency
than Earth-1 folk.
- Wish we had a satellite
that could do that on my Earth.
Wish I had
a bunch of this stuff.
- Oh.
I could hook you up, girl.
How about this, I spend
a few days on Earth-19,
and set you up with something
state-of-the-art.
You know, the only thing is,
I would need a place
to crash, so.
- Cisco...
- Gypsy.
[scoffs]
That kiss, that wasn't
"I'll see you around."
That was like,
"That needs to happen again,
real soon."
Or did I misread that?
- I-I-I've been preoccupied.
- Is that the only reason?
[alarm beeping]
Great timing!
- Looks like David Copperfield's
not too far from us.
He's at one of Mercury Labs'
satellite offices.
- Another tech company?
- The techiest.
- Let's grab the speedsters
and go.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Man, you just can't
help yourself, can you?
- You brought
the whole team this time.
That wasn't very smart, was it?
- Oh, this guy sucks.
I can see why you want
to bring him down so badly.
- Do yourself a favor,
give it up.
There's nowhere
for you to go.
- You can't out-trick
all of us, Kadabra.
- I think I just did.
- He's a hologram.
- Upon further inspection,
there was some rather odd
particulate residue
found at Stagg Industries.
- Yeah, that's
the nanotechnology
that Gypsy was
talking about.
- But what's it made
out of?
- Not exactly sure.
It's definitely organic,
but it seems to have
some sort of metallic
hydrogen properties.
Frankly, it's...
- Beyond your understanding.
- You make a move,
you'll regret it.
- Do you know how many times
I've heard that, Detective?
Told you.
- Damn it.
- [groans]
- Go, go, go!
[dramatic music]
- Guys, move to the side.
♪ ♪
- Now...I can get
what I came for.
[grunts]
- Everybody okay?
Magic or tech, doesn't matter.
You're not getting out of these.
- Maybe not.
[panting]
You let me go, I will tell you
Savitar's greatest secret.
It's the key to defeating him,
the key to stopping him.
- What secret?
- I know who he is.
I know his name.
[dramatic music]
- Hand him over!
♪ ♪
- Why'd you lock him up?
I'm taking him
right back to my Earth.
- Okay, but I need to talk
to him first.
- Fine.
Get what you need from him,
but when you're done,
he's mine.
You are gonna die
for all the things you've done.
I cannot wait to see you
be put to death.
- Uh, I'm gonna
talk to her.
Gypsy, darling?
- You said you know
who Savitar is.
- I know everything
about the God of Speed,
hallowed be his name.
- Like what?
- That he's unstoppable,
that he was
the first speedster,
and that you defeat him,
but not until after he takes
what matters the most to you...
Iris West.
- Tell us who he is, now!
- I don't think so.
It's frustrating, isn't it,
knowing that you're going to die
unless I give The Flash
what he wants.
All that power,
all that speed,
and yet you're still
too slow.
- This isn't a game
or a trick.
This is about
my daughter's life.
- And it's my life
if you hand me over
to that collector.
It's simple.
Let me out, and I'll tell you
who Savitar is.
Give me to Gypsy,
and Iris dies.
The decision lies
with you, Barry.
- Guys, we can't let Gypsy
take him
before we find out
who Savitar is.
- No, we cannot.
- Then what are we
supposed to do?
- I don't know.
- What is it with you
and this guy?
It's like you're hell-bent
on taking him back with you.
- He killed a lot of people
on Earth-19.
- He's killed people
here too.
- No one you know
or care about.
- Did he take somebody
from you?
Hey.
Is that what
this is about?
- What this is about,
Cisco,
is he needs to be
brought to justice,
and I am not gonna let
anything or anyone
prevent me
from doing that.
- [groans]
- You're lucky.
This could've been
a lot worse.
- [groans]
I'm fine, really.
It's merely a flesh wound,
as the "Monty Python" boys
would say.
Anyway, thanks
for patching me up.
- Of course.
- [groans]
- Listen, I've been
trying to find
the right time
to say this, and...
now seems to be
as good a time as any.
I was so focused on not hurting
you as Killer Frost
that I forgot that I could
hurt you as Caitlin Snow,
and for that
I'm very sorry.
So I understand if you don't
trust me anymore, but...
maybe you can find it
in your heart to forgive me?
You're good to go.
[footsteps approaching]
- Thank you.
We're gonna figure
this out, Barry.
- A guy like Kadabra,
he should have no say
whether you live or die.
- How do you even know
that he's telling the truth?
I mean, he's done nothing
but tricks since he got here.
I mean, maybe...maybe
this is one of them.
- It's not, Iris.
- So...what,
you want to let him go?
- [sighs] I mean, it just feels
like our only move.
- He's a murderer.
- [scoffs]
I know he's a murderer,
but I mean, how many murderers
have we put in prison?
How many bad guys have we
taken down?
I mean, don't we
deserve one win
after everything
that we've done?
- Life doesn't keep score,
Barry.
You should know that
better than anyone.
Look, even if Kadabra
hadn't showed up,
we'd still be in the same place
we are right now.
- But he did,
and if he knows
who Savitar is,
he's gonna tell us.
- Barry...
- Iris, he can save your life.
- No, you can
save my life.
Not him.
- [sighs]
- Trust me,
I want to find out
who Savitar is
just as badly as you do.
But I don't want to let someone
who has caused so much pain
walk free
just to save my life.
You know, deep down,
I don't think you
want that either.
[intrigue music]
♪ ♪
- I knew you'd come.
'Cause you're the only person
who's willing to do...
anything.
- What do you want?
- To be set free.
- Murdering people,
stealing smart tech.
You came here
for something.
- Told you before,
Detective,
it is beyond your
understanding.
- This is
about my daughter's life.
It's as simple as that
for me.
You tell me
who Savitar is,
and I will let you go.
You don't,
you're going with Gypsy.
- A leap of faith
for us both then.
[dramatic music]
Open the door.
- If you take one step
before you tell me,
I will blow you away.
Understood?
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
- But you do not know this guy.
- Great timing!
- What is that?
[dramatic music]
No.
- Gypsy!
- Give me the name.
♪ ♪
The name, now!
- Savitar...is...
- No!
What the hell are you doing?
- He was about to tell me
who Savitar is!
- Damn it!
- Kadabra's on the loose!
He's somewhere in the building!
♪ ♪
- And there we are.
[sighs]
Thank you, Doctor Wells.
♪ ♪
- Joe, he's headed
for the elevator!
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
- We had a deal.
Your freedom
for Savitar's identity.
- I've altered the terms
of our agreement.
It appears that you have
as well.
- Move!
- [coughing]
[panting]
Caitlin! Caitlin,
are you all right?
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- I'm okay.
Okay, I'm okay.
[groans]
- Okay, okay, easy.
- [groans]
- Okay, easy.
- [groaning]
- Come on.
- Gentle, gentle.
- Yeah, yeah, yup.
- The...
the...hand me
the x-ray machine,
grab it for us,
would you, please?
- Yup.
- [groaning]
- Here, here.
- Okay, good.
remove it.
- How bad is it?
- Uh, it's bad.
It's bad, there's quite a few
pieces of shrapnel inside you,
and they look deep enough
to pierce your kidney
if they're not
removed immediately.
- [groans]
- Guys, we have to get her
to a hospital.
- We can't, they're gonna
ID her as a meta.
- And not just any meta.
- Yeah, one that we have
a file on for attacking CCPD.
- Then what are we going to do?
None of us are doctors
and she can't operate
on herself.
- We do have
another option.
- What is it?
- When Caitlin goes meta,
her metabolic rate
offsets cold
tissue destruction.
- She can regenerate?
- No, we're not gonna
take off my necklace.
I don't need a hospital.
All I need is a mirror
and a steady set of hands.
You were a field medic
in the Royal Army, right?
- What? No, I-I-I've never
operated on anyone before.
- That's okay,
I'll walk you through it.
- Caitlin, you're talking
about staying awake
during your own surgery.
- I'm putting my life
in your hands.
I trust you, Julian.
- What the hell
were you thinking?
- Now is not the time,
Gypsy.
- You know, you got a really
messed up sense of justice
for a cop?
- Watch yourself.
I took two oaths
in my life.
One, to uphold the law.
The other, to protect my family.
Guess which one
takes priority?
- That was my prisoner.
- He was my prisoner too,
and you're on my Earth.
He has information that could
save Iris's life,
so I don't give a damn!
It's because of you
he's on the loose.
- Because of me?
No, no, because of you.
You opened that door!
You let him out!
That is on you,
Detective!
How much of that
did you hear?
- I heard enough.
This is my friend.
It's the man's daughter.
I mean, wouldn't you do that
for someone you cared about?
- I am doing that,
you idiot!
- Okay, what does that mean?
For who?
Who are you talking about?
- I used to have
a partner.
- Like, a "partner"
or...like a partner?
- Both.
It was a long time ago,
Cisco.
It's not like I'm burning
a candle for the guy,
but he did mean
something to me.
It's been three years since
Abra Kadabra shot him dead.
- I'm sorry.
- I have been searching
for him ever since,
and he finally
showed back up.
Ten minutes ago,
I had him dead to rights,
and then your friend
messed it all up.
So yes, I do know
what it is like
to care about someone so much
that you break the rules.
That's why I have to find
this guy, no matter what,
and when I do,
he is gonna pay for what he did.
No more delays.
- Ready?
- Ready as I'll ever be.
- Okay, let's start
with the shrapnel
on the surface.
- Okey-dokey.
- [inhales sharply]
- Just let me know if I do
any...thing
wrong, okay?
- [groans]
- [grunts]
- Okay, that's the first bit.
Well done.
Okay.
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [inhales sharply]
- Is there supposed to be
this much blood?
- It's normal for the shrapnel
to cavitate
and displace tissue,
but if I lose too much blood,
I'll start hemorrhaging.
- Okay.
- [inhales sharply]
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
- [inhales sharply]
- All right, nearly done,
nearly done, hang in there,
hang in there.
- [whimpers]
- Okay, well done.
Well done, that's all the pieces
of shrapnel
from the surface gone.
- Okay, great.
Now it's time for the hard one.
But you're doing great.
You got this, okay, Julian?
- Yes.
- It's wedged between my kidney
and my inferior vena cava,
and it's surrounded
by some major blood vessels.
If you hit them,
there's a good chance
I'll go into shock.
- Shock?
- But it's okay.
You've got this.
- Okay.
All right.
- [groans]
- Heart rate's increasing.
- Okay, I think I've got it.
- Great, pull it out.
- I can't, Caitlin,
it's stuck.
- Then turn it.
- [scoffs]
- Guys, it's getting
up there.
- It might be
a tendon in the way.
- If it's not a tendon...
- Then I will rip
this necklace off.
- No!
I would rather die.
- Caitlin, this is
going to hurt.
- [screams]
- [grunts]
- Ahh.
- Ohh!
- [laughs]
- [whimpers]
Can you please
stitch me up,
because I think I need
to pass out?
- Yes, yes.
Of course, of course.
Well done, well done.
- She's gonna be
all right.
- Thank God.
- That really was
amazing, Julian.
- Seriously.
Julian Albert, MD.
- Hey, I think I know
why Abra Kadabra's been
stealing all that tech.
- Why?
- Build a time machine.
[dramatic music]
- He's trying to get back
to the future.
♪ ♪
[energetic music]
- Presto.
♪ ♪
- What is that thing
in his hands?
- Everything Kadabra's
been stealing,
these are the exact components
I used to build
Evil Wells's time sphere
two years ago,
but I could never figure out
what he used for a power source.
I think this is it.
- So that's what he took
from the time vault,
its power source?
- Last thing he needs to return
to the 64th century.
- Well, we need
to find his ass
before he pulls
another disappearing act.
- If Kadabra's plan is
to "Marty McFly" himself
back to the future...
- He's gonna have to open
a temporal wormhole first,
and when he does...
- We can nail him.
- Mm-hmm.
- No, he's mine.
I look forward to showing him
the same mercy
he showed my partner.
- Hey, Gypsy.
You can't go
after him alone.
- Sure I can.
- You want justice for all
those people that he's hurt,
for your partner, right?
Right now we're trying
to prevent someone we love
from getting hurt, but we can't
do that without your help.
- I don't trust
you guys anymore.
- Kadabra's already given
both of us the slip.
He does it again
through time,
I don't think we get
this opportunity back.
Only way we catch him
is together.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Guys, Abra Kadabra's heading
south on Ninth.
- He opened up a wormhole.
- What do you say?
♪ ♪
- We can't let him
get past us.
- We're not gonna do that.
- Catch me if you can.
- Where's he at?
- He's on State and Main!
[car horn honks]
[tires screeching]
- We're on it!
You shall not pass!
- Ah!
- Oka, now he's on
Thurlow and Eighth.
We're gonna lose him.
- No, we're not.
He's on Seventh,
and he's moving fast!
You gotta stop this guy.
- Time to go home.
- Bar, he opened up
another wormhole!
- Yes! He did it,
he got him.
- Thank God.
- [grumbles]
- So much for your
disappearing act.
- No!
- By the laws of Earth-19,
I hereby collect you
for the crime
of mass murder.
- Let her take me.
You'll never find out
what I know.
And Iris dies.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
- You've come to see me off.
Really touched.
- What are we gonna do here?
- You're going with her.
I'm not gonna stop her.
- Then you'll never find out
what you want to know.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- I have nothing
to offer you.
No reprieve.
No escape for what
you're facing.
You've done
some terrible things.
But you are still a man.
You have a family,
friends, people
that you care about.
Somewhere inside of you
there must be
a glimmer of light,
of hope.
It's that part of you
that I'm asking.
I'm begging.
Help me save her.
- Flash.
Begging.
[chuckles]
See, here it is.
In the future, you and I
have been enemies for years.
Oh, there have been others,
of course.
There was Thawne,
Zoom, DeVoe,
but none of them hurt you
like Savitar.
He truly broke you.
I have to be honest.
I was always
a little bit jealous.
But now, it's like
I get to kill her too.
If you'll excuse me,
I have my execution to attend.
- Where does this leave us?
- I don't know.
- Cisco, I...
- [whispering] Hey.
- I'm still here.
- Yeah.
Wasn't gonna let you
go that easy.
- Kadabra?
- He's gone.
He's gone for
good, apparently.
- Sorry.
My palm's are sweaty.
- It's quite all right.
Honestly, my stitch work
may leave
quite a lot to be
desired, so.
- It's okay.
I was never much
of a two-piece bathing suit
kind of gal anyway.
- I cannot believe
what you did, Caitlin.
I mean, staying awake
during your own surgery,
that's one thing,
but talking my clumsy hands
through it,
that's quite the other.
You are immensely brave.
You fought through the pain
like I've never seen
anyone before.
- You did all the hard work.
- [laughs]
Hardly.
- You going soft on me,
Julian?
- Yes.
Absolutely.
- [inhales sharply]
- [gasps]
I'm so terribly sorry.
- [chuckles]
- That's most clumsy of me.
- Some bedside manner
you got there.
- I'm working on it.
[both laughing]
- Just rest.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Easy.
- Sorry.
I should've
been stronger.
- You think you should've
shot Kadabra?
Dad, I think you showed
true strength by letting him go.
- I try to be strong
for you guys,
for you and Wally
and Barry.
- Dad, you have been,
and it makes me
stronger too.
- When you were a baby,
I was...
I was terrified
that you might die
in the middle of the night.
I just didn't sleep.
I would just...
sit in your room...
and watch you sleep.
I put my hand
on your chest,
just to make sure
you were breathing,
and then I...
I would just sit there there,
praying that...
you'd just keep breathing.
That's how I feel
right now.
I don't know what I can do
to save you.
- I know how to save her.
- What?
Kadabra, Savitar, Thawne.
You know, they're always
one step ahead of us...
for one reason...
they know what's
gonna happen.
[energetic music]
So every move we make,
every trap we try and set,
it's all just history
to them.
They're armed
with the future.
Well, not anymore.
- What does that mean?
- If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
I'm gonna run
to the future.
♪ ♪
[indistinct TV chatter]
- [gasps] Mmm.
- No more strawberry.
- What do you mean,
there's no more strawberry?
I just bought some,
like, a week ago.
- Yeah, well,
I may have eaten some,
slash...all.
- Cisco.
- Do you want me to go out
and get you
more strawberry Jell-O?
I will get you more.
- No, it's fine,
but next time I operate on you,
you're getting bupkes, mister.
- Mm, next time you
operate on me,
maybe you can...
fix my broken heart.
- I'm sorry it didn't work out
with you and Gypsy.
- If two meta-humans
from two different universes
with the same
vibrational powers
can't make it work,
then what hope is there?
[door opening]
- There you guys are.
I've been looking
all over for...
what are you doing in bed?
- It's a long story, H.R.
- I have a long story.
- Yeah, how about you tell us
where you've been?
- Her name is Rhonda,
and she's into new positions.
We had the...
- Okay. Oh, my God.
Stop talking.
You gotta let somebody know
next time you decide to go
on a two-day love romp.
- Who was worried about me?
He was.
I'm touched.
- You'll be touched in the face
with a hammer
the next time you pull
something like that.
- Guys, stop it.
Don't make me laugh,
or I'll bust my stitches.
- [gasps]
Is that lime Jell-O?
- It's all you, H.R.
- Are you serious?
Ah, ha ha ha ha!
I...love the lime.
I love the lime!
- You were really worried
about him, weren't you?
- Just promise me that
you'll never ever tell him.
- [chuckles]
Cross my heart
and hope to...
[ominous music]
[life-support machine beeping]
- Caitlin?
Hey!
[dramatic music]
Caitlin? Caitlin?
Somebody help!
- [panting] W-w-what happened?
What happened?
- I don't know,
she just started seizing.
- Hold her down,
hold her down.
Hey, H.R., grab her legs.
Hold her down!
- What...what's happening?
[beeps]
- She's not breathing.
- We have to get an ambulance
in here right now.
- H.R., grab the crash cart.
Cisco, grab the oxygen.
Wheel it over here!
♪ ♪
Slow and steady,
over her mouth.
Okay, good.
Come on, slow and steady,
that's it.
That's it.
- What's happening?
- She may have threw
a blood clot, I don't know.
- Julian!
- Charge the paddles!
- Okay...
- Give me the paddles!
- Charging, you're good.
- Okay, give me the...
give it here.
Clear.
[grunts]
[panting]
All the way,
turn it up to the top!
All the way up!
- Okay, you're ready.
- Clear.
- Clear, clear, clear.
[machine charging]
- Char...go.
[ominous music]
- She's gotta...
keep going.
- Come on, Caitlin,
come on!
♪ ♪
- Keep going,
just keep going.
Uh, here, take this.
Here we go,
she's coming back.
She's coming back.
Yes, she is.
[flatline tone]
Come on.
Here she comes.
Come on!
Don't stop.
Please.
♪ ♪
Please don't stop.
[sobs]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
- [sobs]
- She's gone.
♪ ♪
- Stop!
That's not what she wanted!
- I don't care!
I'm not gonna sit here
and watch her die, okay?
Okay?
It's all right, mate,
it's okay.
[flatline tone]
It's okay.
[beeping]
- Caitlin?
[beeps]
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- Huh.
- [exhales]
[ominous music]
[fast beeping]
♪ ♪
- Caitlin.
- Greg, move your head.