Previously, on "The Flash"...
I can do some cool things,
you know.
Sometimes I run so fast,
I reverse time a bit.
Dark and Stormy on the house.
Do I look that pathetic?
You look like you belong here
about as much as I do.
- Cisco.
- Kamilla.
We may have found a way
to suppress the meta genome.
Great, then we can use it
to de-power Cicada,
- stop him for good.
- Who the hell are you?
I'm a reporter.
We're gonna beat you.
Damn, you're good,
real good.
Maybe too good.
We did it.
We did it!
Oh, my.
Cisco Ramon,
tonight you've got yourself
a hot date and a meta-human cure.
We're unstoppable.
Ooh, shrap...
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
We have to wait how long
before we can use
the meta-human cure?
Not even that long.
- Cisco.
- It's gonna go by like that.
Cisco.
- 29 days.
- A month?
- I know, right?
- Just one, teeny, tiny, month
until we stop Cicada's purge.
You know,
historically speaking,
this is way faster
than we've ever
stopped a big bad so...
- We can't wait that long.
- If he finds another meta
or comes after us... we have
to speed this up somehow.
We have to wait for the
compound to fully synthesize
or it won't be able to
effectively neutralize
the dark matter in
a meta-human's pituitary gland.
Without any way to expedite
the exotic evolution...
Barry, we're gonna have to wait.
I think we have to wait.
Unless...
you took it into
the Speed Force.
- Hmm?
- What, you want him to go into
the Speed Force for a month
and then, what,
come out the same
day that he left?
Oh, no, no, I'm not saying
you manipulate time.
I'm saying you manipulate
dark matter.
So very simple.
It's simple chemistry, right?
When you are synthesizing
a compound, you use a...
Commodity, uh, substrate, uh...
- A catalyst?
- Catalyst, right.
And the most efficient catalyst
you can use when synthesizing
a compound that negates
dark matter
is superluminal particles.
- Tachyons?
- Très bien.
Tachyons, and the place where
tachyons are the most dense?
- Speed Force.
- And voilà.
That might actually work.
- Yeah, it will.
- It'll be like nuking it
in a pan-dimensional microwave.
- Nice work.
- I know.
So how much time
would this save?
From 29 days down to 60 minutes.
Yeah, it's gonna be faster.
And also since Cicada
has been quiet
since your last encounter,
maybe there's no time
like the present.
- Do it.
- All right.
I'll see you in an hour.
Nora, you need to stay here.
You don't want my help?
- I just...
- I got this one this time.
Are you sure that now
is a good time to go?
I mean, I just mean,
the city will be Flash-less,
and an hour is a long time
to be without the Flash.
The city is not gonna be
Flash-less. It'll have XS.
Yeah, but what about the time
you had to spend 24 hours
in the Pipeline cell and
Weather Witch and Silver Ghost
- stole that A.R.G.U.S. car...
- And you stopped them
without me.
Eh, with what happened to Mom
because of Cicada...
Iris, it's fine, and this
is the key to stopping Cicada.
I gotta go.
If anything happens,
just do what
I've trained you to do:
Slow down and think clearly.
- Yeah.
- I trust you,
you just gotta trust yourself.
You'll be fine.
60 minutes.
Nora, Cisco hasn't left
for his date yet, has he?
Uh, I don't think so.
Great, we get another
chance at this.
Well, it is... that's why
you don't do it.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Oh, God.
- Not the "Book of Ralph" again!
- Yeah, buddy.
- You successfully completed
my 27 steps to getting over
the love of your life.
Gypsy is in the past.
You have a new siren,
so now it's time for...
"The Art of Love."
Um, Caitlin?
I've gotta finish working on
the device to inject the cure.
Also I have to inject
the device for the cure.
I... I... I... Iris?
Oh, no, this is all you, man.
I got an article I gotta write.
Let me know when Barry
gets back.
Help Me.
"Chapter one: Initial Planning."
Initial planning?
It's a first date, Sun Tzu,
- not an incursion.
- Trust me, Grasshopper,
love is war, but, fine,
if you wanna skip
to chapter six,
"Know Your Terrain."
- We're meeting at Jitters.
- Ah, familiar territory.
You are learning.
Uh, you know,
he really should be going.
- I really should.
- Hang on, hang on one second.
This one's really important.
Chapter thirteen,
"Intelligence and Reconnaissance."
- Wh...
- You cyber-stalked Kamilla?
No, no, no, no, of course not.
That's her public profile.
But it did happen to have
some info
on the types of guys
that she might be into.
The types of guys
that she's into?
Yes, and, unfortunately,
you are nothing like them,
but, hey, if you don't wanna
get a second date, be my guest.
Just don't come crying to me
when everything inevitably
goes horribly, horribly wrong
and you die alone.
No big deal.
See, now he's in my head.
Okay, no thank you.
I didn't take these.
- You saw nothing.
- Nothing.
One Cicada on the bar for Ian?
- It's I-an.
- Sorry, I-an.
Hey, Kamilla.
- Cisco.
- Wow.
- Sorry I'm late.
- I got held up at a meeting.
- That's okay.
- I just got here.
If I'd had known,
I would have dressed up more.
Oh, this old thing?
No, please,
this is work clothes.
You have to wear a suit
to your lab?
My lab?
When we met at the bar,
you were talking about
DNA and genomes,
so I assumed you were
some kind of scientist.
Right, I said that, scientist.
Yes. No. Well,
I'm what you would call
a science businessman.
So, what, you make money off
of other people's discoveries?
Well, somebody has to.
It's just a little joke,
something I always say.
So, uh, what is the name
of the company you work for?
It's called Ramon Industries.
It's named after yourself?
That's humble.
Maybe I should grab us
a couple coffees.
Sure.
- Decaf Flash.
- Decaf Flash, right, okay.
You're not the only one
who does their research.
I know who you are,
Iris West-Allen.
I know you work with the Flash
and the other heroes.
You said you were gonna beat me,
but tonight, I'm gonna beat you,
all of you.
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
- That's the decaf.
- Men in this city...
Tell me about it.
- Uh, I'm sorry, it's work.
- I have to go.
Uh, could we just have,
like, a do-over, please?
It's Mom.
Get away from her.
She's not who you want.
No, she's not, but you are.
Then come and get us.
Ah!
Caitlin!
Told ya.
Nora, Cisco hasn't left
for his date yet, has he?
Uh, I don't think so.
Great, I get another chance
at this.
We do.
What's wrong?
- Nora?
- Nothing.
Come on,
you can figure this out.
Not the "Book of Ralph" again!
Yeah, buddy, you successfully
completed my 27 steps
to getting over
the love of your life.
Gypsy is in the past.
You have a new siren,
so now it's time for
"The Art of Love."
Um, Caitlin?
I gotta go work on the device
to inject the cure.
Also I have to devise the cure.
I... I... I... Iris?
Ooh, nah, that's all you, man.
I gotta go write an article.
Let me know
when Barry gets back.
- Uh, no, you know what?
- Don't go.
Uh, why don't you write
the article here?
Uh, I can make you coffee.
I mean, I know that there's
coffee over there, but I...
I just think it's really
important for the team leader
to stay here until Dad gets back
just in case something
happens, okay?
Okay, lounge it is.
All right, "chapter one:
Initial Planning."
It's a first date, Sun Tzu,
not an incursion.
Trust me, Grasshopper,
love is war.
Yeah, and I couldn't agree
more so read these.
They'll help you,
and you'll know what to do.
- Wait, wait, how...
- And if anything goes wrong,
just give us a call.
You and I are gonna stay here
and have our own coffees
in the lounge.
There's brownies.
- Brownies?
- Yes.
Ralph, did you cyber-stalk her?
You were talking about
DNA and genomes.
I thought I'd finally met
a guy who was more concerned
with flexing his brain
than his muscles.
Ca va?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Sorry, I just...
I'm having the most
wicked déjà vu right now.
Is that right?
Why don't you want your
mother to come here, hmm?
Because you time-travel.
- It's I-an.
- Sorry, I-an.
Kamilla tha thrilla.
Cisco?
- Wow.
- Sorry I'm late.
I just came from a photoshoot.
The things you do
for the 'gram, am I right?
Hey, maybe next time you should
be my photographer.
What do you think?
So you're a...
I'm an aspiring
social media influencer.
This is my card.
You can keep that.
When we met at the bar,
you were talking about
DNA and genomes,
so I assumed you were
some kind of scientist.
Really?
When we met at the bar,
you were talking about
DNA and genomes, so I...
You assumed
I was some kind of scientist?
Yeah, exactly.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm just having
some déjà vu again.
Maybe I should grab us
a couple of coffees?
- Oh, yes.
- Yes, that'd be great.
Will you get me a Zoom, please?
Okay.
What?
Okay, here we go.
Thanks.
- One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
- Thank you.
Something's wrong,
- and I think I have to go.
- Right now?
No, right now.
Yep, gotta go.
Um, I'd ask if we could have
a do-over, but, um, something
tells me I already have.
- The men in this city.
- Tell me about it.
- Come on!
- It's Sherloque.
What? I thought he was here
with Caitlin.
- We gotta get Frost.
- No, no, I got this.
You guys just stay here.
- Garçon, look out!
- Ah!
Told ya.
Cisco!
Why can't I fix this?
Ugh! Why can't
I go back any further?
- Nora?
- Cisco hasn't left yet.
Great.
So we get another
chance at this.
We do.
I'm fine, Sherloque.
I have to fix this.
Okay,
you guys have to stay here.
- Why?
- Because Dad put his trust
in me that I would protect
all of you
and I'm the only speedster here
for the first time
and if something were to go
wrong, I don't know
if I could fix it, in fact,
I'm pretty sure that I couldn't
fix it, so just,
for one hour, stay here.
I have to go finish...
- No, no!
- I got a date with...
Were you cyber-stalking Kamilla?
No, no, no, of course not.
This is her public profile.
You were talking
about DNA and genomes,
so I thought I'd finally met a guy
who is more concerned with
his brain than his muscles.
- Kamilla.
- Oh, I got some details on
- the kinds of guys she's into.
- Mm-mm.
Wait,
were you cyber-stalking her?
- No, I'm not stalking her.
- It's her public profile.
Guys! I'm sorry, but you're
just gonna have to stay here.
- I-an.
- Sorry, I-an.
You have got to be kidding me.
You got the first one.
- I got the next one.
- I think we all got one.
What did you get?
- It's Cecile.
- Guys, um, just stay here.
Told ya.
Nora?
I was supposed to protect you,
but I can't.
I don't know how to.
But my dad does.
I can't get into
the Speed Force either?
You're reversing time,
aren't you?
And I can't fix it.
- So all of us die?
- Sometimes,
or just one of you.
Sometimes Cecile, but every
time, there's at least one.
I thought I was having déjà vu.
I keep seeing my date
with Kamilla again and again,
me failing miserably
every time by using these.
I'm not having déjà vu.
I'm vibing the past hour
over and over.
Yeah.
How many times
has this happened?
- 52.
- 52?
This is one
of those fixed points
the Legends theorized, isn't it?
There's no way to
keep one of us from dying.
- We have to get Barry.
- No, I tried that,
but there's something
wrong with me.
I can't get into
the Speed Force.
Well, then we'll just wait
here until he gets back.
No, if we do that,
Cicada will kill Cecile.
So just reverse time
and go back to before he left.
No, I've tried that too,
but I can't control it.
It doesn't matter what I try
to do. Nothing works!
Believe it or not,
this ain't the first time
I've died in a past timeline.
Ah, I once got a vibrating hand
through the chest
courtesy of Eobard Thawne.
Well, more than once.
I actually kept vibing
that moment until I realized
that it actually happened.
I guess I should have known
the same thing
was happening now, huh?
I keep trying my absolute
hardest to change the outcome,
but I end up failing every time.
What if we can't fix this,
Cisco?
Nora, sometimes we fail because
all we worry about is not failing.
I'm so worried about
my first date since Cynthia
that I don't feel free to be
myself around Kamilla,
and then I'll just end up
screwing it up even more.
This... this intelligence
and reconnaissance mess,
I don't need this.
All I need is to be myself.
Duh! And I sure as hell
don't need to dress up like Ozone
just to impress Kamilla.
Sorry, that is
an outdated reference.
No, from the movie
"Breakin'."
Yeah, I've seen
"Electric Boogaloo" too.
I've seen them both,
like, a hundred times.
I know every move.
Wow, fangirl.
Wait.
Wait, that's it.
Every time I fail,
I take notes in my journal
so I can do something
different the next time.
We know every move.
So all you need to do
is just tell us
everything you've done
and how it went wrong.
So we can figure out
how to make it right.
52 kidnappings, 52 combinations
leading to 52 deaths.
- None of them were Cicada's?
- Exactly.
Yes, exactly.
Wait, does that mean you want
to use Cicada's dagger
against him by having Nora
reverse time?
That's exactly
what I'm suggesting.
Yeah, but how are we
gonna do that?
I mean, Nora can't control it
when she reverses time.
She could control her abilities
if we help her slow down.
Slowing it down.
If she can do that,
we bring the fight to him.
And we all live
through the night.
I like the sound of that.
Well, we have
everything we need.
- Looking for me?
- I know you did your research.
You know who I am,
that I work for the Flash
and the other heroes.
I told you
we were gonna beat you,
and tonight we will...
All of us.
Allez, now!
Ah!
Told you.
No Dark matter anywhere.
Dwyer's gone, again.
Maybe after the ass kicking
he just got,
he'll think twice
before coming after us again.
And if he doesn't think
twice, now you can make him.
Thanks for helping me
slow it down.
Now that I've experienced
a sense of control,
maybe next time,
I can do it on my own.
Thank you for saving us,
all of us.
I didn't save everything.
Maybe you can now?
No, no, that date is over.
There's no way Kamilla's
still at Jitters.
Well, if she is still there,
there might be some stuff
in here that can help you
smooth things over.
But, you can handle it.
You're Cisco Ramon.
Come on,
you gotta get a move on.
Okay.
- Giddyap, Romeo.
- I'm moving.
Okay.
- Sherloque was right.
- One hour, it's cooked.
Something happen
while I was gone?
Kid Flash on the bar for Steven?
- It's Stephan.
- Sorry, Stephan.
- Kamilla, hey.
- Cisco, wow.
- I am so sorry I'm late.
- I had an emergency at work.
It's okay, I just got here.
So you're a scientist, right?
When we were at the bar,
you were talking about
DNA and genomes, so...
Well...
I'm more of a tech nerd,
actually, but the project
that we're working on now,
it gets very scientific.
You sound like
you're really excited about it.
- Oh, my God, I am.
- I'm so excited about it.
You have no idea, um.
I think we might have made
a breakthrough recently,
a breakthrough that could
change a lot of lives.
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
I hope you don't mind,
I called it in ahead of time.
It's the least I could do.
- That's the decaf.
- How did you know what I like?
I had a feeling.
Not like most of the men
in this city.
Tell me about it.
Listen, I know I screwed up
royally showing up late
like this, but it would make me
very happy if...
Can we just
have a do-over, please?
That sounds nice.
52 times?
53, if you include now.
That's a lot.
What was I supposed to do,
let one of them die?
The thing is, Nora, there are
consequences to time travel.
- Oh, I know.
- No, you don't,
not like I do.
Let me show you something.
Imagine this coffee cup
is the space/time continuum.
Whenever you go back in time,
it breaks.
Now, you can try and reset
the timeline,
try and fix it, but no matter
how hard you try,
it's never
gonna be exactly how it was.
It seems like things worked
out this time,
but that's not
always gonna be true,
and it's impossible to know how
these changes are gonna unfold,
the ripples you'll cause,
whose life you're gonna affect.
No one can do that.
No one?
No one.
We're not gods, Nora.
We've just been given
extraordinary abilities.
Thawne, I need to know we're
not making this worse.
Tell me you know
what you're doing.
I am the only speedster
who knows what he's doing!
Stick with the plan.
Follow my instructions
and we'll defeat Cicada,
we'll destroy his dagger,
and then we will
save your father.