You're probably all wondering
why I called this team meeting
at 9:00 a.m., on a Saturday.
- Babe, we should've brought breakfast.
- It's fine. No one's hungry.
Ignore that.
I could get Belgian waffles
from Brussels.
- Yum, that sounds good.
- Yeah?
- Should I do it?
- Barry, the best waffles...
No, no, no. Don't do that.
As much as I hate to say it...
waffles can wait.
First... there's something
we really need to tell you.
And we wanted our closest friends
to hear it first.
Are you guys pregnant?
Wait, is this about another Big Bad?
I'll call Chester and Allegra.
No. No. And definitely not.
What we wanted to say is...
- we're leaving Central City.
- We're leaving Central City.
When?
Tomorrow.
So, wait, you're...
You're moving?
Yeah. We both realize that we're ready
to start something new.
For me, it's my gallery show in Miami.
And, babe?
You two remember that guy, Chip Cooper?
Yeah. The A.R.G.U.S. director
of technology and science.
Well, he's been reassigned to CEMA.
The "Cosmic Emergency
Management Agency."
Wow. I really am the biggest nerd here.
Anyway, Chip's leaving.
And thanks to a great recommendation
from Lyla and Digg, uh...
A.R.G.U.S. offered me the job.
The thing is,
they really need me, like, yesterday.
Yeah. I will be
joining Cisco in Star City
as soon as my exhibition is done.
Look, I know this is super short notice,
but they're both great
opportunities for us.
And we just hope you guys understand.
Of course we do. Yeah, it's great!
- This is great, man.
- So great! We're so happy!
Yeah.
You guys must have so much to do.
Um, I just have to show Chester a couple
things, and then finish packing, but...
Whatever you need, just let us know.
Of course.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
Cool. Thanks.
- Okay.
- All right, congrats.
- Thank you.
- Woo-hoo! Yay!
- That went way better than expected.
- Yeah.
Sweet Sarah E. Goode.
This room has been here the whole time?
Yep.
And I kind of haven't done inventory
in six years, so...
Speed treadmill.
No way.
Yeah.
Yes!
Cool, cool, cool.
Freeze.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
I don't even know what this is,
but it's so cool.
The Thinker's chair?
This is the droid I've been looking for.
Hey, what's all this?
You've got a lifetime's worth
of Comic-Con threads in here.
These bad boys are all coming with me...
- Mm.
- ...but the rest...
The rest is all yours.
Whoa!
Dude.
I'm really gonna miss you, man.
Team Chesco and all that.
Sorry, I know I got to be the zillionth
person to be getting all sappy on you.
You know, actually...
everyone else seems
to be taking the news really well.
Maybe it just didn't sink in yet.
I mean, because, dude...
this is the end of an era.
It is the end of an era.
You are so right, Ches.
This is such a big deal,
that people just...
probably need a little more time
to process it.
Yeah, they just need to soak it in,
you know?
Ah.
I gotta go pack.
Because an hour from now, we could be
knee deep in Kleenex and tears.
- Am I right?
- I bet.
I'm just gonna spend
the rest of the day here.
Go for it!
What the...
"Happy to help. Barry."
So, I guess that's done.
Wow. That was fast.
Yeah, it helps when your best friend's
the Flash, doesn't it?
Sure does.
Since it's just us...
how are you holding up?
You sure you're doing okay
with everything
that's happening, you know, me leaving?
Oh. Of course. I mean, come on,
A.R.G.U.S. has not one
but three bionic neural integrators.
You are moving on up, my friend.
Yeah, but fancy new toys aside,
if you wanna talk about anything...
Oh, there is something
that I wanted to say.
I knew it. What is it? Lay it on me.
"You suck forever.
But I love you, anyway."
It's from Frost.
She's stuck up in Mom's lab.
She's sorry she couldn't say good bye.
Frost. She kills me. She really does.
Me, too.
Do you remember how I got stuck
in the cryo-vault my first day?
You would have hacked
your way out of there.
We all knew you were a genius
from day one.
Yeah.
Can I have your ID badge?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, sure. Right, right.
Thank you.
And your access codes, too, please.
Yes, ma'am. Happy to help.
Thank you.
So, you'd like
to open an account?
Actually, what I'd like to know...
...is what would make you happy?
Quitting this job. I hate it.
Then do it.
Live your best life.
You know what, I will.
I will record an album,
I'm thinking an EDM/country hybrid.
What do you think?
I think what would make me happy
is a cashier's check
for ten million dollars.
Of course, right away.
- And who shall I make it out to?
- Cash.
And there you go.
Oh.
You're the best.
Well...
Now, I need you to wait here.
Okay.
Say, 30 minutes?
Yeah.
Then you can leave
and never look back.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Yes.
Who says money can't buy happiness?
How much was stolen?
Ten million, but no one stole anything.
Somehow, our suspect got Ellis
to give her a cashier's check.
Then she strolled out of the bank
and drove off in a blue van.
But Ellis was acting so weirdly happy,
I thought I'd check to see
if our suspect used
a neurotoxin on him
and found this instead.
Whoa.
It's a lot of dark matter.
So, we know our thief's a meta.
Now, we just need to figure out
how her powers work.
I can help with that.
She makes people euphoric.
Take a look at Ellis' brain scan.
So, she controls people's
cingulate cortexes.
Yes. Which is why
there's such huge levels
of dopamine and serotonin in his scan.
These levels were definitely enough
to make him loopy
and susceptible to suggestion.
Oh, yeah, he would have done
anything she asked him to do.
But the good news is,
the blissful effects
of her powers wear off
in about 24 hours.
Are you guys debriefing without me?
Hey. Yeah, we didn't wanna bother you.
We figured you'd be busy packing
your apartment... or not.
Yeah, well...
I wouldn't pass up the chance
to solve one last case together,
now, would I?
Cisco, this is just a meta
who makes people happy.
I think Barry and I
can handle it ourselves.
Or...
OG Team Flash can make taking her down
part of our last mission together.
Guys, come on.
I want to do this with you.
Oh, okay. Well, then
that's what we'll do.
Thank you so much.
Good news, boss.
Though I didn't get much
from the badge on site,
I did manage to get quotes from
the eyewitness who saw the perp leave.
Okay, great work. I will send you
my interview with Stanley Ellis.
Can you start on a copy?
I need a thousand words ASAP.
On it. I'm gonna need a photo
to run with the story.
Yeah, of course. I have one of Ellis
giving his statement.
Wait, was Cecile here earlier?
Guess so.
That's Detective Finn. Going to see
if he'll chat on the record. BRB.
Hey, Detective Finn...
Hey, so, about Cisco and me leaving.
I would have told you earlier.
It's just we wanted
to tell you all together.
No, don't worry. We were all so busy.
Iris, you trusted me
to be the eyes of The Citizen.
And that gave me the confidence
to take my career to the next level.
You changed my life
and I'll never forget that,
so, thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, I feel guilty about leaving you
on such short notice.
No, it's fine. Really.
No, it's not.
I know you're seeing new candidates
today, maybe I can help you vet them?
- Yeah, that'd be great. Come on.
- Okay.
I checked out Ellis' brain scan
and I had major déjà vu.
Folks, we've been on this exact
emotional rollercoaster before.
Well, sort of.
Last time, it was Roy G. Bivolo.
But our new meta
makes people happy, not angry.
Enter Rainbow Raider 2.0, which means
we already know how to stop her.
Using that prismatic light grid I built
to reverse Bivolo's whammy effects,
we can use it to neutralize
her meta abilities.
Just remember, don't make eye contact.
Hey, how many gadgets do you think
we've built over the years?
Huh?
Really, when you do the math... that's
a lot of bad guys we've taken down.
You know, when you leave,
you should take all the plans with you.
I'm sure everything you've built
must mean a lot to you.
Yeah, it does.
Satellites got a hit
on the van from the robbery.
Let's do this one last time.
All right. Crime spree's over, Miss.
Step away from the case.
You think I'm a crook?
Uh...
Flash, you've got it all wrong.
Nice leotard, by the way.
Thank you.
Mm. Who's the sidekick?
I'm Mecha-Vibe. And you're toast.
Wanna see a real light show, now?
It's not exactly
Circuit de la Sarthe,
but let's see how fast...
...this baby can go.
Uh...
- Flash?
- Yeah, I'm on it.
Where'd she go?
Where'd she go? She had
a million dollars' worth of jewelry.
Mecha-Vibe?
That's my name. Don't wear it out.
Dude, I'm so happy
to have you in my life.
Okay, this is happening.
On a very public street.
Man, don't be embarrassed.
Embrace it.
Yeah.
- We should probably stop.
- You know I love you, right?
I got my dream job
Gonna go to A.R.G.U.S.
And do some science
Sciency science
At least he's not raging out
and trying to kill us.
Why didn't the prism grid work?
My working theory is that Roy
used one color of the spectrum,
red, to induce anger in his victims.
So many lenses!
But our 2.0 version
uses the whole rainbow.
Since that makes her power
seven times stronger than Roy's,
when Cisco tried using the grid...
And Miami Vice...
She overloaded it
with vibrational energy
from the entire
electromagnetic spectrum.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Ouch.
Speaking of overloaded,
he's gonna be like that till tomorrow.
I'll have the satellites keep searching
for Rainbow Raider 2.0.
Once we get a hit, I'll meta-cuff her
and give her a one-way transport
to Iron Heights.
Okay, great. But what about him?
Hey. I'm doing just fine.
Thanks for asking.
We're going to need a babysitter.
All those applicants... I really thought
we'd meet someone you'd like.
Yeah, me too.
I will try again next week.
What was wrong with Kenji again?
She's super talented
and she seemed really nice.
Kamilla, you know better than anyone,
that we don't just cover
local politics and football scores.
We need someone
who can handle everything.
And I get that.
But even I couldn't handle
everything on day one.
So, maybe expecting everything
from the get-go is asking a bit much.
Okay, I will keep her in mind.
I just want to find the right person.
Totally. But she's not the only
good applicant you passed on today.
I said I would keep her in mind.
I'm sorry. That was harsh.
Uh, no, it's fine.
You don't have to explain.
I've got to go.
So I was thinking,
maybe waffles?
You know I love waffles!
Oh, yeah, you love those...
What are these doing down here, man?
Dude, you know I'm Mecha-Vibe.
You know I had to upgrade the specs,
but it's only 'cause
the convex filtration coating on these
wore off over time.
These poor little buggers,
I'll miss them.
Poor guys.
What else you got going on down
here, man? There's just so much stuff.
All that waffle talk made me hungry.
I gotta eat. BRB.
No.
Chester P. Runkonkoma...
You don't want me to leave
the Starchives?
Okay, fine.
Look, they made me do it because...
I know why you're trying
to keep me down here.
It's because they want to throw me
a surprise going away party.
I...
And to think...
I thought they didn't care.
- Spin move!
- No! Cisco, wait!
Come on, Ches!
Oh, man.
Satellites picked up our perp's van
parked right outside Ferris Airfield.
It's registered to a former
collections officer named Carrie Bates.
There aren't any banks or jewelry stores
out there. What's she up to?
Surprise!
Cisco?
Yeah, sans Chester.
Where are all the balloons at?
Am I early?
I'm early, aren't I?
No sweat, Boba Fett.
It's all hakuna matata.
I know exactly how
to get this party started.
Okay. Get ready. Get ready.
I'm almost there.
No, you get ready...
to laugh!
So cute, but also so funny!
Turn it off, turn it off!
What did you do?
I just turned Flash's happy dial
up to 11 with a little suit upgrade.
Cisco, he can't see.
- Yeah, he can.
- No, I can't. I can't see.
Oops. My bad!
Barry, are you all right?
Cisco, shut it off!
Shut it off!
Okay, Bartholomew.
You all right?
I'm fine.
Chipera...
Looking for me, Red?
You heroes. Always on a mission.
Well, I'm on a mission, too,
and you don't want to stop me.
No.
So, be a happy boy and
enjoy some me-time somewhere else.
Okay.
You okay?
Did you stop the bad lady?
Nope, I didn't want to.
Go, Flash! Go, Flash!
Okay, Barry, why don't we
take a break from the dancing?
Yo, she said "breakdancing!"
You saw how he slid in like that?
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, Flash-dance! He's a maniac.
Yeah! Oh, he's a beast.
Yeah. Yeah.
Since when do you know
how to breakdance?
Since I sped-watched
17 breakdancing videos online.
What up, party people?
My dude.
- I'm sending you that.
- Sending me that.
Chester.
Chester!
Oh, right. Yeah, my bad.
Hey, guys, guys.
Say "cheese!"
- Cheese!
How do you guys feel?
Exhausted.
And a lot less happy.
Chester, how did you cure them?
Okay. So, I figured if we focus
Carrie's full spectrum light particles
through a vibrational filter,
the resulting fractal energy
would counteract the whammy effect.
You know, it's kind of like Vibe
saved the day one last time.
Carrie put a Ferris Air logo on her van.
That must be where she's going next.
I think I know why.
Why?
You see that airship?
It's a stealth dirigible
with a bleeding edge,
auto navigation and a two-ton payload.
And guess where it just got stolen from?
Ferris Airfield.
Why would she steal a blimp?
Maybe it's okay. It's not like
she stole the Death Star, right?
No, but it can cloak itself,
making it untraceable by satellites,
including ours.
Cisco, you're going to be
like a boss at A.R.G.U.S.
so, maybe they've got something
that we don't that could help us out.
Yeah.
Yeah. You know what?
Why don't I just show up
to work a day early,
report for duty and ask them in person?
Why don't I just do that?
I was just...
I need a minute.
Listen, I don't know what's got
you two so ready to get rid of me.
Maybe we should just say goodbye now,
and get it over with.
Cisco, we really messed up.
Big time.
You don't...
want to get rid of me?
No, we don't want to get rid of you.
I mean, we're barely
holding it together.
This whole time, I thought you guys
just didn't care that I was leaving.
We're so sorry
we made you feel that way,
but when you told us,
we both decided to put on a brave face
so we could tackle
one last case together...
so, you could move on...
and your last day
wouldn't be a tear fest.
Caitlin, have you met us?
We're going to miss you so much.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
Honestly, man, I was scared if
we started talking about you leaving...
I would ask you to stay.
And maybe, you actually would.
I couldn't do that to my best friend.
From the second I woke up,
after being hit by lightning,
you've been there.
You were there
every step of this journey.
There wouldn't be a Flash
without Cisco Ramon.
I did build
some pretty rad suits.
You did.
Do you remember when Psych
made us see our worst fears?
Mine was seeing myself
30 years from now.
I was still here...
with the next gen of heroes.
I still had my long hair.
But it was gray.
And everyone else was changing...
and growing.
But not me.
And that scares the hell out of me.
Cisco.
You are a born leader.
You're probably gonna be
running A.R.G.U.S. in no time.
I know.
I am a man on a mission.
What do you say, we figure out why
our thief took that blimp for a joyride,
so, we can wrap up this case
and celebrate?
I think I actually know
what Carrie's plan is.
Barry, you were right.
Carrie's been fired from
six different collection agencies
in the last three months.
- What for?
- Says here,
whenever somebody
had a huge medical debt,
she'd cancel it, instead of collecting.
That makes sense.
Carrie told me
she was on a mission, too.
She didn't steal cash
and diamonds for herself.
She's giving it away
like a Rainbow Robin Hood.
Then what's the blimp for?
She's going to make it rain.
All that money and jewels,
it's gonna be chaos.
As they say,
"It's better to give, than to receive."
The Gotham Goliaths
are feeling small in Central City,
where the Sharks are leading
by 21 points in the fourth quarter.
As if things weren't bad enough,
20,000 screaming football fans are about
to exit Sharks Stadium all at once.
Drunken sports fans
tearing each other apart,
fighting over diamonds and cash
falling from the sky.
We have to find a way
to stop her before it starts.
What about Chester's new toys?
To counter Carrie's rainbow blast,
we need a much more powerful light wave.
One the size of Texas.
Good thing we have one.
That's pretty high.
You sure you can't just fathwoom
us up there?
The ship's hull contains
two tons of compressed hydrogen.
One spark of lightning
could make it explode.
You can do this. You've done it before.
Okay. Hang on to your buns.
Flash?
Come on, Red, give me a break.
I'm just trying
to help ordinary people get ahead.
Go, go.
There's a better way to help people.
Is there? Because folks
are really hurting right now.
Some people can barely put food
on the table, let alone pay rent.
You know why?
Because the system's left them behind.
Those people need help. Real help.
The kind that starts after you're gone.
That's where I step in,
because I care what happens, Flash.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
That's why, instead of sending you
to Iron Heights,
I'm going to recommend you work off
whatever sentence you receive
with Mayor Sampson's
economic development committee.
You're right, Carrie.
The city does need you.
From what I've just heard,
I'm confident you're the right woman
for the job.
You'd do that for me?
My hero.
The auto-navigation control's
been damaged.
Looks like that energy tango
fried the system.
Folks, we got less than two minutes
to impact.
Flash, please tell me you can get us
off this balloon before it explodes
because if I use a tele sphere
with us moving this fast...
We might all end up pancaked
in the nearest sidewalk.
I can try and phase us out of here
without sparking an explosion.
I never wanted to hurt anyone.
Damn it! This thing
is stuck on autopilot.
Guys, 90 seconds.
Get them to safety.
And then evacuate the area.
If this thing crashes,
the hydrogen is going to flash-fry
everything within a two-mile radius.
- No...
- Look, Barry, there's not enough time.
I'm not gonna let you die.
I'm not planning on it! Go!
I got this.
Let's go.
Flash, there's
20,000 people in there and the game...
Will be over any minute, I know.
Chester, what do I need to bypass
a six dorsal propulsion unit?
Uh, I don't know.
What do you have up there?
I have me.
Come on.
You can do it!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
You can do it!
Come on, come on.
Come on!
Yeah!
Dude, there is no word to describe
how awesome you are right now.
Actually, there is.
"He's da bomb."
Hell yeah, I am.
Okay, folks, our hijacked airship
is safely back at Ferris Air.
Where in the hell...
Just go on.
Man, this is supposed
to be my last debrief.
It's cool. It's cool. Just keep going.
Just think of it as Team Chesco,
one last time?
Huh?
Well, looks like
the DA is officially on board...
- Mm-hmm
- ...with Carrie working off
the rest of her sentence
at the mayor's office.
Yeah.
Also, the Sharks beat the Goliaths,
28-to-nothing.
Go, Sharks.
As a bonus, CCPN is reporting
a wave of donations across the city
inspired by Carrie's
"unique brand of charity."
There is going to be a surprise party,
isn't there?
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Actually, there's going to be two.
And they're a little last minute.
But Team Citizen is going to party
with Kamilla at their office,
which means...
That the rest of the team...
Is going to kick it at the loft.
At the loft.
The only missing piece
is the guest of honor, sir.
You.
So, you ready to do this thang?
Not yet.
This has all of my conceptual designs
for S.T.A.R. Labs.
Software fixes,
fortifications with the Time Vault,
Babel upgrades...
You're the man now, dawg.
Thanks, Cisco.
This is...
Wow.
I know I'm leaving this place
in great hands.
You want to drop that off
in your new workshop,
so we can skedaddle?
Whoa!
New workshop?
Seriously?
Yes.
Okay.
Oh. I know that look.
You're going to bail on me,
so you can spend all night
organizing your new stuff
in that space, aren't you?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
But I promise I'll be there
tomorrow morning
at the epic good bye
breakfast at Jitters.
I know you will.
Thanks for showing me the ropes, man.
Keep 'em safe for me, will you?
Roger that.
What are you doing?
- He likes this song.
- How could you possibly know that?
I checked his Facebook page.
It's like everyone else
is standing still.
The party's here.
Supersonic punch, baby! Whoo!
I'll always remember this.
Dr. Wells and I...
- Doppel...
- Ganger.
He'd have to be a Weather Wizard.
Captain Cold. The Mist.
The Turtle. Samuroid.
Now, go.
Serve your higher purpose.
I knew you wouldn't let me down.
How did you know what I like?
I had a feeling.
Cisco, you're a hero, man.
How do you feel?
It's the end of an era.
Yeah.
I'm gonna miss you, too.
I'm gonna miss all this.
Even this drafty old building?
Mm...
Kamilla, you know, about earlier,
I wasn't thinking and I was out of line.
It's okay. I totally get it.
I think it was just hard for me
because I'm not just saying goodbye
to a valuable team member,
I'm saying goodbye to a friend...
and I'm gonna miss you.
So, don't be a stranger.
You got it.
And, Iris, for the record,
from the moment I first met Cisco,
I knew things would be great.
But I had that same feeling coming here
and getting to know you and Allegra.
So, to Team Citizen.
Team Citizen.
Looks like I'm just in time.
- Now, it's a party.
- These are for you.
Thank you.
Hey, what's up with you being
at the crime scene this morning?
Hmm?
Oh, uh, I was meeting up
with an old contact.
There's something I've been
trying to dig up for a case,
and I am finally getting close.
Oh, hey, what do you say,
group selfie, ladies?
- Yes.
- Ready?
One, two, three, cheese!
I'm going to miss
speedster delivery so much.
Like, what am I supposed to do
the next time I get a craving
for Lou Malnati's?
Order online like everyone else?
Like a normie? No, thanks.
I guess you're just gonna
have to come back and visit.
I guess so.
So, you're buying a place in Star City?
That is the plan.
It's a big step.
But I'm proud of you.
Kamilla, too.
And it goes without saying,
you always have a place to stay here.
Thanks, Joe.
Hey, it's me
that should be thanking you.
All these years,
you've always had Barry's back.
You are a good man, Cisco Ramon.
Mm.
We're gonna miss the hell out of you.
Speaking of, I have something
that should help with that.
Whoa!
As a token of how special
you all are to me.
You wore this
on your first day at S.T.A.R. Labs.
What can I say?
From the beginning,
you made me feel right at home.
All right, it's your night.
What you want to do next?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh.
This song?
You know, I didn't even put this
as my favorite song on my Facebook.
- I don't know who did that.
- You already know what time it is.
Don't make me sing.
You know
we're gonna compete, right?
This is my jam, though.
- This is my jam.
Oh, my God.
I wanna hold 'em
Like they do in Texas, please
Okay.
Fold' em, let 'em hit me
Raise it, baby, stay with me
Love game intuition
Play the cards with spades to start
And after he's been
Hooked, I'll play the one
That's on his heart
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'll get him hot, show him what I've got
That's scary.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'll get him hot, show him what I got
Can't read my, can't read my
- Take it.
- Dance break.
Do it!
...poker face
She's got me like nobody
Can't read my, can't read my
No, he can't my
- Poker face
It's my favorite part.
P-p-p-poker face, p-p-poker face
Babe?
Cecile.
I will find you.