- My name is Barry Allen,
and I'm the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created
the alternate timeline
Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline
to how it was,
only to find things
weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats
to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- This has been a really
amazing date, Flash.
- Cecile,
thanks for stopping by.
- Hey, anything for my
favorite detective.
- You restored the timeline,
and things were different?
- Exactly.
- Jesse, you're a speedster.
- When I came back,
things weren't the same.
- You mean people.
- Yeah.
[rousing music]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- How do I look?
- Better.
How much?
- Do we really need to
ask that question?
- Our take wasn't that big.
- Big enough.
But the only question
you should be asking is,
what size rock you want dangling
from this beautiful neck?
A kiss from you
makes my world spin.
- [chuckles]
You're so full of it,
you know that?
- I got to be honest.
I never understood...this.
But like my sister says,
anyone can stoop over
and pick up nothing.
- What do you want, Snart?
- I told you two
to sit on your cut for a while,
until things cool down.
- Some of us like to actually
spend the cash
we get from these jobs.
- Not when it's from the ones
with me.
- You didn't pull 'em off
yourself.
Without us, you'd still be
kicking down liquor stores.
- I think you've spent
too much time
staring at yourself
in the mirror,
because your perception
of reality is a bit warped.
You know the rules.
- I don't give a damn
about your rules,
or laying low.
There's no one in this city
who can stop us.
Including you, Snart.
- It sounds to me like
you're saying you want out.
- Mm.
- Guess so.
- Well, if you're out...
♪ ♪
You're out.
- [laughs softly]
[all grunting]
[gunshot]
[grunting, blows falling]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
- No!
[struggling]
♪ ♪
- You lost, Scudder.
- Sam!
[explosion]
♪ ♪
- Go.
Go!
♪ ♪
- Sam?
- Give me a hand here.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Demo starts in a month.
Get everything out of here.
♪ ♪
The hell?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Where's Snart?
Where's Snart?
- This is from a security camera
inside Iron Heights.
- Forensic analysis indicates
that the footage is genuine,
no evidence of tampering.
- And we're pretty sure this is
Doctor Alchemy that did this?
- The last thing Clariss said
before he died.
- Unless someone else
killed him.
- Like a meta with telekinesis
or cloaking abilities.
We've got both on our Earth.
- So what do we do now?
- Our meta-human specialist
at CCPD,
Julian Albert,
he prefers to work alone,
but I got feelers out
on his investigation.
I'm gonna go there now
and see if he dug up anything.
- All right.
- Okay, well, until then,
you guys want to train?
- Well, now,
we have to think about
getting back to our Earth.
We've been here long enough.
- I've still got a lot to learn.
Your words, not mine.
- I...
[sighs]
Fine.
- Well, if you want to train,
let's train...
speedster style.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Damn, Jesse's almost
as fast as Barry.
- Velocity's just under Mach 3.
Heart rate, 100 BPMs.
Her vitals are normal.
- Yeah, no, we already know
all that.
Cisco, we need to test
her reflexes.
Can we test her reflexes?
- Patience, Harry, patience.
If anyone's gonna teach Jesse
the ways of the Speed Force...
- It's Barry.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Aah!
- Okay.
Well, that wasn't very heroic.
- Nope.
But there is a lesson
in there somewhere.
- What's that?
- The difference
between having powers
and having precision.
- Well, what do you mean?
- I mean, it's gonna take
more than speed
to take down
some of these metas.
You got to think, anticipate.
When you enter
a new environment,
you got to case
every inch of it.
You never run in blind.
Oh, my God.
I've become Oliver.
Huh.
- Maybe we should stay
a little bit longer.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- It's gonna take some time
to master your powers, Jesse.
You'll get the hang of it.
- Yeah, I know, thanks.
Well, since I will be here
for a while,
do you want to get out of here?
- Where to?
- Does it matter?
- [stammers]
No touching.
[whoosh]
Not what I meant
by staying longer!
- I should probably
get back to CCPN.
- All right.
- I'll see you tonight?
- Can't wait.
- Okay.
- Hey, Harry.
- Yeah?
- Are you really sure
you have to leave?
- Just a lot I still have
to fix on my Earth.
- Yeah, but you know
it's more fun
when you're here helping us
fix stuff on our Earth.
- He is right.
It hasn't been
the same without you.
- The team doesn't feel complete
without Harrison Wells.
- Then change that.
There's a whole multiverse
of Harrison Wells
out there at your fingertips.
You want one?
Let's go get one.
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
- Yeah, now I remembered it.
Thank you, Officer Mayer.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
- So sorry. I got
held up at the courthouse.
- No problem.
You're the one
doing me the favor.
- Yeah, I wouldn't
thank me just yet.
- Oh, you couldn't
find anything.
- Nope, no one
at the DA's office
knows anything about
anybody named Alchemy.
- Oh, damn.
- This is, um...
[clears throat]
Meta-human related, I assume?
- It appears to be.
- Yikes.
- I know.
- Okay.
You let me know if there's
anything I can do for you, yeah?
- Yeah, thanks for bringing it
yourself, Cecile.
- [laughs softly]
It was my pleasure.
[solemn music]
[Nine Pound Shadow's
"Bridges" playing]
- This is really nice.
- Staying in is so much better
than going out.
- When you have jobs like ours?
Yes.
- Yes.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- What?
- You're just really handsome.
- ♪ I can't say good-bye ♪
- You are not so bad yourself.
- ♪ The summer is almost done ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I still see the sun ♪
♪ Oh, the summer is
almost done ♪
♪ ♪
[door opening]
[whooshing]
- [blowing]
Hey, hey...hi.
I thought...
I didn't think you were gonna
be home for a while, right?
- My plans changed.
[stammering]
Unfortunately.
I'm just gonna go upstairs.
- You can have a beer,
sit with us.
Have a good night.
I-I know.
I'm...I'm sorry.
I-I...should we rain check,
or...
- Barry, I am not upset because
our date got interrupted.
That, I understand.
- What do you mean?
- You, speeding away
when my dad walks in.
- Yeah.
- Because, what, we're kissing?
- Yeah, Iris, exactly.
- What, you don't want
to kiss me?
- Of course I want to kiss you.
But not in front of him.
- What does that matter?
- He's your...he's our...
Joe.
I don't know.
- Barry, we are adults.
- I know.
- We are dating.
- Yeah.
- We should be able to kiss.
- I agree.
- Okay, yep.
Yep.
You should talk to him.
- I...about?
[playful music]
For real?
- Yeah.
Go talk to him.
- Yeah, sure, I'll talk to him.
- Okay.
- About us kissing.
- Yeah.
- It's not gonna be awkward
at all.
- Let me know how it goes.
- It's gonna be awkward,
that's how.
♪ ♪
[hip-hop music playing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Where's Snart?
- Who said that?
Where are you?
♪ ♪
- Boo.
- Scudder?
- Where's Snart?
- I don't know, man.
♪ ♪
- Then I guess I'll just have to
find someone who does.
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
[body thuds]
♪ ♪
- And I know just the girl.
- Yeah, Sam Scudder.
He threw me into a mirror.
I fell out of
a second-story window.
- So Scudder's going after
everyone in Snart's old crew
to track him down?
- Yeah, but the only problem is,
Scudder's not gonna find him.
Snart's gone.
- What do you mean, he's gone?
- He's gone.
I thought I...
Oliver told me that Snart left
with some friends of ours
on a...trip.
- I don't even want to know.
One of Snart's old crew
is at Iron Heights.
I'll go see
if I can talk to her.
- Okay, I'll see if I can locate
any others at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Hey, um, hey, actually...
I'm sorry, I just...
I need to talk to you
about something really quick.
Um...
[laughs softly]
Okay, so I-I know
it's probably awkward
seeing me and Iris kiss.
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah.
So I-I was just
thinking, maybe...
did it have to be awkward?
- Do you mean
like this conversation?
- Yeah, like this conversation.
I don't know, just 'cause
the next time, um, you see us,
we may kiss again
in front of you.
- Okay.
- So I just want to make sure
that that is...okay with you.
- Look, Bar.
- Uh-huh.
- You're an adult.
- Yes.
- Do what you got to do.
I love you.
- I love you too.
- I love her.
I don't love watching
you two make out.
- Um, okay, and just...
just so you know,
I am gonna tell Iris that...
that we talked about this.
- Yeah, like I said.
Do what you got to do.
- Okay.
Wow.
- How sure are you
that this will work?
- Pretty sure.
- Okay, but how's this
going to help us
find another Harrison Wells?
- You ever go fishing, Snow?
- No.
- No, all right.
When you go fishing,
you use lures.
Lures attract fish.
Fish end up
on your fishing pole.
This satellite is
our fishing pole,
through which we're going
to cast our very tempting bait
out into the world's
largest ocean.
- Okay, how?
- How?
Cisco will open a breach,
and this satellite
will shoot a message embedded
with a tachyon-enhanced laser
out into the multiverse,
and any Earth that is
technologically advanced enough
should be able to receive it.
- Okay,
let's say this somehow works.
Just 'cause they can
solve a riddle
doesn't mean they're
a right fit for the team.
- A riddle.
Did you say riddle?
- Yeah.
- How dare you, sir.
This is not a riddle.
This is a complex
algorithmic cryptogram
designed to test
deductive reasoning,
IQ, problem-solving skills,
anything that our team
will need to combat threats,
meta-human or otherwise.
- Okay, so you're just sending
out an intergalactic IQ test
to all of your doppelgangers
in the multiverse.
- Not just a test.
Think of it as an invitation.
Think of it as an elaborate
"help wanted" ad.
- Will it test
their attitudes, too?
'Cause I'm not sure
I can stomach another Wells
with your bedside manner.
- I care for you too,
you jack wagon.
System is calibrated.
What are you waiting for?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
And...
That's it.
- That's it?
- Yeah, that's it.
- So now what?
- Now...
we go get a Big Belly burger.
[whooshing]
- That's insane. What a rush.
- I know.
I mean, it took me a while
to get used to it.
I can't believe
you're not sick at all.
- I must have an iron stomach.
- Okay, so you're telling me
that Barry has never
taken you on a run?
- No.
- Well, then, I guess
it's a good thing you've got me.
- Guess so.
Whoa, um, hold up.
- Oh...I'm sorry.
Am I...am I reading this, like,
really wrong or something?
- No, no.
I like you, Jesse.
It's just...
- It's just what?
- You're going home soon.
To another Earth.
- Ah, right.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, it's...
it's cool, yeah.
- Jesse, I...
- No, no, no.
It's...it's totally cool.
I get it.
[solemn music]
[clears throat]
So...so friends, then?
- Friends.
- Well, as friends, I mean,
we can still run
around the city, right?
- Sure.
♪ ♪
- Good-looking guy.
For a criminal.
- Well, he's more than just
a criminal now.
Apparently, he's a meta
who can travel through mirrors.
- Oh, oh, I got this one.
He's, uh...
- Mirror Master.
- What the...
- Boom.
- That's good.
- Thank you, we had
a Mirror Master on our Earth,
Evan McCulloch.
Wasn't a meta, though.
He had some kind of mirror gun
that he used.
- How'd it work?
- Must've had dimensional
warping tech that changed
everything into two dimensions.
- Well, Scudder is hell-bent
on finding Snart,
and he's going after anybody
that worked with him
in the past.
Joe's interviewing
one of 'em right now.
- Well, all of Snart's
known associates
are either presumed dead
or gone AWOL, except for one.
- That's her.
- Rosalind Dillon.
- Says she has the ability
to induce crippling vertigo.
- Oh, um, uh...
- She's, uh...
- Top, like a top.
She's The Top.
That's her name.
Top. Amazing.
What, you want to go?
- Okay.
Do we think that she can
lead us to Scudder?
- I'll have to see if Joe gets
any answers out of her.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Heard your ex
is back in town.
You know anything about that?
He pay you a visit, Ms. Dillon?
[dark music]
- They don't let people like me
have visitors here, Detective.
All day, all night,
in my boring little cell.
Makes a girl go crazy.
- Scudder tried to kill one of
your old crewmates last night.
Leon Williams?
- Tried? Too bad he failed.
- He's gonna try to kill more.
Any idea who?
- Give us a name.
I'll see what we can do
about your current situation.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Let us know
if you change your mind.
♪ ♪
- Sorry, Joe.
- It's all right.
I appreciate your setting up
the interview, though.
It looks like
I owe you another one.
- You know, these IOUs
are starting to pile up.
- I have an idea about that.
- Do you?
- Scudder?
- You want me?
Come and get me.
[dramatic music]
- So you saw Sam Scudder
and Rosalind Dillon
escape through a glass window?
- Like I said,
he grabbed her hand.
They walked to the window,
and then poof, they were gone.
- So, mirrors, windows.
It sounds like he can travel
through anything
that has a reflective surface.
- How exactly does he do that?
- He must be able to link
Einstein-Rosen bridges
to anything with high solar
reflectance, right?
- So he creates wormholes
through reflections.
That's a new one.
- Look, I can't pretend
to understand or care
about the science of it all,
but we need to find Dillon
and Scudder before something
really bad happens.
So I'm gonna go old-school
at the precinct.
I'll see you later.
[phone chimes]
- Oh, my God.
Pings.
We got pings.
Looks like some of
your doppelgangers out there
actually cracked your code,
Harry.
- That was fast.
- Let's go take a look.
- Guys?
We're...
[tense music]
- Um...Dad seems fine.
- Um, yeah, no, he's still
a little weird about it.
- You talked to him,
though, right?
- Um, yeah, I did.
Yeah, it'll be good.
- Okay, great.
- Yeah.
- Then I'll see you tonight.
- All right.
- You'll pick a good movie?
- I'll try.
- Okay.
[playful music]
- I'm also gonna try to find
our meta-humans
that apparently no one else
cares about right now.
[dark music]
- Where the hell did you go?
- How many times do
I have to tell you, Rosa?
I was stuck in there.
Whatever it was that hit me
gave me this crazy ability.
And to me, all this
just happened last night.
- It's been three years, Sam.
So many things
are different now.
- You were hit too,
weren't you?
You can do things like me?
- Yeah.
- Show me.
♪ ♪
- You might want
to hold onto something.
♪ ♪
- Whoa.
Oh.
♪ ♪
See, Sammy?
Too much has changed.
- Then let's change it back.
Huh?
I can stop Snart, Rosa.
We...can stop Snart.
- Snart?
He's gone.
Long gone.
- Then let's take this city.
We can be who we want to now.
We can be in control.
There's no one in this city
who can stop us now.
- There's one person who can.
- Who?
- The Flash.
- Well, hey, now.
I-I solved the derivative
you done beamed up.
My name is Wells,
Harrison Wells.
You can call me Hell's Wells.
They call me that
'cause of my past.
I won't get into it
with you now right and proper.
I'd like to hitch wagons and...
[burps]
I had a bad dinner.
- Pass.
- All right.
This is Earth-17.
- I'll be in touch.
- Salutations to all of you
out there in the multiverse.
I have of late, wherefore I know
not, received a communiqué
from the citizens
of Terra-Prime.
- Terra-Prime?
- Nerd.
- Pass.
- Bonjour.
Moi, je suis Harrison Wells.
[speaking French]
- You can't trust a mime.
- Can't argue with that.
- Pass.
- Okay, guys.
We're 0 for 3 now.
This is our last one.
It's coming from Earth-19.
- Hello, hello, hello.
Hello, out there
in the multiverse,
whoever you may be.
Um...
I really enjoyed cracking
the cryptogram you broadcast.
I like the cute trick,
embedding the secondary measures
in the primary data string.
It's clever.
Most people wouldn't
have caught it.
I caught it.
But that's the point.
You need a genius, I guess,
to help you in your fight
against these awful
meta-hominids.
Well, I got to tell you...
I got to tell you, to me,
that sounds like fun.
So...I'll enclose
my curriculum vitae.
You already know
we speak the same language.
But take a look.
Tell me what you think.
Until our next communion.
Oh, where are my manners?
Thank you.
- Not bad.
- Not bad at all.
Harry?
- Pass.
- What?
- Wait, what? Wait a minute.
That guy cracked the code,
and he wants to do it.
- And he's nice,
and he's not evil.
And that's a combination of
Wells we haven't had thus far.
- All my life, everyone
I've ever hired to work for me,
I have trusted my gut.
My gut tells me
that's not the guy.
Keep looking.
[scary music]
- [growling]
♪ ♪
- It's all right.
He's my friend.
- [growling]
- Sorry.
I'm just gonna get...
♪ ♪
- Oh, for God's sake.
Okay, you know what?
[TV silences]
I can't take this anymore.
- What?
- I thought you guys
were supposed to talk about us.
both: We did.
- Then why are you being
so weird?
- I'm not.
- Dad?
- Iris.
I already told him,
if you two want to cuddle,
make out, do whatever,
I-I-I...go for it.
I don't care.
- Barry?
- Hey.
- Should we give you guys
a minute?
- Yeah.
- No, no, it's fine.
Look, Barry, this isn't
about my dad anymore.
He's fine with it.
- I'm not totally fine with it.
- So why do you
have a problem with this?
[phone buzzing]
- Thank God.
There's a robbery
at First National.
Suspects match Scudder
and Dillon's description.
- Scudder and Dillon, yeah,
I'm sorry, I got to go.
- Okay.
- Hey...let me help.
We've been training
for a reason, right?
I've got to try.
- Yeah, all right, cool.
Just follow my lead.
- Okay.
[exciting music]
[alarm ringing]
- We keep this up,
baby, we'll be set for life.
- Then what are you waiting for?
♪ ♪
Let's do it again.
[giggles]
♪ ♪
- Anything for you, baby.
- Yeah, so we're not gonna
let you leave here with that.
- Hey, Flash.
Heard a lot about you.
- That's great.
- Can't say the same for you,
though.
- The name's Jesse Quick.
- Oh.
- So...I'm sorry, Scudder,
but your little crime spree,
it's gonna have to end here.
- Oh, I don't think
you have much of a say in it.
I'm gonna take whatever I want.
- I thought you were looking
for Leonard Snart.
- Why bother?
His reign is over.
There's a...a new king in town.
- And I'm the queen.
- Yeah, I wouldn't be
too sure about that.
- Oh, I would, little girl.
- [giggles]
♪ ♪
- Where'd they go?
- There.
Stay here.
I'm not kidding.
♪ ♪
- Nice skirt, Top.
- Top.
I like it.
Because they spin,
spin, spin.
- What?
What's happening?
♪ ♪
Aah...aah!
I can't get my balance.
- I know.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
- But you won't.
- Oh!
- Good luck getting him out.
- Barry!
♪ ♪
- What happened?
- I don't know.
I don't know, okay?
I looked at Dillon,
and I lost my balance.
- She's a meta-human
who induces vertigo.
She just whammied you.
- Yeah, I guess so.
It doesn't really matter,
does it?
Because now Barry's trapped
in there and it's because of me.
- Well, you know,
I...
- I'll go talk to her.
- [sighs]
- [speaking unintelligibly]
- What is he saying?
- Is that some sort of
mirror language?
- Mirrors show objects
in reverse.
Maybe that's what
we're hearing here.
- Only one way to find out.
- What are you
looking for, Cisco?
- You ever seen "Twin Peaks"?
Of course not.
Why do I ask?
This is an old
backmasking trick
they used for
the Man from Another Place,
where they record
his audio backwards
and then play it forwards.
- Like the Ozzy Osbourne
records.
- Sure, let's go with that.
- Okay, Barry, say something.
- [speaking unintelligibly]
- Oops.
[device beeps]
- Say it again.
- Um, get me out of here.
- Now we can understand you.
How do we get him out of there?
- Barry, have you tried
to phase out yet?
- Yes.
It's not working.
- If Scudder used this mirror
as a wormhole,
then these molecules are in a
hyper state of flux, so all...
- We need is something
really cold to slow them down.
- I can help with that.
Let's go.
[tense music]
- Keep him company.
♪ ♪
- Aren't you gonna need that?
- What's the point?
You know, I thought I was ready,
but clearly I'm not.
- Jesse, you can't
blame yourself for this.
What happened to Barry...
- It was totally my fault.
I mean, he told me to stay back,
but I didn't listen, you know?
I just ran in blind, and...
and now he's stuck, so...
- Look, you made a mistake.
So what?
I mean, I'm sure Barry made
a lot of mistakes at first too.
- Yeah.
- Don't let this destroy
your confidence.
You're meant to do this, Jesse.
You're meant to be a speedster.
That's why you have these powers
and I don't.
- You're just trying
to cheer me up.
I know you said
you don't want to hang, so...
- No, I said I didn't want to
hang out because I was scared.
Because you live on
another Earth, but...
[solemn music]
I realized I don't want
to be scared of that anymore.
♪ ♪
[both chuckle]
- I don't think it's gonna work.
- What do you mean,
you don't think it's gonna work?
I built this to go
to absolute zero.
- I realize that.
But we need the mirror
to maintain zero-point energy
long enough
for Barry's molecules
to pass through it.
- Absolute zero's more
than cold enough to do that.
- Normally, but we have to
account for the internal energy
of the mirror's molecules,
as well.
So while absolute cold might be
the lowest possible temperature,
it's not the...
- It's not the lowest
enthalpy state possible.
- Exactly right.
- So what are we gonna do?
- I don't know...yet.
- Okay, go with me here.
What if we send this
to the other Wells
and see if he can
figure something out?
- Yeah.
- What? No. What?
Oh, everybody's
replaceable now, is that right?
Is that what this is?
- What are you talking about?
That's what you said.
- That's not what I said.
I'm saying we need to figure out
a solution to this problem,
and time's not
on our side right now.
- That's not gonna help...you're
not contributing to the problem.
You're making things worse.
- You know what I think?
- I think you don't like
the idea of someone
taking your place here.
- What are you talking about?
- This is why you don't like
the other Wells.
- What are you talking about?
It was my idea.
- But that doesn't mean
you have to like it.
- It's got nothing to do
with liking, okay?
You know what it has to do with?
A molecular decelerator.
- A molecular decelerator.
- If we augment
the molecular decelerator
on the cryogenic generator...
both: Of the cold gun...
- I can build that.
I can build that.
- Great.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
- Do these pants
make my butt look big?
- I'm literally stuck
in a mirror.
- Sorry, yeah.
[laughs softly]
What's it like in there?
- Um...
dark.
- [laughs]
- Look, Iris, I'm...
I'm sorry that I'm...
stuck right now.
- Oh, honey, I know
that you're stuck.
It's okay, we are gonna
get you out of there.
- No, I mean...no.
That was misleading.
Not the mirror.
I mean, with us.
This thing with Joe,
and you were right.
I mean, it's not Joe.
It's me.
It's my problem.
I've just been feeling nervous
about this new dynamic
between the three of us.
I-I don't know.
I have everything that
I have ever wanted right now.
And I've never had
that in my life.
In a lot of ways,
it's scarier than having
nothing, because...
it's easier to fail
than succeed.
And I really want to succeed.
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
- What could you possibly be
laughing about right now?
- I am so sorry, Barry.
You are really sweet.
But it is weird talking to you
through a mirror and a speaker,
and I really want
to kiss you right now.
But can we please
talk about this later?
- Yeah.
We can talk about it later.
Guess it is pretty weird.
It's like I'm here, but I'm not.
♪ ♪
- What?
- I just thought of a way
to stop Scudder.
- What is that?
- This is how we get him
out of there.
- All right.
Let's do it.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
[ice crackling]
- Try it now.
♪ ♪
- It's only negative
280 degrees Fahrenheit.
- We got to get it
colder somehow.
- I thought you guys said
this thing
could get him out of there.
- Okay, this thing
is a highly advanced
molecular decelerator
that's being powered
by a cryo-engine,
and we just kind of improvised
it in the last 30 minutes,
so let's just...just cut us
some slack, please?
- Just keep trying, Barry.
[alarm beeping]
- Meta-human alert.
- Oh, for God's sake.
- If it's not one thing...
- It's the other.
- Hold on, Bar.
[alarm continues]
- Guys?
Hello?
[alarm silences]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[alarm beeping]
- Central City Municipal Bank
just got robbed.
- Let me guess by who.
[whooshing]
- Guys.
- Barry.
- Hey.
[chuckles]
- How?
- Let's figure it out later.
Right now we need to stop
Scudder and Dillon.
- Okay, so...so what do we do?
- We're gonna use mirrors,
an old trick,
and an old friend.
[phone ringing]
- Yeah?
- It's Snart.
I heard you were back in town.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Snart?
- Scudder, Rosa.
Long time.
- Not long enough.
- Hang back.
This guy owes me.
♪ ♪
So you called us.
The hell you want?
- Same thing.
You two, gone.
- Things have changed.
This is our town now.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, it is.
♪ ♪
And that little cold gun
of yours
isn't gonna save you from me.
- We'll see about that,
now, won't we?
♪ ♪
Bang!
- Funny thing about holograms.
♪ ♪
They're just pale reflections
of the real deal.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Hello again.
- Jesse Quick.
Quick to run, quick to fall.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- Quick to learn.
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
- Uh-oh.
- [laughing]
Well played, Flash.
♪ ♪
- Oh.
- What?
- I know, right?
This is the, uh, Droste effect.
I'm sure you've heard
of it, right?
It's an infinite reflective loop
that even you can't escape.
♪ ♪
Good luck getting out.
- So you're sure he can't
Mirror Master his way
out of this cell?
- No, it's impossible.
Every inch has been modified
with an
anti-reflective material.
Even Scudder's gonna forget what
he looks like after a while.
- Well, I should go.
- Hey.
So, thank you for everything.
- Oh, no.
Thank you.
We got another bad meta
right where he belongs.
- Yep, all right.
- Hey, Joe.
We have an awful lot of IOUs.
Do you maybe want to grab
some dinner tonight?
- Dinner?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I...
well, I've got movie night
with my kids tonight.
Rain check?
- Yeah.
Of course.
Another time, then.
[solemn music]
- Yo.
What was that about?
Why didn't you just say yes?
- I don't know.
You're not the only one
that gets nervous around here.
♪ ♪
- You guys, I've never vibed
across 18 dimensions before.
- Just a little bit longer.
♪ ♪
- [deep voice]
Greetings, earthlings.
[dramatic music]
Just kidding.
I don't really talk like that.
I've just always wanted
to say that.
Earthlings.
[laughs]
- Wells with a sense of humor.
That's new.
- Hey, sharpshooter.
[playful music]
You.
You're...handsome.
- [laughs]
I know.
- I know.
- Likewise, I'm sure.
- Yeah.
- Harrison.
You can call me HR.
- HR it is.
This is the team, then.
Um...
This is Cisco Ramon.
He can do anything.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
She is brilliant.
- Hi.
- Single.
- Don't...all right,
that's my daughter.
You don't have
to shake her hand.
That gentleman there
is Wally West.
This is Barry Allen,
or as we call him
on this Earth...
The Flash.
♪ ♪
- Welcome to Earth-1.
- Thanks.
Earth-1, that's weird.
- [laughs]
- Okay, well, we don't have
to stand on ceremony.
We don't have to go through all
the tears again, do we, gang?
Right?
- Well, did I...
did I cry last time you left?
- I was talking about myself.
- Oh, gotcha.
Hey, listen.
Don't worry about him, okay?
There's only one Harry.
[solemn music]
- [laughs softly]
♪ ♪
Oh, I wanted to tell you.
The molecular decelerator,
it wasn't working.
- Okay, what does that mean?
- It means that we did not
get Barry out of that mirror.
It wasn't us.
- Then who did it?
- You tell me.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- Earth-2's gonna have one hell
of a speedster protecting it.
- Well,
I did learn from the best.
- If you ever need any help,
you know how to get back.
- Yeah.
Yeah, definitely, I'll be back.
- All right.
- Okay, you guys.
Ready?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay, Cisco.
Out with the old,
in with the new.
- Aw.
You'll never be old to us,
Harry.
- [laughs softly]
[rousing music]
[portal opens]
Ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do this.
Oh, one more thing.
While I'm gone, never, ever,
no matter what...
- Oh, oh.
What...what was he gonna say?
And we're all like,
"What was he gonna say?"
That's cool, though.
I'm starving.
Do you guys have
Big Belly Burger?
- Some things never change.
- Famished.
[solemn music]
- Did Barry say anything about
this embarrassing moment
with Cecile?
- Mm-mm.
- Hey.
- How did your first meeting go
with the new Wells?
- [chuckles]
Uh, good.
Yeah, I think
he'll work out fine.
- Oh, good.
I look forward to meeting him.
- Whoa.
- What?
- I'm just kidding.
[laughing]
- I got to be honest,
it's gonna take a bit
for me to get used to that.
- Um...
I actually have something
to run by you guys that
I think might help with that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What up?
- Well, I've just been thinking
that maybe for all of us...
that I should probably, um...
get my own place.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What do you think?
- I say yes.
- I thought you'd never leave.
- Seriously?
- Dad.
- Wow.
- Look, Bar, come on.
I'm gonna miss you, but damn.
You grown.
About time.
- I can't tell if I'm leaving
or if I'm getting kicked out.
- You feel like you feel.
- Feel like I'm
getting kicked out.
- I mean, yeah, I feel like
you're getting kicked out too.
Like, it's pretty obvious
you're getting kicked out.
Dad.
- You're grown.
- Oh, well.
Cool.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[ice crackling]
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.