You back off, lady.
Oh, Deon.
Past, present or future,
you can't run from me.
Who said I'm going to run?
Maybe I could just snap my fingers...
send you back
a thousand years in time.
By the time you get back?
Oh, I'll be long gone.
Now that is no way
to treat your big sister.
I don't have a sister.
Yes, you do.
Look inside yourself.
Your stillness knows
my speed, little brother.
We're connected, you and I.
I know you can feel it.
Well, hey, maybe we are the same.
Okay, who cares? I don't know you.
Yes, you do.
We were born at the same time.
What? Lady, you're nuts!
First, you show up trying to kill me,
now you want to chat
like we're in Sunday school?
Nah. [chuckles]
I ain't falling for that.
Oh, Deon.
We may have come
into this world together,
but this isn't my first time.
Which means...
[Deon grunts]
I could kill you at any moment.
And I still might.
Then do it or get out of my face.
[Speed Force as Nora Allen]
You're right.
I don't want you dead...
but I do want your help.
You and I have a common enemy.
Our father, Barry Allen, rejected me.
Just like he rejected you.
Tell me something.
How does that make you feel?
[Alexa] Wait, let me get this straight.
I'm a Force of Nature...
Barry's the Flash
and you two birthed me.
[chuckling] That makes you, what?
My parents?
Something like that.
And I have three siblings,
one who just tried to kill me.
[Caitlin] Technically, Alexa,
she did kill you,
but your biometrics are stable,
so I think you're fine.
Wait, how did you
bring me back anyway?
We don't actually know.
But according to my initial tests,
the three of you share the same
bio-kinetic genome sequence.
Kind of like how a parent
and their child share the same DNA.
Exactly, except we're talking
about cosmic DNA.
So you can sense their cells
on a quantum level, and vice versa.
So they can sense one another?
That is so damn cute.
Wait, if we're all connected,
can't the other Forces
sense each other, too?
- If Nora finds them before we do...
- She's gonna kill them.
All right, well, where are we
with finding Deon and Psych?
Chester and I are working
on a tracking system
to locate Deon's temporal isotopes
across timelines.
I'm monitoring the data while he's
out there setting up the sensors.
And The Citizen
is looking into Psych.
We're going to see if we can ID
his human identity.
If we can do that, we can find him.
Well, we better do it fast.
I've been seeing intermittent spikes
of Nora's isotopic signature
all across the city,
and there's been a ton of reports
of spontaneous lightning.
Your firstborn is pissed.
She's going to come after me again.
And if she does, we will protect you.
How? You couldn't the last time.
She's not going to this time.
We're gonna train you
to control your powers.
Wait, you want me
to control that monster?
Think about it. Nora needed me
to help to take you down.
If you could control your powers,
I don't think she'd be able
to hurt you again.
What if I hurt you or kill
someone else during this training?
I can't hurt anyone else.
We'll make sure you don't.
Let us help you.
[Cisco] You leaving?
Yeah, Iris put me on Psych duty.
It is an all-hands-on-deck
kind of day.
Yeah, this whole
fighting Big Bads thing?
Definitely not gonna miss it.
[laughs]
Hey, what do you think about Miami?
Great mojitos, excellent NBA team.
What, are you thinking about
booking a vacation, like, now?
No, I meant to live
after we leave Central City.
I've been submitting my work
to a few art galleries,
and this one in South Beach
is interested.
Plus, I do love a good mojito.
You're already job hunting.
Yeah. Aren't you?
Mm-hm.
Okay. Well, we should probably
tell the team soon.
I've got to give Iris enough time
to find a new photographer.
- Bye.
Fine. Just call me
when the deal's done.
[Psych in sing-song voice] Caleb.
[chuckles] That's my name, you idiot.
Who said that?
Who's here?
[Psych] Caleb!
Seems like your short game
still needs some work.
[Psych laughing]
Who are you?
- And what do you want?
- [Psych] Aw.
You don't remember me?
Well...
Let's see if I can't jog your memory.
Bashir?
How are you doing this?
It's kind of a long story.
To be honest with you,
it's been a bit of a nightmare.
How about I share it with you?
[screams]
That was Caleb Fairweather,
the billionaire tech guy.
What happened to him?
According to the paramedics,
mental distress and symptoms
consistent with narcolepsy.
That was the mayor's office.
It turns out that Caleb
is the fourth billionaire today
they found like this.
Hold on.
[chiming]
Yeah, I'm picking up a ton
of electrochemical isotopes in here.
Caleb was attacked by Psych?
I don't get it.
You both were attacked by Psych
and you didn't end up like that.
- [phone vibrating]
- No.
I'm needed at C.C.P.D.
Let me know if you find out anything.
What are you thinking?
Well, we both assumed Psych
had an axe to grind with the system,
because he was attacking
banks and the stock market.
But now he's going
after individual people.
- Why the change?
- Yeah, I know. Feels personal.
Maybe there's something here
that explains the escalation.
I'm guessing that's not
Caleb's college chess club.
No.
More like an Ivy League society.
Wait.
My dad did say that four other
wealthy targets were attacked today.
If Psych is targeting
people in this group, then...
Start training Alexa
as fast as you can.
I'm going to try and figure out
who's next on Psych's list.
[knocking on door]
Kramer?
I thought you were headed upstate.
As a result of the Frost case,
the governor wants me
to stick around a bit longer.
Have a seat, Captain.
I'm trying to find
the source of this city's
meta-criminal problem.
And I need your help.
There seem to be a whole lot of cases
where meta-criminals
simply disappear around here.
Like this Rainbow Raider.
One minute he's in C.C.P.D. custody,
the next, missing.
Any thoughts?
None whatsoever.
Okay, then.
Who else worked these cases?
Patty Spivot. Reassigned.
Julian Albert. Also reassigned.
Hm. Barry Allen's still here.
Can you do me a favor?
Send him in.
Maybe he knows something we don't.
He's on a case.
I'll see if I can pull him off.
Thank you.
[Cisco] Don't worry. This force field
can handle just about anything.
Speedsters, futuristic meta-villains.
You've done this before?
[laughs] Oh, yeah.
But you should know
I've reinforced this baby
with inverse surge capabilities.
The harder you push against it,
the stronger it's going to get.
Even Fuerza
can't fight herself, right?
Fuerza...
You named it "Strength"?
I guess that makes sense. [sighs]
What now?
You initiate a change.
The key is to focus,
control the transformation
into Fuerza from the start.
So try to stay calm when I change?
[scoffs] Are you gonna
teach me to meditate?
I mean, it's really just
about your breathing.
Focus on that while you transform
and we'll keep track
of the physiological effects.
You sure I'm ready for this?
If Nora shows up again, you need
to be able to protect yourself.
We'll go slow.
[whirring]
[sputtering]
I don't think I can do this.
Yes, you can. Just try to remember
how you felt the last time.
I can't.
Alexa, you have to.
[Iris West] Excuse me, Ms. LaSalle?
Hi. I'm Iris West-Allen
with The Central City Citizen...
If you're looking for a quote
on our recent merger,
you'll have to contact publicity.
[Iris West] No, actually,
we're here because
you were the president
of the League of Lions.
Is this for that alumni newsletter?
Here's a quote. I'm wealthier
than the whole League combined now.
Ms. LaSalle, please.
There is a meta-human that is
targeting members of that League.
And four of your Richie Rich friends
have already been attacked.
We believe you and the other man
in this photo are the next victims.
If you could just tell us his name.
Lucas Sharpe.
He's into apps
and alternative energy sources.
Bit of a do-gooder.
[Psych speaking Latin]
[in English]
Prosperity equals power.
And judging by this empire
that you've built up for yourself,
it appears you followed
the League's motto to a tee, Naomi.
Congratulations.
I know that voice.
Smashing costume, Bashir.
It's not working. I don't know
how to bring that thing out.
It's because you're holding back.
[alarm blaring]
I've got isotopes downtown!
[whooshing]
[Psych] So, Naomi...
I've been catching up
with the old gang.
Swapping stories.
It's been a lot of fun for me.
And now it's your turn.
Last time I saw you, you got
thrown out of the yacht club
because you couldn't pay your dues.
[Psych] It's true.
The regatta life was never for me.
I was so right about you.
The others thought
you deserved a chance,
but I knew you'd never fit in.
Let me guess.
You're broke again
and now you want another handout?
Sorry, Bashir. You want help?
Help yourself.
- [Psych] Don't mind if I do.
- Bashir!
You don't have to do this.
[Psych chuckles] Oh, yes, I really do.
[Naomi screaming]
[Psych] Whew. Back for another
round, huh, Flash?
Psych, you need to listen to me.
You're in danger.
There are other Forces
out there who are trying to...
[Psych] Boring!
[grunts]
[Psych] So you're Dad?
[Psych laughs]
Life is just full
of little surprises, isn't it?
[gasps]
Your scans show pattern bruising
from where Psych...
Bashir attacked you.
What did he show you this time?
He didn't show me anything,
but his powers are growing.
I mean, somehow he was able to
manifest tentacles
that could move as fast as me.
So we've got a fifth comatose
billionaire in the hospital
and an evil magenta
Sage guru with tentacles?
Magentacles, if you will.
We're gonna have to
change up our plan, I think.
Well, Iris is trying to locate
Bashir's final target.
We need to be ready.
Right. To do what exactly?
I mean, maybe I'm not strong enough
to stop Bashir.
But Fuerza is.
Wait, you want me to fight him?
Hey, uh...
Just long enough to subdue Bashir,
so hopefully we can
get through to him.
What if I accidentally kill him?
Well, you won't if you can get
a handle on your powers,
which is why we've got
to continue your training.
Cisco, are the isotopic
arc radiators still functional?
They need a couple tweaks, but yeah.
I'm sorry,
you want to force Fuerza out?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, we're running out of time.
Barry, you can't push Fuerza out
until Alexa's ready.
It's too dangerous.
Alexa.
This is about more than
protecting yourself from Nora now.
If Bashir uses these new powers
on the city, people will get hurt.
I know you're scared,
but we still need your help.
And this Bashir guy, he's really bad?
He's pretty much the worst.
[sighs]
Okay.
[Iris West] Bashir Malik.
His name was listed on
the League of Lions' member page.
Class of '08. He is the adoptive son
of Adrita and Paul Malik,
owners of Malik Hotels.
He was a rich kid, but it says here
the Maliks died in a plane crash
13 years ago.
He was orphaned twice?
First by his birth parents
and then by his adoptive parents.
And it gets worse.
When the Maliks' plane went down,
there were $50 million in debt.
They were fleeing the country
for tax evasion,
and they left Bashir behind.
And I thought my family
was messed up.
That's why he hates his parents.
They abandoned him,
and they weren't the only ones.
Naomi told him he never belonged.
You think when he went broke,
his friends just bailed on him, too?
Yeah, that's why he's targeting them.
He felt burned by his parents,
his friends
and the system that made him.
Now he's out for revenge.
[sighs] So who's next on the list?
Lucas Sharpe.
I ran his picture and got a hit.
He wasn't at his home or his work,
and all of his social media accounts
were recently deleted.
He's on the run.
I called Cisco. S.T.A.R.'s
search protocols are up and running.
But, Iris, even if we find Lucas,
what's our plan?
I mean, you've tried talking
to Bashir twice now,
and it still hasn't worked.
Well, because
I didn't know what to say.
I think I was trying to be
a mother figure
when I should have been a journalist.
Getting all of the information
before running a story.
And do you think there's more to his?
Yeah. We need to dig deeper.
[locks clicking]
[Kramer] Find what you're looking for?
I checked out the armament delivery
you signed for this morning.
Seeing as I didn't authorize it.
These bullets contain
the meta-human cure, don't they?
Thirty cc's each, yes.
If meta-humans are threatening
the public good,
we need to be able to protect
the people of this city.
This is illegal.
No, there's just
no precedent for them. Yet.
You didn't get the results
you wanted in court,
so now you're trying to figure out
another way
to eliminate meta-criminals.
Meta-criminals are dangerous,
Captain.
The people of this city can see it.
Why can't you?
The last time we talked,
I asked you to make sure
you're on the right side of the line.
Now you're going to go out there
and shoot up metas with the cure?
When it comes to meta-human affairs,
I have full authority
to use extreme measures
in emergency combat situations.
This is still my precinct.
Around here, we take the time
to deescalate the situation
before it becomes combative.
That's what this precinct did,
and your city hasn't been safe.
So we're doing things my way now.
I don't think so.
I'll contact the Governor's office...
The Governor authorized the order.
I'm still hoping that we can
work together on this, Captain.
But this is the new line now.
Figure out which side of
it you're on
and let me know.
All right, remember,
the radiators release isotopes
that'll bring out Fuerza.
So you don't have to do anything.
Just try to stay conscious
during the transformation.
That's the first step
to maintaining control.
If I start to lose control,
promise me
you'll turn these things off.
Of course we will.
Also, I've got backup.
You ready?
[whirring]
Releasing isotopic waves... now.
[groans]
Remember, Alexa, you're in control.
[voice shaking]
I can't. I don't want to do it.
You can.
[distorted]
I said, I don't want to do this.
- [rapid beeping]
- Guys, her biometrics are spiking,
I'm going to reduce
her isotopic exposure.
Don't. Alexa, you can do this.
[alarm blaring]
Uh, that's a problem.
[Cisco] Guys,
she's getting blue and angry.
It'll take 30 seconds
for the isotopic effects to wear off.
[Cisco] We don't have 30 seconds.
She's overloading the force field.
If we don't shut it down,
this thing's going to blow
and then we're all toast.
[growling]
I'm shutting it down now.
[roars]
[grunts]
Hey.
I told you I couldn't control it.
[door opens]
Is he gonna be all right?
He needs to rest,
but he'll make a full recovery.
All right,
we should get back to work.
Barry, why don't we take a break
from training?
Look, I know this is a setback,
but we can't stop.
Lives are on the line.
Don't you know what just happened?
- We can't train that thing.
- Alexa, we don't have a choice...
You don't. I do.
And I won't be your weapon.
I'm done with this,
and I am done with you.
- Wait, Alexa...
- Barry.
- What?
- What are you doing?
She needs to train.
She just found out two days ago that
she has this Force inside of her.
She needs time to process that.
Look, I'm trying to teach her
how to survive.
- Well, she's not ready.
- Well, she has to be.
All right? Look, it's my fault
that Nora wants her dead.
That means it's my responsibility
to keep her safe.
Training her is the only way
I know how to do that.
I am not saying that we don't
train her when she's ready.
Right now, what Alexa needs
from you is patience.
[sighs in exasperation]
When you first got your powers,
Thawne spent months training you.
Your greatest enemy
was more patient with you
than your being
with your own... daughter.
Think about that.
While I try and stop you
from pushing another kid away.
[Joe] Kramer's going to start a war.
She's going after
every meta with a record.
And she's being smart about it.
She's doing everything by the book.
Oh, you almost respect her, don't you?
I know that there is a good cop
in there somewhere
that cares about the safety
of people. But not like this.
What's all this?
These are all the purchases
made by Kramer on behalf of C.C.P.D.
I also have former case files coming
from Keystone, Gotham, Coast City
later today.
It's about time
somebody investigated her.
[sighs] Joe, I just
I went up against Kramer.
That woman knows
how to handle herself.
Plus, she's got
the Governor on her side.
What are you saying?
I should back down?
Joe, it has got to be her choice.
Otherwise, she is never
going to back down.
So until that happens, what are you
gonna do to help her get there?
[Kamilla] Should you be
working right now?
You're still recovering.
I'm just a little sore,
I'll be all right.
[Kamilla] Oh, my gosh.
That gallery in Miami wants
to schedule an interview.
And you don't seem that excited.
Did you know that I'm qualified
for 7,685 jobs in the US alone?
Eighty-three of them in Miami.
And trust me, I know how lucky I am
to be able to say that.
[sighs]
But if I'm being honest,
I have no clue what I'm supposed
to be doing right now.
I never told anyone this,
but when we were at Cleary Capital,
and Psych whammied me
and Barry and Frost
and he showed us
our worst nightmares,
you know what I saw?
I saw myself 40 years from now,
I was still working at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And that's a bad thing?
No, not entirely.
I mean, I've learned a lot here,
and I've made family here.
But in this nightmare...
everybody had moved on.
And I hadn't.
It was just me.
And I felt this insane regret,
not even trying to do anything else
with my career.
I don't want that future.
So, what the hell
am I supposed to do?
Babe,
I know this is a big decision.
But you don't have
to make it right now.
Just give it time.
The right job will find you.
I know it seems safer,
but running away
won't solve anything.
I don't have a choice.
When you turned that machine off,
I could feel that monster
fighting against me
as I was changing back.
It wanted to stay out.
What if I never control it?
You will. Just like I did.
Do you know the meta-human Frost?
She and I used to share a body.
When Frost first surfaced,
she did horrible things,
and I was terrified.
I tried to control her
with meta-cuffs.
I didn't even try to understand her.
But then, after a while, I realized
that there was good
inside that other part of me.
How'd you do that?
By talking to Frost. With this.
It's a mental activity dampener.
It uses neural pathways to connect
multiple consciousnesses.
It's how we talked to each other.
- I could hear that thing in my head?
- Mm-hm.
It will take time, but I think
that's just what you two need.
Or maybe you just want me
to start training again.
[Barry] Forget the training.
I should have listened to you
when you said you weren't ready.
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
If you need more time
to process this, you got it.
Whatever you want to do, we'll do it.
Thanks for saying that.
I guess what I want to do is...
try to get in sync
with my other half.
[alarm blaring]
Satellites are picking up
Lucas Sharpe's license plate.
He's headed north on I-95.
[engine revving]
[Allegra] Hang on.
We've got Bashir's Force signal
heading Sharpe's way, and fast.
Fill the jet. I'm ten minutes out.
[tires screeching]
[panting]
Hi, Lucas.
Bashir?
Oh, my God,
where have you been all these years?
That's an interesting question.
You know, I guess
I could have been out there
trying to find myself,
traveling to Prague
or the Amalfi Coast.
Really living the dream
like all of you did.
But I couldn't do that...
because I couldn't get my friends
out of my mind.
I tried to get in touch.
I was worried about you.
You did? Oh, that's so sweet.
I'm sure you thought
about me every day.
Sure, sure, sure. Hey, listen.
Now that I've got you here,
could I pick your brain
about something?
[distorted] For old time's sake.
Guys, Lucas Sharpe is the last person
on Bashir's hit list.
- And if Bashir gets to him first...
- [Iris West] There's one more thing.
There's more to Bashir's story
than we knew.
If you can get him to listen,
then I can tell you
what to say to him.
- Okay, stay on comms.
- I'm coming with you.
Alexa, you don't have to.
I know. I want to.
Look, Bash. Come on. We were friends.
Whatever you want,
we can work it out.
Oh, Lucas, you always were the optimist
in our little cabal
of spoiled rich brats.
Of course, that's not
going to help you now.
No, no, no, please, please.
[Psych] You couldn't stop the others,
so instead you watched them
destroy my life.
That makes you just as guilty.
Now you're going to pay,
just like them!
[in sing-song voice] Flash.
Why don't you come out
and show yourself?
Are you afraid?
Do you fear me, Flash?
Ah.
You know, it doesn't matter
where you stashed him.
I will hunt Lucas down.
No, you won't.
We won't let you hurt him.
[Psych] We? Who's this?
Oh, I have a baby sister.
Don't care.
Bashir, listen. Iris and I know
what your parents did to you,
but you can't keep
punishing the world for it.
Actually, yes, I can.
[grunts]
[beeping]
I don't know if you can hear me,
but I'm not afraid of you anymore.
What if Alexa's not ready?
Fuerza might be the muscle,
but after everything
she's been through,
I think Alexa might be stronger.
[speaking Spanish]
[exhales]
[Fuerza roaring]
Alexa?
[distorted] And Fuerza, together.
[Psych] You are a very big baby sister.
Not that it's going to matter.
[roaring]
Bashir, you don't have to fight us.
[Psych] Yes, I do, Dad.
Can't you see
we're just trying to help you?
[Psych] Don't bother.
Bashir, listen!
[Fuerza growls]
[exhales]
It doesn't have to be this way.
Tell him that we're
not like his parents,
- and neither were his friends.
- Caleb, Lucas and the others,
they never gave up on you.
[Psych] That's a lie.
All they ever cared about was money.
[Flash] No, they cared about you more.
After your parents died,
they started a fund
to help you get back on your feet.
Iris found bank statements
and donation receipts
all in your name,
Bashir Adil Malik.
You didn't know because you pushed
them away when they reached out.
[Psych] No. No, no, no.
Naomi would never help me.
You're right about that.
Naomi turned her back on you.
So you assumed the others would, too.
But they didn't.
They wanted to help.
So do we.
[Psych] No, no, no. There's no way.
This can't be true.
No, it is. Don't push us away
like you have with everyone else.
You always wanted a real family.
Give us a chance.
We can be your family.
[Psych] There's no such thing.
You don't know my pain.
You're right, Bashir, they don't.
But I do, because my past
is just as dark as yours.
[sighs]
I've been clean for five years.
But when I was at my lowest,
I drove away everyone I ever loved.
My own parents
won't even talk to me anymore.
I know what real loneliness
feels like.
But at some point,
the walls we build need to come down
or they will crush us.
And when they do, the people
who still want to be there for you,
that's real family. That's us.
Continue.
[Iris West] We'll wait for you, Bashir,
as long as it takes.
[exhales]
The choice is yours... brother.
Okay, thanks.
Bashir's victims are awake.
They're going to be okay.
What are you guys doing?
Barry and Alexa are bringing
a monster into our house.
- Two, actually.
- Can't be too careful.
[Bashir] That's probably wise.
Oh.
There's a lot of fear in this place.
I like it.
It's okay.
He's decided to give family a try.
For now.
I'm not sure if I'm sticking around.
Hey, you know those rifles
and whatever those gloves
are supposed to be,
that's not going to help you.
You know that, right?
Just a heads-up.
Don't make me angry.
You got lucky the first time.
You wanna roll the dice on round two?
- I think I have to...
- I gotta call Frost.
- I have a thing...
- Sorry.
You guys got this, right?
- Yeah.
- [phone vibrating]
Look, both of you, stand down.
We're on the same team now.
Her first.
Yeah, this is new for all of us,
so let's just take it slow,
all right?
Fine.
You wanted to see me?
[sighs]
Yeah.
I need to talk to you
about what happened today.
Okay, I'm listening.
As Captain,
it's hard to watch the ideals
that you built your whole career on
get stripped away.
I know, you're just doing your job.
I respect that.
It's just that I wish...
I wish...
that you could try to understand
what this city really needs.
Because, see, it's not just
black and white, or even gray...
I do things by the book, Captain.
Maybe, but it's gonna take
a whole lot more than that
when it comes to protecting
the people of Central City.
Only you can't see that.
And since your "by the book"
is nowhere near mine...
Do you realize what you're doing?
Yeah.
I'm staying on
the right side of the line.
So now you know everything we do.
Okay, so you got four kids,
two of which are so pissed off,
they want to kill you.
This is why some people
shouldn't have children.
[scoffs] You are such an ass.
I'm direct, sis.
There's a difference.
Look, the point is,
Nora will come after you, too.
Yeah, only if she's as nuts
as you say she is.
She is. Trust me.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Either way, I'm not scared of her.
- It's not that simple.
- You're not that simple.
Alexa's right.
We can't underestimate Nora.
As the Speed Force, she is different
than the rest of you.
She's been around since
the dawn of time.
And I thought I was dramatic.
You can't beat her.
Not alone. None of us can.
Which is why we need to find Deon
as soon as possible.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
Nora, please...
You made me do this, Barry.
It's done.
No...