Who's hungry?
Hi.
I didn't think you'd be
out of bed already.
Yeah. There was a car fire
on Route 220
and I thought
I'd bring home some breakfast,
but this looks a lot better.
Is that blueberry compote?
Freshly mashed
and paired with a savory bacon
and baked egg Danish.
Ms. Speed Force.
Are you okay, Barry?
You're not still feeling
the effects of Psych's attack, are you?
No, I'm good.
I just... I had no idea
that you could cook.
Bobby Flay has got nothing on Nora.
You know, it's funny.
Cooking is the process
of combining ingredients with heat
to create molecular change.
But this feels like so much more.
- Huh.
- Mimosa?
Sure.
Actually, I think I'm good.
So Chester has all the satellites
scanning for the new Forces.
There is the Sage Force,
the Strength Force,
and now the Still Force.
Yeah. So far, no hits
on any of their isotopic signatures.
Well, it's still good
that you're here with us.
The last time the Forces attacked you,
you almost died.
I don't want to burden anyone.
No. You're not.
You know, in a weird way,
it's like you've been
a part of this family all along.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm just
a little worried about the fact
that my powers are glitching again.
Especially since I just got 'em back.
Okay. Well, I can call Caitlin.
Have her run some more tests.
How do you feel now?
I feel fine. I just...
I don't know what happened.
Actually, I think I'm the reason.
Since I'm here now,
I'm increasing your abilities
as best I can.
It may take some getting used to,
but you'll need it
if the other Forces come back.
That's work.
I gotta go.
I should come with you.
- Oh.
- I'm like your battery now.
If Fuerza and Psych are back...
Yeah. No, I don't...
Having you at a crime scene
might not be a great idea.
You've already been hurt once.
I can help boost your speed.
I know. I know.
It's just... It might just be like
a traffic accident or something.
So, just... Let me find out.
Of course. But don't worry.
If you need me, I'll sense it
and I'll be there in a heartbeat.
Great.
Okay.
So I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
I hope he's okay.
One count of aggravated assault...
one count of attempted murder...
two counts of kidnapping.
It's a good thing you never lived up
to your original name.
I thought once you started
helping people
CCPD dropped their investigation.
Yeah, they did. They did.
But the state never officially
dropped its charges.
Which means Kristen Kramer
has everything that she needs
to put you in Iron Heights.
I'm gonna find Kramer
and I'm gonna kick her ass.
No! No, you're not!
Kramer is former Army Intelligence.
Wherever she goes, heads roll. Just...
Look, I'm not some thug anymore, okay?
I've grown.
I know that, honey. I do.
Look, I'm one of the people
that you kidnapped.
My advice to you as your attorney
is to lay low.
Wait. So Frost can't do
superhero stuff anymore?
Nope. Not out in the field.
Look, Frost, you're an artist, okay?
Just take some time off.
Chase those canvases. Create.
Just do it all here at S.T.A.R. Labs
where you're safe.
I just got a life and now
you're telling me I can't live it.
For a little while, yeah.
Look, Kramer is appointed
by the Governor, right?
She doesn't get results,
she's gonna get reassigned.
Frost, I know this isn't fair,
but it's our best option right now.
Fine! I'll quarantine here.
Blazing Bessie Blount!
I just got my first
solo crime scene call.
Oh. Cisco and Kamilla are away and all.
I'm the only CCPD
tech consultant around.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe a 10-90.
Maybe it's a 10-11.
Oh, snap! It's a 10-35!
Frost, I am so sorry. But I...
It's fine.
Go have your fun, Peralta!
Thank you. Thank you.
Sorry. Thank you.
Holy baby Grogu!
What happened here?
This delivery van was full of tech
and was hit by a perp in an ice attack.
Apparently, some experimental microchip
was stolen.
Oh. Doesn't sound so bad.
What's all that?
The driver.
Officers.
Looks like Killer Frost
has been busy.
I know how this looks,
but there are other criminals
that use ice to commit crimes,
like Leonard Snart.
Snart was a man with a gun.
Mr. Runk...
you're our new technical consultant
on meta-human affairs,
what's your take on all this?
Well... ma'am...
Shoot!
Dark matter levels are...
Dark matter levels here are...
Well...
Well, they're off the charts.
That doesn't mean it's Frost.
Look, you see the pattern
in these ice crystals here.
They're dendritic, like tree branches.
Frost's ice crystals
are usually hexagonal.
It's Killer Frost, Officer Allen.
And you seem to know a lot
about her powers.
Yeah, I've worked her crime scenes,
and she's never killed anyone.
Until now, apparently.
Officer Allen is our department's
top forensics examiner, ma'am.
If there's any evidence here
that we can use, he will find it.
And Killer Frost is still out there.
Captain, I hate to pull rank,
but Governor Williamson
gave me special authority
in order to address the city's
long-standing meta-human problems.
We need to keep public safety in mind.
- Agreed.
- Good.
Because I'm going to ask the DA's office
to issue a warrant
for Killer Frost's arrest.
I'm gonna need you
and your officers for backup.
I'll alert the Meta-human Task Force.
Thank you.
I need to update the Governor's office.
Excuse me.
Joe, you can't be serious.
We all know Frost didn't do this.
What am I supposed to say, Barry?
Yes, Frost did spend
the evening with Caitlin?
You can't give Kramer her alibi
without admitting
that you've talked to a fugitive.
Dang. That's a real catch-22,
two, two...
I'm sorry.
My timing on that was terrible.
I'm just gonna go tell Frost
what's going on.
We can't let Kramer arrest Frost.
You don't think I know that?
But we gotta follow orders.
So what are we supposed to do?
Frost can't lay low forever.
The only thing we can do, Barr.
Find the real meta-human that did this.
All right.
Huh. That looks painful.
Chuck. You said you had
something important to tell Frost.
Right.
Okay, well...
there's a new ice-meta in town
who killed an IVO Labs employee.
But Kristen Kramer
thinks that it was you,
so she kind of ordered Joe
to put the Meta Task Force on alert
while she gets a warrant
for your arrest.
What? Why didn't Joe and Barry stop her?
Because, technically, she's their boss.
She's also a very intimidating person.
But don't worry.
We're doing everything we can
to get this cleared up.
Me and Caitlin are even trying
to fix one of HR's transmogifiers
to work for you.
Thanks, Runk.
Look... is there anything else
I can do?
I mean, you know, if you need to talk
or vent
or get the weight off your shoulders,
Chester P. is all ears. All right?
Go tech-out, Chuck.
We'll be fine.
She's starting cardio anyway.
Right. Right. Okay.
Okay, he's gone. What's the plan?
I'm gonna do 12 miles.
Five years in Iron Heights over here.
You think I can't tell
when someone's lying?
Plus, there's no way
you'd stay put here.
You're going after Kramer.
No, not that.
You're going after
this new ice-meta yourself.
Yeah. I'm coming with you.
No, you're not.
So you're gonna do this alone?
What about the rest of Team Flash?
I need to handle this myself.
There are places
that Team Flash can't go.
Hell, I used to work at some of them.
And you aren't gonna say a thing.
I used to be a freakin'
car thief, Frost.
I know how to talk to criminals.
I'm not looking for a criminal.
I am looking for a killer.
You wanna help me? Cover my ass.
If I need backup, I'll call. Promise.
You must see a lot of strange
crime scenes working in this city.
Yeah. Yeah, this case is another one.
Usually, I'd find dark matter
dispersed evenly
throughout meta-produced ice.
But from what I can tell,
this ice has dark matter, just...
only on the surface.
What would cause that?
I don't know, but I'm gonna find out.
I'll let you work.
Thanks.
Have you been here the whole time?
She admires you.
Who... What, Kramer?
Okay, well, look,
she could be back any second.
Not to mention,
a dozen other officers. So...
I thought you were
gonna spend the day with Iris.
Well, I told her I needed
to stretch my legs.
Okay.
You know, it's just like you said.
The ice is different.
The particles inside all this,
I can feel them. They're...
compacted, constrained.
Like on a molecular level.
You know what? I... Um...
I need to get this back to my lab.
If I can... No! Hey! Hey!
If I can figure out
why this ice is different,
it might lead to the real...
Right. On my way.
- Allen?
- Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm... tracking footprints
from our suspect.
They led me out here. So...
- Where?
- What?
The... No, they're hard to detect
without one of these...
...infrared...
Cutting-edge tech.
- Yeah.
- Impressive.
Keep up the good work.
I like her.
Yeah...
Look, I really appreciate your help,
but I got it from here.
So I'll see you back at the loft, okay?
Of course. I understand.
The place was a lot more lively
when I worked here.
Yeah. Here for the ambiance?
Looking for a meta who likes ice.
A missing relative?
Ha-ha, funny guy.
Look, I used to do your job.
I know a good bar slinger
keeps his ears open more
than any of these losers.
I might know a few things.
Because... you're a bartender
who tends bar.
I'm looking for intel.
Something was taken
from IVO Labs this morning.
- Do you know anything about that?
- No.
But I do know a bit about science.
If you take a hydrometer
to a bottle of Plymouth Gin,
you'll find that
it has a specific gravity of.94.
Which means, a liqueur like, say...
creme de noyaux here,
will sink right...
to the bottom.
Ergo...
the secret to the smoothest cocktail
is density.
That is...
not bad.
Famous Killer Frost likes my work.
I'll call the Citizen.
It's just Frost now.
Oh.
Turn that up.
So in light of the violence
at IVO Labs this morning,
the Central City Police Department
is offering a $100,000 reward
for information leading to the arrest
of the meta-criminal
known as Killer Frost.
If you have any knowledge
on the whereabouts of Killer Frost
immediately call
the Meta-human Task Force.
Crap.
I had him.
Great. Guess I wasted an IPA then.
It's hot in
So hot in here
Oh
It's gettin' hot in here
Take a picture, why don't you?
Whatever.
See you around... sometime.
Hey, Frost.
There's a new meta in town.
It's got a thing for experimental tech.
Keeps it all at the old Wieringo complex
off Route 119.
If he's the guy,
you're gonna find him there.
What's that gonna cost me?
How 'bout a second visit?
Just ask for Mark.
- And a sprinkle of that
- Ah, ah
Let itjust fall out
- I like it when ya
- Ah, ah
- Girl, baby make it
Dude!
The 24-hour news cycle
picked up on Kramer's
John Wick: Parabellum move.
It's a great movie.
"Yeah, I'm thinking I'm back."
And I'm thinking we need to focus.
Frost is safe at S.T.A.R. Labs for now
but Kramer's not gonna back down,
not until we find proof.
Check this out.
Look at these cryo-membranes.
Speed Force is right.
It's way past compacted.
Now if we can just figure out why.
Barry, these computers
are way slower than you are.
I mean, this much data,
it's gonna take all night.
Cool, but scary.
I can feel how frustrated you are.
How can I help?
Look, it's okay.
We've got this.
Totally!
I mean, we are like the Power Rangers
of forensic science, basically.
Speed... Nora here... is omnipotent,
omnipresent and omniscient.
She's like our Zordon.
Say, can white hole singularities
actually exist without mass?
Yes.
I knew it! I knew it!
Barry, we don't have
to crunch data all night.
Nora can do it right now.
It's our job to find answers.
Of course. But...
You know,
Nora is a literal Force of Nature.
- He's right. Just let me...
- No.
No. We need to do this ourselves.
Maybe just this once?
Anybody else taste pennies?
It takes like there's 78 cents
in my mouth.
Barry, what did you do?
You've lost everything.
What did I do?
I didn't lose the data
that was supposed to clear Frost.
You did. By being here.
I was only trying to help.
I didn't ask for any!
Guys, maybe we should take five.
Barry, you helped me be reborn.
And now you're keeping me safe.
Of course I wanna help you.
I keep telling you
I didn't ask for help.
Look, you chose me to be the hero,
so let me be the hero.
I'm sorry about that.
You know what I meant, right?
Korber. Hey. What's going on?
Kramer's got a location on Killer Frost.
They're gonna bring her in.
I'm calling Frost.
She's not picking up.
Hey, Allegra.
Yeah, is Frost with you?
This is an emergency.
Sorry, Chuck. She's here.
But she's going full Amazon
with her workout.
What's the message?
Okay.
Tell her Kramer's making a move,
so Frost needs to stay put.
Got it.
Come on. Pick up! Pick up! Pick up!
Seriously?
CCPD.
You're surrounded.
Caitlin Snow,
I have a warrant for your arrest.
What's the charge?
Kramer to Task Force Command,
hold your positions around the perimeter
and prepare for prisoner transfer.
Are you alone, Dr. Snow?
Yes, but I think there's been a mistake.
Joe, what is this?
Who are you?
I'm Rene Carpenter,
I'm a clinician with the MHE team.
A mental health evaluation?
Yes, ma'am, it's standard procedure.
I'm just here to help.
Joe, what is going on?
Would you turn around, please?
Killer Frost,
you're under arrest
for aggravated assault,
attempted murder,
and two counts of kidnapping.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
Okay, so I just talked
to the DA's office.
Kramer didn't find anything
incriminating in your apartment.
So, once your blood tests come back
negative for the meta-gene,
they're gonna be forced
to release you from custody.
Great. This is the first
time I'm relieved
that Frost and I are
in different bodies.
Yeah.
- How did she know to come after me?
- Uh...
It was an anonymous tip.
Which means either
somebody got very lucky or...
Or somebody out there
knows that Frost used to be you.
I'm sorry, Caitlin,
but Kramer wouldn't tell me
where the task force was headed.
And by the time I knew it was too late.
It's okay, Joe. This is not on you.
This ain't how law enforcement
is supposed to work.
I'm gonna go talk to Kramer.
Look, I think the next step is...
Oh. Uh...
Frost? Where are you?
Across the street.
You and Caity get away
from the north wall.
North wall, okay. Uh...
I think that Frost
is about to try and bust you out.
- What?
- Yeah.
Put her on speakerphone.
Okay.
Frost, what the hell are you doing?
Getting you out of there.
You promised me
you would stay put.
Yeah, well, I lied. Now take cover.
- Oh.
- Don't you dare.
You're in there because of me.
I'm here because Kramer has
some sort of grudge against you, okay.
But you're innocent, and so am I.
So we just need
to let this play out, okay?
I'll be fine. Promise.
Yes, yes. Frost, she's right.
Look, I know this system.
Just let me handle this.
They have no case against Caitlin.
Honey, please stand down.
This isn't fair.
You shouldn't have to go through this.
Neither should you, okay?
When Kramer looks at you,
all she sees are the mistakes
you've made.
She doesn't see how much pain
you've gone through
or how much you've grown because of it.
You're a good person, Frost,
and human or meta-human,
you deserve the chance to prove it.
Human?
That's it. Thanks, Caity.
Thanks for what?
I figured out who framed us.
Now I'm gonna go find out why.
No. Frost!
Hey?
Sergeant Kramer! We need to talk.
I'm in a bit of a hurry, Captain.
Is there a problem?
Yes, there is.
You mobilized my task force
to harass someone
who, from all accounts, is innocent,
off of a phone call.
There's no way in hell
I would have authorized that.
- Captain...
- Sergeant,
we're not supposed to work that way.
That's your point of view,
and I respect that.
But I also respect the evidence.
Dr. Snow matches Killer Frost
in 80 nodal points
of facial recognition.
Their known whereabouts
over the last few months
line up perfectly.
And her prints
were all over that delivery van.
What's your conclusion?
I promise you, Caitlin Snow
and Killer Frost
are not the same person.
And even if they were, I doubt
that they wouldn't wear gloves
if they went on a killing spree.
This evidence,
this anonymous phone call,
it's like someone
is trying to frame Frost.
Okay, then who?
I don't know.
But Frost helps keep this city safe.
Hell, she saved my life more than once.
She's still a criminal.
Captain, you seem like a good cop.
And I know that Dr. Snow
is a friend of your family.
If you really want to honor your badge,
you need to think about
what is truly best for the public good.
If you'll excuse me.
Nora's still holed up
in the guest room.
I know she's a Force of Nature.
But as crazy as it sounds,
there is a person
forming inside of her too.
Iris, whatever she is, she's not human.
She's the Speed Force.
She powers my abilities.
You don't know what it's like, seeing...
someone like that
eating breakfast at our table.
That's why you don't want
to call her Nora.
Maybe I shouldn't have
invited her to stay here.
No, it was...
It was the right thing to do.
She needs us to keep her safe
and protecting her now
is the least I can do.
So what's wrong with me?
Nothing.
Nothing, Barry, it's just...
I think for you,
she's this all powerful cosmic entity,
but she's changed.
I don't know how or why,
but whatever she was before,
she's even more now.
Do you remember when I first came back
from college after freshman year?
Yeah, I was living in my own apartment,
and you moved back in with Joe.
Yeah, it was great for a while.
I was waitressing and making tips,
trying to write my dissertation.
But after about a week,
me and Dad started butting heads
over the stupidest things.
Me coming in late at night,
him watching sports all day Saturday
when I was trying to study.
I mean, all we did was argue.
I remember. Joe told me how bad
he felt through all that.
Yeah.
And do you want to know why?
Because when I left that fall,
I really was his baby girl.
But when I got back,
we were both adults.
Different habits, different schedules.
We weren't
just father and daughter anymore.
Finding a new normal between
the two of you is gonna take some time
and it may get pretty painful
along the way.
But that's how relationships grow.
It's Chester.
He's got a lead on the new ice meta.
- I gotta...
- Yeah.
What'd you find?
Okay, so I somehow managed to salvage
some of the ice data that we lost.
Remember how the dark matter at the
crime scene had compacted membranes?
Yeah.
It's because it wasn't
dark matter at all.
- It's a half-life variant.
- Artificial dark matter?
That means the killer
that we're after isn't a meta.
They're human.
Somebody's been fooling us
this whole time.
Somebody who's an expert in science
and knows that Frost and Caitlin
used to be one person.
We should ask Frost...
Wait, where is Frost, anyway?
Fine. I lied, okay?
She went looking for our baddie
by herself.
Frost went full Fugitive?
If this new killer is trying to frame
Frost, they might come after her next.
I know. It's my fault.
She made me promise not to tell anyone,
but I should have said something.
It's okay. Let's just...
Let's focus on finding her
before it's too late.
That was fast.
So, Mark, give me one good reason
why I shouldn't live up to my name.
Because Caitlin wouldn't like it.
Thirsty?
All right. I know that you're angry
because I know all about you
and you know nothing about me.
So go ahead.
Ask away.
- How did you know...
- That you and Caitlin were related?
I'm an observant guy. Sue me.
In studying you,
I also traced your movements.
Every fight, every battle.
Stalk much?
Honestly, finding out
that you and Caitlin
seem to come and
go interchangeably was,
well, let's call it
more of a happy accident.
- Did come in handy, though.
- So you could frame us.
That's why you sent me
to that empty warehouse,
which wasn't really empty, was it?
Very good.
See, I already had the chip.
I just needed one final thing.
A neurogenic scan of you
to perfectly replicate your powers.
Neurogenic?
It's quite a fancy word for a thief.
Yeah, maybe because I'm not a thief.
I simply took back what was mine.
The microchip?
You built it. So you worked at IVO Labs.
I'm a cryo-geneticist. The best.
Let me guess.
Your former employers didn't agree.
They said that the experiments
I was conducting were...
inhuman.
So they got a warrant
to put me in a cozy
Iron Heights cell
for the rest of my life.
Unlike you, I've been smart enough
to avoid capture.
I'd rather die than end up
in some warm prison.
Have you even heard of hypothermia?
It doesn't matter.
When I was nine,
I went ice skating up on Central Lake.
It was Christmas, so the ice
should've been thick enough.
But I fell through.
I was submerged body and soul
for over 15 minutes.
Yeah, at first, the cold was terrifying.
But then after 20 seconds or so,
it got warm.
Hot, even.
And then I died.
And the paramedics saved you
and now you're obsessed
with refrigerators.
- I get it.
- No, you don't.
The ice, it holds the power
of life and death.
A power so clearly wasted
on you, Killer Frost.
I've watched you for years,
admiring your abilities,
wondering what I could do with them.
All I needed was for IVO to move
my microchip out of deep freeze
so that I could steal it back again
and then combine it
with that pesky scan of you.
And now, I'm as powerful as you are.
Bring it on, Mark.
If that even is your real name.
Oh, Mark Blaine. That was my name.
But you can call me Chillblaine.
Kind of like this.
You fight like a boy.
What the hell did you do?
Looks like somebody's snow blind.
Guys,
satellites just picked up
one hell of a cryokinetic spike
on the Southside of Keystone.
Frost said she might be going somewhere
she used to work.
O'Shaughnessy's. Let's go.
You still want me to come?
After I lied to you?
Someone's got to convince Frost
to come home.
To think you have so much strength,
so much power,
but so little imagination...
I guess that just means
I'm a better meta than you.
Actually, Chillblaine...
You're not a meta at all.
One thing your bracelets can't copy,
Ice healing.
Frost, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. It's just a scratch.
I could use a little help
with this, though.
I got it.
Thanks.
- They broke you down?
- I tried.
- Honest.
- It's okay.
The only other person I trusted today
just tried to kill me.
So arriving with backup,
I'll let it slide.
So, who is he?
He calls himself "Chillblaine."
Wow, I'm glad Cisco is not around
to hear that one.
Chillblaine didn't just commit
a crime against good taste,
he also killed the IVO Labs driver.
And I've got his confession on tape.
That means you're in the clear.
Killer Frost.
Come out with your hands raised.
You have two minutes to comply.
Flash, there's a whole squad of CCPD
cars outside of your location.
Yeah, we're trying
to handle it, Chester.
Killer Frost,
there is nowhere to go.
We have you surrounded.
You have one minute.
So what?
Let 'em try...
Or we could try calming down.
Chillblaine here is the real killer.
So I'll go out, I'll hand him over,
I'll let 'em know you're innocent.
Guys...
I may not have killed that person today,
but I'm not innocent.
I have to go out there myself.
- What?
- Frost...
Kramer has a warrant for all the crimes
you committed before joining Team Flash.
You get arrested?
You're facing hard time
if there's a conviction.
Uh-uh. That ain't happening.
We can hide you somewhere
while we figure this out.
Right, and then
you're harboring a fugitive.
I can't let you do that.
Guys, before today, I never paid
for any of the bad things I did.
Because you were out saving the world.
And I thought that was enough too.
But if I'm going to prove
that I've really changed,
then I have to own up to it
as painful as that might be.
Frost, I've been to Iron Heights.
Jails do not make better people.
They're hell.
You cannot do this.
I think I have to.
You're not going to try
and stop me, are you?
Not unless you want me to.
- I don't.
- Frost...
Please. What if you don't come back?
Don't worry, I will.
No.
Time's up. Go!
I'm coming out.
Guys.
Is Frost really doing this?
It's her choice, Chester.
Something tells me it's the right one.
Yeah, thanks. Bye.
That was Cecile.
Caitlin is back home.
Now she's trying to get Frost out
on bail before the sentencing hearing.
What about a trial?
Frost is pleading guilty
to all her old crimes.
So whatever happens to her next
is up to the judge.
Well, at least Chillblaine will be
in Iron Heights for a very long time.
Yeah.
How does Caitlin feel about it all?
I'm not sure.
I think she was just getting used
to Frost having her own body.
And I know how hard it can be
when a relationship like that
changes in a snap.
Speaking of which,
I should get ready for work.
Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
No, it's fine.
It's okay.
I could feel you listening.
And I'm glad. I wanted to say I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten
so upset with you earlier.
No, it's okay.
I tried to fit in somewhere
I didn't belong.
Being here in your home
with you and Iris,
it's not my place.
Yes, it is.
Look, I know how much things
have changed between us.
You're not the same as the Speed Force
I'm used to interacting with.
I can't expect you
to be the way you were.
It's not fair to you.
To either of us.
You're something else now.
Something new.
And it's something I'd like
to get to know better, Nora.
And look, no more glitching.
I'm almost fully-healed.
So now we can take on
all three Forces. Together.