Deon, what's happening to me?
The temporal mutations
I've been tracking?
It turns out every one of them
leads to you.
I know I've been treating
your time sickness
like it's a virus
that's giving you symptoms.
The gaps in time.
And now I've been noticing that things
are there one minute
and they're gone the next.
There's something about you that's
causing time to fracture around you.
Iris, this isn't a virus
that you have.
Whatever this time sickness is...
It's coming from me.
What is it?
What's wrong?
How do you feel right now?
Well, I mean, that's what's so weird.
I feel fine.
And this is all because of what happened
in the other timeline?
Yeah.
I should've never reversed
your treatments.
No, it's not your fault, Deon,
I asked you to do it,
and it was the right thing to do.
There was no other way to prove Barry's
innocence and to save my dad's life.
But these anomalies you're experiencing,
I mean, who knows what's next?
- Well, we have to find a cure.
- And we will.
Right now, we've got to
get you stabilized.
I'm sorry,
but you gotta stay put.
Well, I mean, there are worse places
to hang out.
How long do I have to stay?
Well, considering the universe
is like a zillion light years large,
I'd say staying put is a relative thing
when it comes to Earthly movement.
So I'm thinking that if you confine
your movements
to Coast City for a while,
it should lessen the risk.
Or at least I hope so.
Good, because there's still
someone here that needs my help.
What if she has another episode?
Well, I'll have to do something
a little more radical this time
to patch you up.
Look, I won't lie to you guys.
This is gonna hurt.
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Iris, if you have any blackouts
or anything weird happens,
you let me know ASAP.
Okay, I'm gonna go grab
a few of my things from home.
I'll be back in a few seconds.
No, no. Barry, you can't.
I mean, remember what you said
about that black fire.
There are people that are still
in danger. You have to stop it.
But I can't just leave you here alone.
I'm not. I mean, Sue will be back soon,
and besides, I mean,
I have work to do, too.
Your world is falling apart
and you're still worried about
helping other people.
You just call me if you need anything.
- I will.
- Okay.
Now that is what you call art.
Since when do I sweat?
What the hell?
Is Iris okay?
Yeah. I mean, you know,
as well as she can be.
Well, Barry,
are you sure you don't wanna...
I mean, Team Flash can hold down
the fort, if you need to be with her.
No, thanks. Iris is right.
I mean, as long as she's stable,
keeping everyone safe
in Central City is the priority.
Joe, Cecile, you guys found anything?
Uh, well, besides all suffering
recent personal losses, no.
None of our fire victims
had anything in common.
Yeah, Barr, I triple checked
the victims' files.
Stan Mullens, Donna Winters,
that yoga instructor, Parker DeStefano.
At first, we thought
all these freaky flames
are feeding on people
who recently mourned, like Mullens.
Then it attacked me
and my dad died when I was a kid.
Which doesn't follow the pattern.
Maybe it's looking for people
who don't face their grief.
No, I don't think so.
DeStefano had completed grief counseling
after her fiancé died,
and she was already seeing somebody new.
Well, I've assigned Vanya and Aariz
to dig into the backgrounds
of our victims,
for secondary similarities.
You sound just like Iris.
No wonder she put you in charge.
Speaking of similarities,
Kramer pulled files
for every suspicious fire-related crimes
since the particle accelerator exploded.
So, me and Cecile have to
go through all of it.
And there's a ton.
So are you ready, babe?
Mm.
Later.
What's an SR37 alert?
Someone just entered the Med Lab.
What? Is Caitlin back from
her wine country tour with Marcus?
No, not yet.
Stay here.
Hey. Any idea where
Caity keeps the bandages?
It seems more like a "top shelf"
kinda thing, if you ask me.
- What happened to your arm?
- Oh.
Our freaking fire attacked me
at the apartment.
And before you ask,
no, I don't know why it didn't kill me.
- Were you...
- Grieving?
Nope. I was perfectly happy
working on a new piece.
Could be the best thing I've ever done.
But that does not explain
why our Sentient Smokey Joe
would attack me,
and only leave me with this.
Frost, come here. Let me help. Ow.
Ah.
You make a good Caity-substitute.
Maybe it's like Joe says,
there's got to be something more.
- It's after something we're missing.
- Something I have?
I don't know.
But, I mean, this fire attacked
you and me here at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And then follows you home
less than 24 hours later?
That can't be a coincidence.
So if we can figure out why the flames
think I'd be a tasty snack...
Maybe that could tell us how to stop it.
Frost, um, if it's okay, I'd like to
search your apartment top to bottom,
see if there's any clues as to why
the fire is targeting you.
Go for it.
Okay.
Frost. Been a while
since we caught up. What's wrong?
It's about Team Flash's new case,
and this one's a little creepy.
Over the last few weeks,
three bodies have turned up,
all of them burnt to a crisp.
So this is an arson case?
Mm...
More like a ghost story.
The fires that did the damage
were black.
And so cold that they burn the victims
like frostbite,
only 1,000 times more lethal.
And you need my help to figure out
what's causing this phenomenon?
Not exactly.
The flames are alive
and they are attacking people,
and I think they're coming after me.
My God, of course. I'll do
whatever I can to help keep you safe.
Actually, I need you
to do just the opposite.
I want you to help me catch this thing,
using me as bait.
You want to use yourself as bait
to capture the black fire?
I know how it sounds, but hear us out.
If this homicidal stuff is after me now,
why not use it to our advantage?
Carla, you can't actually
be considering this.
I wasn't at first.
And then Frost laid out the facts in the
case, how it's killing innocent people.
And now it's coming after her, too,
with flames that generate a cold
so intense it burns?
That last item is almost an exact
description of how cold fusion works.
But why is the fire attracted to Frost?
I believe it's because
her meta abilities are cryokinetic,
just like our cold fusion fire.
So you think it's hunting her for fuel?
To recharge itself?
Correct. So the key to catching it
is to wait until it comes
after her again and then trap it.
Frost, we are not using you as bait.
Look, this is a perfectly good plan
that could save lives.
Why won't you at least let us try?
Because this feels like a last resort.
Besides, there's still so much
we don't know about this fire.
I mean, even if we tried this,
we still have no way to capture it.
Cold fusion is still a fusion reaction,
one that occurs at
a low molecular temperature.
If we could build some kind
of fusion containment housing...
Then all we'd need to do
is recalibrate the unit
to absorb and amplify
Frost's cryokinetic signature.
Yes. Then, as long as Frost
is in proximity,
the unit can amplify
her cryokinetic signature,
and attract the fire,
allowing us to capture and imprison it.
Of course, building a unit like that
could take weeks or longer.
Well, not that I'm saying
we should do this at all,
but we kind of already have
what you're describing.
We do?
The Fusion Sphere from the ASF.
It can already handle the entire output
of the artificial Speed Force.
If Dr. Tannhauser and I recalibrate it
for a cryokinetic signature,
we'd be in business.
Great. Then it's settled.
Chester, you and Mom
work on the nerd stuff.
- Allegra, you and I...
- Wait around for you to get killed?
Barry, whatever this thing is,
it's coming after me no matter what.
So I am not going to sit around
and do nothing
when we have a plan to fight back.
Barry, it's your call.
Ditto that.
I'm sorry, but I can't support this.
I know we don't have
another plan right now,
but putting you in harm's way?
There's got to be another option.
I still think this could work.
Get started, I'll be back.
Look, I'm not going to change my mind.
Okay, fine. But just hear me out.
Before this, you were telling us
about Iris and her condition.
How she wants to help Tinya,
but Deon told her to stay put.
Do you really think
that's what she's doing right now?
Because if I know Iris...
She's gonna try and help Tinya
find her mom.
Instead of sitting in a hotel,
doing nothing and helping no one.
But she's not
endangering herself either.
But she is doing
what this whole team does best.
Helping people.
Despite what it could mean
for themselves.
Sound familiar?
Look, my mom is the world's
top specialist in cold fusion,
and she thinks this will work.
Chester agrees.
So why won't you give me the chance
to make a difference
that you're giving Iris?
Okay.
- But if anything goes wrong...
- You'll pull the plug. Got it.
Yes!
I finished fine-tuning the sphere to
amplify Frost's cryokinetic signature.
Now make sure to calibrate
the containment housing...
To compensate for the possibility
of a reconfiguration flip
at the subatomic level?
Already done.
Really? Well, when this is over,
there's a job waiting for you
at Tannhauser Labs.
Spoiler, I pay better.
For real?
I mean, nah,
you know, I actually kinda like it here.
Suit yourself.
We're ready. Frost.
Okay. What next?
Chester, activate
the cold Fusion Sphere.
Now remember, the sphere will amplify
your cryokinetic signature,
drawing the fire near.
But you need to stay in the gurney
until the fire is pulled into
that sphere and we've trapped it.
Okay, so now we just wait around
for some sentient fire
to come get its dinner?
That could take forever.
Not if Carla is right.
The sphere will amplify Frost's
cryo signature exponentially.
Like an animal scent
getting broadcast to a larger area
to entice a predator and draw them in.
Making Frost honey on a fly trap.
Once it senses her, it'll pounce.
And then we've got it.
If this spooky thing is looking for fuel
instead of just grief,
it's the place to find it.
Frost, about what you're doing.
I don't know if I'd have
the strength to do the same.
I mean, I'm just saying
you're very brave.
Thanks.
Although right now, I kinda feel like
the stupid person in the horror movie
who runs into the house
instead of running away from it.
Folks, our intelligent ignition source
just popped back up on the grid
and it's heading here fast.
Somebody turned up the heat.
It's here.
It's working.
Why did it stop?
Something's not right.
What are you waiting for?
Come and get me.
It knows what we're planning.
Frost!
Thank goodness you're all right.
We're lucky your boss is a superhero.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- I am fine.
I thought you were on vacation.
I was and then Allegra called and said
you were using yourself as bait
to summon an uncontrollable fire
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
What the hell were you thinking?
That we could end this
and save folks' lives.
Also, your bedside manner is terrible.
Frost, she's right.
We're worried about you.
Barry says you antagonized the flames.
Was that part of your plan, too?
It didn't take the bait.
What else was I supposed to do?
Okay, what happened out there
after the Babadook Blaze went postal?
Once we got you back to the Med Lab,
I did a grid search of the entire city.
There's no sign of it.
We need to get back out there.
What we need to do is find
another way to stop this thing.
Frost, we know how dangerous
this thing is.
I mean, it's killed three people
already that we know of.
It came after me, again.
We can do this.
I hear the cold Fusion Sphere
didn't even work.
More precisely, we never had a chance
to see if it would work.
The fire hesitated,
so it didn't get close enough.
If only there was a way to make Frost
more attractive to the flames.
Sounds like something
Chester can help us with.
I'll have him meet us in the Speed Lab.
Sit down.
Can I have the room, please?
You stay.
I don't understand.
You said over the phone that you could
give me the information in person.
I am sorry, Mrs. West-Allen.
You said you'd fix this.
And I will.
Look, I've worked stories like this
before, and I've never had a problem.
I know. But after your call,
I checked the files in question.
It turns out there's
a no-contact rule in play.
Wait. You mean someone doesn't want me
to find my own birth mother?
Uh, who? I want to know right now.
Okay. Tinya, hi.
Why don't you just give us a few minutes
so that we can work things out?
Right. She's my mom, all right?
I have a right to know the truth.
Okay.
Look, is there anyone we could talk to
about overriding a no-contact order?
No one.
I mean, I'd need approval from our board
of directors for something like that.
Oh! Is that all?
I got this.
Hi, Uncle Leroy.
Yes, it's Sue.
Yeah, I'm in town for the day.
Yeah. I am so glad that you asked.
I just need a little favor
from the R.A.A. Chairman of the Board.
Yes, it's a no-contact order.
It's really important.
I'm trying to help an orphan.
I know, just like you.
It's for you.
Yes, sir.
Of course, no problem.
Thank you.
- Yeah, okay.
- Just a sec.
Sorry about that.
Oh, no problem.
You were just doing your job.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I need a break.
Okay.
Ready for the next step?
How about I go pull up the car?
What's wrong?
I thought this is what you wanted.
Um...
What if my mom doesn't want to meet me?
She will.
Iris, she gave up on me
the moment I was born.
So what if nothing's changed?
Tinya, look, when I was your age,
my mom wasn't in my life, either.
and there was so much trauma around it.
All the lies I had been told,
the feelings of abandonment,
how much it hurt.
And it got so bad
that when I finally had the chance
to reconcile with my mom,
I almost lost the opportunity.
And then someone made me realize
that reconnecting with my mom,
no matter how or why was a gift.
And let me tell you, I am really glad
that I listened to them.
Because I barely
got to heal my relationship
with my mother before she passed.
Um...
Hey, I'm really sorry.
I didn't know that.
No, it's okay. I'm just saying
that I almost made a mistake
that I would have regretted
for the rest of my life.
How did you do it?
I mean, where did you even start?
I told her I was scared.
I told her I was angry.
And also that I loved her,
even though I didn't know why.
And, Tinya, whatever you do,
everything is going to be okay.
Because you're not going to do it alone.
I won't let you.
Come on.
Frost.
Why do you keep doing this?
You need to stop putting your
personal safety in danger for nothing.
Like when you stabbed yourself
just to get Chillblaine arrested
- that first time.
- That turned out okay. This will, too.
You don't know that.
Damn it, Frost, it's like you
don't even care about yourself.
I'm trying to help people.
Right. Okay, but at some point,
you need to realize
that you could also get yourself killed.
And then you need to think, "Hmm.
Maybe I shouldn't do this," or,
"Hmm... Maybe I should come up
with a different plan.
One that doesn't get me killed."
And you, Mom, seriously,
how could you go along with this?
Frost's powers presented an opportunity
to take this thing off the streets.
And that's where our focus has been
ever since.
You put her life at risk.
You realize that, right?
Because she asked me to.
And that makes it okay?
Hey, we made a decision today
to try to protect people.
I would think that you
would be fine with that.
What I am not fine with
is losing Frost forever,
which is what could have happened today.
You used your child as bait
for a monster.
It's not how I see it.
No, you don't, because
you're looking at Frost
as a science experiment
instead of as your daughter.
Frost, please listen to me.
You need to learn
to value your own life.
Carla, you still think
that fusion globe will work?
Yes, if we can find a way
to make sure it gets closer next time.
Great. I'll have Chester
start working on it.
Frost, wait. Uh...
Our plan will work.
You better hope it does, because
right now you have two daughters.
But if something happens to Frost
because of something
you helped her with, you'll have none.
Barr, I ran into Carla Tannhauser.
She told me about her plan
to stop these devil flames.
And your objection.
Yeah.
You want to tell me your side,
because I'm pretty sure I'm not
the only one that wants
to get these damn things off the street.
Look, I know why she's doing this
and she's not wrong.
If there's something
out there hurting people,
then we need to do
everything we can to stop it.
Right. So what's the problem?
She's found a way to use Frost's powers
to lure the black fire here
by boosting Frost's powers to trap it.
- And that's a bad plan because...
- It's too dangerous.
Frost has already been hurt once.
If we try this again,
something even worse could happen.
That's not all
you're concerned about, is it?
I mean, my gut told me
this was a bad idea.
I should have listened to it.
And now you're worried about
not being able to stop it,
because these things
were set in motion?
I'm team leader.
Having a plan
that keeps everybody safe is my job.
Only today,
I don't know how.
And now our only solution is
putting a team member's life
in jeopardy.
Hmm.
Are you talking about Frost or Iris?
Mm-hmm.
I'm worried about her, too.
But you're the one
who also left your wife in Coast City
asking the same question
you're asking about Frost.
Is it safe for her to continue
her mission or pull the plug?
Look, I'm not the boss here.
So I can't make the decision for you.
But I can tell you this.
Sometimes the hardest part
about being a leader is letting go,
and trusting the ones you've trained
to make the call themselves.
And then you'll be there for them
in a blink of an eye.
Took you long enough.
Jeez, where is Chester?
We got a lot of work to do.
He's not coming.
Frost, I talked to Caitlin.
Let me guess.
She changed your mind.
So what, now you're here
to give me some sort of mom talk?
- Seriously?
- Yes, I am.
Because I am your mom.
And it's time I start acting like it.
Frost, I think it's wonderful
that you have such a strong instinct
to protect people.
But from what Caitlin shared
and what I saw
with my own eyes today,
I think your sister's right.
You need to stop being so reckless.
You don't get it. This is Team Flash.
Protecting people,
kinda in the job description.
No, you don't get it.
You can't help anyone if you're dead.
I swear, sometimes
you remind me of your father.
Oh. A murderous psychopath. Gee, thanks.
No, not Icicle. Thomas.
Your father would do whatever it took
to protect his family, too.
Including creating you to save Caitlin.
But he took it too far
and it cost him a future
with the people who loved him the most.
And I don't want to see you
go down that road.
Neither do I.
Look, you people think I have
some sort of death wish or something,
but it's not that.
I was literally born
to be Caity's bodyguard.
Asking me not to jump
in the line of fire,
it's like asking the sky
not to be freaking blue.
Frost, you're more than a bodyguard.
You're an incredible young woman
and a vital part of Team Flash.
And of the Snow family, too.
Because you're my daughter.
And as your mother,
it's my job to protect you.
Which is why I'm telling you
there's a time for protecting others,
and there's a time
for protecting yourself.
And now is the time to do the latter.
I...
I should have seen it before,
and I hope you do now.
Yeah, I do.
But what about the Phantom Flicker?
I still think your plan would work.
We just need to keep you safe.
So the way to do that
is to trap the fire quickly.
I think if we add a secondary
cryokinetic signature,
it would make the meal more appetizing.
- Like frosting on a cake.
- Mm.
But I'm unique.
No one has cryo powers like me.
I do.
After your... After Icicle put me
in his cryo-chamber,
Caitlin and I did a test
for any residual meta-genome signatures
in my body.
Yeah, I remember.
It came back negative.
Mm. It was wrong.
According to my research,
my exposure in Icicle's chamber
activated a latent cryo-gene.
I don't have ice powers yet,
but I have the potential for them.
Frost, if we combine
your cryokinetic signature with mine...
It would be impossible
for it to resist us.
Yes, and there'll be less risk
because the fire won't hesitate
and we'll be able to trap it quickly.
What do you say?
I'm in. Just one more person
we need to get on board.
Not anymore.
I'm still not thrilled
with how dangerous this plan is.
But Mom's right.
If the two of you work together,
the fire won't hesitate,
and then we can trap it.
And that will keep everyone safe.
Guys, the black fire's back.
It just landed downtown.
Yeah. So whatever you guys
are gonna do, it's now or never.
Okay, let's take this thing out.
Once and for all.
How long have you known?
That I have my own
cryokinetic signature? For a while now.
Turns out it runs in the family.
I can't believe you didn't tell us
there's two Ice Queens
in the Snow family.
And if you ever need
to learn more about
how to control your powers,
we're here for you.
Thanks. It means a lot.
- Now let's get to work.
- Yes.
Okay, we are ready.
And, Mom, just so you know,
the tests I ran confirm your findings.
Your latent genome
plus Frost's meta signature
should amplify the sphere's
cryokinetic output exponentially.
Giving our bonfire from hell
an offer it can't refuse.
And then some.
Listen, Barry, I know you've never been
on board with this plan, so,
- if anything goes wrong...
- I know. You'll pull the plug.
I trust you. All of you.
Don't worry.
If it comes to that, I'll still be ready
to get us all out of here in a second.
Do you do this kind of thing
all the time?
Do what?
Be a hero.
What can I say,
it's a living.
Yeah. They just don't tell you
how intense it can be.
You're gonna do great, and remember,
what you're doing will save lives.
- I know.
- And after this, we can get dinner.
Okay. But only if you let me buy.
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
Okay.
Their vitals look good.
Activating the sphere.
Okay. Focus on your powers, like this.
I feel strange.
- Means you're doing it right.
- Okay.
Caitlin, how are they doing?
Their bio-signatures
are in sync.
Yeah, well, the containment system's
active. Chester?
Great Otis Boykin,
It just changed direction.
And heading straight for us.
Contact in five...
Four... Three... Two... One.
It's working.
The sphere is losing its integrity,
it's trying to break free.
- We have to abort.
- No! No. I can do this.
Barry, we can't do this.
She's going into cardiac arrest.
Carla, we have to let it go.
No, it's worth it to sacrifice me.
What happened?
It's gone again.
We still have no idea why.
Did we get it?
No. And that's okay.
Oh.
So you just let that hellfire go?
It's on me. I made the call.
And it was
the right thing to do.
You put Carla and
your own safety first.
And you saved Mom's life.
But Joe's right.
We had a chance to stop it
and we didn't.
No, that was before I knew you made
a judgment call, Frost, and a good one.
Look, don't worry, we will stop
that thing. That's what we do.
Yeah, your mom sounds
like she's a fighter.
She is.
She's going to make
a great meta.
Just one thing, though.
We're back to square one.
Joe, Cecile, have you found anything
that can help us
in Captain Kramer's files?
I wish. We are almost through them all,
and still nothing.
So, we failed?
No, we didn't fail. Thanks to Frost.
Now we know the cold Fusion Sphere
can contain that thing.
And that's a win.
Barry's right. That means
we can try again to capture it.
And this time it will work.
If we could create a strong enough
signal, the sphere could work
without someone's cryokinetic RNA
in close proximity.
Good. So no bait.
Yeah, which'll keep
Frost and Carla safe.
And then we can catch
the fire again.
Take the fight to it this time.
I'm telling you, I'm okay, really.
Caity says you need to rest.
Fine, I'll stay the night.
But then I promise, I'll be
out of your hair in the morning.
It's really no problem.
Also, I'm sorry I yelled at you two.
Don't be. I needed to hear it.
Both of us did.
Thank you for keeping us safe,
like you always do.
Good thing, too, 'cause I
couldn't lose you... Either one of you.
Oh, shoot. It's Marcus.
He has no idea what happened today.
What happened to going all in?
Yeah. I really do need
to tell him everything.
Just, um... not tonight.
Hey! No, I'm fine.
Just a crazy day at work.
How are you?
So about that dinner
we were supposed to have...
How about we make it brunch
in the morning?
Absolutely.
And, Frost, I need to apologize, too.
I should have told you
about my condition sooner.
I just... I guess I was just worried
about what it could mean for me.
Maybe if we talked more,
you would have felt more comfortable
sharing it with me.
Yeah.
It's okay.
- Something to work on.
- Yeah.
I've missed so much of your life,
and that's my fault.
There is so much about you
that I don't know
and so much that I want to know.
Really?
Yes, of course. It's like I said before,
you're my daughter.
And I love you, Frost.
You do?
More than you could ever know.
You're okay.
Can I help you?
Are you Renee Wazzo?
Who's asking?
Your daughter.
All the adoption websites
warn you about days like this.
That's not what...
I mean, it's just...
I guess I knew
this might happen eventually.
Maybe even wanted it.
Yeah, me, too.
Look, I'm sure you have
so many questions.
Just one, actually.
Um...
Why didn't you want me?
I always wanted you, Tinya.
I want you to know that.
The truth is, I wanted to be your mom
more than anything,
but I was so young.
I was 16 and confused,
and my parents were furious.
They convinced me that the best thing
for both of us was to sign that clause,
then give you away.
They were wrong.
I swear to you, I've never regretted
anything more than letting you go.
The only way
I could get through
this crap life of mine that came after
was the hope
that you were living a good life.
A better life without me.
No, I'm not.
I needed you.
I needed my mother.
Tinya, I...
Iris?
Whoa. What is wrong with her?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
What the hell?
Mom?
Mom? Mom?
What did you do to my mom?
Frost?
Frost, that isn't funny.
Caitlin.
The world is different now.
There is no normal life for us.
Oh, my God.
Cait, the world's different now.
Look, I thought we could get away.
Start a normal life together,
but there is no normal life for us.
Ronnie?