To understand
what I'm about to tell you,
there is something
you need to remember.
In every atom,
there is a perfect balance
of protons and electrons.
But it's those negative particles
that let an atom grow.
My name is Dr. Meena Dhawan,
and for the next three minutes and
52 seconds, I'm the fastest woman alive.
Oh. My. Gosh.
Did you see that?
I just hit 300 meters per second.
It's your best time yet.
Now let's see if you can keep up.
Come on.
Come on, Meena.
I'm so sorry. What just happened?
You created
your own lightning bolt again.
Something I couldn't do for months
when I first got my speed.
I didn't mean to do it.
I was just frustrated I couldn't
catch up, and then it just happened.
I've never seen artificial lightning
interact with organic lightning
like this before.
Okay, that's disturbing.
We should go over your biometrics,
make sure everything else
is within normal parameters.
Yeah.
I... I can't,
I have to head back to the lab.
My speed is running out.
Okay, tomorrow 10:00 a.m.
Hi, I just need to...
make a little deposit.
It's in here somewhere.
I have this new client
who decides to pay me in cash.
What year is it?
Oh! Got it. There we go.
All right.
Everybody, on the ground!
Get down!
Move!
You. Cash in the bag.
Don't even think about
hitting the alarm.
Hey, teacup! You trying to be a hero?
Are you for real?
Get down, lady!
What part of "Get down on the ground"
don't you understand? Let's go!
If you don't get on the ground,
I swear to God...
Three...
Two...
One.
No.
What am I doing here?
I should have been an engineer.
I just wanna go home. No voodoo, please.
No voodoo.
C.C.P.D.!
Stay where you are!
Fiery Francis Sumner,
Cecile, according to Gideon,
your empathic capacity's up 1,000%.
Your brain just got supercharged.
Usually when I sense a wave of fear
and panic, it just hits me like a train.
Like when we fought Blockbuster.
Exactly. Except this time
when my powers kicked in,
I barely broke a sweat.
Which is all very badass.
But is anyone else wondering
how the heck this happened?
Well, I mean, I don't know.
My powers have changed before,
like when Jenna was born.
Maybe it's just natural.
It's possible,
but let's run some more tests
just to make sure.
- Barry.
- Hmm.
I can feel a massive wave of concern
wash over you.
You're worried about something.
It's way more than just me.
It's the new speedster I'm training,
Meena Dhawan.
During our last training session, I got
struck by her artificial lightning.
Now, it was an accident.
But when it hit me,
it collided with my lightning
and it set off some kind
of a bio-kinetic chemical reaction.
Okay. Accidental attacks.
Artificial speed...
Is she about to go all Spock, Flash?
No, I don't think so.
I mean, Meena did find a way to generate
her own speed source artificially,
but it's not affecting her
like it did me.
I mean, her emotions seemed fine.
So it's just her powers that are funky.
Maybe you should fathwoom
over to Fast Track Labs,
take a peek at that generator.
See how her speed machine
really works.
- Barry Allen.
- Yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, no.
How can I help you?
Yeah, actually, I am here
on behalf of a mutual friend.
Who likes to run... fast.
- Oh.
- Yes.
Our friend was hoping I could take
a look at your, um, special project.
He thinks it'd be a good idea
to get a second set of eyes on this
just to make sure everything is safe.
I understand.
And he's right.
I could use another scientific eye
on all this right now.
- Okay.
- Follow me.
Yeah.
There she is, my pride and joy.
Wow.
Is that an oscillation chamber?
It's a Biometric Lightning
Oscillation Chamber, technically.
We call it the B.L.O.C.
It's filled with quantum computing
to remotely harness lightning
from the Earth's upper atmosphere,
and turn it into artificial speed.
This equipment is decades ahead
of any other lab.
Oh, including yours, I hope?
But I can't take full credit
for all this innovation.
Sure, I can handle the physics,
but my colleague is more familiar
with the nuts and bolts.
Ah, there he is.
Barry Allen, meet the man
who built this machine.
Eobard Thawne. Nice to meet you,
Barry Allen.
Eobard Thawne.
Nice to meet you, Barry Allen.
Thawne...
I'm chief of engineering here
at Fast Track Laboratories.
Eobard here is our only employee
who knows the truth about this project
while I'm still perfecting it,
and Barry here is a friend of the Flash.
Really?
Yeah. You know the Flash, don't you?
- No. I...
- Do...
You two, have you met before?
- Go to hell!
- You're taking both of us there!
Now who's the villain, Flash?
Now who's the villain?
No. I don't think so.
Uh, but my memory is a little hazy.
Eobard suffers from a rare form
of retrograde amnesia.
You're kidding?
I just I have trouble accessing memories
connected to my personal life.
You know, anything over a year ago,
all I get are occasional flashes.
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, Avery.
I'm supposed to believe
you don't remember who you are.
Or where you're from.
What the hell are you doing here?
Why did you build this thing?
Because Meena asked me to.
Her lightning is like nothing
I've ever seen before.
I guess that's your doing, isn't it?
I assure you,
the B.L.O.C is perfectly safe...
But you aren't.
What he hell do you want from me?
I'm sorry. I have no idea why you're
so upset with somebody you just met.
Stop. Stop!
I've known you all my life.
You're the Reverse-Flash.
Look, Allen,
I have no idea what you're talking about
or why you think I'm
a murderous speedster...
Because you are.
No, I'm not.
Now, if you don't mind,
I have work to do.
Chester, has A.R.G.U.S. posted
any security alerts?
Uh...
No.
Is everything okay, boss?
- No. I just saw Thawne.
- What? How did he escape?
I don't know,
but he's using his original face again,
the one he had
before he killed Harrison Wells.
Okay, how is that even possible?
And how the frak did he end up
working at Fast Track Labs?
I don't know that either,
but I'm going to find out.
I can't hire you, Mr. Thawne.
This resume is a joke.
Well, nobody's perfect.
Wow.
You really are something.
Even after the 11 other interviews
I had today,
I'm starting to think that all this
is just like a huge waste of time.
I mean, seriously?
You call this a resume?
Am I boring you?
When calculating quantum static
and genetic speed,
you have to account for the tachyons.
I have been working on this for months.
No one's even come close.
Well, the other candidates were idiots.
I'm not.
Which is how I can tell
you're trying to create a speedster.
I can help.
How are you still here?
Well, I want to see how this ends.
Don't screw with me.
How'd you get your speed back?
I didn't.
Stop lying! I saw you.
Five minutes ago, a thousand miles
from here, wearing your original face,
pretending you didn't remember me.
So who is he?
A version of you from your past?
Answer me!
I don't know.
And I don't care.
Don't you get it?
You took my speed.
There's no other versions of me
out there.
No other tricks up my sleeve.
You took everything from me.
So why don't you just leave me alone?
When you were nearly erased
during Armageddon.
It erased your past, didn't it?
Which means he must be
from another timeline.
Like when I created Flashpoint,
there was another Thawne.
- I need you to kill my mother.
- With pleasure.
The only way to fix things
was to let him go.
He fought with the Legends.
He tried to keep himself
from getting erased.
But Black Flash caught up to him.
I guess he didn't finish the job.
Here's a suggestion.
Why don't go you bother him?
The other Thawne built this.
Does that mean anything to you?
He didn't build that. That's mine.
That's my Biometric
Lightning Oscillation Chamber
that I built two centuries from now
when I was a younger man
to see if I could become
a speedster like you.
It worked.
But not the way I intended.
Has it tapped into
the Negative Speed Force?
That's why Meena's powers
are so erratic.
They're not artificial.
They're negative.
I've seen what
that kind of force can do.
- Who's Meena?
- Dr. Meena Dhawan.
She's the one that's using the B.L.O.C.
Never heard of her.
And guess what? Neither has history.
So I guess your new adversary, you make
sure that this Dr. Meena Dhawan...
never sees the future.
Because if she keeps using that device,
the Negative Speed Force will start
to alter her personality,
it'll destroy her.
Not "if."
"When."
There's one thing you should know
about us Thawnes, Allen.
No matter when we exist,
no matter what our memories are,
we only look out for ourselves.
So whatever this new guy's endgame...
he'll sacrifice every pawn on the board
to get what he wants.
Not if I stop him
before he has a chance.
Well.
Just when I thought this day
couldn't get any more interesting.
Oh, John,
you can come out now.
It's been a long time.
Last time I saw you, you were still
pretending you needed a wheelchair.
Last time I saw you, your friend
Oliver Queen was still alive.
What do you want, John?
For the past two years, I've covered
every corner of this Earth.
And I still can't get
this damn thing to open up again.
But I believe you can.
This cube fell out of the sky
and dropped into my lap.
Before I could see what was inside,
it shut itself.
I've had friends examine
every inch of it.
I can't get it open.
Damn it. Got that same line
from A.R.G.U.S.
And all they could tell me
is that its...
knowledge is beyond
any current human understanding,
and that it can transport matter.
So when I heard from Lyla
you were here, I...
You thought some
23rd century ingenuity might help.
Good call.
Why not just have Lyla
give it to me herself?
I see. Trouble in Paradise.
Trying to open this box...
I had to spend
a lot of time away from home.
Away from my kids.
But you just can't leave
the box behind, can you?
Even when this thing is away from me,
I can still feel it in my mind,
it's pulling me closer.
And the more I fight it,
the louder I hear its call,
but I have to know what it is.
I have to know what
these damn voices want from me.
Well.
You've come to the right place.
I've seen transmatter technology
like that before
forged at the Orrery of Worlds with
the power to travel across realities.
So, yeah,
I'll help you on one condition,
that when you open up that box again,
John,
I get to see what's inside.
Chester,
I'm heading back to Central City.
I need you to find out who's
still inside Fast Track Labs.
Pretty cleared out
for the night,
just two heat signatures inside.
Meena and Thawne.
What's the 411, boss?
I think
it's the Thawne from Flashpoint.
Now he's pumping Meena
with negative speed.
- If you need backup...
- No, it's too dangerous.
I don't know why he's doing this,
but I won't let anyone get hurt.
Artificial speed saturation at zero.
- Ready for infusion.
- Doc,
you set the oscillation levels
at 52 million joules,
that is more speed
than you have ever absorbed before.
Are you sure the Flash
would want you to do this?
He's why I'm doing this.
I hurt him this morning
when my speed started to run out.
I need to make it last longer.
Powering the chamber.
Activating electrostatic fins...
Ready for biometric absorption.
Meena, stop!
Flash. What are you doing here?
Flash, I know what happened today,
and I know how to fix it.
No, you don't.
I know why you attacked me.
It's because your speed is connected
to the Negative Speed Force.
It's an extra dimensional power source
fueled by rage and hate.
The B.L.O.C is fueled by lightning
from the upper atmosphere.
We've run the numbers a thousand times.
Then your math's wrong
or you're a damn liar.
Eobard. What is he talking about?
I'm talking about who he really is.
The Eobard Thawne that I know,
no matter what body he's in
or what timeline he comes from,
he's always the same person.
A psychotic murderer...
Please don't hurt me.
...known as the Reverse-Flash.
No!
I didn't do anything to you
or anyone else.
Why can't you understand that?
I'm done listening to you.
Whatever you're trying to do to her,
it ends now.
You're making a huge mistake.
No, I'm taking you to Iron Heights,
which is letting you off easy.
Leave him alone!
Meena, don't!
Oh, no.
Her brainwaves are altering,
it's too much power.
Speed.
Need... more...
speed.
Time to get faster.
These cubes appear to people
at a crossroads, at a...
turning point in their lives.
So when the cube first opened,
what was going through your mind?
I had just buried Oliver.
We were moving the kids to Metropolis.
You were starting a new life.
You were in control of your destiny
for the first time in years.
That is why the cube chose you
for that sense of purpose.
Then why did it close?
Because you weren't ready
to accept its power yet.
But really,
the only question, John, is...
are you ready now?
- I am.
- Good.
Then put yourself
in that head space again.
Close your eyes,
think of what your future could be.
All the light you could bring
into this world.
All the cosmic odysseys that await.
No one can know my secret.
You don't come between
those folks and their gold.
Sir, we are quite sure
you will bring them back to justice.
Look at them all.
All those lives you can lead.
Do it, John, do it.
Drink of the Bleed Mandrakk hid
within the cube,
feel its power break through
the source wall,
for when you break through that wall,
all those worlds that await
will be yours.
This universe
is far bigger than any of us...
I couldn't dare imagine.
No.
I don't want this.
I don't want any of this!
Do you hear me? The answer is no!
No, no!
What have you done?
Do you know what you've done?
I do.
I finally do.
I saw a thousand lives I could lead.
But not one of them
led me back to my family.
I was meant to see inside that cube!
To find a way out of this hell hole!
I guess it's a good thing
the cube didn't choose you.
You're not special.
You're not someone important.
This was your last chance
to be someone powerful.
But I am...
someone special.
Now I realize
the cube was trying
to make me someone else,
something else.
And it even tricked me into believing
that somehow
I wanted it to, but...
I don't.
Because there is no power
in the universe
more powerful than the love
I have for my family.
Sweetie.
But I suppose a man like you
wouldn't understand that.
Because if it came down to a choice
between some cosmic destiny or
being a father,
a husband...
there's really no choice at all.
Hey, Lyla. Hey, baby, no, no.
I didn't see Barry this time.
I think he has a lot on his plate.
Yeah, you're right.
We do have a lot to talk about.
But I'm coming home.
Chester, Meena's negative lightning
pulses cancelled out my speed again,
just like this morning.
Chester?
Meena.
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
This is what you wanted
all along, isn't it?
For the Negative Speed Force
to corrupt her.
Why would I want that?
I didn't even know the Negative
Speed Force existed before today!
She protected you from me.
Why would she do that?
Because she loves me!
You idiot!
And I love her.
More than anything.
When I lost my memories,
I had a singular focus in my life.
Somehow, some way,
I was going to be a speedster.
And then I met Meena.
Everything changed.
I know this sounds strange, but
I think I'm supposed to be a speedster.
I think that's why,
despite all the holes in my brain,
I can see the B.L.O.C crystal clear.
I think I'm meant to use it.
So you you want to be
like Flash, be a superhero?
I want to be bigger than a superhero.
I want to recharge power grids.
I want to reverse tornadoes
before they destroy cities and towns.
I want to end famine, end war.
I want to save the world.
But it wasn't meant to be.
I had already fallen in love with Meena
when we discovered her machine
could only work for one person.
This isn't right.
But that wasn't the worst part.
Meena had a heart condition.
And one night,
she went into cardiac arrest.
Meena, no!
There was only one way to save her.
You gave up your dream.
Your chance to save the world.
You are my world.
So please, even if I was this... monster
somehow or in another life,
don't hold my sins against her.
I am begging you.
Save her.
The Thawne I know has haunted my life
since I was just a kid.
He's killed people I care for.
He deserves to rot.
He could never put
someone else's needs before his.
I'm sorry.
You're not the man I thought you were.
You're someone better.
My speed's back.
Flash? Flash, are you there?
Yeah, I hear you. What's happening?
Okay, Meena's attacking power junctions
all over the city.
Why would Meena need electricity?
Her speed is supposed to be temporary.
If Meena runs out of speed, the Negative
Speed Force will lose its grip on her.
It's making her absorb electricity
to make more speed and maintain control.
If that's the case,
then she's going to look
for the largest power source possible.
The Keystone Cleveland Dam.
Time to get faster.
Speed. Unlimited speed.
Meena, I don't want to hurt you.
But you're not in control
of yourself right now,
and if this dam breaks,
thousands of people could die.
Then let them.
Guys, she's right behind me.
Are you in position?
Almost. Everyone okay back there?
I just hacked into Meena's speed gauge.
Her saturation is already
under 40%, it's working.
If Flash can keep her running
for another 119 seconds,
she'll burn off the rest of her speed.
Meena? Are you okay?
Flash? Can you hear me, Flash?
She just summoned power
directly from the Negative Speed Force.
It canceled out the Flash's power.
How pathetic...
Avatar of the speed force
dying on his back.
Meena, stop! I can't let you do this.
Please.
Please, you have to stop this.
The Meena you knew is gone.
Lost in the electrostatic pits
of your precious machine.
I know you're still there.
I can feel you locked away inside.
Please.
Meena, come back to me.
You're wasting your time.
This is who I am now.
And killing the Flash is my purpose.
No. No, it isn't!
Perhaps I should kill you first.
Go ahead, because I'd rather die
right here, right now,
than lose you.
I know the real you.
You're the genius who stumped
every lab tech in Central City.
You have to account for the tachyons.
The health conscious partner
who'd never let me have a cheeseburger.
Don't tell anybody.
The hero who taught me to put others
before myself.
And that Meena, she would never be able
to do something like this.
I love you, Meena.
The chamber's ready.
But only one of us can use it.
I am begging you, please.
I want to save the world.
I want to save the world, too.
You are my world.
No!
I can't lose you!
Please...
come back to me.
Come back to me.
You should go first.
Eobard.
Oh, God.
- Flash, are you okay?
- Yeah, I will be.
So will they.
You saved me.
No, you saved me.
Okay. Well,
my speed has finally worn off.
And so are the effects the
Negative Speed Force had on your brain.
I know that your experiment
didn't exactly go as planned,
but... this is one seriously dope lab.
How do you feel now?
Well, I finally feel like myself again.
I am so sorry
I didn't listen to you, Flash.
We built the B.L.O.C
so we could help people,
but if we can't use it without me
turning into a super villain...
Then it's not worth the risk.
Especially if we don't even know
how we tapped into
the Negative Speed Force to begin with.
What if there was a way around it?
Whenever I start to feel
like I'm in over my head,
I think about the person I love most.
She helps guide me home.
Like a lightning rod.
Just like tonight when the Negative
Speed Force corrupted you.
Eobard brought me back.
So you think that our bond
could help me control my powers?
It would take some tinkering
with the B.L.O.C,
but if Eobard's your lightning rod,
there's nothing
you can't accomplish together.
Well, should we take a look
at the instruction manual?
Oh!
I thought you'd never ask.
Sorry to interrupt the sniffers.
When you said that
Flashpoint Thawne came back,
I reached out to a mutual friend
to gather some intel.
He just left a message.
Chester. Hey, sorry it took me so long
to get back.
The Quincy P. Runk Institute
is having a minor infestation
of serpent creatures
from the Morlay dimension.
It's under control, I think.
As for your question, I was out
having retirement drinks with Nate
and turns out the Legends had their own
encounter with Reverse-Flash this year.
Yeah, apparently the Time Wraiths
saved him from Black Flash.
My power's stripped. I was "re-educated"
and assigned here
to protect this fixed point.
As penance for your past crimes.
Believe it or not, Sarah,
I came to see their point.
That history cannot
and should not be changed.
Thawne spent years
protecting the timeline.
- Thawne.
- It is yours now.
Until he died helping the Legends.
Pretty tragic twist, huh?
Oops!
Another serpent loose,
so I just gotta grab my sword.
And, it's over here.
Wait. If Thawne from Flashpoint
became a hero,
but then, died...
How could he be here?
Maybe when he sacrificed himself,
the Time Wraiths saved his life again.
- Brought him here.
- To Meena.
Guys, I know it sounds crazy,
but however it happened,
I think we're lucky it did.
So are they.
Plus, we could always use
another hero around here.
Stop!
You think I'm playing with you?
Give me the purse!
What's happening to me?
Now that's more like it.
- Mark.
- Yes.
Are you in my apartment?
Yes.
Where the hell are you?
With my mom.
I needed to get out of there,
clear my head.
Then do that and get your ass
back here, okay?
I was looking at our data
again last night.
It all clicked for me.
Caitlin. I know how to bring Frost back.
We can't.
Not now.
Plus, Barry took the Mirror Gun.
I'm sorry, Mark, but It's over.
We don't need the gun.
Not for what we're gonna do.
We just need you.
What did you do?
My speed is my life.
I wonder what face I'll be wearing
next time we meet.
Merry Christmas.
And I'm just getting started!
Everything you are is because of me!
What did you do?
I got faster than you.
Your precious
Speed Force cannot help you now,
because in this timeline,
Iris chose me, I won.
There is no trace of the
Negative Speed Force left in your body.
You took my life!
And left me in hell.
We've been looking
for you, Eobard.
The man with no past.
The anomaly.
You were invisible to us
until the light from that damn cube
showed us where to find you.
Well, good for me.
Now, who are you and...
what do you want?
I guess you could say I'm an old friend.
And a new one all rolled up in one.
Because that's how I roll.
And as for why I'm here?
It's time to fulfill your destiny.