[tense music]
- Eddie?
- Iris.
I've missed you so much.
- This is not possible.
You're--
[grunts]
- Whoa.
You okay, babe?
You look a little flushed.
Yep, that's a fever.
Can I get you something?
Some water?
- No, I'm fine.
- No, I know what you need.
Your favorite:
chamomile tea.
Oh, and don't worry.
I know
I've been gone a long time,
but I'm not leaving
till you're all better.
Okay?
- Uh, Iris?
Why is there an attractive,
blond man in your kitchen?
- Oh, hey.
I'm Eddie.
Eddie Thawne.
Iris' fiancé.
[tea kettle whistling]
[heroic music]
♪
- CCPD has ordered
a citywide curfew
after the shocking massacre
that happened earlier tonight.
The mysterious assailant
remains currently at large...
- No sign
of Deathstorm anywhere.
How's it going here?
- Good.
The Mental Augmentation Chamber
is just like I remembered,
not that I could forget
six weeks
of living inside this thing.
- So we're seriously
gonna turn Frost
into an Anti-Deathstorm?
- We-we know
Deathstorm is made up
of pure thermodynamic energy,
so we use the M.A.C.
to harness particles
from its home dimension
and then beam them
into your consciousness.
- The reaction should transform
Frost's body
into a being like Deathstorm.
You'll be able to create fire,
defy gravity...
- And consume
Deathstorm's fuel source.
Once you absorb all that "grief
energy" out of Deathstorm...
- I'll be able
to snuff him out for good.
- Well, it's official,
this is the craziest plan
we've ever had.
- Then let's get crazy,
'cause I'm not letting
that Skeletor
put another bony finger
on my sister.
- I just gotta finish
the M.A.C.'s cryo-circuits,
and we should be good to go.
- Guys, I need you
in the Med Lab.
It's Caitlin.
- Is she okay?
- I don't know.
Her biometrics are stable,
but I just felt
another huge wave of grief
from her.
- I just keep picturing
Dad dying.
It's all I can see,
over and over again.
Him on the floor...
- What is wrong with her?
- Remember,
when Deathstorm took Caitlin,
it was trying to change her
into something else--
its bride--but it still needs
her to experience more grief
before the transformation
is complete.
- It must've dialed up
one of her worst memories.
- You're gonna be okay.
We've got a plan.
- What if it doesn't work?
What if I'm stuck
like this forever?
- Don't even think like that.
Just get some rest, and
I'll be here when you wake up.
How much longer until Chester
has the cryo-circuit ready?
- I'm not sure.
Maybe an hour.
- We don't have
that kind of time.
I'm gonna call backup.
- We still need
to find Deathstorm.
- I know.
- Can you feel anything?
- No.
It's like he's disappeared.
- ♪ Capacitor's connected
to the inductor ♪
♪ Inductor's connected
to the cryo-circuit ♪
♪ The cryo-circuit's
connected to the... ♪
[lights shut off]
Oh, frak me.
[overlapping voices]
[ominous music]
♪
[overlapping voices]
[electricity crackles]
- I still haven't identified
the cause
of Iris West-Allen's
temporal ailment.
- Okay.
Keep trying, Gideon.
In the meantime,
could you run a search
for any
extra-dimensional energies
or cold fusion anomalies
in the area?
- Of course, Barry Allen.
Search--
[hologram fritzes]
[unsettling music]
- Gideon?
[electronics power down]
♪
[monitor beeping rapidly]
- He's here.
- Actually, I'm everywhere.
And nowhere.
I was born a long time ago--
before Maltus,
before the stars,
during that lonely,
blackest of nights.
I was there when the first
gas cloud sank and collapsed.
I was there
when the first beings drew
their final, hissing breaths.
I am decline.
I am entropy.
I am the master of death
and all of its inhabitants.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Oh, my beautiful boy.
- Guys, it's my dad.
He's back.
- Esperanza's here.
I need backup--
[monitor fritzes]
- [exhales sharply]
That's better.
Where I'm from,
there's not so much noise.
- If you take one step
toward Caity,
I will send you back
to the hell you came from.
- Oh, my home is
much farther than Hell.
It's a lonely place,
or at least it was until
Ronnie died in the Singularity.
His mind found me,
his grief became my hunger,
and his love became
my guiding light.
- So, you're trying to take
my sister 'cause you're lonely?
- Ronnie's feelings showed me
how to end my suffering.
- I'll show you suffering.
[tense music]
♪
- You can't hurt me, but
you're still fighting back...
just like your father intended.
[ice shatters]
- So what, you got my dad
hiding in some other room
so you can sic his grief ghost
on me?
- My phantoms only appear
to those who can grieve them,
which is why you won't
be having any visitors.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It's simple.
You don't have anyone to grieve
because your grief isn't real.
- Hmm, I wish I knew that
all those nights
I was drinking away my pain
at O'Shaughnessy's.
- The sadness you've
experienced in your existence
is just a copy,
an echo of real emotion.
Like all of your feelings.
Like you.
- [scoffs]
You're so full of it.
- Then why can't I sense
any loss inside your mind?
Why can't I smell
those hormones
dancing
along your neural receptors?
It's because when Thomas
built you in his lab,
he gave you everything
you'd need to protect Caitlin--
cryo-kineticism,
healing, rage--
but as for the rest of you,
he just copied
what was inside her.
He cloned a few scraps
of her feelings,
tinkered
with her personality traits,
but he never gave you
any authentic emotions.
He never built you your own
consciousness, your own soul.
- That's not true.
- Grief and pain.
Those are the things
that make people truly alive,
and you don't have them.
- Shut up.
- Because
you are not a real person.
You're a faulty experiment,
a broken mirror
who can't aid me
in my cause like the others.
- I said,
shut the hell up!
[ominous music]
♪
[zaps]
- [panting]
- Come on! Come on!
In here!
[door whirring shut]
[zap]
- [gasps]
Let me guess,
your ghost dad is back too?
- Oh, yeah.
I lost him in the hall.
- Wait, I-I don't get it.
These things can walk
through walls.
Why the hell
aren't they coming in here?
- I don't know,
but is it getting
kind of toasty in here?
- Yeah.
[door latch fritzing]
Oh, crap,
the doors.
- There's-there's no way out.
- They chased us in here
on purpose.
[tense music]
♪
- No, this isn't real.
You're not my mom.
[sizzles]
[cries out in pain]
- Please, sweetie, stop.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
- This is just
another manipulation.
You're some part of Deathstorm
trying to screw with my head.
- Why would you say this
about me?
I'm your mom--
- No, you're not!
- I came here to help you
because I love you,
oh, so much.
You have to believe me.
I've been watching you,
your life,
what's happening to Iris.
There's no cure
for her temporal sickness,
no secret answer.
You're going to lose her,
forever.
- That's not true.
Her condition's stabilizing.
I can still save her.
- Like you saved me?
I'm trying to warn you, Barry.
You can't have a family.
Your father died, I died,
and now your poor, sick wife
is gonna die too.
And there's nothing you can do
to stop it.
[foreboding music]
- Sure I can't get you a cup?
- Oh. No, thank you...
Eddie.
- Um, you know
what sounds great right now?
Some soup!
- Soup? Really?
- Why don't I whip up some
of Uncle Robern's
famous chicken noodle?
- Oh, yeah.
Yummy, babe.
- Okay, I'm gonna need
some chicken stock.
- Um, you know what
would be great with that too?
Some chipotle chilies.
- Yummy.
Do we have any?
- Uh, yeah,
I'm sure they're in there.
Just keep looking.
- [sighs]
Nope, not seeing any chilies.
But I do see you,
Sue Dearbon.
[sizzles]
- Ahh!
- Come on.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
[sizzles]
- Ahh!
[groans]
- Come on, guys.
You know nobody's leaving
till Iris is all better.
[unsettling music]
♪
- The team's trapped.
How's Caity doing?
- It feels like she's getting
worse, and I have no idea why.
Oh, God.
There's something coming.
- Okay. Hold on, ma'am.
- Ah, It's more grief.
[tense music]
- Ma'am.
- Caity, no.
- [groans]
[monitor beeping rapidly]
- Her vitals are spiking
and she's burning up.
She keeps changing
and Deathstorm is nowhere near.
- No, it's not Deathstorm.
I've felt this grief before.
It's the team's.
It's Barry's, and Allegra's,
and Chester's, and even Iris.
I can feel all of their pain
and their sadness
flooding out of them
and pouring into Caitlin.
- That's why
he sent the ghosts after them.
The more grief they feel,
the more goes into Caity.
- And the sooner
she becomes his bride.
- [lowly]
Burn.
Burn for home.
♪
- Please tell me you can
do something stop this grief,
or you can use your powers
to help her somehow.
- Frost,
I am sure as hell gonna try.
- Everybody decent?
- Oh, finally.
What took you so long?
- Hey, the cryogenics
department at Fast Track Labs
has really improved
their security recently,
just not as much
as they thought.
And voilà, madame,
your very own cryo-circuit.
- Wow, you must be
the infamous Mark.
- [chuckles]
This baby here
should modify the M.A.C.,
no problem,
and then we can temporarily
transform you into...
Sorry, what are we
transforming you into again?
- The Anti-Deathstorm.
- Right.
Man, you kids on Team Flash
do some crazy stuff.
- [groans]
- Is Caitlin gonna be okay?
- Yes, as soon
as we get the M.A.C. working.
Let's go.
- I got her.
[tense music]
♪
- [sighs]
Okay.
Trying to blast a hole
in the door is out.
What the frak is this thing
made of, titanium?
- Actually, yes,
and all of my tech just bricked
from the heat.
And then,
the thermostat died at...
[sighs]
137.
- Great, so not only
are we trapped in here,
but we don't know
how hot it is?
- Humans don't go hyperthermic
till 200 degrees Fahrenheit,
give or take,
which means that--
- You've got about 20 minutes.
[dramatic music]
When your internal temperature
reaches 105 degrees,
blood flow starts to decrease.
At 107, organs fail
and brain function slows.
By about 109,
you'll believe in quitting.
- Don't listen to him, Chuck.
Nothing he says means anything.
- "Chuck"?
You let her call you that?
- No. No, she's right.
You're not real.
I'm getting that door open.
- Why do we love science,
Chester?
Because regardless of who's
conducting the experiment,
the results are
right and wrong,
black and white...
just like this situation.
Whether I'm real or not,
you care about each other.
And here you are,
trapped in a room...
forced to watch each other die.
- And when you do...
[speaking Spanish]
♪
- I'm-I'm done with your games.
You could burn me alive
right now, but you won't.
So tell me, what do you want?
- I want to prepare you, Barry.
Iris' impending death won't
just mean that she's gone.
It will mean that Nora and Bart
will never exist.
[dramatic musical sting]
I'm not trying to be cruel,
but the truth is,
your legacy isn't heroism.
It's heartbreak.
- You know what people
like you will never understand?
Love is a strength,
not a liability.
The heartbreak
that I've suffered?
The people I've lost?
They don't hold me back.
They make me fight
that much harder,
and I'm gonna fight for Iris.
- Then why
didn't you fight for me?
Why did you stand by while
Thawne stabbed me in the gut?
- Thawne didn't kill you!
He killed my mom.
And as much as it hurt,
I have accepted her death.
- And what about
the rest of them?
[sinister music]
- Your mother and I love--
- No!
- Thank you for everything.
- [screams]
[overlapping voices]
- Have you accepted
all their deaths too?
- [screaming]
- Barry told us
about Deathstorm
and the ghost
he sent after Chester.
You're one of
those apparitions, aren't you?
- And where's
your precious Barry now?
Nowhere to be found,
as usual,
while you're laid up in here,
waiting to die.
- Iris is not going to die.
- Trust me.
As a dead man myself,
she's toast.
And she knows it.
Just like I knew.
[gunshot]
I thought my sacrifice
would mean something.
That I could erase the
Reverse Flash from existence.
That, finally,
I could be a hero.
But then
Eobard Thawne came back,
again, and again,
and again, and again.
What I did
didn't matter at all.
I died for nothing,
and now you've made
the same mistake.
You sacrificed yourself
for nothing.
- I saved Barry,
and I helped stop Armageddon.
- And then,
what happened?
The timeline got reset,
but you're
still suffering
the consequences.
Can't you see?
Your death is gonna be
just as pointless as mine.
[ominous music]
♪
Something's wrong.
Why are you...
happy?
- Who, me?
Oh, well, that's easy.
I'm young, I'm rich,
I'm a total dime.
Oh, and before you
so rudely destroyed
another one
of my brand new phones,
I hit the panic button.
- Hey, Detective Pretty Boy.
[blasts]
- Come on,
before it wears off.
Come on!
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Nana?
No! Please don't go!
- Chyre?
Chyre, hold on, man.
Please.
Chyre...
- What did you do to them?
- I showed them the deaths
of the people they love.
[overlapping voices]
And now, with the help
of their grief,
the bride's transformation
will be complete.
♪
- All right,
cryo-circuit is functional,
ready to merge
your cold fusion cells
with Douche-Storm's
dimensional particles.
[dramatic music]
- This has to work.
- Hey, master
cryo-geneticist over here,
not just a pretty face.
Trust me.
Okay, cryo-circuit is alive.
Activating
augmentation receptors.
[machine powering up]
♪
Deploying
dimensional particles.
- [cries out]
[computer beeps]
[groans]
- Hey, are you okay?
Did it work?
Are you Anti-Deathstorm?
- Only one way to find out.
[dramatic music]
♪
[sighs]
- What's wrong?
- I'm just me.
No fire powers, no nothing.
This stupid machine
didn't work.
- Well, I mean,
that doesn't make sense.
It should work on anyone--
any organism
or sentient being
with a consciousness.
- Or anyone who's truly alive.
[music swells]
I guess we know
what the issue is here then.
♪
It's me.
- How can you be the problem?
I mean,
that doesn't make any sense.
- Well, you said it yourself,
the reaction depends
on the M.A.C. being able
to put particles
in someone's consciousness.
What if that person
doesn't have one?
- [scoffs]
What are you talking about?
I mean, of course
you have a consciousness.
- Not according to Deathstorm.
He and I had a little chat
about why everyone
on Team Flash
got visited by a ghost
except me.
He said that
I couldn't experience grief
because when Thomas created me,
he just gave me a copy
of all of Caity's emotions.
- Oh, well, he's obviously
just messing with you.
Don't let that fire-freak
get in your head.
- What if he's not?
Do you know
what my earliest memory is?
It's not of Carla
singing me a lullaby
or Thomas throwing me
on his shoulders.
It's of Caity
being hit by a car.
[solemn music]
[screams]
'Cause that's
the first time I woke up,
to take the hit.
And then, I just drifted back
into her subconsciousness,
locked away there for years,
watching Caity live her life
and have friends.
And, you know,
so when I finally started
coming out more,
I wanted to make up
for lost time,
you know,
finally live a life.
♪
Boy, was I stupid for ever
thinking that was possible,
because it doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter
how many life coaches I get,
or if I get my own body,
or do a bunch of art,
or get my own boyfriend,
because I'll always
just be a copy of the original.
An echo.
'Cause I've never
been really alive.
And now,
that's gonna get Caity killed.
- Frost...
If you are not really alive,
where does that leave me?
You're the only person
I've ever cared about
more than myself,
or at least equal to myself.
- I guess
we're both screwed up then.
- Yeah, that's definitely true.
Look, the way I see it,
you and I have been
through a lot, right?
And through
all of those ups and downs,
I, for one, have seen you
have loads of emotions--
all kinds--
especially
when it comes to Caitlin.
You love your sister
like crazy.
And wherever
that love came from--
you know,
whether you were born with it,
or your dad gave it to you,
or you put it together yourself
over time,
built it
with pain and heartache--
that love is
as real as it gets.
Believe me.
- Then why didn't Deathstorm
use any of my grief on me?
He said he couldn't
even find it in me.
- Well,
maybe he couldn't find it
because you've got it
buried so deep
in that foxy head of yours.
maybe because
you love so damn hard
that you know the flip side
would totally suck.
- Yeah, I mean, I have been
a little closed off lately.
- I'm sorry, Snowflake.
Grief is a necessary part
of life,
and you are very much alive.
Whoa, that's it.
Yes!
Frost, the M.A.C.'s been
working fine all along,
but the chemical reaction was
missing a necessary ingredient.
Frost, I think I know how
to finish your transformation.
[overlapping voices]
- Sue, Dad, it's not real.
You guys, you're stronger
than this bastard.
- That's no way
to talk about your fiancé.
- I know you want our grief,
but you're not gonna
get an ounce from me.
I know you are not
the real Eddie.
- No, I'm not,
because he died.
[tense music]
♪
Just like you're gonna die too.
- No, it's not real.
- Yes, it is.
Now you're gonna
lose everything, Iris--
your family, your future,
everything
you worked so hard for.
It hurts, doesn't it?
[ominous music]
♪
- [speaking Spanish]
- [grunting softly]
- You and I,
we had history,
but you and him had a future.
And that's so much worse,
isn't it?
Because you're not
just watching him die,
you're watching everything
you could have shared die too.
[tense music]
- You can try all you want,
but you'll never
get out of here, son.
♪
And neither will she.
She's gonna die
because you're not smart enough
to find a way out.
All that time tinkering
with machines,
building countless gadgets,
and the one time you need
to come up with a big idea--
the one time
it really matters--
you can't do a damn thing.
- Chuck.
[grunts]
I've got you.
It's okay.
- It's not okay.
It's not okay.
I'm so sorry
I can't fix this, Allegra.
- No. No, don't feel bad.
That's how
they want us to feel.
But Chuck,
the truth is,
right now, with you,
I feel happy.
Happy I met you.
[hopeful music]
- Me too.
Me too.
♪
- [screams]
- [cries out]
- Oliver traded his life
for yours.
- Stop! Stop it!
- No.
You stop fighting, Barry.
Give in to the pain,
the pain you still feel.
Let your sorrow
wash over you.,,
so the bride may be reborn.
- [lowly]
I can see them.
Stars, endless stars.
[monitor beeping]
- Hey, Caity.
I'm not even sure
if you can hear me,
but there's something
I need to say.
[pensive music]
You know, I used to be afraid
that because we shared a body,
I was only gonna get
to live half a life,
that I was only
gonna be half a person.
I realize now,
that isn't true.
You didn't take anything
from me.
In fact,
it's just the opposite.
You make my life complete.
I gotta be honest,
I'm a little worried
that we're not gonna
make it out of this
and that
I might lose you forever.
And I can't handle that.
I would die.
♪
I love you more than anything.
[tear freezes, cracks]
[groans]
- Is that supposed to happen?
- Ahh! Ahh!
- The M.A.C.'s been
working fine all along,
but the chemical reaction
was missing one ingredient.
The spark that gave
Deathstorm life--grief.
Frost just had
to let herself feel it.
[dramatic music]
- [groans]
♪
Damn, I've never
felt this warm before.
- It's all that power.
Frost, I can feel it
radiating off of you.
- That's 'cause
I'm not just Frost.
I'm Hellfrost.
[epic music]
♪
[both panting]
- Sue, Dad,
you guys okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
We're okay.
- The team,
they're all okay.
- So, Hot Stuff,
what do we do now?
- We kick some ass
and save my sister.
- You look totally badass.
- Thanks.
I feel badass,
but Caity's not okay.
In fact,
Cecile says she's worse.
- Then this isn't over.
Deathstorm is back
in his home dimension,
which means he can still
put guilt inside of Caitlin.
- Or send more ghosts
after you guys.
- Yeah, I talked to Iris.
Deathstorm sent one
to the loft.
- You saved the whole team.
- And now,
I'm gonna save Caity
by extinguishing
this son of a bitch.
- Well, hey,
when that thing comes back,
you're gonna need some backup.
- No.
I'm the only one
who can do this.
Even Barry's lightning
can't stop him.
- And if anything goes wrong...
- You'll get me out
of there in a flash.
- Okay, wait.
"Flash"? "Lightning"?
Are you saying that he...
Whoa.
But if he can't help you,
you gotta let me try
adjusting the gauntlets
and pump up
the cryo-kinetic outputs.
- There's no time.
- Then maybe we need
to make some time.
- Look, I told you,
I was born for this.
But I'll give you something
to remember me by.
[tender music]
♪
- Uh, damn.
- There's more
where that came from.
- I...
- Did I break you?
- No, I-I...
Go save your sister.
I'll be here when you get back.
[dramatic music]
♪
[exhales sharply]
Okay.
You guys do this all the time?
- Yep, that's the gig.
- How do you stay so calm, man?
This is nerve-racking as hell.
- Welcome to Superhero-ing 101.
- [chuckles dryly]
[monitor beeping]
- This is it.
[tense music]
♪
- I can sense all that precious
grief inside you, Cait.
You're almost ready.
I've waited so long
to end my solitude.
It's time to start
our honeymoon, my bride,
because I want forever
to start right now.
- Surprise.
[device warbles]
- What have you done?
- Now, let's party.
[epic music]
♪
- You sure she can do this?
- We have to trust her.
- [roars]
I will burn you to ash!
- You first!
- [roars]
- Come on, Frost.
Give him hell.
[both grunting]
- [roars]
[monitor beeping]
[grunts]
You can't keep me
from my bride.
Who do think you are?
- More than you can handle.
Go to Hell!
- [roars in pain]
- Now it's time for me to feed.
- No!
[cries out]
[epic music]
♪
[triumphant music]
- [laughs]
That's it, party people!
All traces
of supplemental cold fusion
and barometric anomalies
are gone!
♪
- What happened?
- Frost saved you.
- Hellfrost, you did it!
- Hell yeah, I did.
- That's my gal.
- How's Caity?
- She's doing fine.
- Thank God.
- Hey, I have a bourbon
straight up
waiting for you
when you get back.
- Sounds great...
Guys, I'm not feeling so hot.
[monitor beeping rapidly]
- Her vitals are crashing.
- What?
- Frost!
[dramatic music]
[monitor beeping rapidly]
- You just woke up from a coma.
Are you sure
you're up for this?
- I have to be.
- What the hell happened?
- Mark.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Why isn't she moving?
- We don't know.
We don't know.
But Caitlin is working on her,
and she's going to save her.
- Okay, I can help.
- No, you can't.
I'm sorry,
but you need to leave.
- I can't just--
- Mark. Hey.
It's gonna be okay.
Caitlin has to focus.
- Hey.
Let's give them
some space, yeah?
- Okay, her pupils are dilated.
Her heart rate's spiking.
Talk to me. Tell me
what happened out there.
- We manipulated
her cryo-powers in the M.A.C.
so she could absorb
Deathstorm's energy.
It's what saved you.
- But Deathstorm has been
doing this for a millennia,
so I'm guessing
he can handle a lot more power
than she can.
[monitor beeping rapidly]
- She's going
into cardiac arrest.
Um, okay, I'm going
to inject her with cold fusion.
That'll bring Frost back,
and that'll kick in
her ice healing.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Come on, Frost.
Come back to me.
[sentimental music]
[both sigh in relief]
- You did it.
♪
[monitor flatlines]
- No. No, no, no, no, no.
That's impossible.
- Her ice healing's
not kicking in.
- She's flatlining.
Get me the paddles.
- Here. Here.
[defibrillator whirring]
- Clear!
Clear!
[solemn music]
♪
- Caitlin.
Caitlin.
Caitlin, hey.
- CCPD has lifted
the city-wide curfew
after confirming that,
as of an hour ago,
the mysterious mass-murderer
plaguing our city
is no longer a threat.
Citizens are cleared
to fully resume their--
- Well, Deathstorm's
finally gone.
- Frost is a real hero.
- Caitlin and Barry
have been in there forever.
- Frost is gonna pull through.
- You doing okay, Mark?
- Yeah. Thanks, man.
I'm doing a lot of thinking,
you know?
Frost and I had a lot of plans.
Like, I scored this trip
to the Himalayas,
where you jump out of a chopper
and snowboard down.
And at the bottom,
at base camp,
they have this cute,
little restaurant
where every dessert
is made of ice.
I know she's probably
gonna say it's stupid
but then secretly
not hate it at all.
Kind of like
how she feels about me.
I just want to make her smile.
There's nothing better
than that.
- She's lucky
to have you in her life.
- We all know I'm lucky
to have her in mine.
[somber music]
- Barry.
♪
- Something...
something happened.
- Where is she?
Where-where is she?
- Frost died.
- That's not possible.
- I'm sorry.
She didn't make it.
She's gone.
[sobbing]
[heroic music]
♪
- Greg, move your head.
[lightning crackling]