My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present...
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
You threw yourself
- off a building to save Dad?
- Yeah.
We all know the sound
of Cicada's breathing.
His lungs are injured.
We can't keep doing
this. It's not healing.
Killer Frost has been
gone since the night
the DeVoe took over your body.
Is she gone for good?
I've tried everything I can think of
to get her to reappear.
My father told me to come find him.
My dad's been dead for years.
He knew that there were two of you.
He knew the truth about Killer Frost.
- We've got eyes and ears!
- I knew you could do it.
There's only one sure
place somebody could hide.
A Tannhauser black ops site.
Vanilla latte and a
Medium Zoom for Raelene.
Thank you.
Should've left me alone.
And you never should have existed.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
We are back in business.
And by business, he means
the better-than-Sally
the satellite business.
And what does that mean?
That means we're getting
closer to identifying
the ever-elusive Cicada.
It's Cicada, Sherloque.
Once I hacked DeVoe's satellites,
all I had to do was just use an
impact extrapolation algorithm
to predict where the
shrapnel would've fallen
after Barry and Nora
pulled a Johnny Cage
on Sally the satellite.
May God rest her soul.
So now we got 46 locations
where 46 pieces of shrapnel landed.
And once of these
locations is where Cicada
will have been injured.
Except we don't know which one.
Or maybe we do.
You see, after my hands got
sliced by Cicada's dagger,
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman, here
measured the dark matter in my system.
And its levels of
concentration were higher
than any I'd ever seen before.
Insanely high, and the
only part of the satellite
that would have dark
matter levels that high...
Is the core, which is where
Cicada's dagger came from.
So we find the location of the core
and we'll know where
Cicada was that night.
You know, FEMA set up sites
to help people after the Enlightenment.
If Cicada was injured,
maybe he received medical
treatment at one of them.
That's a great idea.
I mean, we could check with
FEMA to see if any fathers
matching Cicada's description
reported any injuries
- near the crash site.
- So, we split up.
Okay, great. I'm good
at tracking things down.
So I will try and find
the satellite core.
I will come with you
and everybody else look
for the names.
Um, do you mind if I
actually come with you too?
It's just that I saw you
jump off a building last week
and that was awesome.
So I thought maybe I'd come with you
while you did some detective work.
Oh, I think that two people
is going to be more than enough
- for what we need...
- What he's trying to say
is that we would love
to have you come with us.
Okay.
All right, well, why
don't I talk to FEMA
and see if I can get some names.
Hey, I know Joe's been itching
to get out of the
house, and it might help
to have an actual badge.
Nobody does case snacks like Joe West.
- I'll swing by on the way.
- All right, cool.
So, Snow Patrol, what's going on?
You tell me.
I'm guessing it's not a coincidence
that we're left here with nothing to do
for the next few hours.
I know we were supposed to
wait until you were ready
to locate your dad.
But I had the satellites track down
all the decommissioned
Tannhauser black ops sites
that your dad could possibly be in.
Okay.
And... and then I hacked
into their security systems.
He was the last person
to enter one of them.
A week after he died.
And he never left.
Where is he?
It's open. Come in.
Hey! Cecile.
- Hey.
- Is... is Joe here?
Uh, no. He's out with Jenna.
Oh, dang. Okay. Bummer.
All right, I'll go get some
falafel and come back in a bit.
Wait, no. Please don't...
Leave me here. Um, what did you need?
Maybe I can help you.
Oh, I need somebody to flash a badge
and generally look intimidating, so.
You don't think that I can be intimidating.
Oh, my God, you don't, do you?
Ralph, I am the district attorney.
You know I psychically
teleported the Flash
inside the Thinker's mind
whilst giving birth to my daughter,
sans epidural... it hurt!
I literally saved the
world between contractions,
and you don't think
that I am intimidating?
I'm really intimidated
right now, actually.
You are very intimidating.
Okay, what are we doing?
Uh, we are getting a list
of FEMA recipients treated
after the Enlightenment
to hopefully find
Cicada's real name.
FEMA, come on. I worked with them a ton.
I know that org inside and out.
Just, uh... oh, give me
five. I gotta go pump first.
What are we pumping?
Oh.
Coordinates are set for the North Pole.
Thank you guys for coming with me.
Ready when you are.
Okay.
Oh! Here we go.
Can't see anything!
My face just went full Weeknd!
Wait, I think I see something.
Over here!
What?
I think it's a building.
Is there a door?
We don't need one.
Hello? Anybody here?
There.
Hey.
You okay?
When my father entered this facility
nearly 20 years ago,
he had severe ALS.
Maybe the reason he never
left is 'cause he couldn't.
Look, whatever we find in here,
we'll be right here with you.
Ugh.
It smells like science in here.
What kind of research does
your mom's lab do, exactly?
I honestly don't even know anymore.
Caity?
Dad? Is that you?
Is this really happening?
You're alive.
Are you... you're real?
Yeah, Dad, it's me. I'm real. I'm real.
You found me.
You got my message.
I did in the periodic
table we made together.
It took me 20 years to find
it, but it led me to you.
I knew you would come.
Thank you.
I thank all of you.
Dad, these are my friends. This is...
Uh, Barry Allen and Cisco Ramon. I know.
Um, sorry. How do you know us?
Well, when I first came here,
I stayed in contact with scientists.
Louise Lincoln, Victor
Fries, and Harrison Wells.
Dr. Wells was able to
give me full access to, uh,
S.T.A.R. Labs video uplink.
Wait a minute. You've... you've
had video lin to S.T.A.R. Labs
this entire time?
Oh, no. God no. I mean, it
hasn't worked until recently.
And unfortunately, since it rebooted,
its capabilities is
only as a one-way video,
so I could see you but
I couldn't reach you.
Well, it looks like you had
plenty of toys around here
to keep you company.
This neat little incubator.
What's it for?
Well, that was here when I got here.
Never had any use for that thing.
I don't understand. Why are you here?
I mean, how are you still even alive?
ALS is a horrible disease,
and I grew desperate,
and I began experimenting with
therapies using cryogenics.
Something went wrong?
Yes.
The, uh, experiments became
more and more dangerous.
And I quarantined myself
for the sake of everyone's safety.
I did manage to freeze the
progression of that disease.
Not before the site
was entirely closed out,
and I have been here ever since.
They shut down this site
while you were still in it
and locked you in.
It was my mother, wasn't it?
She's the only one with
an authority to shut down
a Tannhauser site.
Listen, your mother
thought it would be easier
for you not to see me.
But I always had the faith
that I could cure this thing.
That's why I sent you the note.
So how... how did you
survive here this whole time?
Water. Rations.
Spending months at a time
in that cryogenic chamber.
Well, you don't ever
have to do that again,
because we can get you out of here.
We're gonna give you your life back.
Shouldn't this place be
packed to the rafters?
I mean, we had a citywide
disaster not long ago.
Don't worry. I got this.
It's time to put the war face on.
Hey, buddy, pull them out.
Lose the music. Hi,
I'm DA Cecile Horton.
This is my associate, Ralph Dibny.
- DA?
- Mm.
How can I help you?
You the field director here?
Assistant. You got a claim or
something I can help you with?
We're trying to ID a suspect
in a criminal investigation
and we're going to need to
take a look at the names of
all the people you've assisted
in the last six months.
I can't give you anyone's names.
You'll need to get a warrant for that.
Listen up, mister!
Bagger Vance!
It's Vance Brandon.
You listen to me when I tell you
that this is my town, baby.
Oh, yeah, and I can make some real
bad stuff happen for you.
Like, really, really no bueno.
Yeah, well, this is my country,
which is a lot bigger than your town.
- That's true.
- So, until you get a warrant,
you're not getting anything.
But wait, did you... Bagger?
Bagger Va... did you...
But this my war face.
I put my war face on.
That was my war face, Ralph.
It's okay, I... I think you're just...
You're... you're a
little rusty, that's all.
Oh, no. That was way more
than a little rust, Ralph.
I've lost my mojo.
Oh, that was a... new mode of travel.
That is what we call an interdimensional
space-time breach.
It takes a little
while to get used to it.
So, this is S.T.A.R. Labs, IRL.
Look at that view.
I want to run some tests.
Make sure everything
is all right with you.
This city is so beautiful.
The sunsets here.
I used to think about them all the time.
Hey, maybe you guys should just
go for a walk or something.
Try and reconnect first.
Yeah.
Um, why don't we go for a walk?
Get some fresh air.
I can run my tests later.
I love that plan.
What's up with you?
Dude, this story is full of holes.
I'm just trying to fill them.
Nora's story had holes in them,
and she was only lying to me
'cause she wanted to meet me.
I've appreciated every second
that we've had together so far.
Caitlin just got her dad back.
Let's be happy for her.
Hey, I'm happy.
So what are we doing first?
Uh, well, you're a speedster.
So I was thinking you
could run around the site.
See if you can find the core.
I thought, since it's
our first time teaming up,
maybe I could go with you and
we can interview the people
who were here the night of
the Enlightenment together.
Oh, um, uh...
- Or no.
- No, no, no.
Yeah, it's just...
Normally, I interview people by myself.
Oh, oh, my God. No, no. It's fine.
It's... I wouldn't ask you
to come speed around the city
with me or anything like that.
- It's fine.
- Okay, well, I'll...
- No, no, no. You come with me...
- I'll come with you, okay.
And we'll interview the foreman.
All right, let's not. How about that?
Look, we have 45 more sites to search.
Clearly we don't have the time
and clearly we must split up.
So you go search for the core
and you go talk to the foreman.
I will look for clues.
And this is how investigations collapse.
Hey, babe.
No, the mother-daughter team-up
is kinda off to a rocky start.
But I don't know, I
think we'll get there.
So?
- The core's not here.
- Well...
why don't you go search the other sites?
We'll finish up here.
Well, no, you don't want
to do that, do you, no?
Because, um, you're not
here to investigate, are you?
No, you're here to spend
time with your mother, right?
Well, I just thought maybe
we would find something
in common if we worked
on a case together.
But she's really good at prying
information out of people.
Believe me, and...
I'm fast on my feet.
I'm gonna go back to S.T.A.R. labs.
Hold on, wait.
I have another plan to
try and find this core.
It involves you and your mother.
So, uh, cherry soda. Popcorn.
I haven't had a cup of Jitters
coffee in quite a while.
But the thing that
I miss the most was...
Peanut butter and jelly waffles.
Yeah, Mom used to hate
it when you made those.
Yeah, well, your mom always wanted
the nicer things in life, I guess,
and I was happy with simple.
It's a wonder you two ever got together.
- How is she?
- The same.
I don't really see her that often,
and when I do, she's cold as ice.
And now, after what she did to you...
Oh, well, look,
she may be a little bit chilly,
but she does love you, Caity.
It's been really hard without you.
I mean, just me and her.
It was tough.
- Yeah.
- I've been through a lot.
A lot of that has to do with me.
- No.
- No, no, listen,
and... and I wasn't there for you.
All these years... They went by and I...
I want to make it up to you, Caity.
I mean, I really should've
been there for you, right?
I mean... and I wish
that I could just...
Dad? Oh, my God.
Dad. Here, sit.
Oh, my God. Dad?
Dad, Dad.
Caity?
Dad? I'm right here.
You saw my disease?
Yeah, uh... the dermis is crystallizing.
And it's spreading.
I ran some tests while
you were unconscious.
You have a cryogenic malignancy
and a somatic mutation.
It's not contagious but...
It's rewriting my genetic code.
And if it continues, you could...
Die.
Well, I cured my ALS,
but I created something
even more deadly.
Every time my emotions
spike, my malignancy spreads.
Like when you're angry or scared?
I wish I had just
left well enough alone.
For both of us.
Wait, did I have the
genetic marker for ALS too
and you tried to cure me?
So my powers came from you?
Killer Frost is my cure?
Killer Frost?
You may know her by a different name.
Khione.
Dad, what did you do to me?
I wasn't gonna let
the ALS manifest in you
like it did in me.
So you used experiments
with cryogenic gene therapy
on your own daughter?
I had already done it on myself.
Caity, I made alterations
to the treatment.
I tried to make it safer, Caity,
and you started to
exhibit dual personality
soon after I treated you.
So is, um, Khione or Killer Frost...
Is she still around?
No, she... she's been
gone for a little while,
but she's still a part of me.
So where's your dual personality?
You and Caitlin carry the same markers,
you took the same cure.
Where your Khione?
I never had one.
That's probably why...
I'm dying and you're not.
Okay, what if we use my
cells to create a serum
to stabilize your body?
Um, we have to stop your
atoms from oscillating.
So get your body to a
temperature of absolute zero.
Caitlin, that could kill him.
My cells can theoretically
withstand subzero temperatures
because of my cryogenic gene therapy.
But the problem is
getting to absolute zero.
We could use a laser cooling array.
The DOD just constructed one
at their site outside of town.
- I could check it out.
- Okay, great.
I'll get started on the serum.
No, no, wait. Hold on.
We... we can't just hack into
the DOD's $5 billion security system.
Cisco.
I just got my dad back.
I can't let him die.
I'll see what I can do.
It's the fifth person to
be sliced up this week.
Take him to OR Three.
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
- I'm fine.
- I need to stitch that up.
You've got abrasions,
possible internal injuries.
You keep going out there,
you're gonna be back here in a body bag.
You can't be a part of this.
Do you know how many patients I've seen
come in this hospital
the past four years
because of those metas out there?
I just treated a man who was attacked by
a human razor blade, and you wanna say
I'm not a part of this?
Oh, I got that razor meta.
Just like I'll get the rest of them.
I know why you're doing this.
And I know that little
girl laying in a coma
is not my family, but
you are not the only one
whose heart breaks every
day she doesn't wake up.
Grace is the one that
needs help. Not me.
Now, are you gonna
get out of my way, Doc?
Or are you gonna call security?
What the heck happened back there?
I froze up.
Look.
When I got canned from CCPD,
I fell in with some legally
questionable individuals.
These are some scary, scary people,
but they all had one thing in common.
They were all terrified of
Ce-Seal-Your-Fate Horton.
And I don't believe for one second that
that woman has gone anywhere.
Don't ever call me that again.
I'm sorry. Geez. I thought
I... I thought we were bonding
and having a moment, but
I think I crossed the line.
I didn't really mean to...
I'm kidding. It's a joke. I was joking.
My gosh, I really got you.
You didn't have to get
so nervous about it.
Nervous. Like the FEMA guy did.
Ralph, I don't think
I froze up back there.
Right. Right, you're...
You're an empath now.
Your powers let you experience his fear.
You're... you're the
Deanna Troi of Team Flash.
I have no idea who that is,
but if he got that scared
when we asked him about
the victims list...
It's because he's hiding something.
Yes.
Whoa, whoa. What's, uh,
what's happening with
your nose right now?
Oh, when I smell a mystery,
that's my thing. I do that.
- That's nasty.
- It is? You don't...
- Please stop.
- You don't like it?
♪ C'est l'aviron qui nous
mène, qui nous mène ♪
♪ C'est l'aviron qui nous mène en haut ♪
♪ C'est l'aviron qui nous
mène, qui nous mène ♪
♪ C'est l'aviron qui nous mène en haut ♪
He has been singing that same
song for the last two hours.
I know, I know.
Are you seriously making tea right now?
Le thé. Oui. Right, chamomile.
You know, to stimulate the
brain, but also, frankly,
the digestive system.
Right, because since
I've arrived at here,
I've been backed up like a traffic jam.
That is so disgusting.
Beyond disgusting.
How are we supposed to investigate
when you're making tea, Sherloque?
Well, you seem very
annoyed, mademoiselle.
- No shrap, Sherlock.
- Sherloque.
Sorry for the language, Mom.
It's okay.
Hey, look.
There was a carnival the
night the satellite crashed.
If my dad is right about Cicada
being a father, then maybe...
He might've brought his kid here.
- Exactly.
- But, I mean, I ran all over this place.
There's no core in sight.
♪ C'est l'aviron qui nous
mène, qui nous mène ♪
What if...
The core fell into the water.
How you will retrieve it?
Nora, why don't you create
a vortex like your dad did
when he fought King Shark?
Oh, no, or what if we do
what you did with the Hotness?
You know about that?
Yeah, of course. I made Papa
Joe tell me everything about
when my mom was a speedster.
So how do we do it?
Um...
Well, you just, um... you
run back and forth in a...
In a really tight formation.
And you want to pull the
water up with your heels.
Okay, right, which will drive
the water away from the shore.
Exactly.
- Schway.
- Yeah.
Do you think I can do it?
Yeah, Nora, you got this.
Okay.
Four satellites?
Give them to Cisco. He's got 'em.
DOD sites? There you go.
All in a day's work for him.
You all think I can
just hack anything, huh?
Yeah.
I can hack anything.
There you are.
Oh!
Found a path into the DOD base.
As long as Cisco can shut down
the interior alarms, it'll work.
Awesome. I just need
to balance this serum
and we should be good to go.
Thank you for this, Caity.
I mean, what you're
doing is beyond the call.
Of course, you're my dad.
I'd do anything for you.
He's not your dad.
Look familiar?
Cisco. What are you talking about?
This is my father.
I went back to the
Tannhauser black ops site,
and I picked up a vibe.
I saw him working in the lab...
Cisco, your vibes have
been a little problematic...
I know what I saw. I saw him
standing over the incubator,
the one he claimed he had no use for,
and he was working on this.
Skin grafts? What does this
have to do with anything?
This is gonna sound whacked-out,
but what if, when you
dad tried to cure his ALS,
it didn't just give
him crystallized skin?
What if it really did
create that dual personality?
- This Killer Frost?
- That's who you think this is?
Thomas' alter ego
wearing a copy of his face
made out of these skin grafts?
Yes, I know. I know it-it sounds...
It sounds absurd, but I can see where
Mr. Ramon is getting his hypothesis.
My, uh, cryo-malignancy
spread further than I admitted,
and it's afflicted my face,
my hands, my arms, my chest.
And I created those skin
grafts from stem cells
that I found in the lab
in order to cover any further outbreaks.
You're lying to us.
- Cisco...
- Caitlyn, you have to see...
No, you need to leave us alone.
- Please...
- Now!
I got it.
Dude. Hey dude, we need to talk.
Why? I thought that dramatic
confrontation worked perfectly.
- We all want to help Caitlin.
- Oh, do you?
Yeah, I want Caitlin to have
a chance to be with her father.
Just like Nora got the
chance to be with you?
See, this is your problem.
You think that this
is just another perfect
father-daughter pairing, reunited.
I'm not blinded by my feelings.
Well, they're not helping
you see any clearer.
You gotta stop thinking
about this like Nora's dad
and start thinking about it like a CSI.
Please?
Don't do it for me. Do it for her.
Didn't I tell you to get lost?
Yes, you did. Thanks for that.
Gave us time to pull your file.
You don't have any priors,
but I did find about
a dozen outstanding
parking tickets, though.
Oh, no.
For, uh, what was it? It was, um...
Oh, yeah, a Lamborghini.
Hmm. Vroom, vroom.
How does a civil servant
afford a $200,000 car?
- Okay, I'm calling security.
- Please do.
I can't wait to report a
case of insurance fraud.
You've been telling citizens
their claims have been denied
and then pocketing the cash for yourself
when the government pays up.
That's why this FEMA center's
emptier than Grandma's whiskey
at a Dibny Christmas dinner.
You can't prove any of this.
Try me.
That's everyone.
Names, addresses, location
the night of the crash.
So... this is gonna stay between us?
You've been profiting
off of innocent victims.
You know I put a call
into your superiors
in D.C. 20 minutes ago.
I got my groove back, Vancey.
That's how I know it's you
that's scared and not me.
Now there's the old
Ce-Seal-Your-Fate Horton
- we all know and love.
- Hmm, great.
Hmm.
Hey.
If you came to defend
Cisco, please don't bother.
He just cares about you.
Come on, don't you think I wouldn't know
if that wasn't actually my father?
You too? Really?
Listen, I wanted to
believe that that's your dad
and that he's a good guy
because I want you to be happy.
But I don't... I don't know.
Maybe I haven't been seeing clearly.
There is a lot about this
guy's story that doesn't add up.
This guy? This guy is my father.
He's the man who held
me when I had chickenpox.
Who told me I could
be anything I wanted to
and made me believe it.
So please stop treating
him like he's a criminal.
Okay.
You know how estranged
I am from my mother
and how empty I felt
without Killer Frost.
He is the only family that I have left.
But Caitlin, that's not
true. We're your family too.
And we're only asking
you to keep an open mind
because we care about you.
Especially Cisco.
If it'll make you feel better,
you can ask him your questions,
but only after I give him the serum.
- What's wrong?
- Oh, my God.
What?
If I give this serum to a human,
it will suppress their malignant side.
But if I give it to a
cryogenic meta-human,
it will permanently
suppress their human side.
If that's your father's alter ego...
He's trying to wipe out my dad.
He needed your cells to make the serum.
"Caitlin, come find me."
Caity.
What's going on?
Dad, why?
Well... I guess, as you're all here...
You have such smart friends, Caity.
That frozen liquid in your lungs
is gonna be turning into tiny icicles.
Making it very difficult
for you to breathe.
But no worries.
You'll pass out soon.
Caitlin. Hey!
Caitlin, wake up.
- Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Um, is my dad gone?
He took the serum.
This is all my fault.
I was so excited to have my dad back
that I... I couldn't
see who he really was.
I owe you both an apology.
Hey, it's okay.
We'll get him.
Hey, guys, get in here.
Come on.
Eyes, please.
- What?
- He's at the DOD site.
Look.
That building's 7 below?
Look at the temperature.
Look at it drop.
He initiated the negative array
but didn't seal it.
The room is -7, but
the array is -100.
That thing's so freaking cold,
it's freezing the whole building.
Wait, at this rate, in 5 minutes,
the temperature will be 460 degrees,
AKA absolute zero.
At which point, he can
inject himself with my serum.
And turn himself into a full-on icicle.
Icicle, that's... Not the time.
- We gotta go.
- Let's do it.
Hey, what... What about your hands?
You're my friend, my family. I'm going.
Almost there.
Ugh... Flash.
Don't you realize that
speed and cold don't mix?
This machine is capable
of producing isotopes
that can freeze carbon dioxide.
You can't run in here.
More superheroes to freeze.
The array's at -220.
You have one minute.
You people are not
as smart as I thought.
Guys, what's happening?
The temperature in the room is dropping.
Everyone's so cold, their
atoms are hitting near stasis.
Why... why can't I see my breath?
It's too cold. There's
no moisture in the air.
Cisco, are you okay?
No. At least I can't feel anything.
Guys, the array's at -350 degrees.
He's gonna be able to
go full icicle soon.
Come on.
- Forty-five seconds.
- What do we do?
Lightning.
Use your lightning to counter the cold
and maybe you can warm
up enough to stop him.
We've been trying to
do it this whole time.
It's too cold.
I'm literally fr... freezing.
399, you have 30 seconds.
Your temperature is
dropping too quickly.
You're gonna go into
hypothermic shock soon.
But not Caitlin.
Look, Caitlin's body
temperature is normal.
Caitlin, you must be immune.
But Killer Frost is gone.
Well, clearly, she's not.
Guys, 400 degrees. We got 20 seconds.
Caitlin, you can do it.
Just concentrate.
Dad!
Please, I know you're in there.
Don't do this.
Do you think Thomas can hear you, Caity?
Thomas hasn't been able to hear
anything for a very long time.
- What is that?
- 460 degrees. We're too late.
He beat us.
No!
My daughter. You've returned!
You're not my family. They are.
You only gave a damn about me
because you wanted that serum.
But I... I can share it with you.
Just imagine.
The two of us, free to
be ourselves without fear.
You are strong.
We can be even stronger together.
I'm strong because I
have people in my life
who actually care about me.
Do you?
No!
Caity?
- Dad?
- You found me?
Temperature's rising.
What's happening? Is everyone okay?
- I think so.
- A little help?
Get Cisco.
Oh, yeah. That's good.
Yeah.
Okay.
My dad.
Our dad.
He was here, but... I lost him.
We'll get him back. Together.
You're not alone anymore.
Neither am I.
No cold signatures in the area.
Snow Country for Old
Men must be miles away,
'cause he sure as hell
isn't in Central City.
Well, we have to find him.
I mean, Icicle wouldn't have
gone through all this trouble
to kill my Dad if there wasn't
a piece of him still left.
We'll find him.
All the things I vibed, they
weren't memories of your dad.
They were of his alter ego.
My dad was trying to protect me.
You know what? My mom probably was too.
I mean, she was just
trying to keep me safe.
All this time, I thought
she was the villain.
How could I not see it was him?
Hey, don't beat yourself up.
Thawne. Zolomon.
We see the good in people.
That's just who we are.
I hope that never changes.
There's something else
you guys should see.
All this time, we've
been trying to figure out
how Killer Frost disappeared,
but we've been looking at it all wrong.
We've been thinking DeVoe
used Melting Point's powers,
that he changed your meta DNA
and removed Killer Frost from you.
But tonight, you proved that
she's still a part of you.
So what caused her to leave?
DeVoe used a different set of powers.
- Brainstorm.
All they did was create a mental block.
One you broke through tonight,
so you can do that again.
You just gotta learn how.
I think it's time we
reintroduce an old friend.
Harry's mental activity dampener.
It'll help me hear her.
That's right.
It's my hope that the more you use it,
the more you connect with her.
Eventually, you won't need it anymore.
Thank you.
Guys, we need you in the Speed Lab.
All right. We'll leave you to it.
Hey, stranger.
Hey.
Well, we sure have a lot to talk about.
Oh! Sally's heart!
You brought it back.
We did, thanks to these two
and their deductive abilities.
And our tidal-wave-breaking skills. Right?
- Like mother, like daughter.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, is it safe for this to be here?
Yeah, a little dark
matter never hurt anybody.
What?
We've seen this puzzle piece before.
Our satellite giveth, and
now we must taketh away.
I think we can finally do that.
We got a list from FEMA of
everyone who reported injuries
the night of the Enlightenment.
None of them matched
Cicada's description.
But there were three kids
who were hit by pieces of
shrapnel from the satellite.
Two of them are twins
whose father is deceased.
Third is a ten-year-old girl,
by the name of Grace Gibbons.
So if my dad's right and
Cicada's a father, then...
We may have just found his daughter.
Orlin?
Orlin.
After I fix up your side,
I'm gonna patch up your chest.
No.
It's making me stronger.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --