[Iris West]
Previously on The Flash...
We have been looking
at that front page for four years.
And I'm the one
that writes that article, Barry.
My boss's husband is the Flash?
Mmm-hmm.
God. Nobody tells me anything.
This substance appears to heal any
and all weaknesses in the human body.
I've learned to control it.
This is my final masterpiece.
Life eternal.
I've seen your version of life.
It's a nightmare.
[Elongated Man] I want to show you this.
[Iris West] I recognize that pin.
[Ramsey] I have a follow-up question.
[grunting]
Whoo!
That was quite the tumble.
I guess you're wondering
why I'm doing this to you.
You're evil. I get it.
[chuckles softly]
[grunts]
[Elongated Man grunting]
[car crashes]
[grunts]
[labored breathing]
I bet it's been a while since
you've felt your own mortality.
But my powers, like yours,
work on a cellular level.
Allow me to demonstrate.
[grunts]
[Ramsey groans]
[Elongated Man groans]
[Ramsey chuckling]
You know, Iron Heights is gonna send me
a "thank you" basket
when I drop you off as a gift.
I've already given you a gift.
And now... I'm gonna need it back.
[grunting]
[coughing]
My destiny is to heal all of mankind.
You and your friends can't be allowed
to prevent that.
Life demands your death.
Ralph!
Ralph! Ralph! Ralph, come on!
Give us a hand.
- What happened?
- Ramsey.
Come on, Coach. We've still gotta
go on that road trip, right?
[grunting]
He's gonna die.
- Frost, how do we save him?
- I don't know. I can't fix this.
Uh, maybe Caitlin can.
Ralph's elastic cells aren't mending
like they used to.
Ramsey must be getting stronger.
- So Ralph can't heal himself?
- No. But maybe you can.
What?
Your speed-healing is the only thing
we've seen
that can repair damage this severe.
Maybe if we gave him
a blood transfusion, that would fix him.
What are you saying? [stuttering]
I can give Ralph my speed-healing?
Theoretically, temporarily, yes.
I don't know.
We're sort of in uncharted
medical territory here.
But your blood type is O-negative,
so you're a universal donor.
[rattling]
Guys, Ralph is elastic.
No needle can puncture through his skin.
- I can phase him.
- Would that work?
Do it.
- Got it?
- [Barry] Yeah.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
[device beeping]
[startled gasp]
Hey. How is he?
He's stable, thanks to you.
We contacted A.R.G.U.S.
and they're gonna move Ralph
to a secure medical facility
for recovery.
Cisco and Caitlin are prepping
for transport right now.
Hey, don't worry, okay?
He's gonna pull through.
[sighs]
It's not that.
What if I hadn't been here?
Ralph's fight was nothing compared
to what's coming.
Crisis is only two days away.
And we're all ready. I promise.
Iris, if I haven't prepared the team...
You have prepared us, Barry.
Hey, don't let what happened
to Ralph fill you with doubt.
You've done the work. We're ready.
For whatever comes next.
[sighs]
[sighs heavily]
I'm gonna give you one chance
to turn yourself in.
Honestly, I hope you don't take it.
Well, there's no need
to involve the authorities.
I just want to talk...
Flash.
Of course. You're the Flash.
But how did...
When...
You were struck by lightning.
[chuckles]
That is quite the origin story.
[shudders]
I don't know how you're doing this.
Real or not, I'm coming for you.
And yet, I'm not your foremost concern,
am I?
Not as much as your inevitable demise
in a coming...
Crisis?
Goodness, you really are
full of surprises, aren't you?
So, tell me.
When you saw all those permutations,
billions of possible futures,
all ending in your death...
what role did I play?
You didn't.
You weren't there.
Really? Not even in one?
Huh.
Then again,
you never saw this coming, did you?
Frankly, neither did I.
Makes one believe in the impossible,
doesn't it?
You look scared.
Well, you should be.
After all,
it is the end of the world, isn't it?
[breathing heavily]
[gasping]
[Allegra] What's that, Flash?
You think I should bust my boss
for keeping yet another secret from me?
Yeah. Me, too.
Drop what you're doing.
The Citizen has a new story.
Look at these.
- Where did you get those photos?
- I pulled them from a bow tie camera.
[Iris West] Long story.
Look, the point is,
this is the same guy
that kidnapped your cousin Esperanza
and turned her into a meta-assassin
against her will.
One of these photos, this one,
shows our mystery man
getting out of his car.
My dad traced his plates
and tracked the car
to a rented parking space
at a nearby lot.
So, now all we have to do is wait
for him to show up.
Cool.
Just checking, are there any
other stories you want to work on first?
Wh... [chuckles]
What could need our attention
more than this?
Your cousin was a victim, Allegra,
and now some secret organization is
using her.
- I mean, how many others are they using?
- We need to help them.
Right. I mean, no one...
wants to find out what happened
to Esperanza more than me,
but is this really what
matters the most to you... right now?
Yeah. Now, come on. Get your stuff.
Kamilla is going to see
if she can recover any other photos.
You and I have a stakeout date.
You're the boss.
Brain activity looks good.
No sign that you're going nuts.
And my blood work?
CBC, metabolic rate, all normal...
for a speedster.
Just a small spike in cortisol.
Caity said that sleep monitor
on your wrist
will tell us if there's
anything seriously wrong.
But if you ask me,
you just had a nightmare.
I don't know.
Ramsey seemed so real.
Something feels off.
I just can't put my finger on it.
[car lock chirrups]
Hi, there. My name is Iris West-Allen.
I'm with The Citizen.
I was wondering if I could ask you
a few questions.
Sorry. Not interested.
Hi. Same paper. Same question.
What the hell is going on here?
I don't have time for this.
I'm late for work.
Which is where, exactly?
None of your business.
Okay, you know what? You're right.
We will just run our photos
without any comments.
What photos?
You know what? I'm sure your employer
will love the free exposure.
- All right. Have it your way.
- Easy. I've got a taser.
And I have a business card.
[chuckles softly]
[man reading]
Transporting what, exactly?
Whatever the wealthy would prefer
to keep under the radar.
Specialty items, mostly.
That woman in a coma was
a government job.
Meister's party, well...
that was more like designated driving
for billionaires falling off the wagon.
Today, it's priceless family jewels.
You're an Uber for the uber-rich.
What I am is late.
Sorry to bother you. Thank you.
[Iris West sighs]
- That was a bust.
- Yep.
But the bright side is we have time for
other stories we might be putting off.
Got any in mind?
You know, I don't know. I think there's
something that we missed.
I don't want to move off of this yet.
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[groans softly]
Mom?
Is this another nightmare?
No, Barry. This is much, much worse.
- You're the Speed Force.
- Yes.
It's been a while since
we've talked like this.
[chuckles softly]
I've missed it.
You need to help.
I don't understand
what's happening to me.
You used your blood
to save your friend's life,
but in the process,
you've endangered your own.
A small amount of Ramsey's cells
remain from the attack.
Hidden from the eye.
- Ramsey's infected me.
- More than you realize.
Ramsey's sentience,
his very being, resides in his cells.
That's how he knew I'm the Flash.
About Crisis.
If this...
If this is all in my mind,
then where's my real body?
After your friend Frost examined you,
you came back home.
Dropped your keys in that bowl.
Poured a glass of water.
Then the infection took hold.
As we speak, Ramsey's infection is
spreading through your body
and your mind.
Your speed-healing is trying
to hold off his disease.
But ultimately,
it's up to you to resist him.
Is he trying to kill me?
Worse, I'm afraid.
He wants to take control of you
and bend you to his will.
Then he's gonna lose.
There must be something that points
to where Esperanza was taken.
I don't know. Hospital records?
Or what about that auction photo?
That mystery man was a dead end,
but Barry did say that there were
a lot of shady people at that gala,
so I don't know.
Maybe one of them might be a new lead.
Or we could talk about
how your husband is the Flash.
- How did you...
- Nash Wells told me.
You're not gonna... Is this the story
that you've been trying to tell?
Allegra, Barry's identity
cannot be exposed.
No, not that.
This.
You've been avoiding it all day.
It's not time for that yet.
Well, according to this,
it will be in two days.
And call it a hunch, but I don't think
you're planning to write it then,
either.
I ever tell you...
why I wanted to be a reporter
in the first place?
It was because of your article
about the Streak.
[exhales sharply]
You know, that was the first name
that I ever gave to the Flash.
Back then, I didn't even know
that he was Barry.
And back then, I was just
a troubled kid in Iron Heights.
But your article...
It made me believe in the impossible.
That maybe someday, I could be like you.
Chasing stories, uncovering the truth.
You gave me hope when I had none.
Just like you have
every day I've worked here.
I don't know how you're gonna
bring yourself to write this article.
I...
I just know you're never
going to forgive yourself if you don't.
What's... How did I...
[laughter]
[silverware clattering]
- [Killer Frost] Mmm.
- [Cisco] Mmm.
Allen, mmm, looks like we're both
back on our feet.
Babe, I'm glad you're feeling better.
Look. I made you a plate.
[Cisco] Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm.
- Delicious.
- I'm all about these mashed potatoes.
I'm gonna need a second helping
of these beans.
That's both praise and a warning.
[laughter]
[Dibny] Uh-oh.
[laughter continues]
This is wrong.
[Iris West] Mmm.
Everyone, I've got homemade lasagna.
[all cheering and applauding]
- [squelching]
- [breathing heavily]
[Killer Frost] Yum.
[Iris West] Barry?
It's rude not to eat.
[Barry] You're not Iris.
This isn't real.
[breathing heavily]
I'm not gonna give in to you.
Barry, you misjudge me.
I'm just here to enjoy supper
with good friends,
and, perhaps, offer you a gift.
What could you possibly offer me?
[all] Everything.
[breathing heavily]
[high-pitched ringing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[yells]
[grunts]
Barry, you can't run away
from your own mind.
At least, not without considerable pain.
Then again, you're always trying to run
away from your problems, aren't you?
[Barry grunts]
You've literally had a newspaper
warning of your demise,
and you've done nothing
to change your fate.
It's almost like you want
to make Iris a widow.
Shut up!
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
This isn't real.
[Ramsey] These deaths were real.
None of them had to die.
Join me and you'll never have to.
[music box playing "Hush, Little Baby"]
- [baby fusses]
- Nora.
Hey.
[music distorts]
[voice trembles]
Please, let me hold her.
I know it's not real. I just...
Please. I just want to pretend.
Please. Just for a second.
I just want to...
Please. I want to hold my baby.
That's not my choice, Barry.
Why are you showing this to me?
[Ramsey] I'm not showing you anything.
All of this is coming from you.
No, it's not. No, it's not.
No, it's not.
[Ramsey] Look deep within, Barry Allen.
This is your mind, your visions.
Your doubt.
We all die without you.
You leave me alone forever.
Your city will burn.
[Eobard] She's even faster than ever.
[exhales]
[chuckles]
The Negative Speed Forces were too much,
even for me.
And now, Barry, everyone is dead.
It doesn't have to be like this, Barry.
Here. Let me show you.
Accept my lifeblood,
and you could use it to achieve
so much more than I ever could.
Become a hero
beyond your wildest dreams.
[gasps]
The power to strike down death.
Life eternal.
The grand miracle at your command.
Save the world and live.
Have all you want.
[baby fussing]
She's so beautiful.
[Ramsey] Embrace it, Barry.
Just confess the truth.
Do you have doubts?
I do.
It's a beautiful life, Barry.
All you have to do is choose it.
Choose life.
[exhales]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[Nora Allen] Barry.
You must gather your strength.
Focus.
Time is running out.
[Joe] Thought you all
would want to see this.
[camera shutter clicking]
Witnesses heard the explosion,
but didn't see much else.
There's gotta be at least half a dozen
cameras covering this lot, I...
And not one of them caught
anyone entering or exiting the scene
when this all went down.
It's like a ghost did this.
[indistinct police radio chatter]
So, the guy you questioned was killed
in the same lot you questioned him,
- on the same day.
- Yeah.
Uh, it gets worse.
This blew away from the scene.
I thought about turning it in
to the cops,
but I only saw it 'cause there's a major
UV energy coming off this thing.
You can see that?
Boss, this really feels like a job
for your husband's friend.
Oh, no, Kamilla knows
that Barry is the Flash.
Seriously?
- Since when?
- Last summer. Cisco used to be Vibe.
Okay. Look, guys. I think this mystery
goes a lot deeper than we thought.
And it's a lot more dangerous.
- So, if you guys wanna walk away...
- Not a chance.
That makes two of us.
Well, boss, looks like
Team Citizen has a new mission.
[Nora Allen] It's okay, Barry. I'm here.
I'm sorry it took me so long
to find you.
Ramsey's infection is stronger
than anything we've ever faced.
And it's only getting stronger.
[Barry shudders]
[groans]
I think I know why.
You feel doubt?
I do.
You've answered our call before.
It's always been difficult.
What's changed?
I've lived more.
I've gotten married.
I've seen a future where...
I'll have a daughter who's the best
of me and Iris combined.
Most of my life has been
driven by my past, but...
but now it finally feels like
I'm living for myself.
I don't wanna leave my family.
Or my friends.
I don't wanna die.
[groans]
I know that's selfish.
[tearfully] I'm sorry I let you down.
Barry, no person is immune
to fear and doubt.
No matter how brave.
That's what makes you human, Barry.
But the courage to move forward
even in the face of overwhelming odds?
That's what makes you a hero.
That's what makes you the Flash.
Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
[gulps]
Don't blame yourself.
His lies...
they were so convincing.
That's because he never lied.
What do you mean?
That's what makes Ramsey so dangerous.
He manipulates the truth
to spread his disease.
What? So...
So the part about his cells allowing me
to save the world from Crisis...
and still survive is true?
Yes.
- But that path's not for you.
- Why not?
Barry, you must understand.
That you want me to leave behind
everyone I love
when there's a way to save me?
[rapid beeping]
[beeping continues]
What is it?
It's Barry's sleep monitor.
This can't be right.
His vitals are spiking.
Barry, your fever is rising.
You must calm down.
Stop telling me what to do!
- His temperature's burning up.
- Why isn't he speed-healing?
I've seen this fever before.
He's being taken over. Right now.
His temperature's rising. Could really
use some cold powers right about now.
No, Ramsey's infection doesn't respond
to ice.
We need to treat him medicinally.
Inserting ten cc's of naproxen sodium.
All my pain, all my suffering has been
because of you.
Because you would rather I be the Flash
than have anything that I want.
Barry, please. I am not denying
the burden that you've carried.
But the Speed Force has only
ever tried to be a guide
on this path that you've chosen.
A lightning bolt shot down
from the sky and struck me!
- [squelching]
- I didn't choose this!
You decided to change my life,
my family's life, my entire future.
This was done to me.
[beeping]
We need help.
Frost.
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[whimpering]
Frost. Frost.
- Hey, hey. Hey.
- [hyperventilating]
Just breathe. Breathe.
Just breathe.
Please understand. The role you play
is vital to the balance of all things.
Oh, stop.
There are universal forces at stake.
They must be protected.
What about the rest of us?
She's right.
There are universal forces at stake.
It's just a pity she doesn't consider
your life among them.
Don't listen to him. He wants to possess
your form no matter the cost.
Cost? All those headstones.
Those people are dead
because of my connection to you.
How many times
do I have to suffer for you?
When is it your turn to suffer?
[winces]
[breathing heavily]
Do you even feel pain?
No... at least not as you know it.
How could it?
The Speed Force isn't human. It doesn't
know what it means to be alive.
To have a family. To love.
It only pretends.
Ramsey's infection is twisting
your heart. You have to fight it, Barry.
- These aren't your true feelings.
- What do you know about the truth?
This isn't what you look like.
This isn't my old bedroom. It's a trick.
This is you manipulating me
so I'll do what you want.
That's not true. I care about you.
All it cares about is using you.
- Barry, you must listen to me.
- No, I don't!
You're not my mom.
You're the reason I buried her.
[gasps]
- [grunts]
- [groaning]
[rattling]
[Nora Allen] No!
[sobbing]
[panting]
No.
[muffled cries]
The Monitor, Thawne, the Speed Force.
For too long, others have used you.
Take command of your life.
Forever.
No. I'm sorry. I have to.
- It's the only way to survive.
- [pounding on door]
We don't have much time
until he returns, Barry. Look at me.
Accepting Ramsey's blood would
save your body from the coming Crisis,
but not your soul.
You would lose the best of you.
Your joy, your passion, your light...
- the part of you that Iris loves.
- [pounding on door]
[growling nearby]
Don't listen to it. It lies.
Come on. Barry.
[Nora Allen grunts]
[groaning]
Only you can defeat this, Barry.
The choice is yours.
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[beeping regularly]
You beat it.
Took me a while, but... yeah, I beat it.
[chuckles]
[sighs softly]
"My name is Iris West-Allen,
and I once met a young man,
a superhero who I called the Streak.
The world has come to know him
as the fastest man alive.
The Scarlet Speedster. The Flash.
But no matter what title you choose
for him, he'll always be remembered
as the protector of our amazing city
and its citizens.
As a beacon of hope for us all.
As the man who sacrificed himself
again and again so we could live.
[voice breaking]
Today, we said goodbye to him.
Not because he was taken,
but because he gave himself willingly.
And in the end, that's what makes him
deserving of the greatest title of all."
"Hero."
[sniffles]
[cell phone chimes and vibrates]
[exhales]
[powering up]
[distorted zapping]
[exhales]
Mar Novu,
you ran and ran across infinite Earths,
and now,
you have nowhere left to run.
It was like... being back in prison,
only locked up in my own mind.
All the terror I felt,
the horrible things I saw,
they were all there,
buried deep inside me,
just waiting to come out the whole time.
Took a lot to win.
Everything that makes life worth living.
Thank you.
You deserve some of the credit.
It takes something special
to beat a sentient infection
that not even speed-healing can cure.
Well, it's not over yet,
so let's get back to work.
Whoa, whoa... What do you mean?
What are you doing? Just get some rest.
Iris is gonna be here any minute.
Crisis will be here
in less than 36 hours.
We have to find Ramsey, stop him.
Make sure there's still
a world left to save.
And away he goes.
You wanna talk about what happened?
I already talked about it with Caity.
Okay. What'd she say?
With Crisis approaching,
we decided it would be best
if she handles the medical emergencies.
I'll take a back seat.
And you're okay with that?
It's what's best for the team.
Hey. I got here as fast as I could.
- How are you?
- Oh, I'm fine.
- Really, I'm okay.
- Your husband had an infection.
It messed with his brain quite a bit,
but we handled it.
Okay, well, just to be safe,
I am not leaving you again
for the rest of the night.
What you working on?
Just running some diagnostics.
Little maintenance.
Why don't you ask Cisco? We could
go home, spend some time together.
Why are you asking so many questions?
[chuckles]
I don't know.
You know, sometimes the reporter brain
in me has a mind of its own.
[clears throat]
I will let you get back to work.
Hey, guys.
That's not Barry.
[whispers] Careful.
Hey. Barry.
Hey.
Barr.
[snarls]
[chuckles]
[footsteps thudding]
[Ramsey] Welcome, my Blood Brother.
I am the world's salvation...
come to save it from all that ails it.
Soon, the entire world will embrace...
[squelching]
Bloodwork!