Please... Please, don't...
Don't do this.
The Indian Ocean?
Yeah, there's this
great island there.
Super secluded, and it's been
pretty quiet here recently,
so I'm zooping Iris away
for a little vacation.
Actually, it was Chester's idea,
you remember?
Can't forget.
Hey, Chester!
Iris! Wait...
Wait, if you're down here
and he's down here, then...
- No.
- Oh, my!
As much as I'd like to.
Cell phone reception's,
uh, nonexistent,
so we're going to be
off the grid for a while.
It should be nice
just to focus on each other
while we're trying to...
Um...
What I mean, Iris and I,
what we're trying to...
- Trying to reconnect, right?
- Reconnect. Yeah.
I mean, you know,
'cause lately, if one of you
- isn't stuck in the Mirrorverse...
- The Mirrorverse.
...then the other is stuck
in some psycho-masked hellscape.
- Yeah.
- Am I right?
- Okay, cool. Have fun.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
So, Frost, with boss man
and boss lady away,
need us to do anything?
Nope. No baddies
means we can take the day.
I think we all need some R&R.
Oh, to start off this R&R,
why don't you guys join me
in a little bit of D&D?
Frost, if you're free,
I could use a chaotic good
ice sorcerer to help me slay
the Bog Beast of Balladok.
I'm gonna have to take a pass.
- I've got a personal errand to run.
- Need any help?
Nope.
I'm going... shopping.
Have fun storming the castle.
What say thee, fair maiden?
Care to join me in an epic quest?
Oh, sorry.
I got a hot news tip. Gotta follow up.
But I'll catch up with you later.
Yeah, yeah. Nice, nice, nice.
News never sleeps. News never sleeps.
I was off base
on R&R, eating at a café,
and I saw Major Kramer in another booth,
arguing with this guy.
- About?
- I don't know.
But I heard him say, "Stick to the plan
and it'll all be over tomorrow."
It didn't sound like
it was anything good.
Now, that was a soldier
who served at Fort Dakota
at the same time
that Kramer was stationed there.
Did they recognize the person
that Kramer was arguing with?
A soldier named Adam Creyke.
This is the same man who led her troops
into an ambush six years ago
that got them killed.
Now, Kramer never logged going off base
the night of this conversation,
which means this was a secret meeting.
Hold on. Are you telling me
that Kramer knew about the ambush,
and maybe she even helped plan it?
I don't know.
They never caught the bomber
and this evidence looks bad,
but my gut says
that something still doesn't add up.
I mean, look, Cecile.
I've looked Kramer in the eye.
I've watched her work.
Uh, we've had our differences,
but... I still feel
she's a good cop.
Joe, she's not just a cop anymore.
She's the head of the C.C.P.D. now.
Well, I might not have a badge anymore,
but I'm gonna find out the truth
about Kristen Kramer once and for all.
Thanks, man.
- Hey.
I see you found someone
to play your dungeon game thing.
Oh, seriously?
I walked all the way here
and nobody told me,
including Marco,
who I literally just talked to.
Well, maybe if you let me
rejoin the campaign, I'd have your back,
like I did in the Battle of Mo'Zoq.
Using fire spells in unarmed combat
is strictly prohibited, Marco.
You're not a new...
He knows the consequences.
Anyway.
I got your text. What's up?
So, you know that message I got earlier?
Mmm-hmm.
I have been using The Citizen tip line,
but not for work.
I just got an anonymous tip
that's gonna help me find my cousin.
As in, Ultraviolet?
As in the Black Hole meta-assassin
that tries to kill you
every time she sees you?
Her name's Esperanza,
and I get how it sounds.
Look, she's been taking out targets.
First here in Metropolis,
then in Opal City.
I think her next assassination
is in Central City.
Chuck, if Team Flash
can get a jump on this...
- Flash isn't around.
- Exactly.
What would Barry do?
He'd find her and get her to stand down.
I have to do the same.
Esperanza blames me for abandoning her.
I have to make that right.
'Cause if I can get through to her,
maybe we can be a family again.
Listen to me. I don't wanna fight.
Wait.
Stop.
I won't let you hurt my friends.
Fine.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Figures
you're a part of this.
Well, I can't expect you to fail
on your missions all on your own.
Except for that one time in Belize.
That was hilarious.
Are you freaking nuts?
I have seen Ultraviolet
melt the face off of someone
and laugh while doing it.
What made you think
going after her alone was a good idea?
Chuck and I were gonna bring
in the team, but Esperanza surprised us.
Side note,
prayer hands emoji for the save.
But how did you know we were in trouble?
It's one of the reasons I stuck around.
I heard chatter
about an ex-Black Hole assassin nearby.
Good thing I went hunting.
Speaking of, where are the big guns?
Frost is radio silent
and Barry and Iris are off the grid.
So, for the rest of today,
this is Team Flash.
Well, that's reassuring.
I don't suppose
you've learned how to melt
someone's face off with your powers yet?
No. Okay, great.
Well, it's a good thing
just his wrist got hurt,
because we don't have nearly
enough muscle to handle this mission.
But I can still save Esperanza.
You want to save her?
Yeah. You know,
like Barry does with the bad guys.
I mean, not so much save her,
but redeem her, I guess.
Listen, I don't think
we can take on Ultraviolet by ourselves,
let alone change her overnight.
Uh...
I don't think we have a choice.
Look, Allegra said that Ultraviolet
is here to kill somebody.
That means there's a life in danger.
Isn't saving people Team Flash 101?
Chester's right. We need to stop her.
Fine.
But family or not, she will try
to kill you if she gets the chance.
That's every location
Ultraviolet's been spotted
in in the last 48 hours,
but so far,
no luck on her current location.
What about the satellites?
Well, her energy signature's
based off of light,
which is like, everywhere at all times,
so it's almost impossible to hone in
on her specific light signature.
This is where she's going.
It's a typical Black Hole recon pattern.
Scope out the surrounding areas
while closing in on your target.
This is a downtown free clinic.
- Why go there to try to kill someone?
- I don't know.
But the bigger question is,
how do we stop her?
With this.
It's a photonic stun grenade.
Procuring it required
two trips to New Delhi,
a helicopter crash
and a very deadly quinceañera.
I'm gonna go make sure
this is fully charged.
I'll be back in ten,
we'll discuss the plan.
Be ready to go.
Yeah!
Time to put my badass face on.
Right. Yeah?
No?
Chuck, maybe
you better sit this one out.
Whoa!
What? I wanna help.
I know, but you're a pacifist,
and that's cool.
But this is gonna be too dangerous.
We'll be back before you know it, okay?
Stay away from me.
Not until you're dead.
Run.
Tell whoever hired you
the assassination is canceled.
You fools. I wasn't hired.
I'm hunting the doctor that created me.
You just saved the man
that turned me into a monster.
That doctor.
Did he really used
to work for Black Hole?
Talk to us or talk to C.C.P.D.
The choice is yours.
Although I hear their cells
are much less comfortable.
Do you know
how I got this little gift?
I remember seeing
white light everywhere.
Blinding me while I was held down.
I was helpless.
Then I felt a scalpel slice into me.
I fought back, but I was tied down.
All I could do was scream...
until they cut my voice out of me.
I'm so sorry.
- I didn't know.
- Where's Dr. Olsen?
We...
don't know.
He must pay.
He is still out there.
Turning new lab rats into weapons
for the highest bidder.
Abducting victims who won't be missed
when they disappear.
Like me.
I never meant for this to happen.
- I swear.
- You abandoned me, cousin.
Left me alone for Dr. Olsen to find.
We'll help you get him. I promise.
Ah...
Sidebar, please.
You want to join her now?
This Olsen guy needs to be stopped
before he hurts anyone else.
And Esperanza's the only one
who's had any luck tracking him down.
Okay. We cannot trust her.
Black Hole has twisted her mind
in ways that you can't even imagine.
There's no coming back from that.
- You can't be sure.
- Yes, I can.
Working with her is a suicide mission.
You need to know that.
I know what Barry would do.
I say we go after this doctor together.
You in, prima?
Come in.
Well, this is a surprise.
We need to talk, Captain.
Interim Captain.
And since you're no longer a cop,
what exactly do we have to discuss?
Where did you get this?
That's not important.
What matters is, I could have gone
to Chief Singh with it,
but I chose to come to you first,
because deep down, I believe you are
doing your best to be a good cop.
Which means I should listen
to your side of the story.
- Get out.
- Excuse me?
I take your job, now you take me down?
So you dig up some crap you can twist
for your personal vendetta?
- I...
- Enough.
You try a stunt like this again...
and I will arrest you myself.
For your own good, move on, West.
Find a new hobby
and get the hell out of my office.
Now, generate
a single blast
that destroys your target.
And focus.
If we're going to face
Dr. Olsen together,
you need to learn how to fight.
Try harder.
I'm doing the best I can.
It's not good enough.
You still think
you can change her?
She's got this crazy idea
that you're not a total lost cause.
Noble, but dumb.
Just stay out of this.
You think you know your cousin?
I know the real Ultraviolet.
Let me show you.
Yo, yo, yo,
who's ready for a snack attack?
Chuck!
He's still breathing.
You could have killed him!
So? He's useless.
As are you.
I'll finish this on my own.
You don't know how lucky you were.
One foot to the right and you would have
a giant hole charred in your chest.
Roger that.
But, hey, I'm good.
Yeah, no. It probably just
looks worse than it is.
Hey, no. The Runk Man's
ready for action...
No, no, no.
The Runk Man needs to stay here.
I'll get you some
naproxen for the pain.
Doctor's orders.
Chuck, this is all my fault.
No, no. It's not that bad.
Where's your cousin?
Did she really leave?
Yup. And good riddance.
Shouldn't we go after her?
I don't know.
Runk! She is still not
thinking straight.
You've gotta help me
talk some sense into her.
- Why me?
- She likes you. She'll listen.
I mean, yeah, we're friends and all,
but I really don't think
I can change her mind.
Not on this.
Okay, fine. Then I will do it myself.
She's got to realize that
sharing a back alley yin-yang tattoo
with someone doesn't mean
you're bonded forever.
Yin-yang tattoo?
Great Rao...
Arrest you?
Are you sure Kramer's serious?
You should've seen her, Cecile.
It was like how a guilty person reacts.
So she really did have something to do
with getting her own troops killed.
My God!
If this is true, I have to go
straight to the governor's office.
It's that big.
Babe, C.C.P.D. was like my second home.
I trained most of the officers there.
They're like my family.
Now I can't help but wonder
who did I leave my kids with?
That's not on you.
I put my badge down,
Kramer picked it up. It's all on me.
It's Kramer.
She wants to meet up.
Joe, no.
She might be baiting you into a trap.
- You can't go.
- I know.
But, babe, I can't help but feel
there's something more to this.
What am I supposed to do?
You are a good man, Joe West.
You forget everything
that's in that folder.
Your heart's always been
your best compass, right?
So trust it.
Trust your heart.
It'll show you what's right.
It was a good try.
But Ultraviolet is never going
to change.
You need to give up before you get
yourself or someone else killed.
I can't just abandon her.
She's my family.
Yeah, I get that.
No, you don't.
You grew up in some mansion
with two loving parents,
but for most of my life,
it was just Esperanza and me.
She's more than just my cousin.
She's the reason I survived
long enough to be here.
I have to save her.
Some people are too far gone to save.
Even if they're your family.
How can you say that?
You fought Black Hole
to save your parents.
That is not the same thing.
Why not?
Why is your family good enough
to save but mine isn't?
Because I didn't save them.
By the time I got my parents
out of Black Hole, it was way too late.
The people that raised me were gone.
Carver put my parents in charge
of all international accounts.
He gave them 10%
as long as they kept
all of Black Hole's overseas assets
hidden from the US government.
Carver bought my parents' loyalty
for billions.
And once they got a taste,
they needed more.
What happened once Carver was gone?
My parents were in too deep.
And worse,
they got used to this lifestyle.
And no matter how hard I tried,
I could not pull them out.
Because they didn't want out.
Which is why you have to pull
with everything you have.
When I first met Team Flash,
it was in handcuffs.
When they first met you,
you were robbing a bank.
We didn't want help, either.
But this team never gave up on us.
So thanks for the reminder.
You want to bail, I understand.
But I'm gonna go find my cousin.
- What the...
- Your tattoo!
It's a yin-yang symbol.
Two sides that make a whole.
Opposite, but the same.
Okay, sorry, look.
I know how to track Ultraviolet.
We couldn't track Ultraviolet's
unique light signature
because there's too much interference
from other light sources in the city.
But you and Ultraviolet
have the same powers.
So if we use you as an input signal,
satellites will search
for its counterpart signal.
Aka the yin to your yang... Ultraviolet.
Just focus your energies here.
Get your shine on.
- It worked.
- What?
- We found her.
- Oh, my arm.
- Sorry.
It's okay. It's okay. I'm okay.
Looks like she's in a run-down warehouse
that's wired for tons of shady tech.
It's got to be Olsen's hideout.
- Okay, we better hurry. Come on.
- No, no.
I almost got you killed once already.
Esperanza's my problem.
I need to do this alone.
Look, I know I can't do the fighting
like you guys,
but I can still help my friends.
You've done more than enough.
- I can't risk...
- Allegra...
I'm not taking no for an answer,
not again.
My favorite patient.
Ha!
You surprised me earlier.
So happy to return the favor.
Dr. Olsen.
Ready to die?
That depends.
Are you ready...
for one last experiment?
Okay, Allegra, I'm set.
Operation "Find your cuz
and convince her to come home" is a go.
Okay.
I'm reading her light signature
in a level below you.
Getting to her is gonna be
the tricky part.
I've got company.
Oh, I got just the thing
for those electro-pulse rifles.
Hold on to your volts.
That is one EMP,
courtesy of...
Chester P.
Okay.
I'm heading down there.
Uh, wait, hold on.
Those guys got backup.
Uh...
Another EMP would be great
right about now.
The mobile unit doesn't have
enough juice for another pulse.
Go find your cousin. I got this.
Don't worry, boys. I'll go slowly.
Esperanza.
You need to come with me now.
We don't have time for any...
She isn't the one
who's run out of time, my dear.
What did you do to her?
I made her into a weapon...
without a voice.
And these hands are the only ones
that can return what was taken.
So, we made a deal.
I'll give your cousin her voice back...
if she kills everyone who knows
the true nature of my work.
You and your team.
Sue, Allegra needs backup.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
Lights out, boys.
He's lying to you, prima. Listen to me.
I'm your family. We're blood.
Blood is a liquid easily spilled.
Power is eternal...
and money provides it.
So now that Joseph Carver is dead,
I work for the highest bidder,
and I don't plan on
going out of business anytime soon.
End her, and get your voice back.
Please... Please, don't...
Don't do this.
Fighting back is useless, child.
You'll never be stronger than her.
Hate fuels your light power.
Not for me.
Yes!
You okay?
We're good.
Is she gonna be okay?
She'll be fine.
She's just resting.
And if anyone can recover from a massive
dose of light-based energy, it's her.
About the whole supernova thing
I did back there...
- is that gonna happen again?
- Maybe.
It's common for meta-powers
to reach new heights
during times of extreme stress.
You just leveled up, Allegra.
You did well out there, you know.
Not sure the boss would agree.
I organized a rogue mission
while Barry was gone.
I almost got Sue and Chuck killed.
But you followed your heart.
And that's what Barry would have done.
And Dr. Olsen's in jail now, too.
And...
there's this.
Hey.
So, uh, Caitlin ran some tests.
She says you're gonna be okay.
Sorry I had to... You know.
How did you... do that?
I don't know.
Dr. Olsen said our powers
are fueled by hate, but...
I thought about something else.
Family.
After everything I've done...
you still call me that?
Always.
What they did to you
isn't who you are, Esperanza.
You're more than that. You know that.
And I do, too.
There's something else.
We recovered these from Dr. Olsen.
They're the files on what he did to you.
Point is,
Caitlin thinks she can use them.
To do what?
Cure you... permanently.
Thanks for meeting me so late.
After how I behaved,
I wasn't sure you would.
I'm sure you had a reason.
Like... probably the same reason
you had me meet here.
Well, figured I did enough damage
to C.C.P.D. morale for one day.
Look, West.
Earlier today, I was... unprofessional.
And you were right to be suspicious.
I mean, all the evidence looks that way.
But that's not the whole story, is it?
The soldier
who betrayed your unit.
His name is Adam Creyke.
He's also my brother.
Not by blood.
But some bonds run deeper.
As two Native kids
growing up off the rez,
we weren't exactly popular
in our community.
But we were still a part of it, so...
we kept in touch in our own way.
But that's how Adam and I bonded.
We didn't have a lot of support...
but at least we had each other.
Anyway, you were right about us arguing
the night before about the mission.
But I didn't know
that he had sold out our unit.
Adam was trying to convince me
not to go on the mission.
Said he had a bad feeling about it.
Mmm.
He was trying to protect you,
and you blame yourself
for not realizing.
I was in charge of those lives.
It was my job
to get them home to their families.
A dozen dinner tables
have empty chairs right now
because I didn't see the clues.
I was too blind and stupid.
Believing in somebody you love
is nothing to be ashamed of.
Take it.
Maybe someday you'll trust
someone enough to share it.
Why do you think I asked you here?
I've been looking for Adam
for six years on my own.
Help me catch him.
All right.
So where are you headed
to next? Some exotic locale?
Actually, I'm thinking about
sticking around.
Maybe even talking to my parents.
Yeah.
I guess you could say
I'm finally seeing the light.
Ciao for now.
Well, I guess we officially survived
our unsurvivable mission.
Barely.
Thanks for having my back, Chuck.
I literally couldn't have
done this without you.
It was nothing.
But we do make a pretty good team.
Hey, do you want to get
a coffee or something?
- Anywhere but Jitters.
- Yeah.
I'd love to, but I kind of set up
a D&D game for tonight.
So, another time?
Sure.
Or maybe I could join you.
For real? Like, you'd like to...
Uh-huh.
- With me?
- Yeah.
- Is that a problem?
- No, no, no.
It's amazing.
Just unexpected.
But in a great way, I mean.
It's... Am I making this weird?
Yeah. No. I don't know.
- It's just a game.
- Exactly.
Yeah, with coffee.
- Whole lot of coffee.
- Yeah. Lead the way.
Hey!
- Oh-ho! Looking refreshed, man.
- Thanks.
Yeah. How was your trip?
Amazing. It was great.
Iris and I...
Uh.
Iris and I are thinking about getting
a time share, actually.
What happened today?
Erm...
- Nothing.
Oh!
Snowflake.
It's great to see you.
Of course,
while I love a show of force
as much as the next guy...
I gave you my cell.
You do know there's a difference between
reaching out and, like, punching, right?
Shut up.
When Norvok told me you broke out
of Iron Heights, I couldn't believe it.
And yet, here we are.
Come on. I'm taking you back... again.
Mmm-mmm.
Looks like somebody
hasn't heard the news.
Ta-da! I cut a deal.
My record is expunged.
Now I'm just like you.
One of the good guys.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::