My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother
killed by something impossible.
My father went to
prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my
mother and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
You're him, the Reverse-Flash.
I am Eobard Thawne...
and the Flash's speed...
is the key to my
returning to my time.
I've been teamed up with
Mason Bridge, who is a legend.
You're the guy who thinks
Wells is a mad genius.
What do you know about him?
I think that maybe you
were right about Dr. Wells.
- Which part?
- All of it.
AmericasCardroom.com brings poker back
Million Dollar Sunday Tournament every Sunday
Come on.
Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
'MOTH! Morn! Barry!
- Stay back!
- Mom!
This is everything that we know
about Harrison Wells...
which is actually not a lot.
Didn't you read
a book about him?
Six hundred pages and the big
takeaway is he's enigmatic.
Your mom was killed
by a Speedster.
Wells' machine turned you
into a speedster.
That's way too many coincidences
for this old cop.
Do you think that he wanted me
to become the Flash?
Everything he's done...
since that night
you got struck by lightning:
bringing you to S.T.A.R. Labs,
giving you the suit...
training you.
It's all been to keep you safe.
And to make me faster.
Wells once said that he needed
more speed from me.
Why?
I don't know.
He wants something
from you, Barry.
We just need to
figure out what it is.
Let's go get him,
let's get some answers.
We can't do that now
as much as we might want to.
Joe, you had your suspicions about
Wells from the very beginning.
You thought that he might be
the man in yellow.
Except the blood from your house
didn't match him.
All right, so maybe he's not
the Reverse-Flash.
You think he knows
what happened.
He may have the key
to getting my dad out of prison.
Whatever Wells wants from you...
it started 15 years ago.
He's been patient.
Scary patient.
You gotta listen to me on this.
We have to be...
just as patient.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Wow. Look.
Wow.
Henry?
Henry!
Henry.
Nice name.
Tricked you. Ha, ha.
Look who's back.
My tricks.
My treat.
But I'll give you
something good...
to eat.
Today's special:
A city in ashes.
The Trickster proudly
welcomes you all...
to the new...
disorder.
Talking in the third person.
That's never a good sign.
- You're mad because he named himself.
- Actually, he didn't.
Twenty years ago, Central City was
hit by a series of terrorist attacks.
One man killed at least
10 civilians, two cops.
That guy called
himself the Trickster.
Whoa. Someone was
rocking the unitard.
James Jesse?
Like Jesse James,
only more twisted.
Where is this Mr. Jesse now?
He's serving several life
sentences at Iron Heights.
He was the most dangerous thing
Central City had ever seen.
You mean until the particle
accelerator blew up.
- Um...
- Barry and I...
will go see this James Jesse
at Iron Heights.
See if he can give us something
that can help us catch his groupie.
I'll analyze the video and see
if I can figure out the source.
Hey, Joe.
Barry doing all right?
He seems cranky.
Even the Flash wakes up on the
wrong side of the bed some mornings.
He's fine.
Mom!
Nora, hold on!
Run, Barry. Run!
Gideon, what's happening to me?
Your latest time jump against the Flash
caused a massive drain on your powers.
Your cells contain no trace
of the Speed Force.
- That's impossible.
- Your ability to move at super-speed...
as well as travel in time
has been completely depleted.
How am I supposed to get back?
You can't.
I've never seen this part
of the prison before.
I had to have this cell specially built
for James Jesse about five years ago.
- Why's that?
- A criminal psychologist set up...
weekly visits with him.
James talked the shrink
into committing suicide.
Oh. You're gonna need these.
Okay.
Gentlemen.
Please, be seated.
I'm Detective Joe West.
This is Barry Allen.
Uh, we'd like to ask
you a few questions.
Mm...
I can smell them in your pocket.
Yesterday, hundreds
of these parachute bombs...
were released
throughout Central City.
Huh.Funidea.
But not an effective
delivery system.
How many died?
No one. Luckily.
You know, when I was free
and at my height...
a day without
casualties was like...
Well, like the Cubs
winning the pennant.
It just never happened.
The explosives I found
in the parachute bombs...
had the same explosive composition
as the bombs you set off...
20 years ago.
That's impossible.
I never told anyone
that formula.
The signatures are
an exact match.
He called himself the
Trickster too, just like you.
He is nothing like me,
detective. Nothing.
Do you know...
who he is?
Oh...
If I did...
I would tell you.
So you could find him...
cut off his head,
and throw it right in his face.
No, this is
obviously the work...
of a rank amateur at best.
A mere pretender
angling for my throne.
I hear you.
So...
Help us catch him.
Prove there's only
one Trickster.
Trying to trick the
Trickster, Joseph, hmm?
No.
There's only one way...
this could happen.
Whoever he is...
he must have found my lair.
I ask only one thing.
When you find this...
shtick stealer,
this gimmick grabber...
this pathetic,
wannabe fake...
make sure...
your safety's off.
Something's happened
to Mason Bridge.
No one has seen
or heard from him.
He's a journalist, Iris.
Maybe he's on a story.
Then why hasn't he answered
his phone or his e-mails?
Maybe he stumbled on the
wrong story and is laying low.
You don't know him like I do.
When Mason's on a story,
nothing is getting in his way.
I mean, he considers threats
minor annoyances.
Maybe he's on a bender, or he met a
girl worth disappearing for a week over.
He said something weird
was going on at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Eddie, something has happened to
him. Something bad, I can feel it.
Please.
Captain Singh has everyone on
the Central City park bomber...
but as soon as I can, I'll
look into Bridge. I promise.
Okay.
This looks like nobody has
been here since the '90s.
Yeah, look at this thing.
You think Jesse doesn't know
who this new Trickster guy is?
He seemed pretty ticked off...
that someone was besmirching
his bad name.
Joe.
Let's see what he's
got stashed in there.
Yeah.
- Damn.
- You good?
The copycat.
He took everything.
- Hey, can we have a second?
- Yeah, sure.
Dad.
_H€Y- Barf)'-
H9)'-
What are you doing here?
Uh, Joe and I have some questions
for an inmate about a bombing case.
Dad, listen.
I'm close.
The man who put you in here,
I'm getting close.
- Closer than I've ever been.
- Barry.
- We have talked about this.
- I know.
And I'm done talking.
You're not gonna pay
for another man's crime anymore.
Just hang in there, okay?
Joe.
- What's he talking about? - Like
he said, Henry, just hang in there.
What, no candy, fellas?
That storage space you sent
us to was booby-trapped.
You can never be too careful
with your private things.
You were protecting nothing.
Your secret stash was empty.
What do you mean?
No firearms, none of
your explosives, nothing.
Whatever you had in there,
it was stolen. All of it.
No.
He's stealing my legacy.
Whoever this is...
you need to find him.
I will not let this, this...
- Trickster?
- That is my name, mine.
What was in that room?
What were you keeping there?
A bomb.
A really big bomb.
HOW big?
Bye-bye, Central City.
- Cisco?
- Yo.
This Trickster guy just posted a vlog, you
gotta see this. I'm sending you the link.
Okay.
Denizens of Central City.
Or those of you who remain.
Welcome to Boom Day, ha-ha-ha.
I'm very proud to report that my
first trick was an exploding success.
- Show him.
- But I think you all deserve...
something much, uh...
bigger. No, no, no.
So for my next trick...
Take off my mask, you fraud.
Keep your eyes
glued to this website.
Pretender. Sham.
What The Trickster
has planned for you all...
- Take off my mask.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
Take off my mask!
This was posted a few hours ago.
Whoever this Trickster is...
he's certainly not shy.
Not every criminal likes
to hide in the dark.
Cisco, can you trace
where the video was posted from?
I tried.
But this guy is using some crazy,
Felicity-caliber scrambler...
like I've never seen.
The origin of the uploads coming
from hundreds of locations.
Until he uploads another video,
it's gonna be tough.
He has the capability
to destroy the city.
Hey, I said tough,
not impossible.
Barry, we'll catch
him. We always do.
Mr. Allen.
A word, please.
I know what's going on with you.
I know what you're thinking.
Do you?
I know going to Iron Heights
and conversing with Mr. Jesse...
has brought about feelings of
your father. How could it not?
Yeah, no, it's, uh...
It's been...
really tough knowing
that my mom's killer...
is still out there.
Of course.
But We'll find him.
Together. You have my word.
Thank you.
But for now...
how about we focus on finding this
Trickster before anybody else gets hurt?
I have to go.
But thanks for the pep talk.
I'm always here for you.
A team of research laboratories
unconnected to the government...
unconnected to any business
interests, or any of that stuff.
We build right downtown
in the heart of the city...
in the epicenter,
and we become...
the heart of the city. We
become the heart of the nation.
We change what you think
about the sciences and then...
What?
Just that my father
would've loved you...
as much as I do.
Well, I Wish...
I could've met him.
Oh.
- What would you call these
laboratories? - Well, we, Tess Morgan...
would call them
the Technological Engineering...
Scientific Studies...
or T.E.S.S. for short.
Well, that is very...
very sweet, but how about:
Scientific and Technological...
Advanced Research
Laboratories...
or...
S.T.A.R. Labs for short?
Because...
in the vast night sky...
you, Harrison Wells...
are the only star I see.
That's gonna get you kissed.
You're a full-time reporter now.
Why are we meeting here?
I still have a key.
And this is...
kind of our place, right?
What's up?
My co-worker, Mason
Bridge, is missing.
He's not at home,
he's not answering his phone.
I mean, it's not like him.
I'm really worried
that something bad has happened.
I'm sure he's fine.
That's what Eddie says,
that's what everyone is saying.
Please, will you look into it?
For me?
For you.
Thanks.
Um...
Are you okay?
You seem like you have...
a heavy heart.
Sometimes I'm not sure
why I wear a mask with you.
Well, maybe one day
you'll take it off.
Heads up, Trickstefls
broadcasting again.
Can I borrow your laptop?
Um...
Sure, help...
Help yourself.
Get ready for the
games to begin!
I have...
a bomb.
It's a big bomb.
It will make a big bang...
and then a big hole,
and then a big drop...
in the population.
But never say...
the Trickster...
is not fair.
The bomb is somewhere...
between 52nd Street...
and Avenue B.
I want all units, every uniform, every
detective searching that area now.
Somehow, we need
to alert the Flash.
Something tells me
he already knows.
Guys, I can't find it.
- I need your help. - There's
nothing on traffic cams or CCTV.
I retasked S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite to
scan the area for incendiary devices.
Bomb that large should be
giving off a thermal signature.
Then why can't you find it?
Because it's a trick.
The bomb's not there.
It has to be. I'm
gonna keep looking.
That is what he wants, you and the
police to keep running around in circles.
There is something else going
on. I can feel it. Trust me.
I'm gonna keep looking.
- Barry.
- Why doesn't he just listen to you?
I found it.
Uh-oh. There's an
explosion at Iron Heights.
- This was all a diversion.
- The prison was the real target.
James Jesse.
I guess he's tricked us all.
Joe. There's no
bomb in the city.
It was a diversion so the Trickster
could help James Jesse escape.
I know, we just got surveillance
footage from Iron Heights.
Jesse got away.
Barry, look, they
took a hostage.
Well, who'd he take?
A guard? The warden?
No, your dad.
You have to admit.
That was one hell of a trick.
I cannot believe
we're finally in the same room.
I mean, you're my hero.
You need a better
role model, kid.
Can't you see? He's
just using you.
Why did we bring him along?
Huh?
Because his son works
for the C.C.P.D.
Should we find
ourselves in a jam...
a cop's dad makes
an excellent bargaining chip.
Right.
I wouldn't worry too much about
what the cops might do to you.
- Really? - If the police aren't
able to find you, trust me...
the Flash will.
Here's hoping.
So, what's next?
In your last letter, you said
you had something big in mind.
I've had 20 years to come up
with the perfect trick.
It's going to be...
my masterpiece.
My Mona Lisa...
my Breaking Bad season five.
They gave me cable in prison
so I'd stop killing the guards.
Right.
There's just one thing
I've been dying to ask.
Why did you choose me?
Because...
I knew you had the strength
to fulfill my legacy.
Besides...
it was in your blood.
What do you mean, in my blood?
The real reason I
tracked you down...
and groomed you to be...
the best you could
possibly be, Axel:
I...
am your father.
Really?
We were able to identify
the other Trickster.
His name's Axel Walker, age 25.
Him and James have been corresponding
through snail mail for over a decade.
I should've been there.
- We're gonna find your dad, okay?
- Definitely.
I guess I should've
listened to you.
- Sorry, I am so tired.
- Hmm.
I think I'm just gonna put on my pajamas,
go straight to bed when we get home.
- Really?
- No.
Definitely not wearing pajamas.
Hello.
No, no, no, Tess.
Tess, Tess.
Hello, hold on.
Oh, oh, thank God.
Help me, please, help me.
She's... She's... Help...
What are you doing? What are
you doing? Help. Call someone.
- Call someone. Can't you see? She's dying.
- This woman has been dead for centuries.
Help!
You okay?
Do you think my
dad is still alive?
Yes, yes, he is. Of course.
Jesse only took your pop
to use as leverage.
He might be crazy,
but he's not stupid.
And everyone upstairs
is looking to find him.
So...
now I'm supposed to just leave my
dad's fate in the hands of a man...
who may have had something
to do with my mom's murder.
- Joe, I can't do this.
- Yes, you can.
This doesn't make any sense. I
mean, if Wells is a murderer...
why does he wanna help me?
Why has he helped me stop so
many criminals, or saved Ronnie?
Why didn't I See this?
I spent a tenth as much time
with him as you did.
He almost had me
believing in him.
Almost.
Look.
Whatever else he is...
he is Harrison Wells.
You love science, he is science. It's
like you made best friends with Einstein.
You're saying I
wanted to be tricked.
You always wanna be the person
who sees the best in people.
I've been a cop for 25 years.
All I can see...
is the flaws, the lies.
The dark thoughts
that people think I don't see.
I wish I could be you.
As fast as you are...
that is your real power.
Don't let Wells
take that from you.
I don't know...
why he's helping us.
All that matters...
is that he is.
- I can't lose my dad, Joe.
- Barr.
Barr.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Hi. Iris West, I'm with
Central City Picture News.
Thanks.
- Champagne, miss?
- Ah, thank you. Heh.
We're almost out of champagne.
Then the fun's about to begin.
Oh, Mayor Bellows.
- Hi. This is a lovely party.
- Thank you.
Welcome, welcome,
Central City's finest.
How about a toast?
To Mayor Anthony Bellows.
He doesn't just
yell at his staff...
he bellows.
You see what I did there
with the word play and the...?
- Tough crowd.
- Excuse me.
Who are you?
How quickly they forget.
James Jesse, your honor.
A.K.A., ha-ha-ha, the Trickster.
And I'm here to relieve
you fine people...
from all your money.
Because we know...
if you're in this
room, oh, ha, ha...
you've got loads of it.
What makes you think that anyone
would give you a cent?
Because...
that champagne they just slurped
down like so much fruit punch?
I added a little
something special to it.
Trimethylmercury-32.
Poison.
Without the antidote, you'll begin to
feel the effects in about, oh, um...
- One hour.
I remember you.
You got to the party
about an hour early.
I offered you the very
first glass of champagne.
An hour is plenty of time for all
of you to call your bankers...
and transfer everything you
have to the account number...
on the bottom of your glass.
Once my young friend
and I are rich...
you'll get the antidote.
If any of you decide
to call 911 instead, well...
then we switch
to lead poisoning.
- Anything?
- I'm scanning traffic cams.
- I got nothing.
- Hey, baby.
Iris?
How many of you feel the trimethylene-32
coursing through your veins?
- That's him, that's Jesse.
- Can you ping her phone?
I'm on it.
Trimethylmercury-32 is a
relatively fast-acting poison.
- Is there a cure?
- Yes. We can synthesize the antidote.
Cisco, where is she?
- City Hall.
- The mayor's having a fundraiser.
Barry, do not underestimate
the Trickster.
Well, hello.
You know, ahem...
I've been in
prison for 20 years.
Then you'll know the routine
when you get sent back.
Where's Henry Allen?
He's where you'll
be soon. Heaven.
Are you familiar
with the movie Speed?
Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock?
You're the bus and
that's the bomb.
Kinetic bomb, actually. If you
go below 600 miles per hour...
it'll explode.
Same thing happens
if you try to remove it.
Ooh! It's active, run, run, run.
Cisco.
He wasn't lying. That thing's
linked to a speedometer.
It will blow if you stop moving.
I can't run forever.
There's gotta be a way to get
it off him without damaging it.
- Barry, do you see any walls nearby?
- Why?
Because I need you to run into one.
Or more accurately, through one.
What?
If you vibrate at the
natural frequency of air...
your body, your cells, will
be in a state of excitement...
that should allow
you to phase...
right through that wall.
Leaving the bomb on the other side.
- Should?
- You can do this, I believe in you.
- I can't.
- Listen to me, Barry. Breathe.
Breathe.
Feel the air.
Feel that wind on your face.
Feel the ground.
Your feet lifting you up, pushing
you forward, and the lightning.
Barf)'-
Feel the lightning.
Feel its power.
Its electricity pumping
through your veins.
Crackling through you...
traveling to every nerve
in your body like a shock.
You're no longer you now.
You're part of
something greater.
You're part of a Speed Force.
It's yours.
Now do it.
- How?
- Barry?
Oh! That felt Weird.
I'm good.
Ooh, I like it.
Look at that.
Lobsters on me, kid.
It's okay, you've all been given
an antidote.
That wasn't very sanitary.
Where's Henry Allen? You're going
to prison either way, James.
All right.
You always did look good in red.
Wow.
Half of this stuff didn't even
exist when I was practicing.
I'd be happy to give you a crash
course on all of it if you get out.
I'm gonna shut up now.
That's okay.
Dr. Allen?
- Yes? - I'm feeling
the need to give you a hug.
Absolutely, I will
always accept a hug.
Thank you.
You gotta tell me:
What does it feel like when you're running
down the street like a bat out of hell?
There's no feeling like it.
I bet.
Actually, you're all heroes in my
book. Especially you, Dr. Wells.
Thank you. For everything
that you've done for my son.
Well, your son is an
extraordinary man, Dr. Allen.
I will do everything in my power
to ensure Barry's future.
It's time, Joe.
- No.
- No?
- Okay.
It seemed like you
could use a hug too.
Your father's an
extraordinary man.
You're lucky to have him.
I'm lucky to have you too.
Who are you?
My name is Eobard Thawne.
But that name doesn't matter, not
anymore. It won't matter for many years.
The only thing that really matters
is who you are. Harrison Wells.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
In 2020, you and your
wife, Tess Morgan...
successfully launched a particle
accelerator that changed history.
I need it to happen a bit sooner
if I'm going to get back.
Much sooner.
What is that?
My way home.
You see...
they're not
coming to save you.
They're coming to save me.
Hi, Joe.
- Desk sergeant said you're
looking for me. - Hey, yeah, um...
Sit down.
It's about Iris.
She's looking into Mason
Bridge's disappearance.
We can't let that happen.
Detective.
Eddie, we need your help.
Brazil?
Why would...
Mason move to Brazil?
Apparently there
was a girl involved.
And he decided to go hike the
Amazon with her for a year.
You know, live off the grid,
write his memoirs or something.
Wow, I guess you really
don't know anyone.
- No, you don't.
- Hey, baby. Everything good?
Yeah, yeah, of course. Um...
- Dinner will be ready in a jiff, okay?
- Okay.
She buy it?
I think so.
Keeping her in the dark,
it's for her safety.
That is debatable
and we will have that debate.
But for right now,
what's our next move?
How do we figure out
what Wells is up to?
When Wells was talking
me through phasing...
so I could get the
Trickster's bomb off my wrist...
the way that he described
my being the Flash running...
feeling the wind...
and the power...
it's like he was
talking from experience.
What are you saying?
I don't know how...
but he's the man in yellow.
Harrison Wells is
the Reverse-Flash.
I got an 11-80,
possible 10-54...
County Road J,
requesting immediate assistance.
Copy that, units en
route to your location.
Sir, we're gonna
get you out of here.
Can you tell me your name?
Do you know who you are?
My name...
is...
Harrison Wells.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3prab
Help other users to choose the best subtitles