My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
That's Barry's old house.
- It's been too long. Everything's different.
- Except that mirror.
This mirror might contain
photographs of what happened that night.
That blood belongs
to one of the speedsters that was here.
It's Barry's. As an adult.
- Mrs. Stein, have you seen this person?
- Yes.
He's not Ronnie anymore.
He's Martin Stein walking around
in Ronnie's body.
Any attempt we make to separate
the two of them could be catastrophic.
A nuclear explosion.
Barry.
Barry, what happened out there?
Are you guys okay?
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
I think so.
Oh, God. The nuclear explosion.
There's no telling how much radiation
we were exposed to.
Wait, wait. This can't be. The Geiger counter in
the suit, it's reading less than one millirad.
- But that's normal.
- There's no radiation.
Let's go.
Did it work?
- Did you separate them?
- I don't know.
Ronnie?
Tell me your name.
Ronnie Raymond.
Cait.
It's me.
Uh, pardon me.
Obviously, I need a change of clothes.
Nice to see you in the flesh again,
Professor Stein.
We're coming home.
All of us.
- Ronnie Raymond. Heh.
- Cisco. Heh.
Oh. Ha-ha-ha.
I missed you so much, man.
- I shouldn't have locked you in there.
- Hey. Don't.
Welcome back, Mr. Raymond.
Dr. Wells.
Caitlin told me what happened to you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm responsible for putting myself
in this chair.
You are responsible for my
still being alive. Thank you.
You said you'd bring him back and you did.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Uh, excuse me.
Are we all planning to sing
"Kumbaya" next?
Professor Stein, I presume.
Harrison Wells.
Do you have somewhere I can freshen up
and get a change of clothes?
Of course.
Right this way, professor.
- General, are you getting this?
- Roger that, sergeant.
Sir, look at this.
Two imprints of impact.
Two imprints.
Two different people.
It's Firestorm. He's separated.
Your vitals appear to be normal...
except you have a slight fever of 100.6.
- Cait, I'm fine. I promise.
- I know, but we just need to be...
Shh.
Yup. Just when I forgot how awkward it was
to walk in on you two.
You can get used to it again.
I did a full medical workup
on the professor.
It turns out that now that
he and Ronnie are separated...
they no longer possess the ability
to harness nuclear energy.
Professor Stein, you seem to be running
a little hot as well.
Same as Ronnie, 100.6.
Hardly a sweat, Dr. Snow.
And hopefully now the only thing...
- Ronald and I have in common...
- It's Ronnie.
- Mm.
- Hey. You're gonna miss being able to fly?
- Yeah, if I was the one holding the controller.
- Meaning?
Meaning you weren't
the most conscientious body-mate.
So you do not consider keeping you alive
to be conscientious?
Alive? We were living under a bridge
eating garbage.
I didn't determine it'd be my mind
that would dominate our existence...
but thank God it was.
I could feel your fear and panic, emotions
that would have gotten us killed in that state.
You kept me buried down.
You kept me from her.
Which is likely why she's still alive.
I believe you and I have spent
quite enough time together.
- Yeah.
- I would like to go see my wife.
- Mr. Allen will take you.
- Thank you.
I need some pizza.
You got it.
I can't believe it. Uh, wait.
Uh...
What should I say?
I don't think
you're gonna have to say anything.
Clarissa.
I'm so sorry I put you through this.
Thank you.
Mr...
- Barry.
- Yeah.
Barry, I know I can be difficult...
but thank you for bringing me home.
I'll see you soon, professor.
- Seeing what could only be described...
- Hey.
- I left you three messages.
- I know. I'm sorry.
About the lack of communication
or that hole out in the badlands?
We're all fine. Thanks.
I wasn't calling about the explosion.
- I have to show you something.
- What?
It's smaller than I remember.
Yeah, it's because you're bigger.
- Have you been in here? I mean, recently?
- No.
I haven't been in this
house since that night.
Bar.
This mirror. Do you remember it?
Yeah. It belonged to my grandma.
How is it still here?
Just be glad it is.
Look...
I don't fully know
how Cisco did it, but...
Did what?
Joe, what are we doing here?
Mom.
You can definitely see two very fast people
fighting around your mother.
Two speedsters.
You see that?
The blood?
Cisco and I had the DNA tested.
It's yours.
No, it's not. That's impossible.
I wasn't even downstairs yet.
No, Barry, not that you. This you.
Cisco had the samples analyzed...
and the proteins in the blood
were that of an adult...
not a child.
But that means...
The speedster trying to stop
the man in yellow...
Is the Flash.
That's me.
Time travel.
If the last five months have proven
anything, it's that anything can exist.
But to actually travel through time?
Well, the greatest
minds in human history...
put their collective genius towards
solving that puzzle.
So is it possible?
Yes, it's possible.
But problematic. I mean...
assuming you could create the conditions
necessary to take that journey...
that journey would be fraught
with potential pitfalls.
Novikov principle of self-consistency
for example...
Wait, the what now?
If you travel back in time
to change something...
then you end up being
the causal factor of that event.
- Like Terminator.
- Ah.
Or is time plastic? Is it mutable...
whereby any changes to the continuum
could create an alternate timeline?
- Back to the Future.
- Oh.
- I saw that one too.
- "Doc Brown." Tremendous picture.
Right. So, what's the answer?
I might be a clever guy, but if you're
asking me to give you a theory...
on how to travel through time,
I'm afraid I just can't do that.
There is someone else
you can talk to about this.
Danish?
Why do you have a blueprint
of the S.T.A.R. Labs' particle accelerator?
- Do you know anything about physics?
- Not a thing. Might as well be in Dothraki.
So, what more is there
with the S.T.A.R. Labs story?
The only new information is Wells admitted
he was warned of a potential disaster.
Yeah.
Why do you think he did that?
Because he's a good person?
- Is he?
- Yes.
He saved my friend's life.
He was struck by lightning
and Dr. Wells and his team kept him alive.
So your friend wouldn't need saving if
Wells hadn't zapped him in the first place.
- It was an accident.
- What if it wasn't?
So you think Harrison Wells wanted
the particle accelerator to explode?
- Why would he do that?
- Don't know what goes on in that building.
But I think you know some people who do.
I'm gonna investigate my friends
because you got me a Danish?
I think that you'll do it...
because you really wanna know
what goes on inside that building.
Barry.
Mrs. Stein, I'm sorry to bother you here
but is Professor Stein here right now?
Well, after a year apart,
I'm not letting him out of my sight.
S.T.A.R. Labs did quite a
few tests on Martin, didn't they?
And they said he was fine?
Yeah. Why? Something wrong?
- He just seems a little different, is all.
- Different how?
He's been asking for pizza.
Martin despises pizza.
Is that the delivery man? Oh, Mr. Allen.
I suppose it's too much to hope
you moonlight as a pizza boy.
I am famished.
Okay.
- Aah!
- Oh.
Bravo.
Please, come in...
Mr. Allen.
Uh, oh. Ahem.
What can I do for you?
I needed to talk to you about a paper
that you wrote 25 years ago...
for the Oxford University Press?
I have written many papers for that
publication. Could you be more specific?
Time travel.
These are just a few of the random thoughts
I've had on the subject.
A few?
See, I believe that space-time...
is a free-flowing highway
that intersects the physical world.
We live in the moments
between the on and off ramps.
Theoretically, to travel through time...
one merely needs to find a way
onto the highway.
Okay. So you're saying that this is actually
possible, to travel into the future?
Undoubtedly.
What about the past?
Yes.
My own personal choice
would be the Chicago World's Fair, 1893.
I think Nikola Tesla and I,
we'd have some wonderful arguments.
What about you? Would you be interested
in taking a trip into history?
I think that I already have.
Professor, um...
15 years ago, my mom was murdered...
and we recently discovered
some evidence that...
I was there that night,
and not just as a kid...
but as an adult.
That must be a side effect
of your incredible speed.
In some future date,
you actually move so fast...
that the resulting
kinetic energy buildup...
smashes a hole
in the space-time continuum.
Ha! Ha, ha.
You seem disappointed by the prospect.
I mean, if I do...
somehow make it back there
to that night, then...
it means that I didn't save her.
My destiny is to fail.
The boomerang goes flying through
the Cortex, smashing everything...
and Cisco's all,
"My bad. This one's on me."
Ha, ha. Sounds like you had
some crazy times.
Yeah, we have.
- Are you ready for life to get back to normal?
- What do you mean?
I was thinking we could leave town...
start fresh somewhere.
Our lives are here, my job is here.
Yeah, hunting metahumans.
There's more to it than that.
And it's dangerous.
It can be.
Look, I stayed at S.T.A.R. Labs
because I believed in Dr. Wells...
but ever since Barry became the Flash...
and we've been working
to keep the city safe...
I found a new way to help people.
Look, Cait, I'm not mad at anyone.
Okay, I know the accelerator explosion
was an accident...
but that building took a year of our
lives, I don't want it to take any more.
Do you guys need anything else?
- We're about to close up.
- I'm good.
Babe?
Ronnie, get down.
Get out of here.
- No, not without you.
- I'm right behind you. Go.
- Professor.
- Martin.
- What's wrong?
- I don't know.
I feel terrified. My heart is racing.
Ugh!
Hands in the air.
I think... I think Ronald is in trouble.
How could you know that?
Jitters. He needs help. Go.
Ronald Raymond.
The burning man himself.
Half of him, anyway.
- Who are you?
- General Wade Eiling, United States Army.
- What do you want?
- Firestorm.
It stings, doesn't it?
Ha, ha.
Had that one developed especially for you.
Micro fragments
attracted to kinetic energy.
Firestorm was tonight's main objective,
but getting you, that's just gravy.
- Unh!
- Get in.
Gentlemen, we are at war.
Hurry. Barry's wounds are starting to heal
with fragments under his skin.
It's just like that time
I stepped on a sea urchin.
Only much worse.
- Ugh! Just don't pee on me.
- You know that's a myth, right?
I'm so stupid.
Jason Rusch, who is helping Professor Stein
with his Firestorm research...
he said that the Army took all of
Stein's material when he disappeared.
- I should have known it was General Eiling.
- Not your fault.
He thinks you hold the keys
to the ultimate human weapon, both of you.
Okay. Let's finish this. I gotta get to
Stein's house, Eiling's gonna be after him too.
- Stein's fine.
- How do you know?
He's right there.
I don't think Mr. Raymond and I
are as distinctive as we had hoped.
I'm still inside Ronald.
There has to be a
better way to phrase that.
Beta, alpha, theta, delta.
All your brain waves are perfectly in sync.
The chances of that happening
are next to impossible.
Impossible is just another Tuesday,
remember?
Yeah, but this is like
some Twilight Zone level stuff...
and I know we have a guy
locked up in our basement...
who can turn himself into poison gas.
- Wait, really?
- Dude, that was like week three.
Look, if this Eiling is as dangerous
as you say, then I need to warn Clarissa.
I promise, I can get Clarissa out of the
city in time, but we need you to stay here.
Professor, I need you to trust us.
Very well.
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's just not the
S.T.A.R. Labs I knew.
Ronnie, this isn't the world that you knew.
Tell me about it.
All right, here we are. Uh...
All right. You guys can stay down in
Iris' old room, it's kind of small, but...
Hey.
- We have guests?
- Yeah, we do. I hope that's okay.
- Mi casa.
- This is Ronnie.
Nice to meet you.
Ronnie? The...?
- Dead fiancé.
- Right.
- Beer?
- Thanks.
Dad? Barry?
- Iris, hi.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Uh, it's Tuesday.
I was gonna make us dinner, remember?
- Yup.
- Yeah.
- Here, I'll help you. Got it.
- I knew you'd forget.
There's plenty for everyone.
Caitlin, what brings you by?
There is a gas leak in my apartment,
so Barry said that we could stay here.
Oh, that's sweet of him.
And, uh, who's this?
This is, uh...
- Her cousin.
- Sam.
Visiting from Coast City.
You look really familiar, Sam.
Yeah, I have one of those faces.
So, what's for dinner?
- Harrison.
- Wade.
I had a feeling you'd be wheeling by.
Tell me.
Are they still pulling needles
out of Barry Allen's hide?
Hmm.
I guess your sweet little Flash didn't want
Sergeant Sans Souci to die...
looking into a mask.
Ugh!
I'm sorry. I didn't see him.
I don't know how Firestorm works.
Well, you may not know the how...
but you know the who.
Both of them.
Thanks to you, it's the dawn of a new age,
Harrison.
The Cold War, the War On Terror...
they'll seem like cavemen fighting with
sticks once those two freaks bind together.
Well, you know where to find me
when you come to the right decision.
And I know you will.
Because, after all,
you're the smartest guy I know.
Barr.
Should I have not shown you?
No, I had to know.
We have been through so much.
You have, all your life.
And you've been...
So strong.
But I...
am still your guardian.
And it's my job to guard you
not just physically...
but from heartache.
I can't help but feel like
I just handed you a brand-new burden.
Yeah.
But it's our burden. Right?
- Hey, can I ask you something?
- Mm-hm.
How did you know that the blood
in the house belonged to me?
You would have had
to have tested it specifically.
Cisco tested it against everyone
who worked at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You wanted to know if it belonged to Wells?
Joe...
Dr. Wells had nothing to do
with my mom's murder.
You believe that now?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Cheers.
- Delicious.
- Mm.
This is, uh, quite an impressive facility.
Well, it was.
Now it's just a shell, I'm afraid.
It must have been devastating seeing...
your life's work fall to pieces
before your eyes.
It was, and yet...
it was the exact same moment
your life's work came to fruition.
Ah, my life's work?
If living the last 14 months
as a conjoined metahuman...
has taught me anything,
it's that my life's work...
should have been being the best husband
I could to my wife.
Are you all right, Martin?
Heh.
I apologize.
It's just...
I feel a little light-headed.
- Are you okay?
- Um...
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just got a little dizzy for a second.
You want the secret to Firestorm.
He has it.
You see, Harrison?
We do work well together.
Oh, hey. You said you knew some of the
leftover scientists at the S.T.A.R. Lab.
- What about a Caitlin Snow, MD? Know her?
- Yeah, I know her. Why?
There was an incident in a
local coffee shop. She was there.
That's Jitters, I used to work there.
Is there anything you can't do?
Witnesses saw soldiers
shooting the place up.
So I contacted the Army's
media relations division and asked:
"Are soldiers permitted to operate like
that on U.S. soil?" Know what they told me?
Hooah.
Weird. Caitlin didn't mention anything
the last time I saw her.
Really? When and where was that?
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure
there's an explanation for all of this.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
He didn't hurt you?
Barry, I told you, only my pride is hurt.
I'm not in the position
to take on armed soldiers.
- Where do you think Eiling took Stein?
- Some off-the-books military research facility.
- We have to get him back.
- Easy. Eiling has already demonstrated...
he has the weaponry
to disable the Flash or worse.
Well, we can't let him
turn Stein into a weapon.
How do we find him?
What?
No abnormal brain
activity. All vitals steady.
You think Ronnie can feel
where they're keeping Stein?
Ronnie got dizzy
when soldiers grabbed Stein...
and Stein developed
Ronnie's obsession with pizza.
I don't feel anything right now.
Just keep trying.
Whatever this is, it doesn't have a switch.
It's possible it's just some kind of
residual connection.
You know, a temporary link
to your time together.
Wait. I feel something.
I'm cold.
It's freezing in here.
My apologies.
It should warm up pretty quick.
I know what you want.
But my research was never intended
to be used as a weapon.
I joined the military
when I was 20 years old, professor.
My father had me convinced
that our greatest threat was the Soviets...
our greatest fear nuclear war.
But then came terrorism.
And Ebola.
And now it's the age of Firestorm.
Soldiers enhanced by your project,
professor.
Soldiers who can generate energy blasts
with their bare hands. Soldiers who can fly.
I would gladly die...
before I see my life's work
perverted in this way.
Good.
Because you will die, professor.
How soon I let that happen though,
is entirely up to you.
What's going on?
The last time I did this was to a gorilla.
- You're okay, man. We got you.
- What's happening to him?
Nothing's happening to him.
It's happening to Stein,
and Ronnie is feeling his pain.
I was wrong.
Their connection is not temporary,
it's only getting stronger.
Just try and hold on.
Water. Water.
My, my, my.
You show remarkable grit for a teacher.
I am impressed.
Why don't we let you catch your breath?
Think about how much more of this
you want to endure.
Hmm?
- Ronnie, no.
- Wait, Cait, wait.
- He's cutting himself.
- I know. Let him.
Huh.
Ronald.
Anything?
Nothing. Nothing, just...
Just cold, like a metal surface.
Pressure on and on and off.
Tap, tap.
Tap. Tap. Tap.
Tap, tap, tap.
- Morse code.
- I got this.
Same thing again. Tap, tap. Tap.
Tap, tap, tap.
- Twenty-seven.
- What does it mean?
Army bases. They sometimes go
by numbers like Area 51.
Facility 27 about 300 miles away.
It was shut down in 1961.
- That's where they're keeping Stein.
- And keeping the aliens too.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, you can't.
I'm connected to Stein. I have to go.
But did you ever stop to think why your
connection to him is growing stronger?
Maybe you're being drawn back together.
Maybe your proximity
will cause you to re-merge into one.
And what happens to me if he gets killed?
Cait, Barry was right.
The world's different now.
Look, I thought we could get away...
start a new life.
A normal life together.
But there is no normal life for us.
You will always risk your life
to try and help people.
And I will always be the guy
that runs into that pipeline for you.
The quantum splicer.
It was used to separate you once.
Maybe it could be of use to keep you, you.
Thanks.
- Okay, let's go.
- Wait.
Come back.
All three of you.
Let's go.
Oh.
This place definitely
doesn't look too shady.
Stein's inside.
I can feel our connection growing stronger
like he's pulling me.
As I feared, the Firestorm matrix...
is building toward
a proximity re-emergence.
Like all matter, it yearns to be whole.
If you two merge...
we might not be able
to separate you again.
We isolated the Firestorm matrix
in the subject's cellular structure.
Excellent.
Professor Stein, I'm afraid
you have made a terrible assumption:
That I need you alive.
Eiling has a gun to Stein's head.
He's about to pull the trigger.
He's here.
Aah! Oh.
Whoa.
I never thought I'd be happy to see you.
- Likewise.
- Let's get out of here.
Aah!
Run!
Okay, come on. Come on.
Barry, I'm picking up some serious
PH numbers on your suit.
They hit me with some chemical.
It's a weaponized phosphorus.
Water or foam won't extinguish it.
But you can't burn in a vacuum.
So you need to create one.
Run, Barry. Run.
- We need to merge again.
- No.
- Cait, we're dead if we don't.
- Listen to me.
The last time you two combined,
you both fought it. This time, don't.
Accept the change. Accept the balance.
Accept each other.
Once more unto the breach, dear friend.
Cait...
whatever happens, just remember...
I'll always love you.
- Can you hear me, Ronald?
- Professor?
It appears we've merged properly
on this attempt.
Wells was right about balance
and accepting it. Behind you.
Ronald, there's more of them.
Eiling, this ends now.
Yes, it does. For both of you.
An ion grenade...
bombarded your cellular structure with
enough ions to destabilize your matrix.
Mr. Raymond, Professor Stein,
you were both fine Americans.
Your country thanks you for your sacrifice.
That was a lot of running.
Ronnie.
- Home?
- Yeah.
I think it looks worse than it is.
Ronnie or Stein?
- It's me, Caitlin.
- Ahem. Excuse me.
- It's both of us. Somehow.
- She's quite lovely.
Acceptance is a powerful thing.
Powerful enough to reverse it?
- I'm game if you are, Mr. Raymond.
- We could try.
Oh. I think we're getting
the hang of this quite nicely.
It's okay.
I understand. You have to go.
- How'd you know?
- I'm connected to you too.
Heh.
- Where will you go?
- Pittsburgh, maybe.
Professor Stein has a colleague he thinks
can help us learn more about our abilities.
We can help you here too.
Eiling's already breached S.T.A.R. Labs.
We need to stay one step ahead of him.
For all of us.
- I'm coming back.
- We'll have pizza.
- Godspeed, Mr. Allen.
- You too.
As per our earlier conversation...
I believe in second chances.
You'll get yours. Give it time.
Ready, Ronald?
Please stop calling me that.
I'll see you soon.
We love you.
I had Ronnie, then I lost him. Then I found
him again, but he wasn't actually Ronnie.
Then I got him back,
but just for a day until I lost him again.
You guys are, like, 10 seasons of Ross and
Rachel but just, like, smushed into one year.
I am not heartbroken this time.
I love Ronnie. I always will.
But there's not this
devastating hole inside me.
I have a life and it's a good one.
Hey, guys.
- Iris, hi.
- Hi.
Where's your cousin?
- Uh, he went home.
- Oh.
Where was that again?
Uh, Midway.
Oh, I thought you said Coast City.
Uh, Midway via Coast City.
He moved around a lot.
Heh. That's always really hard.
- Yeah.
- All right, well, enjoy.
- Bye.
- See you.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
It means that I'm gonna help you figure out
what's going on at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I think our burning man used to work there.
- Hey.
- So why did you bring me here?
I don't know how and I don't know when...
but one day soon,
I'm gonna be in this house again...
15 years ago and I'm gonna fail...
- unless this time I don't.
- What are you saying?
Knowing that I'm supposed to lose
gives me the advantage.
Those images are a
lesson in what not to do.
When I face off against
the man in yellow...
I won't make the same mistake twice.
You're gonna change the past?
Joe...
I'm gonna save my mom.
What...? What the hell was that?
- It's good to see you again, general.
- Who are you?
Who am I?
Harrison.
You're one of them.
Metahuman.
Yes, I am.
And I protect my own.
Who is that?
Now, that...
ils an old friend of ours.
General.
That voice. It's in my head.
- Dear God.
- Not God.
Grodd.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::