[tense music]
♪ ♪
[chime]
- All clear, Ms. Kramer.
- Four scans
and three weapon checks.
I like the way you think,
Agent Cooper.
Were you this serious
back at Fort Dakota?
- The army fights
terrestrial threats, ma'am.
Here, it's that
plus a little...
extra.
- I know what you mean.
- As for the added lockdown,
we're gonna need it for
what you proposing, ma'am.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- News Reporter: The famous
meta-human  Killer Frost
will be sentenced today...
- So much for rebranding.
- Cecile,
how bad is this?
- Uh, typically?
Frost's charges carry
a sentence of 10-20 years.
But...today Judge Tanaka
is gonna weigh that against
all the good
that she's done as a hero,
and given that Frost
hasn't committed a crime
in four years...
I could make a case for
a lighter sentence.
18 months,
maybe less with parole?
- I mean she already pled
guilty and skipped her trial.
What more does the court want?
- They want to know
whether or not
you are responsible
for your crimes.
- This is a load of crap.
You saved the city and more
lives than I can count.
Jitter's named a freakin' drink
after you.
- Exactly. You know,
I say we just make like
"A Few Good Men"
and shove the truth down
the city's throat.
- Guys, we're not looking for
a loophole.
I did these crimes.
And Caity, I know
you want to help,
but ever since becoming my own
person, I've realized that
if I don't own up
for my choices,
I'll never be able to move on.
- What about all the good
things you've done?
Like the life we're building
together?
- I'll miss you, too.
But...until I pay for
what I did,
the rest of the city won't look
at me the way you all do.
[alarm sounds]
- Isotopic signature detected.
- The Forces.
One of them is close.
- Cisco: It's coming from
Keystone City.
Seismic isotopes.
- It's the Strength Force.
- Barry, you have to go.
This is the chance
we've been waiting for.
- Listen to the cosmic lady...
go.
- She's right.
If Fuerza's back,
people need the Flash.
We've got Frost's back.
- Iris is running comms.
I'll come with you.
If that monster is here,
it won't be a match
for us both.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Barry:You sure this is
the right location?
- Yeah, satellites confirm it.
Fuerza should be
right in front of you.
Why? What are you seeing?
- Either our satellites
need to be recalibrated or...
- The Strength Force is better
at hiding than we thought.
- Keystone Cares...
that's a nonprofit
that helps those
those in need.
Why would Fuerza be there?
- So, as you can see,
Your Honor,
my client has already
demonstrated
that, despite her past
mistakes,
Frost now only wishes
to serve this city,
alongside our greatest
protector, the Flash.
Still,
she's aware that justice
must be served.
Which is why she's seeking
a fair punishment.
Not only because
it's the right thing to do,
but to prove once and for all
who she really is.
She's a flawed person
who has changed her ways
and become a hero,
in her own right.
- Well-argued, Ms. Horton.
Counselor Strong,
would the State like to make
an opening remark?
- By her own admission,
the meta-human known as Killer
Frost is guilty of crimes
that have endangered
the peace of our city
and the safety of our citizens.
And the State
finds it absurd that
a former DA would romanticize
this narrative
to avoid punishment.
- It's early and I haven't had
my coffee, Counselor.
But I don't believe
the defendant is
asking to avoid punishment.
- Agreed, Your Honor.
But the State has one goal...
to ensure that this extremely
dangerous criminal
no longer threatens
our good citizens...
which is why we believe
she must have her powers
erased.
[spectators reacts]
- Your Honor,
that is highly irregular.
- I'll decide that,
Ms. Horton.
Ms. Strong, please continue.
- In lieu of prison,
the State moves to submit
alternate punishment...
that Killer Frost be compelled
by this court...
to take the meta-human cure.
[spectators murmurs]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
Kramer is damn good.
We're here looking for a
lighter sentence.
She's arguing that since
felons are prohibited
from owning firearms,
Frost's powers are weapons
that the State can take away
using the cure.
- A cure that CCPD only has
'cause we gave it to them.
A cure that's supposed to be
voluntary.
How can Kramer just force Frost
to take it like that?
- Is that even legal?
- Yeah, you would be surprised
what can become legal when
you've got the full force
of the American justice system
behind you.
It can be pretty scary
sometimes.
- What if we forget the deal,
just take the 10 to 20 years?
- Prosecution's not even
seeking jail time anymore.
Kramer is all about the cure.
She wants Frost neutralized
forever.
- At least
it can't get any worse.
- Actually, it can.
I just talked to Mom.
She's gonna run some more tests
to be sure, but we think
that because you are
uniquely born from meta DNA,
if you take the cure...
it could harm you,
maybe even kill you.
- This is insane.
Okay, no one is touching Frost.
We're gonna stop this, right?
- Hell yeah.
- Okay, we need to
fight fire with fire.
Hack Kramer, dig up dirt,
whatever it takes
to save Frost.
- No.
I didn't just turn myself in
so that I could go
and break the law again.
We're doing this by the book
or not at all...okay, Katie?
- Okay.
You're right.
- Something
still doesn't sit right.
Why would Kramer go so hard
to take you down?
- I have no idea.
But all I care about now
is stopping her.
- Well, we do that by
convincing the judge
that you deserve prison time
and not the cure.
I got some case law books
back at the office
that we need to
look at, and uh, Joe,
I think you can help me out.
- Okay, what are we
really doing?
- I like your hacking idea.
- We need to think bigger.
Frost's life is on the line.
- Guys, I'm still picking up
Fuerza's isotopic signature
in the area.
You still don't see her?
- No, nothing yet.
Fuerza's signature
is seismic-based.
Maybe she hides underground.
Man, there's a lot of
people here.
We should run them all away
before things get dangerous.
- No. The Forces want to feed
off our powers, Barry.
That's probably why this thing
attacked you
in the first place.
Using our abilities too early,
even if it's to save others,
could put them in danger.
- I guess that is possible.
There's still so much we don't
know about these Forces.
- We know all we need to.
They're dangerous.
I still remember
how they attacked me...
eating me alive.
I could feel it.
It's pure evil.
- I know, I felt it too
when Psych attacked me.
Wherever these things came
from, they have to be stopped.
- Iris:Yeah, I'm not so sure.
- What do you mean?
- Well, the Sage Force
is clearly dangerous
and Fuerza too,
but do you remember
what Chester and Cisco said
about Deon, the Still Force?
- That he was just a kid
who wanted to be left alone.
- Yeah, I mean,
does that seem like
a vicious energy feeder
to you?
Iris:Something doesn't
add up here.
- Barry, the creature
that we're hunting
killed someone
and tried to kill you.
We can't let ourselves be
fooled by the
human facades these Forces
hide behind.
Underneath them, these Forces
only have one goal...
to destroy everything
they touch.
You need to remember that.
- Iris:Barry, got another hit,
and it's coming from
the next tent.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Great, just put those
extra rations just over...
wait, are you two volunteers?
- Um...uh, no we're...uh,
no, actually.
- No? Oh...sorry it's been
a pretty busy morning.
I'm Alexa Rivera,
the Field Supervisor
for Keystone Cares.
What can I do for you?
- Cisco:Mic check, one, two,
one, two.
You ready?
- Sure hope so.
Officer Korber,
I'm Caitlin Snow.
I was
detained here the other day.
It was a misunderstanding.
- Right, I heard.
Sorry that happened.
- It's okay.
It's all sorted now.
But when the released me,
they didn't return
all of my belongings.
- Really?
- Yes, I'm still missing
a necklace,
and a bracelet...the bracelet
used to be my mother's.
- I'm sure they're still
in lockup.
- Mm.
- If you just want to fill out
a 10-67 for loss of property.
I'll get them.
[energized music]
- Great.
- Cisco, is the coast clear?
- I am back-looping security
cameras...
now.
You got two minutes
before they're back up.
- Which way am I going again?
This whole breaking into
CCPD
thing's freaking me out.
- When we gave them the cure,
they stored the surplus
in the Armory.
That's where you're headed.
- Uh...
- Just turn right.
Your other right.
All right,
you're gonna attach
the inertial oximeter
to the door.
It's gonna send out a pulse
that will neutralize
all cure samples on site.
- Almost there.
- Can I help you?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- You seem lost.
- I'm from "The Citizen."
I'm...I'm here
for our interview.
- Caitlin,
Allegra needs backup.
Kramer's got her pinned.
[suspenseful music]
- Sorry about that.
♪ ♪
- No one told me about
any interview.
- They had to.
I contacted your office.
They said you were in charge
of meta-affairs,
and, clearly,
you were never told.
- No, I wasn't.
- Okay, look, this is
a huge scoop for me.
Could you just give me
ten minutes?
- How much time do I have left
before the cameras
turn back on?
- 20 seconds. We have to
deliver the oximeter now
or we're screwed.
- Please, if I go back
empty-handed,
my boss is gonna kill me.
Ten minutes,
that's all I'm asking.
♪ ♪
- You've got five.
- Thanks.
Let's go sit.
- Whoa, you should really
get that checked out.
- Yeah, I'll have someone
take a look at it.
- Ten seconds, go, go, go, go!
[energized music]
♪ ♪
- The cure has been
neutralized.
Now get the hell out of there
before I have a heart attack.
- Yeah!
- Wait...so,
am I under arrest?
- No, no, no, no.
I...I am with CCPD,
but I...I'm a CSI,
I...I don't arrest people.
- But you think I'm guilty
of something.
[scoffs] Right.
Never gonna catch a break,
am I?
- I'm sorry, I don't follow.
- Okay, fine.
Yeah, it's true,
I was an addict.
Then I hit rock bottom,
and that was a wake-up call.
So I got clean,
I went to school.
I could have worked
in a hospital,
but this is where I belong.
Helping people, just like me,
turn their lives around.
Look, I've been to rehab,
and I don't have a record,
so whatever crime
you're investigating...
- No, no, it's...it's...it's
nothing like that.
Um...uh, we...
Um...
[clears throat]
It's...it's gonna sound
kind of crazy, but we've been
scanning the city
for a new meta,
and for some reason
our readings led us to you.
- Seriously?
I'm not a meta.
- We're not so sure.
- Well, then what do you
want from me?
- Alexa, we'd like for you
to come to
S.T.A.R. Labs with us.
We work with a team there
that can conduct a simple,
painless test...
- Tell us what we already know.
That you're the monster
who attacked Central City
and killed a man
and tried to kill me too.
- I have never seen you before
in my life,
and I'm not going anywhere
with you,
especially not S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah, I've heard of them.
They're the ones who started
all this meta stuff
in the first place.
- Alexa, hold on,
we just want to help.
- No, you hold on.
I am not a monster.
And if you don't mind,
there are people
who actually need my help.
Please don't contact me again.
- Nora:I don't see why
you're so upset.
We know that woman
is the thing
we've been searching for.
- No,
we think she might be.
But now we'll never
learn the truth,
because you scared her away.
- Barry, the answer is simple.
If she won't come to us,
we'll make her.
- What?
- We move in the blink
of an eye.
She'll never know,
and by the time she does,
we'll test her, and...
if she's innocent,
return her before she
takes her next breath.
- Nora, I know
you're new to all this,
but we don't just grab people
and test them
against their will.
- Why not?
- Because...
- Lives are at stake.
- That's not how this works.
- Well, maybe it should.
Barry, you and I know what this
thing is really capable of.
Now, all I'm asking is
for you to trust me
and do what needs to be done.
Is that really too much
for me to ask?
- You're asking him to give up
a part of what
makes him a hero.
So, yes, Nora, it is too much.
Barry.
It's your choice.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Captain West,
you're here to make a statement
on behalf of the Defendant.
If you please?
- I admit, under oath,
that Frost hasn't always been
on the right side of the law.
But I can also say
that she has put her life
on the line
countless times to save others.
- How so, Captain?
- Frost has fought alongside
Earth's greatest heroes
to save the world, which means
that she's saved every person
in this room
including those
who want to lock her up
for being who she was.
Not for who she is today.
And,
Your Honor...
I don't understand
how this court
can force Frost
to take that cure
without sacrificing
what it stands for...
justice.
- Thank you, Captain West.
Your word goes a long way
in this court.
- [mouthing]
- In fact,
I believe I'm ready
to deliver my verdict.
- Your Honor.
We have a new update regarding
a relevant incident
that could affect your ruling.
If it pleases the court.
- Proceed.
- Earlier today, the meta-human
cure supply
at CCPD was rendered inert.
It is now completely unusable.
The State suspects foul play
by the only person with motive
for such bold treachery...
Killer Frost.
- No, I didn't do it.
It wasn't me,
I have not been to CCPD.
I've been here!
- Let me handle this, please.
Objection. Your Honor, this is
speculative nonsense.
- Sustained.
Prosecutor, do you have
evidence for your accusations?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- CCPD security cameras
were hacked at
the exact moment
the cure was destroyed.
We wouldn't have found out
if not for
Ms. Kramer's expertise
in military intelligence.
She uncovered the hack herself.
- It was me, Your Honor.
I did it, not Frost.
And I acted alone.
- She's lying, Your Honor.
Killer Frost is clearly behind
this crime,
because her criminal past is
the same as her
criminal present.
- I am not a criminal, what is
wrong with her, she keeps...
[overlapping arguing]
- Order.
I said order.
- Everybody sit down.
- Now, Ms. Strong, considering
the cure isn't a viable option,
can the court assume
the State is no longer
seeking it as a punishment?
- On the contrary.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- And where exactly
did you get that?
- My colleague Ms. Kramer
knows the magnitude of
the meta-criminal
we are dealing with.
So, she contacted A.R.G.U.S.
on behalf of the State
and had them replicate the cure
based on CCPD samples.
We should have 100 vials ready
by nightfall.
All we need is your decision,
Your Honor.
- Very well.
I'll retire to my chambers
and make my decision.
Court is adjourned.
-Bailiff: All rise.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- This is for your own good.
- What just happened?
- We just lost.
[dramatic music]
- Babe?
Please, tell us you know
a way out of this.
I'm sorry, but...
I don't.
I don't know...I don't know
how we're gonna keep Frost
from being forced
to take the cure.
- What's Kramer's deal,
anyway?
- Kramer's had it out for me
since before I was arrested.
- My gut tells me she's still
hiding something.
- We need a miracle, and fast.
- No, we don't.
Because we are Team Flash,
and we have more than enough
resources to figure this out.
- Caitlin, we already went
that route, remember?
And all we did
was make things worse.
- Okay, well I can't just sit
here and do nothing, okay?
Because Frost is my sister,
and I have to do everything
I can to protect her.
- Guys, I need to talk
to Caitlin.
Alone.
You want to explain yourself?
Caity, you made me a promise
that we would fight this
the way I wanted to.
- Okay, but that's the thing,
okay...
you are not fighting this.
You skipped your trial,
and look how that turned out.
- And whose fault is that?
[phone buzzes]
- It's Mom, she got the test
results back
from how the cure will affect
your meta-DNA.
Thank God,
she says you'll be fine.
The cure will take away
your powers,
but it won't harm you...
you're gonna survive.
- Great, whatever.
- Frost, this is the miracle
we've been waiting for.
This is gonna save you.
- By erasing my powers?
- You heard Cecile, okay.
Even if we can convince the
judge to give you prison time,
you're looking at
10 to 20 years easy.
- Then I'll take it.
- Why would you give up
two decades of your life
when there is a perfectly safe
solution?
- Changing who I am
is not a solution.
How the hell can you even
ask me that?
You're the one who said the
cure should always be a choice.
- Then why won't you
choose this?
[solemn music]
I...
Do you remember when the
Sage Force attacked,
and I told you
my greatest fear?
It's living life without you.
I am terrified of living a life
that you're not in.
Frost,
you are my sister, I love you.
And I cannot lose you.
- And if I take the cure,
you will.
Caity, don't you see?
It's not me you trying
to protect.
It's yourself.
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
- The Flash.
That CSI sent you, didn't he?
- Alexa, I know everything
you've heard today
probably sounds insane,
let alone terrifying.
But, if you give me a chance,
I think maybe I can explain
why it's so important
you get tested.
- I already know why.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[Fuerza roars]
- You were there when Fuerza
attacked Central City.
- I was part of a team
building low income housing
that week.
And I just remember
feeling so angry
when Abra Kadabra
destroyed our worksite.
But I don't remember much else.
I've been having, um...
blackouts.
Just waking up in strange
places, not knowing...
where I've been, or...
or what I've done.
- When's the last time
it happened?
- When this thing attacked.
What if I...
oh, my God, what if I am
this monster?
- Help me find out.
Trust me,
I know how scary it is to not
have full control of yourself.
- I haven't felt this way
since before I got clean.
I don't know
if I'm strong enough
to know the truth, I...
I just...I feel so weak.
[cries]
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Alexa, the person
who received these cards
is not a monster.
You've dedicated your life
to selflessly helping
those in need.
Finding out the truth about
yourself is the same thing.
You'll be keeping people safe.
- I don't know why,
but I feel like
I can trust you.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- All right, Captain West.
Let's finish reviewing this
so we can...
- Joe arranged a little
meet-cute for us.
- You and Captain West
seem awfully close...
I wonder why that is.
- We're poker buddies.
- What do you want?
- To know why you hate me.
Did I hurt you
or someone you love?
Then why do you want to take
my powers away?
How is that justice?
- You've got a lot of gall
lecturing me about justice.
You only turned yourself in
after years of evading the law,
when you were surrounded
by my officers.
That's not doing
the right thing,
that's called getting caught.
- Look, I'll go to prison,
do my time, fine.
But forcing the cure on me?
I don't deserve that.
- And the court will decide
what you deserve.
This isn't just about what
you've done.
This is about what people
like you do.
- Right.
So you hate all metas.
Very original.
Cicada with a badge.
- I don't hate all meta-humans,
just the ones who pretend
to be heroes.
I lost an entire platoon
because I made that mistake.
On my orders,
they followed a meta I thought
was a hero into a hot zone.
He fooled me.
By the time I realized
his betrayal,
20 soldiers lost their lives,
lives I was responsible
to protect.
Never again.
- This isn't just about me.
You want to go after
all meta-humans.
- Only the criminals.
But your sentence will set
the legal precedent.
First you take the cure,
then any meta who endangers
the good of the people
will have to follow suit.
- You cannot be serious.
- I admire your fight.
But there is nothing
you can do to stop this.
'Cause in the end,
justice always wins.
[edgy music]
♪ ♪
- You know, this whole waiting
for a verdict thing?
It sucks.
- Frost, I am so sorry.
You're right, I wasn't thinking
about what you wanted.
I was only thinking about
what I wanted.
- It doesn't matter.
Kramer's gonna win, and every
meta in this city
is gonna lose because of me.
Kramer's trying to set
a precedent that any meta
accused of a crime can be
punished with the cure.
I was just thinking about all
the meta lives that will hurt.
I don't even care about myself
anymore.
I just want to help them.
Hey...
Aren't you supposed to be the
one telling me not to worry?
That we'll figure it out?
- That's the thing, Sis.
I think I just did.
[edgy music]
♪ ♪
- Okay.
This place is even more
intimidating on the inside.
- Alexa, I know you're nervous,
but the Flash promised
to keep you safe,
and we're gonna
keep that promise.
- Barry's right.
And I'm sorry if I startled
you earlier.
But, don't worry.
If something goes wrong,
I'm sure the Flash will show up
and take care of everything.
Come with me.
The Speed Lab's this way.
[gavel knocks]
- It's been quite the long day,
but before I render my verdict,
I understand the defendant
would like to make a statement.
- You ready for this?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Here's the deal.
Taking away a meta-human's
powers
isn't the same thing as taking
away a gun from a criminal.
Erasing our powers
is erasing our identity.
It's saying,
"Hey, you were
made bad, change that."
But
shouldn't justice be about
changing the way a person acts,
not the way they were born?
I get it.
You fear us
because we're different.
You'd feel safer
if we were the same.
But different can't be cured.
It's here to stay.
We're here to stay.
Some of you only think of me
as the criminal I used to be.
Back then, I was only
interested in
protecting myself.
But, then, I found someone else
worth protecting.
And protecting that person led
me to protecting a whole city.
And slowly I changed.
I learned how...
I learned how to be selfless
instead of selfish.
I learned that I'm my best self
when I'm protecting
other people.
So, with the help of someone
close to me,
I've made a decision.
[mouthing]
I am submitting a request
for life in prison
without parole.
[spectators gasp]
- Your Honor, prison time
is not the punishment
the State is requesting.
- Correction, Your Honor.
The State's own words
made very clear
that their only goal was,
and I quote,
"to ensure this extremely
dangerous criminal
no longer threatens
our good citizens."
- Are those your words,
Counselor?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- Then I'll remind Ms. Kramer
she isn't Counsel,
and kindly ask her to sit down.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- The court would like to
ask the defendant
if she's fully aware of what
she's proposing.
- Yes.
I am.
As am I that my judgement
will set a precedent.
A ruling for the cure sets it
as a viable punishment.
A ruling against it
takes it off the table.
Like my old law professor
used to say,
in order for justice
to be blind,
sometimes she must open
her eyes to ugly truths.
Therefore,
I hereby sentence
the meta-human criminal
known as Frost,
to life in prison without
the possibility of parole.
[indistinct chatter]
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
[knock on door]
- Captain, uh,
I'm all packed up,
just thought I'd say goodbye.
- Good luck.
- Listen, I know...
we've had our differences and
maybe that's an understatement,
especially after today,
but...
I just wanted to tell you,
despite our personal frictions,
you have my respect.
I admire your commitment
to justice.
- The feeling's mutual.
Truth is, I may not always
like your methods.
Sometimes, I downright
despise them.
But I know a good cop
when I see one.
- Only that's not all, is it?
- No.
Make sure
you're always checking
which side of the line
you're on.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[moody jazz music]
[Nina Simone's
"Don't Explain"]
- ♪ Hush now ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Don't explain ♪
♪ There ain't nothin'
to gain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm glad that you're back ♪
♪ Don't explain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All my thoughts are of you ♪
♪ For I'm so completely
yours ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear
nobody chatter ♪
♪ 'Cause I know you cheat ♪
- Every meta in town
will know what you did for us.
- ♪ Right and wrong
don't matter ♪
♪ When you're with me,
my sweet ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Hush now, don't explain ♪
♪ You're my joy,
you're my pain ♪
♪ My ♪
♪ Life ♪
♪ Is yours, love ♪
♪ Don't explain ♪
♪ ♪
- So, I just lie here?
- Yeah, these arc radiators
emit isotropic energy.
I'll be using this tablet
to gradually expose you
to those same isotopic waves.
Are you okay?
- No.
I'm scared out of my mind.
- You're gonna be fine.
I promise.
- So if you're right about
all this...won't I change?
'Cause if that happens,
I could hurt someone.
- You won't hurt anyone.
We're only administering
a tiny dose,
just enough to trigger
the smallest change inside you
on a microscopic level.
So if something...
is inside you,
our instruments will tell us.
[lightly edgy music]
Are you still sure
you wanna do this?
♪ ♪
Ready?
- Yeah.
Her baseline is steady.
[heavy bass thrumming]
- [breathing hard]
[suspenseful music]
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Just...the way
you inspired Barry
to reach out to Alexa.
You really are
his lightning rod.
[stirring music]
[rapid chiming]
[dramatic chords]
[rumbling]
♪ ♪
- Alexa...can you hear me?
- [growling]
Ruhh...raaahhh...
[snarling]
Get...
away...from...
aaahhhh!
[gasping]
- Alexa?
Can you hear me?
- [breathing hard]
- Hey, it's okay.
Everything's okay.
- No, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not... I am that thing!
What am I gonna do now?
How am I...
- You're gonna be all right.
You're gonna be all right,
okay?
You're safe here.
We're gonna help you
deal with this.
I promise.
[heavy music]
♪ ♪
- Nora?
- You still don't get it.
If I don't end her now,
she'll sacrifice me
to get what she wants...
my life.
- Wait, listen to me.
I know you're scared.
We can still help her.
- You should be helping me.
I need your powers to defeat
her, and you promised.
And now you're breaking
that promise.
And I know why.
You may be his lightning rod...
but I'm the lightning.
[electricity zapping,
crackling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Thank you.
[electrical roaring]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Time to choose a side, Barry.
[heavy, dramatic music]
♪ ♪