Previously on The Flash...
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
I think it's time you introduce
these guys to your mean roommate.
Tell Amunet I'm done.
Nobody walks away from me, Frost.
So, you think DeVoe and his wife
are supervillains?
Who are you, really?
I was born
on the same evening you were.
I know every answer
to every question ever asked.
Incredible. Clifford!
Your body's deteriorating
faster than the chair can handle.
It will survive long enough.
What are you doing?
Tinsel.
Your tinsel-to-surface ratio
is terrible.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm not kidding you.
I've done extensive research
to make sure that this tinsel
is properly proportioned for this tree.
- It's terrible.
- "It's terrible"?
- I'll tell you what's terrible.
- What?
Your Scrooge-to-Grinch
ratio is terrible.
You're a mean one. I wouldn't touch you
with a 39-and-a-half foot pole.
- Haven't heard that one before.
- Yeah.
Hey, Cisco. Where's Gypsy?
She had to work the holiday shift,
but I think I got her the perfect gift.
A Gulag-class mech knife
forged in the unholy blood-fires
of Earth-22 by none other than
- Wells 2.0.
Of course, Gypsy should've
sent something for me by now.
Awkward.
I'm sure it's fine.
Yikes.
Did Rudolph
just diarrhea all over your tree?
Cool. Cool. Two humbugs.
It's a Festivus miracle.
No, don't get me wrong.
Ralphy loves Christmas.
I ring in every holiday season
with my nana.
She never remembers me but I am getting
that inheritance.
You are just incorrect.
If you don't want to spend Christmas
conning your grandma,
you're more than welcome to join
your friends at the West family party.
Extremely obvious. I saw that.
And, by the way,
that sounds like a snooze fest.
Unless, of course,
you're serving baking soda!
Baking soda!
What... Sorry, what's that about?
Well, it's a bit of an inside joke.
- Actually, concerning Killer Frost.
- Classic Killer Frost.
You guys were
hanging out with Killer Frost?
Oh, yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
I hope you had a great time.
We had the best time.
I mean, you're great, Snow Cone,
but my girl Frostbite...
Come on.
I'm gonna go get a cup of coffee.
- Caitlin.
Hey, if you see my girl
K-Frost later,
tell her what I said
about the baking soda.
- Dibny.
- Too much?
Okay. From Oliver and Felicity...
We have an espresso machine. All right.
Okay, not on the registry.
But I guess getting married
during our wedding
wasn't on the registry either.
- So, yeah, sure. I'm not bitter.
- All right.
I'll put this in the return pile.
Well, I guess that's everything.
No, we got one more.
There's no card.
Um...
Great, it's another set of knives.
It's not even a full set.
Yeah, it's one knife.
- That's just shoddy gifting.
- Let me see.
I'm gonna clean up.
So, what, no speed cleaning today?
No, we're not in a rush.
Barry, you barely
used your powers in Bali, either.
I mean,
not even to put on suntan lotion.
It was a spray-on bottle.
What is going on, Barr?
Nothing.
I mean, I don't know.
I have been thinking recently that...
You know, when I first got my powers,
I would use any excuse to use them.
It would just be me and the road
and everything around me
would disappear.
It's like the first time in my life
I really felt like I was at peace.
I just...
Feel like that all the time now.
I don't have to run when I'm with you.
Aw.
So sweet.
I love you, Iris West Allen.
I love you, too.
Let me.
The atrophy of my fine
motor skills is accelerating.
I'm so sorry, my love.
The pain is but fleeting.
- After all, today is the day.
- How fitting.
You'll share a birthday
with the Messiah.
The Nazarene wasn't born until spring.
You can check the constellation patterns
to verify that.
You've heard this lecture before,
haven't you?
Maybe.
But I will never grow tired
of hearing your voice.
The words are still mine
even if the voice isn't.
Do you have any doubts?
No, of course not.
It will just take some getting used to.
Don't be afraid, my love.
This is the great work.
I swear,
I will stand beside you in your time.
Ho, ho, ho!
Well, let's see...
Dark roast. The light roast...
What are you having,
the self-pity roast?
I wish.
- "The Killer Frost."
- Finally got a drink. Woo-hoo.
I'm thrilled that she helped everybody
fight the Reichsmen,
but now it's like I can't escape her.
Everybody keeps saying,
"Killer Frost is so funny.
"Killer Frost is so badass."
I spent so long worried
that she was gonna hurt people.
But now, turns out people would rather
hang out with my villainous alter-ego.
Look, I...
I get it. I know what it's like
to have the evil doppelganger,
but you're not like me anyways.
No, you're different. You're special.
And your friends would much rather
be with you than with her.
- Thanks, Harry.
- You're welcome.
Ho, ho, ho.
This is like a lifetime supply
of store credit.
Why would Rory think that
we needed 40 toasters?
He said that there was some
kind of fire sale...
- He stole them. Yeah.
- He definitely stole them.
Barry!
Caity!
- That's Amunet.
- Hide. Hide. Hide.
I blocked your Glock.
Hello, Iris. My deepest congratulations
on your wedding.
No, no, no, dear.
Frosty melted away.
I've come for you, Caity.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I'll be right back.
Barry!
DeVoe. He attacked us on the street.
- He took Barry.
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- What happened to you?
Amunet Black abducted Caitlin.
Two people go missing at the same time.
That's quite a coinky-dink.
Yeah, that's a great observation,
Captain Obvious.
Can you set the satellite
to look for Caitlin's cryokinetic energy
or Barry's Speed Force signatures?
No. No.
We've got to look for both of them.
Cisco, I need you to vibe Barry.
I need to know that he's alive.
Holy poltergeist.
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just not gonna be vibing again
for a while.
What about Allen?
Wherever he is,
I've never experienced anything like it.
Hello?
Here we are.
Really moving up in the world.
You know, a sprinkle of enthusiasm
would not kill you.
Listen, Amunet,
whatever it is you have planned,
I guarantee you Killer Frost
wants nothing to do with it.
It's all right, darling.
I don't need her. I need you.
Meet your patient.
What have you done?
There's no need to be overdramatic.
He's alive.
And I'm sure he'd be happy to meet you,
just as soon
as that tranquilizer wears off.
Why do you have him? What is he to you?
My golden goose.
You see, Dominic here
is a delightful new meta
that I "found."
And I'd intended on selling him,
but unfortunately, he did not want to
go so gently into the good night.
And...
- I shot him.
- That is...
In desperate need of medical attention.
I know.
And now you know
why I need you, Caity, MD.
You're talking about an intricate
cranial foreign body
retraction, at best.
At worst, that's an...
I'm gonna stop you there
'cause I have absolutely no idea
what you're saying.
But, you see, it does not matter.
Because I knew that you would understand
what needed to happen.
Amunet, I won't. I can't.
This environment isn't sterilized,
the equipment is ancient.
I suppose I could
just yank it out myself.
And risk him bleeding out
or a dozen other brain deficits.
Right. Good point.
Well, there's only one way to find out.
No. No.
I'll do what I can.
Excellent.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Should he die,
you die as well.
This Killer Frost iced mocha
is really delicious.
Hello, Mr. Allen.
Not exactly S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Who are you?
- My name is Caitlin Snow,
and you're in St. Andrew's Hospital.
At least, I think that's where we are.
This place has been closed down
for a while.
Please, you have to help me
get out of here.
Easier said than done.
That blonde lady, she took you, too?
God, I don't understand
why this is happening to us.
Dominic, do you know
what a meta-human is?
Listen, I didn't do anything wrong.
- I didn't rob a bank or something.
- No, I know.
People with abilities, people like you,
they're a commodity, especially...
Especially to Amunet.
Yeah.
Listen, I'm gonna be honest with you.
It would be very difficult to fix
what she did to you,
even under the best of circumstances
with the right equipment.
But I feel fine.
My head doesn't even hurt.
Which is a minor miracle.
But if that shard were to fracture...
It could cause permanent motor skills
or permanent brain deficits.
How did you...
You have telepathic abilities.
Can you hear
what I'm thinking right now?
When did I get my powers?
A couple months ago.
I took the bus to my job
at the airport. TSA.
But when I got there,
it was like everyone was yelling at me,
screaming mad,
but their mouths weren't moving.
It only works when I'm close enough
to see someone.
You don't think
we're getting out of here?
I'm gonna do
everything I can to fix you,
but I can't get you away from her.
Not on my own.
Caitlin.
I'm scared, too.
Wow.
What an entrance.
So, where are we?
This is your sanctuary?
What gave that away?
DeVoe, if you wanted to kill me,
you could have just electrocuted me
on the street. So...
I'm here for a reason.
Yes, Mr. Allen.
So that I may teach you.
I am, after all,
first and foremost a teacher.
God.
All right. Fine. Teach me.
But first I wanna make sure
I'm all caught up.
You sent your Samuroid after me.
You arranged to pull me
out of the Speed Force.
You made sure that we turned
all those people on that bus
into meta-humans.
Why?
You see, the finer points of my agenda
are not part of today's syllabus.
Come on. We can squeeze it in.
I'm a fast learner.
Please. You're about as capable
of seeing the breadth of my machinations
as an infant mastering
multivariable physics.
Well...
But the lesson I have prepped for today
is much more simple.
Life 101.
There are no happy endings.
Oh.
We have a guest.
DeVoe...
You should learn to lose
every once in a while, Barr.
A little humility will prepare you
for what lies ahead.
Now, if you will excuse me.
DeVoe!
If you hurt him...
If you put a hand on him...
DeVoe!
It's open.
Good evening, Detective West.
Now, something tells me
you're not here for more
of my wife's world-famous lemonade.
Where's my son?
Mr. Allen? Has he gone missing?
He's not missing. He was taken.
By someone I am eager to meet.
Thinly-veiled threats aside, Mr. West,
I'm afraid I have not a clue
as to Barry Allen's location.
I do know, however, that your colleague
is located behind my front porch,
carrying an ionic subrepeating
pulse firearm.
But the birdbath
it's a much better vantage point.
A smart man
would've taken up position there.
A smarter man would understand
that this gun has no safety
and my finger is still on the trigger.
Is there something you find funny?
Well, it has occurred to me that
there is an amusing irony at play,
you being a detective and all,
yet you fail to acknowledge
the most basic result
in missing-children cases.
And what would that be?
Perhaps your son just ran away.
- Joe...
- Now, I do have
a restraining order against your son.
Shall I add you to the list?
If something happened to Barry,
there ain't a restraining order on Earth
that would keep me from getting you.
- I'm coming back with a search warrant.
- Completely unnecessary, Detective.
If you desire to search my abode,
by all means.
- You're not as smart as you think.
- Yes, I am.
You're only hurting yourself.
Running faster than sound,
vibrating through walls,
even throwing lightning...
None of that can destroy this barrier.
You know a lot about my abilities.
Is that why I'm here?
DeVoe wants my powers?
You don't have to do this.
Whatever he has planned,
you don't have to help him.
A helper. Is that what you think I am?
A mindless minion
carrying out her master's bidding?
Some sort of evil secretary?
You tell me.
No, Mr. Allen.
I am now, and forever will be,
my husband's partner.
I understand that.
You're not the only one
who promised to stand by your loved one
for better or for worse.
In sickness and in health.
If you go down this path with DeVoe,
can't you see that you risk sacrificing
everything that you have together?
Your entire marriage.
You're missing the point.
I am willing to sacrifice everything
for my marriage.
I'd ask if you could do the same,
but there's no need.
My husband already knows.
His body may be human,
but his brain is smarter than yours.
- Zark me!
- What happened?
Well, the satellite's trying to search
for Barry's Speed Force energy
and Caitlin's cryokinetic signature,
so the bandwidth limiters
are overheating.
Well, that's what you get
when you rely on machines
rather than a master private eye.
I've had a ton a missing-person cases.
There was this wife once,
turns out she faked her own death,
she was just living in Arizona.
Are you saying Barry faked his own death
and moved to Arizona?
Well, no.
Well, then shut up.
Oh, boy.
Tell me you got something.
Got nothing.
Searched the DeVoe house thoroughly.
It's clean.
Your father's gone to check the scene
from where Barry was taken.
You know,
there was this other case once.
A woman couldn't find her husband.
Turns out she just had amnesia.
He was home,
she just didn't recognize him.
And I still got paid. Twice.
Ralph.
Please, shut up.
You got something
you wanna say to me, Ramon?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got something to say to you,
Ralphy boy.
Caitlin's been kidnapped.
Of course, she wouldn't have been
at Jitters in the first place
if you hadn't acted
like such a jackass today
but of course,
in true Ralph Dibny fashion,
you drove her away with your fat mouth!
Maybe I should turn my hand
into a fat fist?
- Oh, yeah?
- Hey, guys, cool it.
Listen, the people we love are in danger
and you two can't get it together?
Really?
Whatever.
I'll be in my lab.
And I will be in whatever room
is farthest from that.
Speed lab.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- What is wrong with those two?
- You.
Excuse me?
You're what's wrong.
You are the team leader.
Team leader is supposed
to make the tough call.
I made a call. I said we would look
for both of them.
No. Looking for both of them
is not a choice.
We're overtaxing our resources,
our people,
because you won't face the hard truth.
And the hard truth is
we can't look for both.
We can only look for one.
Harry, I just made a vow
to love and protect Barry,
to stand by him through thick and thin.
And now you're asking me to choose
between my husband's life
and my friend's?
- I can't do that.
- You have to.
Or you risk losing them both.
You have to choose.
Damn it.
Who's Killer Frost?
Sorry. She's just on your mind a lot,
with a lot of cursing.
She is my meta-power.
Whenever I get scared or angry
she takes over.
She is violent and dangerous
and unpredictable
but she's a whole lot more useful
than I am.
No, thanks.
I'm already scared to death
of one psychotic woman.
I'll take my chances with you.
Dominic, I'm sorry, it's too risky
to perform this surgery here.
And I don't have
any powers to save us...
But you do.
Take a right.
Caitlin, get back.
Somebody's made my naughty list.
Gentlemen, can you please
take Dominic in?
I need to have a word
with Caity in private.
Thank you.
Why can't you just appreciate
how nice I've been to you?
I don't think you understand
the meaning of the word "nice."
Now, now. It's not about words,
it's about actions.
And I have not stabbed you
or punched you
or shot a deadly piece of metal
at you once.
Today.
So why did you run away from me?
Tried. Tried and failed.
Killer Frost
would have been able to do it.
Ah.
I see.
Caity, do you know what I was doing
before I became the successful
entrepreneur you see before you today?
Mean British nanny?
No.
I was a stewardess.
You see, unlike you, I did not have
fancy scientists for parents.
I did not collect scholarships
or attend fine institutions.
My career options were limited.
So I spent my days
in a quaint little skirt and vest,
serving coffee to handsy pilots,
powerless to stop them.
But then,
the particle accelerator exploded
and I was powerless no more.
I showed those pilots
the error of their ways.
Why are you telling me this?
Because obtaining my powers
is quite literally what made me me.
But the same cannot be said about you.
There are any number of doctors
I could have come to for this procedure.
I did not. I came to you.
Because you, Caitlin Snow, are
and have always been remarkable.
You are bright, resourceful, resilient.
And I am more than certain
you can do this.
So, with that said,
unless you want to spend the rest
of your medical career in the morgue,
I suggest you buck up, darling.
You know, pull on your big-girl pants
and do the bloody thing.
Find Caitlin and Barry.
Come on, you bum.
Do it.
Do it!
Are you yelling at my satellite?
No, I was just encouraging it.
Although, Sally here
clearly doesn't wanna be encouraged.
Okay, one, her name isn't Sally.
Two...
I'm sorry.
Barry and Caitlin,
we've lost them both before,
and it just feels like
we just got them back.
So, sorry I was a dick.
You weren't a dick.
I'm the dick.
Private and public.
You were just being honest.
If it wasn't for me, Caitlin would be
right here with you, me and Sally.
Not "Sally."
The truth is,
I haven't had friends in a while.
I'm sure you find that hard to believe,
given my good looks
and winning personality.
Mmm-hmm.
But I'm out of practice.
I suck at being a friend.
Now Christmas is ruined,
everyone is kidnapped,
and it's all my fault.
You're here.
And you're helping.
Caitlin's in a vulnerable
state right now
and Barry can take care of himself.
So let's turn off
the Speed Force satellite.
We're going after Caitlin.
We're on it.
Let's go get our girl.
I used some equipment
that I found in the basement
to jerry-rig an MRI machine
so that I don't hit an artery.
Now that's ingenuity.
You know, I knew
you were the right doctor to kidnap.
This is a very delicate procedure.
Do you mind giving me some space?
Right. Sorry.
I'll just... I'm gonna leave this
right here.
You know, medical insurance and all.
Great.
- Ready?
- I trust you.
Now I need you to hold still.
You're gonna feel some pressure.
Extracting the foreign object.
Foreign object extracted.
Applying some surgical glue.
- He's going into shock.
- So un-shock him.
I don't know if I can.
That is not the rhythmic tone
of a steady heartbeat.
I need to hear a beep-beep-beep, dearie,
or Dominic won't be
the only flatliner in the room.
Oh.
Oh, you're good.
We're clear.
They're all out.
Forty psi of inhalation anesthetic,
that'll keep 'em out, but not for long.
Let's go.
Satellite's pinging
Caitlin's latent cryokinetic signature.
Where is she?
East wing of St. Alexander Hospital.
That place has been closed for years.
We'll breach over. You got your suit?
Never leave home without it.
Caitlin!
Damn it! I was aiming for your head.
So pointy! That is not very nice, lady.
Are you a time traveler?
'Cause those white-girl dreads
came straight from the '90s.
Yeah, what he said.
Although, if you wanna give me
your phone number
we could Netflix and chill...
Impossible.
Well, that's the thing.
I am the impossible.
We built that cell
so you couldn't run your way out.
I didn't run.
I just stood still really fast.
You vibrated faster
than the eye can process.
Like your wife said,
your brain may be smarter than mine,
but your body is still human.
It's over, DeVoe.
Far from it, Mr. Allen.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Flotation mode, activated.
Life raft was a good call, Cisco.
Barry!
There's no sign of DeVoe.
The house is empty. Facial recognition
is not picking up him or his wife.
So, what, he just drowned?
Or he went back
to wherever he was holding Barry.
Why do you think he took you?
I'm not sure, but I think
that he's interested in my powers.
Great. We've got evil Mary Poppins
collecting metas, too.
Yeah, and Amunet won't back down.
Nothing like a lingering threat
to put us all in the Christmas spirit.
Speaking of which, with all this DeVoe
stuff and Cecile being out of town,
I didn't have a chance
to decorate the house.
Do you guys still wanna do Christmas?
Yeah, of course,
we have a lot to celebrate.
Do you mind if I invite Dominic,
that meta we just saved?
The more the merrier.
Let's get some nog.
So, everything worked out, huh?
Yeah, but what if it didn't?
What if he killed you
because of a decision that I made?
Honestly, Barry, I don't know
if I can keep doing this.
Hey, Wells told me about the tough call
you had to make yesterday.
You're gonna have to make
a lot more in the future.
But you made the right call.
And I'm proud of you for making it.
So what now?
Now we have ourselves
a merry little Christmas.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- What the...
- Wow.
Ho, ho, ho. Oh.
Wait.
Like a bowl full of jelly.
Ralph, what is all this?
Well, Joe said
he didn't have any time to decorate
and I wanted to do something nice
for my friends.
I realize that I don't usually say
or do the right thing.
So I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Well, you really went all out,
Ralph, thanks.
It looks great, man, thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
Oh, wow.
Uh, Caitlin.
It was wrong of me to say
that Killer Frost is better than you.
Because the truth is
no one is better than you.
Thank you.
And I know, I'm the one
who saved the day this time.
You know, Cisco, a gift came for you
through one of those death holes
that you call a breach.
Oh, well...
Looks like Gypsy came through, I guess.
- Um...
- Wait.
This is a breakup cube.
I thought things were going so well
with you and Gypsy.
That makes two of us.
Ramon, that's not a breakup cube.
You should open that when you're alone.
No, no, no. If she's gonna break up
with me, I wanna hear why.
- No, Ramon, I wouldn't...
- Cisco,
somebody told me you've been
a very naughty boy this year.
Why don't you come over
and jingle my bells, huh?
Sweet baby Jesus.
Told you, not a breakup cube.
...and I promise it's not gonna be...
You use the same button to...
- Joe, do you mind if I...
- Take that to your house.
Yeah.
No Wally?
He couldn't make it.
- He's still in Blue Valley?
- Cambodia.
Dominic, I'm so glad you came.
Come on in.
This is Joe.
Thank you.
This house is...
Bitchin'?
Festive.
Thanks for the compliment
but who the hell are you again?
He's the guy you just helped save.
Yeah, the meta who can read your mind.
Oh, good. Then he knows that I'm
thinking that there is only room
for one new guy in this group
and that's me.
I'm not here to fight crime
or get a code name.
Just to brainstorm ideas
about my powers.
I hereby christen thee "Brainstorm."
Come on, man.
I've been here for months
and I don't have a name yet.
Uh-oh.
- What? What is it?
- Security at the loft.
It's probably just more gifts
being delivered.
I'll be right back.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Allen.
Dominic?
You really have an acute
sense of detection and wit.
But like I said, Mr. Allen,
you are incapable of seeing
the breadth of my machinations.
DeVoe?
You really should have listened
to your teacher.
How is this possible?
I told you
I have a very important buyer, Dom.
As promised.
Always a pleasure doing business
with another savvy woman.
Please, don't do this to me.
I won't be doing anything to you.
Pleased to meet you, Dominic Lanse.
Or should I say, Subject Six?
I have created many meta-humans
but only your unique abilities
will allow me to do...
This.
You see, Mr. Allen, three months ago
you emerged from the Speed Force
a new man.
And in order for you
and the world to experience my plan,
I, too, needed to be reborn.
If you hurt my family...
I have no interest in your family.
Besides, you're gonna need someone
to miss you when you're gone.
What did you do?
I merely left something for you.
It's a regift, as it were.
I don't have need for it anymore.
Allen! C.C.P.D. Open up.
Open up in there.
Breach, breach, breach!
Don't run.
Move, move, move.
Keep your hands
where I can see them, Barry.
Clear!
Barry Allen, you're under arrest
for the murder of Clifford DeVoe.
Excuse me, I have to go.
But thank you so much.
Of course, thank you for coming.
Merry Christmas to you all.
Merry Christmas.
I told you I would stand beside you.
Always.
Now, let's bring about
the Enlightenment.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::