My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs, I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
To be able to control the
weather like that indoors.
He'd have to be a weather wizard.
- This is Sherloque.
- He's the greatest detective
in all the multiverse.
I'm here to catch your killer.
The only part of the satellite
that would have dark
matter levels that high...
Is the core, which is where
Cicada's dagger came from.
We got a list from FEMA of everyone
who reported injuries the
night of the Enlightenment.
Two of them are twins
whose father is deceased,
third is a ten-year-old girl
by the name of Grace Gibbons.
So if my dad's right and
Cicada's a father, then...
We may have just found his daughter.
Excuse me, could you tell me
where Grace Gibbons' room is?
One sec, let me check.
Actually, yeah, she's that first room
- right on the right.
- Great.
Just where do you think you're going?
Into my patient's room
is what I looks like.
I'm sorry. I am Barry Allen.
I'm with the CCPD.
I was hoping to speak
with you, actually.
I'm looking for Grace Gibbons' parents.
Specifically her father.
I'm sorry, but the girl's
parents are deceased.
Are you sure about that?
I can show you her charts.
See for yourself.
She came in with a
wave of new admissions.
No legal guardian
listed, no next of kin.
The sad truth is,
our staff is the only family
this little girl has left.
Okay.
Thank you for your help.
Orlin Dwyer, are you in there?
It's CCPD. Open up.
- Orlin Dwyer?
- Hey, listen, man,
I don't care what that guy says,
he was drunk and I was defending...
This is about your sister, Mr. Dwyer.
There's been an accident, a meta attack.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- Careful.
- I know, I know.
- This is a critical time.
- Okay.
- Steady hands.
- Yeah.
Call time of death.
It's okay. It's a pie.
It's not supposed to be a piece of cake.
Wow.
Hey, thanks for helping.
With Cicada's trail running cold,
at least we have the
extra day to prepare
for our first Thanksgiving at the loft.
What about Joe and Cecile?
They're celebrating with
Cecile's family this year.
So, yeah, this year it's
just gonna be the five of us.
- I'm down.
- Six, actually.
Killer Frost just RSVP'd.
What... you guys can just
talk to each other now,
even without the mental
activity dampener?
Yeah, today's actually the first time.
Wow.
Oh, gosh.
- Hi, guys.
- Yo.
Sorry we're late. It seems like
everyone and their grandma is getting
pre-holiday manis and pedis.
Ooh, let's take photos and post them
on that old-fashioned Insta
thingy that you guys use.
Those two seemed to have
really patched things up.
Yeah, Nora's getting closer
to Iris than she is with me,
and the timing couldn't
have been better.
What do you mean?
I mean, Nora was so young
when I disappeared in her future,
so this would be her first
memory of Thanksgiving
with both her parents.
Feel like it's my job to make it
the most perfect Thanksgiving ever,
And #HandModels.
Wow, I feel famous already.
Oh, man.
Mom, um...
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what, Nora?
For not giving you a chance
to show me how great you are.
This year I'm just really
thankful to get to know you.
The real you.
I'm thankful too.
You know, the West-Allens have
never missed a Thanksgiving.
No gorilla army, no evil speedster,
no giant wormhole in the sky
could break that streak.
Yeah, the singularity.
So the Flash Museum
has a 3-D model of Dad
just running straight
into it to save the city.
God, it must have been
so epic to be there.
Actually, it was...
terrifying to be there.
We didn't know if your
dad was gonna come back.
Ronnie didn't.
What?
The museum says that... That
Dad just saved everybody.
I guess there's things
the museum left out.
Like your Dad giving
himself to the Speed Force
to save the city.
That was another time we
said good-bye thinking...
might be a one-way trip.
Sounds a lot like what took
him from us in the future.
I didn't know dad had
so many close calls.
Look, your dad is always gonna
wanna put his life on
the line for others.
That is what I love most about him,
but, yeah, it... it
does keep me up at night.
Did he come back?
No, the records I falsified
convinced him for now.
So we're safe?
Orlin, I think you need to stay away.
Good idea.
I won't visit till after the weekend.
No, I think you need
to stay away for good.
It's getting too risky.
You want me to give up Grace?
No, no, no, listen,
you can't put me on hold.
I don't care about
this next of kin crap.
I don't want this kid. Hello?
Hello?
Damn it.
Hey...
what?
It's breakfast.
Yeah, it is. Um...
Okay.
Now look, it's only a few days old.
It's still good, I swear.
I don't understand. Explain again to me
what the difference between this day
and every other day in America?
It's a holiday when we all get together
and celebrate and eat a ton of food.
Like, a gross amount.
Again, what the
difference between this day
and every other day in America.
- That's legit.
- Hi, guys.
- What's going on?
- This guy,
he try to explain the
Thanksgiving holiday.
He's failing miserably.
What is this holiday?
- Please explain.
- It's very simple, actually.
It's just about getting
together to celebrate
our loved ones and family.
So simple, this is why I
don't understand this holiday.
- I don't have any family.
- Didn't you have, like,
- seven marriages?
- I did have seven marriages.
Five wives, seven
marriages, but no family.
This holiday is a cruel holiday.
- What's going on?
- I'm seeing a massive
electrical surge at the
downtown power station.
Barry, Nora, you're up.
Guys, what's the problem?
Everything looks...
I think we found it.
- It's lightning.
- Skies were clear
a minute ago. That storm
must have come out of nowhere.
Uh, we got a bigger problem.
There's an experimental cold fusion core
from Mercury Labs in the
plant, and if it blows...
It could take out the whole block.
I see it.
Nora, you've got to evac all
the workers to safety. Barry...
Yeah, I know, I got to grab the core.
No, no, no, something
doesn't feel right.
Just listen to Iris. Grab
the workers from inside.
Dad!
You guys, he's not breathing.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
She needs to restart his heart.
What... how do I do that?
Rub your hands together
to create lightning,
and then give him a chest compression.
Okay! Okay.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
It's not working!
We lost him.
No! No!
No!
Please. Please. Please.
He's back.
- I promise I'm okay.
- Caitlin.
His vitals are stable.
Speed healing to the rescue.
He shouldn't have needed rescuing.
Nora, I know you're upset,
but if that core would have exploded
it would have caused a lot of damage.
It did cause a lot of damage. Dad died.
We made the best decision we
could, given the circumstances.
Maybe someone else should
be making our decisions.
Wow, all right, well,
so much for mother-daughter holiday time.
She did just have to
bring me back to life.
- Let's give her a minute.
- Okay.
In the meantime, where
did that storm come from?
A storm like that coming and going,
disappearing in a matter of minutes,
it shouldn't be possible.
Unless someone was making it possible.
I mean, we've seen that before.
Weather Wizard. But
Mark Mardon is serving
a life sentence at Iron Heights.
Let's make sure he's doing just that.
Let us know if any
other weather anomalies
pop up on the radar.
Okay.
Will do.
I think it's time for
operation: Save the turkey.
What...?
Art is therapy.
So, Sherlock...
Sherloque, simple pronunciation.
We heard what you had to say
about not having a family.
- Right.
- And we here at Team Flash are
sort of a family, and you're
becoming part of that family,
so we would like to invite you
to celebrate Thanksgiving with us.
Caitlin, I'm afraid that
I must decline, all right?
Because I don't have a
lot of reason to celebrate,
and you of all people
should sympathize with that.
- Why should I sympathize?
- You lost your father, right?
And then you find him only
to discover that his body
is being possessed by a icicle demon
who's trying to kill all of Team Flash,
yourself included. Not great, right?
Okay, that's enough, Debbie Downer.
Don't listen to him. You know what?
Maybe you should lay
off the paint fumes.
Do you know what, young Ralph Macchio?
You have nothing to
celebrate either, right?
What your last year has been, huh?
Let me recap for you. First, heartbreak.
And then second, Cicada
crushes your powers
forcing you to fake your own death,
also not great, and as for me,
multiple divorces have left me
with a mountain of debt
that's insurmountable.
So this past year, not
been very kind to any of us.
Pardon.
She's had a few recent outbursts,
and we don't allow cursing here.
This type of behavior cannot continue.
Anyway, that's the long and short of it.
I'll give you two a moment.
You called a kid a rat bastard?
What's wrong with you? Don't you know
you can't go around
saying stuff like that?
Why?
Well, 'cause then I get a phone call.
You know, I had to take
off work to come down here.
- You don't even like your job.
- What?
You stay on the couch all day,
and then when work calls
you curse and slam the door.
"Rat bastards."
Look, I get where you heard it.
All right, but you
can't say those words.
- Rat bastard!
- Hey, quit it.
- Stop.
- Rat bastards!
- Hey, listen to me!
I'm supposed to be the parent here.
No, you're not a parent!
Parents are supposed to me the
world better for their kids.
You make everything worse. I hate you,
and you hate you too.
You have to excuse our dim lighting.
Today's storm out at the power plant
knocked out our main generator,
So we're working off a
backup for the time being.
So does that mean you can't dampen
the meta prisoners' powers?
Prison-wide dampeners are down,
but we got every inmate into
meta cuffs incident free.
I hope you include that in your
article about our readiness.
After the corruption of the last warden,
I am eager to assure the public
that their safety is in good hands.
Now, our CSI's, which
inmate did you need to see?
And he's been here all day?
Never once out of our sight.
There was a crime committed today
with an MO similar to Mardon's.
Can I take a look at the security tapes?
Anything for our friends in the press.
Well, this is a bust.
Yeah, looks like you died for nothing.
Nora, hey, hey, look.
This has been a rough day for you,
but you can't blame
Iris for what happened.
She's doing the best she can.
Besides, we both decided on the plan.
Oh, I know.
What the...?
Hey, don't mind me.
I'm just here to pick up my dad.
Did she say "dad"?
Joslyn?
It's Joss.
Bring me my father! Now!
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
We'll see about that.
Bring my dad to Porter
Plaza in one hour,
or Central City is gonna get wrecked.
I didn't know that
Joss was busting me out.
I didn't know she'd do
half the things she does.
I haven't spoken to her in years.
And you expect me to believe she woke up
this morning and was like,
"You know what?
I wanna break my dad
out of Iron Heights."
I get it, but it's the truth.
Joss was born when me and her
mom were still in high school.
I never could work out
how to be with that woman.
Then when Joss came,
I thought the best thing to do
was to focus on my career.
Your criminal career?
That's why I left her with her mom.
Least until she ran away
because some of falling out.
What happened with Joss and her mom?
The last time I spoke to her
she told me that her
and Joss are broken.
You know how it is.
Sometimes mothers and daughters break
and there ain't no fixing 'em.
Okay, watch your step.
And open your eyes.
Whose house is this?
It's my cousin Robbie's.
He doesn't live here
anymore, but he said
if I fix it up, we could stay here.
What's this?
That is a dollhouse.
Or it can be
once we build it, and,
you know, you can...
Pick out furniture, and colors,
or wall paper, decorate it how you want.
Hey...
I know we didn't get
off to the greatest start
these past few months.
Okay...
it was a lousy start.
But I want to fix all that.
Well, I was thinking that
while I work on this place,
we could work on this
one too... together.
Listen, you were right, kid.
I do hate me.
I don't really know any other way to be,
but I want to do right by you, Gracie.
I want to keep you
safe, and warm, fed...
You know, just...
give you all the things
a kid should have.
Let's start with the dollhouse.
Okay.
How's Dad's interrogation going?
Well, we'll know in a minute.
Hopefully, he'll find something
that'll help us profile
Mardon's daughter.
Okay, well, let me know.
Nora, look, listen, I
know you're upset with me
for sending your dad into
that situation earlier,
and I just...
- I wanted to say that I...
- Mom, it's okay.
I'm not upset with you.
- You're not?
- No, we're good.
I-I promise.
Okay, cool.
That's the other thing,
celebrating the decimation
of an indigenous culture so
a bunch of greedy colonizers
can get their turkey-lurkey on.
Do you know about this?
Do you know about the sham?
The sham we call "Thanksgiving."
Okay, I'm sorry, am I missing something?
Since when did you guys
become anti-Thanksgiving?
Since a bunch of guys
wearing hat-buckles
fed us some old bull, wrapped in lies,
stuffed in propaganda.
It's a deception Turducken.
Actually, I think the hat-buckles
- weren't real either.
- Don't encourage him.
- You get it.
- Okay.
Did you get anything from Mardon?
No, nothing that'll help
us find his daughter.
What about you guys? What'd you dig up?
Meet Joss Jackam.
She is a delinquent teen
turned amateur storm chaser.
A self-taught expert in
theoretical meteorology.
How do we know she's a storm chaser?
'Cause Helen Hunt here has a blog.
Mm-hmm. She lost her grant
from the Science Center
for doing too many dangerous
experiments on the weather.
Well, look like she's way
beyond the experimental phase.
Ooh, Weather Witch?
I'll allow it.
Dad, that weathervane,
doesn't it look a lot like...
The staff she was carrying, yeah.
Cisco, can you pull
up the security footage
from her attack on Iron Heights?
Sure can.
It's infected with a satellite shard.
She's got meta-tech. Like
Spencer Young's phone.
Look, she has instant
lightning on command.
There's no way you're gonna be able
to get that staff from her.
She's gonna have to
give it up willingly.
Okay, listen, we got 20 minutes
before she destroys the entire city,
so what is the plan?
We only have one choice.
We give her what she wants.
No Weather Witch in sight.
Okay, Singh cleared the perimeter,
so it's free of civilians.
And our satellites are on weather watch
for our Weather Witch. Nothing yet.
What?
I wouldn't say nothing.
My data leaves me to conclude
that there is artificially-created
pressure system of uncertain origin
headed rapidement
toward the downtown core.
Listen, Galileo, you
can lick your finger
and stick it in the wind all you want.
Why don't you leave
the actual calculations
to actual compu...
Oh, for Christ's sake.
And your exasperation
leads me also to conclude
that you have realized, although late,
that once again I'm right.
I'm right. I'm right.
I'm right. I'm right...
That's enough out of you.
She's here.
So the rotten apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
You're a poet. Awesome.
Where's my dad?
All right, Joss, we held
up our end of the bargain.
You got your dad.
There's no reason to hurt anybody...
Ah, so boring. Come on.
We'll handle it from here.
Hey, baby girl.
Dad.
That's a pretty cool staff.
Would you just... how
about you just power
that thing off for a
sec and let your dad try.
Try this.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh, oh, don't feel bad.
He was a selfish dick
who abandoned his family.
Anyway, thanks for helping
me drop a truck on my dad.
Uh... guys?
What now?
I didn't see the hummer coming.
I'm so pissed!
This city will drown,
crumble, burn, because of you!
Thanks.
I'm gonna follow her.
Wait, are you serious right now?
- What?
- You almost just died.
Again, and you don't seem to care.
Where is this coming from?
You know how dangerous our job is.
Yeah, but I don't
want to lose you again,
but you don't seem to
give a damn if you lose me,
and... and all for your job.
Nora.
How long you been holding that one in?
My best guess...
my whole life.
Growing up without
you, I was so angry...
but you were my hero, so...
it was easier to put my
anger for you not being around
on criminals and meta-villains...
a lot of times on Mom.
But when I saw you die today
it reminded me that
I'm mad at someone
else about losing you...
you.
I get it.
It's not easy having a parent
who puts their life
on the line for others.
I remember feeling
the same way about Joe
- being a cop when I was a kid.
- No, it's not the same thing.
Did he ever have to say
good-bye to you knowing
that he wasn't coming back?
You did...
and you're gonna do it again.
Nora, you got to remember
you're talking about
a future that we might be able to avoid.
We still have time to
find our way to a solution,
and we will.
But there is a solution.
It's just one that you don't want.
Give up being The Flash.
Come on. It's the only way to guarantee
that you won't disappear
again in the future,
or any other time.
- Nora.
- Come on. Think about it.
You're not the only hero.
Let the others protect the world.
You don't have to keep
sacrificing yourself.
You give your life again and again.
How many times does it have to be you?
It hurt so much
losing you when I didn't even know you,
but now after all of these months
getting to know you I just...
Please, Dad, don't make
me go through it again.
I don't want to go through it again.
Nora, people need The Flash.
I need my dad.
This is the third ice
cream of the day, you know?
Something fishy's going on here.
Okay, you got me.
We're celebrating
because this is a very special day.
One year ago today,
I made you a promise
that I would turn my life around
and make things better for you.
I can honestly say that my life
is a million times
better than what it was.
And it's all because of you, Gracie.
So I got you something.
It's the set I wanted.
I thought your little
dollhouse could use a family.
I already have one.
I love you, kiddo.
Purple.
You know, I think four ice
creams in a day would be the...
Gracie, run.
Run. Run. Come on!
Go this way! Go this way!
Help me!
Help me, please!
- Sir.
- Somebody!
Save her, please.
Get him on a table.
Move!
Gracie...
Help her...
On the eve of Thanksgiving,
reports of devastating
weather phenomena
are streaming in from all over the city.
The exact cause of these
disturbances remains unknown.
I can't believe she's actually willing
to level the city to kill one man.
She doesn't know where Mardon is.
It's overkill, but it's the
only option we've left her.
Well, Caitlin's on radar,
and Cisco's trying to
juice the satellites,
but there's interference.
We can't locate Joss.
You okay?
Look, babe, you're gonna find the words
to make her understand. I know it.
Not sure I have the words
to make myself understand.
She's got a point.
We got a hit on Joss.
She's at Sheldon County Airport.
Barry, you got to move.
- You're good?
- Barry, do you have eyes on Joss?
No, she's damaged the terminal so badly
the hangar's the only safe place.
I'm evacuating everyone
trapped on the tarmac.
I think I can bring Frost out.
- What can we do?
- Flood control down at the Marina.
Guys, how do we fight weather?
We fight weather with weather.
Nora.
We still have Mardon's weather wand.
I need you to get it from the archives
and take it to Barry, okay?
Okay.
- Hey.
- Mardon's wand?
- Cisco says you can use it
to counteract Joss's weather.
Where is she?
Last chance. Where's my dad?
Joss, you know we can't give him up.
Then you know what happens next.
Joss, I deceived you, okay? Not them.
You want make someone pay, it's me.
This is how you make heroes pay!
By the beard of Zeus, she's making
a tornado out of lightning.
Cisco, how do I use
this wand to stop this?
You can attract all the
lightning to the wand.
That'll take down the
tornado, but all that energy
will go through your body.
You'll be a human lightning rod.
It's okay.
I know you have to go.
Run, Dad.
Run!
Back. Everybody, back.
Barry? Nora, do you see him?
I, uh...
I...
I see him. He's still here.
We live in a world full of meta-phones
and meta-weathervanes.
What's next? My electric toothbrush?
Till we figure out how
to remove those shards,
- better safe than sorry.
- Yeah.
Well, now that Mardon and his daughter
are all tucked away in Iron Heights.
What do you say we spend
some time with our own family?
Well, might just be
us and Nora this year.
Caitlin and Cisco are
skipping Thanksgiving.
What? Why?
- Don't even ask.
- What?
- A toast to...
- Mm-hmm.
The thankless.
- The thankless!
The thankless!
Allez-oop.
- Mm.
Aw.
All right, boys, I'm tapping in.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You two losers are sitting here
in what I can only assume
is the cantina of a starship,
drinking and eating terrible food
when you could be drinking
and eating amazing food
with people who actually care about you.
All right, all right, look.
When you put it like that...
- She has a good point.
- You have a good point, yeah.
And, by the way, I have the
least to celebrate this year
because I spent most of it unconscious.
You nerds come to Thanksgiving, or what?
So it wasn't so much the
taste as it was the crunch.
Wait, are you actually saying...
Yes, that was the year I found out
why Grandma Esther's
yams tasted so good,
because she never cleaned
her favorite skillet.
I take it this was also the year
you stopped eating
Grandma Esther's yams?
Uh-uh, I didn't say all that.
Allow me to propose a toast.
Well, first to clean dishware,
and also to... to family, all right,
and to friends, old and new.
And to the colonizers
who conquered this land...
- What?
- And...
- the colonizers who grabbed...
- Remember... no...
What they want, they
just take what they want.
- Yes, I know, but our...
- To taking what you...
That's not... you know what? Let's go.
- Right now.
- Okay, you know what?
I think that it's time
to go carve a turkey.
Great.
Nora.
Um, we didn't have a chance
to talk since the airport.
Oh, Dad, I know what you're gonna say,
and you don't have to.
I saw what it was like
when you hesitated to save those people
because of me, and I felt...
- Horrible?
- Yeah.
And I never want to
feel like that again.
I get it.
Sometimes you have to sacrifice
yourself to save others.
Even if it means leaving
your family behind.
Not exactly.
Look, when I ran into
that storm I was thinking
I want to save everyone, but...
the person I was thinking
about the most was you.
- Me?
- Yeah.
I don't choose being The Flash
over being with my family.
I'm The Flash for my family,
and I don't have to run to the future
to understand why I sacrificed myself.
I'd do it to save you, and your mom,
all the people I love.
You know, maybe one
day if I train enough,
I'll be able to save you.
I don't doubt it.
- All right, come on.
- Okay.
- Ah, yes.
- All right.
- Hey, thank God.
- Carve the turkey.
- Yeah, baby.
- Here we are.
- Each person gets a turkey.
- No.
- Oh.
- We have the one for everyone.
- You all right?
- Just Dad with a knife,
it's a little... It's the most fun part.
Oh, you're very good at that.
Am I?
Orlin.
I told you it's too risky.
CCPD's already looking for
you. What are you doing here?
It's Thanksgiving, Doc. I'm
here to be with my family.
I want you to be optimistic,
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
As far as how long,
with all the brain
hemorrhaging she suffered,
you have to prepare
yourself for the possibility
that she may never wake.
This is all my fault.
No, it's these metas.
Wreaking havoc unchecked.
She didn't deserve this, Mr. Dwyer,
and neither did you.
This was the scene Tuesday
night as, once again,
The Flash saved Central City
from certain destruction.
After a world-wide power outage
blanketed every country in darkness,
a bizarre purple...
The destructive
phenomenon emanated
from a satellite that had fallen
into a decaying orbit.
Thankfully, before the
satellite could strike
the city and create
what scientists believe
would have been "a
catastrophic event,"
The Flash was able to destroy it.
Once again, residents of our proud city,
and perhaps the entire
world owe The Flash
and his allies...
A new meta was last seen
jumping off a building
in order to evade capture
after stealing jewels...
It was reported that he
escaped Flash's grasp
after hijacking an armored vehicle.
I'm gonna make this right, Gracie.
Every meta...
will die.
Guys, this better be good.
Yeah, we've got an
after-Thanksgiving tradition
called sleeping, so what's up?
It's good. Trust us. Detective.
Well, it occurred to me that if you,
monsieur and madam West-Allen,
you want to spend this
holiday with your family.
Well, perhaps your
meta-killer does as well.
So I had monsieur Cisco
hack into the CCTV footage
of the hospital and this what we got.
Ever since Grace arrived,
only one man has come to visit her.
Every day.
Including tonight.
Team Flash, I give you...
Orlin Dwyer, also known as...
Cicada.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --