My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on “The Flash”...
We've got Turtle locked
up in the Pipeline.
All we got to do is
use him to figure out
how to steal Zoom's speed.
That might take longer than we thought.
- Why's that?
- Because Turtle's dead.
You need to figure out
what triggers your vibes.
Sometimes it's when I touch something
that belongs to a breacher;
sometimes it just happens.
There's always a cause.
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
I'm here.
You want me to leave
everything I have here?
I mean, my life...
You don't have a life here anymore.
Zoom is too powerful.
Close it. Close it now.
- No!
- Augh!
Jay's death was not in vain.
We will meet Zoom again.
And the next time, I will beat him,
whoever that monster is.
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Uh, it didn't look this deep on the map.
That's 'cause maps are flat.
This is, like, 1,000 feet deep.
Well, you want to get faster.
Maybe plummeting to your death
is the motivation you need.
So to reach escape velocity,
you're gonna have to go...
that fast.
Well, that fast is impossible.
I can promise you that.
Ah, “Nothing in life is
promised except death”"
- Edgar Allan Poe?
- Kanye West.
If it makes you feel any
better, Evel Knievel
cleared a line of cars
that was twice this long,
and he didn't even have superpowers,
unless you count that sweet-ass ride.
- Do you hear yourself?
- What?
Look, you're gonna be fine.
I'm 80% sure of it.
- Okay.
- 76.
Like, a strong 72.
I can't stop, Caitlin, help.
If you don't feel ready, you
probably shouldn't do it.
Not helpful.
Look, Zoom's still out there.
And once I find a way back to Earth-2,
I have to be faster than him.
And, I mean, right now... I wasn't even
fast enough to save Jay.
I have to try.
He's gonna make it.
- No!
- Oh, damn.
“Why'd you have to bring
those drones along, Cisco”"
“Oh, I don't know.”
You're welcome, everyone.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Signed projects, including releases
of solo albums.
Pop music would never be the same
after Beyoncé left Destiny's Child.
Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
They mean Senator Knowles?
Scooch.
What?
So how'd it go?
Well, he's not a red splat
on the side of a mountain.
That's our new definition of success?
It's one of them.
So, you didn't make the canyon jump?
No. What else can we try?
A bigger canyon?
Okay, fine, no more canyons.
I know I crack this.
I've just been going about it wrong.
I need to find my leg up.
Have we factored in drag?
Wells, can we rerun the simulation?
Let it go for now.
Zoom's still out there.
He's terrorizing a whole world
full of people, your world.
You know, I'm not doing this for fun.
Barry, we've been working
on this all week.
You're tired, we're tired.
Yeah, what we need is some downtime.
Downtime leads to
increased productivity,
ergo we have to have fun.
And the best way to have fun
is for us to go out to the club.
Am I right, Team Flash?
Let's get turnt!
No, but seriously, we need a break.
You know, I think Cisco's right,
and if I'm saying we need a break,
then you know it's serious.
All right, let's go out tonight.
Oh, yeah. Can I go?
Over my dead body.
Look, just 'cause you're
stuck in this lab all day
doesn't mean I should be too.
Over my rotting corpse.
Look, what happened to trying
new things, meeting new people?
You said I should start
a life here, right?
And Zoom's over there,
and we're over here,
so there's nothing to worry about.
There's always something to worry about.
Okay, well, you said Barry
and them are good people
and I should get to know them.
- I did.
- Yeah.
And you know they'll keep
me safe no matter what.
Look, I have a life to live, Dad,
and whole world to explore.
Please?
Fine.
But if you're gonna go, you
should take protection.
Oh, Dad,
I don't need... I don't
know what you thought
I was gonna be doing, but I...
Oh, right.
I mean, is it necessary?
It's kind of, you know...
Or I could always build you
an inescapable daughter cube.
Funny.
You know I'd get out though, right?
All right, fine. I'll do it.
Thank you.
Oh, God, sorry. It keeps doing that.
My dad made me wear it.
Don't worry about it. It's all good.
I'm really glad you came, Jesse,
even though this place
is less than ideal.
Hey, toast?
To Jay.
I wonder what Jay would say
if he was here right now.
“What's a Kamikaze”"
And then you'd spend ten
minutes explaining it.
And he'd say, “Just kidding.
We have those on Earth-2.”
Yeah, well, we don't have those, so...
Eh-eh, I'm sorry, Miss Underage.
None of us plan on getting
murdered by your father tonight.
- Oh, whatever, he's all talk.
- Mm-hmm.
Yo, guys, what's up?
- Hey.
Glad you could make it.
What's up, Wally?
Hey, interesting choice of venue.
The tic-tac-toe theme is cool.
- Barry picked it.
- Cisco picked it.
- I...
- For real?
Yeah, I picked it. I don't go out much.
It had four stars on Yelp, so...
- Okay, fair enough.
- So who's this?
This is Wally. He's my...
foster, or step... adopted...
My new... this is... he's my new friend.
This is Jesse.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
So, Jesse, are you new in town?
Yeah, you could say that.
Yeah, me too. Are you from far away?
Like you wouldn't believe.
Oh, you know what?
Would you just excuse me?
I just need to go powder my... watch.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, so I know I'm
practically your brother,
and I'm, like, half Jay's
size, but you want to dance?
- Sure.
- Come on, let's go.
Stupid watch.
All right, buddy, you have
beeped your last beep.
Something else rising also,
some dark instinct about what I would do
to the person who had taken you,
the things I would do.
So how's Wally doing?
Yeah, he's good; he's just
diving into his schoolwork.
- Good.
- Yeah.
I'm glad.
Oh, God.
Promise me if we ever do get married,
you will not do that
dance at our wedding.
Oh, I can promise you that.
I mean, not the wedding, the dancing.
What?
I don't know; I just think it's weird
that were married in the
future and on Earth-2.
I wonder what our married
doppelgangers are doing tonight.
Probably Earth-2's equivalent
of “Netflix and chill.”
Sounds nice. I mean, for them.
- It was The Flash!
- My wallet's gone.
Someone took my purse.
Who the hell are you?
Okay, I got it. Thanks, man.
- Hey.
- Hey, excuse me.
What happened last night?
I know you didn't rob these people.
No, I was bored. Thought
I'd have some fun.
Well, look, whoever did
this, they got everyone
within a ten-block radius
in under six minutes.
You couldn't catch them?
No, this speedster's
faster than me, I guess.
Unbelievable. Hey, babe.
Hey, so I spoke to that girl over there.
She snapped a photo of the red blur.
- Look familiar?
- This is not good.
I know, it looks exactly like the photo
I took of you last year.
Don't worry, we'll figure it out.
- We always do.
- Hey.
Oh, it's work. I've got to go.
Keep me posted, okay?
Joe, I don't want people
thinking The Flash
is a petty thief.
Well, we need to get to
work squashing those rumors
before they spread.
Here it is, people: evidence
that The Flash has gone rogue.
Couldn't it be the
speedster in the helmet?
The photo speaks for itself.
No helmet glare, confirming that
this is The Scarlet Speedster.
We're gonna expose him as a fraud.
McKay, I want you at
the police department
getting any interview you can.
Okay, on it.
Williams, eyewitness encounters.
The people of this city need to know
what it feels like to
be robbed by a hero.
West, I want you to do a piece
on it from your perspective.
You were there last night.
You've seen him in action.
Okay, but why would The
Flash need to make off
with a couple of hundred bucks
when he's saved so many lives?
I mean, he is actually a hero.
Iris, you're a smart woman.
You can't be that naive.
We live in a city full of meta-humans
who continually do whatever they want,
The Flash included.
Write it up,
his journey from streak to freak,
due on my desk tomorrow.
So... fun night?
Before all the chaos broke loose?
Then I would do anything
to get you back,
including killing a man.
Tell me I'm not hearing this right.
No, that's true.
Zoom had you.
Zoom needed The Flash's speed.
And it was him or you.
And I was not going to lose you.
You know, you were my hero.
My dad, the brilliant scientist
who could accomplish
anything he put his mind to.
He taught me I could
never dream too big.
But now...
now you're a killer,
and I barely recognize you at all.
- Jesse...
- No, no, no.
Don't... don't worry.
I'm not going far.
I mean, where did this
speedster even come from?
I don't know, man.
All I know is that blur made
60 smackeroos off of me.
Ridiculous.
Maybe it's another one of
Zoom's henchmen somehow?
The breaches are closed.
The only other way to become a speedster
is from a particle
accelerator explosion.
Okay, but then why only
make yourself known now?
You see what I'm saying?
We'd have had to seen
them in action before.
I'm not saying it makes
sense; I'm just saying
that's the only other way
to become a speedster.
Actually, there's another way.
It's called Velocity-9.
Ooh, that's a sexy-ass name. What is it?
It's a speed drug.
Jay took it when you were on Earth-2
to save the city from a meta-human.
What? How could you not tell me this?
I promised Jay I wouldn't.
Jay, what do you... why?
Because Jay knew how
dangerous this drug is.
I should know, Barry; Snow
and I worked on it together.
Guys, I have been busting
my butt out there,
pushing myself to the limit,
trying to get better,
trying to be faster,
and you're telling me that
there's been something
this whole time that could've helped me?
This could've helped me take down Zoom.
It could have helped me
save Earth-2 Joe, save Jay.
Jay was sick.
The drug that he took
to regain his speed
was also causing cellular degeneration.
It was killing him.
I tried to help, I tried to find a cure,
but in all my experiments, the
effects were just temporary.
The V-9 is deadly.
Why not tell me this? Why
keep me in the dark?
Caitlin.
Where am I?
- Are you okay?
- Did you vibe?
Uh...
Meta-human.
Yeah, social media app for the win.
Bad Flash is back.
Bad Flash... what?
No. I'm losing my touch over here.
He's coming up on Fifth and Everett.
You can use the alley to cut him off.
A lady speedster?
It only took us two years,
but we finally got one,
a lady speedster.
Hey, here's a question for
you, purely scientific,
was she good-looking?
You know, I was a little busy
getting my ass handed to me,
so I didn't really notice.
Right, right, right, but, you know,
next time, for science?
Okay, yeah, next time she
punches me in the face,
I'll be sure to get her number.
There you go.
But the question remains, who is she?
I have no idea.
We could run her through
the facial recognition.
She had a mask on.
- What was her suit like?
- Hey.
- Hey, it's a valid question.
- It is, actually.
How was her suit constructed?
It was good. It was very good.
It was like mine.
It was made by somebody
who understands the
needs of a speedster.
So that would be someone with
access to tech and a lab.
Oh, no. I'm having a very bad thought.
When I designed V-9,
I was having trouble formatting
the extracellular matrix,
so I called a colleague
of mine at Mercury Labs
for some assistance, Eliza Harmon.
She knows how to make this speed drug?
No, I followed the protocols
of information compartmentalization.
I only gave her three
of the eight components
necessary for V-9's structure.
Okay, so she didn't
have the full recipe.
Unless she reverse
engineered her own V-9.
Eliza's a genius, but that's way
out of character for her.
Well, it's worth taking a look.
I'll go see her.
Hey, I'm coming too.
Great.
I'm gonna go train.
Knock-knock.
Am I hallucinating, or is that disgraced
ex-Mercury employee Caitlin Snow?
Eliza Harmon, burning the midnight oil.
Don't you ever take a break?
Well, you know what they
say, these thiocyanate ions
won't bond themselves.
- Hi.
Who is your handsome friend?
- Detective Joe West, ma'am.
- Detective?
What brings you around these parts?
Well, that's a funny story.
You know how there's a
speedster that's been
wreaking havoc on the city?
Yeah, I heard The Flash went nuts.
Fame will do it to you.
I guess some people can't
handle the limelight, right?
Well, we happen to know
it was someone else.
That's why we're here looking into this.
Wow, how very “Law &
Orde”" of you, Caitlin.
Do you remember that formula
that you were helping me
with a few months ago?
Yeah, vaguely.
We think that it was somehow involved.
How? What did you have me working on?
It's classified,
but let's just say it was
some kind of enhancement,
and we're afraid that
my research was stolen.
Not from this lab.
Okay, between you and me, the
place is pretty vulnerable.
Ever since that break-in
a few months ago,
some of us think McGee
hasn't sufficiently
stepped up security, but I
kept my research on lock
and destroyed the originals
when it was given back to you.
But hey, you're free to look
around my lab if you want.
I don't think that'll be necessary.
Sorry. I wish I could be more help.
It's okay. It's actually
kind of a relief.
Will you call me if you
hear anything, though?
Of course. That's what friends are for.
Thank you.
So what do you think?
For now, we take her at her word.
West, how's your article coming?
Um, great.
I have a source who knows for a fact
that this speedster is not The Flash
but an imposter.
Ah, who's your source?
I am not at liberty to say.
Well, if you can't tell me your source,
I'm running the original story.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're right; what's one unnamed source
compared to dozens of eyewitnesses?
Honestly, I'm just...
I'm having a hard time
wrapping my head around
your vision for the story.
Something isn't adding up.
How about we talk about it some more?
Grab some coffee? What you say?
Coffee? Right now?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, a little caffeine
never hurt anybody, right?
Sure.
I'm so tired.
Oh, well, you've been
pushing yourself too hard.
No, not hard enough.
I'm sick of always being passed over
for the grant, for the promotion.
I'm underpaid and understaffed
and six months behind on my research.
That's why I started all of this.
Your problem is you're too
much of a perfectionist.
You don't have to be.
There's beauty in chaos.
I don't have time for chaos.
This was supposed to fix things,
and it ended up making it worse.
Oh, silly girl.
You know it makes you feel better
to blow off some steam.
You will say anything for a fix.
It's your fault we're hooked.
It's Caitlin's fault;
if she didn't want us
to find out what she was working on,
she shouldn't have made it so damn easy.
There's not enough for both of us.
We... we need to save
it for an emergency.
You take it now; worry
about getting more later.
You'll thank me.
I know what's best for us
and where to get more.
Whatcha doing?
- Training.
- Training?
Allen, don't be stupid.
I know you took the V-9, Allen.
- No I haven't.
- Oh, no?
No.
I took it, but I haven't taken it yet.
- Good.
- Tell me why I shouldn't.
Figure it out.
If the game is already rigged,
why can't I level the playing field?
I mean, if everybody else is cheating,
how can... I want to be fast enough
to stop Zoom and any speedster
that tries to hurt my friends.
Shouldn't I use everything
in my power to do that?
You want to take a
shortcut; is that right?
You want to take a shortcut?
Remember this.
You lose a chunk of your humanity
every time you compromise your values.
Sorry, that's really
good coming from you.
So don't be like me.
Be better.
Be like Jay.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, any luck locating our speedster
since Eliza checked out?
I'm still working on it, but...
Hey!
Time to have some fun.
Hey! Cisco! Hey, Joe!
Hey, she's got me in the Pipeline!
- What do you want?
- Where's the V-9, Caity?
I need a fix.
Eliza, is that you?
Oh, Eliza's not here right now.
My name is Trajectory.
Oh, why do the crazy ones
always name themselves?
Look, Eliza, Velocity-9
is very dangerous, okay?
It made a friend of mine very sick,
and he already had the
speed force in him.
Look, your cellular system...
Enough!
You are boring me to death.
Hand over the V.
I'm a physician. I took an oath.
I can't give you anything
that will hurt you.
Right, so either hand over the V,
or the cat guy gets it.
Oh!
Hey, move, now.
Look, all the flasks are gone.
There's nothing left.
Hey, I was really hoping
you wouldn't make me do
one of those “I have to
kill you each one by one
until you give me what I want.”
Oh, well.
Wait.
You want V-9?
We'll make it for you.
Dad, you can't.
We have all the ingredients.
I'm not a patient person,
so better move fast.
Ah, latte for me, and a Flash for you.
Wow, this guy even gets a
drink named after him.
Yes, he does; he's saved
a lot of people's lives.
They just want to show
their appreciation.
A little too much, if you ask me.
Why can't you see what
everyone else sees?
A few years back, I won
the Dornfeld Award
for Investigative Reporting
for my story on corruption
in the mayor's office.
I investigated a man
that everyone loved.
The mayor was young,
telegenic, a former war hero.
He was voted in with
overwhelming popular support.
It was...
But... but I knew that his
campaign was bought and paid for
by the mob.
Okay, but not everyone
is a corrupt mayor.
But I saw him for what everyone else
was too blind to see.
Everyone wants a hero.
Yeah, but in this case, The
Flash actually is one.
Iris, Iris, it's our job
to ensure that people, even heroes,
are held accountable for their actions.
So I'm guessing
on your list of dating pros and cons,
being anti-Flash is a major dealbreaker.
Dating pros and...
did you think that this...
Oh, what? No, no.
No, forget what I said. I get it.
You just wanted to talk about
the story some more...
To stall.
Right, because you're trying to get out
of writing this article altogether.
Scott, wait, please don't leave.
I'm sorry, I didn't
know that this was...
Why would you?
Excuse me.
It's what you wanted.
Now let her go.
How do I know the two of you
didn't lace this with a
sedative to put me on my ass?
We wouldn't do that.
You can never be too safe, right?
No!
Thanks for the fix, Snow.
- Get Barry.
- Are you okay?
Well, good job on the cell, Cisco.
Jesse.
- What happened?
- Turn her on her side.
Eliza shot her up with V-9.
She's going into shock. It's too pure.
Stay with me, Jesse. Stay with me.
What do we do?
We've got to get the
V-9 out of her system.
She needs a blood transfusion.
The new blood will flush the
drug out of her system.
- What blood type is she?
- PZ negative.
Yeah, that's not a thing
on this Earth, man.
I'm a match.
Jesse.
Hey.
What happened?
We... you're fine. You're...
you're gonna be fine.
We got the drug out of your system.
Oh.
Looks like you saved the day again.
Look, honey, I know
that this isn't enough.
I promise you, though,
I'm going to spend the rest of my life
making it up to you for the...
for that terrible thing that I did.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
And how many more terrible things
are you gonna do to protect me?
What does that mean?
I mean, everything that you do
and everything that
you have done for me,
it's so dark, and... and
you don't even see it.
I mean, you didn't even
hesitate out there.
Of course not.
I'm not going to lose you, Jesse.
Okay, but you just gave
that crazy speedster
everything she wanted
without even blinking,
without even thinking
what other lives could be at stake.
It is my job to keep you safe,
to protect you; that's my job.
That's all that matters.
Well, maybe it shouldn't be.
Caitlin, I know she was
your friend and all,
but homegirl has gone cuckoo bird.
Now she's out there with more V-9.
What she doesn't know is,
I put in micro tracker
in the drug.
Hmm, that's a brilliant idea.
You can run, but you can't hide.
I'm the one to blame for all this,
so I need to help fix it.
There's plenty of blame
to go around, Snow.
What's her location?
Central City bridge.
Why is she running back and forth?
Villains gonna vill.
She's creating friction,
and at that vibration and speed...
- What?
- Complete chaos.
She could destroy that whole bridge.
And everyone on it.
Guys, this bridge is coming down.
Barry, there's about 200 people
on that bridge right now.
You're ruining all my fun.
Trajectory's too far away.
You won't get to her
running across the river.
I will if I jump.
Barry, to make that jump,
you'll need to go Mach 3.3,
but only for a second.
Okay.
Yeah, buddy!
It's over, Eliza.
It is never over.
Wait, hey!
Stop doing this to yourself.
You don't actually want to hurt anyone.
You don't know anything about me.
No, I know you're not a bad person.
This is the V-9 in your system.
I also know what it feels
like to want to be the best.
It makes you feel like
there's not enough time
to accomplish things the right way,
but it's a cop-out.
And this is killing you.
Look at yourself, Eliza.
You're not well.
Let us help you, please.
That is all the help I need.
How does it feel to
know that I am faster
than you will ever be?
See you around.
The lightning, it's turning blue.
Your article was well-written.
Thank you.
You know, it's a lot easier to write
when it's the truth.
Not every hero is a fraud.
It's okay to believe in them.
So I've been told.
And sometimes, even great journalists,
smart and brilliant journalists,
can misread situations.
And sometimes they can
be caught off guard.
Look, about the other night,
it... it just surprised me.
But once the surprise
went away, I, uh...
Not a dealbreaker.
Noted.
Okay.
Hey, have you seen Jesse?
No.
Hey, Dad.
It's me.
Listen, your job over the years
has been to shield me from harm.
But now it's my turn to go
out into this new world
on my own, no shield,
and discover what this Earth can offer.
You know, you are the best
teacher I've ever had,
but I don't know what
more you can teach me.
I love you.
Please, don't come looking for me.
So Eliza just evaporated
from running too fast?
Looks like cellular
degeneration, same as Jay's.
Jay warned us V-9 was dangerous.
At least now we know why.
You find Jesse?
She went out.
Barry, what is it?
It's just right before
Eliza disappeared,
her lightning, it turned blue.
Right.
What if it's a side effect of the V-9?
Yeah, but Jay took Velocity-9,
and his lightning didn't turn blue.
About how fast was he running?
Not as fast as Eliza.
All right, so what if V-9 is
what turns your lightning blue?
I mean, that would explain why
Zoom is so much faster than me.
If that's true, then that
means he's sick, right?
He's dying.
That's why he wants your speed.
He's dying, and he needs a cure.
Same as Jay.
No.
Jay? No.
See, he died right in front of us.
Zoom killed him right in front of us.
Cisco, we've seen a speedster be
in two places at once before.
Then I guess there's
one way to find out.
I guess now would be a good time
to tell you all I've been vibing Zoom.
What?
You... for how long?
It started when we
closed the last breach.
And every time it's happened,
I've been near that thing.
We need to know.
Oh, no.
No, no...
I saw Jay.
He's Zoom.
Barry!
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -