My name is Barry Allen,
and I'm the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
This has been a really amazing date, Flash.
Cecile, thanks for stopping by.
Hey, anything for my favorite detective.
You restored the timeline, and things were different?
Exactly.
Jesse, you're a speedster.
When I came back, things weren't the same.
You mean people.
Yeah.
How do I look?
Better.
How much?
Do we really need to ask that question?
Our take wasn't that big.
Big enough.
But the only question you should be asking is,
what size rock you want dangling from this beautiful neck?
A kiss from you makes my world spin.
You're so full of it, you know that?
I got to be honest.
I never understood... this.
But like my sister says,
anyone can stoop over and pick up nothing.
What do you want, Snart?
I told you two to sit on your cut for a while,
until things cool down.
Some of us like to actually spend the cash
we get from these jobs.
Not when it's from the ones with me.
You didn't pull 'em off yourself.
Without us, you'd still be kicking down liquor stores.
I think you've spent too much time
staring at yourself in the mirror,
because your perception of reality is a bit warped.
You know the rules.
I don't give a damn about your rules,
or laying low.
There's no one in this city who can stop us.
Including you, Snart.
It sounds to me like you're saying you want out.
Guess so.
Well, if you're out...
you're out.
No!
You lost, Scudder.
Sam!
Go.
Go!
Sam?
Give me a hand here.
Demo starts in a month. Get everything out of here.
The hell?
Where's Snart?
This is from a security camera inside Iron Heights.
Forensic analysis indicates that the footage is genuine,
no evidence of tampering.
And we're pretty sure this is Doctor Alchemy that did this?
The last thing Clariss said before he died.
Unless someone else killed him.
Like a meta with telekinesis or cloaking abilities.
We've got both on our Earth.
So what do we do now?
Our meta-human specialist at CCPD,
Julian Albert, he prefers to work alone,
but I got feelers out on his investigation.
I'm gonna go there now and see if he dug up anything.
All right.
Okay, well, until then, you guys want to train?
Well, now, we have to think about getting back to our Earth.
We've been here long enough.
I've still got a lot to learn.
Your words, not mine.
I...
fine.
Well, if you want to train,
let's train...
speedster style.
Damn, Jesse's almost as fast as Barry.
Velocity's just under Mach 3.
Heart rate, 100 BPMs. Her vitals are normal.
Yeah, no, we already know all that.
Cisco, we need to test her reflexes.
Can we test her reflexes?
Patience, Harry, patience.
If anyone's gonna teach Jesse the ways of the Speed Force--
- It's Barry. - Thank you.
Okay. Well, that wasn't very heroic.
Nope.
But there is a lesson in there somewhere.
What's that?
The difference between having powers and having precision.
Well, what do you mean?
I mean, it's gonna take more than speed
to take down some of these metas.
You got to think, anticipate.
When you enter a new environment,
you got to case every inch of it.
You never run in blind.
Oh, my God.
I've become Oliver.
Maybe we should stay a little bit longer.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's gonna take some time to master your powers, Jesse.
- You'll get the hang of it. - Yeah, I know, thanks.
Well, since I will be here for a while,
do you want to get out of here?
- Where to? - Does it matter?
No touching.
Not what I meant by staying longer!
I should probably get back to CCPN.
- All right. - I'll see you tonight?
- Can't wait. - Okay.
- Hey, Harry. - Yeah?
Are you really sure you have to leave?
Just a lot I still have to fix on my Earth.
Yeah, but you know it's more fun
when you're here helping us fix stuff on our Earth.
He is right.
It hasn't been the same without you.
The team doesn't feel complete without Harrison Wells.
Then change that.
There's a whole multiverse of Harrison Wells
out there at your fingertips.
You want one? Let's go get one.
Yeah, now I remembered it.
Thank you, Officer Mayer.
So sorry. I got held up at the courthouse.
No problem.
You're the one doing me the favor.
Yeah, I wouldn't thank me just yet.
Oh, you couldn't find anything.
Nope, no one at the DA's office
knows anything about anybody named Alchemy.
Oh, damn.
This is, um...
Meta-human related, I assume?
- It appears to be. - Yikes.
- I know. - Okay.
You let me know if there's anything I can do for you, yeah?
Yeah, thanks for bringing it yourself, Cecile.
It was my pleasure.
This is really nice.
Staying in is so much better than going out.
- When you have jobs like ours? Yes. - Yes.
What?
You're just really handsome.
You are not so bad yourself.
I thought...
I didn't think you were gonna be home for a while, right?
My plans changed.
Unfortunately. I'm just gonna go upstairs.
You can have a beer, sit with us.
Have a good night.
I-I know.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I-I... should we rain check, or...
Barry, I am not upset because our date got interrupted.
- That, I understand. - What do you mean?
You, speeding away when my dad walks in.
- Yeah. - Because, what, we're kissing?
Yeah, Iris, exactly.
What, you don't want to kiss me?
Of course I want to kiss you.
But not in front of him.
What does that matter?
He's your... he's our...
Joe.
Joe. I don't know.
- Barry, we are adults. - I know.
- We are dating. - Yeah.
We should be able to kiss.
I agree.
Okay, yep.
Yep. You should talk to him.
I... about?
- For real? - Yeah.
Go talk to him.
- Yeah, sure, I'll talk to him. - Okay.
- About us kissing. - Yeah.
It's not gonna be awkward at all.
Let me know how it goes.
It's gonna be awkward, that's how.
Where's Snart?
Who said that?
Where are you?
Boo.
Scudder?
Where's Snart?
I don't know, man.
Then I guess I'll just have to find someone who does.
And I know just the girl.
Yeah, Sam Scudder. He threw me into a mirror.
I fell out of a second-story window.
So Scudder's going after everyone in Snart's old crew
to track him down?
Yeah, but the only problem is,
Scudder's not gonna find him.
Snart's gone.
What do you mean, he's gone?
He's gone. I thought I--
Oliver told me that Snart left
with some friends of ours on a...trip.
I don't even want to know.
One of Snart's old crew is at Iron Heights.
I'll go see if I can talk to her.
Okay, I'll see if I can locate
any others at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Actually... I'm sorry, I just--
I need to talk to you about something really quick.
Okay, so I-I know
it's probably awkward
seeing me and Iris kiss.
- Uh, yeah. - Yeah.
So I-I was just thinking, maybe...
did it have to be awkward?
Do you mean like this conversation?
Yeah, like this conversation.
I don't know, just 'cause the next time, um, you see us,
we may kiss again in front of you.
Okay.
So I just want to make sure
that that is...okay with you.
Look, Bar.
- You're an adult. - Yes.
Do what you got to do.
- I love you. - I love you too.
I love her.
I don't love watching you two make out.
Okay, and just-just so you know,
I am gonna tell Iris that-that we talked about this.
Yeah, like I said. Do what you got to do.
Okay.
How sure are you that this will work?
Pretty sure.
Okay, but how's this going to help us
find another Harrison Wells?
You ever go fishing, Snow?
- No. - No, all right.
When you go fishing, you use lures.
Lures attract fish.
Fish end up on your fishing pole.
This satellite is our fishing pole,
through which we're going to cast our very tempting bait
out into the world's largest ocean.
Okay, how?
How? Cisco will open a breach,
and this satellite will shootho message embedded
with a tachyon-enhanced laser out into the multiverse,
and any Earth that is technologically advanced enough
should be able to receive it.
Okay, let's say this somehow works.
Just 'cause they can solve a riddle
doesn't mean they're a right fit for the team.
A riddle. Did you say riddle?
- Yeah. - How dare you, sir.
This is not a riddle.
This is a complex algorithmic cryptogram
designed to test deductive reasoning,
IQ, problem-solving skills,
anything that our team will need to combat threats,
meta-human or otherwise.
Okay, so you're just sending out an intergalactic IQ test
to all of your doppelgangers in the multiverse.
Not just a test. Think of it as an invitation.
Think of it as an elaborate "Help wanted" ad.
Will it test their attitudes, too?
'Cause I'm not sure I can stomach another Wells
with your bedside manner.
I care for you too, you jack wagon.
System is calibrated.
What are you waiting for?
And...
That's it.
- That's it? - Yeah, that's it.
So now what?
Now...
we go get a Big Belly burger.
- That's insane. What a rush. - I know.
I mean, it took me a while to get used to it.
I can't believe you're not sick at all.
I must have an iron stomach.
Okay, so you're telling me
that Barry has never taken you on a run?
No.
Well, then, I guess it's a good thing you've got me.
Guess so.
Hold up.
I'm sorry. Am I--am I reading this,
like, really wrong or something?
No, no.
I like you, Jesse. It's just...
It's just what?
You're going home soon.
To another Earth.
Ah, right. Yeah.
Yeah, no, it's-it's cool, yeah.
- Jesse, I... - No, no, no.
It's--it's totally cool.
I get it.
So...so friends, then?
Friends.
Well, as friends, I mean,
we can still run around the city, right?
Sure.
Good-looking guy.
For a criminal.
Well, he's more than just a criminal now.
Apparently, he's a meta who can travel through mirrors.
I got this one. He's, uh...
- Mirror Master. - What the--
- Boom. - That's good.
Thank you, we had a Mirror Master on our Earth,
Evan McCulloch. Wasn't a meta, though.
He had some kind of mirror gun that he used.
How'd it work?
Must've had dimensional warping tech
that changed everything into two dimensions.
Well, Scudder is hell-bent on finding Snart,
and he's going after anybody that worked with him in the past.
Joe's interviewing one of 'em right now.
Well, all of Snart's known associates
are either presumed dead or gone AWOL,
except for one.
- That's her. - Rosalind Dillon.
Says she has the ability to induce crippling vertigo.
- She's, uh-- - Top, like a top. She's the Top.
That's her name. Top. Amazing.
What, you want to go?
Okay.
Do we think that she can lead us to Scudder?
I'll have to see if Joe gets any answers out of her.
Heard your ex is back in town.
You know anything about that?
He pay you a visit, Ms. Dillon?
They don't let people like me have visitors here, Detective.
All day, all night, in my boring little cell.
Makes a girl go crazy.
Scudder tried to kill one of your old crewmates last night.
- Leon Williams? - Tried? Too bad he failed.
He's gonna try to kill more.
- Any idea who? - Give us a name.
I'll see what we can do about your current situation.
Okay.
Let us know if you change your mind.
- Sorry, Joe. - It's all right.
I appreciate your setting up the interview, though.
It looks like I owe you another one.
You know, these IOUs are starting to pile up.
I have an idea about that.
Do you?
- Scudder? - You want me?
Come and get me.
So you saw Sam Scudder and Rosalind Dillon
escape through a glass window?
Like I said, he grabbed her hand.
They walked to the window, and then poof, they were gone.
So, mirrors, windows.
It sounds like he can travel through anything
that has a reflective surface.
How exactly does he do that?
He must be able to link Einstein-Rosen bridges
to anything with high solar reflectance, right?
So he creates wormholes through reflections.
That's a new one.
Look, I can't pretend to understand or care
about the science of it all, but we need to find Dillon
and Scudder before something really bad happens.
So I'm gonna go old-school at the precinct.
I'll see you later.
Oh, my God.
Pings. We got pings.
Looks like some of your doppelgangers out there
actually cracked your code, Harry.
That was fast.
Let's go take a look.
Guys? We're...
Dad seems fine.
Yeah, no, he's still a little weird about it.
You talked to him, though, right?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, it'll be good.
Okay, great.
- Then I'll see you tonight. - All right.
You'll pick a good movie?
- I'll try. - Okay.
I'm also gonna try to find our meta-humans
that apparently no one else cares about right now.
Where the hell did you go?
How many times do I have to tell you, Rosa?
I was stuck in there.
Whatever it was that hit me gave me this crazy ability.
And to me, all this just happened last night.
It's been three years, Sam.
So many things are different now.
You were hit too, weren't you?
You can do things like me?
- Yeah. - Show me.
You might want to hold onto something.
See, Sammy?
Too much has changed.
Then let's change it back.
I can stop Snart, Rosa.
We...can stop Snart.
Snart? He's gone.
Long gone.
Then let's take this city.
We can be who we want to now.
We can be in control.
There's no one in this city who can stop us now.
There's one person who can.
Who?
The Flash.
Well, hey, now.
I-I solved the derivative you done beamed up.
My name is Wells, Harrison Wells.
You can call me Hell's Wells.
They call me that 'cause of my past.
I won't get into it with you now right and proper.
I'd like to hitch wagons and--
I had a bad dinner.
- Pass. - All right.
This is Earth-17.
I'll be in touch.
Salutations to all of you out there in the multiverse.
I have of late, wherefore I know not, received a communiqu¨¦
from the citizens of Terra-Prime.
Terra-Prime?
- Nerd. - Pass.
Bonjour. Moi, je suis Harrison Wells.
You can't trust a mime.
- Can't argue with that. - Pass.
Okay, guys. We're 0 for 3 now.
This is our last one.
It's coming from Earth-19.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello, out there in the multiverse,
whoever you may be.
I really enjoyed cracking the cryptogram you broadcast.
I like the cute trick,
embedding the secondary measures
in the primary data string. It's clever.
Most people wouldn't have caught it.
I caught it. But that's the point.
You need a genius, I guess,
to help you in your fight
against these awful meta-hominids.
Well, I got to tell you-- I got to tell you, to me,
that sounds like fun.
So...I'll enclose my curriculum vitae.
You already know we speak the same language.
But take a look. Tell me what you think.
Until our next communion.
Oh, where are my manners?
Thank you.
- Not bad. - Not bad at all.
Harry?
- Pass. - What?
- Pass. - Wait, what? Wait a minute.
That guy cracked the code, and he wants to do it.
And he's nice, and he's not evil.
And that's a combination of Wells we haven't had thus far.
All my life, everyone I've ever hired to work for me,
I have trusted my gut.
My gut tells me that's not the guy.
Keep looking.
Oh, for God's sake.
Okay, you know what?
I can't take this anymore.
What?
I thought you guys were supposed to talk about us.
We did.
Then why are you being so weird?
I'm not.
Dad?
Iris.
I already told him, if you two want to cuddle,
make out, do whatever,
I-I-I...go for it.
I don't care.
Barry?
Should we give you guys a minute?
- Yeah. - No, no, it's fine.
Look, Barry, this isn't about my dad anymore.
He's fine with it.
I'm not totally fine with it.
So why do you have a problem with this?
Thank God.
There's a robbery at First National.
- Suspects match Scudder and Dillon's description.- Scudder and Dillon
- Yeah, I'm sorry, I got to go. - Okay.
Hey...let me help.
We've been training for a reason, right?
- I've got to try. - Yeah, all right, cool.
- Just follow my lead. - Okay.
We keep this up,
baby, we'll be set for life.
Then what are you waiting for?
Let's do it again.
Anything for you, baby.
Yeah, so we're not gonna let you leave here with that.
Hey, Flash.
Heard a lot about you.
That's great.
Can't say the same for you, though.
The name's Jesse Quick.
So...I'm sorry, Scudder,
but your little crime spree, it's gonna have to end here.
Oh, I don't think you have much of a say in it.
I'm gonna take whatever I want.
I thought you were looking for Leonard Snart.
Why bother? His reign is over.
There's a--a new king in town.
And I'm the queen.
Yeah, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Oh, I would, little girl.
Where'd they go?
There.
Stay here.
I'm not kidding.
Nice skirt, Top.
Top.
I like it.
Because they spin, spin, spin.
What? What's happening?
I can't get my balance.
I know. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
But you won't.
Good luck getting him out.
Barry!
- What happened? - I don't know.
I don't know, okay? I looked at Dillon,
and I lost my balance.
She's a meta-human
who induces vertigo.
She just whammied you.
Yeah, I guess so.
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Because now Barry's trapped in there and it's because of me.
Well, you know, I--
I'll go talk to her.
What is he saying?
Is that some sort of mirror language?
Mirrors show objects in reverse.
Maybe that's what we're hearing here.
Only one way to find out.
What are you looking for, Cisco?
You ever seen "Twin Peaks"?
Of course not. Why do I ask?
This is an old backmasking trick
they used for The Man from Another Place,
where they record his audio backwards
and then play it forwards.
Like the Ozzy Osbourne records.
Sure, let's go with that.
Okay, Barry, say something.
Say it again.
Get me out of here.
Now we can understand you.
How do we get him out of there?
Barry, have you tried to phase out yet?
Yes. It's not working.
If Scudder used this mirror as a wormhole,
then these molecules are in a hyper state of flux, so all--
We need is something really cold to slow them down.
I can help with that. Let's go.
Keep him company.
Aren't you gonna need that?
What's the point?
You know, I thought I was ready, but clearly I'm not.
Jesse, you can't blame yourself for this.
- What happened to Barry-- - It was totally my fault.
I mean, he told me to stay back, but I didn't listen, you know?
I just ran in blind, and,
now he's stuck, so--
Look, you made a mistake. So what?
I mean, I'm sure Barry made a lot of mistakes at first too.
Don't let this destroy your confidence.
You're meant to do this, Jesse.
You're meant to be a speedster.
That's why you have these powers and I don't.
You're just trying to cheer me up.
I know you said you don't want to hang, so--
No, I said I didn't want to hang out because I was scared.
Because you live on another Earth, but
I realized I don't want to be scared of that anymore.
I don't think it's gonna work.
What do you mean, you don't think it's gonna work?
I built this to go to absolute zero.
I realize that. But we need the mirror
to maintain zero-point energy long enough
for Barry's molecules to pass through it.
Absolute zero's more than cold enough to do that.
Normally, but we have to account for the internal energy
of the mirror's molecules, as well.
So while absolute cold might be the lowest possible temperature,
- it's not the-- - It's not the lowest
- enthalpy state possible. - Exactly right.
So what are we gonna do?
I don't know...yet.
Okay, go with me here.
What if we send this to the other Wells
and see if he can figure something out?
- Yeah. - What? No.
What? Oh, everybody's replaceable now, is that right?
- Is that what this is? - What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? That's what you said.
That's not what I said. I'm saying we need to figure out
a solution to this problem, and time's not on our side right now.
That's not gonna help. You're
not contributing to the problem. You're making things worse.
- You know what I think? - What do you think?
I think you don't like the idea
of someone taking your place here.
What are you talking about?
This is why you don't like the other Wells.
What are you talking about? It was my idea.
But that doesn't mean you have to like it.
It's got nothing to do with liking, okay?
You know what it has to do with?
- A molecular decelerator. - A molecular decelerator.
If we augment the molecular decelerator
on the cryogenic generator of the cold gun--
I can build that. I can build that.
Great.
What are you doing?
Do these pants make my butt look big?
I'm literally stuck in a mirror.
Sorry, yeah.
What's it like in there?
dark.
Look, Iris, I'm...
I'm sorry that I'm... stuck right now.
Oh, honey, I know that you're stuck.
It's okay, we are gonna get you out of there.
No, I mean--no.
That was misleading.
Not the mirror. I mean, with us.
This thing with Joe, and you were right.
I mean, it's not Joe. It's me. It's my problem.
I've just been feeling nervous
about this new dynamic
between the three of us.
I-I don't know.
I have everything that I have ever wanted right now.
And I've never had that in my life.
In a lot of ways,
it's scarier than having nothing, because...
it's easier to fail than succeed.
And I really want to succeed.
What could you possibly be laughing about right now?
I am so sorry, Barry.
You are really sweet.
But it is weird talking to you
through a mirror and a speaker,
and I really want to kiss you right now.
But can we please talk about this later?
Yeah. We can talk about it later.
Guess it is pretty weird.
It's like I'm here, but I'm not.
What?
I just thought of a way to stop Scudder.
What is that?
This is how we get him out of there.
All right. Let's do it.
Okay.
Try it now.
It's only negative 280 degrees Fahrenheit.
We got to get it colder somehow.
I thought you guys said this thing
could get him out of there.
Okay, this thing
is a highly advanced molecular decelerator
that's being powered by a cryo-engine,
and we just kind of improvised it in the last 30 minutes,
so let's just--just cut us some slack, please?
Just keep trying, Barry.
Meta-human alert.
Oh, for God's sake.
If it's not one thing...
It's the other.
Hold on, Bar.
Guys?
Hello?
Central City Municipal Bank just got robbed.
Let me guess by who.
Guys.
- Barry. - Hey.
- How? - Let's figure it out later.
Right now we need to stop Scudder and Dillon.
Okay, so--so what do we do?
We're gonna use mirrors,
an old trick, and an old friend.
- Yeah? - It's Snart.
I heard you were back in town.
- Snart? - Scudder, Rosa.
Long time.
Not long enough.
Hang back.
This guy owes me.
So you called us.
The hell you want?
Same thing.
You two, gone.
Things have changed.
This is our town now.
- Is that right? - Yeah, it is.
And that little cold gun of yours
isn't gonna save you from me.
We'll see about that, now, won't we?
Bang!
Funny thing about holograms.
They're just pale reflections of the real deal.
Hello again.
Jesse Quick.
Quick to run, quick to fall.
Quick to learn.
Well played, Flash.
- What? - I know, right?
I'm sure you've heard of it, right?
It's an infinite reflective loop
that even you can't escape.
Good luck getting out.
So you're sure he can't
Mirror Master his way out of this cell?
No, it's impossible.
Every inch has been modified
with an anti-reflective material.
Even Scudder's gonna forget what he looks like after a while.
Well, I should go.
Hey. So, thank you for everything.
Oh, no. Thank you.
We got another bad meta right where he belongs.
- Yep, all right. - Hey, Joe.
We have an awful lot of IOUs.
Do you maybe want to grab some dinner tonight?
- Dinner? - Yeah.
Yeah, I-- well, I've got movie night
with my kids tonight.
Rain check?
Yeah. Of course.
Another time, then.
What was that about?
- Why didn't you just say yes? - I don't know.
You're not the only one that gets nervous around here.
You guys, I've never vibed across 18 dimensions before.
Just a little bit longer.
Greetings, earthlings.
Just kidding. I don't really talk like that.
I've just always wanted to say that.
Earthlings.
Wells with a sense of humor. That's new.
Hey, sharpshooter.
You.
You're... handsome.
I know.
- Likewise, I'm sure. - Yeah.
Harrison.
You can call me HR.
HR it is.
This is the team, then. Um...
This is Cisco Ramon. He can do anything.
Okay.
This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
- She is brilliant. - Hi. - Single.
- Don't--all right, that's my daughter.
You don't have to shake her hand.
That gentleman there is Wally West.
This is Barry Allen, or
as we call him on this Earth...
The Flash.
Welcome to Earth-1.
Thanks. Earth-1, that's weird.
Okay, well, we don't have to stand on ceremony.
We don't have to go through all the tears again, do we, gang? Right?
Well, did I-- did I cry last time you left?
- I was talking about myself. - Oh, gotcha.
Hey, listen.
Don't worry about it, okay?
There's only one Harry.
Oh, I wanted to tell you.
The molecular decelerator, it wasn't working.
Okay, what does that mean?
It means that we did not get Barry out of that mirror.
It wasn't us.
Then who did it?
You tell me.
- See you later. - Yeah.
Earth-2's gonna have one hell of a speedster protecting it.
Well, I did learn from the best.
If you ever need any help, you know how to get back.
Yeah. Yeah, definitely, I'll be back.
All right.
Okay, you guys.
Ready?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, Cisco.
Out with the old, in with the new.
You'll never be old to us, Harry.
-Ready? - Yeah.
Okay, let's do this.
Oh, one more thing. While I'm gone, never, ever,
no matter what--
What--what was he gonna say?
And we're all like, "What was he gonna say?"
That's cool, though. I'm starving.
Do you guys have Big Belly Burger?
Some things never change.
Famished.
Did Barry say anything about
this embarrassing moment with Cecile?
How did your first meeting go with the new Wells?
Good. Yeah, I think he'll work out fine.
Oh, good. I look forward to meeting him.
- Whoa. - What?
I'm just kidding.
I got to be honest,
it's gonna take a bit for me to get used to that.
I actually have something to run by you guys that
- I think might help with that. - Really?
- Yeah. - What up?
Well, I've just been thinking that maybe for all of us--
that I should probably, um...
get my own place.
- Really? - Yeah.
What do you think?
- I say yes. - I thought you'd never leave.
- Seriously? - Dad.
- Wow. - Look, Bar, come on.
I'm gonna miss you, but damn.
You grown. About time.
I can't tell if I'm leaving
or if I'm getting kicked out.
You feel like you feel.
Feel like I'm getting kicked out.
I mean, yeah, I feel like you're getting kicked out too.
Like, it's pretty obvious
you're getting kicked out.
Dad.
You're grown.
Oh, well. Cool.