- My name is Barry Allen and
I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs
I fight crime and find other
meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present.
[booming]
And now our world is more
dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one fast
enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Follow my instructions
and we'll defeat Cicada.
Destroy his dagger
and save your father.
That is a new timeline
struggling to break through.
- Thawne,
another Cicada showed up.
[booming]
- I used to think
that keeping secrets
from people would protect them,
but you can't really
know someone with
walls between you.
- Eobard Thawne,
the Reverse Flash.
Your partner.
Your secret.
- Dad, I'm sorry I lied to you!
- So am I.
- Dad, please.
I wanted to tell you.
Dad! I tried to tell you.
I'm sorry I lied to you!
- It's Nora, our daughter.
- She lied to us, Iris.
[dramatic music]
Since the first day
she got here,
about Thawne!
♪ ♪
She knows what he did to us.
To me.
To my mother.
I can't believe
a word she says.
- We don't know that.
- Yes, we do!
- We don't even know why
she's working with him.
- Now the pressing question
is not why Nora is working
with the Reverse Flash.
Maybe I can talk to her and
shed some light on the matter.
- I think you've
shed enough light.
- Why, are you upset at me?
What I should do?
I should just...I should not
have told you?
- How long has it been
since you suspected her?
- Since I arrived.
[dramatic music]
- Wow.
- So you've been following
this trail all this time
and you didn't think to tell
us about it until now?
- I don't know where
this trail leads.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm not kidding you.
You don't come to a conclusion
without facts.
All the facts.
♪ ♪
- Shirley, I think, uh,
maybe you should just give us
all a minute here.
- What, you're mad at me
for doing what
a master detective does.
Figure out something
that you cannot.
I give you that translation.
Your anger is misplaced.
- Look, whatever reason
Nora didn't tell us,
I don't think
she did it maliciously.
♪ ♪
Guys, even from here,
I can feel how upset she is.
- All right, babe,
you've been around Nora
for months.
You never felt that she
was hiding something before.
- No, never.
Never.
- Well, Thawne lied.
He was a master at it.
It stands to reason he must
have taught Nora some
of his same tricks.
- Maybe.
Maybe not.
There's gotta be some way
to figure it out.
♪ ♪
- There is.
I'm guessing this
has everything
from the day she arrived.
Maybe before.
♪ ♪
- Read it.
From the beginning.
[dramatic music]
- Please stand back
from the perimeter.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
Uh, excuse me.
Excuse me, pardon me.
- Incoming call from Mom.
- Mom, come on.
Ooh!
I'm so sorry.
I just...I'm really late.
I'm...I'm really late
for an important date.
Not a date, date.
Not that I don't date, date.
I date, date.
It's just, I have a meeting.
I'm making myself later.
Sorry.
♪ ♪
- Anyone seen CSI?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Where is West-Allen?
- Ah, I'm so sorry,
Detective Curtis.
I didn't mean to
be late. I tried to hail
a hover-taxi but they
kept passing me by
and then I had to run
all the way from...
- I really don't care what
your reason is this time,
West-Allen.
I just wanna find
what meta did this.
- Of course.
- Chemical transport truck
on its way to Dayton Labs.
It was attacked
earlier this morning.
- But that makes two labs
and another two transports
this week.
- And like the others,
no one saw anyone.
[dramatic music]
[beeping]
- God, there's
residue everywhere.
- Benzene Methanol.
- That's what they stole.
- What's that used for?
- Anything from nanotech
to treating lice.
- Halothane.
- Halothane?
♪ ♪
Wait a second.
- What?
♪ ♪
- This truck has an
Affinity 4,000 security camera.
God, Lia's gonna be so jealous.
Whenever the 4,000's
tampered with,
its failsafe releases
a incapacitating agent.
Halothane.
- So you're saying whoever
did this picked the lock,
disabled the camera,
and stole might-be-lice
medicine?
All before this incapacitating
agent could do its job?
- And no one saw them.
- How is that possible?
♪ ♪
- A speedster?
Nora, labmate,
friend of mine,
You didn't happen to pitch
your speedster theory
to Detective Curtis, did you?
- It is not a theory, Lia.
It is the only explanation.
[beeping]
- You know I'm equally a fan
of our fleet-footed
super friends.
I mean, honestly,
if I could have ever
met Jesse Quick, it's like,
hello, new best friend.
[laughs]
No offense, um...
- Some taken.
- Okay, but there hasn't been
a speedster in Central City
since that crisis piece your
mom wrote about, like,
decades ago.
I mean, Flash, Kid Flash,
Jay Garrick,
that...that weird purple
speedster that just
showed up one day.
They're all gone.
So what you're suggesting,
highly unlikely.
- Then we need
to start believing
in the highly unlikely.
- Alternatively, um,
you could...
[clears throat]
Dial back your obsessiveness.
- I'm not obsessive.
- You never got
to know your dad.
So you became a CSI
just like him,
and it's why you keep
investigating the one case
Barry Allen never solved.
Cicada.
- You call that obsessive.
I call that a hobby.
- Right, your, um...your classic
everyday...
murder hobby.
[laughs]
It's like your mom says.
You're, uh...you're excessive.
- Do not quote my mother.
- God, I wish CCPD would
spring for one
of these Affinity cameras.
I mean, trillion FPS,
captures light in motion.
W-T-Shrap?
- That's lightning.
- The canister's gone.
- White lightning.
A speedster.
- Okay, maybe.
- No, not maybe.
It is! I knew it!
- Okay, fine, you're right.
But...
[dramatic music]
But what is a speedster
doing stealing chemicals?
♪ ♪
- And Eobard Thawne,
aka the Reverse-Flash,
was finally defeated
and incarcerated
and will remain in Iron
Heights Prison
for the rest of his days.
- I know.
- Incoming call from Mom.
- [scoffs]
[sighs]
[beeping]
See? I knew it.
There was never a speedster
with white lightning.
- [clears throat] All yours.
- Thanks.
- Thank you for visiting
the Flash Museum today.
The building will be closing
in five minutes.
All guests should make their
way to the exit now.
And Nora West-Allen,
your mother called.
Please,
for your sake and mine,
call her back.
♪ ♪
- So embarrassing.
Mom, why are you calling
Mr. Myles?
- I tried you at your lab.
You weren't answering.
I left three messages.
You never returned
any of them.
What else was
I supposed to do?
- Wait for me to call you back?
- Why isn't your holo on?
- Uh, it doesn't work
in the Flash Museum.
- For the life of me,
I've never understood
your obsession
with that place.
What are you even doing there?
Are you there alone?
- It's fine, Mom.
I'm researching a case.
- What kind of case?
- One that I can't talk about.
- I'm your mother, Nora.
- And I'm an employee
of CCPD who can't talk
about open cases.
Mom, how many times do I have
to tell you this?
You were married to a CSI.
- Yes, I was.
- [groans]
I'm sorry. [grunts]
What were you calling about?
- I thought my daughter might
want to know how I'm doing
in Coast City.
I almost finished my story.
I should be home
in a few days.
- Great.
[device chiming]
Uh, Mom, I gotta go.
It's work.
- Love you.
[beeps]
Hey.
- Hey, meet me
at Ollins Laboratory.
I sent the list of stolen
chemicals to an old teacher
of mine and I think
he found something.
Appreciate the help,
Dr. Bonwit,
especially at this hour.
- Not a problem.
Ollins never lets me leave
this place anyway.
- [chuckles]
So Lia was telling me
you might know
how these chemicals
can be used together.
- Yes and no.
Took me a bit to see it,
but the only way they seem
to work together is if they're
built on a structure.
Like an extracellular matrix.
- But there are thousands
of extracellular matrices.
- So until we know
all the chemicals,
we won't know the end results.
- Sorry I can't help more.
- That's okay.
Thanks, Dr. Bonwit.
- Now what?
- We can't just wait
for another lab to get hit.
[whooshing]
BOTH: Holy shrap!
[exciting music]
- Dr. Bonwit!
[whooshing]
- Oh, my God!
♪ ♪
- Yes, I am a god.
The god of speed.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
[electrical sparking]
[crashing]
♪ ♪
- Nora!
Nora!
[gasps]
Somebody help, please!
Someone help!
- Nora?
[Lady Gaga's "Poker Face"]
- ♪ Can't read my,
can't read my ♪
- Nora?
- ♪ No, he can't read
my poker face ♪
- Oh, I knew an oldie
would wake you up.
Okay, don't freak.
Uh, we're in a hospital.
Me for this burn and you
for a whole lot more.
- Dr. Bonwit?
- Uh, ICU.
But he's gonna pull through.
Um, but the speedster did get
away with a crazy amount
of Carbon Disulfide.
- [sighs]
- Don't worry about
that right now.
How are you feeling?
- I...I feel fine, actually.
My fingers are a little tingly
but other than that,
I...I feel really good.
It's weird, right?
- I'm just so glad you're okay.
Your doctor said you got hit
with five billion joules
of electricity.
Which means, um, I, uh...
I, uh, kind of called your mom.
Um, and she, uh...
She freaked more than normal.
Um, I had to.
You could have died.
- Lia, is she here?
- She's on her way
from Coast City.
Uh, and she is wearing
her aggro pants.
I mean, she has called me,
like, 47 times.
- You should have ignored her.
Just, I don't want
her to worry.
- I did.
Uh, which is why she
doesn't know about this.
The paramedics said that
you went into cardiac arrest
when you got here and so they
had to use the defib nodes
to restart your heart,
and when they did,
they found this.
It was buried underneath the
scar under your right shoulder.
- What is it?
- They say it's a metal
scrap from the shelf
you got thrown into,
but I don't know.
It looks kind of old
and...and pretty fried.
Okay, wait, but now that
we both know you're okay,
can we please talk about
the fact that you got struck
by lightning from a speedster?
- So schway, right?
The only thing is no one's
gonna believe us.
- We both saw it.
They're gonna have to.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
[buzzing]
- Stay calm.
There has been an incident.
System check in progress.
- [breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
- LIA:Catch this.
[whooshing]
- [gasps] I'm okay!
- You sure?
- [gasps]
Yeah, dude.
I'm a speedster.
All of my nerves are tingling
and my synapses must be
going crazy because my reaction
times are way off the charts.
♪ ♪
What am I gonna do
about my mom?
She freaks out any time someone
even says the word meta.
- Okay, well,
that's understandable.
I mean, her non-meta husband
died because of metas.
- Yeah, but writing about
the Flash...the meta-human...
made her career.
- So we can't tell her?
- No, we can't tell anybody.
Not until we figure out
how I got these powers.
And I don't think it's a
coincidence that this happened
after my little run-in
with the god of speed guy.
- You mean when Godspeed
hit you with his lightning.
Which, according
to the Flash Museum,
is exactly what happened to...
BOTH: The Flash.
[chiming]
- 10-90 in progress.
- Bank heist.
Huh.
- No, no.
You can't do that.
That is a bad idea.
That is like cut
your own bangs bad.
- I'm just gonna do
a little run-by.
- You are a CSI,
not a superhero.
- Our jobs are the same
as the cops.
We get the bad guys.
- All right.
Go get 'em, Flash Woman.
- [laughs]
- Lady Flash.
Hot Flash.
♪ ♪
Not that one.
- Okay, we're gonna workshop
that later.
Until then,
I have to guard Central City.
[whooshes]
[dramatic music]
[alarms buzzing]
- Ah!
- Stop or I'll fire!
[electric charging]
Keep your hands
where I can see them!
[whooshing]
- Oh, um, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
[car doors closing]
- Freeze!
- [grunts]
Oh, uh...
[whooshing]
[thudding]
- What in the world?
- Bug and Byte,
you're under arrest!
- Go, go, go!
- Take them down!
- [gasping]
- You fried your gauntlet
and half the fleet.
- It was only three cruisers.
- Now Captain Frye's gonna be
on his warpath
which is gonna make
everybody's life miserable.
- [sighs]
- I'm sorry, Nora.
I know today didn't exactly
go so great.
- Both robbers got away
because of me.
- Cut yourself a slice
of slack pie.
It was your first day.
No one got hurt.
And plus they found Bug
and Byte hunched over
with runner's cramps, like,
ten minutes later.
- But I still feel so bad.
- You're looking
at this all wrong.
Today was not Nora's
big failure.
Today was the Femme-Flash's
big debut.
[dramatic music]
Naming superheroes is not easy.
[both chuckling]
- Lia, you are the best friend
a shrappy speedster
could ever ask for.
But I think we both know
that CCPD isn't equipped
to stop this guy.
The only way we're gonna
catch him before
anyone else gets hurt
is if I start thinking
like a villainous speedster.
- And how are you
gonna do that?
[dramatic music]
- I'm gonna go see one.
♪ ♪
- GUARD:Reverse-Flash, huh?
Well, officer, you're, like,
the second person in 15 years
who's come to visit
this psychopath.
Not even a call.
Are you sure you want
to interview him by yourself?
- I've been alone
with criminals before.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- You have five minutes.
[whirring]
[door clangs]
♪ ♪
- Eobard Thawne?
- My name is Nora West-Allen,
and I'm a CSI tech
with the CCPD.
I wanted to ask you
a few questions, if I could.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Come closer.
Nora West-Allen.
♪ ♪
Don't be afraid.
The dampening capabilities
of this cell can negate
the powers of 1,000
meta-humans.
The glass, the walls,
the ceiling, the floors
are all connected to a power
energizer that will zap
this place with
400 kilojoules instantly
should the dampeners fail.
Making the cell phase-proof.
♪ ♪
I couldn't hurt you,
Nora West-Allen.
♪ ♪
Even if I wanted to.
What are your questions?
♪ ♪
- How did you end up in here?
- Was there nobody at CCPD
that could answer
that question for you?
- All the files pertaining
to the Reverse-Flash
have been cyber locked.
And there's almost nothing
about you in the Flash Museum.
Except for the date
of your imprisonment.
- Really?
That's all there is
in the Flash Museum?
That's interesting.
- Will you tell me how
you were defeated?
- Why do you want to know that?
- It'll help us with
an investigation.
- You need to work
on your lying.
Nora.
Your shoes are new.
But your soles are worn.
You have singe marks
on your sleeves
and singe marks
on your pant legs,
but most of all,
your cheeks are flushed
with windburn.
Oh, I know that windburn.
I can still feel it.
♪ ♪
You're a speedster.
[door whirring]
- Time's up.
- Please, I need your help.
- Come on.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
- Time to repent, professor.
[door clunking]
♪ ♪
[buzzing]
- [shouting]
♪ ♪
- Thawne figured out
I had powers,
but he wouldn't tell me
anything about them.
What?
And don't tell me it's nothing
'cause your whole face
says it's something.
- You know this metal
fragment they found
underneath your shoulder?
- Yeah.
- Well, something about it
was bugging me,
so I did some digging.
It turns out it's not from that
shelf you got thrown into.
It's, uh...It's tech.
A chip made by S.T.A.R. Labs
25 years ago.
- Like a chip you would use
to find a lost animal?
[suspenseful music]
- It's to dampen your speed.
- What?
- You didn't get your powers
when Godspeed hit you
with his lightning.
It looks like you
always had them.
- I...I've always had powers?
♪ ♪
Why do...Who would put a power
dampening chip inside of...
♪ ♪
- Your mom lied
to you your whole life.
I mean, that's
next-level aggro.
- How could she keep something
like that from me?
I mean, what else
has she lied to me about?
- I think you're gonna have
to ask her.
- Oh, just the idea of that
makes my blood boil.
- That could be the macchiato.
It's possible I might have
made that a triple.
[both laughing]
- At least I have one person
in my life I can still trust.
[pop music playing]
♪ ♪
A triple.
- That's been established.
- No, no, no, not the coffee.
I mean, yes, the coffee.
But the chemicals
that Godspeed stole.
Benzene Methanol is unstable,
and if you add
the Carbon Disulfide that
he stole from Ollins lab...
- Kablooey.
I remember that from
9th grade Analytical Chem.
- And the only way to combine
all those chemicals together
is if you add some kind
of binding property.
- Right, you'd need a plus-one
oxidation state,
like a...a Diogygen Diflouride.
- Yes, and somewhere that's
able to store that
and the only place
in Central City that can
is Stagg Industries.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I cannot believe my first
time at Stagg Industries
is as a burglar.
Or are we vigilantes?
♪ ♪
- Lia, I found it.
- Unless your super speed
came with super biceps,
we are not getting
this out of here.
[whooshing]
- That's mine.
[sparking]
- Uh, okay.
Try and get this open.
It'll evaporate in seconds.
If you want it, you're gonna
have to come through me
to get it.
- Ah, you're a speedster
like me.
So you need it too.
Sorry.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
[blows landing]
- [groaning]
[whooshes]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
No!
- [grunts]
[whooshes]
♪ ♪
- Lia! Lia!
[crying]
Lia!
- The one person in the world
she thought she could trust
died in her arms.
- Nora must have felt
completely alone.
♪ ♪
- But she wasn't.
- Yes, she was.
Because I wasn't
honest with her.
- Iris...
- After all I did,
she gave me a second chance.
[dramatic music]
It's the least
we can do for her.
♪ ♪
- Mom?
- Don't make me regret this.
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
- I'm giving our daughter
the chance to explain this
for herself.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
[dramatic music]
- Nora.
[sighs]
I heard about... Lia.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
♪ ♪
I know how it is to lose
someone you love.
♪ ♪
If you don't wanna talk
about it right now,
that's okay.
Or maybe you just don't wanna
talk about it with me.
♪ ♪
Nora, can I just make sure
that you're okay?
Nora, I went to the hospital
and they said that you left.
- I guess lightning doesn't
hurt as much when you already
have it coursing
through your veins.
♪ ♪
Does this look familiar?
[whooshing]
How about now?
- Nora...
- Lia found it before she died.
♪ ♪
You put this inside of me, Mom.
To dampen my powers?
You lied to me my whole life.
♪ ♪
- I know.
- Who else knows?
♪ ♪
Who else?
- Everyone.
♪ ♪
- Everybody?
Everyone that I love has been
keeping this from me?
Why?
- Because I told them to.
- Why would you do that?
- Nora, I was trying
to protect you.
- From what?
- From this city.
From...from meta-humans.
From...from yourself.
- [laughs]
Wow.
- Nora, you don't understand.
- No, I don't understand.
How did I get my powers?
What do you have
against speedsters?
- Nora, I have already
lost so much.
I can't risk losing you too.
♪ ♪
- Well, you just did.
[whooshes]
♪ ♪
[crying]
- I'm gonna miss Lia too.
West-Allen, we all know
how close you two were.
If you need some time off,
I'm sure Captain Frye...
- We need to get the guy
who did this.
Whatever it takes.
- We ran the evidence
from the crime scene.
Turns out there was foreign DNA
in Lia's exit wound.
But we've used it
to positively ID this guy.
- August Hart.
Bio-hacker.
Mercury Labs intern,
and then grad school.
[beeping]
♪ ♪
- All yours.
- Says he was kicked out
for testing tachyon stimulants
on coma patients.
What the hell's a tachyon?
- A particle that moves
faster than light.
- Well, an arrest warrant's
on its way now.
I promise you this guy's gonna
get what he deserves.
♪ ♪
- Yes, he will.
- Did you know
not all villains
had meta-human powers?
Some u...
[beeping]
- Make sure you get this.
- Everybody move!
[beeping]
- Godspeed's lightning...
[suspenseful music]
- It turned blue,
just like Zoom's.
Hey, wait a sec.
♪ ♪
- Although her body
disintegrated,
authorities uncovered evidence
at Mercury Labs
of the illegal
speed-enhancement drug,
Velocity-9.
This volatile stimulant gave
Trajectory incredible speed,
but at a deadly price.
- That's it.
Benzene Methanol,
Carbon Disulfide,
Dioxygen Diflouride.
The base for the extracellular
matrix for Velocity-9.
Only he's trying to make one
that will last forever.
- [screaming]
[electricity sparking]
- [chuckling]
- [coughing]
[door closing]
[dramatic music]
- How do I stop a speedster?
- You can't.
- Not alone.
But with you, I can.
- [coughing]
♪ ♪
- No.
- That plinth,
it takes incoming calls
and from what I hear,
you have a few left.
You could walk me through
it via comms.
- [spits]
No.
- He has stolen enough
chemicals to make
an extracellular matrix that
replicates speed powers.
- I told you to leave.
- The only thing that
is stopping him from becoming
a speedster permanently
is a stabilizing agent.
Once he gets that,
he will be unstoppable.
- I told you to leave!
Guard!
- Please.
He killed my best friend
in front of me.
♪ ♪
She's gone because of him,
and you are the only person
that can stop it.
♪ ♪
- What the hell?
You need to leave now.
- [huffs]
♪ ♪
- Nora.
[whooshing]
- Okay, I'm at the
innovation lab at CCU.
Are you there?
- Yes, I'm here.
- Okay, are you sure this
is gonna short out
the scanner circuits?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Vibrate your hands together.
Build an electric shock.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
[sizzling]
Schway.
It worked.
- THAWNE:Now look for the
brightest room.
♪ ♪
The converter needs constant
fluorescent light.
♪ ♪
Now locate
the biometric converter.
It will be a kidney-shaped
object
- I think I found it.
♪ ♪
No way for Godspeed to
stabilize his Velocity-9 now.
[whooshes]
- You don't learn, do you?
That's mine.
- Come and get it.
♪ ♪
[crashing]
It worked!
♪ ♪
No.
He's got more V-9.
- [grunts]
[shouting]
♪ ♪
- Nora, you need to get out
of there now.
Right now!
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- I can't lose him!
Thawne!
Did you hear me?
I said I can't lose him!
- All right, Nora,
do you see any walls
near where you are,
preferably concrete?
- Why?
- Because I want you
to run into one.
Or rather, through one.
- I can't run through
a concrete wall!
- Yes, you can.
If you vibrate at the natural
frequency of air,
your body...your cells will be
in such a state that they
will phase right
through that wall.
- I can't do this!
- Nora, listen to me.
Listen to my voice.
Breathe.
Feel the wind on your face.
The ground beneath your feet.
And the lightning.
The electricity surging
through your veins.
To your nerve endings
from the crown of your head
to the tips of your toes
like an electric shock
you never want to end.
You're part of something
greater now, Nora.
You are part of the
Speed Force and its power,
it's power is yours to use.
Now do it.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- I can't.
I can't do it.
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
- Then good-bye, Little Runner.
- No, no.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I trust you.
Uh, what now?
- Nora, you can't run forever.
You're gonna have to stop him.
Tell me what you
see around you.
- Um, uh, I'm on 5th and Park.
I see Choi Enterprises,
Peercoin Bank,
and CC Citizen Media.
- Media, the satellites.
Nora, we're gonna use
the satellites' electromagnetic
radiation to break
the V-9 bonds.
Flood Godspeed
with anti-endorphins.
- Neutralizing
the V-9 instantly.
- Exactly,
but here's the thing.
Those satellites recalibrate
on the hour
emitting very short bursts
of microwave energy.
You're only gonna have a few
seconds to get Godspeed
in front of those bursts.
Do you understand?
- So I just need him to follow
me into the building.
- Not into the building.
Up the building.
- Uh, okay.
I can do that.
Um, how fast do I have to go
to run up a building?
- As fast as you can.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Here he comes.
- Then run, Nora.
Run.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
Wait for it, Nora.
Wait.
♪ ♪
And now!
[whirring]
♪ ♪
[crashing]
Nora.
Nora!
- We did it!
We did it.
- Yes, we did.
- Well, we don't have to worry
about Godspeed anymore.
August Hart is in
the custody of CCPD.
- Bravo, Little Runner.
- I still have a lot to learn,
you know.
[dramatic music]
You could train me.
- I can't train you, Nora.
♪ ♪
There's just not enough time.
- What...what are
you talking about?
You're...
- Nora.
My time on this earth
is coming to an end.
♪ ♪
- There's so much
I wanted to ask you.
So much that
I still don't know.
So much that my mom
has lied to me about.
♪ ♪
- You have no idea.
- What do you know?
♪ ♪
Thawne, please, you may be
the only person left
in my life who won't lie to me.
♪ ♪
- Nora,
how much do you really know
about the Flash?
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
- Five, six, seven.
♪ ♪
[whirring]
Holy shrap.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- Good evening,
Nora West-Allen.
- Um, hi.
Uh...
You know who I am?
- Of course.
Nora West-Allen.
Daughter of Iris West
and Barry Allen,
also known as the Flash.
♪ ♪
- Wh...
S...Did you...
Did you just say my father,
Barry Allen,
was the Flash?
- Would you like me to play
your video message,
Nora West-Allen?
♪ ♪
- My...My message?
- Yes, from your father,
Barry Allen.
- Uh, y...yes.
- Nora,
I don't have much time.
[booming]
If you're watching this,
it means you're like me.
♪ ♪
You have powers.
[distant shouting]
It also means I wasn't there
to help you learn
how to use them.
I wasn't there
for a lot of things.
Remember, my sweet Nora,
always remember,
I love you.
I always will.
♪ ♪
[indistinct shouting]
[beeping]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
I just wanted to see you, Dad.
[bittersweet music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Thawne...
showed me how.
- And Cicada?
- The one case
we both couldn't solve.
♪ ♪
It was my idea
to come here and make it right.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- Can I have a minute alone
with Nora?
♪ ♪
- Of course.
- How many times
did you go back to Thawne?
- How many times?
- After the night
of the Enlightenment.
- Five, uh, maybe six.
- [sighs]
Even knowing
he killed my mother?
- Dad...
- I understand...
coming back to meet me...
and the team.
I do.
I even understand
going to Thawne...
to learn how to do it, but...
you kept going back.
Even after you knew
what he did.
Even after he wasn't
your only option anymore.
♪ ♪
And the worst part is,
you lied to us every time.
- D-Dad, I...
- I don't trust you, Nora.
[heartbroken music]
I can't have
anybody here with us
that I don't trust anymore.
♪ ♪
- W-what are you saying?
- It's time for you to go home.
[electricity crackling]
- [panting]
Dad, please don't do this!
I promise I will never
see Thawne again!
Dad, don't do this!
- Nora, if you try
to run back in time again,
I will feel it
in the Speed Force.
I'll know.
[dramatic music]
Good-bye, Nora.
- [ragged breathing]
[electricity zaps]
♪ ♪
- So she finally came clean.
[foreboding music]
Or did you figure it out
all by yourself?
- One wasn't enough?
♪ ♪
You had to try to take
my daughter from me too?
♪ ♪
My daughter!
- I knew you'd react like this.
You're always so emotional,
which is why I had her
keep all of this from you.
You can't blame
the Little Runner, Barry.
She just wanted to spend
some time with her dad.
♪ ♪
Don't hold that against her.
Consider it a condemned man's
last request.
♪ ♪
- You always thought you were
so much smarter
than us, Thawne.
♪ ♪
But you lost.
And now you're finally gonna
get what you deserve.
[electricity zaps]
♪ ♪
[timer beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head!