[light orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Infinite velocity
will soon be mine!
And once my ascension
is complete,
all will bow before the might
of Godspeed!
Ah!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Gideon, let CCPD
know I've got Heart.
I'm bringing him in now.
Guess you couldn't run
away forever, Heart.
[grunts]
[neck cracking]
- Never anger a god,
little one.
[electricity crackling]
- Whoo!
[laughing]
Yo, that was so crash.
- What the hell was that?
You just
phased through a speedster.
- Who didn't see me coming.
- Your molecules could have
conjoined on a quantum level.
Do you not know
what that means?
- No, no, I don't.
I don't,
because I'm a freshman
in college,
and I don't learn quantum
physics till my junior year.
You remember that, right, sis?
- Whatever.
Bart, you have to stop
pulling these crazy stunts.
You're still learning how
to control your meta-abilities.
- My meta-abilities
just saved the day.
You saw that.
Also, I am expanding
my boundaries, right?
Like, who knows
what else you could do
if you actually
pushed yourself?
- Seriously?
Did you not just see
my lightning lasso?
- Okay, that's really bad.
- Gideon:Warning.
August Heart now located
at 5724 Fontana Drive.
- The Flash Museum.
- You're too late.
Now the future
belongs to Godspeed.
- If he gets away...
- We'll never find him, but...
- Mom and Dad will
kill us, so...
- Screw it.
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
-Nora: Wait.
The guy we chased through time,
August Heart,
has no speed and no memory now?
- And he has dozens of clones
all fighting each other?
- Maybe even more now.
- Hey, that was
an amazing story, by the way.
The whole phasing
through the baddies like that?
- Oh, dude, amazing.
Bro, I've been working
on that move for a minute.
- So epic.
I mean...
- Thanks, bro.
I appreciate it.
- Also, I'm Chester P. Runk,
team tech guru,
and it is an absolute pleasure
to meet thekinder
of Flash and Iris.
- [laughs]
Chester, we've already met.
You improved my gauntlet's
efficiency by, like, 2,000%.
You're also
the smartest person we know.
- I am?
- Oh, oh, my God.
Yeah, absolutely.
Dude, you help me
with my differentials
of mathematics homework,
like, all the time.
All the time.
Don't forget that.
both: Grammy Cecile!
- [laughs]
Hi.
Oh, my God.
I feel so much love
from you two.
I can't wait to get
to know you both.
- [laughs]
Oh, hey, Caitlin.
- Oh, what up, Cait?
- Hi.
It happened again?
- Yeah.
Just wish Iris
was here to meet them.
- Dad, Mom's gonna be fine.
It's okay.
- Yeah.
- Well,
with Nora and Bart here,
at least we've got
the extra muscle that we need.
- Uh-uh. West-Allen
family rule #1:
Protect the timeline
at any and all cost.
Can't stay.
[soft dramatic music]
- Actually, you can.
- Really?
- What?
- Look, the Godspeeds
are recharging themselves
in the Speed Force,
so as long as that's the case,
there's no way back.
So maybe you are safer
here with us...
- Oh. [laughs]
- And I don't know.
I mean, maybe you're
the advantage we need
to finally end this war,
once and for all.
- Cecile's helping me
with the MAD 2.0,
so we can unlock August Heart's
memories, but no luck yet.
- Okay, Barry,
I think I got something.
[laughs]
Okay, so I was going through
my Pops' old schematics,
and I found this.
It reconverts the atomic mass
of neutrinovoltaic
energy cells.
Pops called it
a solar encryption engine.
- Cool.
What does it do?
- It neutralizes
artificially created
kinetic energy sources.
- Like Godspeed's
artificial speed.
- And I already built
a prototype.
I just need
to charge the battery
with an electromagnetic source.
Hey, have
you seen Allegra lately?
- No, not since yesterday, when
she said goodbye to Esperanza.
- Hmm.
We'll find her.
But, with any luck,
the S.E.E...
Huh, huh?
S.E...you get it?
Will be fully charged
and functional within an hour.
- All right.
- Dad, with this,
we can stop Heart
and his clones in his tracks.
We can win this war.
- [sighs]
- [burps]
- Ew.
[both laughing]
It's okay, Dad.
We don't bite.
- Okay.
Yo, check this out.
I got one more.
- No.
- [hiccups]
[burping]
- [laughing]
Oh, gross.
- Whoo.
- Nora, you can just ignore
the family rules
for a minute and rewind that.
- Sure.
How would I do that?
Wait.
Is this about the other Nora?
- You know about her?
- Totally.
- Yeah.
- I mean, you and Mom
have told us a ton of stories
about her,
and I'm so glad that you did.
I feel like part of her
is still alive in me.
[alarm buzzing]
- Caitlin:Barry, we've got
more Godspeed clones
southwest of City Hall.
- Okay.
Time to go to work.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
- Let's go?
You mean, like,
all three of us go?
- Yeah.
You ready?
- Okay, yeah.
- All right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Secure the area.
Make sure there are
no civilians in harm's way.
- What about them?
- Let them kill each other
and then clean up the mess.
- Dad?
- Okay.
Split up, and keep moving.
We'll run out the clock
until they have
to go back and recharge.
None of the Godspeeds
are behind me.
Nora, how many
are following you?
- Nora:None here either.
Where the heck are they?
- Bart:Found them.
all: Kill the adversary.
Strike him down.
Kill the adversary.
- Circle back.
We'll fight them together.
- Bart: No!
No.
I'm gonna lead them
away from the city.
- No you're not.
Now, listen to me.
♪ ♪
You all right?
- Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
[laughs]
I mean, yeah.
They couldn't keep up
with the fleet-footed wonder.
- They went to recharge,
you idiot.
What's your problem?
You were supposed
to circle back.
- Bart, why do they all
follow you and not us?
What are you not telling me?
- All right, which one of you
is gonna tell me
what's going on?
All those clones just
tried to kill you, Bart.
They were calling you
"the adversary."
Why?
What's going on?
- Dad, we can't talk
about this.
- Look, right now,
I don't care
about what kind of rules
I have in the future.
I want to know why
every Godspeed out there
just tried to kill Bart.
- Because he's my Thawne.
[dramatic music]
Dad, Godspeed is
my arch-nemesis, okay?
He's my one big bad
to rule them all,
just like you and Thawne.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Bart, Thawne devoted
his entire life
to destroying mine.
He murdered your grandma.
You can't just throw
his name around
without knowing what it means.
- I know what it means!
- Bart, it's okay.
Why don't we all just
try and take a breath?
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
Maybe we should go train?
If we want to take on
those clones again,
we gotta work
on our Fathwoom Boom.
- Fine.
- We'll be in the Speed Lab,
if you need us.
♪ ♪
- Oh, thank the universe.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
Look, you are not gonna
believe what went down
while you were gone.
Barry and Iris' kids
showed up
from the freaking future.
[laughs]
Now it's like we got
two Marty McFlys.
You okay?
- Yep.
Need something?
- Yeah, well, the Godspeeds
left to go recharge again,
but the intervals
between their attacks
are getting
shorter and shorter.
So I need this ready
for when they come back.
Ta-da!
It's my Pops'
solar encryption engine.
I mean, I've still gotta do
a few final tweaks,
but I also need a way
to charge the battery.
- So you came
to the human charger.
Got it.
Fine.
Let's go.
- You forgot your java.
- It's fine.
- Yeah, but you can
just take it to go
and hit it
with a microwave blast later.
- I already nuked it, Chester.
I just don't want it anymore.
Now, can we get this over with?
- Nuked it, huh?
- Kramer:That's when
the suspect confessed
to the bombing in Polokistan.
- Did Creyke say anything else?
- Because Kristen Kramer died
in that explosion,
and that means you're dead.
- No.
That was everything.
- Great.
That should be it on our end.
Car you asked for is out front.
- Great, thanks.
- I'm having a hard time
trying to reach anybody
in Central City.
It's like the whole town
lost cell service.
- You tried CCPD?
- Multiple times.
No answer, and I need
to get in contact with Cecile.
Hey, anything else
you want to say to the feds?
- I've said all I need to say.
Let's get moving.
- Gideon:Bhikkhuni Amala
confirms Wally West
is in deep meditation,
handling unrest
on the psychic plane.
- Which means we're out
of speedsters to call.
Iris?
Hey.
[warm music]
How are you here?
How is this possible?
- Deon was able to stabilize me
enough to come back
until he can find
a permanent cure.
- Oh, thank God.
I've missed you so much.
It's been impossible
without you here with me.
- Well, I'm here now,
and I'm gonna be fine.
- With everything
that's happened...
the war, you needing to heal
in the Still Force...
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, now that you're back,
it's perfect.
♪ ♪
- It feels like you wanted
to tell me something.
- It can wait.
Iris, oh, so much has happened.
You're not gonna believe this,
but...
- Our son and daughter
are here.
- Yeah.
How did you...
- I was watching
from the Still Force.
Deon let me see everything
that happened, and yeah.
They're amazing.
I mean Nora,
she's all grown up,
and Bart,
he's already a young man.
It's incredible.
- So you were with me
the whole time.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- So you know
who Godspeed is to Bart
and how much danger he's in.
[dramatic music]
Bart knows
what Thawne's done to me.
The pain that he's caused,
so if Godspeed
is Bart's Thawne...
- Then what did he do to Bart?
- Iris, those Godspeeds
quit fighting each other
to go after him.
I don't think
they're gonna stop
until they've killed our son.
♪ ♪
- Then we can't let him go out
there until the war is over.
[resolute music]
- Barry's
never gonna believe this.
- I can barely
believe it either.
In the last 40 days,
the Speed Force saturation
in your body has gone
from 0 to 100, Jay.
- [sighs]
You know, a year ago,
I thought I'd never run again,
but then I hit the jackpot.
And just in time too.
- Because an army
of evil speedsters
is attacking Central City?
- Joan, I know I'm rusty,
but Barry needs
all the help he can get.
- Fine, but I've got a patient
going into surgery
at the clinic.
So when you're out there
please remember...
- Be careful?
- Watch your head.
Doctor's orders.
- All right, old man.
Time to get in on the action.
[dramatic musical crescendo]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
What the hell do you want?
- You, Jay Garrick.
We want you.
[dramatic music]
- What gives, Bart?
You can throw stars
with your lightning,
but you can't catch a ball
of it in under 20 seconds?
- Nora...
[heavy breathing]
It's a lot harder
than it looks.
- Well, maybe you
should stop focusing
on being a badass parkouring
off every wall you see.
- So you agree
I do look badass.
That's it.
That's all
that I've ever wanted from you.
Nora, understand, I can do
all the stuff, not...Mom!
Hi!
[laughs]
[all laughing]
- I told you she'd be okay.
- I'm just glad our family's
finally together.
- I am so happy
to see you guys.
I'm so sorry
I couldn't get here sooner.
- No, it's all good.
Seriously.
Deon already told us about
what happens when...
Never mind.
What's up?
- We need to talk to you.
- Oh, can it wait?
We're just...
we're working on a new move
that we're actually gonna
use on Godspeed.
I think you're gonna
like it a lot.
It's kind of old-school,
which I think you're gonna be...
- Bart, you won't be going
into the field.
- Iris: Yeah, Bart,
your dad told me everything,
and I saw the rest
in the Still Force.
Look, it was one thing
when Godspeed was just
some meta
that you two were fighting
in the future, but...
- He's your Thawne,
which means it's personal.
- Yeah.
I mean...
Okay, Dad, I am sorry
for how I reacted earlier,
but I...
you don't know me...
like that yet.
I can keep my cool.
I promise.
I can.
Tell them.
I can keep my cool, right?
- But you can't.
♪ ♪
- Bart.
Dad.
I know Bart can be a bonehead,
but he's right.
You've only known him
for a few hours.
I've known him for 19 years.
I got this.
Trust me.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
They are so incredible.
- We make great people.
- Yeah, we do.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Thought I'd find you
moping in here.
You always come here
when you're angry.
- How could you turn on me
like that?
You're supposed
to have my back.
- I still do.
Look, I get why you're angry
after what Godspeed
took from you, from us?
- Godspeed...Nora,
Godspeed didn't take Uncle Jay.
He killed him.
He killed Uncle Jay...
Right in front of me.
Yeah, sure.
Dad and Uncle Wally
taught me how to run,
and how to meditate,
and all that's great.
Uncle Jay understood me.
He was the first person
that saw my impulsiveness
as a strength
and not as a weakness,
and he would literally tell me.
He'd say, "Bart, sometimes
you have to take a risk.
"Sometimes you have
to go with your gut...
"and is it impulsive?
Maybe.
But sometimes it's right."
He got me...
[sighs]
And now he's gone.
- I know.
But you've still got me,
and Mom, and Dad.
- How can...
can't we just tell them
what Godspeed did?
Like, I feel like if Dad knew,
he would understand
why it has to be me
who takes him down.
- Because if we did that,
we would be breaking
the most important rule.
- I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know.
- Look, Bart,
Uncle Jay did say that stuff
about taking risks,
but if he were here now,
seeing what we were up against,
what do you think
he would want you to do?
- [sighs]
He'd tell me sometimes
you have to take your hat off.
- See?
I'm always right.
- Someti...
You are sometimes right.
- Look, I will take Godspeed
down for the both of us.
I promise,
but you just gotta
stay here, okay?
[heroic music building]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- [sighs]
- Caitlin:
Since the MAD 2.0 isn't working,
we need to try another tactic.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Does this remind you
of anything?
- This seems so familiar.
- Are you all right?
- Ever since
I lost my memories,
I've been trying to understand
who I am
and how I ended up like this.
I figured
I must have had a breakdown.
Maybe somewhere there's
a wife and kids
wondering what the hell
happened to their dad.
I don't know.
Am I ever gonna know who I am?
[machine whirring]
- [sighs]
Come on.
What's wrong with me?
- So I finally finished
the last tweak on the S.E.E.
Now all that's left to do
is to finish charging
the solar panel, and voilà.
[laughs]
Oh, man.
My Pops would be so jazzed
to know that
this baby's maiden voyage
will be to take out
psycho speedsters.
[sighs]
You're almost done, right?
- How should I know?
- Battery's not even
10% charged yet.
With your output capacity,
it should be almost
89% charged by now.
Allegra, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
'Cause, like,
you've been acting...
- Chester, I'm fine.
[alarm buzzing]
- More clones just showed up.
Is your father's device ready?
- Chester's gadget, yes, but
the battery needs recharging.
- It needs kinetic energy
to power it, right?
- Yeah.
- Could it be any source?
- Theoretically yeah, but...
- All right, stand back.
Well, hot damn.
Yeah, it's ready now.
- I need you two
on comms with Iris.
- Wait, Iris is back?
- You heard him, let's go.
- [heavy breathing]
I'm in position.
- Nora, are you ready?
-Nora:On my way
with the guests of honor.
Now!
Holy shrap.
It worked.
[both laughing]
- Chester:Uh, guys?
Sensors are picking up
a massive increase
in the clones' kinetic energy.
They're recharging.
- [grunts]
Nora?
[grunts]
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
Nora?
Nora.
- Flash, we gotta go.
- Barry:You sure you're okay?
- Dad, Mom, I'm fine.
I swear.
So how did
the Godspeeds recover so fast,
let alone recharge themselves?
It's like they got stronger
all of a sudden.
- Chester: I think I know how.
Okay, so the S.E.E. battery
needed 700 nanometers
of microwave energy
to power the device,
but the battery wasn't charged
by Allegra.
It was charged with...
- My lightning.
- Which was equivalent to
5 billion nanometers of energy.
- So Barry's lightning
supercharged the S.E.E.
- Yeah, when the Godspeeds
were blasted,
they got a super dose of
your Speed Force energy too.
Barry, I am so sorry.
Look, I should have seen
this coming, and I...
- No, man.
No.
You did everything right.
This is not your fault.
- Okay, so how long
until the next batch shows up?
- 45 minutes tops.
But I'll see if I can get
my Pops' device
working again before then.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
What are you thinking?
- Even if we get
the S.E.E. working,
we're still outnumbered.
We need reinforcements.
- Hell to the yeah you do.
- [sighs]
- How long were you listening?
- Not long.
Not long.
I mean, just long enough
to hear that Dad
finally realized
that he should tag me in.
- He meant me, dumbass.
- No, I didn't.
- Wait, what?
- Nora,
we almost died out there.
I couldn't protect you.
I'm not putting you
in that position again.
- Yeah, but we didn't die,
and I can help.
Mom, a little backup
here, please?
- Nora,
this war is unpredictable,
and it's getting
more dangerous.
- What do you think
Bart and I deal with
every day in 2049?
- Yeah, come on.
We're heroes.
Dangerous is, like,
kind of part of the job.
- Not this time.
- You don't
just get to decide that.
I'm about to turn 30.
In four years.
The point is, unlike Bart,
I'm the real adult.
- We're your parents,
and we're saying right now
you're still
not going out there.
- You can't stop me
from fighting.
- Okay.
Me either.
Mom?
- Your father is right.
- Well, you can't just
send us back to 2049.
That's not an option,
and we're not gonna go
watch TV at Grandpa Joe's.
- We could always lock you
in a pipeline cell
until this is all over.
- You wouldn't.
- [laughs]
- We will if we have to.
- [sighs]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[knocking]
- So battery's not the problem.
I checked
the spectrum readings,
and you're
not emitting microwaves.
You've been blasting
ultraviolet light,
like your cousin.
As far as I know,
you only hit that range from
channeling negative emotions,
like anger or pain.
Allegra, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- Before,
you said you nuked your coffee.
It was ice cold.
And then you called me Chester.
You never call me Chester.
Did you get in a fight
with Esperanza?
'Cause you can
always patch that up.
- Not this time...
Because she's dead.
- Allegra, I am...I'm so sorry.
- It's not your fault.
It's mine.
Esperanza was my family,
and I should have been there
for her.
Just like I should be able
to charge this stupid thing,
but I can't.
And now, more people
are gonna get hurt,
and it's all my fault.
- It's not...
Your fault.
[sighs]
- This whole parenting thing
is different this time around.
- Yeah, I know.
I always knew our kids
would have a hard life
being speedsters,
but I never thought
they'd have to deal
with a Thawne of their own.
It's like there's
a curse on our family.
I mean, tragedy
follows us everywhere.
Maybe that's our real legacy.
- You don't believe that.
- This all started
the night Thawne killed my mom,
and I might not know
where he is now,
but our fight still isn't over.
And in the other timeline,
Nora's Godspeed killed
her best friend, Lia.
And now, I think this Godspeed
killed someone Bart loved.
History's repeating itself.
[sighs]
Iris, if we beat
the Godspeed clones here,
in 2021,
the real August Heart
will never get his powers back.
- Which means that when Nora
and Bart go back to 2049,
there won't be a Godspeed
there to endanger them.
- We have to break the chain.
- We will.
[alarm buzzing]
- Okay, the rebel Godspeeds
managed to hack
S.T.A.R.'s
communication systems
and send a transmission.
- What does it say?
[dramatic music]
- Godspeed:Flash.
Turn over the adversary now,
or else the one he loves
will die:
Jay Garrick.
♪ ♪
- Barry: What did Joan say?
- It's true.
Jay got his speed back when
the Speed Force was reborn.
- And then
those clones took him.
- They're gonna kill Jay.
- I won't let them.
- Bart, we've got
this under control.
- No, you don't.
- We're working on a plan.
Just give us some time.
- We don't have time, Dad!
- Guys, I'm triangulating
the Godspeeds'
comm signals now.
It came from Zauriel Cathedral
on Morrison Ave.
- Well, that's where I'm going.
- Bart, wait.
Dad, they knew how Bart would
react if they took Uncle Jay.
He knows he's running into
a trap, but he doesn't care.
You have to stop him.
You have to save him.
- We have to save him.
[uneasy music]
♪ ♪
- Jay.
I won't let it happen again.
♪ ♪
- Your inability to suppress
your rash nature
shall be your undoing.
- [screaming]
[screaming]
- You want more speed?
Come take mine.
- Nora, what are you doing?
- Buying you some time.
Save Bart.
- His primal impulses
killed him,
and now he's killed you too.
- Bart?
Bart!
Can you hear me?
Bart?
- They're right behind me.
- Get him out of here.
- Yeah.
- That way.
Okay.
Put him down.
- I say we give them heck,
Flash.
- On my mark.
- I leave Central City
for two seconds...
That won't hold them
much longer.
- Dad, Bart won't wake up.
[machine beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I should have stopped him
from going.
- Nora, this isn't your fault.
- Yes, it is.
I'm his older sister.
I'm supposed to keep him safe.
This is
what Godspeed always does.
He always goes after
the people we love the most.
- How's he doing?
- He's still unresponsive.
Bart's in some sort
of deep comatose state.
- The Godspeeds
were feeding off me
when Bart turned up,
and by the time they turned
their sights on him,
I had nothing left in the tank.
How'd you know
how to stop them?
- Actually,
it was my son's idea.
I guess sometimes it pays
to be impulsive.
- Can't argue with that.
- Why hasn't Bart's
speed healing kicked in?
- It has,
but is Speed Force saturation's
so depleted that whatever
speed he has left
is being used
to keep him alive.
I'll keep monitoring him,
but unfortunately,
all we can do now is wait.
[bell dings]
- I don't know.
[sighs]
Maybe if I would have
gotten there faster,
Bart would be okay.
- No, you saved our butts.
- She's right.
It's good to see you, man.
- It's good to see you.
Dig filled me in.
I figured you could use
a helping hand.
Jay Garrick.
[laughs]
Look at you getting
your speed back.
[both laughing]
And good timing too.
- I'll say.
- Listen, guys.
This war isn't over,
and now, there could be dozens
or hundreds of those things
on the way.
- I'll keep working
on the S.E.E.
- Hey, how about we use
those gauntlets
to fire another entropy trap?
- Synthetic entropy trap.
Unlike Time Trapper,
mine are temporary,
and the stronger
these clones get,
the faster they're gonna
break out of them.
- So we don't have
a way to depower them.
We don't have a way
to capture them.
What do we have?
- We have August Heart,
and we know he went to
the Flash Museum in 2049.
We just don't know why.
But it must have something
to do with why this war
got started in the first place,
which means
Heart has the answer
locked inside his mind.
I need to unlock it.
[sighs]
What about
the neural hypercollider?
I mean, we used it to project
my consciousness
into the future.
- So maybe it could project
your consciousness
into Heart's mind.
- So you want to go inside
the mind of a psychopath?
- It's the only option
we have left.
- If I readjust
the tachyon booster
with a neuro-fiber housing,
I think it could work, kid.
- Can you guys take care
of things in the field
while I'm in there?
- Of course.
Central City's my hometown.
I'm not losing her that easy.
- Me too; I'm ready
to kick some fakester butt.
- All right.
Good.
I need you guys
to protect this city
while I finish this fight.
- Joe:
So you gonna talk about it?
- Talk about what?
- That Creyke said
that he saw you die.
- Just drop it, West.
I spent years
letting Adam haunt me
for the pain that he caused,
the lives he took.
Now I can put it behind me
and get back to doing my job.
[car horns honking]
- My God.
- What the hell?
- Looks like the whole city's
trying to leave town.
Kramer, watch out!
[tires squealing]
Oh!
- That was close.
[sighs]
- Jay:As soon
as I flip the collider,
your synaptic pathways
will open,
and then Ms. Horton will guide
your consciousness into his.
- Don't worry.
I am gonna be right here
with you the whole time.
- Barry, I know
this August Heart
seems harmless,
but the real August Heart is
locked away inside of his mind.
From what we know...
- He's a monster.
- Be careful.
- The collider's primed.
- Ms. Horton?
- I'm ready.
- [sighs]
Yeah.
August?
If you're not comfortable with
this, you don't have to do it.
- It's okay.
I need to know who I am,
even if it's someone I despise.
- Yeah.
[sighs]
Okay.
[electrical zapping]
- Barry's synapses
are ready for transference.
- Barry, follow my voice.
- August:Flash.
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
[heavy bass music]
- I've been here before.
- No, you have not.
This is my mind.
My place.
My future sanctum.
- Heart?
- Congratulations.
You finally found me.
Well done.
- You knew I was coming.
- Actually, I expected you
a lot sooner,
but hey, we can't all
be overachievers.
You must have
so many questions.
Good thing
I have all the answers.
[voice distorting]
This is gonna be so much fun.
[dramatic choral music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.