Hey, it's Jeff and Joanna.
We're here for the sublet.
How are you doing?
Hello?
Wow.
Left a note.
Whoa.
What's all this stuff?
That's interesting.
You will find the key inside the fifth
drawer of the bedroom dresser.
After you've decide this is not
a place for you to stay,
then please shut the door behind you
and leave the building immediately.
Thank you.
Well that's a weird note, isn't it baby.
Yeah.
Let's go see what's over here.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, it's a decent size.
It's good.
Yeah.
What's in here?
It's locked.
What's in there?
Must be where the owner keeps her stuff.
We're not supposed to go in there.
What's this?
That's going to be your room.
That maybe your room.
It looks like...
Wow.
So what do you think of the place?
I just had deja vu.
That's a good thing.
Yeah, it's a good thing.
I don't know.
I guess it will do for now.
Hey, munchkin.
For now?
Well, until you can buy us
a big house in Malibu
and you become rich and famous.
Til then, be a good dad,
go unpack the car.
Alright.
You gonna miss me?
I know.
It's so exciting.
Oh, we haven't done that in forever.
Hasn't been that long.
Oh my God.
That was amazing.
It was okay.
What?
I'm just kidding.
You're right.
You're right, it was good.
Did you hear that?
What?
Sounded like
a rocking chair or something.
Rocking chair?
It's probably just the neighbours.
Yeah.
Hey, wish me luck tomorrow, will you?
You don't need it.
You think?
I know.
I'd still like some though.
Okay.
Hey.
So, I had a great shoot.
Shh, the baby's sleeping.
Right.
The director thinks the role
could be recurring.
No.
Yeah.
That's great.
We have to stay in town all season.
That's okay.
I'm not back to work for a while, so.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah.
My manager's booked me for
a bunch of meetings this week
so I'm gonna be pretty unavailable.
You going to be okay by yourself?
Yeah.
Of course.
Love you.
Hungry?
Here.
I went to the internet place today
but they said they couldn't
hook it up in this building.
So yeah, the address isn't
even listed in their database,
so they think that the wiring
is probably too old or something.
Yeah.
You're not even listening.
Sorry what?
What were you saying?
It's okay.
You done?
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm just really,
really nervous about tomorrow.
It's fine.
Look, if you want some help later on
with your lines,
after the baby's asleep,
I can work with you on it.
Yeah, that would be good.
Thanks.
Jeff?
Hello?
Look at the camera.
Alright here we go.
Aw, that's cute.
Hello?
It's okay.
I know, I know.
Shh, it's okay.
Shh.
It's okay.
Shh, are you hungry?
Shh.
Do you like it in here?
Morning.
Hey, I made you coffee.
Oh, thank you.
Is that sugar?
I think I'm gonna do those
thank you letters today.
There's some protein bars in here.
Jeff, look out the window.
What?
Just look out the window.
I don't see anything, okay.
Jeff.
There's nothing there.
I got to go.
Bye.
There was someone.
Porter?
Porter.
What are you doing over here?
Hi.
What?
You want to go inside?
Don't tell daddy.
We're not supposed to be in here.
They bang on the walls
as if there's something I can do
to stop my baby from crying.
But I never see anyone.
Only hear them banging.
I moved the nursery to the inner room,
in hopes of hiding the sound.
George was upset that I did so
without asking him.
The stress has been hard on him and
the baby keeps him awake at night.
He's in a foul mood all the time.
I have no one to talk to.
I'm so lonely.
Hey, babe.
Hey.
You got it.
Yeah.
But not only that.
But the producer thinks I'd be
perfect for a role in a film
he's doing with Debrowski.
Is that good?
It's amazing.
Okay, that's good.
The only thing is,
there'd be a scheduling
conflict with the TV show.
I'd have to go to LA for six months.
Would you do that?
Yeah, of course.
Give up a solid paycheck for
what's this thing pay?
Not much.
But the chance to work with Debrowski.
Can't pass that up.
Oh, do we have room for three?
Why?
I saw Alex on the way back.
Alex as in your ex-girlfriend?
Yeah.
She's gonna help me run lines.
She's coming over right now?
Yeah.
You have nothing to worry about.
It's just business.
I not worried Jeff.
I just don't like her.
Look at me.
Can you give me some warning.
I love you.
Uh huh.
Very much.
You owe me.
Uh huh.
I do.
I have to go get ready.
Why not.
Hey, you're here.
And so.
You look great.
Hello Joanne.
Hi.
Alex, it's been a while.
Yes.
I hardly ever get time to get back.
My schedule is insane.
Pardon?
I forget.
Can I help you set the table?
No, I'm fine.
I just hope I made enough food.
Jeff gave me no warning
that you were coming, so.
Don't worry about it.
I probably don't eat as much as you do.
I'm going to kill her.
Joanne.
Would you like to work out
with me while I'm in town?
Well you seem to be in great shape Alex,
so you must spend all
your time at the gym.
I work out every day.
Well with a baby, I never
seem to find the time.
You have to make the time.
I do and it can be very therapeutic.
Ugh, is that lamb?
Yes.
I'm a vegetarian.
For health reasons.
But, politically I can't stand
the thought of murdering animals.
I'll have a salad.
You eat salad, oui?
Don't you guys have to run lines?
Hey Joanne,
did you ever get ahold of your family?
Pardon?
Oh not saying,
I just, I over Jeff's agent
telling him that
your family were phoning.
Yeah, shit, Morgan called.
He wants to know why you
haven't called your sister yet.
What do you mean?
Well he said that she wants to know
why you haven't phoned
to you know, tell her you've
arrived safe and sound.
Okay, well that's kind
of ridiculous because
I just talked to her the other day,
and you saw me phone my
mother when we got here.
Alright, I'm just the messenger babe,
don't worry about it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you think that
you're smoking in here?
Is that a problem?
Yeah, we don't smoke around the baby.
For health reasons, you know.
You can, go to the balcony,
it's in the bedroom.
Please don't wake the baby.
She doesn't eat meat for health reasons
but she smokes, are you kidding me?
Come on.
And you tell her to go our bedroom.
Yeah, just give her a chance.
I don't need to give her a chance.
Run your lines, get her out of here.
I'm taking a bath
and then I'm going to bed.
Clean up.
I pity you.
Jeff.
Jeff, wake up.
What are you doing in here?
Hey babe.
I totally passed out last night.
I don't remember anything.
Drink too much?
Breakfast.
Sorry.
Ugh, why do you keep
putting sugar in my coffee?
I honestly don't know.
It's not even ours.
Alright, I got to go.
What, no kiss goodbye?
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Just stressed.
These lines.
Good job.
Don't go in there.
My baby.
I need my baby.
Please.
The routine of every day drives me mad.
I spend my days cleaning.
George offers no help,
but I feel as though I have
somehow disappointed him.
My daughter is the only joy in my life,
but she screams throughout the night.
I'm exhausted.
With no sleep, I struggle
through my empty life in a daze.
I feel such unease in this place.
Even when I know I'm alone,
I feel as though
there is someone else here.
Where's the baby?
In his crib, sleeping.
I was just there.
He's not there.
Don't be mad.
What the hell are you doing?
Shhh.
Why'd you put him in there?
That's the owner's room.
We're not supposed to be in there.
I know, okay.
I don't know how it happened.
The other day he just wouldn't stop
crying so I rocked him in that chair
and he had the best nap ever.
We're not supposed to be in there, okay.
It's also disgusting and musty
and it can't be good for him at all.
It's not that bad Jeff.
And he likes it in there.
He likes it in there?
Yes.
How could,
Jeff.
Please can he just nap in there.
It makes my day a lot easier.
No.
I'm locking it later on.
It should have been locked before.
How'd it go today?
Well I got it.
The TV show thing?
The film.
I got it.
What about the TV show?
I don't know.
Like, I'll know later
next week or something.
He's up.
Yeah.
And do you hear that.
He's not screaming.
He's happy in there.
Maybe that room is good
for something after all.
Yeah, okay.
If you think that we're having sex
while our baby's in the other room
you better think again.
Go change his diaper please.
Hopefully you hear about
that TV show by next week.
I mean it would make everything perfect.
If the schedules don't conflict.
No, I think that you
should try to make it work.
They're not gonna push for me, Jo.
I mean that if you can take both jobs,
I think that you should.
You know it's not like
I'm making a lot of money
on mat leave.
What if we want to have another baby?
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
I just,
I really would like to
find a more permanent place
if we're going to stay here.
What the hell was that?
What?
Didn't you hear that?
No.
This place is so creepy Jeff.
You seriously want to find a new place?
Yes.
What if I have to go to LA?
What, without us?
No, I want you.
I just really want to
get the baby settled.
And I hate this place.
Did you move anything in here?
No.
Okay, I'm locking it.
Hey, hey.
Whoa.
You seriously what to
find a new place already?
I'm sorry, it's just
really lonely and weird.
I mean I can smell people
cooking in the hallway.
I can hear footsteps.
I can hear people talking,
but I never see anyone.
I don't know.
Go outside.
Go for a walk.
I do.
Jesus Christ.
I get enough stress in my life already.
All I know is I'm stuck here
all day while you're out with Alex.
Oh this is what it's all about.
No, it's not.
Okay, I just had a baby.
My career is on hold.
I feel fat and ugly.
And you invite your ex
girlfriend over here
without even asking me.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
All I wanted was a phone call.
With some warning, that's it.
Alright, I'll know for next time.
Next time.
Yeah, okay.
You think she's coming over again?
Actually, she can't.
She's gone missing.
What do you mean missing?
I don't know.
What do you want me to say?
She's missing.
Are you serious?
No.
I don't think it's serious.
She's probably just wandering
off with some producer.
She does that sometimes.
You're jealous.
I'm not jealous.
Well, doesn't surprise me.
She's not that bright.
Hey, can you call
your sister by the way?
I talked to her yesterday.
I don't know.
My agent just keeps calling,
saying that she's calling
and she doesn't know where you are.
Well I don't know what
you want me to do Jeff.
I asked her and she said that
she's never called your agent ever.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know okay.
Listen.
I don't want to argue anymore.
It's my fault.
I brought Alex over.
I'm sorry.
Okay, come here.
I know that I sound crazy
when I say I want to move,
but I,
I don't feel at home here.
Let's just pause that.
Til we wait until we
hear about the TV thing.
Okay?
One moment please.
Hi.
You don't mind if we come in.
Of course not.
How can I help you?
We just have a few questions
about a missing person's case.
Oh right, yeah.
I don't know how much help I'll be,
but I'll certainly try.
My baby's just sleeping,
so if we could take it in here.
Thank you.
Uh huh.
So you are aware there's
a missing person you said.
How so?
My fiance told me that
you had questioned him.
We're here to discuss a
resident of this building.
I'm sorry.
Is Alex a resident here?
I'm sorry?
He said resident.
Yes, a woman named Joanna.
Joanna, but I'm Joanna.
You're Joanna Margaret,
married to Jeffrey Mitchell?
We're engaged.
But you have a child together.
Yes, we do.
Are you aware that you're missing?
Missing?
I'm right here.
You are aware that you
have a missing person's file?
No, why would I be?
Who phoned you to say
that I was missing?
You have family that hasn't
heard from you in nearly a month.
I just spoke to my sister yesterday.
She looks nothing like the photograph.
I'm sorry ma'am.
It's just that you look nothing
like the photo we have of you.
Nothing at all.
Can I see the photo?
Okay, this isn't me.
Isn't you?
No.
Clearly.
That certainly would explain a lot.
Do you not see how absurd this is?
You know, we're gonna
need to see some ID.
To make certain you are
who you think you are.
Look, I can't find my ID.
I thought that.
Oh, look at this.
Can I help you?
Oh, no, we have everything
we need, thank you.
You can't just come in here
and start going through
my private photos
without asking.
Are these private?
The book was on a shelf.
Out in the open.
For anyone to see.
Okay, look.
I'm a lawyer.
Which firm?
I'm not practising right now.
Of course not.
You can't just go into a
person's private belonging
because they granted you
access to the premises
for a case that is frankly ridiculous.
Ridiculous?
You've come in here and told me
that I'm missing,
when I'm clearly right here.
And now you're going through
my family's private affairs.
It's illegal.
And you'll be lucky if
I don't press charges.
We'll come back another time.
After you've calmed down.
I've asked you to leave.
Yeah, but we're gonna need this photo.
For our case.
What case?
You found me.
I'm right here.
Case closed.
Thank you.
But we need this photograph.
Why that photograph?
Jeff is in it.
Take it.
You might want to check that baby.
You know what.
It's okay, it's okay.
He never helps with the baby.
We're nothing but a burden to him.
I would leave but he
has hidden my documents.
He is abusive.
And no longer the man I married.
I'm certain that he has been sleeping
with the neighbour girl.
Although I have never seen her.
I can hear them.
I want to put a hole in
the wall and catch him,
but I'm afraid of what I might do
if I were to see them.
Please.
Hey.
Didn't hear you come in.
I just put Porter down.
I didn't hear back yet.
It must be killing you.
Well I feel like shit.
I think I'm coming down with something.
You feel a bit hot.
The cops stopped by today.
About Alex?
No.
It was about...
I don't even know how to say this so,
there was this homeless woman
who wanted inside of our apartment.
You didn't let her in did you?
Of course not, but,
when the cops were here,
they showed me a picture,
and I think it was her.
Did you tell them you'd seen her?
No.
I didn't connect it at the time,
because she looks a lot older now.
We should probably phone them then.
Yeah.
But this is where it gets really weird.
I think it's the woman
that we're subletting from.
That's crazy.
I know it is.
Well how do you even
know what she looks like?
From the pictures in the room.
That probably just looks like her.
No, I don't think so.
Joanna, we're not subletting
from a missing woman.
Think about it.
They didn't say that she was missing.
They said that I was missing.
You probably just misheard them.
They made comments about my weight.
Don't worry about that.
You just had a kid.
You'll be back to sexy
Joanna in no time.
Well they made me feel really gross.
But I guess I am.
I didn't mean it like that.
You're such an asshole.
Where the hell is this coming from?
I hope you're having fun with Alex
while I'm stuck at
home raising your son.
Joanna.
I love you.
Don't do this.
I'll let you know when dinner's ready.
Look I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
Joanna.
Come on.
Look I said I was sorry.
Joanna.
Look I'm not gonna cheat on you.
I love you.
I've just been distracted lately.
You're so certain about all that,
then why haven't we set a date?
When?
Look I know, okay.
I'm sorry too.
I don't know why it bothered me so much.
I, I could hear myself yelling at you,
and it wasn't even sure why.
I just feel so overwhelmed.
What are you reading?
It's a book I found in the apartment.
I think it's someone's journal.
Someone who lived here.
Probably shouldn't be reading it.
I know.
But I can't stop.
Anything good?
Not in the way you mean.
What do you think I mean?
Jeff don't.
Oh, come on.
It's been a while.
Okay, seriously.
I'm trying to actually have
a conversation with you,
and all you want to do is have sex.
Is that all I'm good for?
Jeff.
Your baby is mine.
Wake up.
What time is it?
It's early.
Why was I on the couch?
I don't know.
I couldn't wake you.
Who moved it across the room?
You did.
Why?
I don't know.
It's before we had sex.
What?
You don't remember.
Don't touch me.
What?
You had sex with me while I was asleep.
What's wrong with you.
You weren't asleep.
You initiated it.
I was exhausted.
I had a dream you cheated on me
with the woman in the photo.
With a dead woman?
It's not funny.
I'm mad.
I didn't do anything.
You need to relax.
I don't feel good.
I think you should take it easy today.
Maybe go outside.
Outside.
Why are you still standing there?
Have you not moved since I left?
I.
Who moved the couch?
You did.
That's it.
I'll call the manager.
Hello.
Hello?
You're baby's mine.
Porter.
What's the matter?
TV thing's gonna work out.
Okay, well that's great, isn't it?
Schedule conflict?
No, that was fixed.
Well then congratulations.
I lost the film role.
Why?
Someone called the producer
and told them that I was an alcoholic
and I was difficult to work with.
Who would do that?
They said it was a woman.
Are you accusing me?
No.
It sounds like it.
Well who else would it be?
Well I don't know.
Maybe your friend, Alex.
Alex tried to get me the
role in the first place.
She's been on my side
since the beginning.
And I haven't been?
No, you.
How long has this been going on?
Just happens sometimes.
That's crazy.
Hey.
Shut up.
I just don't understand why someone
called the producer like that.
What the hell do they want?
I don't like it here.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
I'll say.
I mean here in this apartment.
Shut up.
Are you going to be alright?
Really sorry you didn't get that role.
It's late.
I think my agent can fix it.
I'm just gonna go get some sleep.
You look sick.
I feel terrible.
You gonna come?
No.
I'm going to stay up and read a bit.
Okay.
What's this?
Hmm?
This blanket.
Morgan just called.
What?
There's still a chance
I can get this part.
I can't take it anymore.
George won't even speak to me.
He just yells.
He blames me for the death of our baby.
But it is his fault.
His fault I had to run next door
because of his affair.
His fault I had to leave her alone.
His fault I was so distracted
that I left her alone with the razor,
and she swallowed it.
I will poison him.
I have put cyanide in the sugar,
and mixed it with his coffee
for the last two weeks.
Soon he will be dead.
And I will be free.
Oh my god.
Please work, please, please.
Please stop it.
Shut up.
Please stop.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I thought you went out.
Listen, I don't have time
for your shit today, okay.
I'm exhausted.
I told you that.
What are you doing anyway?
The drains clogged so I
called the manager, and..
It's not clogged.
You have the stopper in.
What the hell's going on with you?
I don't know what's going on, Jeff.
You're tired.
I think maybe we should
call your sister.
I couldn't even use the
phone to call the manager,
because it's broken like
everything else in this apartment.
This again, okay.
I think, maybe you should
take some sleeping pills.
So now you want to drug me?
You need the rest.
You'll be fine.
Trust me.
You're not listening to me Jeff.
I'm done listening.
You keep me up every
night with your cleaning.
And your moving around furniture.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Why do you think people
are banging on the walls?
You're keeping them up.
I don't get up and move
the furniture around.
It's not me.
Bullshit.
Enough.
I don't, I don't want
to stay here tonight.
I don't know what's going on.
We'll figure it out
in the morning, okay.
I'm sorry.
Just take this.
Just take it.
Please.
You need rest.
Come on.
Okay.
That's good, now sleep.
All the anger and rage I have hidden
since the baby died came out.
He's gone.
But the hate remains.
Try as I might, I cannot
remember what happened.
I awoke and found him dead.
And I know that it was
I who had killed him.
The blood covered the
wall of the nursery.
The two cops who visited
when the baby had died
said they'd return.
I had to do something.
I cleaned it as best I could.
But it was no use.
I had to hide the stain.
He is gone and I am still here
in this awful place,
with my baby dead, I
have nothing to live for.
My punishment is to remain here, alone.
Forever.
I will never leave.
Never leave this place.
Never have peace.
I am resolved.
I must take my own life.
Look.
Did you read it?
Yeah.
So what?
Jeff someone was murdered here.
She killed him in that room,
and then she killed herself.
How does that affect us?
Yeah?
I think she's still here.
Listen, that's crazy.
I'm here.
I'll protect you.
You need to go to sleep.
I'm so tired.
Please get me out of here.
Jeff.
I know you're in there.
Open up.
Jeff.
Jeff, is that you?
Who the fuck is Jeff?
Who are you?
Where you been?
You think you just go
out any time of night?
Where is Porter?
Where's Porter?
Who the fuck is Porter?
Who's Jeff, you little slut?
What have you done with my baby?
It was an accident.
I told you that.
How many times do I have to tell?
Porter!
Are you fucking mental.
It's been almost a year.
I'll the police.
Enough of this shit.
I'm gonna teach you a lesson
you won't forget so quick.
My fiance's gonna be home any minute.
I'm your husband, you dumb slut.
I'm sick of your crazy shit.
The baby is dead.
Get over it already.
Porter.
Come on.
Please.
Let me in you bitch.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hello, we're here to see the sublet.
Hello.
Is anyone there?
I don't think anyone's there.
Hello.