Robin!
I heard what happened to Robin.
She wasn't in the street.
She was one step
off the fucking curb.
- I'm sorry, who are you?
- Name's Butcher. Billy Butcher.
Supes lose hundreds of people
each year to collateral damage.
- That's where I come in.
- To do what?
Frenchie, I need
your help, mate.
- Who is he?
- Oh, this here is Hughie Campbell.
Hughie? Mother's Milk.
- Who's that?
- She's a Supe Terrorist.
Her name's Kimiko.
Bonjour, Kimiko.
I have always wanted
to be in The Seven.
Please welcome Starlight.
It's just a question of how bad
you want to be in The Seven.
We are going
to be stationing you
in Sandusky, Ohio for a while.
- I'm Hughie, by the way.
- Annie. Would you like my number?
Hughie.
Looks like you've got
your tongue
halfway down
the opposition's throat.
- She's not a bad person.
- She's a Supe.
Hugh Campbell
killed Translucent.
- What if he was helped?
- Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
Keep those hands
down by your sides.
You have to explain, Hughie.
You were the only thing
that I could count on.
This is about Compound V.
It gives the Supes
their powers.
What are you talking about?
We're born like this.
That was diabolical.
No one's putting Supes
into national defense.
You stay the fuck back
or I'll laser you!
If they let us
into the military,
this will never happen again.
I know what it's like
to lose someone.
Homelander raped my wife Becca.
You and me,
we're in this together.
- We have to go back for them.
- This is never gonna stop...
- it's just gonna be more blood...
- If you don't like to play,
why did you join
the fucking team?
You came here?
- Without Butcher?
- Yeah.
I'm out.
You came.
I'm a fucking superhero.
I think he's having
a heart attack.
No more lies.
You fucking promised me.
Hey, pal.
I'm your father.
Becca?
Baby kale salad?
I'm on page 134.
Chain of command doesn't apply
to other military contractors
in the field; I don't see why
it should apply to us.
Caprese sandwich?
Well, when they're in
actual combat,
whom exactly
do your heroes report to?
Same person as always. Me.
Spicy chicken cilantro wrap?
Subheading 16.
We need a top secret,
Yankee White designation
for Compound V.
Come on, Stan.
Only one man okays that.
You want to stroll into
the Oval Office
and start barking orders?
Hell yes.
Half our own heroes don't know
they have Compound V
in their veins.
You want China finding out?
This one: "Best efforts
to limit collateral damage"?
We'd prefer stronger wording.
That's standard language
for our New York contract.
L.A., Chicago.
Exactly what casualty allowance
are we looking at here?
Officially?
Zero, of course.
But cone of silence? 34%.
Veggie frittata?
Maybe "By The Power
of My Holy Fire"?
That's too wordy.
We want a catch phrase
that is catchy.
How about...
"Burn in Truth!"
That is a good catch phrase.
I think that...
Today I can report
to the American people
that Black Noir
has conducted an operation
killing the Super Terrorist
known as Naqib.
But that doesn't mean
sacrifices won't still be made.
The proof of that, sadly...
lies before us.
For today, we mourn
a fallen member of The Seven.
Translucent.
Murdered in cold blood
by the cartel
Super Terrorist El Diablo.
Before he left,
Translucent said to me...
Almost as if he knew
something was gonna happen,
he said...
"Hey, Homelander.
Tell my son Maverick
that I love him."
And he also said,
"You find
those Super Terrorists..."
Well, Super Villains is really
the only term, but he said,
"You find them, Homelander.
And you stop them."
So I say to you, Maverick...
and to all the sons
and daughters
of this great nation,
I will stop them.
I will save you.
I'll do it for you.
For America.
And for a dear...
dear old friend.
Goodbye, brother.
And thank you.
Hey, that's my shoulder.
What?
Right there. That's my fucking
shoulder, they...
They cut me from the picture.
They can't...
can't just cut me
from the fucking picture!
They can't cut me out!
Okay. That's enough.
Time to go.
Just get me another
fucking lava flow, please.
I said it's time to go,
or I call TMZ.
Out of sight, never out of mind!
Two for $64!
Out of sight, never out of mind.
Two for...
Good to see you.
Thank you.
Yeah. There you go.
I know.
I miss him, too, pal.
- Thank you so much, Starlight.
- Mwah. Thank you, guys.
It means a lot.
- Homelander, Starlight.
- Hi, David.
- David.
How's everyone holding up
in the Tower?
Well...
I'm not gonna lie, um,
- it's hard.
- Mm-hmm.
It's really hard. Um...
It comes in waves, you know?
Yeah, but this one,
he's just really been our rock.
He sat us down and he said,
"We're more than just a team.
We're a family.
And we need to pull together
like one."
Aw... Starlight.
- Thank you for saying that.
- Aw, thank you.
Really. I don't know where we
would be without you.
Isn't she the best?
- Isn't she the best?
- Oh...
You both...
Looks good.
The fuck you going?
Uh... no, I'm just
getting you your Purell.
Get the shit with aloe.
And come right back.
Yeah. Yeah, the aloe.
It's really good.
Keeps your skin s-smooth. Okay.
- Citizen Starlight.
- Coming this fall on Vought.
Justice never looked so good.
The-the burner phone, did you
- snap the SIM card?
- Jesus.
When was the last time
you slept, Hugh?
Head down. Head down. Sorry.
I just... I'm wanted
and you're kind of super famous,
so, uh...
- Did you snap the SIM card? I...
- Yes. Uh, yes.
I snapped the SIM card, okay?
And no one followed me
down here,
and they can't even trace
my chip down here.
We're okay.
You look good.
Yeah, you, um...
you look good, too.
You look very, you know, uh...
Yeah, I'm lying. I'm sorry.
- You look like shit.
- I know.
I know.
Where are you guys living?
Club Med in Ibiza.
It's been awesome.
The foam parties will
change your life.
Idiot.
Oh, um... here it is.
Oh, shit.
I know him.
- You do?
- Yeah.
I mean, not for a while,
but yes, from my
Capes for Christ days.
Are you sure you can do this?
I have a choice?
Hey, I, uh...
I saw a really great picture
of you
at the Teen Choice Awards
with, um... what's his name?
Ansel Adams?
Alden Ehrenreich.
Are you stalking me
on Instagram?
No. No, of course not.
Get over yourself.
So did the PR people put you
together or what, what's...
- No. He's a nice guy.
- He's an actor.
He's an actor who didn't
lie to my face every day.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, I got it. Ouch.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I... Hughie, I...
Times Square, 42nd Street.
Transfer is available...
Hey.
Get some sleep.
I'll sleep when I know
you're safe.
You think this is fun?
You think water's supposed
to be fun?
Try swimming in the
Mariana Trench,
you little fucking idiots.
Yeah, not so fun there.
No, it's dark and it's cold.
- And you're so alone.
- Sir?
- You're so...
...goddamn fucking alone.
Swim free, little fish.
You made bail.
Hey, man.
Want a Fresca?
Thanks.
Hey, I know you.
Yeah, you're, uh, Raven...
Ravenwing.
It's Eagle. Eagle the Archer.
Out of Cleveland?
We met, like, five times
at Vought-Con.
I mean... mm.
No, that doesn't matter.
You bailed me out?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Because even heroes need
a hand once in a while.
Come on.
The Translucent franchise,
especially Invisible Force 2,
is...
Please.
My baby needs a mother.
Oi! Shut your trap,
you dumb bird,
or else I'll bollocks you.
But that's exactly what
William Butcher did.
He murdered Vought Vice
President Madelyn Stillwell
using upwards of 30 pounds
of C-4.
Why would William Butcher
do it?
Disgruntled, perhaps,
over his deceased wife,
a former Vought employee.
And why was Madelyn Stillwell's
baby found safe in a yard
17 miles away?
It is a puzzle.
Where is Monsieur Charcuter?
- Why hasn't he called?
- Who cares?
He could be dead.
No. No.
He's too much of an asshole
to die.
...or any of his known
associates...
Marvin Milk, Hugh Campbell,
or this man,
whose real identity
is unknown...
please call 1-888-0-CRIMES.
Christ.
We gotta get out of here, now.
Good passports do not
come cheap.
I sell the RPGs,
smuggle in the Kalashnikovs.
We have enough money.
That's it.
- Where will you go, Petit Hughie?
- Could just stay here.
With Frenchie's gangbanger
friends.
The cots, they got 31 flavors
of semen on them.
You'll love 'em.
Oh, and you have a better idea?
No, maybe we can stay,
all of us,
in your mother's asshole.
Or... maybe we could not run.
You are like a record
that is broken.
Well, we shouldn't just give up.
Guys, we get some Compound V,
we-we bring it to
The New York Times,
we burn Vought to the ground.
You got some V, Hughie?
- 'Cause I don't.
- We could...
get some.
Someone could help us get it.
And who might that be?
You did not hear the television?
We are famous now.
- Butcher even more so.
- Fuck Butcher!
We don't need him.
A-Team had Hannibal.
Dirty Dozen, Lee Marvin.
Beatles, Brian Epstein.
We don't need Butcher.
Okay, who's going to
be our captain? You?
I mean, guys, just-just-just
hear me out.
Shut the fuck up!
This is over.
Homelander, hi.
Ashley.
Glad to see you're, uh,
making yourself at home.
Yeah.
Renovation is definitely
overdue.
It's like 2003 called,
they want their office back.
You know?
Huh. I liked it.
Yeah, me, too.
It was really great.
Homelander, I just want
to thank you again
for recommending me
for this job.
I was so surprised
to get the call.
I am gonna fill
Ms. Stillwell's shoes
as best I can.
God rest her soul.
Yeah.
God rest it. Yeah.
Any luck catching her killer,
that Butcher maniac?
No, not yet.
But we will.
Oh, good news.
I think I found a hero.
Perfect candidate
to replace Translucent.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
So soon?
He's in the gym right now.
You want to meet him?
Do I?
Lead the way.
That's Blindspot, right?
A differently abled
member of The Seven.
We're gonna poll through
the roof with millennials.
Inclusion's a big priority
to them right now.
- Amazing.
- And then I think we find
an ethnic or female
or, fingers crossed,
an ethnic female
to replace the Deep,
and we're golden.
Homelander, wow, you're...
It's-it's an honor, sir.
Wait. Hold on.
- You can tell it's me?
- Mm-hmm.
Wow.
That's-that's impressive.
You don't need super eyes
when you have super ears.
Can I just say, that is amazing.
And you, my friend,
are a true hero.
Not because of what you do
for a job,
but...
Well, because of what
you've overcome.
Thank you.
That means everything
coming from you.
Aw, stop it. Come on.
Hey, guys, um,
- I just have one question, if that's okay.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
All right, so...
what happens if, uh,
I don't know, I do this?
And now you're just another
useless fuckin' blind guy.
This must be some kind
of a joke.
Ashley...
What made you think I would ever
allow a cripple into The Seven?
For fuck sakes, Ashley,
don't look at him, look at me!
Ashley! Look at me.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Let's get one thing straight.
The only reason you're here
and not doing corporate PR
for fucking Diva Cups
is that I brought you here.
You are dispensable,
which means you answer to me.
Okay. Okay.
From now on,
I will set my own agenda,
I'll approve my own marketing
and write my own talking points.
You will tell me everything
that goes on
on the 99th floor,
and I mean everything.
Every call, e-mail, group chat.
If a fucking light bulb
goes out, you will tell me.
And, Ashley, in no fucking way
do you decide
who goes in The Seven.
I decide.
Do we have an understanding?
Yes.
Translucent was
laid to rest today,
surrounded by his family,
friends, fans
and fellow Vought comrades.
You can see the memorial
featuring a performance
by Starlight
singing "Never Truly Vanish"
on Voughtify.
Available now.
Bet you can't resist
this arrest.
America's hottest crime-fighter
is giving law enforcement
a superpowered makeover
in Citizen Starlight.
Coming this fall from Vought.
Go ahead, make her day.
You know how it is.
Don't want to get stuck
with the cleaning bill.
Okay.
So, what's your poison?
You a leg guy?
Uh, d... a-an arm,
please, actually.
400?
Um, d-do you want me to, uh,
- s-saw or-or chop or...?
- Whatever floats your boat, tiger.
Holy shit.
Holy shit! Holy shit!
Thank you. That was so...
I-I can keep the arm, right?
Yeah, just keep it refrigerated.
For an extra grand,
I'll let you chop off my dick.
Where's the closest ATM?
- What the hell happened?
- Aide!
Holy shit. Sit him down.
- Sit him down.
- Just bring him over here.
Aide le!
- Aide le!
- What's wrong?
Shit.
Listen, he's broken
every single bone in his arm.
Broken half his ribs.
I can't do nothing here.
You got to take him
to the hospital.
Hospital...
Translate for me, Frenchie.
Tell him to take him
to the hospital.
Fuck!
Move, move.
Okay?!
What'd he say? What's going on?
Frenchie, what did he say?
- Cops seen this?
- No one's seen it.
I ain't trying to get
life without parole.
They promised me.
They would only smuggle in guns
and cocaine and fentanyl.
- Not fucking...
- Not human fucking cargo?
- Jesus Christ, Frenchie.
- They didn't tell me.
Or you didn't ask.
A Supe.
Supe Terrorist.
They got paid to smuggle in
a Supe Terrorist.
How about this one?
How does it make you feel?
Anyone?
- I hate it.
- That's a strong reaction, Margaret.
I'd love to follow up on that.
What do you mean
when you say you hate
the term "Super Terrorist"?
I just mean, it's really scary.
It makes me want
to lock the door
and hide under the bed,
you know?
Which means a double-digit drop
the opening weekend
of the Tek-Knight movie.
I keep saying
"Super Villain"
is the better term.
Uh, "Super Criminals" sounds
like something in a cartoon.
Jill, ask them what they think
about "Super Villain."
Uh, what about the term
"Super Villain"?
That sounds better to me.
More exciting.
- More exotic.
- Okay.
Okay, turning our attention
back to these,
which do you prefer?
"Saving America,"
can I get a show of hands?
Okay. How about
"Saving the World"? Wow.
Unanimous, strong reaction.
So what is it about...
Nope. It's "Saving America."
I-I don't know. I-I feel like
"Saving the World" has a...
Okay. But is there
something specific
about "Saving the World"
that "Saving America..."
It's Americans that are gonna
keep us in the Army,
not the fucking world.
It's "Saving America."
Pull the trigger.
Great. Great.
Hey, man.
Thanks for letting me crash.
Sorry, about the bathroom.
- I'll clean it up.
- No need to apologize.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
- You scared me.
- Oh, that's just Carol.
Good friend.
Carol, this is the Deep.
I have been looking forward
to meeting you, Deep.
Would you like a Fresca?
Thank you.
Anyway, no need to apologize.
We've all been there.
It's tough.
- Been where?
- Rock bottom.
I...
I don't think
I'm at rock bottom.
Uh, f-for me,
my aha moment came with
a hostage situation at Kroger.
Multiple shooters.
I showed up, I'm letting
arrows fly, my aim is perfect.
But...
...there's only so many arrows
a quiver can hold.
I just ran out.
And then, we lost
a lot of good people that day.
Then you start to question,
like, fucking arrows
against TEC-9s?
- But?
- But I came to see
that archery isn't irrelevant,
it's timeless.
It's a pure and ancient art.
Carol helped me see that.
And what are you, his therapist
- or something?
- No.
No, therapy's
very destructive, actually.
You could say I'm his teacher.
What about you, Deep?
What-what about, what about me?
How did you end up here?
You can tell her, Deep.
Tell her what?
About your drinking.
About your self-esteem issues.
- Really open up, Deep.
- No, I don't...
I don't have a drinking...
- I'm fine.
- This is a safe space, Deep.
If you don't have
any self-esteem issues,
why are you constantly
demeaning women?
- That's a good question, Deep.
- Okay, thank you.
You know what? I don't know
what the fuck this is,
but it's weird as fuck,
so I'm leaving.
W-We just want to help.
- Carol really helped me, Deep.
- No, thank you.
Help you get back
into The Seven.
Yesterday, the Deep was found
drunkenly ranting at children
at Splash Zone
in Sandusky, Ohio.
He was later arrested
and taken to Sandusky...
...he was released on bail
shortly after.
Did you make this?
You wrote something.
"Boy."
What boy?
I do not understand. What boy?
Okay, so?
They were wired the money
from a blind account
to smuggle the bastard in.
Cold trail.
Amazing fucking friends
of yours.
I never said they were
my friends, huh?
I only said we will be...
safe here.
Okay, okay, all right.
What do we do?
Oh, you just call 911.
What, an anonymous tip?
Yeah, I'm sure that'll go
straight to the mayor.
You saw that video.
What if he does that
to-to an airplane?
Or the fucking Brooklyn Bridge?
So, what's your big plan,
Hughie?
Okay, the CIA lady, right?
Rayner.
Right, the same CIA
that wants to clamp our nuts
into some jumper cables.
We could call Butcher.
For the last time,
we don't need Butcher.
Then what?
We should...
call Annie.
"Call Annie."
Annie?
Yeah.
You mean Starlight?
'Cause that's who she is.
Vought has her phone
so bugged...
they're praying
that you do that.
Oh, no.
You fucking called her?
No, no. I'm not,
I'm not stupid, okay?
- I texted her.
- Oh, fuck.
And then we met up, but we're
getting some Compound V.
-Fuck you, Hughie!
Are you fucking crazy?
-M.M., easy!
- Are you fucking crazy?!
- We were careful!
- What the fuck are you doing?!
- We used burner...
- We used burner phones.
- Kid, you don't get it!
They could've been
following you.
They could be watching us
right fucking now!
If you're the fucking reason
why I can't finish
that Vermont country dollhouse,
I will fucking end you.
You've been walking
around for days
like you want to kick my ass,
so do it already.
Goddamn it.
Shit!
I don't want to kick
your ass, Hughie.
I just don't want to get dragged
back into this shit, all right?
I want to get home to my wife
and my kid.
That's it.
If I still can.
This guy could kill
a lot of people.
Hughie... let somebody else
handle it, okay?
There's no one else!
No one's coming to save us.
You don't get it.
You are not a soldier.
You're not a spy.
You're just a kid that
sells stereo equipment.
No, I don't!
I don't have a job.
Or Robin.
Or my dad.
Or Annie.
One way or another,
they all, uh...
Now all I have is this.
This.
Which is really fucking
depressing, but it's true.
So, maybe I can't be Lee Marvin.
But I can be Harry Potter.
Or, uh... you know, John Connor
or-or-or what's her name
from The Hunger Games.
Katniss.
Yeah, the point is
I could be the person
that nobody thinks is awesome,
but it turns out they're
kind of fucking awesome.
Listen, we help the CIA lady,
she could help you maybe
get back to your family.
Did you ever think of that?
My baby needs a mother!
Oi! Shut your trap,
you dumb bird...
or else I'll bollocks you.
But that's exactly
what William Butcher did.
Gecko?
Is that you?
Starlight?
I mean, Annie, hi.
- Hi.
- Oh, my God, hi!
Look at you,
big-time Seven hero.
Oh, shut up.
You know, I-I work
in Vought Tower
at the, uh, labs on-on 67?
Oh, you don't say?
I see your posters everywhere.
They're marketing
the shit out of you.
I'm happy for you, really.
Buy you some coffee?
Thank you.
Yeah, at the, uh, Capes for
Christ Bible Camp, yes, totally.
Mm-hmm, that Passion play
we put on?
You were the best Jesus.
I mean, no one's gonna take
a nail through the hand
like I can.
And Big Game was Pontius Pilate.
Oh, my God, those freckles.
You know he wanted
to make out with me?
- Pontius Pilate and Mary hooking up?
- Mm-hmm.
Ooh, "sacri-licious."
Yeah, we never did.
Why not?
- He was so cute.
- Yeah, it just,
it was what Ezekiel always said.
And my mom, too.
That God is watching over you,
every second.
You know, I thought
that He was watching us,
and I thought
that He'd be upset.
Yeah, it's a,
it's a messed up thing
- to tell a kid.
- Yeah.
But looking back?
I should've made out
with Big Game.
I should've done
a lot more stuff.
Because...
there is nothing
up there.
There's nobody in the sky
watching over us.
Not God, not Homelander.
Not anybody.
It's all just...
lies.
I need a favor.
Yeah.
Yeah, anything
for a Bible Camp alum.
I need you to go
into the labs on 67,
and steal me
a sample of Compound V.
Um...
I, uh...
I don't,
I don't know what that is.
Ah, see?
Another lie.
I know how we're made.
And it is not Jesus.
I can't.
I mean, it's impossible.
I'm a nobody there.
I'm a lab rat.
They cut off my limbs
and they grow back.
- I can't get you...
- You have to.
Or I put this
on Facebook tonight.
Gecko,
former teen star
of Vought Summertime Clubhouse,
working as an S&M hooker
as a side hustle?
I'm sure inquiring minds
will want to know.
Annie?
I thought that we were friends?
I'm sorry.
But...
we're not anything.
Hi.
You know who we are.
But let's meet another hero.
This is Lance Corporal
Dan Miller.
Dan and the other brave
Marines of Second Battalion
are helping keep you safe
from the Super Villain threat.
We're proud to fly
alongside them.
And now, we could use
your support.
That's right, Maeve, with our
new campaign, Saving America.
Here I go, you guys!
Wish me luck.
Oh, FYI, not a real base.
As if Homelander and Maeve
are gonna eat MREs
and piss in a ditch
with the rest of the grunts.
Uh, hey, yeah, hi, we're
filming right now. Excuse me?
Also, you might recognize
"Army Boy" as Hotel Clerk #2
-from "The Devil's Breath"
-Hello, excuse... okay.
Episode of Criminal Minds:
Beyond Borders.
Well, hello!
Oh, my God, hi!
My nana's your biggest fan.
I'm Stormfront.
- Great.
- Oh, right, yeah.
From Seattle, right?
Uh... Portland, actually,
Your, uh, Highness.
Holy shit!
Your eyes are really
fucking blue up close.
You are... fun.
It's been a hoot,
but we got work to do,
so... let's get back to it.
Oh, totally, uh,
they just wanted me to meet you.
Who?
Oh, the boys on 82.
- I'm the new girl.
- Wait...
what are you talking about?
Oh! Hi.
I'm in The Seven.
Replacing Translucent.
God bless his soul.
Ink's barely dry, but, uh,
yeah, reporting for duty,
so... fuck yeah!
Um, no, I don't think that
this is, it's not true.
I don't know anything
about this.
Wow!
Well, uh, Stormfront?
Who delivered the good news?
Oh, uh, Mr. Edgar,
the big guy?
- All right, back to one.
- Wonderful.
Great.
All right!
- Great!
- We're going again, people.
Well, I think
this is going great.
You know,
you ain't John Cusack, man.
You ain't got
no motherfucking boom box.
- Sorry?
- You want to get back together
- with Starlight.
- No. No-no, I don't.
Yes. Yes, you do.
But this ain't the way
to do it, Hughie.
You can't keep
pulling this shit, man.
Calling her, texting her.
Are you crazy?
You know, you sound
like Butcher.
- She's on our side.
- I know.
I'm saying this for her, kid.
You're putting her in danger.
Homelander finds out that
she's been talking to you?
She's fucked.
The deeper you keep pushing her
into this thing,
the deeper in the meat grinder
she goes.
How are you guys doing?
We're hanging in there.
Has Butcher contacted you?
Nope.
He's completely ghosted.
Do you think he killed
Madelyn Stillwell?
I'd like to think
that he didn't.
But I... I don't know.
Deputy Director,
I know this might not be
the best time to ask,
but do you ever...?
Hear about your family?
Your daughter is, uh,
starting soccer, I think.
Soccer?
Um, ma'am.
Can M.M. see them?
You know what, let's,
let's see if this checks out.
And I will see what I can do.
Thank you, ma'am.
Okay, so give me
the description of this guy.
All right, uh,
about five-ten, 165,
black hair, wearing
knockoff jeans and sneakers
probably from Taiwan,
maybe India.
You got all that from the video?
So, the other shoe drops,
and it just crushes us all.
Meaning?
Meaning I've been trying
to put this puzzle together,
and there's a missing piece
and it's been driving me nuts.
And I think you
just handed it to me.
Okay, so, then, what's
the whole picture?
The whole picture... it's Vought!
It's a fucking coup
from the inside.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
Uh, ma'am, your nose.
- Fuck!
- Let's get the fuck out of here!
- Holy shit!
-Come on! Get in! Go, go, go, go, go!
Must be a Supe out there.
Are-are our heads gonna explode?
Frenchie, who do you know
who could do that?
No one!
Are our heads gonna explode?!
Look, I have a daughter.
I'm worried about
Super Terrorists, too.
But that does not mean
that Vought can use
that fear to control us.
- Morning.
- Mr. Edgar, I'm sorry, I...
That's all right, Samantha.
Busy day.
Morning, Homelander.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Well, you never come up to 99.
So, figured I'd pay you a visit.
- What a lovely idea.
- Right?
After all,
you run a superhero company,
and, uh, you never check in
with your superheroes,
do you?
Like, uh... oh, I don't know...
around the hiring of that girl,
for example.
You wished to be consulted
on Stormfront?
Well, why not?
I signed off on all the rest.
I'm the leader of The Seven.
For which you have
my undying respect.
See, I don't think I do.
No.
Not even Madelyn would've dared
to try and pull
this kind of shit.
Of course you know how important
you are to everyone at Vought.
No, no. Stan.
I am Vought.
You show my photo to some
illiterate fucking camel jockey
in the middle of the Sahara,
he's gonna turn around and say,
"Homelander,"
in perfect American.
You know what?
My contract's up,
end of this year.
Maybe it's time I, uh, move on.
How do you think your
shareholders
would feel about that?
What do you know
about Frederick Vought?
Excuse me?
Frederick.
Vought.
Our esteemed founder.
Well, I don't know, um,
not a lot, probably.
I only read his autobiography...
five times?
Not the self-serving bullshit
that we peddle to the
shareholders, the real story.
- Enlighten me.
- Got his doctorate from Munich.
Ahead of his time in genetics.
Such the rising young star
that in '39,
Hitler appointed him
chief physician at Dachau,
where he enjoyed
a ready supply of human subjects
on which to test his earliest
iterations of Compound V.
For which we condemn in
the strongest of possible terms.
Early in '44,
he felt the winds change,
got spirited away to the Allies.
When Oppenheimer was
flailing with the bomb,
Dr. Vought already had practical
applications of Compound V
tested in the field.
Heroes like Soldier Boy,
killing Germans by the dozen.
So, Roosevelt pardoned him,
and he became
as Wonder Bread American
as Disney and Edison.
Well, this is
a truly fascinating,
if not slightly condescending
lecture, but, um...
I don't think
I see the point, Stan.
The point is...
that you are
under a misconception
that we are a superhero company.
We are not.
What we are, really,
is a pharmaceutical company.
And you are not
our most valuable asset.
That would be our confidential
formula for Compound V.
Which you,
man-child that you are,
released into the wild.
Don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, let me remind you.
You slipped Compound V
to terrorists all over the globe
to get you and your cronies
into national defense.
But maybe at the cost of
destroying the whole company.
I don't think I appreciate
your tone, sir.
Not much at all.
And I don't appreciate that the
FDA now knows about Compound V,
or that it's
only a matter of time
before the public finds out.
While you're preening
at the Golden Globes,
we're busy,
running around like maniacs
trying to clean up
the mess you made.
I don't have to consult you
about Stormfront
or anything else.
Now...
I believe you have a premiere of
Tek-Knight Lives to go to?
What are you doing here?
Well, I've come to see my son.
Fuck, Hughie.
So glad you...
got us into this shit.
She had a husband.
Right?
A kid?
Two... kids.
And I got her killed.
You didn't get her killed.
That wasn't meant for us.
How do you know?
Because our brains aren't
all over the dash, that's how.
Someone was watching her.
And the minute
she said something
she wasn't supposed to?
Somebody from Vought?
So, we're saying that
Vought may have just
assassinated
the deputy director of the CIA.
And now we're
in the middle of that, too.
Happy now, motherfucker?
Hello?
It's me.
Jesus, you shouldn't be calling.
I'm on a burner phone,
it's fine.
Yeah, but somebody
could be listening.
Hughie, we did it.
He's getting me the Compound V
in, like, a day or two.
What do you think? Um...
New York Times?
I mean, I was thinking
CNN or MSNBC, but...
Okay, wait, wait,
just-just-just hold on a second.
Come on, this is
what we've been waiting for.
Let's burn those fuckers down.
Just take a beat,
let's figure out
- the best way to do this.
- Why?
- What happened?
- Nothing.
Vought's just dangerous,
that's all.
I mean, you got to be careful.
I don't want you getting hurt.
I'm not gonna get...
If something happened,
you know you can trust me.
We're in this together.
No, I do trust you. It's just...
I just want to take our time.
You know, do this right.
That's all.
I know when you're not
telling me the truth, Hughie.
I kind of lived with it
every single day.
Don't lie to me.
Not again.
I'm not.
Swear to God.
Whatever. I, um...
I got to go.
All right, easy does it, lads.
Easy does it.
Like I tried to tell
this cunt...
I'm with that lot.
Yeah.
What the fuck are you wearing?
That is a good question.
You called him?
I'm sorry, Petit Hughie.
It's not a game now.
We need a real captain.
Frenchie's right.
This is a fucking mess, son.
We got a Supe Terrorist,
Rayner's blown her canister,
and we're the most wanted cunts
in the country.
But don't you worry.
Daddy's home.