Previously on "The Flash"...
We have a kid who defied
the laws of physics
to hang out with her parents.
- Melt.
- Killer Frost...
Is gone.
The only time you need your mother
is when you're in trouble.
My father's death certificate.
The M.E. who signed off on it,
he doesn't exist.
Now I know why she never wants to leave
her dad's side and never
wants to be by mine.
I just lost my speed.
Sounds like an insect.
Like a cicada.
Who's Cicada?
As a kid
there was a part of the Flash Museum
that always scared me.
I guess it's normal for children
to be afraid of monsters.
But this monster was different.
No one knows where he came from,
how he got his powers,
who he is.
All that's known is his alias,
and the last sound his victim's hear.
But that's not what makes him scary.
What makes him scary is...
you never catch him.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
We never catch him?
Supergirl, The Legends,
even The League tried,
but no one was successful.
Probably 'cause he can
dampen everybody's powers
with that magic friggin' dagger.
Not all superpowers
are meta-humans though.
- What about...
- Green Arrow?
Yeah, he tried too once, but...
So we're dealing with a
meta-human Jack the Ripper.
Amazing.
What else do you know about him?
Just that he...
he's early.
What do you mean he's early?
In my history, Cicada's first victim
was a meta-human named Floyd Belkin.
And he never killed Gridlock or Block.
They're completely different victims.
Because the timeline changed.
Yeah, and now they're both dead...
because of me.
Okay, there's no telling
the ripple effect of this change
or what kind of future
Nora's gonna return to.
We gotta catch this guy fast.
You mean catch the guy
that future us can't catch?
Right, I thought beating
The Thinker was hard.
Guys, it's Joe. CCPD
needs help downtown.
- Okay, I got it.
- No, I'll... I'll do it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I got it.
You guys stay here and deal with
the meta serial killer.
Okay, guys, look, we got this.
Let's just canvass some crime scenes,
interview some witnesses,
and see if there's any
common acquaintances
between Gridlock and Block.
I have a plan.
You... you've got a plan already?
I know how to fix this.
Now nobody try nothing funny.
This baby is solar with
a zero carbon footprint.
I spent a week in the sun charging
with U, V, A, B, and C!
So y'all stay put.
Hey. Hey!
I told you, I brought my own bags.
- Sorry.
- Apology accepted.
Don't forget the other kind of greens.
What the hell?
Fear not, good citizens.
Elongated man is here.
Why do I feel like you're focusing
on the wrong thing?
I just saved you...
Okay, if you're gonna...
Just don't post... don't post...
I saw you post it.
So your plan is to contact Herr Wells?
Yes, that's my plan.
I know in the future you
guys never bring in a Wells
to help you catch Cicada.
So if you want a different
result this time...
I try something new.
It's a great idea.
- 'Cept it's not.
- What?
It's a terrible idea. If you're looking
for cooperation, trust
me, this is not your guy.
He is just an asshat.
That's way harsh, Cisco.
- I'm sorry, I'm being harsh?
- Yes.
Go ahead, call him.
See if you don't get a
steaming pile of side-eye.
Okay.
Yah?
The Flash.
Wait for it.
- I love The Flash.
- What?
Oh, you Barry Allen,
yah? With the zoom, zoom,
and the defy the
physics laws and gravity.
Always with some style and grace, yah.
Thanks, man.
Das Kinder Flash. Child of the Flash.
Obviously, you have your
father's moral fiber, yah.
And your mother's smarts,
and classic beauty.
- Oh, my God. Stop.
- Thank you, Herr Wells.
No, don't thank him.
Don't fall for this ruse.
Clearly this guy is putting on an act.
He's a charlatan.
But you hurt me, stab me in the back,
this guy who must be Cisco.
- You know who I am.
- Hey, don't be rude.
All right, look. Hey, I'm sorry.
We need your help catching
a meta-human serial killer.
Yeah, I have heard of this Cicada.
Of course, the message
already from Kinder Flash.
Unfortunately, I'm otherwise occupied,
unable to assist you at this time.
- You can't?
- Nein.
But, I have done one better
and called someone who can.
This man is a legend, this man is
the greatest detective
in all the Multiverse.
So I've attached his coordinates
- if you want to look at them.
- Okay.
- Yah, do you see it?
- Got 'em.
- Good.
- Cisco.
Cisco what? You want
me to breach him here?
- Yeah.
- Hello? I just got Benihana'd.
- Hurts a little bit.
- Sorry.
Why don't we just breach him
here the old fashioned way?
Hey, man, thank you
for this. This is great.
Privilege and an honor
to help The Flash, yah,
and Kinder Flash, and Iris Flash, yah.
Bye, Kinder Flash.
Bye, Herr Wells.
Nice guy.
What are you talking about, man?
- He's awesome.
- He's not...
You know what?
Let's just turn on the extrapolator
and get this master detective out here.
Well...
I imagine your Earth would be colder.
Harrison Sherloque Wells
at your service.
I'm here to catch your killer.
Barry, what is he doing?
I don't know. Maybe it's some kind
- of CSI kit?
- Voila.
Shh. Just let him...
Mmm. That's the stuff.
And now we can begin.
- Tea?
- That's right.
We've been watching you for 20 minutes.
You're welcome.
- Cannot rush excellence.
- This is a waste of time.
Thank you very much
for coming, Cumberbatch.
I'm sure you would like it
if I took my leave, right?
Could have more time to recover
from your recent heartbreak.
What are you talking about?
Subcutaneous under-eye bruising,
which indicates you've been crying.
Flaky skin, which indicates dehydration,
probably from alcohol consumption.
Alcohol plus crying
can only mean one thing.
You have been dumped.
Wrong, detective.
- I have not been dumped.
- Oh, no?
It was a mutual decision, okay?
Cynthia and I, we reached a
decision together as a team.
Sure. Of course.
Okay, and I haven't been sobbing.
In fact, I can't remember the
last time I cried about it.
Excuse me.
You are the resident
speedster, I presume?
- How did you...
- Who favors stopping
on his right heel?
Can tell from the wear
and tear on your footwear.
It's uneven. A trait
that you have inherited
from your father. Although you do share
a little bit more body
language with your mother,
who's been touching her left shoulder
since I came around here.
What are you hiding from me?
Excuse me?
I am not hiding anything.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, you are, but what?
You have touched it, like...
it's something there, then gone again,
something removed. A tattoo, right?
Yes, perhaps from a former lover?
Okay! You know what?
I think that this
Sherloque has proven himself
and that we should start finding Cicada.
Excellent. Let's find Cicada.
But first, the question of my fee.
You're charging us?
This service is not free, right?
I don't work for charity.
Can already tell the young doctor here
is expecting to hire
me for another case.
I saw you glance at your purse,
and I'm happy to assist
you in that mystery.
But first, I think we can all agree
that a villain of Cicada's caliber...
will require a substantial fee.
Yeah.
Shrap, that's a lot of
money even from when I from.
I'm very expensive, but very worth it.
What do you think?
I mean, we could sell off
some of Star Labs stock.
- Yes! We have an agreement.
- Yeah.
Do you hear that?
Sounds of these frantic
steps, we're being approached
either by a tall, sensitive man, or...
a frightened, baby giraffe.
I got... I got a problem
here, guys, and I...
- Hey.
- Hello, baby giraffe.
Harry, how are you?
This is Sherloque Wells.
Loque. Sherloque. "L-O-Q-U-E."
Sherloque. I'm French.
- "Sher-lowk" here is...
- Loque.
...is gonna help us find Cicada.
Oh, cool, so you're like a detective.
Oh, detective, the fans.
Who should I make the autograph out to?
Little baby giraffe.
Uh, no, no, no. I'm... I'm... listen.
I'm a detective as well.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah, well...
That's right, well, you're a detective.
What... what have you solved recently?
Most recently? I uncovered the case
of the stolen Chevy.
Of Impala.
- Funny.
- Hmm.
Very funny from the looks of things.
Well, okay, so I saved
all these hostages
and... and all anybody can
talk about is this picture,
and turned into a meme.
And... and... it's...
This is... I just... I don't
think anybody in this city
takes me seriously.
Oh, there's 14 million
people in this city.
Only 500,000 have reposted this.
Yeah.
So, uh... Cicada?
Cicada, yes.
I've reviewed your evidence
and I know where to find your killer.
So, shall we, let's get this
done before dinner, right?
All right, allons-y.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not so fast, baby giraffe.
Two detectives only complicates matters.
Especially when only one is a master.
So why don't you stay put?
You can, bite the leaves.
Everyone else, come with em.
- You okay?
- Hmm?
Oh, yeah. I'm...
Yeah, I'm... I'm great.
I just got shut down
by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
You know Cicada's not the only mystery
around here that needs solving.
Yeah.
Mom, I know it sounds crazy,
but we think someone forged
Dad's death certificate.
Have you any proof?
No, well, yes, sort of.
It's complicated, but
I just thought you should know.
- Unless I already knew.
- I didn't say that.
It's why you're here, isn't it?
If this is some elaborate,
possibly nefarious cover-up,
it must be mom's doing.
It's not like she's ever
had your best interests at heart.
You always do this.
I just want to know the truth.
I think I deserve to know that.
Is...
my dad even really...
Caitlin, your father is dead.
And if you care about
my feelings at all,
you'll just let this be.
Thanks, mom. Pleasure as always.
Don't become obsessed with the past.
Your father had that flaw.
It nearly led to his ruin
even before his death.
I trust you know the way out.
I'm sorry we came
all this way for no reason.
No, I'm impressed. Your
mom is a really good liar.
Yeah, I know she forged
this death certificate.
I just... She's never gonna tell us why.
We've hit a brick wall.
Ah, but where you see a wall
this detective sees a
brick door with no handle.
What I mean is I know exactly
how to get what we came for.
- You sure he's in there?
- I'm certain.
Now, your evidence, while slight,
was enough to build
a psychologic profile.
This is a man hiding in the shadows.
This is someone who's been pushed
to the peripheries of society,
and then now he sits alone
waiting for the moment to strike.
All this, plus the census data
cross-referenced with the
location of his attacks,
and the profile narrows to one name...
David Hersch.
Nora's plan might actually work.
Well, it will work.
Once inside, you should
find a small booby trap.
I found it.
I'm on it.
Here is the critical part.
It's a decoy.
Sorry. I got caught off-guard.
Not so tough without your dagger, huh?
We got him.
That's ridiculous!
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't got anything on me!
- Well, he sounds angry.
- Yeah.
Forensics examined Hersch's hideout
and they found evidence linking him
to several anti-government bombings.
He's been doing it for a while.
- So we got him.
- I don't know.
They didn't find any sign of his dagger
or his mask.
Dad, one CSI to another
look at the facts, okay?
Sherloque is the best
detective in the Multiverse.
His profile led us to David Hersch,
and we found evidence that David Hersch
is a mass murderer.
What are the chances
that this isn't our guy?
- I mean, maybe.
- Come on, we should celebrate.
Okay, I'm gonna gather everyone up,
make some drinks,
and we can have our first party
- in the new lounge.
- I don't know, Nora.
I...
Detective Joseph West.
What do you want?
To finish what I started.
The meta-human called Vibe.
Call him here now.
I can't. I don't even know him.
You were saying?
Yes, I mean, he helps CCPD,
but it's not like I have a Vibe phone
so I can just call him up.
He's just a masked do-gooder
that shows up at crime scenes.
This could be a crime scene.
When you said you had a plan, Ralph,
I didn't mean you meant
breaking and entering
into my mother's company's files.
Reinforced steel.
It's times like this I
really miss Killer Frost.
Oh, don't you worry.
Ralphie's got it.
Okay.
Yep. Almost there.
Hang on. Yeah, almost got it.
Oh, my God.
- What is it?
- Lasers.
Rooms filled with lasers!
Holy snakies. Oh, my God.
It's like a Rubik's Cube of pain.
I don't know the code.
Try something
that your mother would...
Caitlin! There's gotta be something.
Got it.
You okay?
Nothing a gallon of Aloe won't fix.
Ooh.
Look for the name Thomas Snow.
Jackpot.
What is that?
It's a game my dad and I used to play.
He would teach me the
periodic table, but...
he would let me make up
my own fictional compounds and elements.
Nerd-onium?
He used to say it's
what made us so smart.
We used to have so much fun together.
Catching bugs in the backyard,
looking at constellations
through a telescope we built.
He taught me so much
about science and life.
Maybe he still has
something left to teach you.
What is it? It's a letter from my dad.
Saying...
goodbye.
It's a suicide note.
Alcohol, thank you, very much. Merci.
- There he is.
- Hey.
Dad, we're all set to celebrate...
No, hey, um.
Actually, Hersch isn't Cicada.
What?
He has to be.
No, I checked Cicada's boot print from
both the Block and Gridlock crime scenes
and it's three sizes
larger than Hersch's.
It's not him.
Well, of course it's him.
It's always Hersch.
Every time I capture Cicada
it's always the same man.
Wait a minute, you've
caught this guy before?
37 times. I've captured 37 Cicadas,
37 different Earths,
and every time I try to capture him
trail always leads back to
that Earth's David Hersch.
So this psychological
profile that you created,
you just made it up?
Not, the first time.
Now the next 36, then I
just trot it out there.
You know, to impress the client,
and then... skip to the end.
And here I thought you
just a bad detective,
but you're not a bad detective.
You're just a lazy one.
I'm not lazy.
I'm efficient, right?
- Anyway, that's not the point!
- Ow!
The point's simply
that there's no reason
for the Cicada of this
Earth to be anyone other
than David Hersch.
Well, there may be one reason.
What's that?
The timeline.
Yes, since Nora got here
things have changed a bit.
Yeah.
Oh, mais no, you must...
How can you not tell me this?
How am I expected to operate
when you don't give
me all the variables?
I don't know, but what we can expect
is a refund, so...
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no. That money is long gone.
What do you mean "it's gone"?
You spent all that money in one day?
- Right.
- On what.
My ex-wife-ves..
Ex-wives. Seven marriages.
Five wives. Lots of alimony.
That's not the point!
The point is simply
this is not my fault.
It's your fault. She is to blame.
Timeline variance.
Dad.
You're not gonna let Hersch off the hook
because of a boot print.
He's a meta.
How do we know what this guy can do?
That's the other thing.
Hersch has no dark matter readings.
He's not a meta.
All right, remember.
From one CSI to another,
we have to look at the facts, right?
We got the wrong guy.
No, not this time. You
know what we should do?
We should throw him in the
pipeline for safe keeping
until he talks. I'm gonna go get him.
Hey, what are you... No, you're not.
We're not gonna kidnap a
suspect in police custody.
If you don't see what's wrong with that,
you can sit this one out.
Well, guess we're back to square one
with Cicada.
Yeah.
Let's hope it's not too
late to save his next victim.
You have a lovely
family, Detective West.
By not giving me what I want,
by putting your life in danger,
you're gambling their future with you.
If you knew what I know,
you'd cherish them more.
I'm not luring Vibe into a death trap.
You can threaten me all you want.
I'm not afraid.
I believe you.
But you should be.
Still swirling around up there?
I just don't get Nora.
I mean, I thought our
training was sinking in.
She defeated Block. She
was really making process.
And next thing I know, she
wants to break into CCPD
and kidnap a suspect in police custody.
I mean, it's like she wants to
make Hersch Cicada.
Barry, you really don't
get why she's obsessed?
- Wait. Should I?
- Think about it.
She's been hearing
about the ripple effects
on the timeline since she got here
and at first they were relatively small,
but now...
- Cicada and...
- It's not so small.
He's one of the worst
serial killers in history,
and now because of Nora...
he's here early.
And an entirely different person.
With an entirely
different set of victims.
That is a huge weight
to bear for someone
who just wanted to spend time
with a dad she never knew.
She feels really guilty, Barry.
She wants to try to fix her mistakes
whatever that takes.
Sounds like another
speedster I know actually.
Nora says there's an emergency
in the pipeline intake.
Are you sure that...
Sherloque.
- Yeah.
- What happened?
As far as I can tell it looks like
he was in the wrong place
when this fusion cell went critical.
I think it wasn't placed
in its cradle properly.
- Vaporized into ash.
- What a way to go.
- Shenanigans.
- Good grife!
I call shenanigans.
You see, these cells right here,
they run in a redundant cascade circuit.
That's how they power the pipeline,
in the first place,
so if one of them blew
they all would have blown.
Yeah, the whole pipeline
would have exploded.
Exactly right.
- Ugh.
- Mm.
Darjeeling, oolong.
Tea leaves.
Barry, be a dear and check the building
for a weasel in a pork pie hat,
about yay tall, smells
vaguely of poutine.
Whoa. Tell me...
who died?
Found him with this.
Of course, you did.
So you thought you could just leave
to another Earth without paying us back?
Worked on my fourth wife...
and my sixth.
- Same woman.
- Oh.
Okay, Cisco,
maybe it's time to have a talk
about a little place
called debtor's prison.
Come with me.
- All right.
- You make me miss Herr Wells.
Come with me.
I'm... I'm taking you!
You okay?
Yeah, yeah. It's just...
for second I thought me
inviting Sherloque here
got him killed, and I just, um...
least that's one thing
that's not my fault.
Hey, I wanted to talk to you actually.
I think I understand how you're feeling.
Sometimes our powers
are so extraordinary
it makes our mistakes feel amplified,
especially guilt.
Yeah, but I should feel guilty.
I've never messed up this badly before,
and I can't stop thinking about it.
That's just cause you care.
It's okay. It's a good thing.
But...
Nora, if every time you make a mistake
you just rush in to fix it
you're only gonna make things worse.
Trust me, I know that
better than anyone.
You just gotta have a
little more patience.
Take a moment.
Think before you act.
Fix the problem the
right way, all right?
Okay.
Listen, Caitlin, I'm sorry.
For what?
For all of this.
Just I-I felt like a complete joke
after that hostage thing,
and then... Sherloque shows up
and everybody swoons
over his so-called
"Master Detective-ness."
You were nice enough to invite me along,
and I pushed you...
into that, and...
I'm really sorry.
Ralph, this thing you pushed me into
gave me something I've never had before.
Your first felony?
No. Closure.
It may not be pretty, but
I finally know the truth.
And that means everything.
So, for my book,
you're the best detective
a girl could ask for.
Hey, you never told me what the code was
on your mom's Resident
Evil laser grid of death.
It was my birthday.
All this and not even a scream.
You've experienced pain before,
but not more than me.
No, Cecile don't.
No. That's what he wants.
I didn't want to do this.
Not to a family man.
But I will.
Time to make a decision, Detective West.
While there's still some of you left.
No, no, no! Leave her out of it!
What's wrong?
He took Cisco!
- Cicada took Cisco.
- What do you mean took him?
- Took him where?
- I don't know.
They jumped into a breach
right when I got here.
But a breach could take them anywhere.
Cisco, can you hear me?
Guys, can you hear me?
Cisco, where are you?
I don't know. My breach fritzed out
and spat us out in a forest somewhere.
Can you breach out?
It's not working.
Cicada's dampening his powers.
Without a satellite I can't
pin point his location.
I mean, in this state alone
there's over 14 million acres of forest.
All right, Black Forest
and Roanoke are closest.
I'll start there.
We're not gonna find
him in time, are we?
Well, before you give up,
- what kind of trees?
- What?
In the forest, what
kind of trees, ask him.
Cisco, what kind of trees are they?
I don't know! I'm in a forest!
What kind of trees, little one?
- Pine trees, I think.
- Good.
Some of them have pointy leaves.
Ah, pointy....
ash trees, of course.
All right, now I need
you to hold your breath.
What? Why?
Because I need to hear the forest,
So, shh.
Crickets.
You hear this? Assuming
that's field crickets.
They live in the soil.
Anyway, cross-reference
field crickets with a high concentration
of pine trees, ash trees,
in an open field, and you have...
- Kolins Woods.
- On my way!
Barry, you got to get out of there!
We have to help him.
Barry?
It takes time to hone your skills, Nora.
You can't just skip rungs on the ladder
or jump right to the big stuff,
that's not how it works.
Take a moment. Think before you act.
Fix the problem the right way.
I got it.
I can fix this.
I've thought this through.
I won't mess it up this time.
I promise.
I trust you.
Go.
All these years in Central City
spent defending metas
instead of ending them.
Those days end now.
Starting with you.
Use this!
Hey, Michael Myers,
dampen this.
No. No. No. No.
Cisco's gone.
Oh, my God...
Cisco?
He's alive.
Hey. Hey.
Sorry. Sorry.
Your daughter.
She remembered there's
more than one way to
open a breach.
Figured Cicada wouldn't give up
until Vibe was dead,
so we gave him what he wanted.
Thanks, fangirl.
You saved my life.
I did good?
You did great.
It's almost like you're really dead.
Yeah.
I almost really was.
How the hell are we
gonna catch this guy?
Not with our powers.
We know that at least.
We don't know much else either.
Variations in the timeline, they've...
shifted the elements,
complicated the equation.
- Now...
- Not all those elements
are bad though.
You could be the new
element that saves us.
You could be the reason we catch Cicada.
I must admit, Miss Nora here pulled
the rug right under from Cicada.
Woof, alley-oop, huh?
- Very impressive.
- Yeah, that's the only
fake death we're gonna see around here
'cause you're sticking around
until you pay us back every cent.
Well, I have to say, prospect
of another mystery with Cicada
puts a little pep in my step.
Also, that breach device you used to get
in and out of places, I suppose
that's under lock and key right now?
That's at the bottom of the ocean
as far as you're concerned.
Well, then I'm staying!
- Great!
- Course you are.
I'm watching you, Holmes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Well, you'll learn a lot.
- Good for you.
- Ow.
All right, shall we, sidekick.
I'll sidekick your face.
Something tells me
those two are gonna be
just great friends.
So...
You guys up for a family dinner night?
Sure.
Yeah. And then maybe after
we could help you move into the loft.
I know you've been
kind of cooped up here,
and now that Sherloque is
gonna need a place to stay
I thought you could...
crash with us.
I think it's a great idea, Nora.
Okay, thanks, yeah. Thanks.
Let me get my purse.
- Okay.
- This will be good.
I think it could be just the thing
to bring you two closer together.
I really hope so.
Hey.
Taking Cisco out for some drinks
in memoriam of Vibe.
- You wanna come?
- I'm okay, but thank you.
Anything you want to talk about?
My dad wasn't really
the letter writing type.
I feel like he would have
found some other way to tell me.
No luck with his work notes?
No, I mean, these molecular models
are gibberish. There's gaps everywhere
and some of these
compounds don't even exist.
It's like his mind was the first to go.
But, maybe I should
just listen to my mom
and forget about the past.
Well...
You left this behind.
Sometimes the past is worth remembering.
Thank you.
They don't exist
because they're not supposed to.
_
So this is all I could remember
about Cicada. It's not much, but...
No. No. No, this is... This is great.
I mean, every little bit we get
helps build a profile on him.
I will comb over this in the morning.
You should go be with Cecile right now.
Feel better.
Wait. There's... There's one more thing.
He made these comments
about family
and cherishing them.
And then the way he
picked up Jenna's blanket,
and I got this feeling
when I looked in his eyes.
What... what kind of feeling?
I think Cicada's a father.
Hello, Orlin.
Any progress?
She's not coming out of it.
Let me see it.
It's not healing.
Doesn't matter.
You can't keep doing this.
You have to stop.
Not until I'm finished.
Oh, hi.
I'm just looking for my purse.
I'm about to have
dinner with my parents.
It's on the chair.
In the Cortex.
By the mannequin.
Right. Thanks.
Well, enjoy the couch.
Nora.
Can you help me with something?
I've been wondering...
You. You've traveled back into all these
great moments of your
parent's lives, right?
Some wonderful, some dangerous.
Most not as dangerous as...
punching a falling satellite, right?
And yet...
that is the moment when you made
the decision to act,
altering the course of history forever.
That decision...
Did you come to it on your own?
Of course you did!
Right? No, of course you did.
You're Excess!
The temptation...
was too much, I'm sure.
It was.
Well, please,
forgive me. You have a dinner to go to.
Good night.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --