- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Photography
was always my passion.
I figured,
why not make it my job?
- These are great.
- Frost, you have always
been there for me.
It never occurred to me
that you might want
to live a life.
- Nice doing business with you.
- This is a potential cure.
What's the bonding agent?
- Dark matter.
S.T.A.R. Labs
has the dark matter
I need to take the next step.
My cure will work.
- Or turn them
into meta-humans
against their will.
- [screams]
- You cannot avoid
the coming crisis.
- Just tell me what I can do.
- The Flash must die.
[dramatic music]
- I stared at that newspaper
for so many years.
- "Flash Missing,
Vanishes in Crisis."
- First it felt like a guide.
You know, like proof
that things were
headed in the right direction.
Then it became a sword
hanging over my head.
A part of me
always felt like...
if I vanish
in whatever crisis
is coming...
Maybe I was still
out there somewhere,
looking for a way
to come back to you.
According to The Monitor,
that doesn't happen.
- "To save the lives
of billions,
the Flash must die."
What kind crap is that?
- [chuckles]
- No, I'm serious.
I mean, The Monitor
shows up here out of nowhere
and says that you're supposed
to die on December 10th?
The last I remember,
that article said
that you were
in a fight with Thawne,
not some cosmic disaster.
- The article changed.
- If that article can change,
then that means that we can
still change the future.
So what do we do first?
- If a doctor told you
you were dying,
you'd get a second opinion.
So I'm gonna go see
this Crisis for myself.
♪ ♪
- You bring the cash?
- I thought Gat would be here.
- Gat's busy.
Change of plans.
It's $5,000 now.
- Gat said it was $500.
Okay, wait, please.
I will get you the rest.
It's a matter
of life and death.
[grunts]
Please, I will get
the rest of the money.
I promise.
- Too late.
- [yells]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
- T-minus 30 seconds, people.
- I knew this was a bad idea.
- This was your idea.
I'm just the guy
making dreams come true.
- 20 seconds, people.
- Okay, fine.
Just do it.
Did it work?
I sound like Caity.
- You sound like a non-meta,
thanks to Ray Palmer.
As long as this nanite
camouflage cocktail is active,
your voice and eyes
will allow you to blend in
with any group of regular Joes,
so you can, you know,
live your life
without scaring the ever-loving
crap out of people.
- And what about my hair?
- Trust me.
You'll fit right in.
[upbeat music]
Welcome.
Now, you two behave.
I'm gonna go find
our star curator.
- What am I looking at here?
- Your next lesson, Frosty.
Some of the very stuff
that makes life worth living:
art.
- Wowsers.
Is this photographer
extraordinaire Kamilla Wang?
- Hi.
- Thank you for coming.
- Mm.
Yeah, of course.
- Mm, very classy shirt,
by the way.
- Oh, a very cute photographer
got it for me.
She looks
a lot like you, actually.
- I hope she doesn't mind
that you already got
some schmutz on it.
- I did not get schmutz...oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, I definitely did.
You know, sometimes you just
want your girlfriend
to have a good turnout
for her show,
so you make everybody clean up,
and who ends up with
nanite juice on their shirt?
- Wait, who'd you bring?
- [chuckles]
You really do blend in here.
- Except this place
is so lame.
I mean, come on.
This isn't art.
It's garbage.
- Come on, Frost.
It's not all that bad.
- There are used tissues
on this.
Okay?
And this is just a plunger.
Oh, my God, look at
the brushstrokes on this one.
All right...
[scoffs]
Whatever guy made this
has some real issues.
- Right, but, Frost,
that's kind of the whole point.
Art reflects how we feel,
so connecting to art
can help us
plumb the depths
of our soul.
- [sighs]
Okay.
What I am connecting to
in these photos
is that the photographer is
afraid to get a shot in focus.
- Those are actually mine.
- They're not all winners.
- Look, I can take a note,
but if this is how Caitlin's
other half is gonna act,
maybe she should skip
my next show.
- Thank you for walking me
through this one, babe.
- No problem.
The suspect is Allegra Garcia.
She's 20 years old.
She runs a carjacking outfit
out of Keystone.
- Thanks to her meta-human
ability to control radio waves.
That's a new one.
How is that possible?
- Key fobs run
on radio transmissions.
Anyway, Garcia has been
in and out of Iron Heights
and juvie since she was 13.
Last week, she tried
to hijack a car
that belonged to some guy
named Salvador Traversoni.
He lost control of the car,
and, as you can see,
he died in the crash.
- It says here
an eyewitness puts Garcia
at the scene,
so open and shut.
- Should be
with you working on it.
- Mm!
- Mwah.
- High five.
Your Honor, due to a
preponderance of the evidence,
the State intends to seek
the maximum penalty
against the defendant,
Allegra Garcia.
- Which is why the defense
would like to plead out.
My client is aware that a jury
would put her away for life
and is willing to settle for,
say, 15 years?
- Is that true, Ms. Garcia?
- I suppose.
- All right, then.
I guess we can save
the taxpayers some time.
[mysterious humming]
Ms. Horton?
[dramatic music]
- What the hell
are you staring at?
- Nothing.
Just, um...
Your Honor, the prosecution
requests bail for Ms. Garcia.
- What?
- The defendant
is pleading guilty.
- I know, Your Honor,
that it's a bit unorthodox,
but...
we've discovered new evidence.
- My office doesn't have
the resources to find anything.
- We just need a little bit
of time to determine
if the State wants to pursue
a lighter sentence.
In the meantime,
we request
that meta-human dampeners
be placed on Ms. Garcia
while we continue discovery.
- Counselor Horton,
this court appreciates
your commitment
to fair jurisprudence,
but are you sure
you want to go down this road?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- [sighs]
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Where will you go?
- December 11, 2019.
It's the day after
I'm supposed to disappear.
- Maybe we should loop in
the rest of Team Flash.
- Not until we know the truth.
- I just...I don't feel great
about you going in there alone.
- I'm not gonna be alone.
I have this.
- Hello, Barry Allen.
Preparing for temporal
observational protocol.
- [sighs]
- Is that Gideon?
- It's a mobile
Gideon unit I built
from salvaged parts
of the plinth.
- You'll come right back
to this moment?
Right to this second?
- I promise.
♪ ♪
- Approaching Mach 1.
Mach 2.
Now approaching
November 30, 2019.
December 1, 2019.
Disruption barrier detected.
- What the hell?
[yells]
[groaning]
- Your wound is still
not healing.
- Mm-hmm.
- My readings indicate
you were exposed
to an extra-universal material
that destroys
positive matter on contact,
a substance
known as antimatter.
- Antimatter?
That's new.
- There's a wall of this stuff
clogging up the Speed Force.
Gideon, how do I get past it?
- Not without
additional assistance.
Fortunately, there is
an expert in the field,
Dr. Jay Garrick,
formerly known as
the Flash of Earth-3.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Good to see you again,
Barry.
- You too, Jay.
- You were right.
You were hit with a dose
of pure antimatter.
Lucky you have speed healing,
or that scratch could've
wiped you out of existence.
- So is there a way that I can
time travel past the barrier?
- You want to tell me
why the hell
you were time traveling
to begin with?
- I needed to see for myself
if The Monitor
was telling the truth
about what happened to me,
and I know what you're gonna
say about time traveling.
- Actually,
I was gonna tell you
you made the right call.
For the past year...
I've been detecting
antimatter signatures
across the Multiverse.
Now, we don't know
their origin,
but if my algorithm is correct,
all Earths could be in danger.
- Then we have to find a way
to break through that wall.
- Ah, your body never could.
But maybe your mind can.
I built this thing years ago,
the neural hyper-collider.
It harnesses neural electricity
and transfers it
across superluminal particles.
- Therefore projecting
human consciousness
across space-time.
You could send someone's mind
past the antimatter wall.
- Not just anyone.
It's gotta be a speedster...
in his prime.
You in?
- Yeah.
- Then let's hustle.
I've already had to postpone
my dinner plans.
- Not any further, I hope.
[whispers] Mom?
- Barry, I'd like you
to meet my wife,
Dr. Joan Williams.
- It is a pleasure to meet you,
Barry Allen.
I've heard quite a bit
about you.
- Allegra Garcia.
Juvie offender
from a criminal family,
in and out of the system
her entire life.
The night of the particle
accelerator explosion,
Allegra was caught up
in a fight.
- [screams]
- Next thing you know,
she's got the power
to control radio waves.
[radio squawking]
Then she gets transferred
to the meta-human unit
at Iron Heights.
- At 15?
- Mm.
Not exactly the justice
system's finest moment.
Now here we are.
Allegra gets arrested again,
but my powers are telling me
that this time,
she's innocent.
- But the victim was killed
by a radio wave attack,
which is Allegra's
meta-ability.
And an eyewitness
placed her at the scene.
Even recognized her tattoo.
- My powers have never
been wrong before,
and I do not want
this kid going down
for something she didn't do.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's not guilty.
- Dude, come on.
Those are mine.
- Sorry. My bad.
See these burn marks
on the vic?
They don't match
a typical car explosion at all.
It's like he was burnt and
toasty before the car crash.
We know that Allegra's
powers give her the ability
to control radio waves
and not heat waves, so...
- Allegra might not
have done this.
- And I told Judge Hankerson
there was new evidence
in Allegra's case.
- Okay, guys.
All we have to do is find it.
- CCPD already
interviewed this guy.
You really think the eyewitness
is gonna recant his story?
- Well, eyewitness testimony
isn't always perfect.
Plus, environmental
factors, stress,
even the order of lineup photos
can affect memory.
So jogging his memory
while he is at home, relaxed
might bring something up.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Unit 37.
Here it is.
Uh-oh.
♪ ♪
I always come prepared.
Oh, boy.
- Allegra?
- You're not going
anywhere, okay?
We just want to talk
for a second.
[screaming]
- Freeze! Freeze!
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Allegra Garcia?
You're under arrest
for parole violation.
- I wouldn't touch that.
- Sorry.
- Jay told me
he's a doppelganger
of your late father.
- Mm.
- Do I remind you of anyone
from your Earth?
- Yeah, you do.
- Hmm.
Who is she?
- Someone very special.
- Ain't she?
I never thought
I'd settle down.
But I needed a neurological
specialist to help
with my depleting speed,
and something just
felt right between us.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- All right. Come on.
- Let's do it.
[clears throat]
- Jay's helmet will help
channel the tachyons
into your frontal cortex
and ignite
your synaptic pathways.
- I won't lie to you, kid.
Beaming your mind past
an antimatter wall...is risky.
- I know.
But right now, it's a matter
of life and death.
Let's do it.
- All right.
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
- His biometrics are crashing.
- I'm also picking up
temporal energy readings.
- [yelling]
- His mind has broken past
the barrier.
It's not just a new timeline
he's found.
It's billions of them.
And Barry's mind
is experiencing them all.
♪ ♪
- The Monitor:In order for
billions  to survive this coming
crisis,
the Flash must die.
- [yelling]
- You have to get him
out of there.
- [screaming and grunting]
- "Oh, why should
the spirit of mortal be proud?
"Like a fast-flittering meteor,
"a fast-flying cloud...
"a flash of the lightning...
"a break of the wave...
he passes from life
to his rest in the grave."
- [exhales heavily]
- Barry.
You're with us.
William Knox.
I've discovered that poetry
can stimulate
collapsed neural pathways.
- Lady Gaga
usually works for me.
[groaning]
What's wrong with me?
- The device overloaded
your neural synapses,
creating a near shutdown.
What you're experiencing now
is called neural entropy.
- It feels like
my nerves are on fire.
- They are.
Because you're a speedster,
your synapses fire ten times
the normal rate,
so you're feeling ten times
the amount of pain
a non-speedster would.
You'll feel better
in a day or two.
- Okay, okay.
- What'd you see in there, kid?
- I saw...
Billions of possible futures.
Billions of deaths.
All their pain,
their suffering.
And then they were gone.
I felt all of it.
Now I know
The Monitor was right.
I have to die.
I need to go home.
- Barry, Barry,
you can't be moving.
- Please, I have to see Iris.
- Ow, ow, ow.
It's not getting any less ow.
- I don't understand.
I thought Allegra
controlled radio waves.
- So did we,
but she fired a heat blast
right at Ralph.
- It wasn't just heat.
It was ultraviolet radiation.
- He got a sunburn.
- Yeah. From hell.
- Look at his face.
Most UV light gets absorbed
by the ozone layer.
This was entirely undiluted.
If it wasn't for his powers,
that "sunburn"
would've killed him.
- So put some aloe on it.
- Okay.
- Can I just talk to Caitlin
for a minute, please?
- No.
I've got things to do.
- What are we gonna do
about this?
- Don't even get me started.
Listen, even though UV rays
have shorter wavelengths
than radio waves,
they're all part of the same
electromagnetic spectrum.
- So Allegra must be able
to control
all the different
types of wavelengths,
which means she could have
killed Salvador
and our eyewitness.
- And I set her free.
- [sighs]
Okay, help me understand
why you pleaded guilty
this morning
and now
you're suddenly innocent.
- A girl can change her mind.
- What were you doing
at the witness' apartment?
- Just needed
to hash it out with him,
prove it was wasn't me he saw.
- That's something
a detective would do.
- I'm trying
to be a reporter, okay?
Figured this was as good a time
as any to get some experience.
Get a story
and my freedom.
But what's the use?
You'll always see me
as a criminal anyway.
- You know what I see?
I see that scared little kid
that I used to pick up
for robbing liquor stores
when she was 13.
That same girl that I would
check on in juvie
who would always
tell me to leave.
This morning, I get a ping
that you'd escaped
from your meta-cuffs,
and we find you in the location
of the dead State's witness.
If you're a reporter,
how does this story play out?
- I didn't kill him
or the driver.
I was trying
to find out who did it.
I swear.
[door clicks open]
- DA Horton.
- I took a chance on you,
Allegra.
So you tell me right now.
Who really did it?
Tell me who killed
those people.
- You wouldn't
believe me either.
I want my lawyer.
- This is insane.
This is insane.
All of the evidence
says that she's guilty,
but...
my powers are telling me
that she's not just innocent.
She knows
who the real killer is.
I just need her to trust me.
- All you need to do right now
is slow down.
- No, what I need to do
is find evidence
to exonerate her
before the trial,
and I am running out of time.
- Well, that's because
you're trying to do
the public defender's work
and not your own.
You do realize how much trouble
you can get in, right?
You let Allegra out of jail
for an inexplicable reason,
and now there's another murder.
- But my powers
are telling me...
- Two people are dead, Cecile.
- You know this kid.
You know her rap sheet.
It's petty crimes, robberies.
It's not double homicide.
That doesn't even add up.
- I haven't known this woman
in a long time,
and the evidence adds up.
We need to recognize
that unlike facts,
feelings can be fallible.
- Except when it's your gut.
- I've never said that.
- You didn't have to.
That is a scared kid
with no one
to stand up for her.
The Public Defender's Office
is overworked and underpaid.
Joe...
I'm the only one
who can prove her innocence.
- Your job is to prosecute
the cases that we bring to you
using the evidence.
I mean, it's like you...
it's like you don't even
want to be the DA.
- Are you telling me
I have to choose
between using my powers
and doing my job?
- That is not what I just said.
- No.
It's what you're feeling.
- It was risky
to move him here,
but he needed to see you...
which we understand.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Your husband stared at me
that same way
when we first met.
- I'm sorry.
You look just like
Barry's mother.
- Oh.
- What?
Well, Barry's physical pain
will go away,
but the mental aspect...
some of that won't,
not for a while.
But I know you'll keep
an eye on him.
- Thank you.
So they are going to scan
our Earth
for any other signs
of antimatter
and figure out a way to prevent
whatever Crisis is coming.
- It's not that simple.
- Well, you said you saw
a wave of antimatter
destroy Earth.
All we have to do
is come up
with a plan to stop it.
- We can't stop what's coming.
The Monitor
was telling the truth.
- We get Kara and Oliver
and everybody.
We create
an antimatter dampener.
I don't care.
We just find a way.
- I saw you and...
Caitlin.
I saw everyone die.
The only timeline where
you all survived was if I died.
- No, no,
that's not the future.
- I saw a billion futures,
Iris.
- Okay, well, what about
the billion and first
or billion and second?
We control our destiny.
We...
can change the timeline
for the better.
- Maybe this is the reason
I was given powers.
To save everyone.
- You said this morning
that you weren't giving up yet.
- I have to accept this.
We both do.
- And do nothing while you
sit here and wait to die?
This isn't you.
The Barry I know
would never stop running.
He would find
another way to fight.
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
- [groans]
It's open.
Hey.
- Hey.
Iris wasn't answering
her phone.
Is she here?
- No, no, she's at work.
She's working.
- What are you doing home?
You okay?
- I got hurt running
a Speed Force experiment,
but I'll be fine.
- Okay.
- If you needed help
with something from Iris,
maybe I could help you out.
- It's this case.
Allegra Garcia.
Cecile has some very strong
feelings about it.
- You want me to take a look?
- Hmm.
- [groans]
- How did you get hurt, Barr?
- [sighs]
- All right, look...
you don't have to share
right now if you don't want to.
Just know that I'm here.
Always.
- Something's coming, Joe.
I have to make a sacrifice.
But at the same time,
I can't help but feeling
like it means I'm giving up.
- Giving up?
- Yeah.
- When I was a beat cop,
you know, I walked
the same patrol every day.
One morning, I'm responding
to a noise complaint.
Out of nowhere, pop.
Bullet flies by my head.
I got pinned down.
I called for backup, but...
everything was telling me...
that's it.
Next morning...
Barr, I can't even
tell you how...
scared I was...
to go back out
in them streets.
- But you did.
- Yeah.
'Cause of this.
Our badges,
your emblem,
they're symbols of the strength
that we're charged with
to get back out there.
And we don't
make the choice to die.
We would never
choose to do that.
But when we hear
the call of duty...
We're willing to make
that sacrifice.
And that's not giving up, Barr.
That's what you call
resilience.
And I know you to have
plenty of that.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Frosty.
Earth to Frosty!
[clapping]
- ♪ What mainstream MC
can take ♪
♪ Raw beats and bless them ♪
- Calling all White Walkers!
You know what?
Frak it.
- Hey!
I was listening to that.
- Maybe you should be
listening to Chester's
molecular monitoring system
so he doesn't, you know,
turn back into a black hole!
- Relax, okay?
I put the freaking alerts
on my phone.
- Oh, you mean
these freaking alerts?
Yeah, see,
I handled the situation
and prevented us from
being sucked out of existence
by a giant death vacuum.
What did you do
with your Tuesday?
- Nothing.
- Is that...
- Nope, nope.
No, no, no, no, no,
stop it, stop it.
No, no, no.
- Were you drawing?
- No.
- You were drawing.
Because drawing
is for losers.
- Mm!
Looks like you were drawing.
- It's really hard, okay?
- This is giving me, like,
minimalist reductionism.
- I was trying to draw this.
I've been
working on it forever.
And it's not getting
any better.
All right, that's...
- Is this why you've been
all cranky pants
since Kamilla's show?
- [sighs]
- You've just been trying
to express yourself.
- I stink, okay?
I don't know why
I thought I could
plumb the depths of my soul.
- Hey.
You do not stink.
You want to go off
and be Vincent van Snow?
You want to show the world
what's inside of you
using art or paint or dance,
do it.
But you gotta
understand that...
other people
are trying to do it too.
- I feel like a Yakuza baddie
is stabbing me in the stomach.
Repeatedly.
Is this how I made everyone
feel at Kamilla's show?
- Yep.
That's a feeling
we like to call guilt.
It's a little stabby.
But...
it can also show us when we
need to make something right.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[door clicks open]
- I told you,
I want my lawyer.
- Steven's still on his way.
Look, I understand
what you're going through.
- Do you know what I see
when these cuffs are off?
I see radio waves
and microwaves
and gamma waves,
and I can't stop seeing them.
So how could you
possibly understand
what I'm going through?
- You have to let me help you.
- So you can put me away?
- No, that's not why I'm here.
- Then why are you?
- Because I...
Because I am a meta-human too.
I can sense
other people's feelings,
and, honey,
I can't turn it off either.
That's how I know
that you're innocent.
If there is anything
that can help me
convince everybody else...
please...
you gotta tell me.
- I told my arresting officer.
He said I was crazy.
I feel crazy.
- Try me.
- Back at juvie...
the night that
particle accelerator exploded,
I wasn't alone.
My cousin was there
at the same time.
Esperanza.
Talk about bad influences.
I wanted out of her gang,
so she jumped me.
- [screams]
- She died in the explosion.
Esperanza!
Or at least I thought she did.
- You think she's still alive?
- Esperanza made me get
the same tattoo as her.
- The witness ID'd you
off that tat.
- But Esperanza's dead.
There's no way it could be her.
I mean, it's impossible.
Right?
- Hey, did you get
those juvie records?
- Oh, yeah.
Took a bit of stretching,
but we got about five years'
worth here.
- Good. Is there a file on
a girl named Esperanza Garcia?
- Yeah, there is.
And I smell a mystery.
- "Inmate was discovered
in a vegetative state.
She has been taken
out of our custody."
- Out of custody into the hands
of a very redacted
organization.
- Esperanza's alive.
Cecile, did you hear that?
[signal breaking]
Cecile, you got...get...there.
- That's not me.
♪ ♪
- Bring me Allegra Garcia...
or burn.
[exciting rock music]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- We gotta get you
out of here.
Come on. Come on.
- [grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct whispering]
[gunshots]
- Get out of my precinct!
[gun clicks]
Damn it.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Hey, what's up?
- Barry, we were talking
to Cecile about her case.
- Turns out that Allegra
had a cousin named
Esperanza with the same
powers as her.
Everybody thought
that Esperanza was dead.
- Esperanza must've killed
the witness, not Allegra.
Now Esperanza can't let
anyone know she's alive.
- CCPD is in a total blackout.
- She's going after Allegra.
- I am going to send Ralph
there right now and...
- No, no, no, there's no time.
I'm going.
- Barry, no.
You're still recovering.
- I'll be fine, all right?
I'm going.
[both yelling and gasping]
- Esperanza.
[speaking Spanish]
- Hmm.
I'm only Ultraviolet now.
- No!
I won't let you do this.
- Then you'll die too.
- Keep them safe.
- [groans]
- Get up, hero.
I want you to die on your feet.
- How did that happen?
- Ultraviolet light travels
at 186,000 miles per second,
which is 80 times
your top speed.
I suggest a hasty retreat.
- Our badges,
your emblem...
when we hear
the call of duty...
we're willing to make
that sacrifice.
And that's not
giving up, Barry.
That's what we call
resilience.
And I know you to have
plenty of that.
- [groans]
- That's better.
- [breathes deeply]
[grunts]
[yells]
- Cecile, call the medic!
- You know what they say.
In a few days,
it'll be tan.
- Yeah, well, I'm just glad
to be alive.
- We were right.
Esperanza Garcia was hired
to kill Salvador Traversoni.
Then she offed the eyewitness.
She tried to kill Allegra
so nobody would know
she was still alive.
- And you skipped over the part
where this Ultraviolet person
might've been trained
in the art of assassination
by a secret organization.
- Yeah, that's on my
to-solve list.
- Yeah, well,
it's on ours now.
If there's a group out there
exploiting metas,
then they're gonna need
our protection.
Yo.
What'd you put
in these painkillers?
- Oh, you're not hallucinating.
That is art.
And some people
might think it's weird.
But I think it is
a beautiful expression
of the artist's inner life.
Even if it's
a weird inner life.
- But you bought
all this stuff?
I mean, how'd you pay for it?
- With Caity's credit cards.
All of them.
- [clears throat]
Maybe our next life lesson
will be in personal finance.
- Actually...
I've got one more piece
to add to the bunch.
From a very daring
young talent.
I think it ties the room
together quite nicely.
- [chuckles]
- Well, there's no accounting
for taste.
- You know,
my mom dated an artist once.
He was a trapeze artist,
though.
No-Net Nick, they called him.
[voice fades]
[somber music]
- Two books
and three bedtime songs...
but little Jenna
is finally asleep.
- She is persistent.
- She gets that
from her mother.
Look,
you stood up for Allegra...
when nobody else did,
including myself.
- Well, you are the badass
that charged
a light-wielding hit woman
in order to save
all of our butts.
- [laughs]
[sighs]
What's wrong?
- [sighs]
I just keep thinking.
I'm not doing everything I can
to help the city
as the district attorney.
The justice system doesn't
always work for metas...
which is why I want to become
a defense attorney
for meta-humans.
I know. I know.
You can tell me that I'm crazy,
and we were not on the same
page about Allegra today...
- No, no, no, that's not crazy.
That is incredible.
- Really?
- Babe, do you know
how many people
you could help
in this city?
- Yeah.
And I know right
where I want to start.
[knock at door]
- Um, hi.
I'm looking
for Iris West-Allen.
I'm here about the internship.
- Hi, yeah, Cecile Horton
told me to expect you.
Welcome to "The Citizen."
- Just don't touch
the vegan doughnuts.
- You can put your things
right over there.
- So what now?
- We'll keep scanning
the Multiverse
for antimatter
from my lab, okay?
But I think, for now,
we should get going.
- Yes, we should.
Ah, the intrepid reporter.
[chuckles]
I thought you had a story
to put out.
- Well, I couldn't let you
leave without saying good-bye.
And I know it hasn't been under
the best of circumstances,
but I hope we will
see you guys again.
- I hope so.
- Yeah.
- Till next time, Flash.
- It was a pleasure
to meet you, Barry Allen.
You keep being the hero
we know you are.
- I will.
- You ready?
- Yes.
- I know she's not
your mom, but...
- Still nice to have a little
hope on a not-so-great day.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry about earlier.
- Don't be.
You were in pain
and shock, and...
I was scared too.
But seeing you at CCPD,
fighting with your all,
it reminded me that...
no matter what
this Crisis brings...
no matter what you choose...
I know that you're never
gonna give up.
- I'm not choosing to die.
I could never make the choice
to leave you.
But...
if my death is...
the only way
to save the universe,
to save you...
I'm willing to do that.
- Then...
whatever we do next,
let's make it count.
- We can start by preparing
the team for this Crisis.
Maybe even a world
without the Flash.
- So what do we tell them?
- Beginning biopsy examination
on Patient 1-A,
Mitch Romero,
male, 40s.
It is my hope
that this procedure
will help to illuminate
the effects of my cure...
when exposed
to another subject.
The body presents no obvious
signs of hemorrhaging.
But it appears
the victim's blood...
Has coagulated
with an unidentifiable
biological substance.
Will run analysis
on substance.
Substance could
have been absorbed
into victim's veins
prior to death.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- [growls]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.