- Last season
on "The Flash"...
Iris isn't Iris...
the real Iris, my wife,
she is somewhere else,
probably in danger.
- Barry!
You targeted me
from the very beginning.
I saw everything.
- As for the other Wellses,
they're as much a part of you
as yourself.
- You mean I'm gonna
keep hearing them?
- Yeah.
- I did this.
I killed the Speed Force.
I need your help to build
an Artificial Speed Force.
I need my speed back
if I'm gonna save Iris.
- This whole time
when you looked at me,
you saw this other person.
- For six years, I've been
in my own personal hell.
You let me rot in here
while you took everything
I created.
- [grunts, wheezes]
- Stay out of my way, Flash.
I will be resuming my position
as CEO.
My husband, Joseph,
he worked tirelessly
to try to find me,
only to be murdered
moments after
we were reunited.
- Eva McCulloch has
never faced us head-on.
That's about to change.
We're gonna find her, beat her,
and get back everyone.
[hip-hop music]
- Yeah, you're right for now,
my sister,
but what if?
What if the entire universe
is just some kind of...
cosmic neural network?
[scoffs]
Then what you gonna say?
[laughs]
[alarm blaring]
Uh-oh.
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay.
[exhales deeply]
You know the drill, Chester P.
Been prepping this for weeks.
Okay, now, that is...
that is not good.
[mechanical whirring]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
Where's Eva?
- Satellites have her
at 2nd and Walczak.
Make that 3rd and Certo.
You doing okay?
I know the Cryo Pod keeps your
residual speed forces stasis,
but waking up can be
pretty disorienting.
- Call Joe.
Tell him I'm heading downtown.
- But, Flash, you only have
1% of your speed left.
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
- Then I better hurry.
- Eva's coordinates
slowed down.
Maybe she stopped moving?
- No.
She's going up.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
- Why do you keep interrupting
my mission, Flash?
I told you,
we're on the same side.
- If we're on the same side,
then give me back my wife!
♪ ♪
- My fractal photons move
at the speed of light.
You never had a chance.
[Eva shimmers]
[gunfire, indistinct shouting]
I don't want to hurt you.
But I'm cleansing the world
of Black Hole's influence,
so you either die,
or you stand down.
♪ ♪
- Flash, are you okay?
Flash?
- [groans]
- Okay, I picked up Eva
at a warehouse
on 199th Street.
Suspected hideout of...
Rosa Dillon and Sam Scudder,
aka...
- Top and Mirror Master.
- Yeah.
- [grunts]
- Mirror, no!
♪ ♪
You just killed
the man I loved.
- He never told you
what he really was?
'Cause Sam Scudder
wasn't a man.
He was my creation.
My first.
- [panting]
- Flash?
Did you make it?
Did you stop Eva?
- [sniffles]
- Flash?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Well, that was the best
takeout world tour yet.
Coq au vin from Paris,
sashimi from the Arctic...
- The Kansas State Fair
funnel cake
was Clark's recommendation.
- I just wish I didn't have
to go back to work already.
- Is anybody still here?
- Allegra went home
for the day.
And Kamilla,
she is...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Missing.
- I've missed you so much.
[high-pitched whine]
- No, this isn't right.
[groans, strained]
This isn't right.
[panting]
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
Barry?
♪ ♪
Oh, God.
I'm still here.
[breathing heavily]
- Eva hit nine more spots
last night.
I missed her every time.
- How much speed
do you have left?
- A few days.
Maybe a few hours.
- Eva's targeting
Black Hole tech, right?
So why go after Scudder
and Dillon?
- They were working
for Black Hole.
I found this
in Scudder's remains.
I'm guessing they've been
on Carver's payroll
since breaking out
of Iron Heights last year.
- And when they got
in Eva's way,
she moved them
off the chessboard?
- Well...
they are not the only ones.
The whole city thinks
that Sue killed Carver.
She and Ralph are staying
way off the grid.
- And Caitlin and Cisco
are still gone, too.
And Iris.
I should get back
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
If we're gonna stop Eva
and fix this,
I need the Artificial
Speed Force up and running.
- [sighs]
- Well, we may not know
where Scudder moved
the Black Hole tech,
but I bet you Dillon does.
I'm gonna go in,
see if I can get her
to talk to me.
- Actually, Captain...
I am.
- Right. When you were
a prosecutor,
you put Dillon in Iron Heights.
- And now I'm
her defense attorney
that's gonna keep her out
and get her to tell me
where that tech is.
- That's my girl.
- Connecting Fusion Sphere.
[grunts]
Fusion Sphere connected.
Activate.
- Uh...activated.
[Fusion Sphere whirs]
- Oh, it's working.
Now we just have to find
a fuel source to put in it.
- And then, we can power
the Artificial Speed Force.
- Exactly.
- [sighs]
[yawns]
Hey, uh...
- What?
- One of the sphere plates
doesn't look fully magnetized.
- Whoa! You can't touch that.
- Oh!
- If you touch the Fusion
Sphere while it's activated,
the Fusion Sphere thinks
you're the fuel source.
- Yes.
- And fuse my atoms,
which would lead to a complete
molecular degeneration.
Sorry. I'm just trying
to get your speed back.
- Don't hurt yourself
trying to do it.
I'd never want you to do that.
- Allen.
- What?
- [yawns]
- Can you get this guy
a coffee?
Wake him up?
- Yes. Let's...
Hey, come on.
Let's get a coffee.
- Whoa, can I use
that cappuccino maker
you guys have in the lounge?
- Um...
- Knock yourself out.
- Yes!
- All right.
- What? What?
- Well, it's nice
to see you, too.
So it turns out we cracked
the fuel problem
for this A.S.F. of yours.
- Pas facile non.
Not easy, not great.
- But so much fun, huh?
I love all the brainstorming.
Plus, we got all the Wellses
back together again.
- So I expect I need
no introduction,
but, yes, it is I,
master of stage and screen,
Harrison Orson Wells.
- Okay, you're new.
- Nash, as I know you know,
when our worlds died in Crisis,
particles from our brainwaves
were drawn to you like...
- Like a moth
drawn to a cosmic flame.
- Whatever happened
to show, don't tell?
H.R.?
- [yelps]
- Oh, nice catch.
- I love this part.
[gasps dramatically]
- So there are
multiversal particles
inside you right now, Nash,
made of synaptic energy.
Now, we take those particles
and you put them
in the Fusion Sphere,
theoretically,
they could power the A.S.F...
forever.
- [gasps dramatically]
Forever.
- Not only would Allen
get his speed back,
but I'd be rid
of you lot forever.
- No, you'd be gone, too,
I mean, because of the whole
organic receptor thing.
- Oof.
- What?
- What's he talking about?
- Multiversal particles are
just...they're very volatile.
Right? And there's no way
they'll stay in that sphere
long enough to be charged
unless...
unless we have
an organic receptor.
- The organic receptor...
is me.
- For the Flash to run again,
Nash Wells must die.
[suspenseful music]
- No.
- Whoa.
- What?
- No way!
- Nash, you're
our organic receptor.
You're the only one
that can contain us
inside the Fusion Sphere.
- By dying?
- Ye...
- By dying, Harry?
- Yes.
- How stupid do you think I am?
- Come on.
- I have a life here now.
I have people that
I actually don't hate.
I'm not gonna give all that up
so Barry Allen can run fast!
- Nash, you're the only one
of us that can help Allen.
- And I will, Harry,
by figuring out another way
to save Allen that doesn't mean
I have to commit suicide!
- Nash!
- Where he's going?
- [sighs]
- Bozos!
- Didn't see that coming.
- And scene.
- [panting]
What the hell?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Maybe I can message Kamilla.
- I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
♪ ♪
- My wife died
in the particle accelerator
explosion!
You're not...
even...
human.
♪ ♪
- You do not control me
anymore, Joseph.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- She killed Sam
right in front of me.
- If you tell me
where you and Scudder
were moving that tech,
I can use that information
to strike a deal for you
with the state and...
catch Sam's killer.
- I wish I knew,
but Sam made all the deals.
- That's funny.
Your IHP file says
that you were running
a psychotropic drug ring
out of the Meta-Wing.
You were flush with cash, and...
- [sighs]
- It's just that
you felt so sad
when you were
remembering that time.
It's almost as...
almost as if you were
deliberately projecting
a fake emotion at me,
but why would you do that?
Why would you do that
unless you already knew
that I was an empath?
- How would I know that?
I'm not psychic.
I just cause vertigo.
- What else can you do
inside people's minds, Rosa?
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
- Let me show you.
- [gasping]
I feel so empty.
♪ ♪
What did you do to me?
- I found a little
kernel of doubt
inside of you
and spun, spun, spun it
into a full-blown crisis
of confidence...
like a top.
[snaps fingers]
- [gasps, breathes heavily]
Scudder's ditzy girlfriend?
It was all an act.
- I was always the brains.
He was just the pretty face.
Then Sam cut a deal
with Black Hole.
We got rich, but
we were in over our heads.
So, when I heard Eva McCulloch
wanted him dead...
- You sold him out to her.
- And in return,
Eva gave me a cause
to believe in.
She delegated her next mission
to me.
And what I've cooked up for her
is gonna blow this city away.
- If you are planning something
that will put people
in danger...
- What?
The Flash is gonna stop me?
[softly]
He can barely run.
[normal voice] You know,
when I first got my powers,
I was an empath, too.
And look what I've grown into.
Who knows what
you would've become
if only you weren't so...
afraid?
Guess we'll never know.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Thought you could use
a pick-me-up.
- Thank you.
- "Organic Receptors
in Nuclear Physics."
- Yeah. Yeah.
- What's an organic receptor?
- Ah, no. I'm just, uh...
This is...I'm just helping Barry
get his speed back,
or I'm trying to, anyway.
- Well, it's nice
to see you care about someone
other than me for a change.
- Well, you're...
♪ ♪
You're the answer.
Multiversal particles
oscillate at certain
frequencies of light.
Allegra can control
electromagnetic wavelengths.
- So she can push the particles
out of you
and into the Fusion Sphere.
- Right.
- Charging a fuel source
for the A.S.F.
- And we take all
that kinetic energy,
and we just transfer it
to the track ring above us...
- Giving Flash his groove back.
- Uh, just...just one thing.
- What?
- Aren't multiverse particles
a little too chaotic
to be contained
in a Fusion Sphere?
- Yes, normally they would be,
but Allegra can use her powers
to contain the particles
inside the Fusion Sphere
from a safe distance.
- [sighs]
- Hey, thanks
for looking out for me,
but if Nash says it's
gonna work, I trust him.
- Okay.
- [clears throat quietly]
All right, then.
Ready?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
The Fusion Sphere is...
ready for particle insertion.
- Okay.
Good?
- Yeah.
- [exhales sharply]
[whirring]
♪ ♪
[exhales sharply]
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
[Fusion Sphere whirring]
- Guys...
something's not right.
- What's happening?
- Uh...
the charge is dropping.
- I can't hold it much longer.
[Fusion Sphere crackling]
♪ ♪
- A-Allen?
- Barry, you okay?
- Please be okay.
Please be okay.
- [groans]
- [sighs in relief]
- [grunts]
[French accent]
Hello.
Qu'est ce qui se passe?
What are you all doing?
- Uh, since when
do you speak French?
- Since always, no?
- Why is he talking funny?
- I think when the particles
left the Fusion Sphere,
they transferred to
Barry Allen.
- So all the brainwaves
of all the Wellses
who've ever lived...
- Are inside
Monsieur Allen's mind.
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
- Allow me, introduce myself.
I'm Sherloque Wells,
master detective,
at your service.
- I'm Chester.
Chester P. Runk.
- Chester.
- Yeah.
- There's a Sherlock Wells?
- Sherloque.
- Yes, there's
a Sherlock Wells.
- Sherloque.
- -loque.
- -lock.
- Sherlock.
- -loque.
- -lock.
- Good. Good.
No great.
♪ ♪
- Vite, mes ami.
We face a mystery stranger
than the King Tut Killer
of Earth-66.
The Many Minds
of Barry Allen.
- Oh, man.
- All of them ended up
inside Barry?
- It looks like, but, listen,
let's not panic.
Between the three of us
and a master detective,
we can figure out
how to fix Barry Allen.
- [grunts]
[as H.R. Wells] You guys
talking about B.A.?
He's so fast!
- Oh.
What just happened to him?
- I think another set
of Wells particles
just took over his mind.
- H.R. Wells.
How you guys doing?
Yeah, so this is simple...
we just get all the Wellses
out of B.A.
into the Futon Sphere.
- It's a...Stop.
It's a Fusion Sphere.
- Huh?
- Can you stop drumming?
- Huh? Huh?
- Can you stop drum...okay.
The drumming is so annoying...
- [grunts]
[as Wells the Grey]
Do you hear the drums?
They are coming.
It is I,
Wells the Grey.
- Oh, Wells the Grey.
- There's a wizard Wells?
- [groans]
This is all my fault.
- Oh, my God.
Do you know Gandalf?
- Barry trusted me to help him,
and I screwed up.
- No, it's not...
it's not your fault.
Look, here's what we'll do.
Um, just blast him again,
and we'll push the particles
back into me.
- Uh-uh. No way.
I'll just make it worse.
- No, you won't make it worse.
- [groans]
- All we got to do is
figure out a way to contain
the particles once they leave
Allen's body, like a magnet...
- Uh...
Guys? Guys?
[sinister music]
- [breathing heavily]
What are you?
- Can't figure it out?
[clicks tongue]
Aw.
Did you lose your dissertation?
- [panting]
♪ ♪
You're a copy of me.
- No.
I'm no fractal anomaly.
I am a product
of your broken mind.
- That's impossible.
- No, it's not.
You pushed your mind
to find Singh
until it broke...
[distorted voice]
Forever.
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- [growls]
[grunts]
- Leave me alone.
- There's no
escaping this, Iris.
How long have you been
trying to get out?
Weeks? Months?
You are weak
in every universe...
an insignificant speck,
a victim.
- [panting]
- Okay. Okay.
Don't worry. I'm gonna use
the Mobile Gideon
to diagnose him.
So, Gideon,
what's wrong with Barry?
- An abundance
of multiversal particles
inside his mind are causing
his cerebral cortex
to overload.
- Yeah, all those brainwaves
at once?
It's like when Grodd
was trapped in his mind,
but to an infinite degree.
- Only Barry Allen's
speed healing
is keeping him alive now.
- Gideon, what happens
when his speed runs out?
- If the particles remain
inside his brain,
Barry Allen
will instantly die.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Barry is going to die
because of what I did to him.
- No. No.
I should've trusted my gut.
Look, I knew
we needed something else
to keep the sphere intact.
- Yeah.
That was supposed
to be my stupid powers.
- No, they're not stupid, okay?
The particles always
needed something stronger,
like some sort of...
I don't know, some sort
of organic receptor.
[dramatic music]
- That's what you were
researching in your office.
You let me think
I was the only solution,
when this whole time,
there was another way?
- No, it's not that simple...
- Yes, it is.
You lied!
- Yes! I lied!
Because I'm
the organic receptor.
♪ ♪
And I'm not ready to die yet.
- Okay, look,
Barry wouldn't let anyone die
for the Artificial Speed Force.
- Yeah, so why lie about it?
♪ ♪
- Because I was scared.
- I get it.
♪ ♪
I thought you had changed.
Chuck...
- It's Chester P.,
actually, but...
- I need a way
to aim the particles
after I push them out of Barry.
- Like a particle magnet?
I can build that.
Oh, I mean, I can try.
- Lead the way.
♪ ♪
- What the hell?
[groaning]
- Harry...
- Look at these
brainwave ratings.
Allen's cerebellum
is burning up.
- Harry, if you want the kid
to survive,
then maybe you better relax...
- I'm fine!
I'm fine.
Do not touch me.
- Mm.
[sighs]
- What happened
to the J.V. squad?
- Ah.
- Why are you
moping around here
instead of helping them?
- Oh, they don't want my help.
Right?
- Mm.
Frankly, I don't blame them.
♪ ♪
- Garcia found out the truth?
- Yeah.
You know what Cisco said
after Crisis?
He said, "An infinite number
of Harrison Wells,
and we're stuck with the one
who killed the Multiverse."
And every day
I ask myself, why?
Why am I the one
left standing?
- So who should've
gotten the slot?
One of us bozos?
- [sighs]
You're not bozos.
I only called you that
because I find
the Wells very annoying...
present company excluded.
But you know what you are?
You're a daily reminder
that even though
we may all look the same,
we're not the same...
because you're all good men.
And I'm...
I'm not.
- So you're a selfish jerk.
- Hmm.
- You think that I wasn't?
That we all weren't?
Hell, when I met this team,
I was working for Zoom.
H.R. lied.
Sherloque...
kept secrets.
We all came here broken men.
Thanks to Team Flash,
eventually we
learned to be better.
That's why I believe
in you, Nash.
There's a good man
in there somewhere.
You just need to dig him up,
let him breathe.
- [panting]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
You're not real.
- Boo.
♪ ♪
- No, I'm not crazy.
- Yeah, you are.
And there's only two options
in this place...
survival...
[distorted voice]
Or madness.
- No.
This is not neural dissonance.
I'm not seeing you
because I'm...
I'm crazy and broken.
This is something else...
someone else.
[breathes deeply]
♪ ♪
Keep trying to break me down...
because I am not afraid
of the woman that I am today.
But you are...
Eva.
You want me distracted.
I must be getting close...
to finding my way out of here.
- You can push yourself
until you break,
and you will never escape
this world.
I'm sorry, Iris,
but if you can't accept
my conditions either,
you might never see
your husband again.
- [growls]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
You actually came back.
- I'm a defense attorney, Rosa.
I can handle a few mind games.
I'm here to get you a deal.
- Am I supposed to be
intimidated by you now?
The woman who's afraid
of her own powers?
- Maybe you're right, okay?
Maybe...maybe I am afraid.
When I first got
these abilities,
I was so excited.
But then when my powers...
they started to grow
and change,
and I...
I bottled them up
because I was afraid.
I was afraid I was gonna
become someone like you.
- Are you trying to rile me up?
- No, Rosa.
I'm trying to remind myself
of all of that fear
that I have locked down
deep inside...
so that I can put it all
into you.
- [gasping]
My heart...is...racing!
♪ ♪
[wheezing]
- You want to go
back to prison?
Or do you want to tell me
what you're planning?
- [panting]
[door opens]
- Hey. What's wrong?
- There's a supersonic jet
about to leave
a secret Black Hole site
in the badlands,
and it is loaded
with all of Carver's
remaining tech.
But that's not the only thing
it's carrying.
[beeping]
Cecile: Rosa Dillon
planted a bomb on board.
If it blows over this city,
hundreds of people will die.
- And the Flash isn't
fast enough to stop it.
♪ ♪
- Okay. Okay.
Here, put this on.
Once Allegra pushes
the particles outside of Barry,
these ionic circuits will catch
them, put them back into you.
- Smart, Runk.
- That's brilliant.
- Thanks.
- Listen, when this is over,
I'll find a way
to make this up to you.
- This is a pretty good start.
Ready?
both: Yeah.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Hey. Hey, hey.
It's working.
Keep going.
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Barry?
Are you...Barry?
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
It's really me.
- [laughs]
- Hey, hey.
- All right,
let's celebrate later,
because we still have
a supersonic jet
about to explode over the city.
- I still can't stop it.
♪ ♪
The plane's only
three minutes out.
We need a plan.
- No.
We need the Flash.
- Nash!
That'll kill you.
- I know.
But I'm the organic receptor
that we need.
You're getting your speed back.
[groans]
- Hey! Hey!
We'll find another way.
- What other way, Allen?
There's no time.
- Nash.
You don't have to do this
just to prove a point.
- I'm not doing it
to prove a point.
I'm doing it because
I won't watch you die.
I won't let any of you die.
[groans]
- Don't! Don't! Don't!
No, no, no, no, no. If you
touch him, we'll lose you, too.
- [grunts]
- Nash, please.
I can't let anyone else
die for me.
I've already lost
so many people.
- Do you know what I feel
right now, Allen?
Pride.
Honor.
It's been so long
since I felt those things.
And it's not just me.
The Council feels it, too.
And we've made our decision.
We're doing this, Allen.
[groans]
Is it charging?
- Uh...
[whirring]
Yeah, the Fusion Sphere
is charging.
- [grunts]
- How can I be the Flash
without a Wells on this team?
- You've always been the Flash.
You always will be...
with or without me.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[as H.R. Wells]
Hey, B.A.
How's it going?
[chuckles]
You're so fast.
No, no, no.
B.A., don't be upset.
This...this is not goodbye.
It's just...
till our next communion.
[grunts]
[as Sherloque]
Not great, hmm?
Our current situation, huh?
But...
it will be.
[speaking French]
[grunts]
[pants]
[as Harry]
Allen...
you know, when I came
to your stupid Earth...
- [chuckles]
- With its good burgers...
I was a broken man...
lost, angry,
blah, blah, blah,
and you showed me...
how to be a better person.
And I'll always be grateful
for our friendship.
Now...
♪ ♪
Run.
Barry...
run.
♪ ♪
- We're at 80%.
- You got this.
[strained grunting]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[Fusion Sphere roaring loudly]
After I'm gone...
look out for one another.
[groaning loudly]
[screaming]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[bomb beeping]
- [panting]
♪ ♪
[solemn music]
[ambient music]
♪ ♪
- A.R.G.U.S. was waiting
for the jet when it landed.
They seized all
the Black Hole tech on board.
- All thanks to the Flash.
- [sighs]
- So Nash died a hero.
And I...
I never really
got to know him.
- ♪ No way to know
what's on my mind ♪
♪ But you always say
the words that save my life ♪
- Look, I know after tonight
that none of us will...
ever be the same.
♪ ♪
But we all heard
what Nash said.
He was so happy
to have you in his life.
♪ ♪
- Thanks, Chester.
- Y-you can call me Chuck.
♪ ♪
- I need to tell
the rest of the team.
I'll call Carla,
make sure Caitlin knows.
Cisco's gonna want to come back
from his trip.
Harry was like a father to him.
When they were all in my mind,
I could...
I could feel their spirits.
I could feel
how much they loved me.
They gave themselves up for me.
♪ ♪
How am I supposed
to live with that?
- Uh, I think that's the point.
You know, they put themselves
in the A.S.F.
so you could live...
and thrive.
- And now, whenever you run,
it'll kind of be like
they'll be running with you.
Right?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
You know, Nash wasn't
the only one who rose
to the occasion today.
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you guys.
♪ ♪
- So...
what now, Flash?
- We go save Iris
and our friends.
- We get everybody back.
- I've got friends
that will run ♪
♪ Through walls ♪
♪ And I've got friends
that don't text ♪
♪ They call ♪
♪ And when I've nowhere
left to go ♪
♪ And I need you the most ♪
♪ I've got friends
that will run ♪
♪ Through walls ♪
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Eva, what was that?
Are you okay?
Eva?
[gasps]
Help!
Someone help me!
[computer beeps]
- I died.
♪ ♪
Everything I thought was a lie.
I'm the mirror duplicate.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.