- Hey, you hungry?
I was thinking
blueberry pancakes
for breakfast this morning.
Or I could get us something fun
from that Brooklyn's Best
Bagels place.
They just opened
a new location downtown.
[inquisitive music]
Iris?
♪
[ominous music]
[touch tones dialing]
[line trills]
[phone buzzing]
[suspenseful music]
♪
Iris.
[dramatic music]
♪
- [chuckles]
Thanks for the company, Cecile.
- Any time.
- You know, I figured you'd
be working this time of day.
- Oh, I was.
Yeah, I'm actually
avoiding a new meta-client.
So I figured I'd
get out of the office,
come over,
see what Team Flash is up to.
- Ah, well,
we're all good here.
Yeah, the town is quiet,
no alerts,
no crisis, just sweet, sweet,
silen--
- Okay.
Barry, what's wrong?
- Yeah, should we be worried?
- It's Iris.
She's missing.
[heroic music]
♪
- Satellites aren't picking
Iris up anywhere in the city.
I'm gonna expand
the physical search radius.
- Cecile, anything?
[tense music]
- Nothing.
I can't sense her either,
and I've reached out
across a five-state radius.
It's like Iris's
mind has just vanished.
- Same here, only worse.
Barry, Iris isn't registering
anywhere on the planet.
How's that even possible?
- It's just like last time,
she's not here anymore,
at least not
in this plane of existence.
She must have
had another attack.
Now she's lost in time.
- Okay, well,
then we need Deon to find her.
- No one's seen Deon
since he disappeared,
and I can't access
the Still Force without him.
- Okay, so--
so what do--what do we do?
- Okay, okay,
it's a long shot, but--
look, when Iris was
in Coast City, it wasn't just
her time sickness
that caused her to vanish.
Tinya Wazzo's powers did too.
♪
- I can't believe
you're serious.
You really want to try
and bring Frost back?
- And I already have a plan--
I'm gonna repurpose
Eva McCulloch's R-CEM chip
to replicate
Frost's cryogene so I can
create a new body for her.
- Caitlin,
I know you're hurting,
and so am I,
but listen to yourself.
- It worked before.
It will work again.
- And what about the thing
that makes Frost, Frost?
- I have already identified
her latent empathic genes
on my DNA.
- I'm talking about a soul
and you give me brainwaves?
- I'm also going
to extract her active imprints
from her own DNA.
Look, I've already
got the sample.
Unfortunately,
the keratin in the cells
is decaying a little
too quickly, so...
I'm gonna need a better sample.
- You talking
about grave robbing?
- It's called an exhumation,
and I am a doctor as well
as the next of kin,
so getting approval won't
be a problem, we just--
we need to do it quickly.
[tense music]
I-I know how this sounds.
- Oh, like that old
horror movie,
"Frankenstein Created Woman?"
Does Team Flash know
what you're planning?
Didn't think so.
- They wouldn't understand.
- Neither do I!
Caitlin, have you forgotten
that you literally just tried
to resurrect your dead husband,
and it was a complete disaster?
- No, I haven't, but that thing
was never Ronnie, okay?
Deathstorm used a physical form
that I loved
to try and trick us.
Look, this is different.
The science is solid, trust me.
- No.
Mad science.
- Mark--Mark,
Frost was supposed
to live a full
and complete life.
You both were, together,
and now that's been
taken from you.
Don't you want that back?
- What do you think?
You can process losing Frost
in whatever way you need to,
but as far as all
of this is concerned...
Count me out.
♪
[door closes]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
- Tinya, um, can--
can we talk?
- Why?
I don't know you.
- I'm Barry Allen.
You know my wife,
Iris West-Allen.
I'm really sorry, but she's
missing again, and I don't--
- Again?
Whatever, I don't care.
Your other half ruined my life.
- You have every right
to be angry.
I need your help.
The first time
Iris disappeared,
she was with you.
- You mean when I wiped
her out of existence,
like she did to my mom?
- Are you okay?
What the hell?
- Mom!
What did you do to my mom?
- Tinya, she never meant
to hurt anyone.
- Well, I did,
which is why
you should back off.
- Do you even understand
how your powers work?
Examining how they work
could help us answer
what's really
happening to Iris.
- I don't care about Iris.
God, what is wrong with you?
You know, I was fine
until Iris found me
and started spewing
all that crap about family
and having faith in people.
She made me believe
that I could
have the life
that I always wanted.
And now that's gone,
and it's never coming back.
So welcome to the club.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[audio distorting]
[distant screaming approaching]
- Deon, thank God.
Iris is missing.
- Yeah, I know.
Yeah, she's in the Still Force.
I've been trying
to track her down, but--
[groaning]
- Hey--
- No, don't--don't--don't.
Don't.
I've been infected
by Iris' time sickness too.
I need you to find
the isotopic sensor.
It's the only way
we can track down
that particle
that I placed inside Iris.
- We?
- Barry, I can't
find her alone.
I-I'm going to need your help.
- Okay.
Okay--the sensor's damaged.
We're gonna need
to repair it first.
- Okay.
Okay, do it fast.
I'll come back for you after.
[chaotic music]
♪
- This is how
we get Iris back.
- So you're saying
that Deon wants to do that
by bringing you
into the Still Force?
- Well, both of us, together.
- I thought he said it was
too dangerous for anyone
to go in there who wasn't,
you know, a god?
- It's risky, but I trust Deon,
and he wouldn't suggest this
if there was any other way.
- Well, Deon's right
about one thing.
Our satellites can't
trace isotopic particles
across other planes
of existence.
- That's why we need you
to repair the sensor.
It's the only thing
that can locate Iris'
temporal particle
inside the Still Force.
But once we find her,
we bring her home.
- Amen to that.
- Not to question a god,
but why would Deon need help
tracking a particle
that he created himself?
- Deon's not at full strength.
Iris' time sickness has
affected him too.
Uh, Chester, how long will it
take to get the sensor running?
- Uh, an hour, maybe less,
but Barr, how are you
gonna get inside
the Still Force
in the first place?
- Deon's gonna come back
for me as soon as he can,
and we need to be
ready when he does.
- And you ran this plan
past the other forces?
Nora, Bashir, Alexa,
they're all on board too?
- Uh, no, I haven't been
able to contact them...
any of them.
- And Iris' sickness,
it could have spread
to them already.
- Which would explain
why they've been radio silent.
- If that is the case,
then maybe we should
all slow down
and figure it out
before we launch you
into a place where
we know nothing about, Barry.
- There's no time.
Look, Joe, Deon is our
only chance at finding Iris.
If he says going
into the Still Force
is the answer,
then I believe him.
I-I'm gonna get the sensor
from the Starchives.
I'll meet you in your workshop.
- I should get back to CCC.
Got to keep the lights on
until Iris is safe.
[tense music]
♪
- Barr, hold up!
- What?
- Look, I'm willing to do
whatever it takes
to bring Iris home,
but something don't
feel right about this.
- Look, it's dangerous,
but we've taken greater risks--
- Yes, we have,
but are you sure
about the facts,
because you seem to be putting
a whole lot of faith
in Deon's plan.
- Because I know it'll work.
- That's what Deon thinks
you should do.
What do you think
you should do?
- That's just it,
I don't know.
- And Deon does?
- Look, Joe,
I owe Deon this.
As soon as I learned
about Iris' time sickness,
I should have spent
every waking moment trying
to find a cure, even when
she told me to stop pushing.
But I didn't.
Now it's worse,
plus Deon's affected too.
If there's a chance
I can find Iris
and make up for all this,
I have to take it.
♪
[phone buzzing]
- Parliament Runkadelic--
- It's Captain Kramer.
- Uh, yes--yes, ma'am.
[clears throat]
How can I help?
- Chester, I need
a full analysis
on an unknown device
we found at a crime scene.
You're not busy, uh,
saving the world, are you?
- No--no, Captain,
your timing is perfect.
Barry's gone to where
no man's been before,
so I'm free to fly solo.
- Great, thanks,
I'll see you soon.
- Oh, you heard it,
Chester P,
the crime-fighting world
needs your mojo!
Mojo.
[whispering] Mojo.
Seven out of ten.
[tense music]
♪
[distant screaming approaching]
- Oh, damn, moving through
dimensions is getting harder.
Is that it?
- Are--are you sure
we can find her?
- There's just one thing.
Where we're going,
there's only one way
in and out,
and it's a bumpy ride,
so hang on.
'Cause things are
about to get real weird.
♪
- [panting]
- Don't worry,
you'll get used to it.
- I've been here before.
When Iris--
- First got sick, yeah.
Place is like a doorway.
I call it my front porch.
I can see everything from here.
[rumbling]
[electricity crackling]
- This place is different
than before.
- Yeah, that's 'cause
it's more dangerous now.
Welcome to the Still Force...
What's left of it.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[dramatic music]
- Sorry about the mess.
- How bad is it?
- Ever since
Iris got lost here,
things have been
mad disorganized.
I mean, night becomes day
in the blink of an eye,
and just as fast,
it's night again.
- And now
it's getting worse.
[tense music]
♪
- You see, past, present,
and future
all exist here simultaneously,
but now the balance
is all out of whack.
See what I mean?
All right, now,
stay close to me,
'cause if we get separated--
- I could get lost too.
- Or worse.
You could get trapped
in the dead zone
where time just repeats
itself indefinitely.
That happens?
I'd never get you out.
[sensor beeping]
- Sensor's picking up
Iris' signature.
- All right. Let's ease
on down the road, man.
[birds cawing]
[distant conversation]
- Don't--don't.
- We're getting close.
- Yeah.
- My decision...
- Oh, one thing,
once we find Iris,
let me try
and stabilize her first,
before we do anything else.
- They need to know
what you've been hiding.
- All right.
- Taylor, don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
- I know those voices.
- They need to know--
they--they need to know
what you've been hiding.
- Taylor, don't--don't--don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
- They need to know what you've
been--you've been hiding.
- Taylor, don't.
Taylor, don't.
Ugh!
This is my life.
- What is this?
- My decision.
- They need to know--
been hiding.
- Future moment,
stuck on repeat.
- Hiding--they need to know--
they need to know...
- They can't move onward
and become part of the past.
- My--my decision.
It's not what you think.
- They need to know
what you've been hiding.
- Taylor, don't--my--my life.
My d-d-decision.
Taylor, don't.
This is--this is my life.
- How do we stop it?
- We can't.
Not till we find Iris
and fix this whole place.
- Help me.
Someone, please help me.
[breathing shakily]
Help me.
Please, I don't know
what's happening to me.
I have to get back
to my daughter.
- Renee.
Renee Wazzo.
You're Tinya's mom.
- Yes.
Do you know where she is?
I have to find before--
be-be-before--
- She's trapped in here too,
just like Iris.
- Mm.
- We have to find her again.
Tinya thought she'd lost her,
but if her mom's alive--
- Uh-uh, she's fracturing just
like me and Iris, all right?
We need to stick
to why we're here.
- Deon, we have to help her.
Renee's been lost
in all this for weeks.
- Hey, what we need to do
is keep moving,
or else Iris is history.
She's the key
to everything, man.
[sensor beeping]
Iris is close.
I can feel it.
- Hey, thanks for coming in.
- Oh, always happy
to tech consult
for Central City's finest.
Also, I am in love
with the artwork in here.
Is it, uh--
- Indigenous, yes.
Reminds me of home.
[sentimental music]
♪
- Nice.
So I'm guessing
this is our mystery machine?
- There was an explosion
at a halfway house
downtown this morning.
Fire department secured this
from the rubble.
Apparently, it was attached
to the water heater.
- Was anyone hurt?
- Well, that's
the strange part.
CCFD got a call
about an imminent explosion.
By the time
they arrived on scene,
everyone had
already been evacuated.
Then this released
an energy wave
that took out
the entire building.
- Damn.
Folks could have died.
How many people were
living there?
- 37 at the time.
We got lucky.
Halfway house staff have
no idea who led the evacuation,
so this device
is our only lead.
I need to know what it is,
what it does, and who built it.
- Oh, I'm picking up traces
of radioactive particles.
This thing was packing
serious kinetic energy
before it went kaboom.
Maybe it's some kind of...
Some kind of like, EMP.
Whoa.
That's quantum coiling.
Captain, whoever built this
got mad skills.
[mysterious music]
♪
- Everything all right,
Chester?
- Huh?
Oh, oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm as good as a hydrogen-phat
sunrise over Jupiter.
Yeah, um, I'm just--
I'm gonna take this
back to my workshop
and do a full diagnostic,
you know, just to make sure
that everything's
totally cool, if that's fine.
- Of course.
I'll authorize it.
- Okay.
- Runk, are you okay?
- Yeah, yep--definitely.
I'm five-by-five
by the wayside.
Just gonna pack up my things.
♪
[sensor beeping]
[eerie music]
♪
- Vanya's the editor-in-chief?
[sensor beeping]
This can't be right.
Where is she?
- Stop.
- What?
Tracing that particle should
have led us right to her.
- Yeah, I know, I know,
just--just hold on.
- What are you--
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Deon!
We needed that to find Iris!
- Sorry, Barr.
Gotta bounce.
[dramatic music]
♪
- What the hell?
I'm back home again...
With no way out.
♪
- Shark Stadium erupted
in cheers
after XS' heroic save.
Even without Impulse,
her partner in crime-fighting,
who was too busy partying
to answer his alerts.
- [belching loudly]
- Ugh.
You are so disgusting!
It is clear that XS is the most
daring speedster
to appear in years.
- Good afternoon,
Nora West-Allen.
How can I assist you?
- Gideon, I need another
word for daring
that isn't too flowery.
- Of course. I have found
twenty-sev--twenty--
- Gideon?
Gideon.
Where'd you go?
[disembodied gasp]
- Nora!
Nor--
Nora!
[suspenseful music]
♪
Nora!
- Deon?
I-is that you?
- Barry's trapped.
I can't help him, but you can.
- [spluttering] Where?
How am I--
- [groans]
- Uh...
Oh, schrap.
[tense music]
♪
- Iris, come on!
This brunch reservation ain't
gonna get any later.
- Joe, don't worry.
I'll make sure we're on time.
- You guys got
any resolutions for 2022?
- I know mine.
More family time.
[building suspenseful music]
♪
- Holy schrap, thank goodness
I found you, Dad.
- Nora?
This place is messing with me.
- Dad!
- Nora?
- Hi.
- You're really here.
- Oh, my God,
I'm a super villain.
- Seriously?
That's what you're
worried about?
Okay, then where's
your meta hunting dagger
or your purple head fan?
- No, no, I'm--
I'm serious, okay?
I'm the bad guy in all of this.
- No, you're not.
- Oh, yeah?
Allegra, the microchip
that I found inside that thing
was hardwired
with a one-of-a-kind
energy converter
that I created.
- But you didn't
build this one.
- So--so what?
I still went live
with the designs
on my blog last month.
- What is this anyway?
- It's a quantum
coil transformer,
which means it's
extremely powerful
and dangerous if used
for the wrong application.
You know what, you were right.
You're ri--I should have
never put my designs online.
I never will again.
- Chuck, you're overreacting.
- I should have
vetted my online posse.
- Your posse could
be anyone, but,
Chuck, you inspire people.
You don't send them
to the dark side.
Think about it.
You said there were no
casualties because the person
that built this
evacuated the place
before it detonated.
Does that sound
like a supervillain?
Or his accomplice?
- No, Allegra, but I--
- Then believe me
when I tell you,
we're missing the real story.
And you're one
of the good ones.
So have a little faith
in yourself.
[uplifting music]
♪
- Dad, how are we supposed
to get out of here?
- I don't know.
You shouldn't have
followed me here.
You were safer in 2049.
- But Deon told me
you needed my help.
- Deon?
Deon's the reason
I'm stuck here.
I never should
have trusted him.
- I mean,
you and Mom created Deon.
Of course you're
gonna trust him.
- I know.
Joe tried telling me
something was off and...
I didn't listen.
I was so focused on...
trying to find your mom,
I ignored the signs.
She's counting on me, and I--
I keep letting her down.
- I want to tell you something.
I mean, you're gonna find out
in a few decades anyways, but--
you know how the other
Nora was a CSI
and was following
in your footsteps?
Well, I kind of
did the opposite.
I'm a reporter.
And even though I love it,
I-I'm just starting out.
And sometimes I'm, like,
how does Mom even do this?
- I'm proud of you.
- So you're not mad I didn't
join CCPD like you
and Grandpa Joe?
- No, of course not.
I'm just--I'm glad you found
a path that's right for you.
- Phew.
So, um, the thing is, is that
I'm having a really hard time
finding my voice as a reporter.
But Mom is teaching me
to have faith in myself
and listen to my instincts.
And if she were here right now,
she'd tell you to do the same.
And that everyone loses faith
in themselves sometimes,
even heroes.
But learning how to keep
believing in yourself
when the whole world
is telling you the opposite,
that's what makes a hero.
[sentimental music]
- You really are
your mom's daughter.
- Well, I'm yours too.
Maybe it's our belief
in each other that keeps us
connected just as much
as the other stuff.
- You're right.
We are connected.
But not just our family.
Me and Iris,
to the Still Force.
It's like you said,
we created it.
Nora, I heard your voice
before you got here.
I think somehow,
just for a moment,
I connected to the future
before it became a part
of the present.
- Or the past.
You must already have a piece
of the Still Force inside you.
- If I can figure out
how to connect to it again
and control it this time,
I can get us out of here.
[saber-toothed cat growls]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Okay. I'm ready.
- Okay, remember,
whatever remnant of stillness
is inside me
won't be there for long.
- You look like Uncle Wally
when he taught Bart
how to create
lightning constructs.
- This is also
how Wally taught me
how to make contact
with the other forces.
[tense music]
♪
Nothing's happening.
[building heroic music]
♪
- Focus on Mom's brush.
She still has it in the future.
You can use it as an anchor.
♪
[heartbeat thumping]
[chaotic music]
♪
- What in the world--
in the world--in the world?
Barry, Nora, what are you two
doing in my living room?
- [echoing]
Grandpa Joe, you can see us?
- Plain as day,
only you're glowing
with some kind of green light.
Barry, I thought you were
in the Still Force with Deon?
- Dad, whatever you're doing,
it must be working,
because if Grandpa Joe can
see us too,
the present must
be stabilizing.
- Barry, can you hear me?
Barry!
[voice echoing]
♪
- Grandpa Joe's gone.
And so is the brush.
Dad, are you okay?
[electricity crackling]
- Nora, the temporal stream...
I can feel
the pure Still Force energy
moving through me.
I can see the past, present,
and future all at once.
I can see Jesse and Harry.
Cisco and Frost too.
I can see Bart's children,
your wife.
Nora, you're all so happy.
I see...
Max?
- I'm getting married?
Who's the lucky lady?
Actually, don't tell me.
- I can already feel
the spark inside me fading.
Take my hand.
- Oh, this feels
seriously weird.
- Let's get the hell
out of here.
[exciting music]
- Where's the exit
in this place?
- Memorial Park.
It's the only way in and out
of the Still Force.
♪
[both yelp]
- Schrap!
What the hell happened?
- It's a temporal barrier.
We have to hit it
with everything we've got
while trying
to phase through it.
♪
[both yelp]
[both groaning]
[tense music]
♪
- We're caught
in a temporal loop.
Dad, we're never
gonna get out of here.
- You see, the past,
present, and future
all exist here simultaneously.
- Yes, we are.
This isn't a time loop.
It's the Still Force
pulling us back
into the past every time
we're about to escape.
- Why would it do that?
- Deon said the past, present,
and future all coexist here,
so if we've already escaped,
the only way to stop us...
- Is to keep us stuck
in the past.
- Nora, use the spark I gave
you to focus on the moment
that's already on the other
side of that barrier.
The moment you
and I get back home.
[exciting music]
♪
Focus on the moment you
and I get back home.
We get back home.
I get back home.
Home.
[both grunting]
[triumphant music]
♪
- Wait, so you're telling me
that you were
able to get out of there
'cause you already
knew you had?
- I know,
it's totally surreal, right?
- Barry, is there still
a spark of the Still Force
inside of you,
because if that's the case,
then maybe we can use that
to help find Iris.
- Not anymore.
I tried to tap into it again
as soon as we got back,
and I must have used every bit
I had to get us out of there.
We'll have
to find Iris another way.
- And we will.
- You know, guys,
there's one thing
that I still don't quite get.
Barry, why would Deon want
to trap you in the past?
- Yeah, I don't know.
I'm really worried about him.
- I'd better get back to 2049,
make sure Mom's still there
and that she's okay.
I'm gonna miss you guys
so much.
- We're gonna miss you too.
- Sweet one.
- But you're right,
we need you there
to keep our family's
future safe.
- Bye.
- [sighs]
I miss her and Bart more
and more every day.
- Yeah.
- And my baby girl.
- Joe, about earlier,
I should have listened to you.
You know, you were right
about everything.
- It's okay, we all stumble.
I'm just glad
you picked yourself up.
- Look, there's--
there's something else.
When I was in the Still Force
and I tapped
into a tiny bit of it...
I could feel Iris,
almost see her.
It was like a spark
of stillness
was inside her too,
that I could sense.
- What do you think it means?
- I'm not sure,
but somehow I know,
wherever she is right now,
she's okay.
[peaceful music]
♪
- No problem, just remember,
you can message me anytime
you need help with a project,
day or night.
- You're feeling better.
- Yeah, yeah--
hey, you were right.
Yeah, there was more
to the story,
and once I started digging,
I remembered
where I'd seen
this circuitry before.
Wookielover77 posted this
in the comments
of one of my live streams.
He was asking the Chester Posse
for tips on renewable energy.
- It was all an accident,
wasn't it?
- Yeah.
Wookielover77 volunteers
at that halfway house.
He was just trying
to provide the residents
with unlimited hot water
from a clean source.
- Someone's a believer again.
- Thanks to you.
- You're welcome.
- So I was thinking, you know,
Marco's birthday drinks are
in ten.
How about I buy you
a root beer?
You know, to say thanks,
and I could
use one myself, actually.
- I would love that.
- Yeah?
Okay.
[cheerful music]
♪
[tense music]
[computer beeping]
[eerie music]
♪
[knocking at door]
- It's me, open up.
- Go away.
- Sorry about that.
I think you're gonna want
to hear what I have to say.
- What is wrong with you?
First, you blow me off,
and now you break into my home.
What, I should--
I should call the Flash?
- Well, that's your choice,
just like this one's mine.
I'm gonna help you.
And don't worry,
I'll pay for a new lock.
Now, you wanna know
why I changed my mind?
Because you were right.
Frost and I were just starting
to build a life together,
and thanks to her,
I was finally becoming the man
that I didn't even know
I'd always wanted to be.
Losing her broke me,
but losing her twice?
That'd kill me.
That's--
that's why I was
so afraid to help you.
So...
if we do this,
I need you
to promise me one thing...
that we won't fail.
- We won't, I promise.
[suspenseful music]
- Then let's get to work.
♪
- Greg, move your head.