[device charging]
[growls]
-[roars]
-[gasps]
-[gunfire]
-[growling]
[ticking]
[heartbeat thumping]
[sighs]
-[children yelling]
-[people chattering]
[chattering]
-[rooster crowing]
-[dog barking]
[siren wails]
-[person shouts]
-[truck beeps]
[baby cries]
[chattering]
Is it ready?
[dog whimpers]
[speaking Portuguese]
[TV audience laughs]
[in English] Eddie. That's a great punch.
[speaking Portuguese]
[muttering in Portuguese]
[in Portuguese]
[dog whimpers]
[chattering]
[trainer, in Portuguese]
[in English] Uh, fear no good. So emotion…
-Mm-hmm.
-…control.
[breathing sharply]
[in Portuguese]
[speaking Portuguese]
[in English] Breathe, breathe.
-[grunts]
-[heart rate beeping on watch]
[breathing sharply]
[in Portuguese]
[inhales]
[beeping speeds up]
[in English] Breathing.
[beeping slows]
-[cars honking]
-[chattering]
[chattering]
[buzzer sounds]
-[machinery rumbling]
-[bottles rattling]
[speaks indistinctly]
[in Portuguese]
Okay.
I can make it work for a while,
but you need, um…
[both speaking Portuguese]
[both chuckle]
[in English] Okay. Okay.
[in Portuguese]
[winces]
[in English] No, no, no.
Shut that off. Turn it off!
Watch out!
[both shouting in Portuguese]
[buzzer sounds]
Okay.
[speaks Portuguese]
[alarm blares]
[worker] Oy-oy-oy-oy-oy.
[speaking Portuguese]
[in English] Martina.
[in Portuguese]
[speaking Portuguese]
-Huh?
-[in English] No, wait.
-Oh, that's not right.
-[shouting in Portuguese]
[chattering]
[both speaking Portuguese]
[in English] Shit.
[speaking Portuguese]
[in English] Oh. Oh, you.
[shouts in Portuguese]
[in English] You see that? You see that?
Our ticket out of here.
[typing]
[yawns]
[slide cracks]
No.
[groans softly] Damn it.
[typing]
[both speaking Portuguese]
-[horns honking]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
[Sparr] Here's something a bit more
interesting. It's possible gamma sickness:
Milwaukee.
A man drank one of those guarana sodas.
Guess it had a little more kick
than he was looking for.
Wow.
-Where was it bottled?
-Porto Verde, Brazil.
Get our agency people looking
for a white man at that bottling plant.
Tell them no contact.
If he even sees them, he's gone.
I got you what I could.
Short notice, but they're all quality.
And I pulled you an ace.
Emil Blonsky.
Born in Russia, raised in England,
and on loan to SOCOM
from the Royal Marines.
[Ross] I know you cashed in
some chips for this, Joe.
Glad I could help.
Just make it good.
[thunderclap]
[Sparr]
This is the target and the location.
Snatch and grab, live capture.
You'll have your dart clips
and suppression ordnance,
but live fire is for backup only.
We got local out there,
but we want it tight and quiet.
Is he a fighter?
Your target is a fugitive
from the US government.
He stole military secrets.
He is also implicated in the deaths
of two scientists, a military officer,
an Idaho state trooper,
and possibly two Canadian hunters,
so don't wait to see if he's a fighter.
Trank him and bring him back.
[rattling]
[computer chirps]
Oh, come on.
[chattering]
[instruments beeping]
[dog barking]
-[thud]
-[dog yelps]
[whimpers]
[baby crying]
[device beeping]
Gentlemen.
[rapid beeping]
-Got him.
-Here we go.
[growls]
Get rid of the damn dog.
-Take him.
-[beeps]
[barking]
Target's on the move.
[dog yelps]
-[speaking Portuguese]
-Hey. Shh, shh, shh.
[in English] Where is he?
Shh, shh. Shh, shh.
[chattering]
He's on the ground.
Let's go. Go.
Move, move.
[in Portuguese]
[horn honks]
Go. Go! Go!
Go! Go!
[shouting in Portuguese]
[Blonsky] Stay on him!
Do not lose him.
[players shouting, laughing]
[panting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[grunts]
Oh! No!
[heart rate beeping on watch]
[beeping speeds up]
[panting]
[breathing sharply]
[exhales]
[beeping slows]
[crowd clamoring]
[brakes squeak]
Get around behind him!
Target moving past Mobile Unit 090.
-Oh, no.
-[speaking Portuguese]
You gotta be kidding me.
[shouts]
[shouts in Portuguese]
[watch beeping]
-[speaking Portuguese]
-[clattering]
-[Ross on radio] Where is he?
-Target acquired.
[watch beeping rapidly]
-[panting]
-[heartbeat thumping]
[heartbeat slows]
[gang leader] Gringo…
[speaking Portuguese]
[in English] Let's go.
Hey. [speaking Portuguese]
-Gringo…
-[speaks Portuguese]
[grunting]
[in English] Please, no.
My computer.
Give me that. No. [grunting]
[in Portuguese]
[in English] You very angry, G?
I very, very angry.
-[laughs]
-[beeping speeds up]
[Bruce, in English] Oh, no.
You don't understand. Something really bad
is about to happen here.
[in Portuguese]
[beeping intensifies]
[gang leader cackles]
[gasps]
[beeping continues]
[Bruce groaning]
Anybody else seeing this?
[speaking Portuguese]
-[Hulk growls]
-[shrieks]
-[Hulk roars]
-[screaming]
[grunts]
[roaring]
[groaning]
[yells]
[commando] We got a bogey of some kind.
Please advise.
That is the target!
Use every trank you've got.
Do it now!
[growls softly]
Go wide! Go wide!
Go wide! Move!
Go!
No.
[gunfire]
[growling]
[Hulk growls]
[alarms blaring]
[commando] Behind him. Get behind him.
Move! Move!
[Hulk roaring]
Get him!
Get him! Get him!
[Hulk grunts]
[metal creaking]
[Hulk] Leave me alone.
[Hulk roars]
[grunts]
[growling]
[grunting]
[roars]
No! No!
[Hulk roars]
I knew something was different
before I got the shot off.
Had it on him when he bolted.
[computer beeps]
Is that a girlfriend? She helps him maybe?
She is no longer a factor.
We closed that door to him
a long time ago. He's alone.
He wants to be alone.
Let's see if he's been talking to anybody.
Forgive me, sir.
Doesn't anybody wanna talk about
what went down in there? 'Cause…
he didn't lose us.
And he was not alone, sir.
We had him, and then something hit us.
Something…
Something big hit us.
It threw a-- a forklift truck
like it was a softball!
It was the most powerful thing
I've ever seen.
Well, it's gone.
Well, if Banner knows what it is,
I'm gonna track him down,
I'm gonna put my foot on his throat and--
That was Banner.
"It"…
was Banner.
You have to explain that statement, sir.
No, I don't.
Now, you've done a good job.
Pack up and get our men on the plane.
We're going home.
[groans]
[thunder rumbles]
[vehicle approaching]
Hey.
[in Portuguese]
[in Spanish]
[in English] What? Where-- Uh…
[Bruce]
[Blonsky] I've run into bad situations
on crap missions before.
I've seen good men go down purely
because someone didn't let us know
what we were walking into.
I've moved on to the next one,
because that's what we do, right?
I mean, that's the job.
But this…
This is a whole new level of weird.
I don't feel inclined
to step away from it.
So if you're taking
another crack at him, I want in.
And with respect,
you should be looking for a team
that's prepped and ready to fight,
because if that thing shows up again…
you're gonna have a lot of professional
tough guys pissing in their pants…
sir.
[chattering in Spanish]
-[chickens clucking]
-[dog barking]
[coins jingle]
[speaking Spanish]
Uh…
[both speaking Spanish]
[in English] Oh, yeah.
Perfecto.
[motorcycle passes by]
[gasps]
Let me emphasize that what
I'm about to share with you
is tremendously sensitive
both to me personally and the army.
You're aware that we've got
an infantry weapons development program.
Well, in WWII, they initiated a subprogram
for biotech force enhancement.
Yeah, a super soldier.
Yes.
An oversimplification, but yes.
And I dusted it off.
Got them doing serious work again.
Bold work.
Across the hall,
they were trying to arm you better.
We were trying to make you better.
Banner's work was very early phase.
It wasn't even weapons application.
He thought he was working
on radiation resistance.
I would never have told him
what the project really was.
But he was so sure of what he was onto,
that he tested it on himself.
And something went very wrong.
Or it went very right.
As far as I'm concerned,
that man's whole body
is property of the US Army.
You said he wasn't working
on weapons, right?
-No.
-But you were. Weren't you?
You were trying other things.
One serum we developed,
it was very promising.
-So why did he run?
-He's a scientist.
He is not one of us.
Blonsky, how old are you, 45?
Thirty-nine.
It takes a toll, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
So get out of the trenches.
You should be a colonel by now,
with your record.
No, I'm a fighter.
I'll be one for as long as I can.
You know, if I could take what I know now,
put it in the body I had ten years ago,
that would be someone
I wouldn't wanna fight.
I could probably arrange
something like that.
[metal detector beeping]
[chattering]
[inaudible dialogue]
[door opens, bell jingles]
Take care, kids.
Stan, I give you my word.
Whatever you've heard about me,
it's not true.
Oh, I know it. I always knew it.
I mean, you know how I felt about you two.
Have you talked to her?
No. She doesn't know that I'm here.
She's with somebody?
He's a-- He's a head shrink.
They say he's one of the best.
But a really nice guy.
-Oh.
Good. That's good.
Bruce.
What can I do to help you?
I could use a bed for a few nights.
Well, you can have
the spare room upstairs.
That'd be so great.
There is, um-- There is one other thing.
[bicycle bell rings]
Excuse me. Pardon me.
[bell rings]
Coming through.
[clears throat]
Hey, pal. I got a delivery on 5.
I don't think there's anybody up there.
Oh, man. I'm gonna catch hell
if I don't collect.
You gotta let me try.
I tell you what. I got an extra medium.
Take it on the house.
You are the man.
God bless you, partner.
[beeps]
Oh, boy.
[computers beeping]
[Hulk roars]
Okay.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
We're pretty well closed here,
folks. I'm sorry.
Oh, come on, Stan. It's Friday night.
Oh. Kids.
I got nothing but marinara now.
Oh, I gotta have a Mr. Pink, please.
She worked through dinner again,
of course.
Ah…
[chattering nearby]
Stan?
[laughs] And he-- I go,
"So, yes, I mean, where were you?
I can't-- I don't know
where you were, Cecil."
And he goes, "Not where you've been at."
I thought, "Oh, my God."
I just felt so awful.
You know, I ended up spending, like…
[continues, indistinct]
[thunder rumbling]
Bruce.
[Leonard] Betty?
What's going on?
[door closes]
Betty.
Just tell me if I saw what I think I saw.
I don't know what to say.
Please. Just tell me the truth.
[rumbling continues]
[breathing heavily]
Oh, God. Thank God.
Oh.
I want you to come with me now.
Please. Come with me.
Please.
[Betty] It's our data.
I got in there
before they carted it all away.
Hoped somewhere that it might
tell us something someday.
[thunder rumbling]
Does the general know that you have this?
No. I don't think so. I--
I haven't spoken to him
in a couple of years.
-You have to be sure.
-Bruce.
I don't understand why we can't
just go in there together and talk to him.
He told me what he wanted to do.
He wants it out of me.
He wants to dissect it
so that he can replicate it.
He wants to make it a weapon.
[beeping]
[lock clicks]
[thunder rumbling]
[footsteps approaching]
-Hi.
I, um, thought you might wanna…
Thanks.
Listen, um… I should leave early.
As early as I can.
Really? You can't stay at all?
I want to, but it's just not safe
for me to be here.
If I could borrow some cash…
-Of course.
-I need to take a bus.
Well, at least let me
walk you to the station.
Okay.
-You have everything you need?
-Yeah.
-Good night.
I hope you get some rest.
[rain pattering]
We're giving you a very low dose only.
Need you sharp out there and disciplined.
First sign of any side effect,
we stop, and you're off team
until you straighten out.
-Agreed?
-Agreed.
You'll get two separate infusions.
One into the deep muscle,
one into the bone-marrow centers.
The bone ones are gonna hurt.
[grunts]
-[bone cracks]
-[gasps]
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight…
[chattering]
Is everything okay?
I think so.
-[bell tolling]
-[thunder rumbling]
-Come here.
-What?
[chuckles]
-I just wanna do this.
-Oh.
-It's better like that.
-Yeah.
-It's too tight, huh?
-Yeah, a little.
Okay.
[Betty] What?
They're here.
Betty. Look at me, look at me.
You have to go as far away
from me as you can.
Don't argue with me. Just go. Go!
[car alarm wailing]
Damn it. We'd have had snipers on target
in three more minutes.
I wanna know who jumped the gun.
He's heading 2-7-0.
[commando] Move it.
[tires squealing]
Blonsky, not yet.
Sir.
Look alive. This could get interesting.
[panting]
[soldier] Stop!
[breathing heavily]
[soldiers shouting]
[panting]
I got him!
[Betty] Stop!
Stop!
I know you're in there.
General, please.
Sir.
Dad!
Dad, please don't do this.
You can't see this clearly.
-Now, get inside.
-There he is.
[soldier on radio] Target is
in the overpass. We have a visual.
Do not engage. Repeat, do not engage.
[doors slam]
[soldier] He's locked in.
Put two canisters in there with him.
Fire!
-[gasps]
-Get her back here.
[grunts]
[both grunt]
[shouts]
[grunting]
[growling]
[roars]
Now she'll see.
[growling]
[roars]
Alpha Team.
Let him have all of it.
[grunting]
Light him up. Come on, light him up.
Where are the .50 cals? Move your asses!
[automatic gunfire]
[grunts]
[soldier 1] Fall back!
Oh, my God.
[shouting]
-Blonsky, now you're up.
-Yes, sir.
Cover me.
[growls]
Remember me?
My God, he's doing it.
Move him toward the cannons!
-Move!
-Hold your positions!
-[Blonsky] Do it now!
[high-pitched hum]
[Blonsky grunts]
[growling]
[groans]
Please. Please. Please, no. Please.
-Get her back.
-You're killing him! Stop! Get off of me!
[growling]
[Betty, distorted] No!
No!
Where's the gunship?
[growls]
Is that it?
Blonsky, pull back now.
Pull back.
Is that all you got?
[growls]
[gasps]
-Fall back.
-[soldier 1] Fall back!
-Let's go, let's go.
-[Ross] Find cover.
-[soldier 2] Move back. Get down.
-[soldier 3] Move it!
Betty!
[soldiers shouting]
[growling]
Fire, goddamn it!
Bruce.
[helicopter approaching]
[instruments whirring, beeping]
[Betty screams]
Stop firing!
[Betty shouts]
No!
[growls]
You did the right thing, calling us.
I need to know where they're going.
She'll be in incredible danger
as long as she's with him.
From who?
He protected her. You almost killed her.
I give you my word. Her safety is
my main concern at this point.
You know, it's a point
of professional pride with me
that I can always tell
when somebody's lying.
And you are.
I don't know where he's going.
I know she'll help him if she can.
Then she's aiding a fugitive.
And I can't help either one of them.
I used to wonder why
she never talked about you.
Now I know.
[engine starts]
[Ross] Where does she meet these guys?
[siren chirps]
[growling softly]
-No!
-[growls]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Bruce?
[growling]
[roars]
It's okay. It's okay.
[grunts]
Come here. Come this way.
Watch your head.
[grunts softly]
[sighs]
We're okay.
[grunts softly]
It's okay.
It's just the rain.
[sighs]
Will he ever walk again?
Most of the bones in his body
look like crushed gravel right now.
I will say this for him.
-He's got a heart like a machine.
-[gasps]
Never seen anything like it
outside of a racehorse.
[ventilator whirring]
[birds twittering]
Here.
Okay.
[pipes humming, rattling]
[automatic gunfire]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[retching]
[spitting]
Bruce?
Oh, hi.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, actually, I feel a lot better.
-Oh, good.
-I just, um--
I just had to get my data back.
-You ate it?
-Well, you know,
the circumstances called
for a little improvisation. [chuckles]
Wow.
Okay, so they didn't have
a great selection,
but I got you a few options.
First things first.
-[Bruce] Oh, you're kidding me.
-[chuckles]
Um…
What?
-No.
-They were the stretchiest pair they had.
I'll take my chances.
[reporter on TV] Rumors continue to swirl
about a violent clash between forces
of the US military
and an unknown adversary
on the campus of Culver University
earlier today.
Sophomores Jack McGee and Jim Wilson
witnessed some of the battle.
[Jim] It was-- It was so big.
-It was like this huge, like, hulk.
-Yeah.
[reporter] McGee, who happens to be
a reporter for the campus paper
captured this on his cell phone.
Further search for the mysterious hulk
was postponed by powerful thunderstorms
in the Smoky Mountain National Forest.
[dogs barking in distance]
Not too short back there, okay?
[chuckles]
I have done this before, you know.
I don't know how you've done this
on your own for all this time.
-Hmm, with clippers, usually.
-[chuckles]
Mmm.
[moaning softly]
[heart rate beeping on watch]
[Bruce groans]
[beeping speeds up]
-Wait. Wait, wait.
-What?
-Wait.
-We-- We can't do this.
-It's okay. I want to.
No. No.
-I can't.
-[beeping slows]
I can't get too excited.
[beeping stops]
Not even a little excited?
[sighs]
[Betty] It's okay.
Sir. It's Blonsky.
Has anyone found out
if he has next of kin or family?
Ask him yourself.
Sir.
Good to see you
back on your feet, soldier.
Thank you, sir.
How do you feel?
Pissed off and ready for round three.
Basically, we can't use any of this,
'cause they can track all of it.
Well, my lip gloss, can they track that?
No. You can take your lip gloss.
Thank you. Well, I need my glasses.
[Bruce] Well, you can take
your glasses and your watch, okay?
We can use most of it. We just can't use
the credit cards, the ID or the phone.
-Don't even turn that on.
-Okay.
And we'll take the cash, obviously.
How are we gonna get where we need to go
on $40 and no credit cards?
Well, we could sell this.
No. No, that's the only thing
you have left from her. No.
Well, we'll have to try and get it back.
Federal is already monitoring phones,
plastic, and Dr. Ross's web account.
And local PD have been placed on alert.
They'll pop up somewhere.
And when they do, it comes straight to us.
They're not gonna just pop up.
He made it five years and got across
borders without making any mistakes.
He's not gonna use a damn credit card now.
If he was trying to escape,
he'd be long gone.
He's not trying to escape this time.
He's looking for help.
And that's how we're gonna get him.
We know what they're after.
And we know he's been talking to somebody.
You'll have copies of the correspondence.
And the aliases Mr. Green and Mr. Blue
have been added
to the S.H.I.E.L.D. operations database.
If he comes up for air, we'll be waiting.
If he makes a peep, we'll hear him.
And when he slips up, we'll be ready.
[chattering]
[beeping]
-Hey.
-[truck door closes]
Smile.
What is it like?
[sighs]
When it happens, what do you experience?
Do you remember those experiments
we volunteered for at Harvard?
Those induced hallucinations?
It's a lot like that,
just a thousand times amplified.
It's like someone's poured
a liter of acid into my brain.
Do you remember anything?
Just fragments, images.
There's too much noise.
I can never derive anything out of it.
But then it's still you inside it.
No. No, it's not.
I don't know. In the cave,
I really felt like it knew me.
Maybe your mind is in there.
It's just overcharged
and can't process what's happening.
I don't wanna control it.
I wanna get rid of it.
-You ready?
-Let's even the playing field a little.
Gentlemen?
-[car horn blares]
-[Betty] Bruce, wake up.
-There's something going on.
-[horns honking]
[chattering]
We gotta go. Walk toward the back.
Just don't move too fast.
All right. Come on.
-[horns honking]
-Taxi!
[Betty] It is a long way uptown.
I think the subway's probably quickest.
Me in a metal tube, deep underground,
with hundreds of people,
in the most aggressive city in the world?
Right. Let's get a cab.
-[driver] Come on, now. Let's go!
-[hip-hop blaring on radio]
You're too slow. You drive like a woman.
-[horns honking]
-[tires squealing]
-Very nice. You see her?
-Oh, my God.
She's very pretty. Yeah!
Look out, you goat.
-[watch beeping rapidly]
-Breathe, breathe, breathe.
[tires screech]
[screams] Are you out of your mind?
What is wrong with you?
What's the matter, baby?
You don't like a good ride?
Ugh!
-[tires squealing]
-Asshole!
-[beeping slows]
-[groans]
You know, I know a few techniques
that could help you manage
-that anger very effectively--
-You, zip it.
-We're walking.
-Okay.
[horns honking]
-[helicopter whirring]
-[siren chirps]
[bell ringing]
-Excuse me. Dr. Sterns.
-Yes?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Elizabeth Ross.
Oh! Dr. Ross.
I have someone who'd like to meet you.
Okay.
It's Mr. Blue, isn't it?
Mr. Green?
I've gotta tell you, I-- I've been
wondering if you were even real.
And if you were, what would it look like?
A person with that much power
lurking in him…
Nothing could have surprised me more
than this unassuming man shaking my hand.
But look, we're not strolling
into the park for a picnic here.
Even if everything goes perfectly--
if we induce an episode,
if we get the dosage exactly right--
is that gonna be a lasting cure?
Or just some antidote
to suppress that specific flare-up?
Uh… [snaps]
I don't know.
What I'm saying is that,
if we overshoot this
by even the smallest integer,
we're dealing with concentrations
with extraordinary levels of toxicity so--
You mean it could kill him?
Kill him? Yeah.
[stammers] I should say so.
You should know that there's
a flip side to this too.
If we miss on the low side,
if we induce me and it fails,
this will be very dangerous for you.
[chuckles]
Look, I've always been
more curious than cautious.
And that's served me pretty well.
So, are we gonna do this?
[crackling]
[ramp whirs, shuts]
How you feeling, man?
[sighs]
Like a monster.
[machines humming, beeping]
Okay. On the table.
[straining]
These will protect you from yourself,
if you have a strong reaction.
You can tell me later
if you thought it was strong.
[machines powering down]
Okay.
-[beeping]
-Oh, come on.
-Stupid graduate students.
-[machine powers up]
-[beeps]
-Okay. You. You. You.
This will be a somewhat novel sensation.
[machine whirs, hums]
We have begun.
The dialysis machine
will mix the antidote with your blood,
except the antidote will only take hold
once we've achieved a full reaction.
-[Bruce breathes deeply]
-Just relax.
Okay. We are comprehensive.
[machine whirring]
Here you go.
All right. We set to pop?
I'd take your hands off him.
[muffled grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
Oh, my God.
[gasps] No…
[screaming]
Wait, wait. There's more. Wait.
-[growls]
-No. Hang on.
[Sterns] Wait.
Now, do it.
-Do it!
-[grunts]
[groans]
[roars, growls]
Bruce. Bruce, look at me.
Stay with me. The antidote. Now.
Sterns, do it now.
Bruce, look at me. Look in my eyes.
Please look in my eyes.
-[beeping]
-You've gotta be kidding.
[machine powers up]
[Hulk grunting]
[gasps]
[groaning]
-Bruce.
-Oh, my God.
[crackling]
Bruce? Bruce, can you hear me?
Bruce.
[gasps]
[groans]
It's okay. You're okay. You're okay.
You did it.
He's fine. It's fantastic.
[Betty] It's over.
-Hi.
-[sirens wailing]
-[helicopters whirring]
That was the most extraordinary thing
I have seen in my entire life.
Okay, you know what? Stop, please.
We need to go back and talk about
what just happened in there.
Absolutely. Okay.
The gamma pulse came from the amygdala.
-I think Dr. Ross's primer…
-Are you okay?
…lets the cells absorb
the energy temporarily and then it abates.
That's why you didn't die
of radiation sickness years ago.
Now, maybe we've neutralized
those cells permanently,
or maybe we just suppressed that event.
I'm inclined to think the latter,
but it's hard to know,
because none of our test subjects
ever survived.
-But they weren't getting the primer.
-Wait. What did you just say?
-They weren't getting the primer.
-No, no. Test subjects?
What test subjects?
Come with me.
[sirens wailing]
-[Sparr] What's the activity level?
-Snipers are covering Alpha Sector.
[Sterns over headset]
We started on rats and mice,
but it just completely fried 'em,
so we had to go bigger.
And we still don't know
which is more toxic:
the gamma or your blood.
What do you mean, my blood?
Bruce, this is all you.
You didn't send me much to work with,
so I had to concentrate it and make more.
With a little more trial and error,
there's no end to what we can do.
This is potentially Olympian.
This gamma technology
has limitless applications.
We'll unlock hundreds of cures.
We will make humans impervious to disease.
No, no. We've gotta destroy it.
Wait. What?
All of it, tonight.
We're gonna incinerate it.
Is this the whole supply?
What-- We could get the Nobel for this.
You don't understand
the power of this thing.
It is too dangerous.
It cannot be controlled.
At your discretion, shooter.
[Sterns] Yeah,
but this is Promethean fire.
-[sniper] No shot.
-[sighs]
Blonsky's going in.
[Ross] Blonsky, stand down.
My daughter's in there.
We have the antidote now.
They don't want the antidote.
They wanna make it a weapon.
[sirens wailing]
And if we let it go,
we will never get it back.
You don't have any idea
how powerful this thing is.
I hate the government
just as much as anyone.
But you're being a little paranoid,
don't you think?
[grunts]
-[shrieks]
-[helicopter whirring]
Bruce. Bruce.
[Bruce] Get out.
[screams]
Where is it? Come on, where is it?
-[shouts]
-[watch beeping]
[beeping speeds up]
Show him to me.
Blonsky!
-[sirens wailing]
-[indistinct radio chatter]
[soldier] Miss.
Take this.
If you took it from me,
I'm gonna put you in a hole
for the rest of your life.
Betty.
I will never forgive
what you've done to him.
He's a fugitive.
You made him a fugitive.
To cover your failures
and to protect your career.
Don't ever speak to me
as your daughter again.
It's only because you're my daughter
that you're not in handcuffs too.
You telling me you can make more like him?
No. Not yet. I've sorted out a few pieces,
but it's not like I can put together
the same Humpty-Dumpty,
if that's what you're asking.
He was a freak accident.
The goal is to do it better.
-So Banner's the only--
-[thud]
She's an annoying bitch.
Why are you always hitting people?
Now what possibly could I have done
to deserve such aggression?
It's not what you've done.
It's what you're gonna do.
I want what you got out of Banner.
I want that.
You look like you've got a little
something in you already, don't you?
I want more.
You've seen what he becomes, right?
I have.
And it's beautiful. Godlike.
Well, I want that.
Need that. Make me that.
I don't know what you've got
inside you already.
The mixture could be…
an abomination.
I didn't say I was unwilling.
I just need informed consent.
And you've given it.
[machines powering up]
[buzzing]
This is what I was trying to explain.
I don't know what
you've been ladling into yourself.
-[growling]
-[Sterns] But clearly it worked.
Let's assume you don't understand
a word I'm saying,
but if you'll just get back on the table
I can fix this.
[growls]
[laughing]
-[soldier 1] Shoot it!
-[soldier 2] Run!
-[snarling]
-[soldier 3] No!
[automatic gunfire]
[soldiers screaming]
[officer] Delta 4 to Leader.
They still got two of our guys.
Two of our guys,
Blonsky and the major, are still inside.
[snarling]
Come on. Move, move, move, move.
-[soldier] It's over there!
-[Abomination roars]
-What is that thing?
-Shoot it!
-[tires screeching]
-[people screaming]
Oh…
Okay. All right. You. You drive.
Let's go. Move, move.
Delta 4 to Leader.
Something big just went off down here.
General, you should hear this.
The Hulk is in the street.
I repeat, the Hulk is in the street.
That's impossible.
You get ahold of yourself, young man.
You get it together.
What is your position?
121st Street, heading north on Broadway!
Turn us around.
We're going back. Why are we going back?
Damn it, get me eyes down there!
Yes, sir.
What the hell was that?
Go, go, go!
-[Abomination growling]
-[people shouting]
-[car alarm blaring]
-[screams]
No.
[people screaming]
[growling]
One of yours?
Oh, my God. What have you done?
Fire! Fire!
[people screaming]
Do you think a rifle's gonna hurt that?
Come on!
Sweet.
Booyah.
[laughs]
-[growling]
-[car alarms blaring]
Get out of there, soldier.
Stay back!
[whimpers]
Give me a real fight.
No. No, no! No!
[soldier] Sir?
Sir?
Tell them to bring everything they've got
and head for Harlem.
[sighs]
It has to be me.
You have to take me back there.
What are you saying?
You think you can control--
No, no, not control it.
But, I don't know, maybe aim it.
And what if you can't?
We made this thing.
All of us.
Please.
-Land us near it.
-No, no. No, keep us high.
Open the back door.
Bruce. Bruce, stop.
Stop! What are you doing?
Think about this.
You don't even know if you'll change.
You don't have to do this.
Please. This is insane.
Betty, I've gotta try.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
[people scream]
Get her in here!
Come on, miss.
[growling]
There. Betty.
[people screaming]
[roars]
[soldier screams]
Hulk.
[snarls]
[both grunt]
[car alarms ringing]
[groaning]
[laughing]
Come on.
[police radio chatter]
[roars]
[spits]
Is that all you've got?
[roars]
[residents scream]
Use that thing, soldier!
Give him some help.
Which one?
Help the green one, damn it!
Which one do you think?
Cut the other one in half.
Ross. [growls]
[groans]
Keep it on him!
[both grunting]
-[alarm blaring]
-I gotta put it down.
Hang on!
[gasping]
[screams]
[groans]
[gasps]
-[Betty] Dad.
-[groaning]
Are you hurt? Let me help you.
I'm all right. Just find a way out.
[growling]
[bones crackling]
[laughs]
[snarls]
[sighs, growls]
[panting]
[both grunting]
You don't deserve this power.
Now, watch her die!
[screams]
[both snarling]
[sighs]
Look out!
[growling]
General.
Any last words?
Hulk…
smash!
[both grunting]
[roars]
[Betty] Stop!
[both panting]
[bones crack]
[roaring]
It's okay.
Betty.
[growling]
[sighs]
-[ship horn blowing]
-[seagulls squawking]
[camera beeps]
[beeps]
[heartbeat slowly increasing]
[inhales deeply]
[grunts]
[Ross] Reload.
[glass thuds]
[groans]
Reload.
[chattering]
[Tony Stark]
Hmm. The smell of stale beer and defeat.
You know, I hate to say
I told you so, General,
but that super-soldier program
was put on ice for a reason.
I've always felt that hardware
was much more reliable.
Stark.
General.
You always wear such nice suits.
Touché.
I hear you have an unusual problem.
You should talk.
You should listen.
What if I told you
we were putting a team together?
Who's "we"?
[clears throat]