What is it?
It's satellite
It wasn't just me who took it down.
Who was it?
Another Speedster.
Hi.
We Need to Talk.
Who are you?
I'm your daughter,Nora
From the future.
Anybody need a refill
Just me!
Hmm.
People call me excess.
it's a nickname you gave me when I was a kid.
and kind of stuck here now.
so
Anybody know what to do?
This is so weird.
God,I love this place.
I can't believe that's our daughter up there.
Nora shouldn't be here.
She could Marty McFly herself out of existence.
she needs to be with her parents
30 years from now
Not us,now
Nora
I need to know
My poker face is that bad.
Please.
Why you keep this from us?
I think,
I made a big big mistake.
I'm sorry.
and we can't let this get any worse.
Here we go
Now,let's do this
I don't have a suit.
Actually I have a backup.
Totally fan favorite.
The Subtitle Created By MJBN
.:MJBN:.