- Previously on The Flash
- You never come back.
- You are not stuck here,
are you?
- Bye, Cisco.
- Bye, Cynthia.
[dramatic music]
- My father's death
certificate.
- The ME who signed off on it,
he doesn't exist.
- So this death certificate...
- Is a fake.
- Who the hell are you?
- What do you want?
- For all of you
to die.
[action music]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[distant moaning]
[electricity crackles]
- [grunting]
[heavy breathing]
[electricity crackles]
- What the...
[strains]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- Damn, man.
Another fight?
[both grunting]
- Yeah.
- I'd hate to see
the other guy.
See you on the floor.
[ominous thrum]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- So you're not stuck here.
- No, I'm not.
- So they will reverse
tachyons in your system?
- Were put there
because of me.
- Are you kidding?
You know how many credit card
points I just blew just
trying to get rid of your
negative tachyons?
I just bought a brand new
spectral tachyeometer
when I could have
my Fiji get away.
Not that I have
anyone to go with, anymore.
I'm not taking you to Fiji,
Ralph.
- Why didn't you guys tell us
about this before?
- Oh, my God!
- Barry never returns?
- That's why
you came here.
To see you father,
because you
were raised without him.
- So what?
- Iris.
- So what that that article
says that you never come back.
So what if the other one says
that you vanished.
I mean, it's said other things
before, right?
We made it say other things
before.
So whatever the future brings
we are gonna deal with it
when it gets here.
And change it if we need to.
- She has a point.
If there's anything Team Flash
is good at,
it's handing the future
its own ass and then some.
- What he said.
- Well, looks like Nora's
gonna need more training
after all.
[baby cooing]
- Oh, okay.
She's hungry.
- Yeah, why don't we, uh,
all meet back at S.T.A.R. Labs,
all right?
- Wow, first you meet your
adult daughter from the future
and now this.
I mean, it's a lot.
[soft dramatic music]
- Yeah.
Well, I guess now I know why
she never wants
to leave her dad's side
and why she...
Never wants to be by mine.
- Nora will reach out
at some point.
The trick is you gotta keep
yourself busy.
- Yeah.
Thanks, Dad.
♪ ♪
- Joe!
[baby crying]
- Cecile?
Cecile, what's wrong?
- I can't hear
what she wants.
I can't hear anything.
I think I'm losing my powers.
♪ ♪
- Hey babe, uh, it's me,
just checking in, for my dad.
[footsteps approaching]
He...
- Hello there.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- I was just trying to get
Barry's new suit
into this ring.
Oh, it's...it's tiny.
- Yeah, you weren't watching
old holograms of Gypsy.
- Why would I be doing that?
- Because you miss her.
- We just had something
so special.
Shouldn't it have worked?
Of course now it's
not so special anymore
now she's just rattlin' around
inside my head.
- I'm sorry
this is so hard for you.
But it's okay that you are
still thinking about her.
- I don't think you understand,
Caitlin.
I mean, she's literally...
inside my head.
I can't vibe.
Everything I vibe
connects to her.
I put some music on,
I hear her voice singing along.
I'm painting my figurines,
I see her face
on Captains Kirk's body.
Shh...
Do you smell that?
Of course you don't.
'Cause that's her perfume
and I'm only one smelling it.
- Of course.
Your powers linked you guys
over pan-dimensional spacetime,
so it makes complete sense
that your vibes echoes
would still be...
- Connecting us to each other.
Yes, I know.
Thank you for the diagnosis.
- I'm sorry.
You don't need a doctor.
You need a friend.
- I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I'm a mess.
- Oh, perfect.
Been looking for you two.
We need to talk.
I've hit a real wall
trying to figure out
who forged this
death certificate,
so I was thinking maybe Cisco
could give this
a little bit of a...
[buzzing sound]
- Cisco is not available
right now.
Please leave a message.
- Oh, hey, Cisco, it's Ralph.
Hope you are doing well.
Just get back to me.
I need to vibe this
as soon as possible.
Bye, bye.
- Ralph, um, Cisco
can't vibe right now,
so we're just gonna have to
deal with this a little later.
- Why can't he vibe right now?
What's going on?
- Because we need
to help him get over Gypsy.
I mean, like you said,
Cisco get his vibe back,
we can crack this case.
- Please, stop caring about me.
- Ralph, I mean,
you don't have any ideas about
how to help a man get
over a heartbreak, do you?
- Oh, my God,
you stop it, girl.
You know I have plenty.
Cisco, you wanna know
why I'm perfect guy
to help you get over this and
get back into the game of love?
Because trust me, buddy,
nobody, I mean nobody,
has been kicked out of
that more than me.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[explosion]
- Hello, Bobby.
- Vanessa Jansen.
You got out of the slammer.
- Now I'm gonna loosen
up that chokehold
you and that punk-ass
brother of yours
have on all the big arms deals
in this city.
- I don't think so.
- [distant]
What the hell?
- Do you know what four years
in Iron Heights
will do to you, Bobby?
It makes you very,
very, angry.
- [distant] Vanessa,
you ain't gonna do this.
Vanessa, please.
[screams]
[bones crunching]
♪ ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
[dramatic music]
- [sighs]
Okay.
- So this is where
the Moretti brothers
have been running guns.
- Yeah.
Stealing from these guys
takes some cojones.
Any idea who our
bold thieve might be?
- Not yet.
Made my rounds too.
So far the only prints belong
to Bobby and Bruno Moretti.
- Well, whoever did this,
they're running fast and loose.
- Mm-hmm.
- If we don't stop this,
a lot of high powered weapons
are gonna flood the streets.
Central City is gonna be
a war zone.
- Don't worry about the city,
friend.
CCPD's finest are on the case.
- And you are...
- Nora, CSI intern.
Who are you?
- The captain of CCPD.
- Captain David Singh.
Oh I've read so much about you.
It's really nice to meet you.
- You hired an intern, Allen?
- I am very sorry, sir,
but I needed help with, um,
the cases that accumulated
while I was suspended
and you said
the Mayor wasn't going
to give us any money
to help solve them,
so I hired an intern
to help for free.
- Mm.
- Well, make her official
when you get back.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- I know you're
surprised to see me
but I found this badge
and this jacked and thought,
"I'm a CSI too"
so I should help my dad.
- [laughs weakly]
Right, okay.
You said you were still
a rookie, right?
- Well, yeah, but forensic
sciences in the future
is like way advance, so I can
totally handle a robbery scene.
Like, not a prob.
- Ah, got you.
That's great.
- What is that?
- That I haven't gotten to yet.
But it looks like somebody
wanted their pound of flesh.
Nora, wait.
- Wha...
- What are you doing?
You can't touch that.
You'll contaminate
the evidence.
- Sorry,
you mean you don't have
a scene-wide modified
bosonic frequency field
to avoid cross-contamination?
- I don't even think we have
some of those words yet.
- Oops.
Well...ugh.
It's just this seems
way denser than human tissue.
- Yeah, you're right,
actually.
[mysterious music]
I can't even move this thing.
This isn't a pound of flesh.
This is a whole human body.
- [laughs]
That is so schway.
- Let's hold off in telling
the Mayor about this
until we have some more info.
She's still be upset
about the Lang homicide.
- Hey, Captain,
did you mean Gridlock?
I thought he was locked up
in Iron Heights.
- Iris, it's a pleasure
to see you.
Can we secure
the crime scene, please?
You know I can't make
a comment on the record.
- Okay, well,
how about off the record?
- Just once and that's it,
and only because it's you.
- Okay.
- While in transport
to Iron Heights
the convoy was attacked.
Lang was killed
by something strong.
We think maybe a meta.
- Were there any survivors?
- Four guards,
they are still in the hospital.
So if you hear anything...
- Yeah, I got you.
- Thanks.
[suspenseful music]
- Put this away,
and, hey.
Here, put these on.
- Okay.
You do have...
- [laughs]
[soft dramatic music]
- The book of Ralph.
- Yep, and we are gonna
start with a page of Ralph
'cause he's nowhere near ready
for this whole book.
- "Ralph Dibny's 27 steps
to getting over
the love of your life."
Are you kidding me with this?
- We just want to help
you get past Gypsy.
And if this has worked
for Ralph...
- Multiple times I will add.
- Then I think
it's worth trying.
Come on, what's step one?
- Shark cage diving.
- What's step two?
- Affirmations.
- Oh.
- Okay.
[playful music]
Ralphy is kind.
Ralphy is great.
Ralphy is
a brilliant detective.
- Yeah, buddy, I mean,
I know all that.
But it works a lot better
if you use your name instead.
Cisco is creative.
Cisco is good.
Cisco is smarter
than your average bear.
That's Yogi's.
You stole Yogi's affirmation.
- Yeah, I did,
'cause it's a winner.
You don't see him moping
over any lady bears.
- Okay, you know what, Caitlin?
I changed my mind, all right?
I...I don't care
about the Gypsy vibes.
I'll just muscle through them,
let's just help you
with your thing
and just get me the hell
out of here, please?
- No, Cisco,
after Ronnie and Jay
you helped me get back past it.
Now it's my turn to help you.
Okay?
So...
We don't have time
to find ourselves in Thailand.
And we are certainly not
watching "Beaches"
while painting
each others toes.
- That's a really
important one, though.
But step twelve isn't so bad.
- Holy Kafka.
- Come on, Cisco,
change is good.
- No, no, no.
Change is pain.
- It's not as painful
as seeing you like this, buddy.
- Fine.
Whatever you say, doc.
[soft dramatic music]
- Um, Officer Matthews?
- Yes.
- Hi, I'm Iris West-Allen.
I'm reporter, and I'm doing
a story about William Lang.
- Gridlock.
- Pardon?
- You call him Gridlock.
In your blog I've read it.
It's good.
- Thanks.
Um, I understand that you
were part of the convoy
that was escorting him to Iron
Heights when you were attacked.
- Something like that.
- What do you mean?
- I mean I really don't
remember what happened.
One minute I was in my vehicle
there was a pile up,
I got out
to see what's going on.
[grunts]
Everything went black.
Finally came to and Lang's
laying there on the ground,
beaten to a pulp.
- He was beaten to death?
- Beaten, then stabbed.
- Was anyone else hurt?
- No.
Everyone else on SWAT
was concussed like me.
- So, Lang was the only target?
- Looks like it.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Thanks for your time.
- Oh, hi, sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Hey.
- I just...
I got a little too excited.
Okay, guess what?
You know my powers have
been fading in and out.
Mostly out.
Well, I am definitely
losing them.
- You weren't that excited
about that this morning.
- No.
No, I was not.
But I'm excited now
because I have a fix.
I have a fix!
Mental activity dampener 2.0.
2.0.
Harry altered it so that
you can hear the thoughts
of whoever is wearing it.
- And why would
we wanna do that?
- So we can make sure it works
before we put it on Jenna.
- Uh-uh.
- Oh, honey,
it's completely safe,
Harry used it on
his own daughter,
- It doesn't mean
we have to use it on ours.
- Oh, ok...okay.
Honey, listen.
I have had a constant
telepathic connection
to our child
since before
she was born.
It's been constant.
Babe, now when she cries
half the time I don't know why.
- Look, she's an infant.
They cry and you always
get to know why.
- No, not...me.
You don't understand.
I haven't been the mother
to a newborn in a long time.
When I got pregnant,
baby, I was so scared.
But then I got powers.
These powers that...
gave me a chance
to be a perfect parent.
The parent
that our child deserves.
And now they're going away?
[dramatic music]
I'm scared I can't live
up to that.
- I know you're struggling,
babe.
But that device...
isn't the solution.
We'll figure out, okay?
- [sighs]
But...
[baby cries]
- I got it.
- Ugh,
these old-timey computers
are even slower than the ones
in storage at the Flash Museum.
- DNA analysis used to take
a lot longer
even just ten years ago.
- So, Mom took the news
about you being gone
better than I
thought she would.
- Iris is
as though as they come.
I'm sure you know that.
[computer beeps]
Got a match.
Vanessa Jansen.
- Low level weapon dealer
affiliated with the
East Street Skulls gang.
- I ran into a couple of them
when I was in prison.
- You were in prison?
- Mm-hmm.
- That wasn't in the museum.
- The Skulls make
the Hell's Angels
look like a knitting club,
drug trafficking,
armed robbery.
- Any places Jansen's
known to frequent?
[computer beeps]
- East Street Auto Haven.
Looks like it's probably
a front for Skull's activities.
- Yes, time to take down
my first baddie!
Uh, with your permission,
of course.
[chuckles]
- Let's do it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- What is the hold up?
These you are gonna move fast.
- Well, I guess, I heard right.
You got something
you're selling.
- Too late, another interested
customer just showed up.
You're looking to buy, Bruno?
- From the broad who killed
my brother and stole our stash?
This is way out of your league,
Vanessa.
- See,
I would've agree with you...
before prison.
But then I got out
and it hit me...
I'm tougher now, Bruno.
I got connections
with people
that would pay big money
for my weapons.
- Except,
they're not your weapons.
- [distant chuckle]
Like I said...
♪ ♪
I'm tougher now.
- All right, I'm gonna take
Vanessa and the gangster.
Why don't you
just scan the perimeter
for any back up
she might have.
- I can do better than that.
- What?
Whoa, what're you...
Crap.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Sorry,
I can't let you hurt him.
Or take this.
- Didn't know I was a meta.
Don't feel bad,
it's my new look.
- Vanessa!
- The Flash!
I guess I better put
my hands up.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- How long
do you think it will...
- I think Nora is good to go.
She didn't even need
an Ibuprofen.
- You sure you feel okay?
- I'm totally okay.
Come on,
let's get back to work, Flash.
- [sighs]
Okay.
All right, well let's
figure out where Vanessa went.
If she sells those stolen
weapons to the wrong people I...
- Um, Cisco, were you able
to get the satellite
up and running?
Cisco?
[playful music]
- We weren't able
to track Vanessa,
but we did find
a scientific anomaly
that we've never seen
before, right, Cisco?
♪ ♪
- Han shot second.
- That doesn't even make sense.
Ralph, it's you.
- Sorry to lie
like that, man.
We just...we need the CCTV...
- CCTV, yes.
Vanessa Jansen's concentrated
air squares are dense
very dense, stupid dense.
The kind of dense reserved for
people who still believe...
in love.
- I think what Cisco
is trying to say
is that Vanessa can manipulate
the movement of atoms
to created concentrated
air molecules in cube form.
The space between the molecules
is so compact that...
- That there isn't enough room
for a speedster
to vibrate through them.
- What do you call someone
who can compress air molecules
into solid blocks?
- I don't know, Block.
♪ ♪
- So, I guess
Cisco is still
taking the Gypsy thing
pretty hard?
- Well, we're working on it.
But you can't expect
real progress
till you hit step 17.
- It's this thing
we're working on with Cisco.
You can do without us
for a little while, right?
- I mean, we are blind
without our satellite
so we're just
gonna have to wait
until Vanessa makes
her next move anyway.
[soft dramatic music]
What about you?
Gonna hang out here for a bit?
- Actually,
I am working on a lead.
- Huh.
- Can I use your lab?
There's something
I wanna follow up on.
- Yeah, of course.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Uh, what kind
of training is this?
- Well, speedsters need
to know about physics,
aerodynamics,
trajectory formulas.
And after your
last encounter with Jansen,
I think is time for you
to get back to basics.
- My training is math?
- Yeah.
I think chapter one is probably
a good place to start.
- Alright,
you're in for a real treat.
He initially said no,
but after I told him
that your cousin
was John Stamos.
- My cousin is not John Stamos.
- He agreed to you on.
I proudly present
my personal stylist, Bruce.
[playful music]
This guy does it all,
hair, makeup.
He picks everything I wear.
- That explains that.
- Come on.
Bruce is gonna help us
accomplish step twelve.
Metamorphosis.
- Does that mean you think
there's something wrong
with me?
- Even a Ferrari needs a
tune-up every once in a while.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- This feels like purgatory.
You cut my hair,
I cut you.
[playful music]
- [gasps]
- [exhales]
- My work here is done.
- So...
I hate it.
I hate it all.
- [sighs]
- Great, now that that's over
and done with.
Why don't we focus
on the death certificate?
- Well, I mean, we
need to vibe it.
- Or we can ask Joe to do some
good old fashion police work.
Did you ever think of that?
- Let's not worry about it,
okay?
- No, I mean,
it's a good idea.
We'll just ah...
- Let's give him a call.
- Guys, stop.
Seriously, cut it out!
Okay?
Forget about the death
certificate
and let's just focus
on helping our friend, okay?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I need a break.
- Okay, so the key with Higgs
particles isn't the math per se
but the effect they have
on the mass of other particles.
Yeah.
- Question.
How would one go about
performing a supersonic punch
on one of those particles?
- Nora.
- Dad, I'm sorry,
but I already know all of this.
My high school textbooks
had laws of physics
that this time
hasn't even discover yet.
I don't need
this kind of training
I need to learn
how to be like you.
- What do you think it means
to be like me?
- You know, running so fast
you can stop a tsunami.
Or vibrating something bigger
than a plane.
Or how about defeating
a sand demon
by throwing lighting at him.
- Nora, look,
all those things
are way behind
your current skill level.
You gotta stick to what
you can handle right now.
- Uh, just because
I'm your daughter
doesn't mean you have
to baby me.
I can handle
way more than you think.
Watch.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[groans]
- Dad!
Dad, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I've been hit
with lighting before.
[laughs]
Ow.
It's okay.
- It's not okay.
I guess
greatness isn't hereditary.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Body cam footage.
Officer Matthews.
Bingo!
- What the hell was that?
- Stay where you are.
Freeze don't move.
[thumps]
[thrumming]
- What was that?
[thrumming increases]
- [breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
- Hey, I need your help.
- That's blunt.
- Yeah, so Nora,
isn't really spending any time
with Iris.
So she's kind of with me
all the time, you know?
And I've been training
her a lot by myself
and I just don't get it.
I mean, it's like...
she keeps taking things on
that she can't handle yet.
It's like she wants
to go big for big sake
and I try to walk her back, but
it's like she's not listening
to what I'm teaching her,
you know?
It's actually that she hears
the opposite
of what I'm saying.
Why are you nodding?
Are you agreeing with me?
- Do you remember
your 4th grade science fair?
- Yeah, but what does that
have to do with this?
- All you had to do is make
a baking soda volcano.
And what did you do?
- I...
- You built a robot
with wheels,
pretty much set
the gym on fire.
- Almost got Mrs. Dumas too.
But that was different.
- How so?
- That was the first year
you took me in.
I mean, you took me
when I had no one.
I looked up to you.
I mean, you were my hero.
I...
[soft music]
♪ ♪
I really wanted to impress you.
- Bar, all the information
this girl has on you
comes from that museum.
There're literally statues
of you on pedestals.
How much do you think she
wants to impress her hero?
♪ ♪
- So what do I do?
- Well, show her
it's okay not to be perfect
coming out of the gate.
There's no shortcuts.
Takes time to get things right
and that's not a failure.
That's life.
And also show her
that no matter what
you're always gonna love her.
That's what parents do.
- Yeah.
Yeah, thanks, Joe.
- Mm.
- See you later.
♪ ♪
- Mm.
Mm.
What was that for?
- Just 'cause.
[baby crying]
Uh-uh.
I got her.
- Yeah, you do.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Ah, yes,
the sugary pastry.
I think as far as avoiding
your feelings goes,
cinnamon bun
was a solid choice.
- You look nice.
- Yeah, well, I think Bruce
burned all my clothes, so...
- Hmm.
Why don't you want
to investigate
your dad's
death certificate?
- [exhales]
Because...
if it's true...
if he has been alive
this whole time...
I just means
he didn't want to see me.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- Step 27:
Accept that she isn't
the love of your life
because if she were,
she'd still be in it.
- [laughs softly]
Pretty deep for Ralph Dibny.
- Yeah.
Granted it took him 26 swings
before he could hit the ball.
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
I don't know...
I think he might of knocked
out of the park with that one.
Gypsy isn't the one.
I know that.
And there's no amount
of new clothes or...
crazy makeover distraction
that can change that fact.
Because some truths
you can only hide for so long.
The truth is, it's too late for
me to change things with her.
But it's not too late for you.
It's not too late for you
to change things with your dad.
♪ ♪
- But what if he doesn't want
anything to do with me.
♪ ♪
- Maybe he doesn't.
but wouldn't you rather
face that truth
instead of spending the rest
of your life wondering?
♪ ♪
- Is this part of my training?
- Just watch.
- [gasps] Schway, is that you?
- Yeah.
A few weeks
after I got my powers.
- OG Flash.
God, look at you move.
- Yeah, just wait for it.
[explosion]
- [gasps]
- And this.
- [inhales]
[inhales]
- And this.
Yeah.
- Oh!
- It takes time
to hone your skills, Nora.
You can't just can't
just skip rungs on a ladder
or jump right to the big stuff.
It's not how it works.
[grunts, groans]
All right,
that's enough of that.
Look, when you first got here
you said that you weren't
a great speedster.
But obviously neither was I
when I first started.
- Um, do you think one day
I will be great like you?
- [chuckles]
You punched out a satellite
while it was falling
to the earth and on fire.
And you were moving so fast
even I couldn't
see who you were.
- Yeah, that was pretty epic.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry I didn't listen
to you today.
I just wanted to make
you proud.
[soft dramatic music]
- Sometimes for people
with our abilities
the most impressive feat
is restraint.
♪ ♪
- I want what's mine, Vanessa.
Now step aside.
- [chuckles]
Because you brought
a bigger gun this time?
Not happening.
[dramatic music]
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- I'm sure.
[gun cocking]
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys.
Any luck with Block?
- Nothing. No.
Anything at the lab?
- Uh, maybe. It's still
a little too early to tell.
- Unit 7-5-2 requesting
a 10-61.
- What is that?
- Nothing.
An officer requesting
to go on a coffee break.
Not having our satellites
is killing us.
I mean, we can't scan the city
for dark matter
we don't have
facial recognition.
All we'd need to do
is see if there any pockets
of compressed air around
the city and we'd have her.
- You mean gauging atmospheric
pressure like a barometer?
- Yeah, but it would have
to be a big barometer.
- You mean like channel 52
Doppler radar relay?
- Yeah, I mean, Vanessa's
blocks are constructed
of highly dense air, so they'd
have the same composition
as an extreme
atmospheric system.
- So, we track the weather
and we find her.
That's so schway.
- Okay, yeah.
- Let's do it, yeah.
- [exhales]
[computer beeps]
- Go Team West-Allen.
Yeah!
Okay, look, there's a
high-density low-pressure zone
in a six block radius
around Pacific and Davies.
Okay, cool.
All right, let's go.
- Hey, maybe I should
just stay here.
- Or you could put
some of that training to use.
♪ ♪
- Last chance, Vanessa.
- To do what?
- Just give me the keys
so I can drive my weapons
out of here.
Come on.
Just hand them over
nice and easy.
- [laughs]
- Yeah, right.
- Light her up!
[gunfire]
- You two.
I swear...
[grunting, straining]
- She's getting tired.
- [grunts, groans]
- We got her.
- Yeah, we did.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Gotcha.
- Uh-oh.
- Flash is trapped!
- What's wrong?
What's happening?
- Barry's in trouble.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- She gets tired.
Hey, blockhead!
Try that on me!
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[groans]
- Bit off more
than you could chew, huh?
♪ ♪
[whirring]
- Well,
my work here is done.
- Looks like she's a regular
chip off the ol' block.
Am I...
- Don't.
- Okay, yeah, I know.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Get her to a hospital.
XS! Now!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Barry?
What is it?
Who's there?
- I don't know yet.
[electricity crackles]
[electricity sputters]
I just lost my speed.
- I got nothing.
- Negative, Ghost Rider.
- Guys, I know we're
three against one, but
something tells me this guy's
got the advantage.
[action music]
- [grunts]
[blow lands]
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
[blows landing]
[grunting]
- Barry!
- [strains]
[electricity hums]
[shouts]
[breathing heavily]
- [breathes weakly]
[coughs]
- What is that sound?
- [heavy breathing]
- Oh, my God.
Barry!
Barry, you got get out
of there right now!
- [heavy breathing]
[electrical whoosh]
- Dad!
[tense music]
[heavy breathing]
[distant sirens wailing]
- [breathes weakly]
- Dad.
Dad, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
[sirens wailing]
[ominous whoosh]
- I mean, this is
definitely dark matter,
but these levels
of concentration are unlike
like any dark matter levels
I've ever seen before.
- Yeah, well, that wasn't quite
like any ass kicking
I've ever gotten before either.
- That dagger he had,
I think that
negated our powers.
And he control it too,
like Mjolnir.
That's Thor's hammer.
- I'm just glad
you guys are okay.
This could've been a lot worse.
- Yeah. [grunts]
- Careful.
Those cuts are pretty deep.
It could take a while
for them to heal.
[soft dramatic music]
[sighs] Cisco,
that's not important right now.
♪ ♪
- Look, if you wanna know,
this is your chance.
- I support you
either way, Caitlin.
[intense electrical whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
- [grunts]
[breathing heavily]
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened.
- Caitlin,
did you see something?
- Yeah, I did.
My mother.
- Hey, guys.
- Let's go.
[uneasy music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, we got a big problem.
- So I talked to Captain Singh
and he said that Gridlock
was killed during his transport
to Iron Heights.
- Gridlock's dead?
- How?
- I'm not sure.
I interviewed everyone
that was there
and no one knows.
But I did some digging...
[computer beeping]
- What the hell is that?
- Stay where you are!
Freeze! Don't move!
[gunfire]
- Okay, so what are we
looking for here?
- Not looking.
Listening.
- [heavy breathing]
- It sounds like the guy
who just attacked us.
- [heavy breathing]
- Sounds like an insect.
- Yeah, it does.
Like a...
- Like a cicada.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Who's Cicada?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.