- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Next time you decide
to release my friend's
inner ice demon,
you do it sometime in July.
- I was trying to save
her life, Cisco.
- When I became Killer Frost,
Savitar appeared to me
and showed me the way.
- If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar
and save you are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
You trapped Savitar
in the Speed Force.
Just tell me how you did it.
- I had help.
- Help from who?
- A physicist.
Her name's Tracy Brand.
[thunder booming,
electrical zapping]
[ominous suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I know who you are.
[soft dramatic music]
- [exhales]
- Whew!
Cecile?
- [giggles]
- Most people quit...
their New Year's resolutions
by now.
- Uh-uh. Central City Marathon
is in two months,
and I gotta shave...ooh!
I still got half a minute
I gotta take off my time.
You?
- A lot more than 30 seconds.
Look, I am going
to wait for you...
at the end of the marathon.
- No, you're not pulling out
of this thing.
- I am not as easy
with running
as some other members
of my family.
- Mm, I'm gonna let it slide.
I'm gonna let it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Are you getting mad?
[both laugh]
- I would never get mad.
I love you too much to be mad.
Uh, um...
that, uh...I, uh...
I didn't really mean to...
- No, absolutely...
[cell phone buzzes]
- I was looking at you,
and then it just came out,
and I didn't want you
to feel uncomfortable or...
- I'm sorry. Hold on.
Sorry. I gotta take this.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go for it.
- Yeah? Okay.
I'm on my way.
Yeah.
All right, sorry.
I gotta head out.
♪ ♪
- Her name is Tracy Brand.
She's one of the world's top
theoretical physicists...
you know,
or at least she will be.
- No kidding. Girl Scout
earns her merit badges.
2021 Nobel Prize,
Copley Medal,
presidential commendation.
- She's a genius,
but what's that to us?
- She's the key
to stopping Savitar.
Future me said
that four years from now,
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar
in the Speed Force.
- Four years too late.
- Yeah, but if she invents
the tech then, then maybe she's
working on the prototype now.
- That's exactly right,
so we should find her.
- Agreed.
- Sorry.
Why are we not looking
for Caitlin again?
- Easy, Romeo and Juliet.
None of us have forgotten
about Caitlin.
- Right, but future Flash
already confirmed
that she teams up with Savitar.
We should be doing everything
in our power
to stop that from happening.
both: We know.
- Right, so what is Wally doing
swanning off to Earth-3
to be with his girlfriend?
He could be here right now
looking for her.
It's like no one's doing
a thing.
- No one's doing a thing?
Barry and Wally searched
the city half a dozen times.
No one's doing a thing?
Every chance I get,
I try to vibe where she is.
We're using facial recognition
technology.
We're using the meta-human app,
the satellite.
We're doing everything we can.
- I just want her back, okay?
- Yeah, well,
if you wanted her here so badly,
maybe you shouldn't have
ripped off that necklace
and turned her into a killer.
- Okay, okay.
All right.
- Just saying.
[computer chimes]
We got a hit.
Tracy Brand,
currently enrolled in CCU's
Theoretical Physics program.
- So our hopes of defeating
an evil speed god
hinge on a grad student?
- Yup.
- Could be worse.
B.A., Cisco, let's do this.
- Let's go.
♪ ♪
- Ahh, the soul-sucking
fluorescence of academia.
- Yeah, this is
exciting, though.
It's like meeting Norbert
before he was Einstein.
- Albert.
- Norbert Albert?
- Do you guys smell that?
- [sniffs] Toast?
[gas hissing]
- Holy...
[dramatic music]
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
- You mean save you
from a painful, fiery death?
- I had it under control.
[torch clicks on]
- Aah!
- Come on!
- Okay! You know what?
Let's put this down
while you still have
your eyebrows.
- Did you set the fire
on purpose?
- Yes, I'm burning
everything.
- W...ev...
- What?
- Everything? What...
- My work.
Well, I don't know why
they call it "work,"
because none of it works.
- This isn't exactly
what I expected.
- Me neither.
- Um, Dr. Brand?
- Oh, no.
Just Tracy.
I failed my dissertation.
Nothing like ten years
down the drain
and a pile of debt as a legacy.
- Tracy, uh, w-w-we were
just hoping
that you'd have a moment
to talk.
- Oh, no.
My bus leaves in five minutes.
Oh, please tell me I didn't
burn my bus ticket.
- Uh...
- Yeah, that's hot.
Your bus?
Where...where are you going?
- Big Belly Burger.
I hear they're hiring.
- [laughs]
What? You're seri...
Well, what about
all your research?
- Oh...[chuckles]
You mean
my "unsubstantiated
and transactional" inquiry
into the
"purely suppositional" nature
of extra-dimensional energy?
both: Yes?
- Yeah?
- A waste of time,
or, as Dr. Hersh puts it,
"A total misapplication
of the university's resources."
I might as well
start practicing,
"Do you want fries with that?"
- Yes.
- No.
- B.A.
- Stop.
- Look, don't let the naysayers
get you down.
Your doubts,
they're traitors.
Don't believe them.
Your mind is too fine to waste
turning tubers
into finger chips.
- Finger...chips?
- Finger chips.
There's, like, a...
- He's from out of town.
- Stop.
Look, look, look.
You can't give up.
Your work on relativistic
quantum mechanics
and its application
to interspatial theory
to manipulate matter
on a subatomic level,
it's groundbreaking.
- I haven't shared
that hypothesis with anyone,
other than my therapist.
Who are you?
- We're therapists.
- Yeah.
[ice crackling]
[tense music]
[glass shatters]
- Admission here is so easy.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Get her out of here.
Go.
[grunts]
[groans]
- So...
you've gone full-on
Killer Frost, huh?
New threads and everything.
- No more pencil skirts for me.
- I don't want to hurt you.
- You won't.
But I will hurt her.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[glass shatters]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
[fire whooshes]
- Cisco! Hey!
Hey, you good?
- Yeah.
That's gonna leave a mark.
- Come on, come on.
- [groans]
♪ ♪
Caitlin's after Tracy.
- Yeah.
- That means she's working
with Savitar.
[soft dramatic music]
- That's definitely her,
Detective.
Icy eyes and all.
- [sighs]
Yup, that's her.
♪ ♪
- So I'm gonna
spread this around
so everyone knows
to look for her.
Uh, can you give me one second?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, so if Caitlin
wants Tracy dead,
I guess what you saw
in the future was true
and she's teamed up
with Savitar.
- I just didn't think
it was gonna happen this soon.
- It certainly makes things
more complicated.
- Makes what more complicated?
- Uh...
t-there was a meta attack
at CCU,
and we just
don't have much
to go off of.
- Really?
It's a college campus.
Isn't there video footage?
- Uh, no.
It got...erased.
- Uh, well, I'm sure you two
will figure it out.
Joe, can I, um...
- Yeah.
[sighs]
So I'm feeling weird
about this morning.
- Uh...
- Look, when I told you
that I loved you, I-I didn't
mean to make you feel pressured.
- No, no, no, no,
I-I didn't feel pressured.
- Okay.
So...we're good?
- We're great.
- Great. Okay.
Um, in that case, uh...
good luck with your meta.
♪ ♪
- Um, so I totally heard that.
Do you want to talk?
- No.
Hey, where are you going?
- Oh, uh, nearest bus stop.
- Uh, no, you should stay here,
um, with Detective West
for a little bit.
- Why? That sketch artist
was like freaking Michelangelo.
I mean, you've got your woman.
- Not yet.
And until we do, you could be
in a lot of danger.
- You really think Jack Frost's
sister wants to kill me?
I'm no one.
- In my experience,
if she's come after you once,
she's likely to do it again.
- Look, this whole
witness overprotection thing
is totally unnecessary.
It was just a random attack.
[cell phone chimes]
Oh! The bus is coming.
I gotta go.
- We need to keep
an eye on her.
- Yeah, we do.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- She got away.
- I told you
exactly where she'd be.
- Barry and Cisco were there
when I arrived.
- As I told you
they would be.
Maybe there's more
Caitlin Snow inside you
than you led me to believe.
- Are you saying I let her go
on purpose?
- Did you?
You call yourself Killer Frost,
but you haven't actually
killed anyone yet.
You and I can both be gods,
free of the pain and suffering
of man.
All you have to do...
is kill the girl.
[tense music]
- Okay. [groans]
Look, I might not have any cash.
But I have one of those, um,
Jitters cards
that has ten stamps on it,
which means you owe me
a free drink.
Okay?
- Allowmoi to help out
a damsel in distress.
I will pay for myself
and the lady.
I will have a triple-shot,
no-whip mocha Flash,
and anything
this young lady desires.
- Yeah, I, um...I need
to calm down, so a Zoom.
- A Zoom?
- Mm-hmm.
- Never heard of it.
- Oh, it's on the secret menu.
- Secret menu?
- Triple espresso
with a shot of cayenne.
[clicks tongue and whistles]
- Marry me.
- Hey, wait. You were
at the college this morning.
- No...oh, this morning?
Oh, yeah.
No, I remember you now.
Yes, I was.
H.R.
- Wait, what is it
with you people?
Did the CCPD send you
to find me?
- No, no, no, no.
The reason I'm here is...
my team and I
are very interested
in your research.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You're interested
in my theories
on quantum mechanics?
- Your ideas
of wave-particle duality,
your quantization of energy,
and your time-symmetric
formulation
of quantum theory and...
- How the boundary conditions
lead to principle causality
and the psychological arrow
of time.
- And the psychological arrow
- You really know your stuff.
- Well,je suis...
smart.
- Lay off the French, and
lay off the improv too, please.
Just keep her talking.
- Ah.
Thank you, Mischa.
Please.
The Zoom.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Let's zoom.
- Mate, was it just me,
or did it sound like H.R.
was trying to flirt?
- Hmm.
Didn't notice.
- Listen, the, uh,
security footage today from CCU,
the stuff that we wiped
to protect Caitlin's identity?
I-I saw it.
As in, I-I saw the two of you
squaring off.
- Okay.
- Well, from the angle
that I saw,
it looked like you had
a pretty clear shot.
- Okay.
- You had a clear shot, Cisco,
and you didn't take it.
Why?
- Julian, I'm trying to focus
on what we're here to focus on.
I suggest you do the same.
[dramatic music]
Gents, how we doing?
- Uh, all good.
- I don't know
about this one, Bar.
H.R. isn't exactly
our best closer.
- Ah, he'll be fine.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Just...
- Cecile?
- [sighs]
She's just...
she caught me off guard.
- Mm-hmm?
- Just didn't think
we were there yet.
- Well, obviously she is.
Are you?
- I-I care for her a lot.
It's just with everything
going on with Iris and Savitar
and now Caitlin,
I just feel like I...
lie to Cecile all the time.
- Then maybe you should stop.
You're gonna have
to tell her about Wally
and me and all this
at some point, right?
So why not now?
Well, just so you know,
you don't have
to keep her
in the dark for us.
If you love her,
you should be honest with her.
At least that's what
you'd tell me to do.
♪ ♪
- Okay, so...
- Mm-hmm?
- Here's the thing that I could
never get them to understand
at the university.
See...
I've been studying speedsters.
- Oh.
- And so you know how,
when they run,
they generate a trail
of lightning behind them?
- Light...lightning.
- I don't think all of that
is generated by them running.
I think...
- No?
- Some of it comes
from somewhere.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, it's some sort of a...
like a...hmm.
- Speed Force?
[suspenseful music]
- Yeah.
Wait.
That is a great term for it.
- [chuckles] Well...
- Speed Force.
- [stammers] Thanks.
- Anyway, so I've been doing
some calculations.
- Mm-hmm?
- I think there might be a way
to manipulate it.
- Mm-hmm?
- Maybe even...control it.
- Maybe even turn it
into a prison.
- Maybe.
Um, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah. [chuckles]
- I mean...
- Just a random thought.
How do you think one
would accomplish that?
- See, I don't know...
- Okay.
- Because the university
wouldn't fund my research.
- Ahh, mm-hmm.
- Why are you so interested
in this?
Because everybody thinks
I'm a crackpot.
[gentle music]
- I certainly don't think
you're a crackpot.
♪ ♪
[ice crackling]
I...
- What's wrong?
[dramatic music]
- We should go.
- Wait. What?
- I think we should go.
Yup.
Guys, guys,
we need a little help here!
We got a little trouble here!
[ice whooshes]
[dramatic music]
- Hey.
- Flash?
♪ ♪
- Where is she?
- Right here!
♪ ♪
- Her again?
- Caitlin! Caitlin, stop!
- Get her out of here!
- What? What?
What did I ever do to you?
♪ ♪
- So what?
You're Savitar's lackey now?
- More fun to reign in hell
and all that.
♪ ♪
- All right, I'm gonna get her
to head back this way.
When she does,
you gotta knock her out, okay?
Okay?
- Yeah.
[whoosh]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Now, Cisco!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[grunting and groaning]
[ice dagger scraping on metal]
- Savitar says
I'm not allowed to kill you,
but I can't have you
following me around.
It was the left leg
last time, right?
- What?
[screams]
- Scar tissue's a lot more
sensitive than regular tissue.
- [grunting]
This isn't you!
- It is now.
- Cait! Cait!
[yells]
♪ ♪
- This is where the Flashy Flash
goes down?
It's not exactly what
I imagined, but it's cool.
So I always wondered
how you kept the friction
from building up a lethal dose
of static charge.
- Yeah, that's vulcanized
Teflon.
It neutralizes
any electron imbalance.
- Okay, and the...
the White Witch?
I'm guessing you know
why she's after me.
- Well, she's teamed up
with an evil speedster
from the future,
and apparently you developed
the technology to trap him
for an eternity, so...
- You can't be serious.
- Totally serious.
- An evil speedster?
- He calls himself Savitar.
- Savitar?
And he's from the future?
- Yup.
- And I build a trap for him?
Me?
- You.
- He wants to kill you
before you build it.
That's why he's sending
Killer Frost after you.
- Killer Frost?
Her name...is Killer Frost?
- Yeah.
- We know it's a lot to take in.
- Well, to be fair,
you're basically telling me
I'm Sarah Connor
in "Terminator."
- Well...
- Uh, more like...
- Miles Dyson.
- Yeah,
but good effort, though.
- So wait.
You're telling me my ideas
about the, um...
- The Speed Force.
- Speed Force,
being able to control it,
manipulate it, all of that...
I'm right?
- It appears so.
[device chimes]
- That's me?
[laughs]
Nobel Prize?
All of that?
- In the future, yeah.
- [sighs]
- Look, Tracy.
[device chimes]
We need your help.
We need you
to build this trap now.
- What happens
if I don't build the trap?
- Someone very important to us
is going to die.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
♪ ♪
- Uh, I know that, uh,
normally one of you fellas
goes out for the chat,
but, uh...
I got this one.
Tracy!
Oh, Tracy!
♪ ♪
[light knocking]
- I'm working.
- I can see.
I thought you'd like
to be informed
that H.R. has managed
to talk Tracy around.
- Ah, perfect.
That means we can get to work.
- Yeah, there's one thing
I need to know first.
Outside Jitters earlier,
you could've stopped Caitlin
with a vibe.
But just like CCU,
you didn't.
- I'm not doing this again.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You are.
I need to know, Cisco.
Tell me why
you couldn't do it.
- Get out of my way.
- Caitlin could be home now.
Had you stopped her,
she would be here.
But you didn't!
You couldn't!
Tell me why!
- Because I'm afraid!
- Afraid of what?
- Afraid of killing her!
[tense somber music]
I'm walking around
with two loaded guns here,
ready to go off.
What if she's hurting Barry
or Joe or you
and I have to save you
and I can't control my powers
and I end up killing her?
She's my best friend.
And I'd rather it be me
than her.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
How's Tracy holding up?
- Ah, we'll see.
Um...
[clears throat]
Have you told Cecile
about us yet?
- Cecile is the only thing...
normal I have
in my life right now,
and I like
having something normal.
If I tell her about all this...
that goes away.
- But if you don't tell her...
- There may not be an "us."
- Mm-hmm.
Joe, there's no such thing
as normal.
Love is the only thing
that makes the fight worth it,
and it's the only thing
that's gonna get us through it.
♪ ♪
- Guys.
Guys, there you are.
We got a big problem.
Tracy's gone.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I checked CCU,
her apartment, and Jitters.
Tracy's not in any of them.
- I'll bet you Savitar
and Killer Frost are hunting
her down as we speak.
- H.R.,
you were with Tracy last.
How did she seem?
- Rattled, Miss West.
Rattled, but I gave her a
rousing and reassuring pep talk,
so I think she's okay.
- Oh, that's why she left.
- That's not why...look,
I will have you know my book
on motivational speeches,
"All's Wells that Ends Wells"...
- Tracy is in danger.
- You're right.
Iris! Focus!
- What?
- We need to find her. Now.
- Yeah, we gotta find her.
- [sighs]
Where else could she be?
- Oh!
[snaps fingers]
Why don't we start
with her future hologram, right?
That's...that would
give us insight
into her psyche, no?
- Of course, yeah.
- That's pretty good.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
[device beeps]
- [sighing]
[tense music]
- She's cute.
- This is creepy, right?
- Yeah.
- I find her charming.
Do you think you could
screenshot a hologram?
- Go back to that last one.
- Yeah, there's another one
like it.
- Whoa, whoa, look at that.
Zoom in.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Eppur si...
- [snaps fingers]
Eppur si muove.
Tracy, you blessed paramour
of science.
Gang, I know
exactly where she is.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
Eppur si muove.
"And yet it moves."
Galileo's famous statement
uttered moments
after being forced to recant
his theory that the Earth
revolves around the sun.
"And yet it moves."
Mocha Flash for me.
A Zoom for milady.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
- How did you know I was here?
- Um, I might have done a bit
of holographic stalking.
I stalked you holographically.
- You mean, in the future,
I'm still obsessed
with a 500-year-old
Italian polymath?
- [laughing]
Yes, it would appear so.
- I'm sorry I ran off.
I just...
- No.
- Just needed to clear
my head and think...
- Of course.
- And this is where
I do it best.
- Well, I can see that.
That statue is nothing
if not inspiring.
Concrete beard,
foreboding, smart.
- Totally inspiring.
- Yup.
- You know, Galileo's peers
thought he was a crackpot too.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
And I used to find that
comforting.
- Oh.
- But then when your team
showed me the future
and showed me
that my crazy ideas
aren't so crazy after all,
I just felt more intimidated
than ever.
- Well, I can see that.
It's like you're sitting
in the shadow of greatness.
Your own greatness, right?
- Exactly!
It's like I've failed
so many times.
That's all I know how to do.
I don't know how to be that...
brilliant woman
in the hologram.
♪ ♪
But you wouldn't understand.
You are a born genius.
- Yeah, about that.
Um, I'm not...
technically a genius.
That was a cheap thing to do.
I'm sorry I misled you
about me being a genius.
The point is, you...
are...a genius.
You are.
I know it.
I can...I can feel it.
It's right there.
It's right there,
just brimming
just below the surface.
- It is?
- Yes, absolutely!
Yes, it is, Tracy.
And you can defeat Savitar.
All you need is to just
believe in yourself.
And for what it's worth...
I already do.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[knock at door]
- [groans softly]
- Hi.
- Hey. I didn't know
you were dropping by.
- Yeah, well,
if you had read any
of my texts, you'd know.
- Yeah. Um...
I'm sorry.
- I know.
It's why I'm here.
Look, I...
You know, it doesn't take
a detective to see
that something's not right.
- Look, Cecile...
- Is it because I said,
"I love you," this morning?
Because, Joe, it's...it's okay if
you're not ready to say it back.
- No, no.
It's not about that.
- No?
Well, then what's going on?
'Cause you've been acting weird
all day.
I mean, not just with us
this morning
but at work with that meta case.
You gotta give me
something, Joe.
- All I can say is...
that part of my life
is very complicated.
And if you were
to become part of that,
your life would be
very complicated,
and it would change us.
And I mean change us forever.
- [chuckles softly]
That's not a bad thing,
you know.
It's called growth.
- And then I was
thinking about...
what you said this morning,
and it told me where you were.
It also showed me where I was,
and...
and you add
those complications,
and I think we should stop
seeing each other.
- Really?
[somber music]
That's what you think
we should do?
- I-I-I think it's
the best thing for both of us.
- Here I was,
thinking that being together
was the best thing
for both of us.
♪ ♪
I guess I'll, uh...
I'll see you around
the station, Joe.
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
[gasping]
- Cecile!
- Joe!
- No! Guarantee you I'm faster.
- Caitlin...
we can talk about this.
- I'll talk.
You listen.
In an hour, you're gonna get
a message with an address.
Bring me Tracy Brand, or I will
kill your little sweetheart.
- [sobbing]
Joe.
- Wait!
[Cecile screams]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- So you're saying that if we
don't turn Tracy over
to Killer Frost...
- She's gonna kill Cecile.
- Correct me if I'm wrong,
but Tracy is our key
to finding Savitar, right?
- Yes, but what are we gonna do?
We gonna just let Killer Frost
live up to her name
and kill somebody?
- Not if I have anything
to say about it.
- All I'm saying is, we need
to do whatever it takes
to save her.
- No one's gonna die, all right?
We're gonna get her back.
I promise.
[cell phone chimes]
- That's them.
They're at the old
Dressler Factory.
- Okay, we know where they are.
That's something.
So what do we do?
- I have a plan.
- Cisco, can I have
a quick word?
- Not now, Julian.
- Listen, please, mate.
Just...just hear me out.
[soft dramatic music]
I know you're terrified
of losing her.
So am I.
I know you're...you're worried
about not being able
to control your powers,
but I know you can.
I don't think your abilities
have ever come from a place
of...of negativity or...or hate.
They come from somewhere good.
They come from love.
And if you can find it in you
to stop her,
then I really think
we can save her.
♪ ♪
Cheers, mate.
- Hi.
Yeah, you know how I said,
you know,
we were gonna keep you safe?
[drumming on leg]
- Um, yeah.
- So, um, now I need to ask you
to do something dangerous.
[dramatic music swells]
♪ ♪
- Cecile!
Are you all right?
- Joe!
I'm okay.
She didn't hurt me.
- That's because killing you...
does nothing for me.
[dramatic music]
Killing you, Tracy?
That's everything.
♪ ♪
Hand her over.
- You don't have
to do this.
- Yes, I do.
- Why?
Because Savitar commands it?
He's not a god.
He's just a man
that's using you.
Come on, you're one of us.
- One of us?
- We're family.
- We're family?
both: We protect each other
till the end.
- [chuckling]
- How are you doing that?
- Savitar told me everything
you'd say.
You two are more alike
than you realize.
You see, that's how Savitar
knows every move
you're going to make.
He's always one step
ahead of you,
because this is all history
to him.
That's how I know Cisco's
in the rafters right now.
[bomb beeping]
- Oh, no.
[detonator clicks]
[whoosh]
[explosion booms]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[ice crackling]
[ice shatters on ground]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- It's over, Caitlin.
♪ ♪
- Caitlin is dead.
- Not to me.
♪ ♪
- Go. Go. Go. Go.
- [grunts]
[ice crackling]
♪ ♪
[shouts]
[panting]
[vibration humming]
- [grunts]
[both panting]
- Caitlin.
You're alive.
[panting]
I'm sorry.
I had to stop you to save you.
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
[grunts]
[dramatic choral music]
- My ascension is nearly
at hand, Flash.
As I rise, you will fall.
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
- How do we keep surviving
these things?
- Because we're in control
of our fates.
- And how did she know
I was up in the rafters?
Is she psychic now too?
And that thing where you guys
were talking at the same time?
How do you think
she was doing that?
- I don't know.
She said Savitar told her
what was gonna happen.
- No way, man.
This wasn't just brushing up
on days to come.
This was precise.
Scary precise.
Like Savitar was there.
- Mm-hmm.
- What I don't understand
is why Savitar
wouldn't kill Tracy
when he showed up.
I mean, why would he choose
to rescue Caitlin?
- He needs her
for something.
We gotta figure out
what that is.
- Agreed.
Thanks to Cisco, we now have
a sample of her blood
when she was fully mutated
as Killer Frost.
This?
It could be the key
to reverse engineering a cure,
so...
it's good work, mate.
- You too.
- [chuckling]
Oh, there you are.
I brought us
some coffee treats.
Unfortunately,
we were all out of cayenne.
Careful, that's hot.
- [gasps] Ah!
- Yeah, hot, hot, sorry.
How are you?
Oh! Ha! Whoo!
- Careful.
- Ah, how are you holding up?
Whew, it's hot.
- Well, I'm processing.
- Mm-hmm.
- That was really...
I mean, the voice...
- [blubbers]
- And the "whoom!"
- Pshh!
- Killer Frost? Savitar?
You know some people
with really scary names.
- Eh, but is it too much?
All of us here
would understand.
Personally, I just...
I just wanna make sure
that, you know,
you don't get hurt.
As a matter of fact,
I was thinking...
- I was thinking too.
- Yeah?
- About Savitar.
- Mm-hmm?
- The way the light reflects
off his suit,
it's unlike any other metallic
compound I have ever seen.
- Hmm, you and I were thinking
about different things.
What do you think it is?
- In Fermi liquid theory,
any sort of non-Fermi liquid
is called "strange metal."
- Mm-hmm.
- It's a theoretical compound
capable of dispersing heat
at high temperatures.
I think Savitar travels so fast
that he needs that suit
to neutralize the charge
he builds up around him.
- Huh.
Interesting.
So without the suit,
he's just a dude
with a bad case
of static cling.
- Yeah.
So if we could build a device
capable of harnessing
that power,
theoretically, we could use
his own velocity against him.
- And trap him
in the Speed Force.
Tracy, you are indeed a genius.
- I'm getting there.
- Well, yes, you are.
[gasps] That means you're
gonna stay and help us.
Is that what that means?
- If I do, does that mean
the future's changing?
- I think it means
mine certainly has.
[light knocking]
- Hey.
- Thanks for seeing me.
Come on in.
So how are you doing?
- Joe, I'm fine.
I just...you know,
I wish that you would've told me
what was going on with you.
Although I...obviously
have some idea now.
- It was my fault that you got
caught up in all this.
I'm so sorry, Cecile.
- Joe, me too.
Look, I...
- When you told me that you
loved me this morning...
I froze.
- Yeah.
- I knew that it meant
that we moved up a level
in our relationship.
And...for me,
that level comes
with a lot of baggage.
- Like Killer Frost
and The Flash?
- Yeah.
- So you thought
that pushing me away
was the thing to do?
- I thought
that I was protecting you.
Clearly I was wrong,
because not only
did I lie to you.
I lied to myself.
And you know what?
I'm done with that.
[soft sentimental music]
♪ ♪
And I'm done with this.
Thank you for not making
a big deal
about me wearing this.
♪ ♪
Cecile Horton...
- [exhales]
- I love you.
- [chuckles]
- I love you
with all my heart.
And I'm sorry that I was
dishonest with you.
And from now on,
there will be no secrets
between us.
- [exhales]
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
[giggles]
[sighs, clears throat]
- Okay.
- Mm.
- I should have told you
a long time ago.
But it's not bad.
♪ ♪
Wally!
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey.
How was it?
- It was...yeah, it was great.
Jesse says hi.
- So you talked to Cecile?
- I did.
Told her everything.
Told her I love her.
I told her that you
were The Flash
and that Wally was Kid Flash.
Don't worry.
She promised me...
that she wouldn't tell Joanie.
[laughter]
- What changed your mind?
- You.
All of you.
I mean, love's the only thing
we got in this world.
Without it,
nothing really matters.
- Hmm.
- And who knows
what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
How was Earth-3?
- Yeah, um,
hanging out with Jesse
was awesome.
- [echoing] I mean,
love's the only thing
we got in this world.
Without it,
nothing really matters.
And who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
- You did this to me, Barry.
- I created you?
- I created myself.
- You're even gonna create
time remnants of yourself,
but he's gonna kill them all.
- Savitar told me everything
you'd say.
You two are more alike
than you realize.
Savitar knows every move
you're going to make.
He's always one step
ahead of you.
[echoing] This is all history.
- This wasn't just brushing up
on days to come.
This was precise.
Like Savitar was there.
- Who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
- One step ahead of you.
All history.
- I am the future Flash.
- One step ahead of you.
- [distorted] Barry?
[normally]
Barry!
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Uh, I'm sorry.
[tense music]
I'll be...I'll be right back,
all right?
♪ ♪
[whoosh]
I'm here!
[panting]
[whoosh]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
I know who you are.
- It's about time.
- Yes, it is.
Everything with you
is about time, isn't it?
The past, the present,
the future...
you know all of it, right?
And you know everything
about me!
About Joe!
About Wally.
And Iris!
You know our strengths.
You know our fears.
You know how much
we love each other.
And you know how to use
that love against us.
All this time, we thought
that we couldn't stop you
because you were one step ahead,
but that's not it!
You don't just know
what's gonna happen to us.
You were there.
You lived it.
You remember...
when you were me.
[tense musical flourish]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[sinister dramatic music]
- Like I told you
from the beginning...
♪ ♪
I am the future Flash.
[dramatic choral music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.