[soft dramatic music]
- Barry:He was the most
brilliant  mind I ever met.
♪ ♪
They all were.
Whatever the problem,
you could count on a Wells...
A council of them,
to have the answers.
Now, they're all gone.
♪ ♪
We gotta find
the answers ourselves.
♪ ♪
- Why does it always feel like
for us to win,
some of us have to lose?
♪ ♪
This wall is nano-engraved
with the names
of everyone we've lost
so that no matter
how the timeline changes...
They'll never be forgotten.
♪ ♪
- Those Wells,
they took some getting used to,
didn't they?
- [sorrowfully chuckles]
- If we learned anything
from them,
it was that our greatest weapon
against darkness
isn't our superpowers.
♪ ♪
It's our humanity...
and our love for each other.
♪ ♪
Bar?
Bar, I know what you're doing.
Don't.
Don't blame yourself.
- But what you just said...
Ramsey infecting me,
Eva using a copy of Iris
to manipulate my emotions...
Lately, it feels like my heart
is my enemies' greatest weapon.
- Have faith, son.
We will get Iris back.
I feel that in my heart.
♪ ♪
[electronic ting]
[intense dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What the...
[soft dramatic music]
- This is supposed to open
a portal to the Mirrorverse?
- Yeah.
Supposed to.
I thought
I could use Atlantean tech
to tackle perpetual motion,
one of science's
greatest problems,
but guess what I found
waiting for me?
[electronic beeping]
[crackling and whirring]
More problems.
This thing's a dud.
[sighs]
I don't know what to do.
I lost my friend.
My girlfriend is trapped
in another dimension,
and nothing my brain
comes up with
seems to get me
any closer to saving her.
- I promise you,
we will get them back.
Kamilla, Iris, Singh.
All of 'em.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
Okay.
Refocusing!
So Chester's away
at Grandma Runk's,
but lucky for us,
he's been science-ing
in between bingo rounds,
and he seems to think
there are two problems
we need to solve
if we wanna open our portal.
Problem number one...
[chaotic chatter]
- You haven't found the method
to reconfigure
the molecular stability
of the dimensional barrier
that damages organic matter?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
How did you know that?
- I saw you write it.
- [chuckles]
No, you didn't.
- I thought I did.
- I was about to.
But you guessed right.
Eva used Ramsey's blood
to tackle that problem
and open her portal.
Unfortunately for us,
without a replacement
for Ramsey's evil sentient goo,
we're kind of up a creek.
So that brings us
to problem number two...
[chaotic chatter]
- Quantum entanglement from
reversed Higgs boson particles
disrupts
the geospatial algorithm,
preventing us from locating
people in the Mirrorverse,
meaning we have to know
Kamilla, Singh,
and Iris's location
in order to pull them out.
- You freaky.
- I know where they'll be.
Iris sent a message to Kamilla
and Singh in the Mirrorverse
telling them to meet
in the Speed Lab tonight.
Don't ask me how I got it,
'cause I have no idea.
- Iris's neural pathways
have likely achieved
an equilibrium
with the harmonic frequency
contained within the
fractalized dimensional plane.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- He freaky.
[tense music]
[whooshing]
[door clicks]
- Our mission's going better
than expected.
Hoshi and Ultraviolet's raids
on Black Hole stash houses
have liberated crates
of your mirror-tech.
- Good.
Rawlins, do you
notice anything...
different about me?
- Sorry?
- Do you see
anything out of place?
♪ ♪
- Yeah, now that
you mention it.
You look tired,
your desk is a mess,
and you skipped
your coffee today.
- You got me.
- But there is something...
familiar.
That look in your eyes.
It's how Carver looked
when he kept secrets from us.
- I'm nothing like Joseph.
I will never lie to you.
I promise.
- Good, because we've located
our next stash house.
Want me to gather
the Assassins Three?
- No.
It's been a while
since I've enjoyed the pleasure
of tearing down
my husband's empire,
so I will handle
this one myself.
- Allegra:So he's, what, a
genius now?
- No, I'm a genius.
My guy's on
a whole other level.
His neurons are firing
at super speed.
Synaptic connections
are off the charts.
The quantum computers
can't even keep up
processing his results.
- The Artificial Speed Force.
- The Artificial fracking
Speed Force.
It didn't just give you
your old powers back,
it gave you a new one.
Enhanced cognition
by way of a Speed Force
booster shot!
- Huh?
- Barry can think fast now.
- Cool.
How fast?
- Let's find out, shall we?
Lady and gentleman, this...
is a Quantum Ball.
Trademark pending.
Ever heard of it?
Of course you haven't,
but you will.
Mark my words, one day,
Quantum Ball,
trademark pending,
will be the world's
next great sporting event.
You see, this little sphere
amplifies kinetic energy,
firing in directions
that can only be described
as "unpredictable,"
but not for you.
Your enhanced cognition
should let you analyze
every variable
in every scenario...
and predict the unpredictable.
Barry Allen.
Places, please.
- [clears throat]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Call it.
[whooshing]
- Eh, no cheating.
Turn around.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Ready.
Wall, lamp,
pipe, conduit, duck.
Now!
♪ ♪
I have superspeed thinking.
I know how to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse.
- Uh, what?
- Yeah, repeat that.
For Allegra.
- All right, I'm sorry.
Um...
let me show you.
[whooshing]
Ramsey's unique cells
created a polar covalent bond
with the molecules
in Eva's mirror portal.
That's why she needed
his blood.
- Right, it formed, like,
a bio-friendly skin on the
interdimensional barrier.
- So we need Ramsey's blood.
We knew that.
- No, we don't need it.
His blood would have bonded
with the
electronegative particles
and become dark matter photons.
Those particles wouldn't
just stay on the mirror portal.
- No, they wouldn't.
They'd attach
themselves to Eva.
Those photons are still on her.
If we could collect them,
we could open our portal.
But it would take, like,
years to develop
a prototype that could do that.
[whooshing]
- Not if we integrate
the neural net
in the Thinker's chair,
synced to a nanite bridge,
fed into the Tachyon Enhancer's
non-reductive loop.
- N...no, but wait,
wouldn't...
well...
well, yeah, I guess...
I guess that could work.
- But isn't Eva
still holed up behind
McCulloch Tech's force field?
We'll never get close to her.
You're gonna bring out
another board?
[whooshing]
- Factoring in
geographical analytics,
concealment probability,
these are the remaining
Black Hole stash houses.
There's a 97.6% chance
Eva's hitting this one next.
[thoughtful music]
- Right.
Right.
So that's where we go.
And that's what we do.
[sighs]
Just wish I could have
seen it earlier.
- This isn't on you.
We wouldn't be in this mess
if I'd seen through
Iris's mirror duplicate sooner.
Eva's not the first
to use my emotions against me.
Let's make sure she's the last.
[spray paint spritzing]
- Kamilla?
- Iris!
Thank God.
When you disappeared,
I thought
that neural dissonance
sickness got you.
- Yeah, well, she tried
to use it against me,
but I was able
to fight her off.
I think I've been in this place
for so long
that I've gained control
over it.
I think that's how I was able
to send you
and Singh that message.
- That's amazing.
- [sighs]
What about Singh?
Did you find him
at the hospital?
- I looked everywhere, but...
Iris, what if we never
find him?
What if we never escape?
What if we stay here so long
that our minds just get
completely destroyed and...
- Kamilla, we have been through
our fair share of danger,
so no matter
what dimension we're in,
no matter what kind
of villain we face,
there is nothing
that can stop us
as long as we stick together.
Are you with me?
- [sighs]
Let's do this.
- Good.
Because I'm thinking
if my message got to you,
then it could have gotten
to Singh too,
so let's go find him.
Come on.
[intense dramatic music]
[engine roars]
- That doesn't belong to you.
Then again, it never belonged
to my husband either.
It was my reflective
chip technology
that was twisted to create
that weapon,
so it's mine
to wield or destroy.
Now step aside.
[guards screaming]
♪ ♪
- You were right.
Eva's here, and she's amped.
- How do you like your phantom
now, Joseph?
- Not the day for us
to be short-staffed.
- Actually, we're good;
I called in
a little bit of extra muscle.
♪ ♪
[sharp whooshing]
- 'Sup?
Nice outfit, by the way.
- Why are you here?
- You know, for funsies.
[blaster whooshing]
- Looks like someone's
back to 100%.
Long live the snow queen.
- Eva's faster than me.
Frost is gonna distract her
while I run by
with the Tachyon Enhancer
and collect
the particles we need.
- We might only get
one shot at this.
Let's make it count.
[whooshing]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
[hums]
- [grunts]
- Flash!
[electrical zapping]
♪ ♪
Barry, help her!
- [grunts]
- [yelling]
♪ ♪
Frost!
Frost.
♪ ♪
You let her get hit.
- Whatever Eva hit Frost with,
it's light-based.
Her healing's trying
to compensate,
but it's not enough.
[dramatic music]
I can't fix this
without Caitlin.
[whooshing]
What is that?
- A cure.
- Has it been tested?
- I ran 2,371 tests in my head.
We're good.
- Barry, that is not a...
what are you doing?
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- What happened?
- You took the brunt
of Eva's laser blast
to help us.
I just returned the favor
with a cryogenically-fortified
paracetamol cocktail...
- That fortified
my cellular walls.
Yep, that'll do it.
- Of course,
you wouldn't have had to take
the brunt of the blast
if Barry hadn't
let you get hit
in the first place.
- Cisco, let me explain.
- Barry...
what were you thinking?
I saw you.
You had the time
to run her out of the way,
and you just stood there
like you wanted her to get hit.
- There was a 0.0002% chance
of the Tachyon Enhancer
getting damaged
in that scenario.
I couldn't risk that.
I also knew
I could reverse any ill effects
Frost received
from Eva's blast.
- These aren't ill effects!
This was a light wound,
like the kind
that almost killed her,
and we just got her back!
- Cisco, it's okay.
I'm fine, and now we have
a chance to save our friends.
I'd take a hit
for that any day.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
You got lucky
with that cocktail.
- Luck had nothing
to do with it.
- So superspeed thinking, huh?
What's that like?
- Sometimes it's like a barrage
of images flying at me.
Others, it's like a scene
playing out in my head.
- So what does your speed brain
say our next move is?
- You saw Iris's message,
"Eva is watching."
She would no doubt see
our attempt to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse and stop us.
I need to find a solution.
You should recuperate
for 14.2 minutes,
then help Cisco
gather our McCulloch intel
so I can cross-reference it
with our Eva data.
I need to aggregate.
♪ ♪
- Huh.
- Cecile:Wow, Barry seems like
he has things in hand
and then some.
- Yep.
He'll probably have
this Eva sitch
wrapped up in no time.
- You're thinking about Nash.
I'm sorry.
Honey, I just...
my empathic abilities,
they take on a mind
of their own sometimes.
- It's okay.
It's just...
my dad left me
before I could walk,
and ever since then,
anyone who's
even come close to being...
- A father figure?
- Yeah, I...
I cut them out of my life
before they could cut me
out of theirs.
That's why I pushed Nash away.
Anyway, I should just
get over it.
He's gone.
- Only if you let him be.
Did you know
that the law goes way back
in my family?
Yeah, my...my granddad
was the first
Black paralegal in Oklahoma,
and my mom, first female
independent counsel
in the state of Texas.
Both of them were pioneers
for social justice
and my heroes.
- I'll say.
- Yeah.
Right now, my granddad's
file cabinet
is in the corner of my office,
and I carry my mom's briefcase
into court with me
every single day.
Honey, the people that we love,
they're only gone when we stop
carrying them with us.
How you choose to carry Nash
is up to you.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Barry:I figured out her
secret.
This isn't her world.
It never has been.
♪ ♪
[electronic beeping]
- Thank you, Arielle.
I'm glad to be here.
I'm lucky to be anywhere.
- Indeed.
Let's jump right into it.
You came here today
to make an announcement.
- Yes.
Before I was kidnapped,
I was developing technologies
with promise
to advance the world.
Fresh water, healthier crops,
clean, renewable energy.
I am thrilled to finally return
to my life's work,
improving our world.
- Why are we watching this?
- At the stash house,
Eva referred to herself
as a phantom.
It reminded me
of Carver's dying words
when Eva killed him...
that she wasn't his wife.
I've analyzed behavioral
patterns, body language,
even graphological handwriting.
That...
is not Eva McCulloch.
- What?
What do you mean?
She's sitting right there,
talking to Rachel Maddow 2.0.
- I slept in the same bed
with a mirror duplicate of Iris
without knowing the difference.
You did the same with Kamilla.
- So you think this is
a mirror Eva?
- McCulloch's security database
will show us.
[electronic beeping]
- Yeah, good luck.
I tried hacking them
a week ago.
[electronic beeping]
What?
How...
McCulloch's black box servers
run a hybrid
theorem-proving system
with model checking.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
His mind is getting faster.
- Yes, it is.
[flame whooshing]
- Did she just die?
- Oh, my God.
- No.
Help!
Someone help me!
- Which brings us to why
you're here today.
- Precisely.
Allow me to present
McCulloch Technology's
future for humanity.
[electronic beeping]
- Whoa, what are you doing
with that footage?
- Exposing the truth.
♪ ♪
[flame whooshing]
- Eva?
No. No. No.
Please. Come on.
Stay with me.
- I don't think
that's such a good idea.
- Help!
- No, no, no, stop that!
Stop!
- Someone help me!
- No, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, no, no!
Stop!
- [screams]
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
- That footage we saw.
Does it show you
killing the real Eva McCulloch?
- No, of course,
I...-I wouldn't do that.
I...I didn't do that.
- What are you, a meta?
A shape-shifter?
- No, I...
- The world wants answers.
We deserve to know.
- Rawlins!
- If you're not Eva McCulloch,
who or what are you?
- I'm not a monster.
I'm not a monster!
[whooshes]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Why did you do that?
- Eva would sense us
opening a portal.
Now she is too distracted
to notice.
- And there couldn't be
another way to distract her...
- There were 141 ways.
This was the most efficient.
- Uh, I'm not sure
emotionally wrecking
an already-whacked-out villain
was "efficient."
- Historically speaking,
when our enemies are upset,
which is exactly
what I accomplished,
they make mistakes.
We need to prep
the portal machine
while Eva is on her heels
and then retrieve our targets.
- You mean our friends.
- One and the same.
♪ ♪
- Cisco?
- I know.
Something's seriously wrong
with Barry.
[earpiece beeps]
- Gideon:
Greetings, Barry Allen.
Your biological signals
indicate a state of distress.
May I assist you?
- I needed
a second opinion, Gideon.
I just ran
the necessary calculations
to operate
Cisco's portal device.
The results have me concerned.
- Analyzing
temporal-spatial data.
Estimated time to complete
quantum computations,
18.4 hours.
- Invert the Feynman shortcut
and apply it to 1/2 mass
times velocity squared,
compensating for tachyon decay.
- Thank you
for a more efficient method.
[electronic whizzing]
Calculations complete.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I was correct.
We cannot save all of them.
We have to choose.
- Would you like me to inform
the rest of the team?
- What do you mean,
we have to choose?
- Simply put, the longer the
person is in the Mirrorverse,
the more dark matter photons
are required to pull them out.
Kamilla and Singh have been
trapped for less time.
Therefore,
they can be retrieved together.
With Iris,
it would take everything
we have to retrieve her.
- Well, there's gotta
be another way.
♪ ♪
- Barry, what's your
speed brain tell you?
- We have to choose.
Kamilla and Singh or Iris.
It is the only way.
- How the hell are we supposed
to do that?
- I guess we vote?
- On this?
- I don't know, dude.
Do you know another way
to be fair?
- [laughs]
This is beyond screwed up.
But if this is the only way...
Who thinks we should save Iris?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
And Kamilla and Singh?
- Sorry, Barry.
Gotta go with the numbers.
♪ ♪
- Are you all right,
Barry Allen?
You appear to be distracted.
- I just ran a simulation
to see how this would play out.
- Would you like me to inform
the rest of the team
of this development?
- No.
This is something
I must do alone.
- Are you sure
that's the best...
[electronic beep]
[intense dramatic music]
[keyboard clicking]
[electronic whirring]
♪ ♪
- What is all this stuff?
- I have no idea.
[suspenseful music]
- Iris, help me, please.
- David!
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- David, can you hear me?
- Is this neural dissonance?
- No, but it's similar.
It's a side effect of being
sent to the Mirrorverse
by the Mirror Gun
instead of Eva
pulling Singh
through her office mirror.
- How do you know that?
- I don't know.
I just do.
- Iris, I was shot too.
Wou...
[grunting]
- Kamilla!
♪ ♪
[electronic beeping]
- Hey.
Talk for a sec?
- Of course.
- What's with the suit?
- We are about to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse.
One must be prepared.
- Right, about that.
I looked over the schematics,
and I think there might be
something wrong with
the Artificial Speed Force.
[electronic beeping]
You remember how Thawne
used negative emotion
to stabilize
his Speed Force machine?
Well, since we didn't wanna
make the same mistake,
we used an inert substance,
an argon-xenon hybrid
that would generate
no emotional fallout.
But I think that was a mistake.
Yes, the ASF gave you
increased cognitive function,
a thousand times over, but...
it's done the exact opposite
to your emotional response.
- I am better this way.
The team is safer this way.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Look, man.
I know you think your heart
has been used against you,
but it's not a weakness.
It's what makes you human.
I mean, without it...
♪ ♪
Why is the portal target
set to Iris?
♪ ♪
What about saving the others?
- We do not have enough
dark matter photons
to save all three of them.
♪ ♪
- So, instead of consulting
your team,
you just decided on your own?
- I've already seen the outcome
of this debate.
You eventually vote
to save Kamilla and Singh.
- Like hell.
I would never vote
on something like that.
If you had come to me,
I would've told you
we'll find another way.
That's what we always do.
- Your emotions are
making you irrational.
- And your lack of them
are making you wrong!
You cannot predict
what I would've done
because you cannot
predict emotion!
♪ ♪
Barry, I know you.
I know your heart, and I know
that you're doing this
because you miss Iris.
- My feelings are irrelevant.
Iris has knowledge of Eva,
which could give us
a tactical advantage.
Therefore, Iris is
the logical choice to liberate.
The fact is,
Singh and Kamilla
are expendable.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Expendable?
[electronic whirring]
Don't ever call her expendable.
♪ ♪
We're gonna give you back
your heart, Barry,
and it's gonna be by choice...
[gun clicks and whirs]
Or by force.
♪ ♪
- Don't make us do this, Barry.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[electronic whirring]
- Iris would agree with me.
- No.
She wouldn't.
♪ ♪
You've just been hit
with Velocity-Zero charge.
It temporarily dampens
your speed.
You're not the only one
who can predict reactions.
♪ ♪
[gun clicks]
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
[electrical zapping]
- [grunts]
- Your defeat is inevitable.
The Velocity-X in your system
is nearly depleted.
Your time as a Speedster
is coming to an end.
- [breathes heavily]
Maybe.
But I'm not only a Speedster.
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[grunting]
[electronic whirring]
[grunts]
- The Babel Protocols aren't
just force fields and tech.
It's us.
- Sorry for the tough love.
- But we need
the real you back.
- Don't worry.
We're gonna shut off
the Artificial Speed Force
and get your head straight.
♪ ♪
- You lost this fight
before it even began.
[blaster pulse whooshing]
- Look out!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[electronic buzzing]
[dramatic music]
- Hang on, guys.
I'm gonna get you
to the med lab,
and we'll get you...
[high-pitched
electronic buzzing]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
Barry?
Oh, my God.
Please tell me
this isn't a trick.
- Your message to Kamilla
and Singh led us here.
I am ready
to bring you home now.
- Okay.
Um, I just wanna get
Singh and Kamilla
through first.
They're in pretty bad shape,
and they're gonna need
some help...
- Not them.
Just you.
We cannot bring you all back.
You have been there longer.
You have more knowledge of Eva.
Therefore, retrieving you
is the logical choice.
- Did you hear
what I just said?
Barry, they could die.
They need you to save them.
♪ ♪
- This is not the outcome
I predicted.
- What?
- You need to come through.
Now.
[electronic whirring]
[intense dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[whooshing]
[grunting]
- Iris, stop.
Your resistance
is destabilizing
the portal's energy.
That is dangerous.
- Barry.
Barry, this isn't you.
This isn't right.
[electronic whirring]
♪ ♪
[yells]
[screams]
♪ ♪
[strained breathing]
- Iris?
Iris?
Hey, hey.
- [strained breathing]
- Hey, Iris.
- I didn't see this.
No.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[screams]
[electronic buzzing]
[breathing heavily]
Iris.
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[electrical buzzing]
[screams]
- [strained breathing]
♪ ♪
- Eva: This isn't my world.
This isn't my world.
This isn't my world anymore.
This isn't...
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
But it can be.
- Good night, Hawkshaw.
Tell Gwen
thanks for the brownies.
- I will.
[elevator dings]
[sighs]
[keys clatter]
[intense music]
[gasps]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
- Man 1:Help!
-Man 2: You see,
they're not coming to save you.
They're coming to save me.
- Ah!
- [breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[leaves rustling]
[whooshing]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Greg, move your head.
[electric buzzing]