- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world
is more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- I want to believe
that there is good
inside of you
somewhere, Thawne.
- Let me prove there is.
- The shards weren't
dampening my powers.
They were removing them.
We could make
a meta-human cure.
- Earl Cox.
Ralph Dibny's gone straight.
- So when you let
your new friends down,
give your old one a call.
- So he thinks the kid
is hiding out here,
just lurking
behind those doors.
- It's the inside
of Dwyer's house.
- Didn't you have, like,
seven marriages?
- I did have seven marriages.
Five wives, seven marriages.
- So I'm gonna need you
to tell me right now
why you're investigating Nora.
- I've made a career
out of noticing things
that other people miss.
[computers beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[exhales sharply]
Who is your accomplice,
Nora West-Allen?
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- There's always a Wells.
- He knows I'm working
with someone.
- But he doesn't know
with whom you're working.
Not yet.
- How can you be sure?
- Because if he did,
your father would be here
right now in a flash,
threatening to put his hand
right through my heart.
- Eobard, if my father
finds out
you've been helping me
try to catch Cicada
behind his back,
he'll hate me,
and...
- Shh.
This can all be fixed.
I can fix this.
- How?
- A man...does not wear
another man's face
unless he understands
his mind.
Not just through time
but across infinite Earths.
This Sherloque, yes,
he's brilliant,
but to redirect his gaze,
one only has to nudge him
toward his weakness:
love.
♪ ♪
- Tell me what to do.
[whooshing]
- [sighs]
Well, what do you think?
- [sighs] Looks great.
- I mean, I can move the couch
against the wall,
if that'll help.
[whooshing]
Iris, it's just couch in
the corner or against the wall
is pretty much the extent of my
interior design knowledge.
- [sighs]
I'm sorry, babe.
It's...it's just,
it's been a week since
I launched the
Central City Citizen,
and I am still struggling
to gain readers,
and I think I just
figured out why.
- "Iris West-Allen's first
published articles
"as an aspiring
online news maven
"bring one word to mind:
"'boring.'
"Her stories lack the edgy
content made popular
"by sites such as
Spencer Young's
"game-changing Spyn Zone.
In short,
Iris West-Allen plays it safe."
Iris, come on.
You can't listen to this.
You're a real journalist.
You don't want to write
like Spencer Young.
She didn't care about facts.
- Yeah, but at least
she wrote about things
that people cared about,
like I did when I was
writing about DeVoe.
- You wanna write about Cicada.
[soft music]
Fine.
Call me if you need me.
I'll be at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Yes, of course.
[sighs] I've got a lot
of digging to do,
and I think I have a hunch
where to start.
Mwah.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- So you really think
this might be it?
- Cisco sent me this sample
to corroborate his findings,
and it all checks out.
I'm sending it back to him
for final processing,
but I think we may
have found a way
to suppress the meta genome.
- Great.
Then we can use it
to de-power Cicada,
stop him for good.
- So what's the plan?
Put this thing in
a tranq gun and go all
"American Sniper" on him?
- It's not that simple.
So Cisco's breakthrough came
from analyzing identical twins
who were hit by the particle
accelerator dark matter,
cases where one developed
powers and the other didn't.
The key difference
in both cases...
- The pituitary gland?
- Exactly.
In some cases,
the pituitary gland
metabolizes dark matter,
thus manifesting
in meta powers.
- So to turn a meta-human
into a human-human...
- We neutralize the dark matter
in the pituitary gland.
Except there's one problem.
The cure isn't instant.
We would have to immobilize
Cicada for long enough
for the cure to take effect.
- How long will that take?
- Best guess, a minute.
- It's gonna be damn near
impossible to hold him still
for one second,
much less 60.
- Okay, but we're so close.
I mean, there's...there's gotta
be something we can do,
even if we have to think
outside the box.
- I do have one more idea.
[mouse clicks, computer beeps]
Van Horn Industries
created a peaceful
anti-riot device
called a Neuro-Stasis
Field Generator.
It's basically a bio-EMP
that can immobilize
any living organism
within a confined radius.
Of course, the few devices
they had built were stolen.
I wouldn't even know where
to begin looking for them.
- I do.
Can you at least try
not to look so surprised?
Look, if we need this, uh,
Neo-Matrix whatever it is,
if it's stolen tech,
I think I know where to look.
- Earl Cox, Ralph says
you've got some information
that could help us.
- Well, turns out, that device
you're looking for
has been circulating in
the underground black market.
- Sounds like
Amunet Black's territory.
- Eh, Amunet's still MIA.
But believe it or not,
her ex-boyfriend
is filling the void.
You ever heard of Goldface?
- Yeah, he's stolen
more weaponized tech
than any criminal in the city.
CCPD's been looking
for his black market for years.
- Oh, aye, and they'll
keep on coming up empty.
You pay at the market,
and then poof,
your goods turn up a day later
in an abandoned warehouse.
- So by the time
we get what we want...
- Goldface will be long gone.
[whistles]
- Well, listen, uh,
thanks, Earl.
And, you know, try to eat
some fruit or something.
- Oh, will do.
Right, then, gents.
See you around.
Hopefully.
Just tell them
Big Raf sent you.
- Thanks for the tip, Earl.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
I know what you're thinking.
- We're supposed
to pay Goldface
and then just let him get away?
- Come on, you said we needed
to think outside the box.
- This is making a deal
with the devil.
- No, this is stopping Cicada.
Look, I don't like this
any more than you do,
but in some cases,
the ends justify the means.
And stopping a psychotic
meta-killer who we are
literally powerless against,
that's one of those cases.
- All right.
- What we are doing here?
- So Jitters has imported
a brand-new oolong tea,
and it's super rare and I
really want you to try it.
- Okay, look,
I'm busy right now.
I'm working, all right?
I don't have time for this.
- Well, what are you...
what are you working on?
- [sighs] Well,
I'm working on a mystery,
if you must know,
nosy Parker.
- Well, what kind of mystery?
- One that maybe I will
tell you before too long,
Nora West-Allen.
- Great, so, um,
let's grab a tea, then.
- All right, we'll have
one cup of tea.
To go.
- Tell me what to do.
- It's amazing how malleable
the timeline is.
Even the tiniest refinement
can birth a whole new reality,
an object above placed below.
♪ ♪
One path blocked
leads to a whole new one.
And if your timing is right,
everything falls into place.
♪ ♪
- Keep the change.
- Whoo! Oh!
Oh! [laughs]
Wow.
- Wow.
- That would have been
an embarrassing way to go.
My gosh.
Death by decaf.
- Flattened by flat white.
- [laughs]
- This woman is special.
Help him win her love,
and his attention moves
from you right onto her.
- Renée Adler.
- Ah, Miss Adler.
Sherloque Wells.
- Can I buy you a scone
or something to repay you
for saving my life?
- Scone? Yes, all night.
I mean yes.
- Great.
- Thank you very much.
- Um, uh...
- What we shall talk about
while we eat our scones,
I wonder?
- Oh.
- Maybe about, given your grace
and your posture,
your years of ballet training?
- Since I was four.
- Hmm.
- Wow, you're really
perceptive.
- Well, it's a modest talent,
I suppose.
- Notice anything else
about me?
- Challenge accepted.
Um, well, East Coast girl?
- Yes.
- From a small village,
maybe, um, by a bay?
Work with books?
A librarian?
At a university?
Live by a train station,
small split-level pad?
You, um, have a dog.
Older dog.
Corgi.
Anyway, about that scone...
- Okay, stay away from me.
- What?
- I don't know how long
you've been watching me,
but it ends now.
- No, no, no.
- Or I'm calling CCPD, stalker.
- No, uh, Miss Adler.
[sighs] I...
- Sherlock!
- Sherloque.
- Why did you say
all that stuff to her?
- You know,
skip the small talk, no?
- No.
- I have work to do.
- No, no, no, um, I just...I'm
not really a romance expert,
but I just feel like you
were really into her.
- [sighs]
Well, yes, maybe
a little into her.
- Okay, so don't give up
so fast, you know?
Maybe you could, um, try
to find a way to say I'm sorry
and I could help you with that.
- How could one say no to that?
- [chuckles]
- All right, we're approaching
the position.
- Copy. These are
the coordinates
of the black market.
Team Snow and Frost
are standing by for backup.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
What do we do now?
- I guess we say
the magic words.
The streets are
paved with gold.
♪ ♪
- Maybe you didn't
say it loud enou...
[both scream]
[both groan]
[computer beeping]
- Barry? Ralph?
[electrical buzzing]
- Uh...
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Meta cuffs?
- That's right,
power-dampening cuffs
fitted with an explosive charge
in case you're both metas.
So tell me, who sent you?
- That's really sweet.
Look how threatening
they're trying to be.
Boys, uh...
[clears throat]
We really appreciate all this,
but you can relax.
Big Raf sent us.
- [chuckles] Big Raf, huh?
All right, then.
Gentlemen,
welcome to the market.
♪ ♪
[laser blasts]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
- So nobody, including us,
knows where we are right now.
- And we are
totally powerless.
- Dude, if we make
the wrong move in here,
these cuffs are gonna be
the least of our worries.
- New game plan.
The antihero of our dynamic duo
will find the Field Generator.
And you're just gonna stay here
and try not to look like a cop.
Or a superhero.
- Okay.
- Or really anything
you actually are.
- Just go.
I'm fine.
- Hey.
You look like
a discerning consumer.
Might I interest you
in a little firepower?
- No, I'm good.
- Come to a weapons market
and you don't want any weapons?
- I said I'm good.
I'm here for something special.
- What's more special
than a CCPD killer?
- What do you mean?
- That's what's great
about these babies.
Burn through police-issued
body armor.
I call them toastmasters.
Try it for yourself.
♪ ♪
[laser blasts]
[laughs]
Can't wait to see cops' faces
when these hit the streets.
Or what's left of their faces.
♪ ♪
- How much for all of them?
- Uh, all of them?
There's a limit per customer.
I guess I could ask
Goldface for approval.
- No, why don't we just
work this out between us?
♪ ♪
How much will it cost to take
all these off your hands?
♪ ♪
[alarm beeping]
- Thank you for meeting
with me, Mr. Osmack.
- Oh, call me Brent.
And it's no problem.
Any interview about union
reform is time well spent.
- What about workers' opinions?
I imagine, as a manager,
you must get them all the time.
- Yeah, I know most of my guys
better than their wives.
[both chuckle]
- So I guess
it must be difficult
when one of them
surprises you.
Like that, um...that killer
that everyone's talking about,
Orlin Dwyer.
Did he ever say anything that
indicated how he was feeling
or what he was up to?
- No comment.
- Okay, well, did he give you
any kind of clue about
where he might be now?
- I said no comment.
- Did he threaten you?
Look, I know you're scared.
A lot of people were scared
when DeVoe attacked last year.
But the Flash defeated him,
partially because I wrote
these articles that encouraged
people to come forward
with information.
We can stop Dwyer.
[dramatic music]
- Okay, his paychecks
went to a P.O. box.
But there was a problem once,
and I had to forward
to his cousin's house.
Uh, his name was, uh,
Robbie something.
Robbie...Robbie Byrne.
- That's great.
[gun cocking]
- I'm telling you, man,
I don't have the authority
to okay a purchase that large.
- Uh, listen...
- Excuse me, um, Bartholomew,
a word?
- Just a word, yeah.
[suspenseful music]
- What the hell are you doing?
- Okay, this guy has got crates
of cop-killing guns.
Would you prefer
he sells them to criminals?
- I would prefer that you
not blow our cover,
and you're going
to blow our cover.
Come on, man,
I asked you to turn off
hero mode for, like,
ten minutes.
- Okay, all right, whatever.
Let's not argue
about this here, all right?
Did you find
the Field Generator?
- Of course I did.
But you're not gonna
like who has it.
- ♪ You see these
invisible borders ♪
♪ They keeping people apart
and they giving people ♪
♪ Important signs with God ♪
♪ I mean, I'm bored of that,
I'm bored as heck ♪
- What up? What up?
And welcome.
I hear something special
in my collection's
caught your attention.
- You heard right.
The Neuro-Stasis...
- Neuro-Stasis Field Generator?
It's a nasty bit of business,
if used properly.
- There's nothing proper about
the way we're gonna use it.
- My kind of people.
Okay. Let's chop it up.
Let's make a deal.
- [whispering indistinctly]
♪ ♪
- Look, we gonna do a deal
or what?
- Shut your mouth.
[ominous music]
Unless you wanna be one-handed.
[device beeping]
♪ ♪
Thought not.
See, here's the thing.
Scum recognizes scum.
I'm scum.
And I've survived this long
by recognizing the same.
Like you.
You're scum.
I sniffed you coming
a mile away.
- Thanks?
- But your partner,
I don't sniff nothing on him.
And that worries me.
So the question is...
♪ ♪
Who are you?
- Well, I can vouch for him.
He's just...
- I said shut your mouth!
[blow lands]
- [groans]
♪ ♪
- I wanna hear it from him.
[gun cocking]
- I'm only gonna ask once more.
Who are you?
[suspenseful music]
- I'm nobody.
No arrests.
No convictions.
Not for the Star City Museum
heist
where atomized lorazepam
knocked the guards out
or the acid bomb that blew open
the Federal Reserve
vault last month.
- That was you?
- Not according
to police reports.
Because the only evidence
I leave behind are red herrings
for idiot cops to chase down.
You wanna know who I am?
You can call me the Chemist.
But I really don't care
what you call me.
Just stop wasting my time.
♪ ♪
- You should let him
do the talking.
- Yeah, I get that a lot.
Uh, so we back in business?
♪ ♪
- With a twist.
Got a big job tonight.
Could use a guy
like the Chemist
to cover our tracks.
You help me get what I want,
I'll give you what you want.
- And what exactly
do you want?
- Ivo Labs has this
cutting-edge 3-D printer.
Sold it to some hospital.
- What's so special
about a 3-D printer?
- This one prints
artificial organs.
If I've got it, I can sell
life to the highest bidder.
- You want us
to rob a hospital?
- Of course not.
I'm not a monster.
I want you to rob the lab
before it ever gets
to the hospital.
Smile, boys.
Tonight you're working
for Goldface.
♪ ♪
[knocking at door]
[lock clicking]
[hinge creaking]
♪ ♪
- Best birthday present ever,
Ralph.
♪ ♪
[keys jangling,
door clicks]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[groans]
[pills rattling]
♪ ♪
[soft tap]
[computer beeping]
- [sighs]
-Allô!
- Oh, good, you're here.
So since you let me agree to
help you with your love life...
- Right.
- I came up with
an unusual idea.
- Spectacular.
- Mm-hmm.
I have asked your
ex-wives for help.
- Great. What?
- Five women married you
for a reason.
So who better to ask why
they fell in love with you
than them?
- Okay, except...
- I didn't think any
of them would agree,
but four of them actually
jumped at the chance.
- Of course they did.
- Mm-hmm.
- Because I owe them money.
I'm behind on all
the alimony payments,
and they don't know what
Earth I'm on, until now.
- What?
- That's right.
[electronic beeping]
[playful dramatic music]
- Hello, Detective.
- Hello,chérie.
- You married the same
woman seven times?
- Well, she's the one for me.
- Darling, you can't
run forever.
We'll always find you.
- You're in violation
of alimony order 1152.
- Time to pay up!
- Ladies.
- We know you had Superman
deliver your alimony
to your ex on Earth-38.
- [laughs] What?
- You think we don't all talk?
- I was hoping
they don't all talk.
- Oh, no, we talk.
We get together all the time.
- We have to talk.
- Oh, we do.
Except I can never
get you on the phone.
- I text.
- Mm.
- Look, I understand.
You want your money, right?
So maybe we can...maybe we can
come to an agreement, hmm?
- We had an agreement,
one that you're currently
in breach of.
- Uh...
- Uh, ladies.
[laughs]
Ladies, just a big
misunderstanding here.
- Big misunderstanding.
- I thought you were all
coming here
to help Sherloque.
- Sherloque.
- [laughs]
- Help him?
You can't help a man who
thinks he knows everything.
- Yeah, like the time clues led
him to believe it'd be romantic
to release fruit bats
at our wedding.
- It's because she support
the endangered species,
so I say fruit bat.
[mimics wings flapping]
I do.
I was being thoughtful.
- Oh, for our anniversary,
he bought me a puppy dog.
- That's...that's not really...
That's kind of nice.
- Thank you.
- I am deathly allergic
to puppy dogs.
The dander makes my throat
just...[mimics choking]
- It's true, but studies
show that more exposure
to the allergens, it builds up
your immune system,
so I'm trying to give you
a healthy life.
Again, thoughtful on my part.
- Well, at least he didn't
deduce that the nicest way
to break up with you
was to fake his own death.
- Ooh.
- Not so thoughtful.
- Twice!
- Oh, that last one
really was on you, dear.
- Yeah, seriously.
Look, there's gonna be
a real death here
if you don't pay us
our money back next month
with interest.
- We know where you are now.
- Plus, we got a great
alimony recovery agent
by the name of Breacher.
- Breacher?
- Ticktock, Sherlock.
[kisses]
- Sherloque.
Where you're going?
- Oh, I like how you say it.
- I don't mean
to sound heartless,
but, darling, not everyone
is meant for a relationship.
Some people are just
destined to be alone.
[electronic beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Sherloque, I...
[sighs]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- We roll out in five.
Look, uh, I don't have
to ask you
how you feel about this.
Stealing from a hospital,
that's...[scoffs]
That's way more
than we bargained for.
So if you don't want
to do this, I'm...
- I'll do it.
- You will?
- Yeah, what choice do I have?
You warned me to get my head
on straight for this job,
and I didn't.
You had Goldface ready
to give us what we needed,
and I blew it trying to get
those guns off the street,
and here we are.
- Barry,
this is not your fault.
- Yeah, it is.
And you were right.
If I wanna stop Cicada,
I can't be so precious
about getting
the Flash's hands dirty.
Sometimes the ends
justify the means.
I get that now.
Let's just get this over with.
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
[door creaking]
♪ ♪
- Who the hell are you?
- Sorry, um, the door
was unlocked.
I'm a reporter.
I'm...
Uh, I'm looking for the owner,
Robbie Byrne.
[door creaks]
♪ ♪
- I'm Robbie.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- So...
what kind of story you writing?
- It's an investigative
report about
lead leaking into
the water pipes
in this neighborhood.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
Um, yeah.
And it would be, um, very
helpful if you could answer
a few questions for me.
- All right.
But I haven't noticed
anything strange in the water.
- That's the scary thing
about lead.
I mean, the first sign
would probably be a trip
to the hospital.
Young children are
especially susceptible.
Do you have a daughter?
♪ ♪
- I used to.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
And what about you?
- Me?
I'm feeling better than ever.
- Well, lead poisoning
can present itself
in a variety of ways.
- Look, it's late.
And I've got to get
to bed soon, so...
- Of course, Mr. Byrne.
I understand.
Um, I still have
a few more questions.
I mean, I could always come
to your office tomorrow,
if you like.
Would you prefer I see you
tomorrow, then?
- No.
Let's finish this now.
♪ ♪
[machine humming]
- Making tea?
- No, making an espresso
because the mind
needs more caffeine.
- Um, that's just hot water.
- No, no, it...
[sighs]
Nom de Dieu.
- Sherloque, you know
that stuff your ex-wife said
isn't true, right?
- No, I'm destined to be alone.
- [sighs]
No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
- Listen.
You treat love like it's
a mystery that can be solved.
But you can't deduce your way
to a happy ending.
You just have to let it come
one step at a time
and enjoy whatever step
you're in.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[engines revving]
♪ ♪
- Okay, listen up.
[guns cocking]
Get in, get out.
Our guy on the inside
said the place is empty,
and you all have the code
and the pass cards.
Switch your weapons from stun
to meet your maker.
[guns beeping]
Let's go.
- Go.
♪ ♪
- Barry, let me check
your rifle.
I think it needs a new clip.
- What?
- Left my phone in there.
Can you check for me?
- We gotta...
- Clear.
- Move, move, move.
- Ralph, there's no phone, man.
There's...
[door slams]
What are you doing?
Hey, hey!
What are you...Ralph!
- You're right, Barry.
Flash doesn't have to do this.
- What?
- But I can.
- Ralph.
Hey, hey!
Ralph, let me out!
I can back you up, man!
Don't go alone!
Ralph!
Ralph.
I can have your back, man!
Don't go alone!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Where's the Chemist?
- He said something about us
leaving an orgy of evidence
in the truck.
He's handling it.
♪ ♪
- All right,
fan out and search.
[device beeps]
Signal back when you find it.
♪ ♪
- Hey, anonymous
criminal colleague,
this is it.
♪ ♪
Kind of overkill
with the packaging.
♪ ♪
Yo, this ain't a library, man.
You wanna give me a hand?
- Yeah, how about two?
[blows landing]
[body thuds]
Sorry, not sorry, pal.
This baby's going
to a hospital.
- Honestly, I never liked you.
Take this trash out
to the truck for disposal.
And his friend too.
- Come on, come on.
♪ ♪
All right, let's pack it up.
Chop-chop.
♪ ♪
[blow lands]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
- Brick!
- Ralph!
- [groans]
- Oh!
- Well, thank you,
but for the record,
I meant throw the brick to me.
- I was trying
to throw it to you.
[groans] I see you couldn't
go through with it either.
- Not after I saw
those little kids.
Carver's in there
with the printer.
There's a lot of guns.
We don't have any powers.
- But these do have
a stun setting.
Come on.
[Rob Zombie's "Dragula"]
[guns cocking]
- All in a day's work, people.
- Cover me!
- Break, break, break!
- Go! Watch it!
- Go, go, go, go!
- ♪ Slipping through
the trees ♪
♪ Strangling the breeze ♪
- Where'd that come from?
- I tripped.
- Let's get that printer.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Dead, I am the sky ♪
♪ Watching angels cry ♪
♪ While they slowly turn,
conquering the worm ♪
♪ Dig through the ditches ♪
♪ And burn
through the witches ♪
♪ I slam in the back
of my Dragula ♪
♪ Dig through the ditches ♪
- Barry!
[blows landing]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Don't move!
- ♪ Spreading from the fool ♪
♪ Weak and want you need ♪
♪ Nowhere as you bleed ♪
- [screams]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Dead I am the rat,
feast upon the cat ♪
♪ Tender is the fur,
dying as you purr ♪
[glass shattering]
♪ Dig through the ditches ♪
♪ And burn
through the witches ♪
♪ I slam in the back
of my Dragula ♪
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[all groaning]
- I knew all that "Red Dead"
would pay off.
[devices beeping]
♪ ♪
[radio crackles]
- Good help's so hard to find.
Both of you, loading dock.
Now.
- Go.
♪ ♪
- Good boys.
I was hoping you wouldn't
make Daddy use his belt.
♪ ♪
Since you obeyed me,
I'm not gonna
blow your arms off.
I'm gonna kill you
in a more traditional way.
And I prom...
[grunts]
[lasers blasting]
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
He really should have
frisked us first.
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
[groaning]
See, that's the thing...
my gold...
♪ ♪
It don't just make me
look pretty.
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
[metallic thud]
- [grunts]
[groaning]
[blow lands]
[crashing]
- [shouts]
[blow lands]
[both grunting]
- [panting]
- [grunts]
[whip cracking]
[whip cracks]
[both grunting]
- [grunting]
All right, Goldie Hawn.
Let's do this.
[whip cracks]
[choking]
- Since I'm going into
the organ donor business,
you'll be happy to know
that your corpse is going
to a good cause:
making me rich.
- [choking]
♪ ♪
- Hey!
Why you so mad at him?
He's not the one that made you
fall for a fake backstory.
[whip cracks]
- [gasping]
- Goldface, huh?
More like Fool's Gold.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[whip cracks]
[electricity buzzing]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Good thing he didn't know
this wasn't loaded.
- [breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
- He's alive.
- Yeah, and so are we.
Thanks to you.
The Chemist?
♪ ♪
- Well, I, um...
I should get going.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- You didn't have that bag
when you came in here.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[spraying]
[screams]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[shouting]
[glass shattering]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
[both shouting]
[grunts]
- [screams]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
- We're gonna beat you.
- [groaning]
[dramatic music]
- Well, you got
pretty banged up,
but your powers are already
working their magic.
No signs of permanent damage.
- Guess the only real loss
today was our mission.
- Yeah.
- No, we'll find another way
to get the Field Generator.
And besides, we did have
another win today.
We took down a powerful
meta-human without our powers.
That's a good reminder that
even when Cicada dampens us,
we have other ways to fight.
[cell phone buzzing]
Hello?
Iris?
[whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
Dwyer's gone.
I'll get Iris.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- I got nothing in here.
- Ditto upstairs.
- Yeah, there's
no evidence here
that points to where he went.
- Did you find that
device you needed?
♪ ♪
Maybe we don't need it.
[exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
I know how to give
the cure to Cicada.
♪ ♪
I know his weakness.
- Uh,pardon.
May I offer you a refill?
- Oh, God.
- No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need to tell you something.
Don't be alarmed.
I am not a stalker.
I'm a detective.
This is how I knew
all these facts about you.
I deduced them.
It's immodest to say, but I
happen to be quite good at it.
- Prove it.
-Pardon?
- Show me.
Do, um...
[pop music playing]
Do that guy.
♪ ♪
- Challenge accepted.
- Great.
- So if you look at the size
of his drink,
small relative
to his body mass.
And the hesitation but also
the enjoyment with which
he consumes his beverage,
it's elementary.
This is a man
who has a dairy allergy
but still prefers
to drink milk lattes,
but not without consequence.
Oh, wait for it.
And...
- [groaning]
- Oh.
-Et voilà.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Mm.
- You are really good at this.
- What can I say?
It is a modest talent.
But I must apologize for...
how do they say...
creeping you out.
But if perhaps you would allow
yourself to forgive me,
then I could buy you a tea
to make it up to you.
- Well, I have to go
to work now.
- Ah, all right, no.
- But...but I...
- Yes, of course.
- You can call me sometime.
- Really?
- [laughs]
- Well...
[soft music]
Ah,merci.
- Mm.
- I look forward to,
um, sometime.
- Me too.
- Mm. So...
- Thanks.
Whoa, oh!
[glass shatters]
- Oh, you all right?
- Oh, gosh.
I guess I should have
started ballet
when I was
three, right?
- Of course, yes.
- Whoo!
Okay, bye.
-Au revoir, Miss Adler.
♪ ♪
Ah, you're amazing.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
You're a meta.
Computer on.
♪ ♪
Close Nora West-Allen file.
Open Cicada casework.
[computer beeping]
[sighs]
All right.
♪ ♪
He will not harm you.
[whooshing]
- [sighs]
- If your mission
is successful,
your secret is safe.
And you and I are free
to continue what we started.
- Greg, move your head.