BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash and Arrow...
The person who broke into my facility
last night was Harrison Wells.
Dr. Caitlin Snow, Cisco Ramon,
meet Dr. Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
I came hereto help you, Barry.
He may not be
Harrison Wells from your Earth.
He has just as many secrets
as the one you knew.
I get these feelings sometimes.
These vibes.
I'm not sure what triggers it.
And sometimes itjust happens.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
OLIVER: You can always talk to me.
- Partners?
- Partners.
This is a million dollars.
That money is yours, once you tell Oliver
that you've lost the baby.
BARRY: I've been running a lot lately,
trying to go faster than
I've ever gone before,
because there's someone out there
who's better,
faster and stronger than I am.
And I need to be ready.
But no matter how much I try,
or how hard I push myself,
I keep running into the same problem.
He just hit 1,375.
What's the fastest Barry's run?
Little over Mach 2,
when he ran back in time.
That's not good.
That's good, Barry.
We have our work cut out for us.
I'm not getting faster, am I?
- Well...
- No. You're not.
All right. Well, let's fix this, right?
I mean, I can't beat Zoom at this speed.
It felt like I was standing still
next to him.
Oh, that's because you practically were.
Zoom is at least three,
four times faster than you at this point.
How is he so much faster than Barry is,
and Jay was?
Physiology, form, strength.
Could be a number of things.
Attitude, diet...
Okay. Well, there's gotta be
something we can do about it.
- So, let'sjust figure it out. Fast. Okay?
- (PHONE BUZZING)
All right, I gotta go. I'm meeting Patty.
I'll see you. Thank you.
So how are we gonna help Barry?
I'm out of ideas, and we've tried
everything you suggested.
Well, not everything.
(RATTLING)
POLICE CHIEF: Welcome home.
Any trouble?
Nah. But believe it or not,
we got ourselves a stowaway.
POLICE CHIEF: Give you his name?
Didn't say.
Sat in the brig silent for three weeks.
He was all decked out in this
when we found him.
POLICE CHIEF: Jeez. How many are there?
Thirty-two. And I will polish them all
in blood before long.
I've waited a long time for this hunt,
and you have brought me
very close to my prey.
Mister, you're not gonna do
any hunting in those handcuffs.
Oh, but, Captain,
you're wearing the cuffs.
(GRUNTS)
Who taught you that? Houdini?
Actually, I taught him.
(GRUNTING)
Soon, another sacrifice will be made.
I feel you out there.
Man, this was a bloodbath.
Done by one person.
One person did all this?
Oh, yeah. You can see
from the blood pattern.
This guy was shot first,
then the Police Chief,
then these three were stabbed,
before finishing off the Captain.
Wow! Do you think a meta-human did it?
I don't know, but I found this
in all of the stab victims' wounds.
It's some type of cryptocrystalline.
Flint, most likely. Probably broke off
the blade during the fight.
I'll run it to make sure.
Let's see what stores
sell those kind of flint knives.
Will do. And I'll call you later.
- Okay.
It's so cute. You guys are trying
not to be affectionate in front of me.
No. We're just showing
some professionalism.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
- Advantages of a trusting manager.
- (CHUCKLES)
Ah! A lot's gone down in this place.
Nice.
So what's up?
I thought we were gonna go to dinner.
Whoa. What's going on here?
I couldn't decide
which restaurant to go to,
so I thought we would create our own.
Voila'! Short rib,
Yukon gold puree and asparagus.
Gotta have a vegetable.
This is nice.
I like to cook. I didn't know if you like
red or white, so I got you both.
Ooh! Two bottles.
That's kind of dangerous, don't you think?
You're not gonna run away
all of a sudden, are you?
Trust me, I'm staying by your side
as long as possible.
Good.
You know, it's been really great
hanging out these last few weeks.
And it's helped make the move
a lot easier, so thanks.
You're very welcome.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Sorry. How did you get in here?
Hey, man, this place is closed.
You are just as beautiful in this life
as any other, Priestess Chay-Ara.
Priestess?
Uh, you gonna have to go, dude.
Not without her, dude.
Oh, my God! Cisco.
I don't understand. What do you want?
I believe I was clear.
(TRILLING)
Kendra's not going anywhere with you,
Highlander.
Oh, is that your name now?
Kendra? Quite boring.
I believe it allowed you
to blend in for a while.
Now, give her to me
and I'll make your death fast.
It ain't gonna happen.
You are done here, pal.
So is he.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Thank God, Barry.
Dude. Come on.
I can't believe you're the Flash.
And that you work with the Flash.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah. Let's keep that on the DL.
This is the same knife that was used
to kill the men at the docks.
The residue's a perfect match.
So it is the same guy.
Definitely. But the thing is,
these blades are old. Centuries old.
Do you have any idea why this guy
would be after you?
No. I've never seen him before in my life.
Well, he was certainly
acting like he knew you.
He kept calling her Priestess Chay-Ara.
That's Coptic.
- You mean Egyptian?
- That's right.
Well, I grew up in Wisconsin
and I've never even left the States, so...
This guy, he's clearly
incredibly dangerous.
So I need you to at least
let us try to protect you.
I can put a detail on her.
You didn't see this guy, Joe.
No offense, but I don't think
a cop is gonna be able to protect her.
No, but we do have a few friends
who can lend a hand.
But we're gonna need
to leave Central City.
And go where?
You really wanna go to Star City?
Come on! We don't need
Team Arr0w's help.
Yeah, I think we do, man.
Man, you fought meta-humans with abilities
a lot worse than "knife-throwing."
I don't think this guy's a meta-human.
There's something different about him.
Something mystical.
Mystical, really?
We stop meta-humans
because we're scientists.
We can figure out
what their weaknesses are.
But we don't have any experience
when it comes to guys like this.
- With magic. They do.
- Mmm!
This wouldn't have anything
to do with Zoom, would it?
No. I'm just trying to keep Kendra safe.
This is the best way to do that.
Right. Okay. I'm with you.
But how do we even know Oliver and them
even have time to help us?
How busy can they be?
(CHOKING)
Oh, gosh, that's fun.
I really could do this all day.
Open it up.
They could have at least tried
to hide this chemical bomb.
Serves them right it's getting stolen
and used against them.
- (GUNS COCKING)
- Ah!
You brought arrows to a gun fight.
What guns?
DARH KI Oh!
That was actually pretty clever.
Kill them.
(IMITATING OLIVER) "Felicity, the magnetic
arrow gag will never work."
(CHUCKLES) "Yes, it will, my love,
because I am really smart."
And guess what, Oliver? lt did work.
OLIVER: Felicity? Honey?
It's a little hard to fight with you
doing that in my ear.
Oh, I totally forgot that
this was an open line.
Keep doing what you're doing.
Make smart decisions.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Ooh, you know, I gotta be honest,
I really thought we'd be doing this dance
a lot longer. Night, night.
(LAUGHS)
What was that?
(DIGGLE RETCHING)
Damn it. Every time.
It's the Flash!
Did I know we knew the Flash?
We know the Flash. Okay.
I didn't know we knew the Flash.
Thank you. But I don't think that
you ran all the way here to protect us.
No, not to protect you.
I need to protect a friend.
Wow!
Nice new digs.
Also, I Just noticed, no sleeves.
Don't you get cold?
I spent the better part of five years on
an island near the North China Sea.
I don't get cold, Barry.
Barry! So good to see you.
Felicity.
Oh! Good to see you, Felicity.
How come you didn't tell me
Zoom broke your back?
- I...
- (EXCLAIMS)
I'm so glad you're okay.
So this is what it's like dating her.
More bruises from her
than from Deathstroke.
Okay. S.T.A.R. Labs is impressive,
but this is...
This is completely wrong.
Did you guys even look
at the specs I sent over?
This is a tragedy. I'm mourning
for the death of engineering.
Copper wiring to handle
the processing speed
from the Palmer Satellite
or else your system is gonna overload.
Yeah, but that hasn't happened
since last week.
I mean, it didn't...
It happened yesterday.
- Hi.
- I'm Felicity.
I'm Kendra Saunders. I'm Cisco's...
She's my new beautiful friend,
who kisses me, occasionally.
- That's nice.
- (CLEARING THROAT)
Right. I'm Thea. This is John Diggle.
And my brother.
Oliver Queen.
- Hi.
- Wow.
Okay, first, I meet the Flash,
and now, the Green Arrow.
- Do you have any other surprises for me?
- (CHUCKLES)
Please. No more surprises.
Barry said that you need our help.
Somebody very dangerous is after you.
Yeah, and I have no idea why.
What's does this guy even look like?
Uh... Hold on.
(CLEARS THROAT) Okay. This is him.
Yeah. See, that's something
I would never think of.
Hmm, kinda rockin'
that Dothraki look. Hot.
Let's see if facial recognition
can find a match.
(BEEPING)
That's him.
Yeah, strange.
This picture's from 1975.
Which would make him about
80 years old right now.
Okay, what else can you tell us?
He said we've known each other for ages,
but I've never met the man before.
But there has to be
some kind of a connection.
Not one I can think of.
I just moved to Central City,
six months ago.
Why'd you move there?
I just felt drawn to the city, I guess.
Kendra, there is a reason
this guy's after you. Think.
Look, man, we just came out here
to hide out for a bit
until we figure things out, so you can
just take it down just a little.
You came here because you need our help.
This is what my help looks like.
Oliver, I just saved you guys
from whatever the hell Flock of Seagulls
was about to do.
The least you can do is just...
Barry, none of us have superpowers.
You brought Kendra into our world
without knowing who she is
or what this dude
that is after her is looking for.
You made all of us unsafe.
So maybe you ask the questions.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- We're all friends here, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
Why don't we go back to our place
and have some drinks,
and we can talk.
Cool.
What you working on?
This is a formula meant to increase
a speedster's velocity
that I've been developing
since Zoom showed up on my Earth.
Ironically, this was meant
to help out Jay Garrick.
You want to give Barry a drug
to make him run faster?
Temporarily enhance the Speed Force
in his system, yes.
So you're trying to make
nitrous oxide for speedsters.
Good analogy. Yes, I tried.
Five times I've tried,
five times I've failed.
That's what you get when your background
is technology and not biochemistry.
- Well, then you are lucky I am here.
- What does that mean?
You've been thinking of this
as a mechanical problem,
not a biomechanical one.
And what does that mean?
When a speedster runs, they consume
an extraordinary amount of oxygen.
So we just need something to give
an extra boost of oxygen during that time.
- Like an oxygen generator.
- Exactly!
So we just need
a chemical that's rich in oxygen,
that would release it as a nearly pure gas
as it decomposes.
- Something like sodium chlorate.
- Sodium chlorate.
Then, all we need is heat
to release the oxygen.
Which a speedster generates naturally
in the form of lightning.
I think something like this
just might work.
You think you can help me figure it out?
I can certainly try.
I'm not changing my nickname.
I like Speedy.
CISCO: Are you familiar
with my body of work?
If you are, then you know I can come up
with something so much
better than "Speedy."
Why don't you get a haircut,
and then maybe we can talk about it.
I think you just mad 'cause
my conditioner game is on point.
So, the CEO of Palmer Technologies
is living with Oliver Queen.
It's insane how much
life can change in six months, huh?
Which you would know better than anyone,
considering that there's another Flash,
- another Dr. Wells, from another Earth?
- Mmm-hmm.
- I mean...
- Yeah. I know. It's been trippy lately.
I wonder what Oliver's doppelganger
would look like. Bald. Pot-bellied.
- Uh-huh.
- Agreeable.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You seeing anyone?
- I am, actually.
- Good.
Patty is her name. She is amazing.
- You deserve someone amazing.
- Thanks.
- (BELL DINGS)
- (GASPS)
My pigs in a blanket.
Hey, Ollie. Look, I'm sorry
that I laid all of this on you.
- I know that it wasn't fair.
- (SIGHS) That's okay.
- I'm sorry if earlier I was a little...
- Snippy?
- I have been called worse.
- (CHUCKLES)
No, but I'm glad that you're here.
I'm glad you reached out.
It shows a real maturity. And I would know
that because I've never been that mature.
(LAUGHS)
I'm always here for you.
Thank you.
I gotta say, I mean, this isn't the same
Arrow team I'm used to seeing.
Or the same Oliver Queen.
You seem really...
- Happy?
- Hapr>y. Yeah.
I am happy. I finally have everything
that I've ever wanted.
Being with Felicity has given me
a real sense of peace.
It's something that I haven't had
in a long time.
Didn't you tell me that guys like us
don't get the girl?
Yep. I was wrong.
(LAUGHS)
I would like to propose a toast.
I wish it wasn't just the dark times
bringing us together.
But it is friends like you
that make those dark times worth having.
(CHUCKLES) What a guy!
Steals my drink, steals my words.
As I was saying,
it's good to see everyone.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- Mmm.
Look, don't worry, all right?
We're gonna keep her safe. I promise.
Yeah. I know.
Look, there's something I never told you.
The first time I kissed Kendra,
I got a vibe.
No, not like that kind of vibe.
- Like I vibed-vibed.
- Oh!
Remember the man with wings?
It wasn't a man.
It was Kendra.
And she was, like, a bird.
You think that she's a meta-human?
(MUMBLING UNCERTAINTY)
Wait, why didn't you say anything
about this sooner?
Well, I didn't think it was related,
but I guess, now, it has to be.
Look, I don't, I don't want her
to know about my powers.
I have this great thing going with her.
And she laughs at myjokes,
and she loves movies, and...
I just...
I've never felt like this before,
and I don't want to sabotage it.
I get the feeling.
Look!
I will always find you, Chay-Ara.
Don't move!
Then how will I kill you all?
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Yeah, I can do that too.
(GROANING)
Thea, no!
What did you do?
I ended it.
This is why we ask questions!
- Where did he go? Oh, boy.
- Oh, boy.
(SIGHS)
Okay. Thanks.
All right. Lance is gonna call if he gets
any information on whoever that is.
I know where we can get some info.
Kendra, I have powers.
I get these vibes from people,
they're visions of meta-humans.
And I had one of you.
So, A, you're saying you're a meta-human,
and B, she's a meta-human?
I don't know. In these visions,
you could fly.
It was like you were a bird of some sort.
- A bird?
- Yeah.
(STUTTERS) What else did you see?
That's it. Just you with wings.
Oh! I did not see that one coming.
(FELICITY GASPS)
Oh, I think there's a lot
you didn't see coming.
Great. More surprises.
Who the hell is this?
That's my dad.
(COMPUTER TRILLING)
(SIGHS)
I think I did it.
What do you know, Snow.
I think you did do it.
- Velocity-Six?
- Ah!
This is what was so urgent, Harrison?
You get me to come here
so I can take your speed drug?
- That's right.
- You knew about this?
- Of course she did. She figured it out.
- Uh...
I thought this was to help Barry.
It is to help Barry. Which is why we need
to do test runs on subjects
who once had the Speed Force
in their system.
Speed Force doesn't work like that.
It's not something
you can create in a lab.
How do you think you became
the Flash, Garrick?
By me and a lab. Science is what
did this to you, to Barry, to Zoom.
And science is what we need to stop Zoom,
and this is our only option.
Find another one! Speed Force
can't be replicated or enhanced.
It's a living thing.
It's a gift that was given to me.
That drug, you have no idea
what it's gonna do.
I'm not letting another one of your
experiments mess with me again.
You find someone else
to be your guinea pig.
Jay!
Caitlin, keep that serum away from Barry.
- Where are you going?
- To pick up what we need.
Wait! Jayjust said
we shouldn't give it to Barry.
We're gonna do what we need.
The man you're looking for
is Vandal Savage.
- Vandal Savage? Never heard of him.
- Well, who is he?
Some say he was the most trusted adviser
to Genghis Khan.
Others say he guided Julius Caesar
through the Gallic Wars.
But one thing the League knows for sure,
he was there for all of it.
So what are you saying?
He's like a vampire or something?
Not a vampire. An Immortal.
Okay, we've officially stepped
into crazy town. Immortality?
But wait, no, no, no. This makes sense.
This explains why he looks the same
as he did in 1975.
This can't be possible.
There's nothing you can do
to save her now.
Kendra, do not listen to him.
I just need some air.
Hey. We are gonna do whatever we have to
to keep Kendra safe.
Whether you think we can or not.
Hey, Joe, it's Patty.
I just interviewed a weapons expert
about the flint knife our attacker used.
I found out something pretty interesting.
So, call me back.
Harrison Wells?
(PANTING) Kendra! Hey.
- You gonna be all right?
- This is a lot to take in right now.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry
I didn't tell you about me before.
I didn't want things to be
different between us.
It's not that, Cisco.
If what everyone's saying is true,
and it's beginning to seem like it is,
my whole life just changed.
And I am so not ready for that.
I hear what you're saying. I do.
When I first learned about my powers,
I remember feeling
that exact same feeling.
And sometimes, I still feel that way.
And all I can say is,
every day gets a little bit more normal.
I promise you.
Thank you.
You're so welcome.
(KENDRA YELLS)
- Kendra.
- Let me go!
Guys, did you find anything?
- I'm on it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! This is my house.
Don't worry. We're gonna find her.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Wow.
You look as beautiful as ever.
Chay-Ara, it's me, Khufu.
Do you remember? Look at me.
You need to wake up.
What are you talking about?
I don't know who you are.
You will once you emerge.
Until then, you need to stay by my side
so that I can protect you.
Protect me? From what?
The man who is hunting you. Vandal Savage.
I got 'em! 57th Street tower.
ARROW: I'm right near there.
Always a pleasure
watching you work, Smoak.
- Yeah!
- Mmm!
- Ah!
- That was pitiful.
I know this is a lot to take in,
but you sort ofjust
kinda have to trust me on this.
I... (EXHALES) Just one second.
Stay right there.
ARROW: I got eyes on 'em.
Give me the girl!
Not gonna do that, Robin Hood.
- You're making a big mistake.
- I'll take my chances.
(GRUNTING)
Barry! Change of venue.
Birdman and Oliver are at
54th and Motor now. Hurry!
On my way!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
We need to expose his wings.
I'm open to suggestions.
What, now you're listening to me?
It's your city, Oliver.
All right.
(GROANING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
- That's new.
- (CHUCKLES)
Yeah. Comes in handy.
We can't use that serum on Barry.
That's up to him, isn't it?
If Barry wants to stop Zoom,
this is what he needs.
Jay said it could hurt Barry.
Well, Jay's a coward.
Jay's a scientist
who knows a lot about speedsters.
You're a scientist, Snow.
You've been watching Barry, you know
he's nowhere near fast as he needs to be.
This other mentor,
this other Harrison Wells,
did not want him to reach
his full potential. ldo.
You know, you're really starting
to sound a lot like him.
PATTY: Put your hands in the air.
- Who are you?
- You're under arrest.
Dr. McGee was right. She did see you.
- Christina McGee?
- At Mercury Labs. You're Harrison Wells.
Yes, I'm Harrison Wells.
I'm not the Harrison Wells...
Stop! You move closer and I'll shoot!
Give me that...
(GASPS)
Oh, my God! What have you done?
Harrison! Harrison Wells, stay with me.
Harrison. Harrison, stay with me.
Stay with me, Harrison Wells. Come on.
Why did you shoot him?
I thought that was a gun.
I'm sorry. I'll call 911.
- No! Don't!
- Why?
Because this...
Didn't Joe West explain this to you?
- No.
- Just call Joe!
Okay.
(GRUNTING)
Where is she?
- What's your name?
- You're putting her in danger
and I'm the only one
capable of saving her.
A very interesting perspective
on what the word "saving" means.
She's the love of my lifetimes,
sweetheart.
I was not gonna hurt her.
You need to let me go!
Chay-Ara...
My name is Kendra Saunders.
In this life.
And I am, was Carter Hall.
But that is not who we are.
What does that mean?
You're Priestess Chay-Ara,
I'm Prince Khufu.
And we're lovers, soul mates.
We've been partners
for 4,000 years.
We're drawn to each other in each life,
and after we die,
we reincarnate to find each other again,
and again, and again.
And now that I've found you,
we should really get out of here.
Okay, Romeo,
why don't you pump the brakes?
These people cannot protect you
from Savage any longer.
D0 you know who Vandal Savage is?
In every lifetime,
he hunts us down and kills us.
He's done it 206 times.
And I'm not planning to make it 207.
Why does he kill you?
His life force is tethered to ours.
Every time he kills us,
he becomes more powerful. You do the math.
You're 0 for 206,
and you still think
you're her best bet, hmm?
Okay, so what we need to do
is just find Savage and get rid of him.
(SCOFFS) Well,
you can't get rid of him, my friend.
Oh, yeah? Watch us.
It might be harder than you think.
(STUTTERS) ls that the only way
this guy knows how to enter a room?
My associates tell me
Savage left Star City a few hours ago.
For where?
We're not quite sure. But I assume
after his run in with you,
he realized he needed something
more powerful to complete his mission.
(SCOFFS) Well...
We think he's trying to locate
the Staff of Horus.
Sorry, what is that?
It's a relic from our past.
An ancient and powerful weapon.
If Savage gets his hands on it, it's gonna
be nearly impossible to stop him.
Since when did our lives suddenly become
an Indiana Jones movie?
- Felicity? Think you can find it?
- Yeah.
Yes. It's probably at some
museum somewhere.
I'll work my magic.
See what I can find.
We're running out of time.
You need to emerge, now. Come on.
What is it going to take for you
to believe me? You saw my wings.
I know you know this is true.
Please, just let me show you how.
- How's he doing?
- He's losing oxygen.
- I need you to leave.
- Joe, I...
Patty, go.
There's a bullet in a branch
of his pulmonary artery
that's blocking off most of the blood flow
from the left lung.
Are we able to get the bullet out?
Not without causing too much damage.
I need Jay's help.
So,
you just want me to jump?
Fall, jump, swan dive,
whatever suits you. Just, do it.
Okay. This isn't the X Games.
OLIVER: And this is how she emerges?
She just falls towards her death?
Yep. 4,000 years of experience
says that's exactly how.
Just watch and learn.
No, I'm sorry. What are we doing?
Why are we listening to this guy?
Come on, Oliver. You're supposed to be
the one who asks questions.
Okay, but after what we saw,
after what Cisco said,
I cannot believe I'm gonna say this,
but it kinda makes sense.
Hey, hey, hey.
I need to try.
Are you serious?
- Yes, she is.
- (GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
What the hell was that?
Saving her life. You should have emerged.
Something is blocking you.
Well, we should just try again
and see...
- No!
- Yeah, no! No, no, no.
No. We're not doing that again.
Kendra, you don't have to do this.
Oliver, we can stop Savage, okay?
- Barry!
- What?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Okay.
Keep an eye on him.
What is going on with you?
I'm trying to keep her alive.
- Then I think we let herjump.
- Are you kidding?
Barry, I get that you're desperate to help
and you want to be the hero,
and you wanna save her yourself.
But I think she has to have
a part in it, too.
(SCOFFS)
- What?
- Lt'sjust the rules keep changing.
One day, I have to run through time,
the next,
I'm fighting a telepathic gorilla.
(STUTTERING) And now, we're what?
We're, we're chasing down
an immortal madman
on a rampage against
a reincarnated warrior Priestess?
(BOTH SIGH)
I Just never thought I'd have superpowers
and feel more powerless
than I ever have in my entire life.
That part, I understand.
But you have already helped Kendra.
You have kept her alive.
So now, let's help her get her wings,
and then she can give you
a lift back to Central City.
- Central City.
- What?
We need to check Central City
for the staff.
- Kendra, you said you were drawn there?
- Yeah.
I think you're drawn to things
that destroy you,
the same way the two of you
are drawn to each other.
That's why it wasn't in any museum
or private collection,
because it was consecrated eight months
ago at St. Mark's in Central City.
We've gotta get it before Savage does.
Carter, stay here.
I'm not going anywhere.
Call Thea and Dig and we'll have them hold
down the fort in case Savage shows up.
Kendra, last year, I lost my powers.
The only way I could get them back is
if I just forgot about everything
happening around me,
and focused on who I was.
Just believe in yourself,
and your true selfwill emerge.
Thanks.
Hey. Are you sure that
you want to do this?
If this guy's immortal and Merlyn's right
about how powerful this staff is...
We'll be fine. Kiss her.
We'll be fine.
- Careful.
- Let's go.
Now what?
His systolic pressure's dropping.
He's gonna code.
How bad is it?
There's a bullet in his pulmonary artery.
- Can you close the wound if I get it?
- Yes.
How are you gonna do that?
- What is that?
- Lt's a serum, called Velocity-Six.
It could give Jay temporary speed.
He can phase through Dr. Wells' chest,
and remove the bullet.
Yeah. But I told you, I've no idea
what's gonna happen if I use that.
It's our only option.
If you don't do this,
Dr. Wells will die.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
It's working.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
BP and oxygenation is rising.
Blood flow's returning to his lungs.
Thank you.
I was just thinking,
all the moments in my life
when I felt different,
like something was wrong with me,
now I know why.
It's gonna be all right, okay?
Look, I know what it's like to have
your life suddenly change like this.
I can help you get through this.
I don't know if you can.
Cisco, there is a whole
other life inside me.
Hundreds of lives
that I need to know about.
I think I need to do it by myself.
I have to embrace my destiny.
I have to believe.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You don't have to do this.
What's going on?
Nothing. I just like to speed
into rooms, usually.
ARROW: Uh-huh. And where do you think
we find this thing?
I haven't been in
one of these places in a while.
We're too late.
Something you're not used to
saying very often, I'd imagine.
You tried those arrows
once before, remember?
They didn't quite finish the job,
now did they?
I'm not gonna make that mistake again.
You're gonna leave Kendra alone.
I can't do that.
While my destiny is to live forever,
Chay-Ara's is to die, as is yours now.
- Any ideas?
- Oh, now you'll listen to me?
It's your city.
- Let's just try to get the staff.
- All right.
- On my mark.
Carter was right.
Something's holding me back.
Maybe it's Central City, or you.
Or what I thought my life was going to be.
But I'm never gonna become
who I really am unless I let go.
I have to do this.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
(CHUCKLES) In all my countless years,
I've never encountered
anybody with your capabilities.
Astonishing!
No!
Chay-Ara...
(CHUCKLING) on, my God!
(EXCLAIMING)
I used to enjoy slow deaths.
Now, I Just find them boring.
(EXHALES) Thanks.
Yeah. Any chance he blew
himself up in there?
Not likely.
So that's like a tie, right?
- I guess.
- I will take it.
(EXCLAIMING)
Hey,. are you okay?
I'm gonna have to learn
how to use these things.
(CHUCKLES)
You'll get the hang of it, Hawkgirl.
Dr. Wells, you're gonna be okay.
That's good news.
You will probably be very sore
for a little while, though.
Sore's better than dead.
Yes, it is.
How you doing, Garrick?
Your serum's out of my system.
And I will never take it again.
Jay.
Thank you.
You can thank me by keeping
that Velocity-Six away from Barry.
That was Oliver.
Savage has the Staff of Horus.
He wants us all in Central City
as soon as possible.
Okay, well, Laurel's already
there visiting her mom,
so I'll call her and let her know
we're coming by.
If Savage is in Central City,
then why are we going back there?
So we can end this.
And if anybody's gonna take down Savage,
it's gonna be Barry and Oliver.
Plus, you've emerged.
It's gonna be much harder for him now.
And together, all of us,
we can take him down once and for all.
Okay. So how are we gonna get there?
Did I mention I'm the CEO
of a big company with a private jet?
Since when is that a thing?
About eight months.
Maybe if you save Star City,
you might get one, too.
By the way, we still need to get Savage.
We'll get him.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Watch yourself, buddy.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Don't want to lose this guy.
- Thanks, mister.
Yeah.