BARRY:
Everyone has a hero.
Someone they look up to or admire.
Someone they just wish they could be.
It's easy to believe in heroes.
What's hard is when our heroes
stop believing in us.
Oh, Barry, there's an intersection
coming up. Hurry.
This should slow them down.
[HORN HONKS]
Guys, which way?
-Left. Right.
-Right. Left.
You both hear you're telling me
two different things, right?
Barry, listen up. Listen carefully.
Here's what you're going to do.
Now, Queen is trying to make it to the bridge,
but I have a shortcut.
And left. Left. Right.
FLASH: I see her.
-Make her go west before Fremont.
FLASH: Okay, how?
-I recommend a detour.
The King is headed for the interstate.
FLASH:
What entrance?
Attaboy.
Check...
FLASH:
Got the keys!
...mate.
-Give me some. Ha, ha.
CISCO: Yo.
-Efficiently done, Mr. Allen.
-We need a picture.
I'm pretty sure rule number one
of having a secret identity...
...is not taking pictures
in your super suit without a mask on.
Oh, come on. Please?
This is just for us. Just to document all this.
Who knows? Maybe people in the future
will wanna know how all this happened.
All right, if you want the future to have
the whole story, we all need to be in it.
-Let me put on some makeup.
-The future does not care about your makeup.
Mm-mm.
Okay.
Big smiles.
Three, two, one.
Ha.
-Does that count as a selfie?
-Absolutely.
CISCO:
Sick. Damn, I look good.
Thanks for talking me through things
out there.
My pleasure. Well done.
It was bit of a rush. Feeling like a...
-A hero.
-Yep.
You're pretty good at it.
-Hey.
IRIS: Hey.
You do realize the whole point of moving out
is not being at home anymore, right?
Ha-ha-ha.
I forgot a few things.
So how is it living back in the house?
JOE: Hey, Bar.
-Yo.
JOE:
Babe.
Spaghetti à la me.
You sure you don't wanna stay for dinner?
Thanks, but Eddie is painting all day,
and I swore that I would help.
Although I'm really just gonna do that thing
where I get paint on my hair and nose.
Ha, ha. Oh, hey, someone from Central City
Picture News called you the other day.
-I left the number on the fridge.
-Why didn't you tell me?
Chill. I just did.
Hey, I heard that some members of
the Royal Flush Gang are headed to prison.
IRIS: Aah!
-Is that a good scream or bad scream?
Good. So good.
I just got offered a job as a reporter
at Central City Picture News.
-Awesome.
-The editor's a fan of my blog.
-That is amazing.
-Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
[PUCCINI'S "NESSUN DORMA"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Harrison Wells.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Hello?
MAN [OVER PHONE]:
We both know what you did.
[OVER PA]
It's time to pay the piper.
Come in.
Look, Joe. I apologize for all of this.
It really feels like a case of so much
for so little.
The police should not have been called.
I got a prank call before all this happened.
This feels like more than just a prank,
doctor.
Well, there are those who feel
I did not suffer enough...
...for the particle-accelerator explosion last year,
and some of them act on it.
Dr. Wells. Dr. Wells, are you okay?
Dr. Snow, I'm fine.
A little chilly. Otherwise, I'm fine.
Hello, Cisco.
Make yourselves at home as best you can.
I'm gonna make a hotel reservation.
[CHUCKLES]
-This place is so sick.
-Yeah.
Hey, what took you guys so long?
-We got lost.
-We've never been here before.
-Really, never?
-He tends to keep his private life private.
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
A precipice in front and wolves behind.
In other words, you're between a rock
and a hard place.
Check.
WELLS:
The king is dead.
Checkmate.
[CHUCKLES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Dr. Wells?
There he is.
Hartley, allow me to introduce you
to Cisco Ramon.
Mr. Ramon here is one of the finest
mechanical engineers I have ever seen.
Wow, I can't believe Harrison Wells said that
about me.
He should prove to be an invaluable member
of your team, trust me.
You I trust.
I don't foresee myself trusting someone
who showed up to his first day of work...
...in a billion-dollar research facility
wearing a T-shirt...
...that says "Keep calm and Han shot first."
Huh. Would you give us a minute, Cisco?
Yes, sir.
I realize you don't have to explain
your hiring decisions to me...
...but maybe for the sake of a fun exercise,
we could pretend you did.
I have a good feeling about him.
Just as I did about you.
Oh.
Hartley.
You're still my guy.
Nothing and no one
is ever gonna change that.
EDDIE:
I canvassed the street.
No other reports of vandalism.
No strange cars.
Get this, Wells says he's right there
when it happened.
All that glass shattering down around him.
-He can't walk.
-And he didn't have a scratch on him.
There's no point of impact.
No rock or bat...
...or any solid object went through
these windows.
It's as if they just shattered themselves.
This wasn't some teenage prank?
No, it wasn't.
But you don't want our help.
Why?
Because I already know who did this.
Hartley Rathaway.
Who is Hartley Rathaway?
Hartley Rathaway is the prodigal son.
And he has returned.
Rathaway possesses one of the finest
scientific minds I've ever encountered.
Any ties to Rathaway Industries?
His grandfather founded it,
his father expanded it.
Hartley was set to inherit the throne.
-What happened?
-He came out to his parents.
Old money, old values.
They were estranged when we met
but brilliant.
I couldn't have built the accelerator
without him.
You guys have never even mentioned
his name.
That's because Hartley
had a challenging personality.
What she means is he was mostly a jerk.
But every once in a while...
...he could be a dick.
[CHUCKLES]
Let's just say that Hartley, like many outliers,
had trouble relating to his peers.
-Yes, but he was always your favorite.
-The chosen one.
He referred to himself like that.
So if you two were so close,
why would he target you?
Hartley left S.T.A.R. Labs about a year ago
after we had...
...a disagreement.
About what?
Look, don't worry. We'll stop him.
I won't let him hurt you, any of you.
Let's get back to my lab.
I could have gone my whole life
without seeing that jerk again.
-Yo, this place is so dope.
HARTLEY: What a coincidence.
We were thinking of making
"Yo, this place is so dope" our new slogan.
CISCO: If you're so convinced
Dr. Wells made a mistake hiring me...
...why don't you try proving it to him?
Magnetic flux is measured by what?
Hall-effect pickup.
The dual of a parallel RC circuit?
Series RL circuit. I can go all day, pal.
Hartley, it looks like you have met
your match.
-I am Dr. Caitlin Snow. It's nice to meet you.
-Cisco Ramon. Nice to meet you.
And just ignore Hartley. We all do.
Tell your boyfriend I need the specs
on the synchrotron by end of day.
Actually, it is the end of Ronnie's day.
We are leaving early.
My boyfriend is taking me out of town
for our one-year anniversary.
-Oh, that's sweet.
-Thanks. I'll see you guys on Monday.
See you.
She seems nice.
You don't.
I give you a week.
Max.
Hi. I'm Iris West.
-It's my first day.
-I can see that.
Really, does it show?
The fact I've never seen you before shows.
Mr. Bridge, nice of you to make
an appearance at a staff meeting.
I do love a good shmear.
-Everyone, welcome Iris West, our new cub.
-Hi.
Anyone wanna volunteer
to be her mama bear?
-Mason, you pick a bad day to show up.
-I don't nanny.
I lost the ability to make a joke back in '05.
Today you do.
Deadlines. All new stories are due
on my desk at the end of the day.
Oh, actually, I had an idea for a piece.
There's this program in Keystone that helps
battered women get back on their feet.
Ah. That sounds really great, West.
Actually, any thoughts on a piece
about the Flash?
Something you haven't written about yet?
Something new?
Um...
No, not currently.
All right. Sally forth, everyone, sally forth.
Everything has a natural frequency.
Since sound is expressed as a vibration...
...if the pitch of the sound matches the natural
vibration frequency of an object, then...
[HIGH-PITCHED NOISE PLAYS
OVER SPEAKER]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
So you're saying that can happen to anything,
not just glass?
Oh, yeah.
I think that's absolutely what happened...
...to the window at Wells' house.
He's using some kind of sonic technology.
I'm getting this feeling that Wells
is hiding something.
About what's going on
with this Rathaway character.
Don't touch that.
I mean, it sounds like this Hartley guy was a pill
before he went all super villain.
So I get why he never mentioned him.
Like he never mentions his girlfriend
that got killed.
No.
How do you know about her?
He's taken up a big part of our lives.
I wanted to know more about him.
Well, if you wanna know more about him,
you could just ask me.
Sounds like you don't know him
as well as you think.
Joe, multiple 911 calls.
Rathaway Industries is under attack.
Sector cars are en route.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-Hey.
-Barry, it's Caitlin.
I think I know why you're calling.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Get down, on the ground.
[HARTLEY GRUNTS]
It's over, Rathaway.
You know my name.
I know some names too.
Caitlin Snow.
[OVER COMM]
Cisco Ramon.
Harrison Wells.
I can hear their radio waves emanating
from your suit.
About 1900 megahertz.
Is that them on the other end listening?
Are they gonna hear you die?
No. They're gonna hear you
get your ass kicked.
HARTLEY:
Okay.
Looks like you're not as smart
as everyone says.
Smart enough to have figured out
who Wells really is.
You see, I know his secret.
Being scooped up by a guy clad in head-to-toe
leather is a longtime fantasy of mine.
So thanks.
Well, well, the gang's all here.
You've lasted a lot longer
than I'd have thought, Cisco.
And you didn't last 10 seconds
against the Flash.
-I was thinking of calling myself Pied Piper.
CISCO: Hey.
I assign the nicknames around here.
Although that one's not bad.
Caitlin, never did get that wedding invite.
-Shut the hell up.
-Stay in front of me.
Scanner's detecting foreign metallic objects
in your ears. Take them out.
I can't. I suffered head trauma
when S.T.A.R. Labs exploded.
My hearing was severely damaged.
Without these, I'm in pain you can't imagine.
We all lost something that night.
Heh. Very clever, repurposing
the antiproton cavities into confinement cells.
-Wells' idea, I'm sure.
-It was mine, actually.
[IN SPANISH]
Hartley, don't make this more difficult
than it has to be.
[IN FRENCH]
WELLS:
Enough, Hartley.
Give us a minute.
-[IN ENGLISH] See you soon, Cisco.
-[IN ENGLISH] Doubt it.
[IN LATIN]
God, I wish I had taken a language
in school.
[IN ENGLISH] How did you know
we were working with the Flash?
[IN ENGLISH]
I wrote a hexagonal algorithm...
...tracking all of his sightings,
extrapolating a theoretical exit trajectory.
In other words...
...every time he ran from the scene of the crime,
he ran in this general direction.
You are brilliant.
And any anguish you have been through...
...because of me was never my intent.
Not bad.
As far as heartfelt apologies go.
Except that wasn't for my benefit.
[ON MONITOR]
That was for you, Flash.
It feels good to have the great Harrison Wells
behind you, doesn't it?
But one day...
...this man will turn on you...
...in a flash.
And even you won't see it coming.
My only hope is that he leaves you
in better shape than he left me.
If you're lucky, you'll only be dead.
Because every day,
I have to live with the agonizing...
...piercing screaming in my ears.
Heh. I almost forgot. I told your pet I know
your deep, dark secret, Harrison.
Have fun letting him in on that one.
I assume you were all listening.
Hartley was telling the truth.
I have not been honest with you.
With any of you.
The accelerator.
Hartley warned me that there was indeed
a chance that the accelerator could explode.
His data did not show 100 percent certainty.
Just that there was a risk
but it was a real risk...
...and yet I made the decision...
...that the reward...
...that...
...everything we could learn...
...that everything we could achieve,
that all of that...
...simply outweighed that risk.
I'm sorry.
The next time you choose to put our lives
and the lives of the people that we love...
...at risk...
...we'll expect a heads-up.
After the explosion,
when everyone else left you...
...Caitlin and Cisco stood by you.
You owe them more than an apology.
They might seem to get more than that
with Hartley so intent...
...on sending me to the next world.
What...?
That wouldn't make it right with them.
You broke their trust, our trust.
Oh. Hi, chief. Is that what people call you?
Uh, no. Not really.
Listen, eyewitnesses say that the Flash
thwarted an attack downtown today.
-Look into it.
-Uh, yeah, sure.
Great.
-Mason, you're looking rumpled today.
MASON: Mm-hm.
So, what are we working on?
I am following up on a lead
on corruption at the DWP.
You, I think you just got your assignment
from Larkin, didn't you?
Look, I'm not stupid, okay?
I know that Larkin hired me because he thinks
that I have some sort of in with the Flash.
-But I am serious about being a journalist.
MASON: Why?
Because you write a blog?
My mother writes a blog.
I may not have a lot of experience,
but I do have...
MASON:
Spunk.
Grit.
Gumption.
What is this, a chick-lit novel?
No, no, no. I am having the worst day ever.
We both can't be having
the worst day ever, okay?
I was really looking forward
to getting some complaining in.
Well, fire away.
Okay, well, turns out
that the real reason they hired me...
...is because they think I have some sort
of connection to the Flash, which I don't.
Not anymore.
And I've been teamed up with Mason Bridge,
who is a legend, who I admired...
...before he told me I was a worthless,
talentless millennial.
Well, the people we admire
aren't always who we'd like them to be.
Well said.
So I'm screwed.
No. Look.
If this Mason guy doesn't see
what a talented journalist you are...
...then he's probably a lousy writer.
He won the Pulitzer. Twice.
I think.
Oh. Good for him.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Thanks, Barry.
Having someone believe in me, it's a small...
...really, really big thing.
-Yeah.
Where's Dr. Wells?
I'm not sure.
Barry was right.
Hartley was using sonic resonance.
The intensity regulator's measuring decibels.
But you know what's weird?
He had it set to the lowest setting.
What do you mean?
Well, he could've completely destroyed his
father's building if he wanted to in one blast.
So why not just do it and leave?
I mean, why stick around
and run the risk of getting caught?
Unless he wanted to be caught.
Dr. Wells, there's been a pipeline breach.
Hartley.
[ALARM BLARING]
Stay here.
[GROANING]
Not now.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING]
Cisco, can you hear me?
[CAITLIN GRUNTS]
[DEVICE WHIRRING]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-Hey, what's up?
-Hartley escaped. He's loose in the facility.
Okay.
[AIR WHOOSHES]
Okay, your turn.
Why are you having the worst day?
Tell me, Harrison.
Am I still your guy?
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah. Cisco and Dr. Wells.
He's gone.
Hey.
Welcome back, Mr. Ramon.
Oh.
Oh, man.
-Caitlin.
-Hey, she's fine.
You need to rest. You have a concussion.
You're lucky.
Please tell me you got him.
I guess the attack on his family's company
was a fake-out so we'd catch him.
Give him direct access to S.T.A.R. Labs.
-But why?
CISCO: Should've know he was up to something.
-This is my fault.
-Hey, man, this is on me too.
-I shouldn't have left before...
WELLS: This is no one's fault but mine.
I earned the blame.
I'm not interested in sharing it.
Hartley doesn't think I've paid for my crimes.
He's right. He won't stop until I do.
Where are you going?
To earn back your trust.
Hmm. Now, what were you doing
in my accelerator?
I thought it was our accelerator.
Because it will be our fault if we turn
this thing on and blow a hole in Central City.
[IN LATIN]
You are wagering the lives of everyone
in this building. Everyone in this city.
If you don't have the courage to admit
you could be wrong, I will do it for you.
WELLS [IN ENGLISH]:
Hartley Rathaway.
Your position at S.T.A.R. Labs is terminated.
If you think you can shut me up...
WELLS:
Oh, I know I can, Hartley.
Because if you breathe one word of any kind
of unsubstantiated accusation...
...I'll make sure the only job you get in physics
is teaching it to high school juniors.
What is going on here?
Press conference.
Thank you for coming on short notice.
And for those of you
that read the 10-volume report...
...issued by the Norris Commission,
well, I commend you on your tenacity.
You already know, then,
the circumstances that led to the explosion...
...of the S.T.A.R. Labs particle accelerator.
[ON TV]
Or rather, you think you do.
Now, the commission's finding
was that the catastrophe...
...was caused by a chain of events...
...that nobody could have predicted,
including myself.
The truth is, I was warned there was a chance
the particle accelerator might fail.
I was warned by a former colleague. A friend.
I chose to ignore the warning,
and in so doing...
...I let down all of you.
As a new friend pointed out...
...I failed this city.
I failed this city,
and I failed those who trusted me the most.
But coming forward today...
...it's my hope I'm taking the first step
toward regaining that trust.
And your trust as well.
-Are there any questions?
MAN 1: Mr. Wells...
Do you have any intention
of rebuilding the particle accelerator?
Ms. West.
Do you have a question for me?
I don't believe you answered my colleague's
question, Dr. Wells, so I'll ask it again.
Do you have any intention of rebuilding the
particle accelerator, either now or in the future?
Of course not.
Thank you for your answer, doctor.
-It's my pleasure.
MAN 2: Dr. Wells. Dr. Wells.
No further questions.
MASON:
Hey.
What was that?
Gumption.
-Hartley made contact yet?
-What makes you so sure he will?
Because he's Hartley,
and he'll wanna have the last word.
Cisco, you should be resting.
The answer to why Hartley fooled us into
catching him is in here, and I'm gonna find it.
WELLS:
You have nothing to prove.
Not true.
[SCOFFS]
Do you know why I hired you, Cisco?
You said you saw something in me. I know.
What I saw was humanity.
You and Hartley, Cisco, you're both brilliant.
You both have mental...
...sparks, but his brilliance subtracted
from the experience of working here...
...whereas your brilliance, your heart...
...your warmth, your humor, it just adds to it.
There's no chosen one, Cisco.
There's no second or third favorite.
Never was.
It's just us.
[CEILING RUMBLES]
What's that?
HARTLEY [OVER PA]:
Nice gambit, Harrison, but this isn't over.
Hartley, what do you want? What do you want?
I already gave my mea culpa today.
The city already hated you.
You don't think I noticed that press conference
was a pathetic bishop sacrifice?
No, no, no, I've played with you too many times
to let you get away with that.
This is between you, me and the Flash.
You don't wanna play for those kind of stakes
with me, Hartley.
Actually, I really do.
What do you say?
One last game of chess?
You and I both know that the winner of the game
is the one who makes the next to last mistake...
...and you have a move in mind.
HARTLEY:
You're right, and I'm already at the board.
So why don't you move
your precious scarlet knight...
...while I take out a few pawns?
[TIRES SCREECH]
-All right. All right, Cisco, where do I go?
-I can't trace his signal.
He could be sending messages
from anywhere.
Cisco, scan for seismic activity.
If Hartley's using sonic blasts,
the vibrations could cause tremors.
[HORNS HONKING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Look, over here.
Quake activity but no fault line.
I think he's on Cleveland Dam.
Barry. Don't underestimate him.
He's brilliant.
Well, good thing I'll have you in here.
Rook to Knight 4.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
WELLS [OVER COMM]: You need to disarm
Hartley immediately. Do you hear me?
He is a master of distraction.
He is a master of hiding his true endgame.
Aha.
-Uh-oh.
-"Aha" what?
I figured out what Hartley stole,
why he let himself get caught.
-Which brings us to the "uh-oh."
-He has all the data on Barry's molecular scans.
-Why would he want that?
-He can get Barry's frequency.
Barry, you need to get out of there.
Get out immediately.
It's over!
You lose.
Amazing.
He replaced me with you, a total moron.
I got you with the same trick twice.
[WHIRRING]
[GROANING]
I got the idea
watching you and Harrison chit-chat.
To use your suit's own speakers to kill you.
That feeling?
That's your organs shearing apart.
And you activated the frequency
when you disarmed me.
In chess, we call that a discovered attack.
You don't see it until it's too late.
Right, Harrison?
Barry's vitals are bottoming out.
We need to do something.
CISCO:
What are you doing?
Barry's on the travel road of the dam
at rush hour surrounded by cars.
Those cars are gonna have satellite radio.
Satellite sends a signal,
song comes out the speaker...
I know how satellite radio works.
How does that help?
I'll have a satellite send something
other than a song.
Hartley is about to hear something
he was not expecting.
A sound wave that'll meet the frequency of
and destroy his weapons.
[RADIOS WHIRRING]
You don't seem so special anymore.
Given how easy it was to bring you down,
I wonder if Harrison will even miss you.
No, no, no.
[SCREAMING]
Checkmate.
Barry, can you hear me?
Sort of.
BARRY: Okay.
-How do you feel?
[SHOUTING] Fine. There is a little ringing
in my ears. But other than that, I'm good, so...
You're speaking very loudly.
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] Sorry.
-It's okay. It'll pass.
Nice moves.
-Thank you.
-Anytime.
I think I'm gonna take my doctor's advice
and go lie down.
-What a great idea.
-Heh.
Man, I feel like I'm hungover times 10.
CAITLIN:
Not surprised.
It's difficult for me...
...to admit when I'm wrong.
Certainly in front of an entire city,
but also...
Also to my closest friends.
So I hope one day...
...to restore your trust and faith in me.
That day was today.
Yeah.
BARRY:
Not every hero wears a mask.
Some heroes save the day
in the simplest of ways...
...by just being there for us.
Or letting us know we're believed in.
If I'm any sort of hero today,
it's not because of my speed.
It's because I learned how
from the people in my life.
All of them.
Hey.
Man, that press conference today
was something else.
Dr. Wells. Took a lot of guts to do that.
I have to give him that.
He has his moments.
What's up?
-Must have been hard for you.
-What, to be this handsome?
Raising me.
Oh. No.
Well, a kid who loved math and chemistry.
Whose idea of a fun afternoon
was doing experiments in the garage.
-Ha, ha.
-It couldn't have been easy.
Soon as I started AP classes, you had
no clue how to help me with my homework.
-No.
-You must have always felt...
...like you were competing
with Richard Dawkins and Neil Tyson...
...and Henry Allen too.
But look, none of them,
no one, could ever replace you.
Not even Wells.
-Aw.
-Ha, ha.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
-All right, I'll see you at home.
-All right.
BARRY: Hey, Eddie.
-Hey, Barry.
Hey. What did you find out?
I searched Wells' entire house like you said.
There was nothing.
Are you sure you wanna do this,
investigate Wells?
Hundred percent.
Your evil hearing aids
won't help you escape this time.
So I'd get comfy.
You must be enjoying this, Cisco.
I am.
If that scares you, I can't imagine how
you're gonna feel when you let me out of here.
Hmm. Maybe I'm going deaf, because I could've
sworn you just said I'm gonna let you out.
And very soon too.
Why would I ever do that?
Because I know where Ronnie Raymond is.
I know what really happened to him
that night.
And I know how to save him.
GIDEON: Warning. Tachyon output
has passed acceptable tolerance range.
Continued exposure is not recommended.
Increase to maximum, Gideon.
GIDEON:
Increasing to maximum, doctor.
Speed force absorption at 35 percent
and rising.
I'm not stabilizing.
I can't hang on to my speed.
It comes and goes and I cannot control it.
Gideon, for how much longer
is the tachyonic device viable?
GIDEON:
Calculations inconclusive.
-I'm sorry, doctor.
-Well, that's okay, Gideon.
This is only meant to be a temporary fix.
The real endgame is almost here.