My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash" and "Arrow"...
The person who broke into my facility
last night was Harrison Wells.
Dr. Caitlin Snow, Cisco Ramon,
meet Dr. Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
I came here to help you, Barry.
He may not be Harrison
Wells from your Earth.
He has just as many
secrets as the one you knew.
I get these feelings
sometimes, these vibes.
I'm not sure what triggers
it. Sometimes it just happens.
[tires screeching]
You can always talk to me.
- Partners?
- Partners.
This is a million dollars.
That money is yours once you tell Oliver
that you've lost the baby.
I've been running a lot lately,
trying to go faster than
I've ever gone before.
Because there's someone out there
who's better, faster,
and stronger than I am,
and I need to be ready.
But no matter how much I try
or how hard I push myself,
I keep running into the same problem.
He just hit 1,375.
What's the fastest Barry's run?
Little over Mach two,
when he ran back in time.
That's not good.
That's good, Barry.
We have our work cut out for us.
- I'm not getting faster, am I?
- Well...
No, you're not.
All right, well, let's fix this, right?
I mean, I can't beat Zoom at this speed.
It felt like I was
standing still next to him.
That's because you practically were.
Zoom is at least three, four times
faster than you at this point.
How is he so much faster
than Barry is and Jay was?
Physiology, form, strength,
could be a number of things...
Attitude, diet.
Okay, all right, well,
there's got to be something
we can do about it, so
let's just figure it out...
- fast, okay?
- [cell phone vibrating]
All right, I got to go. I'm meeting Patty.
I'll see you. Thank you.
So how are we going to help Barry?
I'm out of ideas,
and we've tried everything
you've suggested.
Well, not everything.
Synced and corrected by -ROBTOR-
www.Addic7ed.com
[metal rattling]
[dramatic music]
♪
Welcome home.
- Any trouble?
- Nah.
But believe it or not, we
got ourselves a stowaway.
- He give you his name?
- Didn't say.
Sat in the brig silent for three weeks.
He was all decked out in
this when we found him.
- Jeez, how many are there?
- 32.
And I'll polish them
all in blood before long.
I've waited a long time for this hunt,
and you have brought me
very close to my prey.
Mister, you're not going to do
any hunting in those handcuffs.
Oh, but, Captain, you're wearing the cuffs.
Who taught you that... Houdini?
Actually, I taught him.
[gunshots]
Soon another sacrifice will be made.
I feel you out there.
Man, this was a bloodbath.
Done by one person.
One person did all this?
Oh, yeah, you can see
from the blood pattern.
This guy was shot first,
then the police chief,
then these three were stabbed
before finishing off the captain.
Wow. Do you think a meta-human did it?
I don't know, but I found this
in all of the stab victims' wounds.
It's some type of cryptocrystalline...
Flint, most likely...
Probably broke off the
blade during the fight.
I'll run it to make sure.
Let's see what stores sell
those kind of flint knives.
Will do.
And, uh, I'll call you later.
- Okay.
So cute.
You guys are trying not to be
affectionate in front of me.
Oh, no, we're just showing
some professionalism.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
♪ I know that you're
unstoppable, babe ♪
♪
Advantages of a trusting manager.
[laughs]
Oh, a lot's gone down in this place.
Nice.
So what's up?
I thought we were gonna go to dinner.
Whoa.
What's going on here?
I couldn't decide which
restaurant to go to,
so I thought we would create our own.
Voilà.
Short rib, Yukon gold puree, and asparagus.
Got to have a vegetable.
This is nice.
I like to cook.
I didn't know if you
like red or white, so...
I got you both.
Ooh, two bottles.
That's kind dangerous, don't you think?
You're not gonna run away
all of a sudden, are you?
Trust me, I'm staying by
your side as long as possible.
Good.
You know, it's been really great
hanging out these last few weeks.
And it's helped make the
move a lot easier, so...
thanks.
You're very welcome.
[speaking Egyptian Arabic]
Sorry. How did you get in here?
Hey, man, this place is closed.
You are just as beautiful
in this life as any other,
Priestess Chay-Ara.
Priestess?
Uh, you're going to have to go, dude.
Oh, not without her...
dude.
Oh, my God. Cisco.
I don't understand. What do you want?
I believe I was clear.
- [cell phone dialing rapidly]
- _
[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
_
Kendra's not going anywhere
with you, Highlander.
Oh, is that your name now?
Kendra... Quite boring.
I believe it allowed you
to blend in for a while.
Now, give her to me, and
I'll make your death fast.
It ain't gonna happen.
You are done here, pal.
So is he!
Oh!
Thank God, Barry.
Dude, come on.
I can't believe you're The Flash.
And that you work with The Flash.
[chuckles] Yeah, let's keep that on the DL.
This is the same knife
that was used to kill the men at the docks.
Residue is a perfect match.
- So it is the same guy.
- Definitely.
But the thing is, these blades are old,
centuries old.
Do you have any idea why
this guy would be after you?
No, I've never seen him before in my life.
Well, he was certainly
acting like he knew you.
He kept calling her Priestess Chay-Ara.
That's Coptic.
- You mean Egyptian?
- That's right.
Well, I grew up in Wisconsin,
and I've never even left the States, so...
This guy, he's clearly
incredibly dangerous,
so I need you to at least
let us try to protect you.
I can put a detail on her.
You didn't see this guy, Joe.
No offense, but I don't think a cop
is going to be able to protect her.
No, but we do have a few
friends who could lend a hand.
But we're going to need
to leave Central City.
And go where?
You really want to go to Star City?
Come on, we don't need Team Arrow's help.
Yeah, I think we do, man.
Man, you've fought
meta-humans with abilities
a lot worse than knife-throwing.
I don't think this guy's a meta-human.
There's something different about him,
something, ah, mystical.
Mystical, really?
We stop meta-humans
because we're scientists.
We can figure out what
their weaknesses are,
but we don't have any experience
when it comes to guys like this,
with magic.
They do.
Mm, this wouldn't have
anything to do with Zoom, would it?
No.
I'm just trying to keep Kendra safe.
This is the best way to do that.
Right. Okay, I'm with you.
But how do we even know Oliver and them
even have time to help us?
How busy can they be?
[gasping]
[gasping mockingly]
Oh, gosh, that's fun.
I really could do this all day.
Open it up.
They could've at least tried
to hide this chemical bomb.
Serves them right, it getting
stolen and used against them.
Oh, you brought arrows to a gunfight.
What guns?
Oh, that was actually pretty clever.
Kill them.
"Felicity, the magnetic-arrow
gag will never work."
[chuckles] Yes, it will, my love,
because I am really smart.
And guess what, Oliver. It did work.
Felicity, honey, it's a little hard to fight
with you doing that in my ear.
Oh, I totally forgot that
this was an open line.
Keep doing what you're
doing. Make smart decisions.
[suspenseful music]
Ooh! You know, I got to be honest.
I really thought we'd be
doing this dance a lot longer.
Night-night.
[laughs]
What was that?
[vomits]
Damn it.
Every time.
It's The Flash.
Did I know we knew The Flash?
We know The Flash. Okay.
- I didn't know we knew The Flash.
- Thank you.
But I don't think you ran all
the way here to protect us.
No, not to protect you.
I need to protect a friend.
Wow.
Nice new digs.
Also, I just noticed, no sleeves.
Don't you get cold?
I spent the better part
of five years on an island
in the North China Sea.
I don't get cold, Barry.
Barry, it's so good to see you.
Felicity.
Good to see you, Felicity.
How come you didn't tell
me Zoom broke your back?
- I...
- Oh, I'm so glad you're okay.
So this is what it's like dating her?
More bruises from her
than from Deathstroke.
Okay, S.T.A.R. Labs is
impressive, but this is...
This is completely wrong!
Did you guys even look
at the specs I sent over?
This is a tragedy.
I'm mourning for the death of engineering.
Copper wiring to handle
the processing speed
from the Palmer Satellite,
or else your system is gonna overload.
Yeah, but that hasn't happened.
I mean, it hasn't happened since last week.
I mean, it didn't... It happened yesterday.
- Hi.
- I'm Felicity.
I'm Kendra Saunders. I'm Cisco's...
She's, uh, my, uh, new, beautiful friend
who kisses me occasionally.
Right. Um, I'm Thea.
This is John Diggle and my brother.
Oliver Queen.
- Yeah, I know.
- Hi.
Wow. Okay, first to meet The Flash
and now the Green Arrow.
Do you have any other surprises for me?
[chuckles] Please, no more surprises.
Barry said that you need our help.
Somebody very dangerous is after you.
Yeah, and I have no idea why.
What does this guy even look like?
Hold on.
Okay, this is him.
Yeah, see, that's something
I would never think of.
Hey, kind of rocking
that Dothraki look... hot.
Let's see if facial
recognition can find a match.
[keys clacking, computer beeping]
- That's him.
- Yeah, strange.
This picture's from 1975.
Which would make him about
80 years old right now.
Okay, what else can you tell us?
- He
- aid we've known each other for ages,
but I've never met the man before.
There has to be some kind of connection.
Not one I can think of.
I just moved to Central
City six months ago.
Why'd you move there?
I just felt drawn to the city, I guess.
Kendra, there is a reason
this guy's after you.
Think.
Look, man, we just came out
here to hide out for a bit
until we figure things out,
so you can just take it down...
You came here because you need our help.
This is what my help looks like.
Oliver, I just saved you
guys from whatever the hell
Flock of Seagulls was about to do.
The least you can do is...
Barry, none of us have superpowers.
You brought Kendra into our world
without knowing who she is
or what this dude that is
after her is looking for.
You made all of us unsafe.
So maybe you ask the questions.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- We're all friends here, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Why don't we go back to our place
and have some drinks, and we can talk?
Cool.
What you working on?
This is a formula
meant to increase a speedster's velocity
that I've been developing
since Zoom showed up on my Earth.
Ironically, this was meant
to help out Jay Garrick.
You want to give Barry a
drug to make him run faster?
Temporarily enhance the Speed
Force in his system, yes.
So you're trying to make
nitrous oxide for speedsters.
Good analogy. Yes, I tried.
Five times I tried. Five times I failed.
That's what you get when
your background is technology
and not biochemistry.
Well, then you are lucky I am here.
What does that mean?
You've been thinking of this
as a mechanical problem,
not a biomechanical one.
And what does that mean?
When a speedster runs, they consume
an extraordinary amount of oxygen,
so we just need something
to give an extra boost
of oxygen during that time.
Like an oxygen generator.
Exactly.
So we just need a chemical
that's rich in oxygen that would release it
as a nearly pure gas as it decomposes...
Something like...
Both: Sodium chlorate.
Then all we'd need is
heat to release the oxygen.
Which a speedster generates naturally
in the form of lightning.
I think something like
this just might work.
You think you can help me figure it out?
I can certainly try.
I'm not changing my nickname.
I like Speedy.
Are you familiar with my body of work?
If you are, then you know
I can come up with something
so much better than Speedy.
Why don't you get a haircut?
And then maybe we can talk about it.
I think you're just mad
because my conditioner game
is on point.
So the CEO of Palmer Technologies
is living with Oliver Queen.
It's insane how much life
can change in six months, huh?
Which you would know better than anyone,
considering that there's another Flash,
another Dr. Wells, from another... earth.
I mean...
Yeah. No, it's been trippy lately.
I wonder what Oliver's
doppelganger would look like.
- Bald, pot-bellied...
- Uh-huh.
- Agreeable.
- [laughs]
You seeing anyone?
- I am, actually.
- Good.
Patty is her name.
She's amazing.
You deserve someone amazing.
Thanks.
[oven timer dings]
[gasps] My pigs in a blanket!
Hey, Ollie, um...
look, I'm sorry that I
laid all of this on you.
- I know that it wasn't fair.
- [sighs] It's okay.
I'm sorry if earlier I was a little...
Snippy?
I have been called worse.
No, but I'm glad that you're here.
I'm glad you reached out.
It shows a real maturity,
and I would know that
because I've never been that mature.
[laughs]
I'm always here for you.
Thank you.
I got to say, this isn't the same
Arrow team I'm used to seeing
or the same Oliver Queen.
- You seem really...
- Happy?
- Happy, yeah.
- I am happy.
I finally have everything
that I've ever wanted.
Being with Felicity has given
me a real sense of peace,
something that I haven't
had in a long time.
Didn't you tell me that guys
like us don't get the girl?
Yep.
I was wrong.
[laughs]
I would like to propose a toast.
I wish it wasn't just the dark
times bringing us together.
But it is friends like you
that make those dark times worth having.
[chuckles] What a guy.
Steals my drinks, steals my words.
As I was saying, it's good to see everyone.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
- [clears throat]
- Mm.
Look, don't worry, all right?
We're gonna keep her safe.
- I promise.
- Yeah, I know.
Look, there's something I never told you.
The first time I kissed
Kendra, I got a vibe.
No, not like that kind of vibe.
- Like, I vibed vibed.
- Oh.
Remember the man with wings?
It wasn't a man.
It was Kendra.
She was, like, a bird.
You think that she's a meta-human?
Mm...
Wait. Why didn't you say
anything about this sooner?
Well, I didn't think it was related,
but I guess now it has to be.
Look, I don't want her
to know about my powers.
I have this great thing going with her.
She laughs at my jokes,
and she loves movies,
and...
I just... I've never felt like this before,
and I don't want to sabotage it.
I get the feeling.
[gasps] Look!
I will always find you, Chay-Ara.
- Don't move.
- Then how will I kill you all?
[dramatic music]
[grunts]
Yeah, I can do that too.
Thea, no!
What did you do?
I ended it.
This is why we ask questions.
Wait. W-where did he go?
Both: Oh, boy.
[sighs]
Okay.
Thanks.
All right, Lance is gonna call
if he gets any information on...
whoever that is.
I know where we can get some info.
Kendra, I have powers.
I get these vibes from people.
They're visions of meta-humans,
and I had one of you.
So, A, you're saying you're a meta-human,
and, B, she's a meta-human?
I don't know.
In these visions, you could fly.
It was like you were a bird of some sort.
- A bird?
- Yeah.
What else did you see?
That's it... just you with wings.
Oh, I did not see that one coming.
Oh, I think there's a
lot you didn't see coming.
- Great. More surprises.
- Who the hell is this?
It's my dad.
[computer beeping rapidly]
I think I did it.
What do you know, Snow?
I think you did do it.
- Velocity-6?
- Ah.
This is what was so urgent, Harrison?
You get me to come here so
I can take your speed drug?
That's right.
- You knew about this.
- Of course she did.
She figured it out.
I thought this was to help Barry.
It is to help Barry, which is why we need
to do test runs on subjects
who once had the Speed
Force in their system.
The Speed Force doesn't work like that.
It's not something you can create in a lab.
How do you think you
became The Flash, Garrick?
By me and a lab.
Science is what did this
to you, to Barry, to Zoom,
and science is what we need to stop Zoom,
and this is our only option.
Find another one.
The Speed Force can't be
replicated or enhanced.
It's a living thing.
It's a gift that was given to me.
That drug... you have no
idea what it's gonna do.
I'm not going to let another
one of your experiments
mess with me again, Harrison.
You find someone else
to be your guinea pig.
Jay.
Caitlin, keep that serum away from Barry.
- Where are you going?
- To pick up what we need.
Wait. Jay just said we
shouldn't give it to Barry.
We're gonna do what we need.
The man you're looking
for is Vandal Savage.
Vandal Savage? Never heard of him.
Well, who is he?
Some say he was the most
trusted adviser to Genghis Khan.
Others say he guided Julius Caesar
through the Gallic Wars.
But one thing the League knows for sure...
He was there for all of it.
So what are you saying?
He's like a vampire or something?
Not a vampire, an Immortal.
Okay, we've officially
stepped into crazy town.
Immortality?
Wait. No, no, no, this makes sense.
This explains why he looks
the same as he did in 1975.
This can't be possible.
There's nothing you can do to save her now.
Kendra, do not listen to him.
I... I just need some air.
Hey, we're gonna do
whatever we have to to keep Kendra safe,
whether you think we can or not.
Hey, Joe, it's Patty.
I just interviewed a weapons
expert about the flint knife
our attacker used.
Found out something pretty interesting,
uh, so call me back.
Harrison Wells?
Kendra!
Hey, you going to be all right?
It's just a lot to take in right now.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't
tell you about me before.
I didn't want things to
be different between us.
It's not that, Cisco.
If what everyone's saying is true...
And it's beginning to seem like it is...
My whole life just changed,
and I am so not ready for that.
I hear what you're saying. I do.
When I first learned about my powers,
I remember feeling that exact same feeling,
and sometimes I still feel that way,
and all I can say is...
every day gets a little bit more normal.
I promise you.
Thank you.
You're so welcome.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Aah!
- Kendra!
Help!
Guys, did you find anything?
Both: I'm on it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, this is my house.
Don't worry. We're going to find her.
Wow. You look as beautiful as ever.
Chay-Ara, it's me, Khufu.
Do you remember?
Look at me.
- You need to wake up.
- What are you talking about?
I don't know who you are.
You will once you emerge.
Until then, you need to stay by my side
so that I can protect you.
Protect me? From what?
The man who's hunting you, Vandal Savage.
I got them! 57th Street tower.
I'm right near there.
Always a pleasure watching you work, Smoak.
Yeah!
- Ow.
- That was pitiful.
I know this is a lot to take in,
but you sort of just kind
of have to trust me on this.
I...
[sighs] Just one second.
Stay right there.
I got eyes on him.
- Give me the girl.
- Not gonna do that, Robin Hood.
- You're making a big mistake.
- I'll take my chances.
Barry, change of venue.
Birdman and Oliver are at
54th and Motor now... hurry!
On my way!
[dramatic music]
- We need to expose his wings.
- I'm open to suggestions.
- Now you're listening to me?
- It's your city, Oliver.
All right.
That's new.
[chuckles] Yep, comes in handy.
We can't use that serum on Barry.
That's up to him, isn't it?
If Barry wants to stop
Zoom, this is what he needs.
Jay said it could hurt Barry.
Well, Jay's a coward.
Jay's a scientist who knows
a lot about speedsters.
- You're a scientist, Snow.
- You've been watching Barry.
You know he's nowhere near
as fast as he needs to be.
This other mentor, this
other Harrison Wells,
did not want him to reach
his full potential... I do.
You know, you're really starting to sound
a lot like him.
Put your hands in the air.
- Who are you?
- You're under arrest.
Doctor McGee was right.
- She did see you.
- Christina McGee?
At Mercury Labs.
You're Harrison Wells.
Yes, I'm Harrison Wells.
I'm not the Harrison...
- Stop!
You move closer, and I'll shoot.
Give me that...
Oh, my God, what have you done?
Harrison?
Harrison, stay with me.
Harrison, Harrison, stay with me.
Stay with me, Harrison, come on.
- Why did you shoot him?
- I thought that was a gun.
- I'm sorry. I'll call 911.
- No, don't!
- Why?
- Because this...
Didn't Joe West explain this to you?
- No.
- Just call Joe.
Okay.
Where is she?
What's your name?
You're putting her in danger,
and I'm the only one capable of saving her.
You have a very interesting perspective
on what the word "saving" means.
She's the love of my lifetime, sweetheart.
I was not gonna hurt her.
You need to let me go.
Chay-Ara.
My name is Kendra Saunders.
In this life.
And I am... was Carter Hall,
but that is not who we are.
What does that mean?
You're Priestess
Chay-Ara. I'm Prince Khufu.
And we're lovers.
Soul mates.
We've been partners for 4,000 years.
We're drawn to each other in
each life, and after we die,
we reincarnate to find each
other again and again and again.
And now that I've found you, we
should really get out of here.
Okay, Romeo, why don't you pump the brakes?
These people cannot protect
you from Savage any longer.
Do you know who Vandal Savage is?
In every lifetime, he
hunts us down and kills us.
He's done it 206 times,
and I'm not planning to make it 207.
Why does he kill you?
His life force is tethered to ours.
Every time he kills us,
he becomes more powerful.
You do the math.
You're 0 for 206,
and you still think
you're her best bet, hmm?
Okay, so what we need
to do is just find Savage
and get rid of him.
Well, you can't get rid of him, my friend.
Oh, yeah? Watch us.
It might be harder than you think.
Is that the only way this
guy knows how to enter a room?
My associates tell me Savage
left Star City a few hours ago.
- For where?
- We're not quite sure.
But I assume after his run-in with you,
he realized he needed
something more powerful
to complete his mission.
We think he's trying to
locate the Staff of Horus.
Sorry, what is that?
It's a relic from our past...
An ancient and powerful weapon.
If Savage gets his hands on it,
it's going to be nearly
impossible to stop him.
Since when did our lives suddenly become
an "Indiana Jones" movie?
- Felicity?
- Yeah?
- Think you can find it?
- Yeah.
It's probably at some museum somewhere.
I'll, uh, work my magic,
see what I can find.
We're running out of time.
You need to emerge now.
Come on, what is it gonna
take for you to believe me?
You saw my wings.
I know you know this is true.
Please, just let me show you how.
- How's he doing?
- He's losing oxygen.
- I need you to leave.
- Joe, I...
Patty, go.
There's a bullet in a branch
of his pulmonary artery
that's blocking off most of the
blood flow from the left lung.
Are we able to get the bullet out?
Not without causing too much damage.
I need Jay's help.
[wind whistling]
So...
you just want me to jump.
Fall, jump, swan dive, whatever suits you.
Just, uh, do it.
Okay, this isn't the X Games.
And this is how she emerges...
She just falls towards her death?
Yep. 4,000 years of experience
says that's exactly how.
Just watch and learn.
No, I'm sorry. What are we doing?
Why are we listening to this guy?
Come on, Oliver, you're supposed to be
the one who asks questions.
Okay, but after what we
saw, after what Cisco said,
I cannot believe I'm going
to say this, but it...
kind of makes sense.
Hey, hey, hey!
[dramatic music]
♪
- I need to try.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, she is.
- [screams]
- Barry!
- [screaming]
- What the hell was that?
- Saving her life.
You should have emerged.
Something is blocking you.
Well, we should just try
again and see what's...
- No!
- Yeah, no, no, no, no.
We're not doing that again.
Kendra, you don't have to do this.
Oliver, we can stop Savage, okay?
Barry. Barry!
What?
Talk to you for a second?
Okay.
Keep an eye on him.
What is going on with you?
I'm trying to keep her alive.
- Then I think we let her jump.
- Are you kidding?
Barry, I get that you're desperate to help
and you want to be the hero
and you want to save her yourself,
but I think she has to
have a part in it too.
[scoffs]
It's just... the rules keep changing.
One day I have to run through time,
the next I'm fighting a telepathic gorilla,
and now we're what?
We're chasing down an
immortal madman on a rampage
against down a reincarnated
warrior priestess?
I just never thought I'd have superpowers
and feel more powerless than
I ever have in my entire life.
That part I understand.
But you have already helped Kendra.
You have kept her alive.
So now let's help her get her wings,
and then she can give you
a lift back to Central City.
Central City.
What?
You need to check Central
City for the staff.
Kendra, you said you were drawn there.
Yeah.
I think you're drawn to
things that destroy you
the same way you two
are drawn to each other.
That's why it wasn't
in any museum or private collection,
because it was consecrated eight months ago
at St. Mark's in Central City.
We've got to get it before Savage does.
- Carter, stay here.
- I'm not going anywhere.
Call Thea and Digg,
and we'll have them hold down the fort
in case Savage shows up.
Kendra, last year, I lost my powers.
The only way I could get them back
is if I just forgot about
everything happening around me
and focused on who I was.
Just believe in yourself, and
your true self will emerge.
Thanks.
Hey, are you sure that you want to do this?
If this guy's immortal
and Merlyn's right about
how powerful this staff is...
We'll be fine.
Kiss her.
- Careful.
- Let's go.
[exciting music]
Now what?
His systolic pressure's dropping.
He's gonna code.
How bad is it?
There's a bullet in his pulmonary artery.
Can you close the wound if I get it?
- Yes.
- How are you going to do that?
What is that?
It's a serum called Velocity-6.
It could give Jay temporary speed.
He can phase through Doctor Wells' chest
and remove the bullet.
Yeah, but I told you, I have no idea
what's gonna happen if I use that.
It's our only option.
If you don't do this, Dr. Wells will die.
[dramatic music]
♪
Ah!
It's working.
♪
BP and oxygenation is rising.
Blood flow's returning to his lungs.
Thank you.
I was just thinking...
all the moments of my
life when I felt different,
like something was wrong with me.
Now I know why.
It's gonna be all right.
Okay?
Look, I... I know what
it's like to have your life
suddenly change like this.
I... I can help you get through this.
I don't know if you can.
Cisco, there's a whole
other life inside me,
hundreds of lives, that
I need to know about.
I think I need to do it by myself.
I have to...
embrace my destiny.
I have to believe.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You don't have to do this.
[exhales deeply]
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
I just like to speed into rooms, usually.
Uh-huh. Where do you
think we find this thing?
I haven't been in one of
these places in a while.
We're too late.
Something you're not
used to saying very often,
I'd imagine.
You tried those arrows
once before, remember?
They didn't quite finish
the job, now, did they?
I'm not gonna make that mistake again.
You're gonna leave Kendra alone.
I can't do that.
While my destiny is to live forever,
Chay-Ara's is to die, as is yours now.
- Any ideas?
- Oh, now you'll listen to me?
It's your city.
All right, let's just try to get the staff.
- All right, on my mark.
- All right.
Carter was right.
Something's holding me back.
Maybe it's Central City or you
or what I thought my life was gonna be,
but I'm never gonna become who
I really am unless I let go.
I have to do this.
[speaking Egyptian Arabic]
In all my countless years,
I've never encountered
anybody with your capabilities.
Astonishing!
No!
Chay-Ara.
Oh, my God!
[laughs]
Whoo-hoo!
I used to enjoy slow deaths.
Now I just find them boring.
[explosions]
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Any chance he blew himself up in there?
Not likely.
So that's, like, a tie, right?
- I guess.
- I will take it.
Whoo!
Hey.
You okay?
I'm gonna have to learn
how to use these things.
You'll get the hang of it, Hawkgirl.
[monitor beeping]
[inhales sharply]
Dr. Wells?
You're gonna be okay.
That's good news.
You will probably be very sore
for a little while, though.
Sore is better than dead.
Yes, it is.
How are you doing, Garrick?
Your serum's out of my system,
and I will never take it again.
Jay...
thank you.
You can thank me by keeping
that Velocity-6 away from Barry.
That was Oliver.
Savage has the Staff of Horus.
He wants us all in Central
City as soon as possible.
Okay, well, Laurel's already
there visiting her mom,
so I'll call her and let
her know we're coming by.
If Savage is in Central City,
then why are we going back there?
So we can end this.
And if anybody's gonna take down Savage,
it's going to be Barry and Oliver.
Plus, you've emerged.
It's going to be much harder for him now.
And together, all of us,
we can take him down once and for all.
Okay, so how are we gonna get there?
Did I mention I'm the CEO
of a big company with a private jet?
[upbeat music]
Since when is that a thing?
About eight months.
Maybe if you save Star
City, you might get one too.
By the way, we still need to get Savage.
We'll get him.
Watch yourself, buddy.
You don't want to lose this guy.
- Thanks, Mister.
- Yeah.
♪
[dramatic music]
Synced and corrected by -ROBTOR-
www.Addic7ed.com