[Barry softly] Oh, God.
No.
[sniffles]
Iris.
[Bashir] So that worked.
What just happened?
How are we still alive?
Iris.
- I don't understand.
- Neither do I.
What did you do?
Mrs. West, as soon as Nora came in,
I knew you were right.
I could see the hate in her eyes.
Real anger issues.
I mean, no match for me,
but I wanted to protect you all.
So I took care of it.
You made her think we were dead?
You made us all see it.
It wasn't a nightmare.
That was an illusion.
- I didn't know you could do that.
- [softly] Yeah, it's...
[scoffs]
Neither did he.
You were just trying
to save yourself, you jerk.
Hey, hey, hey.
How about "Thank you, Bashir.
That was baller, the way you stopped
that mean lady from murdering us."
I don't get it.
Why would Nora attack you?
I think she sees me as competition.
[thunder rumbling]
[Barry] Have we been able
to locate Nora?
There's no sign of her
on our satellites.
She could be anywhere.
She's probably out there somewhere,
Sith-corrupting Deon.
I'm the reason he ran to Nora.
If anything happens to him...
He's a god, too. Won't he be safe?
None of us are. Not anymore.
Yeah. She's right.
It's only a matter of time
before Nora senses
the other Forces are alive.
Iris, it's up to us.
We have to protect them.
If Nora wants Bashir
and Alexa dead, then...
we need to hide them.
Hide them. Where? A.R.G.U.S.?
Guys, there's nowhere on Earth
to hide from the Speed Force.
Then we won't hide them on Earth.
There's only one place Nora can't go.
A place where she didn't exist
for a few months.
Like, in the past.
When Nora first died.
Does that place still exist?
It's a moment in time.
A dead zone that she can't access.
But a speedster can.
I can take Bashir and Alexa
and once they're inside...
Once we're inside.
They're my responsibility, too.
I swear, that kid of ours can sleep
through absolutely anything.
[reporter on TV]
Breaking news coming in
regarding the storm. Central City...
Babe, what happened?
Multiple lightning strikes took out
a wall at Iron Heights.
Two dozen inmates escaped,
most of 'em metas.
Oh, no, what about Frost?
You don't think that...
No... but this storm
is the perfect cover
for criminals to lay siege.
[grunts]
You regret giving up
your badge, don't you?
If I hadn't I could've stopped this.
Now people are gonna get hurt.
Or worse.
No, no, please don't do that
to yourself.
[grunts]
I can't help anyone from a couch.
Yeah, maybe not.
But you know what?
You can do more than you think...
Cecile!
[Alexa] This is the Speed Force?
It was.
It was nice of the Addams Family to
lend you their place for the weekend.
All right, I'm gonna go find Deon.
If Nora somehow
finds the three of you first...
Yeah. Use the transmat orb
that Cisco gave me.
The hyper-tachyon particles inside
will pull any organic matter
back to Central City.
We'll be safe.
Go save our family.
I wanted to say goodbye.
That was rude.
Is he gonna be okay?
Yeah, I'm sure it's nothing.
You should get some rest.
There's no telling how long
we're gonna be here.
[groans]
[Speed Force as Nora Allen]
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Where were you?
Nora... what happened to you?
I couldn't feel you at all...
which shouldn't be possible.
You brought me here?
I had to make sure you were safe.
From who?
From you?
You tried to kill them, Nora!
Even Iris.
And I let you live. For a reason.
Do you have any idea
what death is like?
It's an agonizing emptiness
that turns your soul inside out.
And that loneliness it brings?
- It burns.
- Iris and I brought you back.
You brought them back, too.
As soon as I was reborn,
I could feel those new Forces
trying to snuff out my existence.
They wanted to drag me back
into the darkness, Barry!
But I won't let them.
Now bring my brothers
and sister to me...
or your city dies.
[thunder rumbling]
[rapid beeping]
We've got category three winds
and over 22 lightning strikes
a minute.
It's Nora.
She says she's gonna
tear the city apart
unless I bring her all three Forces.
I gotta find Deon before she does.
I got your back on that, Flash.
I rebuilt the isotopic sensor.
Now all you need to do
is sweep through the city
in a standard grid pattern
and it'll sound off once you're
within a hundred yards
of our teenage time god.
Now all you need is a little
mecha-back up.
Not this time.
I need you and Chester on comms.
But Deon knows us. We can help.
Bringing Deon in
is my responsibility,
but we need to find a way
to stop Nora, so focus on that.
[Frost] Mark!
You need to turn yourself in, now.
[breathes deeply]
Ladies first, Snowflake.
After all, we're both
escaped prisoners tonight.
A little something else
we have in common.
I didn't escape.
I came here to turn you in.
Yeah, that's still
breaking out of prison.
Look, before you try
to impale me again,
I just wanna say I forgive you.
You what?
You tried to murder me last time.
What you want me to say?
You're a hero and I'm a bad guy.
We all do what we gotta do.
Like this.
I really needed these
biotech interfaces for my work, so...
So you stole them.
Hey, if I can ignore your
stabby faults,
then the least you could do
is ignore my klepto ones, maybe.
Besides, I'm all done here.
You wanna get a drink?
You already know
I make a mean martini.
No, not happening.
Come on.
We had so much fun last time.
You know, before the whole
attempted murder part.
Look, would you stop
bringing that up? Okay?
Yeah, you're probably right.
I will say this.
You are the first person
that I've met in a very long time...
that I don't wanna try
and kill a second time.
So how about that drink?
No, there's no freaking way
I would ever go out with you.
Wait. Hold on. Are you talking about
dinner and the whole nine yards?
Look, would you just stop doing that?
All right?
What?
- Just trying to get a little clarity.
- That. Right there. Just stop it.
It is okay if you're into me.
For the last time, I am not into you.
Mm.
Then why don't you stop
staring at my six pack?
[Caitlin] Tell me exactly what happened.
[Joe] Lightning shot through
the window. I mean...
It was like
someone wanted to hit her.
Maybe someone did.
Nora is controlling the storm.
Why would she do that to Cecile?
Why did she attack Iris?
Joe, don't worry.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to figure out
what's wrong with Cecile
and get her back on her feet, okay?
[sighs softly]
[Bashir] Why do I feel like the Brady
Bunch might have died in here?
[Iris West] This place is an exact
replica of the house
that Barry and I grew up in.
It looks terrible now,
but it wasn't then.
What was he like back then?
Barry? [chuckles softly]
He was small for his age.
Bet he loved that growth spurt
when he was 13.
Not really. He was pretty clumsy.
Wow. Isn't this great?
Mom and the kids reminiscing
about old times.
[Iris West] Anyways.
He was pretty sensitive about it,
so I wanted to help.
I would place all of my books
on top shelves
where he thought
I couldn't reach them.
[Bashir] Hey, baby sis.
Look what I can do.
Don't react.
This is just between us siblings.
Nora is not gonna stop
until we're dead.
We need to face her
and fight together.
First, we need to get outta here.
I know how.
Are you with me or not?
He was so proud of himself
when he pulled them down.
It made me smile.
- [device beeping]
- [panting]
My life was supposed to be
on this field as a football god.
Then I became an actual god, and...
Somehow I still can't make
my life go in the direction I want.
[sighs]
I wanted you to die... not them.
I just wish I could take it all back.
You don't have to take it back.
Iris, Alexa, Bashir...
They're not dead.
What?
It was an illusion.
[scoffs]
Bashir...
It was him, wasn't it?
[scoffing]
Look, I just wanted you to feel
the same pain that I felt
when you called me a mistake,
all right?
Nora is the one who took it too far.
You're not a mistake, Deon.
I'm glad you're here.
I know that now.
[thunder rumbling]
Deon, Nora is looking for you.
Man. She's the devil, that girl.
Look, she's the one
that should have never existed.
You need to unmake her the same way
you were gonna unmake me.
All right, so come on,
let's do it together.
No. No, I can't do that.
But I'm gonna find
another way to stop her.
I promise. After you're safe.
Man, here's no hiding
from her crazy ass.
Look. Old man, either you
need to help me take her down
or I'll start running again.
Deon, I'm trying to protect you.
Killing her is the only thing
that's gonna keep us all safe.
- Why can't you see that?
- [loudly] I said...
[panting]
I said we'll find another way.
We... ain't doing jack.
- I am.
- Deon.
How are we supposed to keep
people safe and stop Nora?
C.C.P.D. is evacuating
people downtown.
Let's call Team Citizen,
have them help
get people to shelters.
I'm gonna find Deon again
before he does something
he'll regret.
Hey. What if he does
kill the Speed Force?
He could save lives.
Joe, you know that's not an option.
These are gods, Barr.
We're ants to them.
What are we supposed to do?
Just pray that it all works out?
These Forces exist
because of me and Iris.
I have to do everything I can
to protect them.
Well, at least you still can.
Joe.
Poor Joe.
First the job, now Cecile...
I know. But right now
I need you guys to stay focused
on finding a way to restrain Nora.
Restraining a Force of Nature?
Barry, we've been putting
our heads together,
I just... I don't know
if it's possible.
It has to be.
We're doing everything we can.
I promise.
All right. Well, call me
if you have something.
I'm gonna keep searching for Deon.
[thunder rumbling]
Leawood and Petersburg
are being evacuated.
Kamilla and I are gonna help.
Wanna come with?
Might take your mind off things.
Allegra, things like that...
It's not your responsibility.
Sometimes there isn't anything
we can do.
And that officially makes you
an old man feeling sorry for himself.
- [sighs]
- Yeah, I talked to Barry.
Look, Joe, you need to hear this.
You're not a cop anymore.
I know that.
So, what are you?
Because I still see the man
who sat on a bomb
to save Cecile's life.
Or who helped a juvenile delinquent
achieve her dream
of becoming a reporter.
You did those things.
Not because you had a badge,
but because you care
about helping others.
So...
what do you say?
I can't leave Cecile.
I get it.
It's your call.
Nice look.
Big improvement.
At least my alter ego doesn't
parade around in blue spandex.
You two really are like
brother and sister.
Iris, that device Cisco gave you.
What if Nora finds us
and it doesn't work?
Chester and Cisco designed it.
It will.
Okay, but if Nora did find us,
she could overpower you.
Maybe I should hold onto it.
[scoffs]
- What's up with you?
- Just give her the orb, Iris.
We're gonna take down Nora before
she gets to us.
We're trying to keep you safe.
The last time that happened...
[distorted] I died.
[grunts]
Give me the transmat now.
[gasps]
I'm sorry.
It was the only way.
[Bashir] Are you sure about that?
Wait, don't.
An Einstein-Maxwell gravitational
trap could hold Nora, but...
But the coils would need enough
current to power Las Vegas.
Exactly, so...
- Still no sign of Deon?
- [Barry] No.
And the storm's taken out
more electrical grids.
Please tell me you've got a plan.
No actual plans yet. Just theories.
Barry, look, we've been racking
our brains nonstop here.
You can give us weeks to solve this,
and we still might not know
how to stop her.
- I don't know how we win this one.
- [exhales]
- [rumbling]
- [alarm blaring]
[Chester] Kinetic isotopes.
It's Nora. What do we do?
The only thing we can.
You didn't bring them.
Do you want your world to end?
No.
And neither do you.
Nora, you and the other Forces
were created by something
just as powerful as all this.
The love that Iris and I
have for each other.
That love is a part of you.
That means you're more
than just a Force of Nature now.
Our humanity is inside you, too.
So please... stop!
You still don't understand.
[rumbling]
You feel that?
That wasn't me.
It never has been.
[rumbling]
That was a show of strength, Barry.
Just like what happened
to Cecile earlier.
Sage...
Just like what's happening right now.
The Still Force.
You didn't create this storm.
No. Your children did.
And that's why they must die.
[Deon] You first.
[grunting]
Help him.
- What happened?
- I found out the truth.
Everything that's happening
out there, Nora isn't doing it.
The other Forces are.
They have been the whole time.
Wait, so Alexa, Bashir and Deon
are the bad guys now?
I thought Nora was the problem.
[Speed Force as Nora Allen]
You know I'm the solution, Barry.
Your children's sacrifice
is necessary.
Three of them
for three million in return.
There's still time.
Now, bring them to me
before it's too late.
I couldn't stop him.
Just like I couldn't stop Nora.
What's even worse...
I'm not sure what the right thing
to do is anymore.
Hey, you're doing the best you can.
It's not enough.
[Iris West] Barry.
- Iris.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
Are you all right?
They took off with the orb
and escaped.
I ended up halfway across town.
- Where are Alexa and Bashir?
- They're going after Nora.
Deon had the same idea.
Now he's wounded.
Barry, our plan didn't work.
What are we gonna do?
[softly] I don't know.
Why is all of this happening?
Nora says the Forces we created
are what's tearing the city apart.
And you believe her now?
We do, too.
For weeks, we've been experiencing
Strength Force earthquakes
and Still Force time anomalies.
But those were all Force events
on a cosmic scale leading up to this.
- And what about the Sage Force?
- The tests I ran on Cecile earlier
show that the lightning
she was struck by
was composed
of electrochemical isotopes.
- The sheer psychic energy.
- So it's not just one Big Bad.
We're fighting the Forces
of the universe itself.
Talk about a family feud.
Barry, how do we choose between
saving them and saving our city?
It's okay to admit that you like me.
I'm a likeable guy.
No, you're not. I changed my mind.
So you did like me.
Shut the hell up, Mark.
Okay. [panting]
Am I crazy or am I sensing
some wild chemistry here, huh?
Don't tell me you're not
feeling that.
The only thing I'm feeling
is my fist on your jawline.
Come on, Frosty.
I can counter everything you do.
You don't know everything I can do.
[grunts]
Chill out.
[people screaming]
- The entire city is terrified.
- I know.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't protect them all.
Barry, I can't lose anyone else.
Not like Nora.
Maybe we're not meant to be parents.
I mean, if we can't even keep
our own family safe...
That's a load of crap.
Look, I've been feeling so sorry
for myself
that I've been neglecting
the people that need my help.
Baby girl, you and Barry think
that you can help your kids
because parents are the only ones
that can keep a family safe?
- It's our job to protect them.
- She's right, Joe.
Barry, when you decided to be
the Flash,
I tried to talk you out of it.
Said you were just a kid.
Did you stop?
No. No, it just...
made me want to prove
I could make a difference even more.
And you sure as hell have.
But Iris,
when Barry can't do it alone,
or those times when he is gone,
like the first time
he went into the Speed Force,
who took charge of this crew
and kept us safe?
You did.
You're always there,
side by side with him,
just like now taking care
of business.
You two don't get it?
Sometimes, it takes a family
to protect a family.
Iris, we've been trying to keep
the Forces apart.
When we should be bringing
them together.
I couldn't stop her.
Because you're not supposed
to do it alone.
I thought you wanted to run and hide.
Not anymore.
[rumbling]
[Caitlin] Guys...
We've got company.
You both came back.
Things are different now,
aren't they?
I could feel it.
We both could.
Sorry for almost killing you.
I'll tell you what.
You help us survive,
we'll forgive you.
Maybe.
[Barry] All right. No more running.
No more hiding.
This time we face Nora,
only we do it together.
Everyone ready?
- Any sign of Nora yet?
- No. Not yet.
Nora!
I brought them.
I did what you asked!
[distorted] No, you didn't.
You're going to betray me.
We're connected, Nora.
All of us, whether we like it or not,
we're a family.
- That includes you, too.
- Stupid boy.
I can see
I'm going to have to kill you, too.
Barry!
- Where the hell are we?
- We're dead, right?
No. But somebody's about to be.
[Speed Force as Nora Allen]
Your children did this, Barry.
This isn't how it should be.
So...
It's family game night.
Fine. But I play to win.
[rapid beeping]
I can't get a lock.
It's like the Forces are everywhere.
- They're all around us.
- Like cosmic Forces of Nature.
That's why we can't find them.
Because they're in the Speed Force.
[growls]
[roaring]
[screaming]
[grunts]
What the hell just happened?
She must have given up because
there are too many of us to fight.
No. No, no, no.
We're not that lucky. Are we, Dad?
Bashir is right. This isn't over.
[microphone feedback]
- [Iris West] Barry, can you hear me?
- Yeah. I'm all right.
We all are.
[sighs]
Guys, I'm picking up electromagnetic
particles gathering in the area.
Is it part of the storm?
No, no, no.
It's as if there's some sort of
collider reaction
forming over Central City.
- [rapid beeping]
- It just keeps getting more powerful.
If...
If this thing achieves
enough atomic mass,
it's gonna snap back
like a rubber band.
Big Bang in reverse.
How much time do we have?
[Chester] No idea.
It's like all four isotopic Forces
are returning to their original state
like when they were born.
But in reverse.
If that's our timetable, then we only
have about three minutes.
Maybe less.
Barry, you have to keep
the Force event
from reaching optimal expansion.
You have two minutes and 55 seconds
before the Forces snap back
and destroy everything in existence.
We heard. Your thoughts.
Apparently it's hereditary.
So what do we do?
This.
You really can't take a hint.
[distorted] And you can't kill me.
Well, it was worth a shot.
Now that Daddy's gone,
there's no one here to protect you.
Once you're all gone,
my future will be safe.
Now, surrender.
[Alexa] Bashir, Deon, listen up.
We've got one shot at this.
Little sister, what're you doing?
Are you hiding something from me?
[Speed Force as Nora Allen sobbing]
No.
Hello?
Where is everyone?
No.
[grunts]
No, no.
No. This is worse than dying.
No.
Hello?
No!
No.
[sobbing]
I'll be the only Force
for eons to come and I'll be alone.
All alone. I can feel it.
No, no.
Don't let it happen.
Please don't let it happen.
Please don't let it happen. Please.
Don't let it happen.
It's just one possible future.
But you can choose another.
One where you're not alone.
Where you're a part of a family.
Ours.
Alexa.
Deon, Bashir.
Forgive me.
- He's not fast enough.
- He's gotta be.
Concentrate, and follow my thoughts.
[panting]
[all exhaling]
Oh, my God.
Nora.
It's really you.
You saved me.
You saved us all.
How do you feel?
Like I'm home.
Nice crib.
You should have seen it
before the remodel.
Yeah.
[Barry] This place feels different.
- With you all here, I feel...
- Faster?
You are.
With all of us together, you'll be
faster than you ever imagined, Barry.
So what happens now?
Four of us expand this place.
Use it to bring light to everyone
in the universe.
Together.
Sounds like a new beginning.
For all of us, I hope.
I never really had a home.
But...
this sure feels like one.
I guess I never had a real family.
I might as well start somewhere.
I always knew
I'd make the big leagues.
Ain't nothing bigger than this.
We're so proud of all of you.
Iris...
How can I ever apologize?
You don't have to.
But you believed me
through everything.
Thank you for seeing my humanity
long before I ever did.
And Barry...
Today, you really were my hero.
[gasps]
Hey.
You feeling okay?
[groans softly]
Tired.
Yeah. But okay.
Where's Jenna...
With Rob and David Singh.
It's okay.
Caitlin says that
you're gonna be fine.
- Yeah?
- Thank God.
What about the storm and Nora?
Team Flash for the win, again.
Okay.
What about you?
Have you been here the whole time?
Doing what?
Looking after the people
who need me the most.
Yeah.
[Allegra] I need to take these
powers to the next level.
So come the next apocalypse,
I can be more than just
a human glow stick.
Oh, you should yell a cool catchphrase
before you fire your badass
energy beams like, "Flame on."
- You are such a dork and I love you.
- Not as much as I love you.
That's actually not possible,
because my love knows
no cosmic bounds, so...
Oh, yeah? Well...
[whispers indistinctly]
Oh, it's like that, huh?
[Allegra clears throat]
Come on.
So I binged a whole
Chopped marathon last week.
Nice. Nice. I built a pair of
electronic sock warmers
for Grandma Runk.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
[Chester mutters]
- [phone vibrating]
- [Allegra clears throat]
What's up? Is that Barry?
Will you please tell me
there's another apocalypse?
It's...
It's nothing that can't wait
till tomorrow.
Chopped, huh?
[knocking on door]
[gasps]
Frost! Oh, my God.
Are you okay? Are you a fugitive now
because of this jail break?
Yeah. Slipped out of Iron Heights,
just like the rest of the meta wing
during the storm.
But what... Why would you do that
after everything you've been through?
You know, get some
much needed exercise...
To beat up and put away
a dozen meta-humans?
And what about your sentence?
Even the DA's office has a heart
when it sees you
on the news saving lives.
That and a good word from Flash,
and I got out on probation
for good behavior.
That's incredible.
- What?
- Nothing. You just...
I don't know. You seem different.
- What?
- Fine.
I have a crush on someone.
Who?
He's a bartender.
It's weird that Alexa, Deon
and Bashir are just gone.
Yeah, everything feels different.
It's like...
I don't know. We lost a part of us.
[singing]
Don't turn off the lights
Is this what it's going to be like
when our actual kids go to college?
I mean...
We'd have to actually try and...
You know.
Fluent in the sheet
You read in between me
I ain't a stranger to the foreplay
It makes you wonder.
So we can skip to word play
Leave the lights on
Yeah, it does.
Leave them lights on
Leave 'em, leave 'em lights on, on
Iris?
Where are you going?
I'm tired of wondering.
Let's start a family.
I love that impulse.