Barry! Please!
That's not me!
This can't be happening.
Are you real?
No. Of course you're not.
That's it.
That's it, I've finally lost it.
It's okay. I'm real.
I...
I can't believe I'm talking
to another person. It's been so long.
Wait. I know you.
You and your husband, Joseph Carver,
you founded McCulloch Technologies.
You're Eva McCulloch.
But you're supposed to be dead.
No. Not dead.
Just trapped.
Now so are you.
You see, until now, this place was
a whole world with one inhabitant.
- Me.
- This must be another Earth.
Same Earth, another dimension.
You see, a mirror version
of Central City.
Same city, same buildings,
just... empty.
Who are you, anyway?
I'm Iris West-Allen.
I'm a reporter for The CC Citizen.
Never heard of it. Not that it matters.
God, it feels so good to have
a conversation that's not one-sided.
Everything is backwards.
Eva, you said
that this place was a mirror version
of our own. How is that possible?
Think of it like this.
Our reality is observed
by three dimensions
with depth and length.
But superstring theory posits
that there are other realities.
Fractal dimensions humans can't see.
So...
two sides.
One, our world.
The other is just an empty reflection.
I'm a quantum engineer.
It's my wheelhouse.
Yeah. That is a side effect
of this dimension.
I barely notice them anymore.
How did you end up here, Eva?
Six years ago,
I was developing the technology
to open doors
to other planes of existence.
I was in my office
the night Harrison Wells' dream
went up in smoke.
I've been here ever since.
Dark matter must have washed over
that mirror and created a doorway.
I was in this office
when I got pulled in, too.
But that's not all.
There is someone else
on the other side of that mirror.
Another me. How is that possible, Eva?
A fractal variable caused by the mirror.
A duplicate of you.
You mean the mirror left
a fake clone of me in the real world?
- We are getting out of here.
- I've tried.
For six years,
I've been in my own personal hell.
Eva, I have to go home.
I'm sorry you're stuck here, but...
I thought I was gonna die here alone.
At least now, there's two of us.
Investigation into the disappearance
of socialite Sue Dearbon.
Day 274...
since her parents first hired me
to find her.
Status update. Nothing.
Sue's trail went cold in Midway City
after Remington Meister
provided a dead end.
However, she was there.
Meister confirmed that much.
Hey,
what are you still doing here...
Aw, seriously?
Ralph, when I left last night
you were standing here,
staring at the exact same board,
same as the night before.
Honey, don't you think maybe
it's time you got a little help
and a shower?
Cecile, this is my process.
I work things out with the only person
that can keep up
with my beautiful detective mind, me.
You could work with me.
We took down the FEMA guy together.
That was so great.
You're not loving that. All right, um...
Cecile, you know me.
I like doing things my own way.
Ralph, every Holmes needs a Watson.
- Hang on.
- Mmm-hmm.
What is it?
So, a couple of months ago,
I put up these alerts
on Sue's bank accounts,
trusts and credit cards.
Apparently, she just made
a small deposit on...
an apartment in Central City.
See? Told you.
- Only partner I need is...
- this guy.
Mmm-hmm.
See you.
Oh, wow, something definitely
just died in here.
Kara and Lex Luthor?
Man, this post-Crisis world gets harder
to understand every day.
- Right?
- Man.
- What's wrong?
- I'm still sore
from our little double date
with Amunet and Goldface.
This feels so weird.
- Maybe you should stay home today.
- No, no.
Are you working
on more Black Hole stuff?
Yeah. I think I'm getting really close
to taking this son-of-a-bitch down.
Hmm.
This is the Mirror Gun.
Yeah. It contains a bleeding-edge
reflective micro-chip technology.
If I can examine the gun up close,
then maybe I can find
some kind of small clue
that connects the gun to Black Hole,
since McCulloch created it.
It's still in the Starchives, right?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Could you, um, get it for me?
Uh...
I mean, unlocking a weapon like that
sounds like a bad idea.
Barry, it's me.
I know, but, I mean, after what
just happened with you and Carver,
what if the gun fell into
the wrong hands?
Just like
the Cold Gun fell into Snart's.
It won't. Trust me.
Iris, look, you I trust,
but the guy who just tried to
have you assassinated, not so much.
And if Black Hole had a weapon
as powerful as the Mirror Gun,
I mean, there's no telling
what could happen.
Yeah, you're right.
I'll, um, try a different angle.
I'm just being cautious.
Yeah. No, I get it.
Have fun.
Okay.
Not exactly the Ritz.
Get down!
What the hell, lady?
Hey, I just saved your life.
You're welcome, by the way.
Oh, my God.
It's you.
You're Sue Dearbon.
In the flesh.
And you are?
No one followed us. We're clear.
Sue, I... I have been looking for you
for nine months.
Ouch. I hope you don't bill by the hour.
Where have you been? And why did
your apartment explode in my face?
Yeah. I hate it when that happens.
Look, I'm serious.
Now, who set that bomb?
Why are they trying to kill you?
And how long has this been going on for?
Uh, my ex. Because I know too much.
About nine months.
- You done?
- No, I'm most certainly not done.
Why is your ex sending you
explosive candygrams?
Ooh, the cheap stuff.
Look, drinks later.
Spilling your guts to tell
a tragic story, that'd be now.
Fine. I fell in love with a murderer.
Happy?
John Loring.
Turns out Mr. Dreamy Muscles
and Charisma for Miles
was also a major arms dealer
on the black market.
So why does Loring want you dead?
Because I stumbled across
his client lists, weapons inventory
and everything else that exposes him
for the bag of crap that he is.
The first time he tried to kill me,
I was asleep.
All right. Well...
- Who are you calling, slick?
- Your parents.
Let them know you're safe.
Hmm.
Come on. I just switched plans.
John can track your phone.
You call my parents, they're dead.
All right, then, uh,
we'll go to the police.
I know a precinct captain
who can help us.
The last time I tried that,
they tried to kill me, too.
John's got cops on the payroll
in every city he does business.
Then, what's your plan
to get out of this?
Sue, you can't run forever.
Who says I'm running?
You and Loring are hunting each other.
That's why you're in Central City.
John's in town for a massive sale.
If I can get damning evidence
on what he's doing,
he goes to jail.
And I go home.
I smell a mystery.
I smell... expired milk.
Look, everything's gonna be fine.
Your parents hired me to do
whatever it takes
to bring you home safely,
and that's what I'm gonna do.
- How?
- Easy.
I'm gonna find Loring.
I'm gonna get you evidence.
Then I'm going to take you to C.C.P.D.
And after I do that,
I'm gonna take you home.
John's a killer.
You'd be risking your life.
For me.
If you get killed...
my parents are out good money.
I'm coming with you.
One thousand,
three hundred and twenty-two.
One thousand, three hundred
and twenty-two.
Eva, there has got to be
a way out of here
that we haven't thought of yet.
There isn't.
There's only two options in this place.
Survival or madness.
Eva, my husband will be
looking for me. Please...
This is how it all starts!
Don't you understand?
You sit here and you think
everything's going to work out!
You cannot possibly stay here forever!
And then, 1,322!
That's how many times
I tried to escape this place!
That's how many times I failed!
One thousand, three hundred
and twenty-two reminders
that I am never leaving this place.
So please don't... give me another one.
I'm having a really bad hair day.
I'm sorry.
I've been alone for a very long time.
Well, you're not anymore.
We just need one way out of here, Eva.
That's it.
Sam Scudder.
Who?
He was one of the bad guys.
He trapped...
someone in a mirror, a few years ago,
and my friends got him out
by bringing it to absolute zero.
Eva, we just need to find
some liquid nitrogen.
Well, I have a lab down the hall.
There should be some in there.
The nitrogen should slow down
the mirror's molecules
to the lowest entropy state possible.
Oh, my God.
This could work.
Hey, Barr. Morning.
- Hi.
- You got a second?
Yeah. What's up, Captain?
That never gets old.
It kind of does.
Uh, listen, there was a house fire
- on Baton Street last month.
- Okay.
The occupant died of smoke inhalation.
Uh, I'm wondering
if you could take a second look.
Joe, this case was already declared
an accident.
Yeah, I, uh, need a fresh pair
of eyes on it.
Okay. I mean, what am I looking for?
Whatever you find.
Joe, I mean, I've got a mountain
of cases I need to go through,
ones that haven't been solved already.
Okay. All I can say is
that you'd be doing me a favor.
And whatever you find, Barr,
bring it directly to me.
Okay.
Thank you.
John owns that warehouse.
That's where the deal will go down.
Where are you going?
- I'm going with you.
- No, no, no.
Oh, Look, I get it,
chivalry's your brand...
You're an MIT grad, speak six languages,
and you play polo.
You belong in a country club,
not in the field.
You belong
in the 19th century with your Victorian
"save the damsel in distress" crap.
Loring doesn't know that I'm coming,
so I have the element of surprise.
You, on the other hand,
he might kind of know
that you're coming.
Translation, stay in the car. Please.
I hope Loring looks good in orange.
Uh, I don't suppose
you're a fellow bird-watcher?
Huh.
Hey, Vin Diesel!
You still want me to wait in the car?
So, you mind telling me
how you know martial arts?
My parents sent me to Kyoto
for a summer.
Trained with a blind sensei.
Taught me everything I know.
- Really?
- No.
I trained with a guy named Frank
at a YMCA.
Will you relax? We're safe here.
John's not stupid.
Killing me in a public place?
Uh-uh,
It's not gonna happen.
I'm sorry. I believe he blew up
an apartment to get to you.
That building was scheduled
for demolition next month.
But he does know
that someone's after him now.
It'll make him harder to get to,
thanks to you.
Where are you going?
Sorry, slick.
I can't partner up with someone
who doesn't think
- I can pull my own weight.
- Hang on a second, Sue.
Hang on. Will you just hang on
one second, please?
Look, when I take a case,
I see it through to the end.
And this doesn't end until you're safe.
Do you trust me, Ralph?
I just met you.
But you did save my keister, twice.
And that means I owe you.
And I always pay my debts.
I'll take that as a yes.
- So, without those pictures...
- We are back to square one.
Fortunately,
we still have John's ledger.
He keeps a detailed record
of every deal he's ever made in it.
Years of evidence against him.
But his office is still on
the seventh floor of that warehouse.
Which has probably doubled
its security by now.
The sewer system, that's a good way in.
Those tunnels, they lead directly
to the center of the building.
And then we time our entry
for when the guards...
Change shifts.
And then we mosey up the stairs
into Loring's office,
we get the prize.
Well, you are slick.
Oh, my God, Ralph, you found her!
Oh, technically, I found him.
Sue Dearbon.
- Hi.
Cecile Horton, metahuman attorney,
but I also have 20 years of experience
defending non-metahumans.
The law is my game, Cecile is my name.
I can cover you no matter what
you've had going on all this time...
- Could I get a quick word?
- Oh, gotcha. Just one sec.
Listen, we're, we're kind of
in the middle of something.
Uh, Sue's been on the run
for the last year.
It turns out that someone's after her.
And you're her knight in shining armor.
Ralph, I love it!
By the way, you two, hmm...
When I read the both of you
with my powers,
I could barely tell you apart.
Like, emotionally speaking,
you and Sue are definitely
surfing the same wave.
Just trying to keep her safe.
I mean, it's not like we're dating.
Do you want more coffee?
No.
I can't believe
I didn't think of this before.
You would have, eventually.
What's happening?
No.
It should have worked.
I really thought
I was going back to my old life.
Eva, you will.
Yeah, it doesn't even matter anymore.
My sweet Joseph.
We were so in love.
I saw him in the mirror.
I watched him for five years
as he mourned, grieved and...
moved on.
And I can't. I...
I can't move on.
Oh, my gosh, Nash.
I didn't think anyone else
would be down here.
I lost something down here, so...
Oh, right. Well, that makes sense.
These Starchives are so massive.
- Okay.
I'm sorry,
what were you doing down here?
Cisco asked me to hold down the fort
while he, uh...
He wanted me to take the inventory,
so I gotta do that. Sucks.
That's a lie.
Uh, what are you doing here?
I lost Nora's journal.
I haven't seen it for a couple of weeks.
And, um, you know, it's the only thing
I have left of my daughter.
- So...
- Uh, must be hard.
You would know, wouldn't you?
Now that I think about it,
that's probably...
I am digging up the past and...
You know, maybe I should
start living in the present.
- So should we all.
- Mmm-hmm.
But it's difficult for you,
isn't it, Nash?
With so much unfinished business.
- Look, Nash, Barry...
- Right.
...doesn't know about this.
He would be crushed
if he knew that I lost
anything of Nora's.
So could you maybe not mention
me being down here?
Maybe you should mention
why you're down here.
It'll be our little secret.
I always knew I liked you.
Loring's office is
right up those stairs.
Last one there buys the Gingold.
Hey!
Freeze! Stop or we'll shoot!
- At least he's not a pack rat.
- Focus.
Uh...
- Not finding it.
- Search faster.
- Think I've got something.
- That's not a ledger.
No. It's a key for a safety deposit box
at the CC Mercantile Bank,
where I'm guessing your ex
hid the ledger for safekeeping.
Good point. Time to go.
Uh, we have a problem.
- Do you trust me?
- Define "trust."
Hang on.
Are you crazy?
Sometimes. Don't let go.
We just... You just...
You're the Elongated Man?
Yeah, I'm just full of surprises.
How did you become
the Elongated Man, anyway?
I was brutally experimented on
by a covert organization for years.
They forced me to consume
rubber-based polymer compounds.
- Seriously?
- No.
I rode a bus.
So you're like
an honest-to-God superhero.
- What's that like?
- It's like any other job you love.
It's rewarding as hell.
But boy, the hours,
let me tell you.
Seriously, you're like a...
good person.
I helped you get a key. It's no ledger.
Well, Loring's ledger will definitely
be in the box that goes with this.
And now we know
where the box is located.
All we have to do is open it.
And then, you can get back to your life.
Listen...
I want you to know
how much I appreciate you...
trusting me with your secret.
It means a lot.
Uh...
I can call my friends at C.C.P.D.
and get a warrant
for Loring's deposit box.
Shouldn't take more than a day.
We don't have a day.
Loring's already spooked.
He can move that box at any minute.
I feel like our only chance...
No, it's too crazy.
Come on,
share your thoughts with the class.
What if...
we break into CC Mercantile Bank now.
Just us,
and take the ledger for ourselves.
I believe that's called stealing.
Oh, come on, slick.
You're also a PI.
You can't tell me
you've always operated by the book.
No, but I can't commit a crime.
I get it.
And I respect that.
But, Ralph, I'm not a hero.
So if this is the only chance I have
to see my parents again...
I have to take it.
Sue, being a hero,
it's about helping innocent people.
I'm not going to let you do this alone.
- You're not?
- No.
But we do this my way.
We get inside, get the ledger
and immediately bring it
to my friends at C.C.P.D.
Deal or no deal?
Deal.
- So, what'd you find out?
- These scorch marks...
- Yeah.
- ...they're giant burns,
like sunlight
through a magnifying glass.
So in your expert CSI opinion...
The fire was started by UV light rays.
Same way Dr. Light torched The CC Citizen.
Joe, what's going on?
Look, this isn't the only file
I've found where it looks like
something has fallen through the cracks.
All of these cases involve
accidental deaths.
All the victims are associated
with this guy Joseph Carver.
I'm starting to think
that somebody here in C.C.P.D.
is helping him cover this up.
You think there's a mole here?
Carver's influence runs deep, man.
Governors, Mayor, CEOs.
Okay. Right, um...
Look, this is
what Iris is already investigating.
Her lead had to do
with the Mirror Gun that we stole
from McCulloch Technologies last year.
It fell through
because I wouldn't give it to her.
Why wouldn't you give it to her?
I mean, was it dangerous?
Yeah. I mean,
it could put her in danger.
I don't trust what the world might do
if the gun got out there.
You're right, the world is crazy,
but it's clear
that Carver is really dangerous.
Iris is your partner and family.
And I don't think we can
trust this right now with anybody
other than family.
I'm sorry you're not gonna see
your husband again,
but it's easier if you just accept it.
Eva, you said that you want
to go back to your old life.
Look, maybe it's gone,
but you can start a new one.
I'm glad it's broken.
I'm tired of looking at a world
that doesn't want me anyway.
I'm tired of waiting for someone
to come and rescue me.
And I am sick and tired
of people telling me
that everything is gonna be all right
because it isn't.
It's never gonna be all right!
Never!
What just happened?
I think we just found
our way out of here.
And you're sure this is necessary?
A credible tip came in to C.C.P.D.
saying this branch was
a target for robbery, so yes.
Well, this is
the only way in or out of the vault.
The inner gate is fitted with
an anti-theft electrical system.
Opening or closing it
without the manager's key
automatically activates
a 50,000-volt fail-safe.
An electric fence to keep the cattle in.
- Yeah.
- Smart. Thanks, pal.
Sweet fancy Moses.
Hmm.
Oh, I understand why people
are grossed out when I do that.
Your turn, slick.
Oh, right.
You know,
besides a passion for fisticuffs,
you've got a real knack
for detective work.
You ever think about
getting behind a desk?
Ugh, that sounds worse
than my boarding school.
Or the times my parents made me
take horseback riding lessons.
Or learning French every Saturday
at the US embassy in Paris.
Gee, your childhood sounds just awful.
I didn't say it was awful.
It just wasn't me.
The truth is I always hated
the whole... socialite scene,
which is why one day I woke up
and realized I had no idea who I was.
Guess I still haven't figured out
exactly where I belong.
Poor little rich girl.
How could she be so lost?
No, I... I get it.
I used to wear that uniform
you've got on.
I was a cop, and a damn good one.
And then, that ended abruptly
and I got lost, too.
Then I rode that bus
and found where I belong.
So you're saying there's hope for me?
There is from where I'm standing.
So, partner.
It's a big moment.
You mind if I do the honors?
Of course.
You earned it.
- Found it.
- Must be a tiny ledger.
Now, what do you say we get out
of here and play Mario Kart...
What the hell?
I guess you're not the only one
who's full of surprises.
We are this close to taking down Loring.
Ahh!
Sue, why are you doing this?
Who cares about Loring?
I don't even know the guy.
I do, however,
know where he keeps his valuables.
There never was a ledger.
- Keep going.
- That's why you rented
an apartment in Central City.
You knew I was keeping tabs on you,
so you lured me in.
You rigged your own apartment
to explode?
For what? Just to sell the story
of a sympathetic socialite
- running for her life?
- You bought it.
But don't feel bad, you're a good guy.
And a hero.
You probably see the best in everyone.
Me, I see what I want.
And I take it.
You used my detective mind
to track down Loring's deposit box.
You, you played everyone.
Your parents are desperate to find you.
Do they even know what you really are?
No. That's our little secret.
If they found out
their only daughter was a thief,
they'd be devastated.
So you keep your mouth shut
about who I am,
I keep mine shut about who you are.
Deal, Elongated Man?
Sue, was anything you told me real?
Yes.
And no.
See you around, slick.
C.C.P.D. You're all under arrest.
Nice try, Officer, but I have
a silent alarm in my deposit box,
so I know you stole that from me.
No phone.
Can't stretch through these bars
without getting seriously toasty.
Always come prepared.
You don't want to do this.
Yeah, I do.
I'm that guy.
You're not getting rid of me
that easily.
- Give us a minute.
- Kill them both.
I'm inside you?
Do you have any idea
how disgusting this is?
- I'm saving your life.
- No, you're not.
We are not partners.
I've handled being shot at before.
Why does that not surprise me?
- Let me out.
- Sure.
I'll let you out, and then
I'll take you to Iron Heights
as soon as these idiots run out of ammo.
- Ugh, do you ever shut up? Do something.
- I am doing something.
What's your contribution
to this quaint little scenario?
Oh, wait, nothing.
This is all your fault.
Always come prepared.
Is there anyone
that doesn't want to kill you?
Not really.
I have really gotta learn Spanish.
You want the diamond?
Come and get it.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Looks like we've both been had.
She softened him up.
Let's finish the job.
- It's all yours, Captain West.
- Thanks, Flash.
Clear this out, guys.
Hey, bud.
- Flash. It's him.
- Yeah?
He's the one who robbed us.
Excuse me?
It's a case of mistaken identity, sir.
I'm sure Captain West can explain.
It's all right.
Hey, man, I'm sorry. I got word late.
But I searched the whole area.
Ultraviolet's gone.
I couldn't stop her.
Don't worry, we'll get her. I promise.
I wasn't talking about Ultraviolet.
Loring's in custody,
but facial recognition
isn't picking her up
anywhere in Central City.
Looks like Sue Dearbon has vanished.
- Again.
- That's on me.
She played me, Iris,
like Coltrane's soprano sax.
Ralph, you can't beat yourself up.
I mean, it's not like you knew
who you were dealing with.
I'm supposed to be a master detective.
Ralph, we've all put our trust
in people who have betrayed us.
God knows I have.
I'm gonna go tear down my crime board.
It's gonna take him awhile
to get over this one.
Hey, Joe told me
that you came by C.C.P.D. today.
I think I know why
you didn't come say hi.
What happened to it
falling into the wrong hands?
These are the right hands.
Joe and I found evidence
linking Carver's assassins
to more killings,
crimes that C.C.P.D.
thought were accidents.
Black Hole is a lot more dangerous
than I even realized.
But if you can use this
in your investigation in any way
to bring down Carver
and his people faster,
then that's a good thing.
And while I don't trust the world...
I do trust you with everything.
Thank you.
You have a connection to the mirror
even when it's broken.
Now who sounds crazy?
I've seen a lot of strange things
in the last six years.
You being able to control that mirror
is the least of it.
Sam Scudder could even
travel through them.
Well, I'm not a meta-criminal
who jumps through mirrors
- to rob banks.
- I know.
You're much more than that.
We're the only people in this world,
Eva,
so trust me when I say
that you are stronger than you think.
You're a survivor.
Now, prove it.
You did it. Now, keep going.
One thousand, three hundred
and twenty-three.
I'm still with you.
How did I do that?
I don't know.
But I promise you we will figure it out.
Game on.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::