- Previously on "The Flash"...
- We've been looking at that
front page for four years.
I'm the one that
writes that article, Barry.
- My boss' husband
is the Flash?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, God,
nobody tells me anything.
- This substance
appears to heal
any and all weaknesses
in the human body.
I've learned to control it.
This is my final masterpiece:
life eternal.
- I've seen your version
of life.
It's a nightmare.
- I want to show you this.
- I recognize that pin.
- I have a follow-up question.
[snarling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
- [groans]
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
That was quite the tumble.
I guess you're wondering
why I'm doing this to you.
- You're evil.
I get it.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[glass shatters]
- I bet it's been a while since
you felt your own mortality,
but my powers, like yours,
work on a cellular level.
Allow me to demonstrate.
♪ ♪
[groans]
[both grunting]
- [laughing]
You know, Iron Heights...
is gonna send me
a thank-you basket
when I drop you off as a gift.
- I've already
given you a gift,
and now I'm gonna need it back.
- [coughing]
- My destiny is
to heal all of mankind.
You and your friends can't be
allowed to prevent that.
Life demands your death.
- [grunting]
- Ralph!
Ralph...
Ralph.
Ralph, come on.
[intense music]
- Give us a hand.
- What happened?
- Ramsey.
- Come on, Coach, we...
we still gotta go
on that road trip, right?
[machine beeping]
He's gonna die.
- Frost, how do we save him?
- I don't know!
I can't fix this.
Uh, maybe Caitlin can.
- Ralph's elastic cells aren't
mending like they used to.
Ramsey must be
getting stronger.
- So Ralph can't heal himself?
- No.
But maybe you can.
- What?
- Your speed healing is
the only thing we've seen
that can repair damage
this severe.
Maybe if we gave him
a blood transfusion,
that would fix him.
- What are you saying?
I...I...I could give Ralph
my speed healing?
- Theoretically,
temporarily, yes.
I don't know, we're sort of
in uncharted
medical territory here.
But your blood type
is O-negative,
so you're a universal donor.
- Guys, Ralph is elastic.
No needle can puncture
through his skin.
- I can phase him.
- Will that work?
Do it.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
[dramatic music]
[device beeping]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
How is he?
- He's stable
thanks to you.
We contacted A.R.G.U.S.,
and they're gonna move Ralph
to a secure medical facility
for recovery.
Cisco and Caitlin are prepping
for transport right now.
Hey, don't worry, okay?
He's gonna pull through.
- It's not that.
What if I hadn't been here?
Ralph's fight was nothing
compared to what's coming.
Crisis is only two days away.
- And we're all ready,
I promise.
- Iris, if I haven't
prepared the team...
- You have prepared us, Barry.
[solemn music]
Hey, don't let what happened
to Ralph fill you with doubt.
You've done the work.
We're ready...
For whatever comes next...
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[intense music]
I'm gonna give you one chance
to turn yourself in.
Honestly, I hope you
don't take it.
- Well, there's no need
to involve the authorities.
I just want to talk...
♪ ♪
Flash.
- Of course.
You're the Flash.
But how did...
when?
You were struck
by lightning.
[scoffs]
That is quite the origin story.
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
- [breathing heavily]
I don't know how
you're doing this.
Real or not,
I'm coming for you.
- And yet I'm not
your foremost concern, am I?
Not as much as your inevitable
demise in a coming...
Crisis?
Goodness, you really are
full of surprises, aren't you?
So tell me, when you saw
all those permutations,
billions of possible futures
all ending in your death...
[claps]
What role did I play?
- You didn't.
You weren't there.
- Really?
Not even in one?
Huh. Then again,
you never saw
this coming did you?
Frankly,
neither did I.
Makes one believe
in the impossible, doesn't it?
You look scared.
You should be.
After all, it is the
end of the world, isn't it?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- [breathing heavily]
Oh, my...oh.
- What's that,
Flash?
You think I should
bust my boss
for keeping yet
another secret from me?
Yeah, me too.
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
- Drop what you're doing.
"The Citizen" has a new story.
Look at these.
- Where did you get
these photos?
- I pulled them from
a bow tie camera.
- Long story.
Look, the point is,
this is the same guy that
kidnapped your cousin Esperanza
and turned her into a
meta-assassin against her will.
One of these photos,
this one,
shows our mystery man
getting out of his car.
My dad traced his plates
and tracked the car
to a rented parking space
at a nearby lot.
So now all we have to do
is to wait for him to show up.
- Cool.
Just checking,
are there any other stories
you wanna work on first?
- [laughs]
What could need
our attention more than this?
Your cousin was a victim,
Allegra,
and now some secret
organization is using her.
I mean, how many others
are they using?
- We need to help them.
- Right, I mean,
no one wants to find out
what happened to Esperanza
more than me, but...
is this really what matters
the most to you right now?
- Yeah. Now come on,
get your stuff.
Kamilla is going to see if she
can recover any other photos.
You and I have a stakeout date.
- You're the boss.
- Brain activity looks good.
No sign that
you're going nuts.
- And my blood work?
- CBC,
metabolic rate,
all normal for a speedster,
just a small spike in cortisol.
Katie says that
sleep monitor on your wrist
will tell us if there's
anything seriously wrong,
but if you ask me,
you just had a nightmare.
- I don't know.
Ramsey seemed so real.
Something feels off.
I just can't
put my finger on it.
- Hi, there.
My name is Iris West-Allen.
I'm with "The Citizen."
I was wondering if I could
ask you a few questions.
- Sorry, not interested.
- Hi.
Same paper, same question.
- What the hell's
going on here?
I don't have time for this.
I'm late for work.
- Which is where, exactly?
- None of your business.
- Okay, you know what?
You're right.
We will just run our photos
without any comments.
[dramatic music]
- What photos?
♪ ♪
- You know what?
I'm sure your employer
will love
the free exposure.
- All right,
have it your way.
- Easy,
I've got a Taser.
- And I have a business card.
Maelstrom Couriers,
the premiere name
in high-end transport.
- Transporting what exactly?
- Whatever the wealthy would
prefer to keep under the radar,
specialty items mostly.
That woman in a coma
was a government job.
Meister's party, well, that was
more like designated driving
for billionaires
falling off the wagon.
Today it's priceless
family jewels.
- You're an Uber
for the uberrich.
- What I am is late.
- Sorry to bother you.
Thank you.
- That was a bust.
- Yep.
- But the bright side is,
we have time for other stories
we might be putting off.
Got any in mind?
- You know,
I don't know,
I think there's something
that we missed.
I don't want to
move off of this yet.
- [breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
Mom?
Is this another nightmare?
- No, Barry.
This is much, much worse.
[dramatic music swells]
- You're the Speed Force.
- Yes.
It's been a while since
we've talked like this.
I've missed it.
- You need to help.
I don't understand
what's happening to me.
- You used your blood
to save your friend's life,
but in the process,
you've endangered your own.
♪ ♪
A small amount of Ramsey's
cells remain from the attack,
hidden from the eye.
♪ ♪
- Ramsey's infected me.
- And more than you realize.
Ramsey's sentience,
his very being,
resides in his cells.
- That's how he knew
I'm the Flash,
about Crisis.
If this...
if this is all in my mind,
then where's
my real body?
- After your friend,
Frost, examined you,
you came back home, dropped
your keys in that bowl,
poured a glass of water,
then the infection took hold.
[eerie music]
As we speak,
Ramsey's infection is spreading
through your body
and your mind.
Your speed-healing is trying
to hold off his disease,
but, ultimately,
it's up to you to resist him.
- Is he trying to kill me?
- Worse, I'm afraid.
He wants
to take control of you
and bend you to his will.
- Then he's gonna lose.
- There must be
something that points
to where Esperanza was taken.
I don't know.
Hospital records?
Or what about
that auction photo?
That mystery man was a dead
end, but Barry did say
that there were a lot
of shady people at that gala,
so, I don't know, maybe one of
them might be a new lead.
- Or...
we could talk about how
your husband is the Flash.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- How did you...
- Nash Wells told me.
- You're not gonna...
Is this the story that
you've been trying to tell?
Allegra, Barry's identity
cannot be exposed.
- No, not that.
This.
You've been avoiding
it all day.
- It's not time for that yet.
- Well, according to this,
it will be in two days,
and call it a hunch,
but I don't think
you're planning
to write it then either.
♪ ♪
I ever tell you
why I wanted
to be a reporter
in the first place?
It was because of your article
about the Streak.
- [sighs]
You know,
that was the first name
that I ever gave
to the Flash.
Back then, I didn't
even know that he was Barry.
- And back then, I was just
a troubled kid in Iron Heights,
but your article,
it made me
believe in the impossible,
that maybe someday
I could be like you,
chasing stories,
uncovering the truth.
You gave me hope
when I had none...
Just like you have every day
I've worked here.
I don't know how you're
gonna bring yourself
to write this article.
I just know
you're never going to forgive
yourself if you don't.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- [breathing heavily]
What's...how did I?
[laughter]
[silverware clattering]
- Allen.
Looks like we're both
back on our feet.
- Babe, I'm glad
you're feeling better.
- Thanks.
- Look, I made you a plate.
- Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm,
delicious.
- I'm all about
these mashed potatoes.
- I'm gonna need a
second helping of these beans.
That's both praise,
and a warning.
[laughter]
Uh-oh.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- [whispers]
This is wrong.
- Everyone.
I've got homemade lasagna.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
[all eating nosily]
- Nom.
- Barry.
It's rude not to eat.
- You're not Iris.
This isn't real.
- [breathing heavily]
I'm not gonna give in to you.
- Barry, you misjudge me.
I'm just here to enjoy supper
with good friends
and perhaps offer you a gift.
- What could you
possibly offer me?
[silverware clatters]
all: Everything.
- [breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Ah!
[screams]
[grunting]
- Barry, you can't run away
from your own mind,
at least not without
considerable pain.
Then again,
you're always trying
to run away from
your problems, aren't you?
- [screams]
- You've literally
had a newspaper
warning of your demise.
You've done nothing
to change your fate.
It's almost like you want
to make Iris a widow.
- Shut up!
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
This isn't real.
- These deaths were real.
- [gasps]
- None of them had to die.
Join me,
and you'll never have to.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[music box playing
"Hush, Little Baby"]
♪ ♪
[baby cries]
- Nora.
Hey.
[whooshing]
Please, let me hold her.
I know it's not real, I just...
please, I just wanna
pretend for...
please,
just for a second...
I just...please,
I wanna hold my baby.
- That's not my choice, Barry.
- Why are you
showing this to me?
- [echoing]
I'm not showing you anything.
All of this
is coming from you.
- No, it's not.
No, it's not.
No...
- Look deep within,
Barry Allen.
This is your mind,
your visions,
your doubt.
- We all die without you.
- You leave me alone forever.
- Your city will burn.
- She's even faster than ever.
[laughs]
The negative Speed Forces
were too much, even for me,
and now, Barry,
everyone is dead.
- [breathing heavily]
- It doesn't have
to be like this, Barry.
Here, let me show you.
Accept my lifeblood,
and you could use it to achieve
so much more
than I ever could.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Become a hero beyond
your wildest dreams.
- [inhales sharply]
- The power to
strike down death,
life eternal,
the grand miracle
at your command.
Save the world and live.
Have all you want.
[baby cooing]
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
- She's so beautiful.
[Ramsey]
- Embrace it, Barry.
Just confess the truth.
Do you have doubts?
- [whispers]
I do.
- It's a beautiful life, Barry.
All you have to do
is choose it.
Choose life.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- [breathing shakily]
- Barry...
You must
gather your strength.
Focus.
Time is running out.
♪ ♪
[Joe]
- Thought you all
would want to see this.
[camera clicking and beeping]
Witnesses heard
the explosion
but didn't
see much else.
- There's gotta be at least
half a dozen cameras
covering this lot. I...
- And not one of them caught
anyone entering or exiting
the scene when
this all went down.
It's like a ghost
did this.
- So the guy
you questioned was killed
in the same lot you
questioned him on the same day.
- Yeah.
- It gets worse.
This blew away from the scene.
I thought about turning it in
to the cops, but I only saw it
because there's some major UV
energy coming off this thing.
- You can see that?
- Boss, this really
feels like a job
for your husband's friend.
- Oh, no, Kamilla knows
that Barry's the Flash.
- Seriously?
Since when?
- Last summer.
Cisco used to be Vibe.
- Okay, look, guys,
I think this mystery
goes a lot deeper
than we thought.
- And it's a lot
more dangerous.
- So if you guys
wanna walk away...
- Not a chance.
- That makes two of us.
- Well, Boss, looks like
Team Citizen has a new mission.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[Nora]
- It's okay, Barry.
I'm here.
I'm sorry it took me
so long to find you.
Ramsey's infection is
stronger than anything
we've ever faced,
and it's only getting stronger.
- [grunts]
[whispers]
I think I know why.
- You feel doubt.
- I do.
- You've answered
our call before.
It's always been difficult.
What's changed?
- I've lived more.
I've gotten married,
seen a future where I'll have
a daughter who's the best
of me and Iris combined.
Most of my life has been
driven by my past, but...
but now, I...
It finally feels like
I'm living for myself.
I don't wanna leave my family
or my friends.
I don't want to die.
I know that's selfish.
[crying]
I'm sorry I let you down.
- Barry.
No person is immune
to fear and doubt...
No matter how brave...
That's what makes
you human, Barry.
But the courage
to move forward,
even in the face
of overwhelming odds,
that's what makes you a hero.
That's what
makes you the Flash.
- Thank you.
I needed to hear that.
- Don't blame yourself.
- His lies...
They were
so convincing.
- That's because he never lied.
[ominous music]
- What do you mean?
- That's what makes
Ramsey so dangerous.
He manipulates the truth
to spread his disease.
- What, so...
so the part about
his cells allowing me to save
the world from Crisis and...
♪ ♪
Still survive is true?
- Yes.
But that path's not for you.
- Why not?
- Barry,
you must understand...
- That you want me to
leave behind everyone I love
when there's a way to save me?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What is it?
- It's Barry's sleep monitor.
This can't be right.
His vitals are spiking.
- Barry, your fever is rising.
You must calm down.
- Stop telling me what to do!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- His temperature
is burning up.
- Why isn't he speed-healing?
- I've seen this fever before.
He's being taken over
right now.
♪ ♪
- His temperature is rising.
We could really use some
cold powers right about now.
- No, Ramsey's infection
doesn't respond to ice.
We need to
treat him medicinally.
Inserting 10ccs
of naproxen sodium.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
All my pain,
all my suffering,
it's been because of you
because you would rather
I be the Flash
than have anything
that I want!
- Barry, please.
I am not denying the burden
that you've carried,
but the Speed Force
has only ever tried to be
a guide on this path
that you've chosen.
- The lightning bolt shot down
from the sky and struck me!
I didn't choose this!
You decided
to change my life,
my family's life,
my entire future.
This was done to me!
[dramatic music]
- We need help.
Frost.
♪ ♪
Frost!
Hey, hey!
Hey.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
- [hyperventilating]
- Just breathe.
Just breathe.
- Please understand.
The role you play is vital
to the balance of all things.
- Oh, stop.
- There are
universal forces at stake.
They must be protected.
- What about the rest of us?
- She's right.
There are
universal forces at stake.
It's just a pity she doesn't
consider your life among them.
- Don't listen to him.
He wants to possess your form
no matter the cost.
- Cost?
All those headstones?
Those people are dead because
of my connection to you.
How many times
do I have to suffer for you?
When is it
your turn to suffer?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Do you even feel pain?
- No,
at least not as you know it.
- How could it?
The Speed Force isn't human.
It doesn't know what
it means to be alive,
to have a family, to love.
It only pretends.
- Ramsey's infection
is twisting your heart.
You have to fight it.
Barry.
These aren't
your true feelings.
- What do you know
about the truth?
This isn't what you look like.
This isn't my old bedroom.
It's a trick.
This is you manipulating me
so I'll do what you want.
- That's not true.
I care about you.
- All it cares about
is using you.
- Barry, you must listen to me.
- No, I don't!
You're not my mom.
You're the reason I buried her.
- [yells]
[tense music]
[groans]
- [distorted]
Barry!
No!
- [crying]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[muffled cries]
- The Monitor,
Thawne, the Speed Force,
for too long,
others have used you.
Take command of your life!
[whispers]
Forever.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
- [groans]
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, I have to.
It's the only way to survive.
[pounding on door]
- We don't have much time
until he returns.
Barry, look at me.
Accepting Ramsey's blood
would save your body
from the coming Crisis
but not your soul.
You would lose the best of you:
your joy,
your passion,
your light,
the part of you
that Iris loves.
[pounding on door]
[growling]
- Don't listen to it.
It lies.
- Come on!
Barry!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
- [groans]
- Only you can
defeat this, Barry.
- The choice is yours.
- [screams]
[EKG beeping]
- You beat it.
- Took me a while,
but, yeah, I beat it.
- [chuckles]
[tranquil music]
♪ ♪
[somber music]
- [sighs]
My name is Iris West-Allen
and I once met a young man,
a superhero
who I called the Streak.
The world has come to know him
as the Fastest Man Alive,
the Scarlet Speedster,
the Flash.
But no matter what title
you choose for him,
he'll always be remembered
as the protector
of our amazing city
and its citizens,
as a beacon of hope
for us all,
and as the man
who sacrificed himself
again and again
so we could live.
♪ ♪
Today we say good-bye to him,
not because he was taken
but because
he gave himself willingly.
And in the end, that's what
makes him deserving
of the greatest title
of all...
[whispers]
Hero.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[phone chirps]
[spirited music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- [sighs]
[electrical whirring]
[distorted zapping]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
Mar Novu.
You ran and ran
across infinite Earths,
and now you've
nowhere left to run.
[suspenseful music]
- It was like
being back in prison
only locked up in my own mind.
All the terror I felt,
the horrible things I saw,
they were all there
buried deep
inside me just
waiting to come out
the whole time.
Took a lot to win.
Everything that
makes life worth living.
Thank you.
- You deserve
some of the credit.
It takes something special
to beat a sentient infection
that not even speed-healing
can cure.
- Well, it's not over yet,
so let's get back to work.
- Whoa, whoa, what do you mean?
What are you doing?
Just get some rest.
Iris is gonna
be here any minute.
- Crisis will be here
in less than 36 hours.
We have to find Ramsey,
stop him,
make sure there's still
a world left to save.
- [sighs]
And away he goes.
You wanna talk
about what happened?
- I already talked
about it with Caity.
- Okay.
What'd she say?
- With Crisis approaching,
we decided it would be best
if she handles
the medical emergencies.
I'll take a back seat.
- Are you okay with that?
- It's what's
best for the team.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, I got here
as fast as I could.
How are you?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Really, I'm okay.
- Your husband
had an infection...
It messed with his brain
quite a bit, but we handled it.
- [sighs]
Okay, well,
just to be safe,
I am not leaving you again
for the rest of the night.
[computer beeping]
What you working on?
- Just running
some diagnostics,
little maintenance.
- Why don't you ask Cisco?
We could go home,
spend some time together.
- Why are you
asking so many questions?
- [chuckles]
I don't know.
You know, sometimes
the reporter brain
in me has a
mind of its own.
[clears throat]
I will...
let you get back to work.
[computer beeping]
Hey, guys.
That's not Barry.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[whispers]
Careful.
- Hey!
Barry.
Hey.
- [snarls]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
[electricity zapping]
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
- [distorted]
Welcome, my blood brother.
I am the world's salvation
come to save it
from all that ails it.
Soon, the entire world
will embrace
Bloodwork!
[intense music]
[inhales and exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
[frenetic music]
- Greg, move your head!