BARRY: How often do you think
about why your friends came into your life?
Was it random, by design,
or maybe a little of both?
Regardless of the reason...
...some friends, you just know,
are gonna be by your side for a while.
Others, you're not so sure.
And then there's that one friend...
...who, well, you hope someday
becomes something more.
But friend will have to do for now...
...and that's okay, I guess.
I'm glad you invited Caitlin and Cisco.
-They're cool, right?
-They saved your life.
That makes them the coolest people
I've ever met.
It's nice that you guys became friends.
To friends, old and new.
Ooh. I'm up. Wish me luck.
-I am going to destroy you.
-Don't get cocky, West.
IRIS:
Mm.
BARRY:
Guys, I have a problem.
We all do when guys like him exist.
Yeah. He's so hot.
Uh, I mean, genetically speaking.
Because I'm a geneticist, of course.
-God, do I sound like Felicity?
-I'm not talking about Eddie.
I'm talking about this.
I can't feel anything.
Yeah, that's usually what happens
when you drink too much.
No, the alcohol is not affecting me.
I mean, I literally feel nothing.
It's your hypermetabolism. I need a sample.
-I'll get more shots.
-I swear I had a Vacutainer.
Wait, you carry a blood-collection kit?
You have your hobbies...
-Fourteenth floor, secure.
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Roger that.
[WHISTLING]
Hold off on that check.
Lock down the building. Hold it!
-Don't come near me.
-You need to come with me. Come on.
Get down.
[EXPLOSION]
-Ah. Still nothing?
-I can't get drunk.
I mean, I'm only 25,
and my drinking days are already over.
Come on, Allen, you're up.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
There was a bombing on Eighth and Pass.
-I gotta go, babe.
IRIS: Okay.
Sorry, guys.
I've got an early shift at Jitters.
-We'll catch up tomorrow. Great.
CAITLIN: I'm beat.
It's getting late anyway, so I'm just gonna...
[WINDOW CLEANER]
Help! Somebody!
Guys, there's a window washer,
and he's gonna fall.
Don't try and catch him.
You don't have super-strength.
Is there a bed store near here?
What if I get mattresses and stack them?
-Barry, this isn't a Road Runner cartoon.
WINDOW CLEANER: Help! Help!
How fast would I need to go
to run up a building?
How far up do you need to go?
WINDOW CLEANER:
Hurry! Somebody!
Uh, I don't know, 50 meters give or take.
Thirty-two point fifty-seven...
Guys, hurry.
CAITLIN:
Just run really fast and you'll be fine.
-Maintain velocity on the way down, or...
-Or what?
-Splat.
-Great.
WINDOW CLEANER: Help!
-All right, all right, all right.
Here it goes.
Barry, what have you got?
Bombers typically have
their own unique signatures.
Crimped wires, fragmentation.
The level of sophistication is telling
once I've analyzed it.
-You show me a bomb, I can find a clue in it.
-Sounds like there's a "but" coming.
Yeah. I haven't found any sign
of an oxidizing agent.
-It's as if the floor just blew itself up.
-Things don't just blow up.
Security guard said our bomber
was a woman, red hair.
Also cut the security cameras.
There's no footage.
But there might be something else.
Some kind of small charge
blasted the doorknob off.
-Any idea what's missing?
-My guess is one of these files.
-It will take days to figure out which one.
-Let's let Barry do his thing.
[CHATTERING]
-What's going on?
-I have no idea.
Came in here like they owned the place.
Been talking to Singh for the last half hour.
This can't be good.
-General Eiling, this is Detective West.
-Detective.
What's this all about?
The Army's taking over
the bombing investigation.
I'll need everything you have.
Physical evidence, photos...
-...witness interviews, notes.
-I've been on the job 20 years.
Never heard of the Army
investigating anything civilian.
Well, it's not civilian. She's one of ours.
We'll send over everything we got.
Very kind of you.
I think we'll take it now, though.
Give them what they want, Joe.
You heard him, Joe. Give me what I want.
Hey, what's going on?
General Eiling is relieving us
from the bombing case.
Give these men everything that's relevant.
Sure thing, yeah.
You and a few civilians from S.T.A.R. Labs
might wanna check into that.
I think we might.
Can I talk to you for a minute, Joe?
It's about Iris.
IRIS:
Hey, Dad. You're home early.
What were you doing
at the bomb site last night?
Don't deny you were there.
Officer Vukovich saw you.
-It's complicated.
-You can't be coming to every crime scene...
...because you're worried about Eddie.
He's a big boy.
I didn't go there to see Eddie. I...
I went there to see the Streak.
The Streak.
Hmm.
-What is that?
-My blog.
I've been collecting posts about
the Streak sightings and writing about them.
Baby, there's no Streak.
Yes, there is. I saw him last night, Dad.
I looked right at him.
Something incredible is happening in
Central City, and I am gonna write about it.
If you'll excuse me, I have to get to work.
Blogging about supernatural events
doesn't really pay well.
[IRIS CHUCKLES]
CISCO: A VA file number is all the info
you have on the bomber?
C.C.P.D.'s been ordered off the case.
-Well, who has the power to do that?
-The Army.
Yeah, some general.
His name was Eiling, I think.
General Wade Eiling.
-You know him?
WELLS: Yeah, I know him.
About 10 years ago General
Wade Eiling contracted S.T.A.R. Labs...
...to develop enhanced gene therapies
for soldiers.
I was interested in the medical benefits
for civilians.
General Eiling really wanted
to develop mind-reading capabilities...
...for interrogation purposes.
I ended the study when I saw his techniques,
but our split was less than amicable.
He took the evidence
I collected on the bombing.
Everything but the folder.
Well, lucky for us,
the VA finally joined the new millennium...
...and digitized their records.
A lot of redacted info...
...but our girl's name is Bette Sans Souci,
an EOD specialist for the Army.
-EOD?
-Bombs.
-Is there an address?
-Hold on. Here we go.
One person in case of emergency:
Cameron Scott, Anglewood.
Bette Sans Souci?
-I need you to come with me.
-Don't touch me, please.
Get whatever you're wearing off of you.
Hurry.
Barry, can you hear me? Barry?
There must be a perfectly reasonable
explanation for why he's not answering.
Barry!
-Uh...
BARRY: Don't ask.
I'm gonna ask. Where's my suit?
It's gone.
What do you mean, it's gone?
-What did you do with my suit?
-It blew up, dude.
I managed to get out of it
before it went kaboom.
My suit went kaboom?
Fun fact about Bette Sans Souci:
She's not carrying bombs.
She touched the emblem on the suit
and turned it into a bomb.
She's a metahuman.
With the ability to cause spontaneous
combustion upon tactile contact.
-She blew up my suit.
-You have like three more.
Okay, I have two. And I loved that one.
-All right, what else do we know about her?
-Oh, I don't know, she's pure evil?
We're gonna find this girl
and send her butt into the pipeline.
No one blows my tech to smithereens
and gets away with it.
Unless she looks like that.
I don't think she meant to hurt me.
Or her being a metahuman explains
General Eiling's interest in her.
And why he stole the case from us.
He didn't want anyone
to know what she could do.
-Detective.
-Doctor. So human bomb.
Must be Tuesday in Central City.
Yes. And General Eiling's not one
to give up a potential asset without a fight.
-We have to find her before he does.
-Barry, can I see you for a second?
When were you planning on telling me
that Iris saw the Streak?
That was not planned.
She caught me off guard.
We had a deal.
Keep her in the dark about metahumans,
and I don't go Floyd Mayweather on you.
-Okay. Joe, I know...
-And she's writing a blog now.
-I already talked to her about that.
-Talk to her again.
And be more convincing.
Okay.
-You mean right now?
-Yes, I do.
You gotta stop writing about this guy.
-He doesn't even exist.
-I saw him, Barry.
He wears a red suit,
like a uniform or something...
...with a lightning bolt on his chest.
[CHUCKLES]
Iris, come on.
You were drinking last night at the bar.
I was not drunk, and I know what I saw.
He wears a mask.
I think he smiled at me.
Okay, first of all, if he's wearing a mask,
he doesn't want people to know who he is.
It doesn't matter who he is.
What matters is that people know
that he's out there.
[SIGHS]
What is wrong with you?
This is important to me.
Why can't you be more supportive?
I'm just...
You haven't even put your name on it.
I mean, how serious can you be
about an anonymous blog?
[SCOFFS]
Okay, you know what?
Our entire lives, you couldn't scream
loud enough that the impossible existed.
Now it's actually happening in Central City...
...I have proof of it,
and you don't wanna know about it?
That doesn't make sense, Barry.
So when you're ready to tell me
what this routine is really about...
...then we can talk.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Yeah.
CISCO:We've piggybacked
onto Eiling's surveillance.
According to what they're saying,
the lovely Ms. Sans Souci...
...was just spotted in Anglewood.
The same neighborhood
as Dr. Harold Hadley's office...
...the military surgeon
who performed procedures on her.
That's why she was looking for the folder.
-You gotta get to her before Eiling does.
-Okay.
-Sergeant Sans Souci.
-You remember me. Good.
Because I remember you, doctor.
I remember waking up from a coma.
You'd started cutting me open.
I was trying to help ease your condition.
You couldn't control it.
You did this to me. You and Eiling.
[BETTE GRUNTS]
-Go bring me my asset.
-Sir.
You okay? I can get you out of here. I can
help you understand what happened to you.
-How?
-Because it happened to me too.
Please.
SOLDIER [OVER RADIO]:
Target is gone.
WELLS: As the detonation dispersed
throughout Central City...
...a number of people were exposed
to a wave of unquantifiable energy.
One of those people was you.
You were in Central City 10 months ago.
Uh, I had just returned from Afghanistan.
I was there diffusing roadside bombs...
...and shrapnel ripped through me.
I was flown back Stateside.
Spent months at the base recuperating.
And next thing I know...
...I became the thing that almost killed me.
And Eiling's favorite new lab rat.
The dark matter must have combined
with the bomb particulate inside your body.
I thought Eiling did this to me.
Eiling is not smart enough
to create someone like you...
...but clever enough to see your value.
Do you know of any others
who were changed?
-There have been a few.
-But no one that looks like you.
I'm sorry. That was inappropriate.
[CHUCKLES]
-Please don't leave.
-I know how to perform a lobotomy.
WELLS:
Cell structure's unlike anything I've seen.
Her nitrogen levels are off the charts.
You think we can help her?
To answer that,
we have to understand how she works.
To understand that,
we have to study her in action.
You want her to blow stuff up.
-Yes. Now we're talking.
-Not in here. She's too unstable.
-I know.
-I know you know.
So this is your life now, huh?
Testing people like me?
Stopping people like you.
It's not what I thought I'd be doing.
Actually, aside from Barry, you're
the first metahuman that we've tested.
-"Metahuman"?
-It's just a term.
Oh, my God. What happened?
-Why didn't you say that you were shot?
-It just grazed me.
There's something in there.
A tracker.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Lock down the pipeline. Get Bette
out of here. I'll take care of Eiling.
Harrison Wells.
-How the might have fallen.
-General.
S.T.A.R. Labs.
This place used to be so important.
Tell me, what does one do
after such a spectacular public failure?
One adapts. One evolves.
One becomes intent
on reversing one's fortune.
Always the idealist.
-What do you want, Wade?
-Where's my asset?
-I have no idea what you're talking about.
-We tracked her here, Harrison.
Turn her over before you see the rest
of your precious palace crumble.
Wade, Wade, Wade.
We could've changed the world, you and I.
Four hundred twenty-seven kPa's.
Her Trauzl rating is around 45.
That's the same as any plastique.
"Plastique." Ha! First try.
Didn't really think
this one through, did you?
Downrange insurgents
started booby-trapping cars.
For the rest of my tour,
I was terrified to touch another vehicle.
Now I'm gonna spend the rest of my life
terrified to touch another human being.
Have they tried to help you?
Uh...
They've helped me
learn how to use my powers...
...not reverse them.
If they could reverse it
so you weren't a metahuman...
...would you?
A friend told me
I was given my speed for a reason...
...that I was chosen.
I don't know if I believe that.
But I always wanted to help people.
Now I can.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
I'm sorry.
-Hey, Joe.
-I see your little conversation with Iris...
...was a rousing success.
She just posted another story
about the Streak.
-Joe, I tried. I really tried.
-She's got her name on it now, Barry.
-What? Joe...
-It's my fault.
I shouldn't have asked you to say anything.
I just wanted you to know. Okay? Bye.
What was that about?
[SIGHS]
Iris posted about the Streak again.
She signed her name to it.
-Oh, that's not good.
-No.
If one of these bad metahumans
figures she knows something...
They may target her. I know.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Sorry, we're closed.
Oh, my God. It's you.
[IN DISTORTED VOICE] Iris West,
I hear you've been writing about me.
You are real.
I should, um...
Let me just clean up...
FLASH:
Meet me on the roof.
-I'll give you a head start.
-Okay.
I need you to stop writing about me.
There are a lot of people
who need someone like you right now...
...to know that you're out there.
I have so many questions.
Where are you from?
I can't say.
Who are you?
I can't tell you that either.
How can you do what you do?
You're a terrible interview.
There's more to this
than you can understand.
Just trust me, please. I need you to stop.
Can you stop?
Running into buildings and rescuing people
without them even knowing you're there?
-I don't do this for the glory.
-So why do you?
Look, I have this friend...
...and he had something terrible happen
to him when he was a kid.
And his whole life, he's been telling stories
about this impossible thing.
And people laughed at him,
and shrinks analyzed him.
And he's been searching
for an explanation ever since.
But now suddenly it's like he's lost his faith.
But you, you are proof that he wasn't crazy.
Help me save my friend.
He's a lucky guy.
Hey, what's wrong?
-Did Eiling find out you're here?
-No.
Caitlin was about to give me
the not-so-good news.
The shrapnel in your body
has merged with you on a cellular level.
The technology required
to unsplice your DNA...
It hasn't been invented yet.
Bette...
It's okay.
Roger that. I...
I just need a minute.
Don't worry. I'm pretty sure I can cry
without blowing stuff up.
What now?
She joins us. Becomes a part of the team.
Barry, you have an amazing ability
to help people.
She makes things explode.
She's the first metahuman not hell-bent
on destroying the city.
It's too dangerous.
-She's not going in the pipeline.
-I'm not suggesting she go in.
But were she to remain at S.T.A.R. Labs,
it would put all of us at risk.
From who, Eiling?
Eiling is a dangerous man, Barry.
We do not want him as an enemy.
After the lightning bolt,
what if you hadn't found me?
It could've been me.
Hunted, on the run, cut off
from everyone I know and care about.
You guys saved me.
And I wanna save her
just as bad as you do, Barry.
We all do.
Joe.
What are you doing here?
Going over the materials
in your mom's case.
How's it going with you?
Stellar. I made friends with a human bomb...
...who I promised I could help
and then I couldn't.
And I finally diagnosed
why Iris is writing about the Streak.
She's doing it for me.
[CHUCKLES]
To prove the impossible is possible.
How do you know that?
The Streak may have talked to her.
Barry, don't you think
Iris would recognize your voice?
[IN DISTORTED VOICE] No, I can do
this cool thing with my vocal cords...
...where I vibrate them so I sound like this.
[LAUGHING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I know.
It's cool. It's cool.
-Whoa.
-Yeah.
Well, you put that out there now, so...
I want to keep her safe.
You know the only way to get her to stop
is to tell her the truth.
Man, you really wanna tell her.
I tell her everything.
Hmm.
Not everything.
[CHUCKLES]
Is it that obvious?
Not to her.
How long have you known for?
[CHUCKLES]
I have watched you be in love with Iris since
you were old enough to know what love is.
Heh. And I've been waiting years
for you to tell her.
But you haven't.
-Guess I was too slow.
-Hmm.
Now she's happy
and with someone else, so...
When the universe wants
to make something happen...
...whether it be giving a young man
lightning speed...
...or putting two people together...
...it has a way of figuring those things out.
I gotta get home.
Thanks.
[CHUCKLES]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
BETTE: Cisco?
-He went home.
I think our Cisco's developing a little bit
of a crush on you.
Not sure I'm prizewinning
date material anymore.
Change is hard.
The same accident that changed you
put me in this chair.
Sorry. I didn't know.
I don't share that story with you
to garner sympathy.
-I tell it to illustrate a larger point.
-What point is that?
That I would do anything...
...to get back what I lost.
As would you.
I would.
I just don't know how.
You soldiers,
you call yourselves sheepdogs.
Am I right?
Happy and normal
until someone attacks our flock.
Every good person who was changed
that night, people like you...
...people like Barry Allen,
those people are your flock now, Bette.
And General Eiling will never stop
attacking that flock.
And he always gets his target.
Unless you stop him.
You know your duty, sergeant.
Kill Eiling.
One last mission...
...and then you go home.
Where's Bette?
-She left.
BARRY: What do you mean?
-Where'd she go?
-She didn't say.
Well, where the hell could she be?
SOLDIER:
Let's go. Go, go, go.
On me.
-I'm ready to give myself up.
-Oh, I highly doubt that.
Think you can put one over on me?
You can't.
-Stand down, soldier.
CISCO: I got back on the military feed.
Looks like they've gone to the waterfront
to rendezvous with Bette.
She's turning herself in.
She's not turning herself in.
Please let him get there in time.
All over the world,
people are plotting to destroy our country.
To end our lives.
Brave American soldiers
are gonna die in that fight.
But they don't have to. Because of you...
...we could have victory.
All I've ever wanted
was to make the world a safer place.
And it will be...
...when you're not in it.
EILING:
Take cover!
What are you doing here?
Being a soldier
doesn't mean you're a murderer.
Don't become one now.
[GRUNTS]
-I'm sorry. I didn't see him.
BETTE: Don't be.
It's not your fault. I'm glad you stopped me.
-I'll get you back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
-Barry.
Dr. Wells, he...
He...
BARRY: We have a problem.
-Is Bette okay?
No. Eiling killed her.
-She's glowing. She's gonna detonate.
CAITLIN: Oh, my God.
-A mass that size, the explosion would be...
-Devastating.
-You have to get her away from the city.
-But there's no time.
Can I run on water?
I built up enough speed to run up a building.
How fast do I need to go to run on water?
Assuming your weight...
...450 pounds of force per step
for vertical suspension.
-Accounting for fluid drag...
-Approximately 650 miles an hour.
You have to outrun the blast,
or you'll die too.
Nothing out of the ordinary occurred.
The military was simply conducting
an underwater weapons test.
There is no need for panic or alarm.
Central City is safe, I guarantee you.
He murdered Bette right in front of me,
and there's nothing we can do to him?
Powerful men have a way
of avoiding consequences.
-You gonna be okay?
-Yeah.
You can walk on water.
Puts you in pretty interesting company.
If you came to do laundry,
I already have a load in.
Uh, no, I came to talk.
[BARRY CLEARS THROAT]
I...
[SIGHS]
I was working a case...
...someone I really thought
I could help befriend...
...but they died.
Barry, I'm really sorry.
I didn't know her that well, but it still hurts.
And as bad as I feel right now...
...I know how much worse it is
to lose someone who's family.
Iris, writing about this stuff...
...putting your name out there,
it's dangerous.
So I'm asking you one last time,
please stop.
And I am asking you one last time
to tell me what is really going on with you.
Why am I the only one of us
who's interested in this?
I guess just all this stuff with my family,
I finally just...
...put it behind me.
I'm asking you to also.
That may have been how this started,
but it's about something more for me now.
Whoever this Streak is,
wherever he comes from...
...I am not stopping
until the rest of the world believes in him.
Maybe we shouldn't see each other
for a while.
Yeah.
Can I get another club soda, please?
Hey.
-Hey. What are you guys doing here?
-We thought we should have a toast.
Doesn't work on me, remember?
Barry Allen, you of all people should know
that nothing is impossible.
I distilled a highly fermented
potent suspension.
It's basically 500-proof.
I figured if anybody could use
a drink tonight, it was you.
So here's to Bette.
Bette.
[COUGHING]
Whoa. Oh!
-That hits you quick.
-Are you buzzed?
Um...
Yeah. Heh. Yeah, I'm buzzed for sure.
Whoa.
Oh, that is good stuff.
[BARRY CHUCKLES]
And it's gone.
-Right.
-Work in progress.
BARRY: For a guy who has experienced
his fair share of mysteries...
...one mystery I still can't figure out
is why some people come into our lives...
...why some people go,
and others become a part of you.
Some friendships feel like they'll last forever.
-Hey, sweetheart.
-Hey.
There's dinner in the fridge.
Okay, thanks.
-Iris, about your blog...
-I don't wanna talk about it, okay?
BARRY:
And others end far too soon.
Not every friendship is meant
to last a lifetime.
What does last forever is the pain
when that person is gone.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
EILING:
I was wrong about you, Harrison.
You're still one step ahead.
Impressive for a man
without the use of his legs.
I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
A girl who can transform ordinary objects
into explosives with the touch of her hand.
Today I saw a man who can move faster
than the blink of an eye. Extraordinary.
The night your particle accelerator died
was the night the impossible was born.
I think we should start working
together again.
I think you should leave.
I can have a squadron of soldiers
here in minutes.
You know I can have an army
of press here...like that.
Believe me, general,
I'd be more than happy...
...to testify to your involvement in activities
that were less than humane.
Threaten me again,
and I will end you, general.
And I am not talking about your career.
You know,
I figured out your little secret, Wells.
Won't be long before the public
catches on as well.
-This is everything we've worked to achieve.
-The same goals, but not the same means.
I will not have this project end
before it even begins.
And as long as he's on my premises...
...I will not have him subjected
to that kind of cruelty anymore. We're done.
We're done.
General, get out.
Hey.
[CREATURE GROWLING AND GRUNTING]
It's okay.
It's okay, boy. It's okay.
He's gone.
Don't you worry.
I have a whole different future
in mind for you.