[Nora] Bart's going to be okay.
He has to be...
He will be, Nora.
[sobbing] You don't know that.
Nobody does.
Caitlin, we can't get back home.
Central City is being torn apart.
My dad's out there doing something
that will probably get him killed.
It just feels
like everything's falling apart.
[electricity crackling]
Get out of the car. Go, go.
[tires screeching]
Heaven help us.
Fine. You got what you wanted.
I'm here.
Now tell me what you were doing
at the Flash Museum.
What do you really want, Heart?
My, oh, my.
You're really direct.
Then again, you're meeting me
for the first time.
We're bound to learn new things
about each other.
Tell me what the hell is going on.
Or what?
You'll force me to?
Oh, Flash.
I'm the living god of speed.
The one.
Unlike you and your infernal spawn.
You're going to leave them alone.
Or I swear...
Are you threatening me, Flash?
Here?
Seriously?
You still can't comprehend
what you're dealing with.
So let me enlighten you.
Once upon a time,
there was a young physicist named August
who dreamed of moving faster than light.
So he developed a way
to achieve his goal
and created the Velocity formula.
But it wasn't enough,
because no matter how fast he ran,
he soon came to realize
one salient fact.
That he'd never be fast enough.
Heart, tell me how to stop this war.
Both sides are looking for you.
Including one that wants to kill you.
And what?
You're gonna turn me over to them?
Mm-mm.
You're too much of a hero
to sell me out.
Now, Impulse, that's a different story.
I said leave my son out of this.
Oh, but I can't.
He's the one who helped me
realize the truth.
That artificial speed would always
be a pale imitation of the real deal.
Spoiled little brat.
He's not just reckless, he's unworthy.
All the times we fought,
he was so cavalier with his gift.
A gift that should have been mine!
[inhales sharply]
And now it will be.
Thanks to you.
[laughs]
That's what this is all about.
You want organic speed.
[applauds]
Keep going.
Everything that's happened,
us finding you, your clones,
this war...
It was all a part of my plan.
To force your hand.
So why the act
if your memories are still intact?
That's the one thing I didn't foresee.
Memory loss is a side effect
of fracturing myself in time.
Who knew, right?
Then again, I knew you'd come
looking for answers,
which eventually, would bring you to me.
Give me the gift I deserve
and I'll save your precious city
by reabsorbing my other selves.
Or refuse my request...
watch your city burn.
There's no way that's happening.
Besides, what you're asking me to do,
it's impossible.
The impossible is your thing.
You can figure it out.
Or watch more cities fall,
as my army spreads
and this entire world is torn apart.
[laughs]
[hoots]
I can see those little wheels
turning in your head.
You're trying desperately
to think of a way out of this.
Well, guess what, there isn't.
So what's your answer?
- Answer me, damn it!
- I already did.
I said no.
Well, you'll change your mind.
You have no choice.
[yells]
[panting]
Kid.
You all right?
Yeah... Yeah.
Oh, thank God.
What happened?
Did you find the real me?
Yeah.
What did I say?
So what are we going to do
about Godspeed's ultimatum?
We have to give him what he wants.
Organic speed.
Nora, I'm never gonna do that.
Dad, everything will be destroyed.
Not just Bart, but whole families.
We have to protect them.
What about our family?
If Heart is Bart's Thawne,
that means he's already caused Bart
a lifetime of pain and suffering.
But we can stop this. Here.
In this time. By finding another way.
But we've tried everything, Dad,
and nothing's worked!
And now Bart's dying and we're still
no closer to ending this damn war!
Nora, honey, if his clones
could do this to your brother,
then what do you think would happen
if the real August Heart
got organic speed?
It just all feels so hopeless.
It never is. I promise you that.
He's right.
As long as we're still standing,
we can still win this.
Let's go check on your brother.
Kid, I know giving August Heart
his powers back is crazy,
but if we don't,
we'd better come up with another idea.
A big one.
Not a big one. A fast one.
[footsteps approaching]
What am I supposed to do now?
August.
I know that things seem
really hopeless right now,
but believe me when I tell you
that this team of ours...
If there is anyone
who can find a way out of this thing,
it is Team Flash.
I believe you.
I do, but I saw Barry's face
when we both came back.
It's true, isn't it?
I'm a monster, aren't I?
You don't have to be.
What if I don't have a choice?
You all think
I'm someone from the future.
A future where I'm supposedly a killer.
Obsessed with taking speed
and ruling the world.
You know how that feels?
Imagine getting the thing you want most,
your memories,
your whole life.
And then learn that you're the bad guy.
If that's true,
how am I supposed to live with that?
I'm no fortune teller,
but I can tell you that
the sorrow I feel coming from you,
August, bad guys...
They don't feel remorse like that.
Maybe the future
is not so set in stone after all.
[Chester] Hey.
Chuck, I'm done with pep talks, okay?
I can't charge your dad's gizmo.
Not now, not ever.
Allegra, I don't give a crap
about the S.E.E. right now.
Right now,
all I care about is my friend.
Now look, Esperanza chose to go
on that mission, that's not on you.
But you know what is?
The Flash being alive today
because you didn't go with her.
That doesn't make any sense.
That makes all the sense.
That Godspeed clone in the pipeline?
He was going to kill Barry.
[grunts]
And you stopped that.
Which means the Flash can get back
to the business of ending this war.
But Esperanza? She left to start one.
She let the city down. You didn't.
You helped lift it up.
You really think so?
Girl, I know so.
Now, I don't know about you,
but I'm ready to get back
to the business
of keeping Central City safe.
So what do you say, you with me?
I... I guess that means a yes?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[laughs] Cool.
Hey, don't forget the java this time.
[chuckles]
Ever since this war began,
we've been outfought and outnumbered.
That ends now.
For all their speed, our opponents,
no matter how fast they are,
they can't outrun a force of nature.
Big Nora! It's so good to see you!
Yeah, we've already met.
Remember when I first saw you?
I was like, "Oh, my gosh!
The freakin' Speed Force!"
And I was just so amazed and nervous,
and I just kept rambling
on and on and on
and totally embarrassing myself...
It's good to see you too, little Nora.
This is a rare pleasure, ma'am.
And if I may,
you look a whole lot like someone
very close to me.
I get that a lot.
Barry, Iris, it's good to see you again.
- Are the other Forces coming too?
- No.
With me here,
they're all working overtime
to keep the universe in balance.
I've seen what you all have been facing.
I've been fighting it myself
within the Speed Force.
Now, you all need to be at full strength
in order to defeat this threat.
Which is why whether
you're already a full speedster,
or have just a spark
of Speed Force inside of you,
I'm going to give you all a boost.
That is if everyone's okay with that.
- Schway.
- Yep.
That works.
- Barry, Bart's still...
- [Speed Force as Nora Allen] I know.
Oh, my impulsive boy.
[exhales]
[medical device beeping rapidly]
What in the world?
- Whoo-hoo! Oh, I'm back.
- Bart.
[laughs] Hi! [moans]
- Did you miss me? Did you miss me?
- [Nora chuckles]
Thank you for the reboot, SFN.
I appreciate it.
Oh. Speed Force Nana.
It's our little thing.
Oh, someone redid did my nails.
It must've been Caitlin.
Uncle Jay, you're...
You're here.
Uncle?
That's new. Um...
Yeah, I kinda like it. [chuckles]
It's good to finally meet you, Bart.
Yeah.
All right. What's next, Pops?
We end the civil war.
Once and for all.
[people screaming]
Hey, hey, hey,
you got to get out of here.
Come on.
You gotta get up. Run. Run!
We gotta get in contact with C.C.P.D.
[mechanical screech]
West!
[Kramer panting]
How did I...
What just happened?
You just ran as fast as the Flash.
[crackling]
Kramer!
Kramer, can you hear me?
Hey. Looking for me?
[Godspeed clones]
Kill the Adversary. Kill the Adversary.
Kill the Adversary.
Kill the Adversary and his allies.
Kill them. Kill them all.
Kill The Adversary and his allies.
All right. Remember, hit 'em hard.
Wear them down and drain their energy.
[Godspeed clones]
Kill The Adversary and his allies.
Kill them. Kill them all.
[mechanical droning]
Frost? Mecha-Vibe? How you doing?
[Mecha-Vibe] We're holding our own.
[Frost] Wouldn't say no
to back-up, though.
All right. We'll be there in a minute.
[XS] Dad?
Something's wrong.
What's happening to us?
Flash, we have a problem.
[mechanical whirring]
But we knocked them all out!
- [Jay] They're being recharged.
- [Speedster-Iris] How?
They're feeding off me.
It's what happened
inside the Speed Force.
And now that energy drain
is affecting all of us.
- Nora, you have to go.
- I can't let you fight alone.
You'll still be with us.
But you have to leave. Right now.
We're not going down without a fight.
Hang on to your butts.
[device powering up]
Whoa.
The S.E.E. readings are
at five times their maximum strength.
Oh, yeah! Watch out, world.
This wavelength's off the charts!
[sizzles]
Nice timing.
[Caitlin] Flash,
more Godspeeds just arrived
and they're headed your way.
Continuous waves.
Wherever we run, they'll follow.
This could put more people
in danger. Flash...
I know.
[Caitlin] Thank God you guys are okay.
- We managed to save the reactor.
- [computer beeping]
But it looks like round two's
about to begin.
And this time, there's no
Speed Force Nora or the S.E.E.
We threw everything we had at them.
What are we gonna do?
Dad?
We need to get back out there.
Frost and Mecha-Vibe need our help.
Yeah, we will. As soon as...
They're gone again.
Wow. Frost and Mecha-Vibe
make a hell of a team.
Chester, how long would it take
to rebuild the S.E.E.?
Uh, four or five weeks maybe.
How come your tech-thingy
affected the clones and not us?
Well, you're all organic speedsters
so I tweaked my pop's design
to only target
artificial cell membranes.
Making it ineffective against us.
Well done.
Dad. Mom.
I know you both
wanna keep the future safe.
But if we don't stop this right now,
there won't be a future to save.
Please can you just consider
giving Heart organic speed?
Nora, I know that seems like the answer.
But we're your parents,
it's our job to protect you.
Maybe so.
But Central City
doesn't need parents right now.
Dad, it needs heroes.
I know I said we'd protect the city
while the team figured out
a way to end this.
- But can a man get a timeout?
- Not happening.
- Hey, how long can you hold your breath?
- What does that matter?
When I say "now,"
we're gonna suck in
as much air as we can and hold it in.
- What's that gonna do?
- [gauntlet beeps]
- Wait, you're not actually gonna...
- Oh, I'm gonna.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Now!
[Frost inhales]
[both gasping]
Yeah!
Thank God, those bubbles are temporary.
- [gasps]
- That's right.
Your boy put an auto-timer
on the entropy bubble,
and in the process,
answered his own question,
a man can get a timeout!
Am I a genius?
Never do that again!
I'll take that as a yes.
[laughs]
Oh, you guys are stellar!
Thank you. What did we just do?
Well, you saved me at least three weeks
in the proverbial salt mines of science.
At this rate,
the modified version of my pop's S.E.E.
could be up and running in...
[chuckles] A day or two.
A day or two?
Isn't there some way
we can speed that up a little?
There is, but Mom and Dad
won't change their minds.
We already did.
We're gonna give August organic speed.
[laughs] Okay.
Oh, you're not kidding?
Where's Mom?
[Barry] She's still
with the Speed Force.
They're both helping too.
What changed your mind?
My kids.
When I realized that their future
starts right now.
How exactly will this give me
my memories back?
The theory is
your artificial speed cells
have gone dormant.
But we believe that a speed boost
from Barry can jumpstart them
and give you organic speed.
And the harness should trigger the rest.
Hey.
Don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
Yeah. If this does work,
I'll try to come back... differently.
Good luck.
Are you okay?
[sighs] If Dad is right,
and we're actually creating the future
by doing this,
everything from now on
could be different.
I know you don't have to do this.
So whatever your reasons are,
I know they're pretty important.
I just hope this works out.
For both of us.
Me too.
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
[screams]
August! No!
Sorry, Cecile.
Turns out I like being the bad guy.
No matter what happens, stay here.
- What?
- Absolutely not!
Your mother and I have a plan.
[in other language]
[in English, distorted]
At last, true speed for a true god.
You got what you wanted, Heart.
Now what?
Now you die, Flash.
By my hand.
[in other language]
[in English]
No one's dying tonight, Heart.
[Godspeed laughs]
But you are going to Iron Heights.
You'll have to catch me first.
Dad, be careful!
You don't know what he's capable of.
I will.
[Speedster-Iris]
What do you need me to do?
You be my anchor while I concentrate.
[thunder rumbling]
[Jay] Heart's got organic speed,
he just reabsorbed all his clones.
[Chester] Jay's right.
Until the excess speed burns off,
Heart could be faster than you.
[groaning]
There can only be
one God of Speed, Flash.
[groans]
This didn't work out
like you planned, Flash.
Now guess what comes next.
Tag. You're dead.
Dad!
- Bart!
- I know what I said. I know what I said.
But this is different.
This is different.
I am not going to let Heart
kill anyone that I care for.
Not now, not ever.
I believe you, son.
Now, we just met.
You have no reason to listen to me.
But we both know Barry, right?
And if he says to stand down,
no matter what, he has a reason.
But...
It's time to take our hats off, okay?
[in other language]
[in English] Now that you've leveled up,
what better time to feast?
[Chester] Wait, is that Thawne?
It sure as hell is.
Miss me?
Save it, Thawne.
- You're back because of us.
- Right.
And in exchange, I've agreed
to help you take down a psychopath.
[Godspeed] Flash! That was nuts!
You do like to party.
Joining forces with your worst enemy
just to take me down?
That's very flattering, Flash.
But it won't do you any good.
Don't you two get it?
You can't kill a god.
[thunder rumbling]
[crackling]
[grunts]
Thawne!
You could've killed him.
Wasn't that the plan?
Didn't you say you needed help
dealing with a threat?
Well, I dealt with it.
And now... And now... [chuckles]
it's just you and me, Flash.
I've been waiting for this moment...
For a long, long time.
I'm only gonna say this once.
Walk away. While you still can.
Allen.
You're too weak to stop me.
[voice distorts]
And I'm just getting started.
[groans]
What did you do?
I created you.
I taught you everything you know!
Everything you are... is because of me!
What did you do?
I got faster.
Didn't you?
No.
But I will, Flash.
Mark my words.
I will.
[Caitlin] How did you bring
Thawne back?
Well, the Speed Force did it
by connecting with the Negative side,
which is pretty dangerous.
So with Barry occupied,
I was the perfect choice
to anchor the Speed Force.
[Nora] Wait.
Tapping into the Negative Speed Force?
Do I even know who you guys are?
[Bart] Okay, but why Thawne?
Like, why not just
let us come help instead?
Sometimes, what makes a speedster
dangerous isn't just speed.
It's having no limits on
how they use it.
Right. Godspeed has no limits.
But Thawne?
His one limit
is he can't let anyone else kill me.
That's why I knew he'd turn on me
the first chance he got.
But, Dad, Thawne is still out there.
Yeah, and he'll be back someday,
but that's future us's problem.
What about August Heart?
[Barry] He's in Iron Heights now.
But, Barry, he knows your real identity.
What if he talks?
Luckily, he's a speedster,
so Speed Force Nora was able
to remove that from his memory.
- It's finally over.
- [Bart] Great.
Can we eat now? I'm starving.
Family dinner tonight? On Dad.
- Yeah, I would love that.
- [Caitlin] That sounds perfect.
I'll get us a reservation.
Iris, hang on.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Okay. [chuckles]
Um, ever since you came into my life,
I've been more
than just the fastest man alive.
I've been the luckiest.
Marrying you was the best decision
I ever made.
Well, I agree.
And even though we're husband and wife,
you never really got
the wedding you deserved.
And these past few days when it looked
like I might never see you again,
I swore if I ever did,
I would make it up to you.
So...
- Iris West-Allen...
- [chuckles]
Will you renew your vows
and re-marry me?
Yes. [chuckles]
Yes, I will.
Oh, I'm obviously interrupting.
No, it's okay. It's good to see you.
- I should go.
- Kramer.
We haven't talked in a week.
How are you?
I don't really know how to answer that.
I just wanted to let you know
that my meta test came back positive.
So you are a speedster?
Yes. And no.
Adam was right. I should've died
in that bombing, but I didn't.
And neither did he because
he has immortal healing powers.
And so did I
when I absolutely needed them.
Just like when I needed super-speed
to save your life,
I had it for just a moment.
That's incredible.
Turns out I can mimic the abilities
of any meta in close proximity.
Which sounds insane. But it's real.
Well, it's...
It's given me new perspective
on the path I took
as a member of law enforcement.
I'm so sorry, West. For all of it.
You lost your way a little,
but I always knew that your heart
was in the right place.
You just needed to find it.
Agreed.
That's why I'm taking an indefinite
leave of absence from C.C.P.D.
Take care of yourself, West.
Kristen.
Call me Joe.
Yeah.
Are you sure you're okay with me
being your plus one? Because...
Do not say his name.
Frost, I know...
He lied to me and then totally bailed.
I hate weddings.
Technically, this is...
Okay, fine. A renewal ceremony.
Maybe we should renew our vows.
I'd marry you again in a heartbeat.
Aw... I love renewal ceremonies.
And weddings.
- Good to know.
- Mm.
Everyone, if I may direct your attention
to the stairs.
Hi, Daddy. [chuckles]
[Iris West laughs]
- Nice entrance.
- Thank you.
[Cisco] Now before we get
to the main event,
I know you two have asked us all
to keep it simple for this occasion.
- [laughter]
- But one of us couldn't resist adding
a little something extra special
to the festivities.
So without further ado, my man.
Thank you, Cisco. Appreciate it.
Mom. Dad. This is for you.
[singing]
Could you be that fine love?
That 1949 love
The quiver in your spine love
That summer wine love
Just grab a warm body
And pick up the keys
You need somebody, somebody to be
You can't count on timing
And I'll just wait and see
I'll be that somebody
So settle for me
I'll give you all the affection
You've been craving
When you're ready
I'll be waiting
Waiting
Baby, I've got
I'll give you all the affection
Just grab a warm body
And pick up the keys
If you need somebody, somebody like me
You can't count on timing
And I'll just wait and see
I'll be that somebody
So, darling, if you're ready
To settle
- Bart. That was crash.
- Yeah?
- What? That's how you say it.
- No, no, just no, you say it weird.
Just do the thing, again.
My fellow earthlings, today,
we are here to witness
the greatest sequel
since Empire Strikes Back,
as Barry and Iris renew their vows,
and lend new meaning to the term
"relationship goals."
Now, I understand you both wrote
a little something for each other.
If you'd like to share,
this is the time.
- Iris.
- [clears throat]
Barry.
They say that love is a friendship
that's caught on fire.
But ours is a friendship
that was struck by lightning.
You and I are our own force of nature.
[voice choking]
And I promise today... [chuckles]
To continue loving you
with my whole heart.
[whispers] That was beautiful.
Good luck following that.
Iris.
Thank you.
Ever since we met,
you've been my lightning rod.
But now that you're my wife,
you are my past, my present,
and my only future.
That's why today
I promise to continue loving you.
Now and forever.
[mouths]
Okay, that was... That was decent.
Ten points for Gryffindor.
Now, then.
- Ah, yes.
- [laughs]
Do you, Iris, Bartholomew,
take each other
to cherish and to love
in good times and bad,
for all the days of your life?
- I do.
- Again. [chuckles]
- Again.
Then by the power vested in me
by a last-minute Internet web search...
[all laugh]
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Again.
- Am I forgetting something?
- Yes, the kiss.
- Oh, yes! Do the kiss! Do the thing.
- [laughs]
Flashtime, huh?
Can you blame me?
I want this moment to last forever.