Who are you?
Can it or not?
You are the King, no?
It can be arranged.
I have been sent by the King of France
to assassinate you.
Charles himself sent you?
You know this to be certain?
The order's origin I know, yes.
From the King.
What was the order?
That I should kill the King of England.
How?
However. Any way.
There are many ways to kill a man.
It is my talent...
killing men
who do not expect to be killed.
The day is yours.
We ask only
that our women and children be freed.
Many are hungry and wounded
and becoming sick.
I see no reason to deny your request.
You will have tonight
to oversee this evacuation
and to corral your men prisoners.
Come.
Where is the Dauphin?
I humbly thank you for receiving me,
noble lord.
Your Majesty...
Henry, King of England.
Leave us.
Please sit, Your Majesty.
You are beautiful.
I will no longer speak French.
We must speak English.
I cannot speak English.
You will learn.
I wonder, then,
how our union might proceed
in the meantime.