My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster, Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in my power
to change the future.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force,
I accidentally ran to the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
We can't do this alone, Barry.
Why don't you come work with us?
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
- Welcome to the team.
- Yeah.
If his powers are linked to the energy
that ties together the multiverse...
He can open a breach
to any Earth he wants.
The thing they never tell you
about fighting villains
is that nothing ever stays the same.
The harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
the more they up their game.
Gentlemen, welcome to the future of crime.
Not even the military has these yet.
Looks like Christmas came early.
You know what the only problem is?
You're on Santa's naughty list.
Christmas is canceled.
Fortunately, our team
has a secret weapon of its own.
A man of science, a man of action,
and that man's name is H.R. Wells.
Look who has a vortex cannon.
Ho, ho, ho!
H.R.? H.R.?
With a blast from my trusty vortex cannon,
I dispatched the miscreant...
- H.R.!
- Hey! Yup. Here we are.
- Barry needs help.
- Yeah, Barry needs help!
- Where is Kid Flash?
- He's on his way!
Are you on your way?
They need you at Keystone Bridge.
Surely all your adventures
are not this disorganized?
There's a method
to the madness, mate, watch and learn.
The Electric Gang
is headed north.
You got to cut them off
before they reach the freeway!
Oh, hey, how you wanna play this?
I have an idea.
Eyes up!
Here he comes. Just the red one.
Nice work.
They're out cold.
Hey, boys.
They saved us. They saved us.
Who are you?
Um...
I'm Kid Flash.
- Oh, my gosh, can we get your picture?
- Yes.
Ooh.-
Okay. Bye.
- Go, Kid Flash!
Nice save!
- Could not have scripted it better myself.
- Thanks.
- But Barry did most of the heavy lifting.
- B.A.
Yes, bravo, boys.
Although I did find at least six ways
you could've done it more efficiently.
Just saying.
I mean, the busload of hot cheerleaders
seemed to like the way that we did things.
That's going in the book.
You know what, I'm running low.
Let me buy you a cup of coffee
over at CC Jitters.
- Bond, are you coming?
- No, thank you.
- So, exactly how many "hot" cheerleaders?
- I was a good boy.
You know, he has just been
looking forward to this for a long time.
He's enjoying the moment.
- Well, I'm glad you have his back.
- We have each other's back.
It's actually been really nice
having him out there.
Hey, I meant to ask you,
when you found the Electric Gang,
did you see them meeting with anyone else?
- Like who?
- Well, word on the street is,
there's a new arms dealer in town
with access to sophisticated weaponry
like the gun that Plunder used.
Don't you think that's something
for the police to handle?
I'm still a journalist, Barry.
I can't hide from the world
because of what you saw.
See you at home.
I can't lose her, Cisco.
Please tell me you've found a way
to change the future.
We found a way to change the future.
Did you really?
No, but Caitlin and I
did find a way to map it.
You're gonna love this. Follow me.
Julian suggested we make
a 3D reconstruction
of the scene from the future
exactly as we saw it.
With toys.
The medium's not important.
Thank you. Eye on the ball, Barry.
Is this me? Why is he an astronaut?
Eye on the ball, Barry, okay?
Now, this diorama tells us
you need to cover this distance
in less than 0.21 seconds
if you wanna save Iris from Savitar.
What do you guys think?
I think what you're proposing
is impossible.
- Therefore, you will fail.
- Why?
Multi-universes may be a new
concept to me, but mathematics is not.
Pay attention, Allen.
This is your speed timeline.
This is your maximum velocity
when you first acquired your powers.
This is your current top speed.
And this is where you need to be in May
to cover that distance in 0.21 seconds.
At your current rate
of improvement, impossible.
Wow. Thank you
for that rousing pep talk, Coach.
Okay, why don't you take a knee,
I think we got it covered here.
It looks like it.
I actually have to be back at CCPD.
As do you. Cheerio.
He really does wanna help,
in his own snobbish, thoughtless way.
Nah, he is right.
I mean, he's kind of a dick about it,
but you can't argue with his math.
Okay, well, then we'll find
another way to make this work.
We need to. Iris isn't gonna die.
Thank you very much.
- Gotcha.
- Freeze!
How'd you get in here?
You know what they say,
every time a door closes...
a window opens.
- Barr...
- Hey.
- Nothing's missing.
- Nope.
Cash is still in the register.
Safe's not touched.
I mean, seems like a lot to go through
to get a late night cup of coffee, right?
Yeah, it's definitely a meta.
I'll have Julian
look into his meta database,
but I think this is someone new.
New and dangerous.
Well, it's nothing that the Flash
and Kid Flash can't handle.
- My two superhero boys.
- He is doing great.
Speaking of my kids, Iris,
she tell you about this arms-dealer story
she's following?
Yeah, she's mentioned it.
Well, now that you're
her live-in boyfriend,
could you look out for her
and maybe get her to back off a bit
because this isn't something
she should be doing on her own.
I agree, I'm trying.
She seem okay to you otherwise?
Yeah, why? Do you not think so?
If you guys got something going on,
I hope you know you can talk to me.
Yeah, I know, Joe. Thank you.
We're both doing great.
Okay.
- Okay. Talk to you later.
- Yeah.
So, this is the footage from Jitters,
it should help us ID our new meta.
- Brunette? That really narrows it down.
- I'll clean that up.
Wow, look how clear
the picture is on that screen.
That's 'cause that's not from Jitters,
that's our security footage.
H.R. Wells, I know you're in there.
Come quietly if you don't want trouble.
"H. R.?" How does she know you?
Talk! Who is this gorgeous intruder?
Her name is Gypsy, and she's what's
known on my Earth as a "collector."
- What is she collecting?
- She's come to collect, you know, me.
Oh!
Where does it hurt?
Oh, everywhere.
You can vibe? Oh, I like it.
Slow down, there.
Let's just talk about this.
Like two adults, over coffee,
or maybe dinner, if you prefer that.
There's a great Thai place up the road,
if you like Thai.
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must be Gypsy.
It's nice to meet you.
- Are you asking her on a date?
- Are you kidding me?
I am negotiating.
Well, you showed me yours,
only fair I show you mine.
Cisco.
Ma'am, I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave the building.
Speedster. That's fun.
I like to have fun, too.
I see you've got a lot
to learn about your power.
Yeah, like that.
How do you do that? That's cool.
You're harboring a fugitive from justice.
Our world has a strict ban
on inter-dimensional travel.
He knew that when he came here.
- So, you tracked him here?
- Honestly, it wasn't that hard.
Not when he's beaming H.R. Wells'
Adventures in The Multiverse back
chapter by chapter.
You know what, whatever H.R. did,
you can't just come here
and take him by force.
Not without going through us.
If I really wanted to "go through" you,
you would all be dead.
I've got a lock on you now.
There is no getting away.
You've got an hour
to get your affairs in order,
and then you are coming back with me.
Adios, Cisco.
What an accent.
"As Francisco threw back
his lustrous locks and laughed,"
"I outlined my plan for neutralizing
the rampaging creature..."
It goes on like this for pages.
He's been broadcasting this,
without our knowledge or permission,
all the while making himself the hero.
Yeah, every book
needs a central protagonist
that the audience can invest in.
- I would've gone with Barry.
- Barry?
Cisco, what was that back there?
First, Golden Glider, and now her?
I can't help who I'm attracted to,
even if it is the sexy,
intense, deadly ones.
So, she takes you back to Earth-19,
and what, you pay a fine?
The punishment for non-authorized
"breach travel" on my Earth...
It's death.
- Death?
- Yeah, about 24, 25 years ago,
a neighboring Earth
invaded our planet through a breach,
and almost destroyed the place,
so to prevent it from happening again,
they banned all inter-dimensional travel.
And then they put the collectors in place
to punish those of us
who violated the ban.
I didn't think that she'd track me down.
So, why would you
risk your life by coming here?
I'm gonna get packing.
It's time for H.R. to face the music.
Mmm-mmm.
Guys, I know H.R. can be annoying,
but he doesn't deserve to die.
Different Earths, different morality.
But he doesn't go back, I saw him.
In the future, with me and Iris,
and Savitar, he was there.
I mean, that must mean we don't
let her take him back.
Maybe we do.
Maybe by letting him go back to his Earth,
it changes your future
and prevents Iris' death.
I got to go see her.
Are you just gonna
let this woman take H.R.?
I don't know. No, I just...
I wish I knew if it would
make a difference, you know?
I mean, what if he goes
and nothing changes?
How do we ever know if our actions now
impact the future?
Yeah.
You know, sometimes I wish
we had normal-people problems.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Hey, you didn't tell Joe
about the future, did you?
No, of course not.
The last thing I need
is for him to worry about something
four months away that might not happen.
That won't happen.
Maybe in the meantime, you could
let this arms-dealer thing go?
Oh, God, did my dad
put you up to this, too?
- No, he didn't have to.
- Barry, look, this...
No, look, I'm sorry, I'm not trying
to keep you from doing your job, okay?
But when we're all focused
on this H.R. thing,
and trying to prevent the future,
do we really need to
go looking for more trouble?
Please?
Okay, I'll drop it.
Really? Just like that?
Um, yes. Sometimes I do listen to you,
you know.
That hasn't been my experience.
Shut up.
All right, I'll see you later.
- Okay, bye.
- Thank you.
Don't you get tired of running?
That's the thing, running just sort of
keeps my mind off of things, I guess.
Must be an amazing feeling.
It is.
You know, cracking a big story
gives me an amazing feeling,
and I think I'm on to one.
Oh, that, uh, arms dealer thing?
How do you know about that?
Because both Dad and Barry
want you to lay off of it.
The phrase "death wish"
got tossed around a lot by them.
Okay, I do not have a death wish.
I just want to see justice done,
like everyone else in this building.
I get that, but it is dangerous, Iris.
Wally, how dangerous could it be?
I don't die till May.
Barry said that in Flashpoint,
you and I were a brother-sister
crime-fighting team.
I say we make that a reality again.
Shouldn't we ask Barry first?
No, this is just between us, Wally.
We can do this together.
Do you know what I'm really
gonna miss about this Earth?
- I don't know...
- Soap operas.
I mean, a long winding story
served up daily in hour-long chapters?
You never answered Caitlin's question.
Oh, about why I put mustard on my fries?
- Why you risked your life to come here.
- That.
I looked in a mirror.
I don't follow.
Look, on my Earth,
I had fame, I had power, I had respect.
I was "H.R. Wells..."
But when I looked in the mirror,
I knew the truth.
And the truth was...
I didn't matter.
I was a fraud.
That is why I came to this Earth.
So I could rewrite my story,
both literally and figuratively.
There's got to be
something you can do, H.R.?
There's not.
You can't hire a lawyer, appeal the case?
There's nothing I can do, B.A.!
I don't mean to snap at you.
I just... I don't have any options here.
All right?
Unless, of course,
I appeal for trial by combat.
Guys, Gypsy's here.
Always so punctual.
I'm impressed.
I thought you'd try and flee again.
Time to go.
All right, Gypsy.
- Take me home.
- Wait.
You're not taking him anywhere.
- What?
- Why not?
Because I challenge you
to trial by combat.
- What are you doing?
- I'm challenging her to trial by combat.
No, no, he isn't, okay?
Lam. I'm gonna fight you.
Well, that one spoke first.
What? That's like a real rule?
By the laws of Earth-19,
I hereby challenge you
for possession of H.R. Wells.
If you want,
we can solve this another way.
There's a great spot for drinks.
You realize trial by combat
is to the death?
Yeah, for the loser.
Listen, you want him,
you have to come and claim him.
Hmm.
It's Arwen. It's fun.
I take it you also want
the customary 24 hours to prepare?
- Do I want the customary...
- Yes, you do.
I would love to take advantage of the
customary 24 hours, if you don't mind.
Very well. One day.
One day.
See you then.
She's gonna kill me, isn't she?
She's good.
She's great.
Gypsy is a legend on my Earth.
So why exactly did you agree to fight her?
- I don't know.
- You did what any of us would've done.
I might not have done it,
just being honest.
Okay. All right. Lay it out for me.
What are my chances here,
scale of one to ten?
- She's gonna kill you.
- It's a pretty solid "one," mate.
You have the same powers
Gypsy does, right?
I mean, she's not doing anything
you can't do.
Much better, I mean,
she's doing it just much better.
You can do this, okay?
You just need a little practice
and a little confidence,
and we're all gonna
help you with that, right?
- Yes.
- Uh, sure.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I believe in you, all right?
You can beat her.
Listen, I have some ideas for
a training regimen I can set up in here.
Caitlin, why don't you get
the medical bay prepared in the meantime.
What? Why does she need to
set up the medical bay?
For when you beat her.
When you beat her, she's gonna
need medical attention.
'Cause you will beat her. I have every
faith that you're gonna beat her.
We need to work
on your interpersonal skills.
I was really trying.
Has anyone ever beat her?
Yeah.
No. Oh.
Okay. Well, I've officially reached
a nice, comfortable level
of just straight-up panic.
You don't even like me.
Why would you risk your life for me?
Well, you heard Barry,
it's what we do around here.
Come on. Why?
You're not like the other Wells-es.
Yeah, so you keep reminding me.
No, I mean, those two,
they were geniuses, we depended on them.
But with you, the roles are reversed.
You depend on us.
Harrison Wells was always there for me,
so, I guess, in some weird way,
I just wanna be there for Harrison Wells.
- Anyway...
- Yeah.
What are we doing here?
I thought you didn't want Dad to know
we're going after this arms dealer?
Oh, yeah, no, I don't, but actually,
I need you to swipe his file on the case,
photograph the pages,
and then put them back. Thanks.
What? Iris, have you lost your mind?
Dad will kill us.
No, no, Wally, he won't.
He won't even know
that Kid Flash was there.
First, you have to tell me why.
Okay, look, I know everyone is working
really hard to prevent Savitar from...
Yeah.
But, honestly, these could be
my last few months on Earth.
Can you not talk like that?
I'm just being realistic, Wally,
I get to do that.
Look, I want my life to mean something,
more than just a daughter,
or as a sister, or as a girlfriend,
but as a reporter.
This story can do that, it can say that,
I, Iris West, mattered.
You know, my life was a lot easier
before I had a sister.
But it's a lot better now, isn't it?
Come on.
Okay.
I can get you
the no-knock warrant, but, Joe,
this guy is armed to the teeth
with God only knows what.
You're gonna have to
move in there fast and hard.
- "Fast and hard," okay, I kind of walked...
- Hey, sorry.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hi.
Hi, Iris.
Hi, good to see you, Cecile.
Um, Dad, can I borrow you for a second
for a little father-daughter talk?
I need to go catch up with Captain Singh,
so I will be back in a little while, yeah?
- It was good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
So, what's up? How can I help you?
Can I talk to you for a second over here?
Um...
Yeah, so, um...
I wanted to speak to you
about me and Barry.
You and Barry?
- Yes.
- Okay.
So, there comes a time
in every couple's relationship
when you realize that there is
too much love for two people.
And, uh, when that happens,
you know in your heart
that the only solution
is to make your family a little bigger.
Okay, I'm gonna need a second...
Oh, Dad. Hey, hey, listen to me
very closely, this is so important to me.
Oh, God.
Um...
Uh...
- Is Barry a dog or a cat person?
- What?
Yeah, what kind of animal does he like,
because I was thinking about
getting him a pet,
and I don't really remember him
having a preference.
Oh, man, you had me
going there for a second.
What did you think I was talking about?
Nothing, nothing. You can get him
any kind of animal you want
as long as it has four legs.
Good, great advice. Four legs, copy that.
Thanks for the chat. Okay, bye.
Bye.
Damn.
Oh. Yeah, facing the wrong way again.
- How many is that?
- Three.
- Nine.
- You'll get there.
Yes, hopefully in the next 21 hours
and 46 minutes.
All right, look, whenever I'm out there,
I'm in a tough fight,
I think maybe I don't have it,
I just take a deep breath,
trust my instincts.
Trust my instincts, that's good.
That helps.
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know.
Guys, up here.
- Let's go talk.
- All right.
We can't let Francisco fight Gypsy,
because if he does, he is a dead man.
- You don't know that.
- Oh, I know that, you know that,
- he knows that, she knows that...
- Okay. I get it.
- We know that, everybody knows that.
- What are we supposed to do?
We're supposed to stop her
before she fights him.
That would be great
if we knew where she was.
- Yes?
- I know where she is.
- How?
- I tagged her with a tracer
the last time she was here.
A magician friend told me,
you kind of distract them and tag...
- H.R...
- I needed to know where she was,
so I could stay one step ahead of her.
She is...
- At the waterfront.
What do you say, for Francisco?
All right.
This world may be a primitive,
uncultured backwater,
but they do make
an excellent cup of coffee.
That they do.
You know what you got to try?
You got to try the Brazilian roast.
It's new, it is so good.
- Maybe I'll take a few bags back with me.
- Yeah, I think that's wise.
Will you be going back in a bag?
Look, that kid, Francisco,
he's just trying to protect me.
Then he's as foolish as he is cute.
Okay, Gypsy, let's go home.
B.A.!
Nice try.
You think I didn't see that coming?
- Stop. Stop!
- Stop what?
- Stop...
- Stop trying to enforce the law?
You are a criminal.
Now, it's great
that you made friends here,
but that doesn't change
the fact that you lied.
You broke our most sacred laws,
and now it is time
for you to face justice.
Wait! You still need to face Cisco.
No, I think this little stunt
forfeits his claim and his time.
You just said
you believe in the law, right?
We made a mistake, but Cisco
will hold up his end of the deal.
He will.
You have really
pulled a number on these people
if they would die for you.
Tell Cisco there is no backing out now.
I'll keep this one
as insurance until then.
B.A...
That's not good.
- She took H.R.?
- Mmm-hmm.
Can she do that?
I mean, I thought this whole
trial-by-combat thing had rules.
Which, apparently, we broke
when we tried to get the drop on her.
Well, that wasn't very clever, was it?
A deal's a deal, it should be honored.
You know what? You're right, Julian.
A deal is a deal, and our deal was that
I would train so that I could fight Gypsy,
but I guess you two wanted to go
behind my back and try to sub in?
We didn't go... We just thought maybe
you could use some help.
Yeah? What happened to,
- "Cisco, you can beat her"?
- You can.
- "I believe in you."
- I do.
"Trust your instincts."
Well, right now,
my instincts are telling me
I should be writing
my last will and testament,
- so, please excuse me.
- Cisco, come...
- Should I go talk to him?
- No. I... I got it.
Looks like I'm not the only one who
has to work on their interpersonal skills.
Oh, hey, I'd be careful if I were you.
Last thing we want
is for me to touch a button
and blow your head off, right?
'Cause I don't know what I'm doing, right?
You know I don't think that.
Yeah, well, you have a very,
very strange way of showing it.
You're right, man, I'm sorry.
I don't know, I just
guess this whole not-getting-faster thing,
it just has me rattled.
I was always able to do it before,
you know?
I mean, against Reverse-Flash,
and then against Zoom,
but Savitar's on a whole other level.
And knowing what he'll do to Iris
if I fail...
I'm afraid just thinking
what's gonna happen to H.R.
if I don't beat Gypsy.
But you, you're the hero.
I mean, how do you handle
all this pressure all the time?
Byjust leaning on all of you guys,
you know?
I mean, you're always in my corner,
helping me face my fears.
And it is okay to be afraid, trust me.
And when you are,
I'll be there, in your corner.
Yes, lovely little speech, Allen,
but what Mr. Ramon needs to defeat
his inter-dimensional adversary
is a practical stratagem.
Lucky for you, I found one.
This is Gypsy's signature move,
I call it her "breach and blast."
Oh, yeah. That move.
You see, just before she comes
in and out of a breach,
her feet come off the ground.
So, for that split-second
she's off the ground,
- she'll be off-balance.
- Yes, and vulnerable.
It might behoove you
to use this during the battle.
This is great, Julian.
Hmm. Just glad I could be helpful.
This is more than helpful.
I got to work on this. Thank you.
Cheers.
Thanks.
- You sure this is the place?
- Positive.
All right, you ready
to bust an arms dealer,
get me a front-page headline?
Wally, wait. CCPD's been looking
for this guy for months.
He might have
some sort of secret tunnel network
that helps him slip out and get away.
I should do a quick recon.
Yeah, thorough.
We don't wanna miss anything, okay?
Be back in a you-know-what.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Hope you like what you see,
'cause this sneak preview's
gonna cost you your life.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Are you crazy?
This will rip a hole right through you.
Everyone's got to go sometime, right?
And I am pretty sure
today just isn't my day.
What the hell, sis?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
God, okay. Look, we got to get you
out of here before CCPD sees you.
Don't worry, Dad's, like,
my biggest fan now.
He's totally cool with me
doing stuff like this.
Hell, no, I ain't cool with this!
You two almost compromised
a major CCPD sting operation
that took the DA's office
months to assemble!
- You still got the guy, right?
- That is not the point, Iris.
The point is, you had you and your brother
out there in danger, and for what?
A story? And where the hell were you?
Dad, this is more
than just a story for me.
Yeah, which you almost got shot for.
Okay.
What?
Iris, what is going on with you?
Joe, I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a second?
We'll be right back.
Joe already suspects something's up.
You going out there like that,
it just hangs a bell on it.
This story is going to
change lives, Barry.
Why do you think that you're the only one
allowed to risk your life to do good?
I don't.
It's okay to be afraid of the future.
But I won't let you die.
I am not afraid to die, Barry, I'm not!
Then, what?
I'm afraid...
What if I end up just like my mom?
Just gone, without making a mark,
without leaving anything behind.
Iris, your mom, she left something behind.
She left a brave, wonderful son
and the woman that I love.
All right?
I don't know what the future holds,
none of us do.
I know that we will face it together.
Gypsy just vibed me her location.
Let's do this.
I don't think
the literary critics on our Earth
would know a real
sci-fi, romance bestseller
- unless it bit them in the...
- Time's up, Wells.
Looks like your so-called friend
is a coward after all.
He's not a coward.
He's one of the finest men
I've ever known.
Oh, you're right about that!
I'm fine as hell.
There he is.
Didn't think you'd show.
Oh, I wouldn't miss an evening with you,
even if it is for a showdown.
I will kill you, Cisco.
We'll see who dies tonight.
To the victor goes H.R. Wells.
May the best vibe win.
Part of me was hoping
you wouldn't show tonight.
How do you wanna do this?
Westworld style, back-to-back 10 paces,
turn and shoot?
No.
- This does not bode well.
- Cisco can hold his own.
Barely.
Barry, we can't let this happen.
What if he can't defeat her?
I can't interfere again. If I do,
then we forfeit, H.R.'s a dead man.
At this rate,
Cisco's gonna be the dead man.
Ooh!
Ooh, girl, you done did it now!
You're stronger than I thought.
I'm just getting warmed up.
Yeah, maybe not do that.
Time to turn things up to 11.
Spinal Tap. That's, like,
one of my favorite movies.
- Where did they go?
- They could be anywhere by now.
In any universe.
This is Earth-2.
You're cute, but you talk too much.
Oh, you wanna play dirty, huh?
Let's play dirty.
That hurts.
That, too.
Is it me, or is this city getting weirder?
Well, this is hot.
I think you're flirting with me
to distract me 'cause you're afraid.
My collection record is flawless.
In these trials, I am undefeated.
Oh, please,
everybody's got a weakness.
Even you.
Says the man afraid of showing everyone
how powerful he can be.
You and I resonate
on a similar frequency, I can feel it,
yet you allow your fear and insecurity
to hold you back.
That's why you're gonna lose.
Does this look like holding back to you?
I could do this all night.
How did you...
You might wanna work
on your balance next time, girl.
Admit it, I won.
- He won?
- Yes! Yeah, he did.
- He won! Yes!
- Yeah.
She must've been having an off day.
- What?
- Wow.
By the laws of Earth-19,
prisoner is yours for the taking,
as is my life.
Oh, no, no, no.
We don't roll like that around here.
Come on.
In all the multiverse,
I have never met anyone like you, Cisco.
Please, call me Vibe.
Or you can call me Cisco,
that's also allowed.
Just a regular guy,
just a regular single guy.
It says you're totally fine.
So, what happens now?
Go back to your Earth,
tell all your superiors that
you were bested in battle,
all the charges against H.R. are dropped?
No, I tell them I killed him.
Wait, what?
If I return empty-handed,
they'll know I failed,
and I never fail, until today.
Okay, but if you tell them
that you killed me, then I...
You'll never go back to Earth-19, ever.
Do we have a deal?
Yeah, I guess we have a deal.
I don't really have anything
to go home for.
You'll always have a home here, H.R.
Listen, I know there's
no coffee on your Earth,
'cause of the whole blight thing
or whatever,
but this is an absurd amount of coffee
to be bringing back to your Earth.
- That can't be legal.
- I mean, I won't tell if you won't.
You know, for someone so fixated
on enforcing the law,
you sure seem oddly at ease
about breaking it.
I guess some laws are worth breaking
for the right person.
Hmm.
So, it's goodbye, then?
For now.
Wow.
What an exit.
Okay, you know, for the fastest man alive,
you are the slowest reader.
Hey, this is your big article,
I'm not gonna rush through it.
I'm just kidding,
I read it five times already.
You sure sold the hell out of Kid Flash
as Central City's next super-savior.
I'm sure Wally's loving that.
Well, I did promise him the front page.
What do you think?
Do you think it will make any difference?
Kid Flash already changed one thing
that we saw in the future.
No, I meant the article.
- What?
- The article?
I think you should be really proud.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's the beginning of
an amazing journalistic legacy.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
How amazing? Like, Pulitzer amazing?
Time will tell.
Hey, I'm sorry.
- You know what I realized?
- Hmm?
Savitar, he said that I trapped him
wherever he is.
You know what that means?
It means I beat him,
and I'm gonna do it again, I promise.
So, don't worry,
the Flash is gonna save you.
My hero.
The thing they never tell you is that
nothing ever stays the same.
So, the harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
the more they up their game.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
- No, no.
- Just had to grab some stuff.
- Yeah.
I thought you were finished
working with that.
Oh, no, it's just... This is just for me.
No, the book, it...
You know, my own personal
sense of accomplishment.
Well, you've accomplished plenty.
What have I accomplished, Francisco?
Well, for one, you got me
to risk my life to save yours,
and, trust me, my friend,
that is a huge accomplishment.
Yeah, about that,
I just wanna say that I appreciate
what you did for me.
Yeah, it's what we do
for our friends, right?
Besides, it was a way for me
to balance the scales.
Balance the scales, right.
What does that mean?
I just mean, I can't tell you the amount
of times that I've been in your shoes,
and a man with your face
has made me feel better.
Yeah, about that, I would
love if you could share some
of my doppelgangers' knowledge.
I would love to know what
the smarter versions of me think.
Okay. Um...
The first Wells told me
my time would come to be a hero.
That it was my job to show up,
to be ready for when it did.
You know why I love working here?
Why?
We're all making investments
in each other.
I made an investment in you.
And one day,
that investment's gonna pay off
when you use that crazy way of thinking
you have to help me out.
I guess if he were here,
he would say, "Show up."
Yeah.
- Be ready.
- Yeah.
'Cause one day
you might need to save my ass.
Keep it up, at this rate,
you're gonna reach Mach 3 soon.
I know, it's crazy how fast I've gotten
in such a short time, right?
Yeah, and I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
- Why's that?
- Because I've done the math over and over,
and I finally realized that I've been
looking at things the wrong way.
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar,
you are.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::