My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
How come you haven't
given me a code name?
What do you think I should be called?
Golden Glider.
Smart is sexy, Cisco.
Then why didn't you just kill me?
Well, I guess you owe me one now, too.
My name is Jay Garrick.
Where I came from,
I was a speedster like you.
When you created the Singularity
above Central City,
you also created a portal
connecting our two Earths.
I somehow ended up in your world.
There isn'tjust one breach.
There's 52 of them.
But the most significant breach
of all appears to be here.
Inside S.T.A.R. Labs.
Hey, Iris, what's up?
Barry, I need your help. Now!
- Were those gunshots?
- Yeah.
I'm at Baldwin Tower.
I can't find a way out.
Window. Is there a window?
Over here!
Um, yeah. Up ahead.
Okay. I'm by the window. Why?
Okay, great. You're gonna need tojump.
What? Are you crazy? Barry, no way!
Iris, do you trust me?
Yes. I trust you.
Okay. Then jump.
I can do this. I can do this.
All right. You good?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Wait. How many guys are up there?
- Two. They both have guns.
- Okay.
Okay. Now they're taking little naps
until the C.C.P.D. wakes them.
So what exactly were you thinking?
I got a hot lead on a
real estate scam. I mean,
these guys have been
illegally evicting people,
breaking up families.
Okay, look. No story is worth your life.
- Thank you for coming.
- Yeah.
I can't wait to write about this.
Pretty amazing, isn't it?
I still can't believe what I'm looking at.
Fifty-two breaches in Central City
and the biggest one just
happens to be in our basement.
We need a name for it.
It's not a pet, Cisco.
No, it's a wormhole.
Professor Stein, what are you doing?
Your blood pressure is 147 over 82.
You could pass out again.
It's merely a few points above the
140 average for someone my age.
Besides, I have some ideas
I would like to contribute
to this discussion, Dr. Snow.
And lwant to hear them.
This isn't just a wormhole.
It's my way home.
Back to Earth-2.
Jay, you really think that we can use
this as some kind of bridge
from yourworld to ours?
Zoom uses the breaches. Why can't we?
Well, we don't know how.
Everything I put through
just bounces back.
If Zoom's using these breaches
to transport people from Earth-2,
maybe it takes a speedster.
- He's not gonna...
- Yeah, he is.
Maybe I'm not fast enough.
I don't believe your speed
is the entirety of the issue, Barry.
It might be the breach's stability,
or lack thereof.
He's right. We need to think
of the breach as a door.
And on Earth-2 there's another door.
In between we have a hallway.
But the hallway's constantly shifting,
twisting, collapsing upon itself.
And the doors keep moving with it.
So we stabilize the door,
we stabilize the hallway.
- And then I can jump through it.
- Exactly.
It would serve as a kind of cannon.
A speed cannon.
Mmm...
We should hang out more.
All right. No more tests today.
All of you are leaving now. As am I.
Cherish the gift of youth
as I will go cherish my much-needed nap.
Clarissa's already on her way
to pick me up.
Joseph.
You're wearing your wedding ring.
Divorced men take them off.
Widowers don't.
I need you to leave town.
And you thought you could pay me
to walk away from my own daughter?
Last time you walked away for free.
No amount of money
is gonna keep me away from Iris.
It has been 20 years, Francine.
Why did you show up now?
Now, I'm different. Now, I'm ready.
No, now you're too late.
Iris is fine without you.
You've done a...
You've done a wonderful job, Joe.
Better than I ever could.
But right now, she needs her mother.
Losing the love of your life
isn't something
you can just get over in a few months.
I would know.
Would you?
You have 48 hours to leave Central City.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Oh!
- Hey. Hey!
Hey! The Flash!
What?
The drinks that they're serving today.
They're called "The Flash."
"A brewed coffee with an extra shot
of espresso to keep you running all day."
But you should maybejust,
you know, have one of those.
Yeah. No, my friends ordered
these. I didn't even realize that, umm...
Are you sticking around to celebrate?
I don't know. Should I?
You know, actually, never mind. I can't.
- L... I have to head into work.
- Okay.
- But it was great to see you.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you. Bye, Patty.
- Okay. Bye.
- All right. Four Flashes.
- Mmm-hmm.
Be careful, apparently
they are super-caffeinated.
First, I had a day named after me,
now I have a drink.
Well, all the things you do,
rebuilding this place, protecting people,
everyone's appreciative, right?
- Mmm-hmm, I'll drink to that.
- Yeah.
Hey, you guys think
Professor Stein is okay, right?
I mean, Clarissa would call
if there was anything wrong?
- Yeah.
- All right.
I'm just going to call and check in.
I'll be back.
I don't see that call going well.
Young lady, these
repeated intrusions are interrupting
what should be a speedy... Oh!
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
You can bump into me any day, Cisco.
Huh. Lisa Snart.
You here to double-cross us again
or are you and your big bro
holding up coffee shops now?
I need your help.
In your dreams, Sister Cold.
You know I could call The Flash,
he'd be here in, like,
two seconds. Probably one.
Call him.
Oh! Okay. lmma call him.
Mmm-hmm.
You really want me to call The Flash?
I need his help, too.
My brother's been kidnapped.
All right, so you really
want us to just believe
that Captain Cold was kidnapped?
- I saw it happen.
- Hmm...
Last night, Lenny, me,
and Mick were knocking over
the cashier's cage
at Central City Racetrack.
Does it physically pain your
family not to rob people?
I never finished the job.
Well, after Mick torched through the
side entrance, I looked back for Lenny,
and saw him getting thrown
into the back of a van.
And why didn't you and Mick follow?
Iwould have.
Someone hit me from behind
and knocked me out.
When I came to, Lenny was gone
and Mick already made off with the cash.
How do we know
this isn't some kind of a trap?
If Lenny wanted Flash dead,
he would have let Mardon, Simmons,
and Bivolo take that honor, remember?
- Yeah, I remember.
- Good.
Then you'll also recall that you owe
Lenny a favor for saving your life.
Time to make good on that debt, Flash.
I do not like her.
Yeah, but she makes a point.
What? We should at least
hear her out. Right?
Even if I wanted to help,
how are we supposed to find him?
Not a problem.
See, when I rebuilt the cold gun,
I didn't have time
to place a tracker on it.
So I devised a method of locating it
by borrowing some military technology.
See, the gun works
the same as thermal imaging,
only instead of infrared heat signatures,
it's looking for
ultraviolet cold signatures.
Whoa, look at that.
The gun's UV thermal reading
was last picked up at 5th and Hoyt.
- Eight minutes ago.
- All right.
Let's see if you're a liar.
Snart.
Barry.
Are you okay?
Peachy.
Okay. Well, uh...
I'm supposed to be here to rescue you.
That's not necessary.
You can speed along now.
Look, Snart, if these guys
are making you do this...
No one makes me do anything.
Then why does your sister think
you've been kidnapped?
What's taking so long?
Igot held up.
Always the excuse with you...
Well, look at that.
I didn't think you had it in you, son.
Thanks, Dad.
Come on.
We're behind schedule.
You know what they say.
"Live fast, die young."
Talk to me. What's going on?
Cisco! Snart hit me with his cold gun!
His vitals are bottoming out.
I'm bringing the heat right now.
What?
The suit. What's happening?
Therma-threading, baby!
It's a little something I added
for situations exactly like this one.
Please... Please tell me it's working.
Yeah. It worked.
But Snart's gone.
And Lisa has a lot of explaining to do.
So, your brother was not kidnapped.
He was pulling ajob.
With your father.
What?
No. Lenny would never do that.
Oh, just like he would never try
and kill The Flash with his cold gun.
Are you sure it was my dad?
That's him.
Lewis Snart.
Convicted of larceny, armed robbery,
aggravated assault,
assault with a deadly weapon...
You have to believe me.
Lenny would never work with him.
He's a bad guy.
You and your entire family are criminals.
Why should we trust anything you say?
I didn't get this scar being a criminal.
I got it being a daughter.
Let me go. I got this.
I see you found my hiding spot.
This is usually where I come to, you know,
get away.
First time my father came
after me, I was seven.
Second time, I was eight.
That's when I learned that a
bottle hurts worse than a fist.
He used to say he was
trying to teach us lessons.
I must have been a slow learner
because the lessons never stopped.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
Lenny practically raised me.
If it weren't for him,
I would have turned out a lot worse.
I know.
How could I be any worse?
I didn't say that.
You didn't have to.
But believe me, there is worse.
And look, he may be a jerk brother,
but he's the onlyjerk brother I've got.
He protected me.
Now it's my turn.
If he's with my dad,
he is in serious trouble.
Please.
You've gotta find out what's going on.
- Hey, baby.
- Dad.
What are you doing here?
I came to check in on my
favorite crime-fighting reporter.
Dad.
Actually, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Hey, Iris, Editorial needs your
photos and story ASAP.
Congratulations, Detective.
Your daughter's exposé
just made the front page.
What?
I am so happy for you.
A little bit jealous,
but I'll get over it.
Thanks, Linda. I... lgot lucky.
No. She's being modest.
Your daughter's a serious badass.
You don't have to tell me.
Well, I better let you get back to work.
Wait, there was something that you
wanted to talk to me about, right?
Later. It can wait. Go be fabulous!
Okay.
Back from the dead so soon, Barry.
Pass me the salt.
Don't spill, it's bad luck.
Why are you working with Lewis?
Lisa told us you hate him.
Things are...
Complicated with family.
As you know with your own parents, hmm?
Tell me what's going on. Let me help you.
Don't waste your time trying to save
people who don't want to be saved.
Yeah, well, maybe it's not
just about you, right?
I'm betting, whatever you two are up to,
innocent people are gonna get hurt.
Don't worry. I remember our deal.
You leave me alone,
I make sure no one dies.
All right. You're a criminal, Snart.
But you live by a code.
It sounds to me like Lewis doesn't.
Like he won't care if people die.
That's why I can't leave this alone.
Then everyone will know who
The Flash is under that mask.
I don't care.
I will take you down anyway. Both of you.
We'll see about that.
Thanks for dinner.
Mmm-hmm.
Iris' mom is alive.
I lied to Iris. You. Everybody.
Why?
I felt like I didn't have a choice.
Francine did so many things wrong.
Just about everything.
I don't know. Now I feel like
my one wrong might be worse.
Look, Joe.
I've known you for,
you know, most of my life,
and I know that you always have
a good reason for the decisions you make.
And obviously, you were worried
that Iris would go down
the wrong path if Francine raised her.
I mean, look at Snart.
He's a criminal because he had Lewis
for a father. That could have been me.
Oh, come on. Never.
Yeah, because I had you.
And so did Iris.
You just gotta trust in that
and tell her the truth.
Yeah, how do I do that
without hurting her?
She's not a little girl anymore.
You should've seen her
in action the other day.
Putting her neck on the line for a story.
She can handle anything
that comes herway.
I've just lied to her for so long,
I'm scared she's not
gonna understand or forgive me.
I could lose her.
No. She's gonna forgive you.
You just gotta give her a chance.
We make our move at 9:00.
That's when the cleaning crews go in,
and the daytime shift leaves.
Now we'll go up in the
service elevator to the 27th floor.
They got a two-man team of armed guards
working the 27th to the 29th floor.
But if we time it perfectly
with their shift change,
we should be able to get in and out.
And if timing doesn't work out?
- Then those guards don't make it home.
- But ifwe start on the top floor,
- there's a service elevator that will...
- Son.
You and I both know that there's
casualties in this line of work.
Rutenberg, you're the tech guy.
Did you find a solution
for the vault hallway?
Not yet. That Draycon Systems
keypad's gonna be a problem.
Fine. How about you?
You gonna disappoint me too,
or is that freeze gun of yours
gonna look after the
power source for the laser grid?
It's a cold gun.
And yes. But I have a better way
to get past the lasers.
That gun is the only reason you're here,
so shut up before I make you...
Ow. Ow, my... My head!
Oh, my head!
Ow! Ahhh!
It feels like it's gonna...
Nobody talks to my son that way. Nobody.
Don't worry, sir.
I waited for you this time.
Okay, I may have done a quick
preliminary assessment of my own.
Something is definitely weird.
- Oh.
- Decapitation.
- Yeah.
- Yikes.
We're still recovering parts of the head,
so the ID is taking
a little longer than normal.
Ugh! Sorry.
I thought I stepped on an ear.
I didn't. lf I did, I'd be hearing things.
Oh, hell no.
It doesn't look like the head was sliced
off with any weapon I'm familiar with.
And I'm familiar with most weapons.
Yeah, you're right.
Perforation around the neck is too jagged.
It's almost like the head was blown off.
Like a meta-human
who can explode heads, right?
Not necessarily.
Traces of thermite.
- Bomb residue?
- Uh-huh.
But then why wasn't the
rest of the body blown apart?
I don't know.
The victim is David Rutenberg,
security systems expert.
And guess who's on his list
of known associates.
Lewis Snart.
Lewis Snart? Isn't he related
to Leonard Snart AKA Captain Cold?
Please don't call him that.
Okay.
- Uh, one second. Come here.
- Sure.
I think this guy is part of Snart's crew.
So, Snart put a bomb in him
to keep him in line?
No, Snart wouldn't do that.
But his father would.
Wait, so Lewis is killing people,
and Snart's still working with him?
What happened with the deal you had?
Maybe he doesn't have a choice.
So you think Lewis
put a bomb in his own son
to force him to pull off a heist?
Snart still wouldn't do it.
He'd dig the bomb
out of his own head if he had to.
So there must be something else
that Snart cares about.
The only thing Snart
cares about is his sister.
- Hey.
- Thought you might be hungry.
- Ah!
Good to know whatever Earth you go to,
there's always a Big Belly Burger.
Thank you very much.
Looks like you're making progress.
Slowly.
I should be able to do this a lot faster.
You miss it. Your speed?
Yeah. Surprising how much.
So what will you do
when you get back to your Earth?
I don't know.
Guess I'll just have
to get used to being...
Normal?
Yeah.
Two years ago, I was just a scientist
slowly trying to save the world
by purifying heavy water
without residual radiation.
Important work.
Yeah. It was.
But after the particle
accelerator exploded,
I didn't need to wait years
for my research to save a life.
I could save one before breakfast.
I could save 50 before going to sleep.
There's nothing like that rush.
You guys have been fighting
so many battles, one after another,
I'm not sure Barry's
had time to take it in.
To appreciate how great it can feel.
Being a superhero isn't always
about how fast you can run.
It's about helping however you can,
wherever you're needed most.
I think that Jay Garrick, physicist,
has just as much to contribute
as Jay Garrick, superhero. Maybe more.
You know what would help me
build the speed cannon faster?
- Hmm?
- An extra set of hands.
Specifically ones
with a surgeon's precision.
Me?
Sure, if you think I can really help.
Hey, Caitlin. We need you up here.
Like, right now.
Sorry.
Oh, boy.
What is it?
Lisa, there are traces
of thermite on your skin.
Thermite? Like an explosive?
Not like an explosive...
It's a bomb.
When you were knocked out,
your dad must have injected you with it.
Hey. Dad, what's up?
Your message was pretty cryptic,
even for you.
Hey, baby.
I need you to sit down.
Dad, what's going on?
Okay.
When I was still a beat cop,
me and my partner were on patrol.
And dispatch came on the radio.
A little girl had called in.
She said her mom had taken
some pills and she wouldn't wake up.
And the little girl gave the address.
The address was mine.
By the time I got here,
your mother was unresponsive,
passed out on that couch.
And in that kitchen, the stove was on.
There you were,
standing in front of an open flame.
If I hadn't gotten here when I did...
Wait, my mom...
Your mom was a drug addict.
This wasn't the first time
something like that had happened.
I got Francine into another rehab,
and a couple days later,
she was gone.
I looked everywhere for her, but...
Wife of a cop. She knew how to disappear.
I couldn't stand the thought
of you growing up
thinking you were abandoned.
Going to sleep at night
thinking your mother left
because you weren't enough to
make her stay, that you weren't loved.
Because I loved you.
I loved you with everything I got.
Then we took Barry in.
And I saw the trauma
he was going through, and I...
I was sure. I was sure
that I did the right thing.
Not giving you that burden.
What do you mean Mom left? l...
I don't... I don't understand.
I don't understand.
What are you telling me?
Your mother's alive.
She's here in Central City.
She wants to see you.
All these years, I thought...
Dad, you told me that my...
I know.
I should've told you sooner,
but I couldn't figure out the right way.
And the mother you thought you remember,
the perfect mother in the stories
I made up for you,
that is the mother you deserved.
And I knew Francine couldn't be like that.
She would only break your heart.
I'm so sorry.
Dad.
It's okay. I understand.
You were just trying to keep me safe.
The micro-bomb casing must be made
of some kind of a ferromagnetic material.
Once you hold it steady with the magnet,
I can surgically excise it.
Put the magnet down!
This is a really concentrated bomb.
It's gonna combust if it's exposed
to magnetic friction and an oxidant.
What's he talking about?
- Air.
- Uh...
The... The bomb will explode
if it comes in contact with air.
Don't worry, Lisa. We're gonna find
another way to get it out.
Scientific minds, can we confer, please?
What if The Flash speed-extracts it?
No. It's too risky.
I'm gonna find a way to get it out,
I just need a little time.
Well, we need to keep track of Lewis
Until you figure out
how to disarm the bomb.
I wish we knew what he was
gonna steal next. And when.
Maybe I can get them to tell me.
Their tech guy is dead.
So I'm betting they're
gonna need a new one.
I'm saying I'm gonna
infiltrate Lewis' crew.
You're going to pretend to be a criminal?
How hard can it be?
These visits are getting old.
Third time's a charm.
I told you. I don't need saving.
But your sister does.
I know your dad put a bomb in Lisa.
And Lewis told you he'd kill her
if you didn't help him, right?
Look, don't worry.
My team's working on a way
to remove the bomb.
Hope you got that gun of yours
ready to blast 'cause...
- Who the hell is this?
- Uh, I'm...
Lenny said you need a new tech.
What's up? I'm... I'm Sam. What's up?
You're telling me you think this kid
can crack a Draycon keypad?
Well, I did help Snart steal
the Kahndaq Dynasty Diamond
from Central City Museum last year.
That was locked up behind an AmerTek
Industries Phase Three Suppression Door
with a Draycon XL-1218 keypad.
So...
Couldn't have done it without him.
Draycon's my jam.
Ah...
Okay, Sam. Let's go.
Right now?
You got a problem with that?
No. All good. Can't wait.
Oh, this should be fun.
Keep quiet and follow my lead.
Just like old times.
You watching the Diamonds game?
Yeah. The Salamanders are killing 'em.
IDs.
- What floor are you going to?
- 27th.
Hey, what's the hold up, guys?
I mean, you wanna call management
and explain why the toilets
are still overflowing?
We're all on the clock, right?
Yeah. You guys are good to go.
- Thanks.
- Ah...
You enjoy the game, guys.
- Diamonds don't stand a chance.
- Not tonight they don't.
Oh, hold on. Did you hear that?
I got it.
It's two armed guards.
Guess your timing
didn't work out after all.
Yeah, that's why we got a Plan B.
'Cause you always needed one.
Yeah, but...
Your sister turned out
to be a disappointment also.
Hey, what do you guys say
we get on with the job?
Guards are gone.
I don't know, must've taken a break.
Yeah. Must've.
Okay, Sam. Show us what you got.
Yeah. All right.
I'll just...
You guys just keep a lookout and I'll...
Told you Draycon was my jam.
- Nice job, Sam.
- Yeah.
It's good to go out on a high note.
Sorry, Barry.
What are you going
to do to me with that thing?
Operating pressure on this
is over 1,000 PSI.
This will easily suck the
micro-bomb out of her neck
and into the barrel of this
with one high-powered shot.
There is one slight risk.
Besides shooting a high-powered
weapon directly against my neck?
The gun does use compressed air.
I trust you, Cisco.
Okay, son, make me proud.
Like I care.
Now what?
I told you I had a better way
past the lasers.
Step aside. Time for another lesson.
You've got 125 seconds
before the system defrosts.
- Then what?
- Sirens.
How do you feel?
Like we should've put down some plastic.
That's not funny.
Yeah.
But I like it when you smile.
Okay. Ready?
Shoot me, Cisco.
It's... Flash!
Cisco, how you doing with Lisa?
Uh, kind of in the middle of it
right now, buddy.
All right. We need that bomb out.
The heist is going down right now.
Time's up.
Let's get outta here.
Only place you're going
is back to Iron Heights, Lewis.
Ah...
- You wanna bet?
- Do I wanna bet?
Do not bet! Give me a minute!
Tell me this. What kind of man
puts a bomb in his own daughter?
- A very rich man.
- Ah...
Shoot him, son.
Kill him or you'll never
see your sister alive.
Do it, Cisco.
I got the bomb out!
Lisa's safe.
You're working with The Flash?
I thought you hated him.
Not as much as I...
Hate you.
Lisa was safe.
Why did you do that?
He broke my sister's heart.
Only fairl break his.
Last time I was in Iron Heights,
I was visiting my dad.
Yeah, me too.
- And yet you killed him.
- He deserved it.
Is that funny to you?
No.
What's funny is I finally
figured out your secret.
And what secret would that be?
You'd do anything to protect your sister.
Well, I know your secret too.
Better hope I don't talk in my sleep.
You won't.
Today just proved what I've always known.
There's good in you, Snart.
Yeah, you don't have to admit it to me.
But there's a part of you that knows
you don't have to
let your past define you.
A part of you that really wants
to be more than just a criminal.
So I should be a hero like you, Barry.
What exactly does that pay again?
It's just a matter of time.
Something you'll have a lot of in here.
Not as much as you think.
Be seein' you.
You really think that leopard's
gonna change its spots?
I do.
Maybe we should transfer him
to the meta-human wing anyway.
I already got Patty on the papewvork.
All right.
Hey, I wanted to thank you
for the advice you gave.
I told Iris.
She's going to sit down with Francine.
It was hard, but it was for the best.
I'm glad. Anytime.
You're a good son, Barry.
I know.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Fancy seeing you here.
Okay, we have to stop
running into each other like this.
I know. We should just
make a schedule or something.
Okay, great. Well, then I'll just have,
you know, my people call your people.
See, that's the problem.
Neither one of us have people.
So, how are we possibly gonna do this?
There. My number.
Oh!
That... That's what you meant, right?
Yes.
- No.
- Yeah, uh...
No, you didn't. Um...
You know what, though?
I've actually been meaning
to give you my number,
in case you had questions about a case.
You know, sometimes when you call
through dispatch, it gets all jammed up.
And this is efficient.
And as law enforcement colleagues,
efficiency is important.
Yes, it is. No, that's...
Yeah.
That's exactly what I was thinking too.
Okay, great. Awesome.
- Okay, I'll see you.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Oh!
Just kidding. Okay.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
So, taking off?
Thought I'd say goodbye.
And thank you.
Yeah, well,
I wouldn't leave a bomb in anyone.
Not even you.
It's more than that.
You were there for me
when I was feeling weak.
I hate feeling weak.
It's hard for me to trust people,
but I trusted you.
You know, you might actually
be my first real friend.
Is any of that true?
Until next time, Cisco.
Later, Golden Glider.
Ta-da! The speed cannon.
Wow! Look at that.
Dudes, you actually built the thing.
Mr. Garrick, I am...
I am quite impressed
by what you've accomplished
during my recent wellness hiatus.
- Have you tested it out yet?
- Not yet.
Want to do the honors?
No, no, no, no! Now that I...
Now that I am back to optimal health,
please, allow me.
Excelsior!
How did you stabilize it?
- CFL quark matter.
- Ah!
Negative energy density
with positive surface pressure.
- It's genius!
- You created CFL Quark Matter?
It's something we perfected on my Earth.
I'll show you some time.
You mean,
sometime in the next few minutes?
Oh...
Yeah, I guess this is it, huh?
Time for me to go back home.
Right now? I mean, we still need
your help with the breachers.
My first priority is Zoom.
I need to find out what he's up to.
How he stole my speed.
But you can do that here.
And, you know, if you go back
then we can't get in touch with you
when we need your help,
or with Zoom,
or whatever else.
It would be nice to be able to
pick your brain every once in a while.
Get some more speedster tips.
Hmm.
Okay.
Once we take care of Zoom, I'm going home.
- That's fair.
- Good.
'Cause I could use a shower
and a shave, and some sunlight.
I'll, uh, see you later.
So, Professor Stein, how are you feeling?
Well, uh, it appears that
a little rest heals all maladies.
I couldn't feel...
Professor?
No, no, no, no. Get back! Come here!
Professor Stein!
Professor Stein, can you hear me?
- Professor Stein?
- What happened to him?
He... He went up like Firestorm,
but the flame, why was it blue?
I don't know. This isn't good.
We need to stabilize him fast.