My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
He only wants the bus metas,
he wants their powers, all of them.
DeVoe has absorbed the powers
of Kilg%re, Hazard, Black Bison,
Brainstorm and Dwarfstar.
- I'm gonna take DeVoe down.
- Just like Izzy would have wanted.
DeVoe orchestrated everything to get
the people he wanted on the bus.
We've got a planner, just like Thawne.
This is an intelligence booster.
I'll finally be able
to outthink The Thinker.
- Daddy?
- Pleased to meet you, sir.
The last two remaining bus metas.
Janet Petty and Edwin Gauss.
- Ralph.
- Ready.
Connect double Scarlet Speedster
in three, two, one.
Wait. I got a better idea.
Over here, Doc Ock.
Watch this, Master Splinter.
Turtle power.
Shut it down.
All right, let's run
it again. We gotta make this work.
Does he know that?
Ralph?
What?
One more time, please.
Follow Barry's plan.
You know, the one where I've spent
hours of my precious time
programming realistic holograms for you?
Which, bravo on that, by the way.
- Thank you.
- Look, just...
Morph yourself into Barry,
there'll be two Flashes,
Thinker won't know which
one is which, and we'll confuse him.
Kind of a "her," actually.
Ralph, you're missing
the point of this exercise.
No, I get it.
I was just doing a little improv.
But this
isn't stand-up comedy!
Yeah, I know that,
but you just let it play out,
it would've worked, you could've
done some improv-ing of your own.
Comedy comes in threes, man.
We're trying to protect you.
DeVoe's coming.
We need to be ready, all of us.
Okay?
I still think it's a pretty good plan.
I hide my face, I save my ass.
We'd make a fortune.
An improv group made up of superheroes?
We can take it to Washington.
- We'd be the DC Comics.
- No, Ralph.
First rule of improv is say yes.
Would it kill you to take
training seriously?
Would it kill you to open up
your mind grapes just a little?
Hey, we'll get there.
Eventually, but we'll get there.
He's just making a big joke
out of the whole thing.
It's just the way he is, Barry.
I know, but he needs to think
like a hero, stay on point.
DeVoe's thought of everything.
We can't just wing this one.
Look, we'll figure it out.
We always do, right?
Melting Point's on our team now,
we just need to find
the other two bus metas.
And we'll be in good shape.
Yeah.
Where are we with tracking down
Edwin Gauss and Janet Petty?
- No, no. He's... He's still...
- What?
Working on it.
I can't work with all this noise!
That is disgusting, Harry,
really, grow up.
Really?
Wasn't me.
That was expensive.
Harry, look, every time
you try to locate these guys,
it's the same thing.
I'm telling you,
you just crack that thing open,
- it's probably broken.
- It's not broken.
It's just finding these two
is complicated.
Why is that?
Because this dude, Edwin Gauss,
flat out disappeared the day
Allen came out of the speed force.
No credit card charges,
no bank withdrawals,
no social media posts, nothing.
- Gone.
- What about Janet Petty?
Just as tricky. I asked Joe
to pull her file from C.C.P.D.
Her first known record wasn't
until she was 13.
Some sort of a nomad.
Last known address, Iron Heights.
- What's she in for?
- Trifecta, breaking and entering,
trespassing, and burglary.
What we should be worried about is,
where is she now?
And what are her powers?
Is that really her handle?
"Null"?
Okay, DeVoe needs both of these
people for whatever he has planned,
so we have to figure out where they are.
I will, Allen, if I can get
a little peace, a little quiet,
and no interruptions!
Great.
- Cisky.
- Breacher?
I need your help.
Little bit
of a mixed message here.
I was hunting Lord Crucifer,
leader of the Tenth Circle.
His cult of bloodsuckers ambushed me.
- They had me surrounded.
- So, you were attacked by...
Vampires?
Hundreds of vampires.
The battle was fierce,
but I managed to dismantle
his entire force.
But when I went to finish off Crucifer,
something happened to me.
My powers, they were gone.
What do you mean?
I couldn't vibe blast.
Crucifer got away.
He must've done something to my powers!
Has this ever happened before?
Never.
But Cynthia always said
you were an intelligent man.
Well versed in the meta-science.
Glad to hear Gypsy
still remembers who I am.
Hey, you're her boss.
You would know the answer to this.
Does she ever get a day off?
Cynthia is very devoted to her job.
But in regards to your skills...
Yeah, yeah, let me guess.
- You think she's wrong.
- No!
What I wanna say is,
I think you can fix me.
Oh.
Well...
Sir...
We would be happy to run some tests
in the speed lab, you know,
see if everything's okay.
Thank you, Cisco.
Now, I must get some tea.
- He didn't insult me once.
- Nope.
I just hope we can help him.
How was your rest, my love?
Wonderful, I've never felt more
rejuvenated and ready
to realize our dream.
Clifford.
The additional dark matter
from our subject metas,
is overwhelming this host's body.
How long do we have?
At the present rate...
Just over a week's time.
No, I will not allow it.
It may be possible to adjust
the biomass index,
re-calibrate the energy distribution,
extend your current host's life.
Odd.
There are already plans for such
an adjustment partially designed.
I attempted the same course of action.
Though my mind for engineering
is nowhere near as gifted as yours.
Well, you got a good start.
I will be able to complete
these designs within a few hours.
Rest, my love. I will handle everything.
You always do.
And then we will continue on our search
for the remaining two bus metas.
You mean, three.
The Weeper is still at large.
Yes.
Three.
Perhaps my mind is being
affected as well.
Come on, put your back into it.
Put your fat back into it.
This stinks, man.
This is too heavy and you're too weak.
Let's get the big dolly.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Dude, the crate's gone.
We gotta call the boss.
Well, well, well, well, well.
If the crown fits...
We're moving, I was telling the guy,
"It's gonna take all night
to move this stuff."
Okay, remember.
Let's just be discreet.
Neither one of us
are supposed to be here.
- Can you do that?
- Can pigs fly?
- No.
- They can if you put 'em on an airplane.
Think, Allen, think.
Okay.
Just here with your chai latte,
Detective West.
Subtle.
- It was gone.
- Excuse me, just a second, okay?
Hey.
What happened?
Robbery.
Stole the Kahndaq dynasty family crown.
It was brought here
for the museum exhibition.
The security guard said that
it was being transported
in a steel-plated crate,
weighs about 200 pounds.
Suddenly disappeared without a trace,
and then reappeared completely smashed.
So was anything else
missing in the museum?
Just the crown, nothing else is missing.
Should I stretch around the perimeter,
check things out?
No, not yet. I can tell from here
to cause that type of impact,
case had to be moving at
at least 55 miles per hour.
So we're looking for a meta
with super strength?
Maybe. Are there fingerprints
on the case?
I'll have them dust it,
send the results in.
Why wait? I can just grab the tape,
get the prints right now.
No, no. Hey!
It was definitely Killer Frost,
and she looked at me.
Ralph!
Dude!
I need this job!
Allen, look what you did.
That's you, bro.
Die, Plastoid, die!
Again.
All right.
I think that's enough.
All right. Hey, look, Breacher,
I know you're clearly very...
Frustrated, uh,
but don't stress, okay?
We're gonna figure this out,
and once we do,
we're gonna fix it, I promise.
Cisky, look.
I'm sorry for the way I've treated you.
But when you fix me,
I'll give Cynthia more time
to be with you.
Really?
Yeah.
Now, I'm hungry.
We can fix that, too.
Um, there's donuts
in the downstairs break room.
Help yourself, it's a huge selection.
Yeah. Try the pineapple fritters.
And don't forget to try
the nacho donuts.
Those are really good.
Looks like things are looking up
for your boy, Cisco.
Yeah?
What? What?
What is... What? What is it?
What is wrong with him?
Nothing, really.
He seems to be in good health.
There's nothing abnormal
in his blood work
and his body scan showed
no signs of cellular damage,
despite years of using
vibrational powers.
Okay. So, then, why the face?
Because Crucifer didn't take
his powers from him.
Father Time did.
He can't blast
because he's getting older?
Mmm-hmm. Powers like yours requires
a lot of energy,
and when that energy
starts to dwindle...
Vibe blasts are the first things to go?
I think you have to tell him.
He's never ever gonna let me
see Gypsy if I tell him.
He's probably gonna send a knife
flying right through my skull
if I tell him.
He might...
But it's the right thing to do.
What the...
Initiate chemical analysis.
A $40,000 vase?
It's not like it was made of gold.
Actually, it was, and you two
can't go to crime scenes anymore,
- PIs or not.
- Don't give me that look.
I was just trying to speed up
the process of finding this meta, Allen.
Which is taking forever.
Wait, we got a hit.
Jeannie Williams.
Um, oh, wait, we got multiple hits.
Jane Liska, Judy Newton...
She's used like 17 different aliases.
Okay, so how do we find her?
And we can't just wait for her
to rob somebody else.
Well, we don't have to.
We have the many variations
of her facade.
All right? We simply plug these
many variations into
- the facial recognition software.
- See if we get a hit.
Exactly right.
You're starting
to come in handy, Harry.
That's 40 minutes ago.
Corner of Orchard and Broome.
Orchard and Broome? What's over there?
Not "what."
Who.
- Come on. Come on.
- What are you...
It smells like liverwurst.
Yeah, wait till we get inside.
Open up.
Okay, stick to the plan.
We question her.
We find Null, we cuff her.
Got it. Little good cop/bad cop action.
Who the hell are you?
Your worst nightmare.
Uh, Joe? What are you
doing?
Detective Joe West, C.C.P.D.
We got a couple of questions
for you, scumbag.
Hey, only my closest friends
can call me that.
Word is, there's a new cutpurse in town
who likes fancy jewels,
last seen in this part of town.
- PI Barry Allen.
- PI Barry Allen...
Show him, show him.
Oh, Barry Allen, I know all about
your spectacular fall from grace.
- Tragic, really.
- Yes, thank you. Just take a look.
We're guessing she came here
for help to wash the sparklies.
Oh, I should be so lucky.
Certainly wouldn't mind a drop-in
from a lovely-looking lassie like this.
You know what I mean?
But unfortunately, not in my cards.
I'm sorry, can I keep this?
I will mess you up for lying in my face.
- Ralph.
- "Ralph"?
- There's no Ralph here.
- Joe.
I'm Detective Joe West,
the baddest damn cop
you've ever come across.
As God as my witness, I am not lying.
I'm not.
Oopsy-daisy.
I knew it.
- Joe West doesn't make any mistakes.
- Okay.
Where'd she go, Earl?
Deal's off.
Damn it.
Cuffs.
- Cuffs.
- Allen.
Babe, you okay?
I just wanna get down from here
as soon as possible.
Maybe you should try to burp
yourself down like Charlie Bucket.
Ralph.
- Anything?
- Well, as best I can tell,
Null's powers affect
the density of his cells.
It's like
you've been filled with helium.
- Terrific.
- Always knew you were a lightweight.
I swear, Ralph...
Hey, is there a way
to reengage his gravitational...
Gravitational force.
Huh. Turns out...
Not necessary.
Do not let go.
Based on Barry's standard mass
and gravitational force G
and taking into account
the half-life decrement
of Null's dark matter infusion,
this effect should eventually
just wear off.
- "Wear off"?
- Your cells should return to normal
- right about...
- What the hell?
Now.
Two for the landing,
but perfect 10 for the "thud" noise.
Why are you joking right now?
I mean, seriously, what the hell
was that back there,
pretending to be Joe?
I committed to the bit,
I couldn't blow my cover.
Ralph, what if that had
happened outside on the street?
I could've floated away
into the stratosphere,
- fallen to my death.
- I would've figured something out.
Ral...
Out of the 12 bus metas we've found,
DeVoe is in control of seven of them.
If he gets Null, it'll be eight.
If he gets control of her powers...
We're talking about your life here.
Sorry, I was just thinking about
the end of Lost.
I mean, were they in purgatory?
What did Kate really see in Jack?
Ralph...
I'm sorry, man, but I'm benching you.
- Why?
- Because you're constantly
in the middle of a comedy routine
instead of doing what you should.
If you had just tossed me the cuffs,
we would have Null right now.
Yeah, or she could have ran out the door
and I'd stretched the cuffs
on her when she didn't see it coming.
It's fine.
Look, I'm doing what's best for you.
No, you're not.
You're doing what's best for you.
Display complete physiological
results for "DeVoe, Marlize."
Cortisol levels low.
Recent display of tachycardia.
Repetitive pupil dilation.
Display serotonin level.
319 nanograms.
Levels found in patients
using psychoactive narcotics.
How is that?
Subject four still at large.
"Created to provide
widespread euphoria...
"Or feelings of love."
What if we put him
on an all-alkaline diet,
full of antioxidants?
- Nope.
- Okay, what if we...
Oh, what if we make a super-shake
full of, like, enzymes and probiotics?
Neither of those
are gonna work long-term, Cisco.
Okay, well, we gotta come up
with something, right?
I mean, how old is this guy, anyway?
This guy's old.
We have to solve this.
'Cause I don't know about you,
but I actually like my life.
I know this isn't the easy answer.
But I think you have to tell him.
Cisky!
Oh, hey, you, we were
just talking about you.
I've tasted all your donuts.
Where is my cure?
Well, it's a little, um...
It's a little complicated.
But, you are lucky,
my friend, because...
Your fix is as simple
as taking one of these
- little pink pills.
- Blue.
Blue pills.
Right there.
"Antihistamine."
That... That's right, antihistamine.
See, uh, "stamine,"
that's Latin for "stamina,"
which you have plenty of, you know.
You have so much of it
that it's actually hurting you.
But this antimatter pill,
it's gonna level you right out.
Oh, you're taking it now.
He's taking it now.
Why is my vibe blast different?
I think it's a side effect of the pills.
Hasn't been thoroughly researched yet.
But, you know, headaches, nausea,
different, uh, colored vibes.
I'm cured. Thank you.
Anytime.
You do realize
you're just making this worse?
Nothing on Null so far.
Harry's gonna try something else.
- We'll find her.
- We have to.
Even if Ralph does everything
in his power to screw it up.
Barry.
- That is not his intention.
- Well, he could've fooled me.
It's his life. I mean,
if there's anything he cares about,
- it's losing it.
- Well, he's gonna lose it
if he doesn't start thinking like me,
like I taught him.
Thinking like you?
No.
He's never gonna do that, Barry,
and you can't expect him to.
Oh, boy.
Robbery at Central City Jewelry.
- Man, she loves bling.
- I'm on it.
Wait, you need backup.
Well, Ralph's too much
of a liability right now,
he stays benched.
- Caitlin, Cisco?
- They're with Breacher,
it would take too long to wait for them.
- Then what's the plan?
- The plan
is oculation.
You said her fingertips,
they illuminated when she used
her powers,
that means dark matter accelerant,
that means powers are generating
from the optic nerve...
What I'm trying to say is...
Null can't gravitate
what she cannot see.
So you vibrate beyond the speed
of sight as you approach her eyeline.
I'll be invisible to her.
- It worked against DeVoe.
- That's right.
Didn't see that coming.
That's kind of the point.
No, you didn't see that coming.
See, I call it my "getaway car."
'Cause either the person in there dies,
or you let me get away.
You okay?
It's okay, just stay here.
This useless piece
of trash is... Useless.
It's like... I'm so dumb, I can't even
come up with a good synonym
- for this useless piece of trash.
- Harry.
No one could've predicted that
Null would have picked herself
out of the cuffs or taken a hostage.
Nor did either of you predict
the location of a 120-pound woman
using the curvature of space-time
caused by the uneven
distribution of mass,
yet still somehow
failed to account for
the gravitational pull
of a 4,000-pound car
floating right above her head.
Scientists have spent decades
trying to understand relativity
and quantum gravity...
This is not about
understanding gravity, Allen,
it's about understanding her,
or not understanding her.
As it turns out, DeVoe can somehow
calculate human behavior.
Harry, stop. Look, I'm the one
that let her get away.
- You did your best.
- Did I, Allen, really?
This is the second meta
to evade the dampening cuffs.
It's been almost a year.
And where are we?
And where is DeVoe?
What?
Nothing, it's just...
You went out into the field
and you had a plan and...
It didn't work.
But they do for DeVoe.
Harry's not wrong.
DeVoe's gone over every possible outcome
before making his plans.
Which we can't do,
and neither can Harry.
Well, then, what are we supposed to do?
I mean, you want us to just
ad-lib like Ralph wants us to?
Barry, you didn't see it,
but when you were gone,
Ralph rose to the occasion.
He cracked jokes,
he thought outside the box.
I mean, he got the job done
in the way that he knows how.
So, the question is,
are you upset with Ralph
because you think he's screwing around,
or because he's not following your plan?
Breacher.
I thought maybe we could have a drink.
I don't know, you strike me
as kind of a tequila guy, so...
Oh, crap.
You've come back
to die, Breacher.
Time has come, Crucifer.
Die, vampire, die.
Frak me, he's gonna die.
Die!
Wait a second.
Hey, back up, viejo.
Yo, Dusk Till Dawn.
I think it's time you saw some sun.
Idiot, sunlight doesn't hurt
this type of vampire.
What?
Time to go.
You said your antimatter
histamine would cure me.
Uh, yeah, I did say that, didn't I?
You lied to me.
You said you could fix me.
Now...
I'll fix you.
Breacher, stop.
Your vibe blasts don't work.
And they're not gonna work.
Why not?
Because of your age.
I should've told you earlier.
It's just I know
how special our powers are,
and you were so happy
at the thought of having them back.
And I miss your daughter.
I just wanted to see her again.
I'm sorry, Josh.
I hate you.
You did the right thing.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Just wish he knew that.
Clifford is lying to you.
He is drugging you with sedative tears
to keep you idle.
Please.
Please, remember.
Escape.
New lemonade recipe...
It already exists.
Please, don't forget, he's lying to you.
He's drugging you.
He's a monster.
You must escape.
You always save it
under the same name.
Escape now.
Every time you discover it.
It's quite clever, really.
I would expect nothing less from you.
How many times have I been through this?
Too many.
But that is of no concern.
Because with tears from the Weeper
mixed with Dominic Lanse's powers,
I can alter your memory.
So that's why you created the Weeper.
You didn't need a potential host, he...
Worked for you, yes.
I knew that the same thing
in you that I fell in love with
had the potential to destroy us.
Your humanity.
I couldn't let that get
in the way of us achieving our goal.
The enlightenment.
Clifford, I am your wife.
And I love you.
But you are nothing without me.
This is an interesting place
to hang out.
You come here to suck
the fun out of being benched?
I...
No, I came for your help, actually.
You want help from the guy
who can't take anything seriously?
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been
so quick to judge, uh...
But with DeVoe
so many steps ahead of us,
just to see you joking around
in the middle of this,
it just made me feel like
you weren't taking it seriously.
I know this is serious.
I watched...
I watched Izzy die in front of me.
I'm scared out of my mind.
Well, you know,
you got an odd way of showing it.
Yeah, well, not everybody grew up
with a super-dad like Joe West,
who makes it easy
to talk about your feelings.
When I was 10 years old,
my dad walked out on me and my mom.
And I was terrified.
But my mom, she was even more afraid.
So, you know,
I just started making jokes.
Started doing stupid gags
and funny bits and...
Whoopee cushions.
Anything to push her fear away.
And the thing is after a while,
I started to push my fear away, too.
I had no idea, Ralph, I...
It's not that I don't care
about beating DeVoe.
about being a great hero.
It's just that ever since then,
anytime that I'm afraid,
I either hide...
Or I make jokes.
Barry, we found Null,
Central City Museum.
So what do you say?
You wanna get off the bench?
I really could use your help.
Well, if duty calls.
- You get it?
- Yeah. Let's just go, all right?
Now this is my kind of party.
Listen up, people.
Anything that shines,
shimmers or sparkles,
goes in the bag.
Ooh, I love me some sapphires.
You're out of your mind
if you think I'm giving this to you.
Oh, give it to me? No, no, no, no, no.
There's no need for that. No.
I'll just take it.
And the rest of you? Sparklies.
Just hold on, all right? Just hold on.
It's over, Null.
So, back again.
Oh, with a friend.
A good friend, actually.
We hang out on the weekends,
I know where he liv...
- No getaway cars this time?
- Right.
No cars.
But there are an awful lot
of passengers.
Oh, my God. She's gonna send
everyone into the atmosphere.
Allen, you gotta get
everyone out of there right now.
All right, that's everyone.
Where is she?
- Whoa.
- No!
Looking fly, Flash!
Back to business.
Oh, God!
Guys, I can't reach him!
Cisco, you have to breach him somewhere.
He's too high in the atmosphere,
I don't have aim like that.
- Let Ralph improvise.
- What?
- Yes, do something Dibny-esque,
be your own hero, just do it fast.
Uh, "Dibny-esque," right. Um...
Okay.
All about that bling.
Ralph!
That was your plan?
He's gonna fall to his death.
- I know what I'm doing.
- Any time, Ralph!
10,000 feet, he's falling fast.
Now, 5,000 feet.
Ralph did it.
Nice work, Ralph.
Nice work.
Classy.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Ralph.
All right, Null's in the pipeline.
She's not too happy about it.
Well, she's a lot safer there
than she is on her own.
Just one more bus meta out there.
We better find him before DeVoe does.
Where's Harry?
Isn't he supposed to be working on it?
He grumbled something
about something and then left.
I'm fluent in Harry grumble.
He said he was gonna work on his cap.
Or he was making himself a turkey wrap.
Well, I'm gonna head over
to C.C.P.D., do some more digging
on this Edwin Gauss.
Ralph.
Why did a scared-sounding
Earl Cox call me saying
he was clearing your tab?
I have no idea.
That's really weird.
Hey, guys, would you, uh,
help me in the speed lab?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
We're gonna go work on some improv?
Yeah.
You were great out there tonight, man.
Thank you.
I had a lot of help.
And I had a great teacher.
You've helped me realize that
I can't always take everything
so seriously,
even when it comes to Thinker.
Wait a second, are you telling me
that I, Ralph Dibny,
taught Barry Allen,
superhero extraordinaire, a lesson?
- What could this mean?
- Means you're a great hero.
And you make this team
better by being on it.
Ah, the circle is now complete.
When I came here, I was but the learner,
now I am the master.
It's also good to be humble.
But how can I be humble...
When I am swollen with pride?
- Cisky.
- Ah, jumpin' jellyfish!
I like your new threads.
Yeah.
I went back to my Earth.
Saw my reflection in my knife.
I saw an older man.
I'm curious. Have you never
looked in a mirror before?
- I'm not a teenage girl.
- Okay, you're not a teenage girl.
But I realized,
time to hang up my coat.
This is my new uniform.
- Like it?
- Yeah.
Retirement suits you.
So, what do you do with all this time?
There's a dragon farm
on Earth-47 that I have
always wanted to visit.
A dragon farm?
Okay, get your Khaleesi on.
I'm not a Khaleesi.
Okay, you're not a Khaleesi.
But, I just wanted to tell you, Cisky,
goodbye forever.
Oh, wait, just one more thing.
Now that I've retired,
there's an opening
at the collection agency.
I would like you to replace me.
Wait, I'm... I'm confused.
You wanna see my daughter more?
Work with her.
Together, you and Cynthia
could be an unstoppable duo.
So what do you say, Vibe?
You wanna be the new Breacher?
How was your rest, my love?
Wonderful. I've never felt
more rejuvenated
and ready to realize our dream.
Clifford.
The added combination of dark matter
from all our subject metas is
overwhelming this host's body.
How long do we have?
At the present rate,
exactly one week's time.
No, I will not allow it.
It may be possible to adjust
the biomass index,
re-calibrate the energy distribution,
extend your current host's life.
Odd.
There are already plans for such
an adjustment partially designed.
I attempted the same course of action.
Well, you got quite a good start.
I will be able to complete the designs
in under an hour.
Rest, my love.
I will handle everything.
You always do.
And then, when you complete your work,
we will continue
on our journey to find
the remaining two bus metas.
Team Flash has captured Subject 11.
Now, it's time for us to act.
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
It's been 1,078 days since
we last spoke.
How can I be of service?
Hello, Gideon.
A lot has changed since then.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::