- Oh, wow!
You really did it
this time, Barry.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, seriously!
You come to Star City,
you ask for my help,
and then, inevitably,
immediately, we end up
up the creek!
- Yeah, okay.
That's fair.
They're moving in.
- On three, Team Leader.
What's that?
- That would be heat vision.
- Three.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Kid gets faster
every time we test him.
- Mach 2.
- Already?
He just got his speed
a few days ago.
How are his vitals?
- His running economy,
lactate threshold
are all way above
expected levels.
- I think we might have
a little prodigy on our hands.
Like a Wizard of Whiz.
- Guys, I don't want Wally
thinking that he's Barry,
rushing off half-cocked,
trying to take down
Alchemy or Savitar
the next time
one of them shows up.
- Okay, but guys,
Wally's not like me.
He doesn't want his powers gone.
We're gonna have a hard time
convincing him not to use them.
- Yeah, well, we have to.
Until he's ready.
- [laughs]
How?
- By convincing him
that he isn't.
That means no encouraging him,
no training him,
and you...
no talking to him
about a suit, please.
It's for his own good.
- [scoffs]
Why the hell not?
It's just another lie
between friends, right?
- Cisco.
- [chuckles]
What?
Still not good?
- Um, I think maybe we should
try again tomorrow.
I can run a few more tests.
- That was amazing.
Dinner's on me.
Whatever you want.
[terminal chimes]
- Test. Test.
Fellow S.T.A.R. Labs employees.
Your presence in the cortex
would be greatly appreciated.
- That's tonight?
His presentation?
[sighs]
Great.
- What do you think if,
after, maybe we get a drink?
You, me, Barry?
- Barry?
We're just gonna get drinks?
Pretend like we're friends?
Nice try.
It ain't gonna happen.
- You want to open S.T.A.R. Labs
to the public?
In two weeks?
- Soft open.
Not a hard open.
But, you know,
I'll use your input.
All right?
Right now, it's very important
'cause the clock is ticking.
My vision is set to include,
but not limited to...
bam... a personal
transportation tour
of the facility.
Or, for the faint of heart,
we have...
pow...
a virtual reality alternative.
Both set to include
particle vision.
- Particle... vision?
- Particle vision, which is
a moment-to-moment reenactment
of the particle accelerator
explosion,
but seen from
the point of view of...
- Part...
- The particle!
- Listen, H.R., I know
that you're trying to figure out
how you add value to the team,
I get it, but this...
- Let me stop you
right there, B.A.
- Okay, don't call me B.A...
- I can make S.T.A.R. Labs
the powerhouse in the
scientific community
that it once was,
and, moreover,
earn back the people's trust.
Look at you guys.
You just...
your faces are so darn gloomy.
Here's what we'll do.
I'm gonna make you guys a...
[klaxons blaring]
- Was that... was
that the satellite?
I hope that wasn't
the satellite.
- Is that a meteor?
- Why, yes, that is a meteor,
and yes,
it is heading for downtown.
♪ ♪
- I got to go.
Guys.
[static cracks]
-What is it?
Barry, what do you see?
- This isn't a meteor.
-Barry?
Hey, Barry, come in.
Can you hear me?
- Guys?
♪ ♪
[Dominators growling]
Oh, come on.
Aliens!
- Government officials
are reporting
the mysterious object
that crashed
in downtown Central City
was simply a DOD aircraft
on a routine training operation.
- Thank you,
but we'll brief the White House.
- You're not listening to me
about this.
The intelligence we've gathered
at A.R.G.U.S...
- Is not accurate.
We've got this covered,
Director Michaels.
Go back to Star City.
Let the big guns take over.
- Lyla, what is this?
I saw the weird ship
that crashed...
- You saw a ship?
What else did you see?
- Enough to give
Ridley Scott nightmares.
♪ ♪
- Meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'll tell you everything I know.
- Aliens?
Are they "Alien" aliens
or little green men?
- Both, sort of.
- Since we learned of them,
we've been calling them
the Dominators.
- That is not the name
of a species
that comes in peace.
- No, no, it's very aggressive.
- So how long have you known
about these Dominators?
- Since the '50s.
- That was them.
Redmond, Oregon.
The government tried
to cover it up.
What?
I watch Syfy channel.
- In 1951, they appeared under
the same sort of circumstances.
A ship crash-landed.
Little to no communication.
We learned
they were abducting humans
to gather intel about us.
They attacked, and hundreds
of soldiers lost their lives.
Then, for some
inexplicable reason, they left.
All contact had been lost
until three months ago
when the DOD received this.
- We pose no threat,
human inhabitants.
Understanding is our purpose.
Any action against us,
as shown to us in the past,
will prompt swift retaliation.
- So when we discovered four
ships heading towards Earth,
we were concerned that it was
happening all over again.
One of them, obviously,
landed here.
- Right, 'cause we ain't got
enough crazy going on here
in Central City.
- Do you know what they want?
- They've ignored all attempts
to communicate,
but we do know,
just like before,
that the dropships contain
reconnaissance teams
sent here
to gather more intel about us.
- Looking for our weaknesses.
- We need to do something.
- We are.
Nearly every member state
in the UN is in talks
to coordinate a response.
Action is being taken.
- So, wait, you want us
to just sit this one out?
- These things
are like "World War Z" zombies.
If they decide to attack,
no military can stop them.
- Neither could you.
Not by yourself, anyway.
Just let us handle this.
For now.
I'll be in touch.
- So the plan isn't
to just stay still
and do nothing, right?
- No.
- Barry, you heard Lyla.
You can't do this alone.
- I don't plan to.
♪ ♪
- Anything?
- Zilch.
- He's got to be here somewhere.
- What are the chances
the guy just decided
that he had enough
of this life, you know?
No health insurance.
He was sick
of the crazy hours.
I mean, bullets aren't actually
that cheap, and he...
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, man. I...
- It's okay.
[vomits]
Man...
Hey.
- Hi, Barry.
- So, who was that guy?
- That was Vigilante,
and we nearly had him.
- You nearly had him, Ollie?
It looked like he was about
to "Scarface" you guys.
- Barry, is there something
that I can do for you?
Another evil speedster
to help you with or...
- Maybe, actually.
That's not why I'm here, though.
- What's so urgent that
you had to rush to Star City?
- Aliens.
- Aliens?
- I swear to God, Barry.
My life was somewhat normal
before I met you.
- I...
I mean, I'm sorry.
Look, okay, they're real,
and they're already here,
and, from what Lyla told us,
it does not appear to be
for peace.
- Oh, no.
- Lyla knows about this?
- Lyla...
yeah, she came to...
where are you...
- I called Thea.
- Yeah, I came
to have you sign this
before City Council
went in to mutiny,
but that can totally wait.
Count me in.
- For what?
I thought you retired.
- Yeah, but it's...
it's aliens.
- Aw, that is so cute.
You guys are just
gonna get together
and go fight some aliens...
have you lost your mind?
They're aliens,
and there's only four of you.
- Not if we get Stein
and, you know, all the others.
- They're calling themselves
the Legends.
- Egotistical but catchy.
- Do you know where they are?
- I know where they were.
- What is this place?
- It's this old hall hangar
thing that S.T.A.R. Labs owns.
Or I guess I own it.
- Well, you should do
something with it.
- All right, so let
me get this right.
Our time-traveling buddies
in a flying timeship
are supposed to just pop up
right here, right?
- Yeah. This is the time
and place I gave them,
so if they got my message,
they should be here...
♪ ♪
Right now.
- You know why
I've never done drugs?
It's 'cause I was always afraid
I'd see weird stuff.
- Okay, take everybody inside,
all right?
Tell Oliver I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- Well,
since we're fighting aliens,
I figured we should get
one of our own, right?
You found the right Earth?
- Tachyon device tracked you
on Earth-38 when you met her,
so you should find her there.
- All right.
- Just so you know,
I'm only doing this
because we're on a mission.
I'm not gonna let my issues
with you get in the way of that.
This might take a few tries.
♪ ♪
This better be the right place.
'Cause if this isn't
the right place,
someone's about to be
real confused.
- Barry?
- Hey.
- I knew it!
I knew that was you.
I knew it was you
in that weird space...
- Sorry, it took a couple tries
to get here.
This is my friend, Cisco.
- Well, friend is a loose term.
We work together.
Hi. Cisco.
I have to say it...
this is a nice universe
you got here.
- Thank you.
- Okay, do you remember
last year
when I helped you out
and you promised
to do the same for me?
- What are we up against?
♪ ♪
- Team Arrow is here.
Team Legends is here.
Is that everyone?
- I think so?
- Nate and Amaya are back
watching the Waverider.
The newbies.
- That was cool.
- Guys.
Thanks for coming.
- Barry, I thought
you were bringing an alien.
- And, yeah, we did.
Everybody, this is
my friend, Kara Danvers,
or, as she's known
on her Earth, Supergirl.
- What makes her so super?
- Well?
- I'm convinced.
- Best. Team-up. Ever!
♪ ♪
[Dominators speaking
alien language]
- Okay. I think I have this.
Oliver.
- Green Arrow.
- Dig.
- Spartan.
- Thea.
- Speedy.
- Okay.
And Sara.
- White Canary.
- Jax and Professor Stein.
both: Firestorm.
- Ray.
- Palmer. The Atom.
- And Mick.
- Hmm?
Oh. Heat Wave.
- And Iris, Caitlin,
and Felicity.
- Whoo!
- Yes!
And you have cold powers,
but you can't use them?
- You have powers?
- It's a long story.
- Barry, so, Oliver Queen
is the Green Arrow?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
He just got so much hotter.
- Okay, Cisco,
we should probably get started.
- Okay.
These are the Dominators.
We don't know much about them.
- Except they're really strong.
I heard a lot of stories
about them when I was a kid.
They came to my planet
before I was born.
They did experiments
on a lot of people.
Killed a lot more.
- Well, they're
not the only ones
with superhuman strength,
I hear.
Barry says that you're more
powerful than a locomotive.
- We should use Kara
as a stand-in for training.
- Since when is Robin Hood
calling the shots?
- What I think
Mick is trying to say
is it would be nice if we knew
who was in charge around here.
- Maybe we should take a vote.
Choose a leader.
Someone we can all trust.
- Well, I trust Oliver.
He's got my vote.
- Appreciate that, Cisco,
but Barry put us all together.
It should be him.
- Fair enough.
- Okay.
Cool, all right, well,
I guess as Team Leader,
first thing to do
is start out by...
- Doing a test run.
- Let's do a test run.
Yeah, let's do a test run.
- Against Supergirl.
- Against Supergirl, all right?
Test run against Supergirl.
- Are we
just supposed to pretend
like we don't hear him?
- So just suit up.
Mm-kay? Look alive.
We're training to fight aliens
by fighting an alien, so...
- Do it.
- Suit up.
- Stop.
- What?
- Oliver. Hey. Kara.
Really quick.
I was excited about the two
of you guys meeting each other.
Oliver was the first person
to train me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, you did
a really good job.
- It's 'cause
I didn't hold back.
I shot him.
You can't hold back either.
- He did shoot me.
- Ouch.
Okay, are you sure about that?
I just met these people...
- These people need
to understand
this isn't gonna be easy.
Don't hold back.
Especially against me.
- Yes, sir.
Wow.
Does he not like me?
- He's like that with everyone.
He'll warm up to you.
- Old West Dwarf Star
plus Replicator,
equals new suit.
- You know what, Ray?
Maybe it's just me, but I think
this thing's due for an update.
- Ha. Yes.
But after we dominate
the Dominators.
- Oh! I see what you did there.
- [chuckles]
- Hey.
- Listen.
I got to get to work.
Felicity's waiting for me.
But we'll talk about this later.
- Hey, Barry.
- Where's Snart?
- Man, I'm sorry, Barry.
I forgot that we never told you.
- What happened?
- He sacrificed himself.
Saved us all.
He died a hero.
- A Legend.
- Wally,
what are you doing here?
You can't just show up and think
you're gonna train
with everyone else.
- Why not?
- Because we need
to test you more.
- H.R. said that
my results were great.
He said I'm good to go.
- I don't care what H.R. said.
You are not ready.
- I am ready.
- Wally.
Everyone here
has been doing this
for a long time,
and this is gonna be
the hardest challenge
they have faced.
Fighting Alchemy
or Savitar or aliens
isn't something
you just show up and try.
If you screw up, you could die.
Do you...
do you get that?
Great.
- Satellite's not picking up
anything abnormal.
- No.
- I don't know if we're gonna
find any Dominators this way.
- Hey, I...just,
I couldn't help but notice
things are a little bit tense.
You don't need to be able
to Vibe to figure that out.
- Okay, so apparently,
it's, like, illegal
to be mad at Barry,
but guess what.
He screws up,
just like the rest of us.
- Yeah, and when he does,
he feels bad
like the rest of us too.
- Felicity, he took
it upon himself
to change the timeline.
And because of it,
my brother was killed.
So there's no amount
of feeling bad
that could ever
make up for that.
- Barry.
Before we start training,
there's something
you need to hear.
- A message that would be better
if we could share with you
in private.
- All right, I'll step away.
- No, no, it's fine.
You can stay.
- All right, but no one else.
- All right.
Let's make it quick.
♪ ♪
A war is coming,
Captain Hunter,
and at some point
you're gonna be called back
to Central City to fight it.
So you need to know that,
while you and your team
have been in the temporal zone,
I made a choice
that affected the timeline.
As you know,
whenever you alter the past,
those changes affect
the present
and get compounded
in the future.
When you return, you will be
in the new timeline I created,
where everyone's past
and everyone's future
has been affected,
including yours.
When you come back,
don't trust anything or anyone.
Not even me.
Where did you get that from?
- We found it in a secret room
inside the Waverider.
It was sent by you,
40 years from now.
-40 years from now?
Barry, what the hell
does this mean?
- It means I screwed things up
when I changed the past.
- What did you do?
- I went back in time,
and I saved my mom.
I created a timeline
where she's alive.
It's called Flashpoint.
I lived in it for a few months,
until I realized that
I made a big mistake,
and I tried
to reset the timeline,
put things back
to how they were supposed to be,
but...
- But it didn't work.
- No.
- Wow.
Barry, that's...
- So what's changed
since you did this?
- Cisco's brother is dead.
Caitlin has powers.
Diggle has a son now
instead of a daughter.
- What? John had a daughter?
- I didn't just screw up
my life, man.
I screwed up everybody's lives
and, apparently,
everybody's lives in the future.
It felt like,
when these aliens got here,
that finally something
had happened I didn't cause,
and maybe I could make up
for everything I'd done
to everybody, but I...
- I think we should be
on the up and up with everybody.
We got to tell 'em.
- We're going up
against a bunch of aliens,
and you want to tell people
that their lives might have been
affected by time travel?
One sci-fi problem at a time.
You made a mistake, Barry.
It's part of the job.
But we can't
deal with it today.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Professor Stein, are you okay?
- I'm not sure.
Ms. Snow, would you mind
accompanying me to my home?
There's something I need to do.
- Sure.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
[all groaning]
- She really is a badass.
- Yeah, it's kind of hot.
- Let's go again.
♪ ♪
- So this is, what, your way
of advising me to do nothing?
- The Dominators
have yet to engage
in an act of aggression, sir.
- What does A.R.G.U.S. think?
- I think us being passive
is exactly what they want,
Mr. President.
- Well, finally,
someone here with balls.
Ike ignored all the signs and
waited until it was too late.
I'm not gonna make
that same mistake.
- You saw what happened
the last time we engaged them.
That's a lot of casualties
to be remembered for.
- Four dropships landed
on this planet,
all of them sent
to gather intel.
If we do nothing
and they attack,
that's what I'll be
remembered for.
Proceed as instructed.
♪ ♪
- You know, Director Michaels,
the reason that Amanda Waller
lasted as long as she did
is because she learned
how to follow my lead.
I suggest that
you acquire that trait.
Soon.
♪ ♪
[overlapping chatter]
- He's gone.
♪ ♪
- Traveller has been taken.
I repeat,
Traveller has been taken.
The Dominators have
the President.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, son.
- I don't understand, Dad.
No one in this family
wants me to have powers.
You don't.
Barry doesn't.
Even Iris.
According to this,
everything's fine with me.
In fact, everything
is better than fine.
What, did you run back
to make sure I didn't see these?
I'm faster than you now,
remember?
Whether you or Barry or anyone
likes it or not.
- Wally, look.
I know you're upset with me.
I was just trying
to protect you.
- Come on. I know
you don't want me training.
I just don't get why.
Because I'm better than Barry
was when he first got his speed.
You know, in Flashpoint,
you and I were a brother-sister
crime-fighting unit.
So it sucks you don't have
the same faith in me here
as you did there.
- Brother and sister
crime-fighting unit?
Hi, there, Wallace.
I came back to
get some lip balm.
- It's okay.
You seem to be the only one
that'll tell me the truth
around here.
- Me?
- We're kind of treated
the same way, right?
No one shows us any respect.
- Respect, I'm just trying
to earn that, Wallace.
- Maybe we should stop
listening to them.
- Yeah, what?
What does that mean?
- It means
I want you to train me.
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- I would be gone faster than
humor in a Liam Neeson movie.
Do you know what I mean?
- No.
- Yeah.
- Not if they don't find out.
- Wallace.
- Come on, no one's
gonna do this for me.
I want to make
a difference, H.R.
I'm never gonna be able to
if I don't know
how to use my powers.
Please. I want to help people,
same as you do.
So show me how.
- Nah.
- Thank you
for joining me, my dear.
- Of course. I wasn't being
much help back there anyway.
- You know, having powers
isn't exactly a death sentence,
no matter who
your doppelganger is.
- I attacked my friends...
my best friends...
and said horrible,
horrible things to them.
- But that wasn't you.
And believe me, as a person
who sometimes shares a body
with another human being,
I know the difference,
and so do your friends.
- I'm just so scared.
What if she comes back
and I can't keep her out?
Then what?
- We'll all be there for you.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Are you okay?
- You're back!
- I'm sorry.
I was looking for my wife.
- Very funny.
She's not here.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
I missed you so much.
- Did you?
- Of course.
I love you, Dad.
- I love you too.
- [laughs]
- But I'm sorry.
We have to go.
Please...
- Oh.
- Tell your mother
I'll see her soon.
- Professor Stein?
- We have to leave now.
- Where are you?
[device beeps]
- A war is coming,
Captain Hunter...
- Are you sure you want me
to keep going?
- Yeah. Yes.
Just give us five minutes.
Please.
- Hey.
- You know what this is?
This is really you.
Like, future you.
- Come on, look...
- You told 'em, right?
- I'm gonna tell them, yeah,
when this is finished.
- When this is finished?
Even though you're about to
lead them through an alien war?
Even after Flashpoint?
After everything
you've messed up?
All the lives you've changed?
Youstill don't think
you should tell them?
- Tell us what?
- Jax and Professor Stein found
a message from me in the future
saying that, right now,
I can't be trusted.
- And why would future you
say that?
- I think because I went back in
time and changed the timeline,
and now things here are
different than before I left,
including some of your lives.
- Some of our lives?
Like who?
- Cisco.
Caitlin. Wally.
Dig.
- Me?
Why? What happened?
- Hey.
Apparently, you had a daughter.
♪ ♪
- I had a daughter, Barry?
- Baby John was Baby Sara.
So, wait, you...
let me get this straight.
You just, uh...
You just erased a daughter
from my life?
- Yeah.
- You can't go back
and just change things
like that, Barry.
- I know.
- You know how hard it is
for me to not alter events?
To bring my sister back?
But I don't,
because I know the implications.
- And all those aberrations
we spent the
last eight months
traveling through time
trying to correct...
you just decided that it was
okay for you to create your own?
- We should've told 'em before.
[cell phone chimes]
- Guys? Guys, it's Lyla.
The President's been abducted
by the Dominators.
She needs us now.
- Okay, you guys go.
All right, I'm gonna
sit this one out.
Obviously, you have Supergirl.
She's just as fast as I am.
Get the President, we can
talk about this later.
You still trust me, right?
- I'll always trust you,
but it might take more
to convince them.
- If you need me,
I'll be there.
- Guys, this is cr...hey!
This is crazy!
Everyone is going,
including Barry.
I...
I'm not going without him.
- Then you'll be here, Oliver.
- Okay.
You know what?
Oliver, it's okay.
I will go with them.
We'll get the President.
You stay here with Barry.
- Sure we're in the right place?
♪ ♪
- Well, this is the last place
the President's tracer
gave a signal.
Must be nearby.
Yep.
He's in there.
- How do you know that?
- I can see him.
Oh, I have X-ray vision.
- Oh.
You can see everyone's bits
with those little peepers, huh?
- No, I...
- Ignore him.
- How did you get
the name Heat Wave?
- I burned my family alive,
and I like to light things
on fire.
- Aah. Well, that's
a colorful backstory.
- Well, my shrink thinks so.
By the way, I'm not gonna
call you Supergirl.
It's stupid.
- You could call me Kara.
- That won't work either.
- Well, what're you gonna shout
if you need my help?
- Skirt.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
But I'm not gonna need
your help.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- Look! The President!
- Get me out of here!
- This doesn't feel right.
- I agree, Jefferson.
- Something's coming.
- Release the President!
- We knew you would come.
- Did you guys hear that?
'Cause I heard it in my head.
- Yeah, we heard it.
- Well, if nobody else
is freaked out by it,
far be it for me to panic.
- You don't need to harm him
to get whatever it is
you want from us.
Release him and nothing
will happen to you.
- He's not who we want.
- It's a trap!
[orb whistling]
[all groaning]
- Supergirl, do something!
- I didn't think about it,
Oliver.
I didn't think about the future.
I was so focused on the past,
I didn't think about it
until now.
I changed so much.
- What is this?
- This is an article
from the future.
It's a story
about me vanishing.
Used to be written
by Iris West-Allen.
But now, I don't know.
Something's...
something's changed with Iris.
Something's changed
with our future.
God, what did I do?
- Barry, this is a weird-looking
newspaper article.
It doesn't mean anything.
You need to stop
beating yourself up over this.
- I'm sorry,
but how can you say that?
I'm responsible for all of this.
- Maybe. Maybe not.
Barry, you made a choice.
You wanted to see
your parents alive again.
Do you honestly know
anyone that,
if they were in your shoes,
wouldn't do
the same exact thing?
I would do
the exact same thing.
Barry, after theGambit
went down,
it was me, my father,
and a crewmember on a life raft.
Lost at sea.
Enough food and water
for one person, maybe.
My father took a gun,
shot the crewmember,
told me to survive,
and then turned the gun
on himself.
He shot himself in the head.
He sacrificed himself
so that I could live.
Nothing I could do.
No choice.
Slade Wilson drove a sword
right through my mother's heart,
in front of my sister and I.
I was there.
I was helpless on the ground.
I was powerless to stop it.
No choice.
Do you not think
that I wouldn't give anything
to go back
and to make things different?
- You never told me that.
- Barry,
the world isn't different
because you changed
the timeline.
Change happens.
Tragedy happens.
People make choices,
and those choices affect
everyone else.
You're not a god, Barry.
[building rumbles]
- Hey, guys, wherever
you are right now, we need you.
- Oh, things just got
so much worse.
♪ ♪
Guys.
Can we talk about this?
- Guess not.
- What's wrong with them?
- I don't know,
but we need to find out.
Okay!
You really did it this time!
- Seriously?
- Yeah, seriously.
- What's that?
- That would be heat vision.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What is going on?
- Barry and Oliver
stayed behind
while everyone went
to go save the President,
but now everyone's crazy
and going all "Kill Bill"
on the both of them.
- The Dominators have them under
some sort of mind control.
- They can't hold them off
forever.
- I got to get out there.
- The hell you do.
- They can't beat them
by themselves,
especially not with Supergirl
against them.
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
Wally?
- Kid Flash.
- Wally? Wally?
Talk to me, Wally.
Hey! Come on.
Guys. Wally's hurt bad,
but he's alive.
- Let's get an ETA
on overriding the mind control!
- Bingo!
- Yahtzee!
- You go first.
You go first.
It's your office.
- There's a weird signal coming
from the salt mines.
- For the record,
thatis what I was gonna say.
- Can you jam it?
- Uh, no.
- How many of those
do you have left?
- Probably not enough.
- Okay, this hallway leads
to a bunker under the building.
Just hold 'em off
as long as you can.
- Where are you going?
- If they can't shut it down,
maybe she can.
Hey, Supergirl!
Let's finally see who's faster.
♪ ♪
[groans]
Too slow.
- What is he doing?
- He's making her angry.
- But he knows
Supergirl is invincible.
- Think maybe that's the point.
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
Barry?
- [groans]
♪ ♪
- Guys, they're back.
- What happened?
- You didn't kill me,
so my day's looking up.
- I'm so sorry.
- Hey, you're not the first
superhero to be mind-controlled.
- Okay, I know
what you're gonna say,
but I had to do something.
- I'm glad you're okay.
Don't ever do that again.
- Aah!
- Sorry. Not sorry.
- Come on.
Let's get you checked out.
And then we can talk about
how dumb that was.
- Okay.
- Okay what?
- They don't see your potential.
I do.
One of my many gifts.
You want to train?
I'll train you.
- So, what was it like being
all mind-controlled and stuff?
- I didn't realize he had
a mind to be controlled.
- Barry, about before.
Message or no message,
we're with you.
- Thank you.
- Where's Supergirl?
- Scanning the city
to make sure there aren't
any more of the orbs
that whammied all of you.
- Okay, so now what?
- We call Lyla.
Tell her these Dominators
aren't here peacefully.
Sara!
♪ ♪
- Everybody inside! Go!
- Greg, move your head.