I thought we had a truce.
- I thought as much.
Your bravery is strengthened
by the reassurance you gain
from enhanced healing.
- It doesn't mean it hurts
any less.
- Pain is the debt we pay
for change,
and I'm here to change
the future.
Thanks to this experiment,
I now know the force required
to kill you
when the time comes.
- Oh.
- I've seen
your destiny, Flash.
I've watched you use your power
to destroy everything
and everyone.
- You still haven't told me
why I would do this.
Huh?
What would cause me
to turn my back on everything
I've sworn to protect?
- Madness.
Many times in the past,
the pain you've suffered
nearly crushed you.
But soon, a new despair
will befall you.
And it will create
an unbroken chain of sorrow
so great...
your mind will crack.
And with it, the world ends.
You see...
your power has
recently accelerated.
But so too has your ability
to descend into madness.
Tragedy is coming for you,
Flash.
What remains to be seen isn't
whether or not you'll break.
It's when.
- I have seven days.
- I'd worry more
about tomorrow
if I were you.
I don't know the details
of what will happen.
But I know tomorrow is
the beginning of the end.
Your end.
I've granted you a chance
to defy destiny.
But I'll be staying close by.
As soon as I sense
your mind turning mad,
I'll find you.
Good luck fighting fate, Flash.
♪
I'll be watching.
- Okay, uplink to the Tower
mainframe is secure.
You now have access
to our alien database
including any intel we have
on this "Despero."
- We appreciate you helping,
Alex.
- How long will it take
to download?
- Well, this new algorithm
works at light speed.
In fact, Caitlin,
that guy Marcus
that I connected you with,
he designed it.
- Well, if the world's
still here in a week,
I'll be sure
and give him a call.
- Oh, I'm sorry, guys.
I'll keep digging and see
what I can find out.
But if this Despero
has managed to stay off
of our grid,
then he is a greater threat
than any alien we've faced.
Keep your guard up.
- Well, you heard her.
We have to protect Barry.
There's no way he would
destroy the world.
- What if he's right?
I mean, look, we all saw
how a massive boost of speed
affected Barry before.
- Oh, crap, you're right.
Remember the ASF?
He gained speed-thinking,
but as a result...
- I turned on the people
I love.
Look, I--that's not gonna
happen this time.
- But Barr, what if you just
leveled up too much, too fast?
- Barry isn't a threat to us.
Despero is.
And his story doesn't add up.
I mean, come on,
doesn't anyone else think
it's weird that an alien cares
so much about Earth?
He's not even from here.
- Wherever he's from,
here's what we know.
I ran a bio-scan on Despero
the minute he entered
S.T.A.R. Labs.
His anatomy is unlike anything
I ever studied before.
He has strength
and invulnerability
that rivals Kryptonians.
How are we gonna stop him
from killing you?
- Prove him wrong.
Despero says tomorrow,
my mind starts to break.
So all we have to do is make it
through the next 24 hours
without that happening,
and he'll have to back down.
- I like that plan.
- Let's get some rest.
Tomorrow, we'll need to be
on the lookout for anything,
and if something does happen,
then we need to be ready
to stop it.
Protecting this city is still
our top priority.
- Even from you?
- It won't come to that.
I promise.
- These are the bio-scans
Caity did on Despero's brain.
- Study them, and let's
figure out a way to stop him.
- Oh, I heard that.
I was already planning
on pulling an all-nighter.
You know, I was thinking,
maybe we can find a way
to restrain him or--
- I'm not talking
about restraining him.
- Look, we need to level up
our offense.
And I'm not talking about
some containment unit
like we did with Bloodwork
or taking out his lair
with an EMP.
We need to hit him.
Hard.
- You're--you're asking me
to build a weapon.
Frost... I've never
built something
to hurt someone before.
♪
- Think of it this way.
You're gonna help save
Barry's life.
Whatever it takes.
♪
- Couldn't sleep either?
Something bad's supposed
to happen today.
All I keep thinking about
is you.
- I'll be fine.
- We can't take any chances.
- I promise, I have a very safe
and boring day planned.
Cecile's working on a big case,
so after some work,
I'm gonna stop by and help her
with Jenna.
They both have been having
a pretty hard time lately.
♪
- Iris, if anything happens
to you...
- Hey.
Baby, we're gonna be okay.
♪
Look, how many times
and how many timelines
have we found each other?
Doesn't matter what anybody
says about your fate.
Our destiny is to be together.
♪
- CCPD.
- Allen, just in time.
- How bad is it?
- Just your typical
makes-no-sense bank robbery
in Central City.
No one's hurt,
but the on-duty security guard
is being hospitalized
for some sort of breakdown.
- Wait,
like a mental breakdown?
- Yeah, witnesses said
the guy lost his mind
and started babbling nonsense.
♪
Then he fired his weapon
into the air,
and everyone ran out.
By the time
anyone got back inside,
the vault was empty,
and the guard was
stark raving mad.
It took four officers
to restrain him.
- I'm on it.
- Allen!
I need you to stand down.
- Why, is Gibson working
the case?
I'll just help him investigate.
- I need you
to turn in your badge.
You've been suspended.
- What?
- I just came
from the mayor's office.
You're under investigation
for federal crimes.
Your badge, Allen.
Now.
♪
- You're under investigation
for federal crimes.
Your badge, Allen.
♪
- Allen, I know
this must be a shock.
- Captain, hold on.
What am I supposed
to have done?
- Two years ago,
Joseph Carver had a mole
manipulating evidence in CCPD.
- Yeah, Milly Rawlins,
aka Sunshine.
We caught her.
- And the DA was reviewing
her case
as a part of an internal audit.
Now, I don't know what exactly,
but he also found new evidence
that points to Carver having
a second inside man.
You.
-
That's crazy.
I mean, why would I help
Joseph Carver?
- That's for the DA
to suss out.
I'm sorry,
it's above my pay grade.
Now, please leave the scene.
- I have to find out
what happened here.
- I mean, I think you'd have
other concerns right now.
- I just... I mean, Korber said
a guard lost his mind.
What if that happens
to somebody else?
People could get hurt.
Look, Captain, I know
you only have my word,
but you--you gotta believe me.
I'm innocent.
So please,
just let me do my job.
- If Joe were here right now,
he'd say I should learn
from last year
and keep an open mind.
♪
Which is why I promise you,
I will get
to the bottom of this
and find out the truth.
But until I do, I'm sorry.
Allen, you have to leave.
♪
- This is insane.
Your CCPD record is stellar.
Everyone knows that Rawlins was
nothing but Carver's lackey.
- Can you find out what
evidence they have against me?
- Oh, Barry, I'm gonna do
a hell of a lot more than that.
I am about to slap CCPD
with the biggest wrongful
termination lawsuit
this city has ever seen.
I am gonna bleed them dry
for doing this to you.
- Are you feeling all right?
No.
I'm sorry.
It--it's just been...
hard lately.
I mean...you know why.
- What's wrong?
- We're not alone in here.
I can feel another presence
in this room.
♪
- Why are you here?
-
I'm not.
This is a physic manifestation
of my consciousness.
Appearing only to you
in order to assess
your mental stability.
- Barry?
Who are you talking to?
♪
- There's nothing wrong
with my mind.
- It's him, isn't it?
Despero?
- Your mind is suffering
due to this tragedy.
But no...
it hasn't broken.
Yet.
♪
His energy.
His energy, it felt like...
the whole room was flooded,
and we were both drowning.
- Despero's watching me now.
Waiting for the proof he needs
to kill me.
- Are you sure he's not
what drives you insane?
- No, I'm not.
But I do think
there's another explanation
for what's happening.
Korber said a security guard
at this morning's robbery
lost his mind.
- That can't be a coincidence.
Not today.
- No, it has to be connected
to what Despero said happens
in the future.
I need to talk to that guard.
♪
Xotar.
Xotar!
- Caitlin, hey. Good timing.
I think I've got a clue
to run though the S.T.A.R.
Labs' search satellites.
- Barry, we need you here
right now.
The city is shutting down
S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Okay, lock this place down!
I want
that radiation leak found.
- Get here. Fast.
-
Xotar. Xotar.
Xotar.
- You can't just
come in here and kick us
out of our own offices.
Public Safety Act?
- Passed four years ago
after the meta fallout
nearly took out the city.
Means we can do
whatever we have to do
for the greater good.
Post teams at every entrance.
No one gets in
without clearance.
- Right away, sir.
- Excuse me, I'm Barry Allen.
I own this facility.
- Mr. Allen, we've detected
dangerous levels of radiation
within your facility.
This lab's a day away
from a meltdown.
- That's impossible.
We would've noticed
if things were that bad.
- Uh, maybe not.
I just checked out
the safety logs.
Our radiation scanners haven't
updated in over a week.
Doesn't make...any sense.
- What happened?
- This is part
of our early detection array
that monitors radiation levels
inside the place,
but it's corroded.
Hasn't been functioning
for a while.
Sensors in the subterranean
power core
currently read over 1,000 RADS.
- Consider yourselves lucky.
Another day,
you'd all be in ICU.
Seal off that power core!
And get an external
containment team STAT.
- What kind of containment?
- We need to construct
a concrete
and steel encasement
around this entire facility
in order to contain
the radioactive material.
Then we'll demolish
S.T.A.R. Labs
and move the debris
to a nuclear waste site.
- You're gonna demolish it?
- The safety board makes
the final call.
But this looks pretty bad.
Now gather your people
and say goodbye.
You got five minutes to make
like a banana and split.
Fan out and search all levels
for additional leaks.
Excuse me.
♪
-
Okay.
This place is already swarming
with city workers.
If they get
to the inner levels...
- They'll find out
it's Flash HQ.
- Aka our home base.
- That's why I need you
to grab what you're able to,
conceal the labs'
critical areas,
and get out as fast as you can.
♪
- Hello, Barry Allen.
- Gideon, can you pull up
the controls
for the holographic emitters,
then set them to manual?
- Understood.
Preparing task.
- What do you need, Chester P?
♪
Where are you?
Yes.
- Instruction set received.
Holographic emitters
reconfigured.
- Initiate.
♪
- Must be old plans.
- All clear.
- Okay, let's head back.
♪
- Sequence complete.
However, Team Flash data
on internal servers
will compromise your identity
if discovered.
Standing by
for emergency data wipe.
- Gideon, is there
any other way?
- No, Barry Allen.
All information
within S.T.A.R. Labs
must be erased in order
to assure your safety.
This includes myself.
This is the best option.
- I'm so sorry, Gideon.
- It has been an honor
working with you, Barry Allen.
Farewell.
♪
It has been an honor
working with you, Barry Allen.
Farewell.
♪
- Frost ice-bridged
a bunch of stuff out of here.
She's gonna bring it
to Caitlin's.
- Okay, it's time to go.
-
I can't believe
this is happening.
- This was our home.
♪
- This--this is so unreal.
- I spent more time in that lab
than anywhere I've ever lived.
- Guys, I know how much
this hurts.
And I know
what you're thinking.
But these setbacks aren't proof
that Despero's right
about the future.
- They're not proof
he isn't, either.
- I know, but hey,
we gotta have faith.
Not just in me,
but in each other.
♪
- Barry, we're with you.
I think we all just wish
that there was some
other explanation for all this.
- I think there is.
Something caused
a security guard
to lose his mind
at a bank robbery this morning.
- Uh, you mean exactly like
what Despero said
would happen to you?
- This has to be related.
- I was gonna use
the S.T.A.R. Labs satellites
to follow a lead.
Luckily, we have someone
on our team who is an expert
at exposing the truth.
♪
- The Xotar story
is priority one.
Okay, the word's out.
If there's anything
to this "Xotar" lead,
my people will find it.
- Despero said I'm gonna
destroy the world.
If that's true...
I'm the reason
everyone I love is gonna die.
- Barry, do you remember
the last time
that something messed
with your head?
When you had speed-thinking?
- It was like
I was on autopilot.
My mind just took over.
Yeah, but you snapped
out of it.
'Cause you saw that
your friends were in danger.
I mean, you could never
really hurt us.
- Even so, if something does
happen to someone I love,
because of my
leveled-up speed...
I don't know how I'd react.
- It's Taylor.
She found out that Xotar is
the name of a meta-criminal
in National City.
- Xotar's a meta?
- A psychic meta
who controls her victim's minds
and drives them...crazy.
You know what this means?
- Xotar could be
the real reason
I lose my mind today.
- And catching her
will prevent it.
- All I have to do is find her.
♪
Xotar.
-
Flash, you found me.
- Yes.
- Let me guess.
You're psychic too?
- Not psychic, just patient.
I knew if I ran around the city
long enough,
eventually you'd show yourself.
- How very underwhelming
and basic of you.
So what's next?
We fight?
How passé.
- Actually, what do you say
we take a quick trip
to Iron Heights?
♪
- What the hell is wrong
with you?
- What's going on?
- You--you zooped in
outta nowhere
and started destroying
the place.
- What? No, I--
- You almost
lightning-blasted Chuck.
♪
- I--
I don't remember doing
any of that.
♪
- Okay, listen, I--
I don't know
what just happened,
but I--I didn't do this.
And I'm not going insane.
- Barry, we saw you!
- No way, I--
- Dude, she's right.
You came in here all
lathered up, out of control.
Allegra had to blast you, man.
- Okay.
All right, look,
whatever happened,
I can prove I'm myself now.
Or at least Caitlin can.
♪
- Cover me.
Your amygdala activity
and cortisol levels
are elevated.
But...
within normal parameters.
♪
- Well, even if you're
really you again,
it doesn't explain
what just happened.
- No, I know
who's responsible for this.
Right before it happened,
I intercepted
a meta called Xotar.
She controls
her victims' minds.
What are the odds
a meta who commits
telepathic assaults on people
shows up
the same day Despero claims
I'm gonna lose my mind?
- Well, that does make
a lot more sense.
- Okay, we need to find Xotar
and stop this from happening.
- And keep Despero
from killing you.
- Back at S.T.A.R. Labs,
we could scan
for Xotar's energy signature
and find her,
but without satellites,
we're blind.
- I can search the city.
I found her once,
I can find her again.
- Frost needs help
setting up a portable med lab
at the apartment.
- Oh, me and Allegra can set up
- a comms/
- Cortex-type sitch
in my garage.
- All right, do it.
And, look, guys,
I--I know today...
started with a loss,
but we can end it with a win.
We got this.
♪
- Sorry.
It's all right. It's all right.
- Search for Xotar
all you want.
But the answer
you're looking for
has been with you all along.
- Enough!
No more cryptic prophecies,
no more games.
Why do you care so much?
You said yourself,
this isn't your world.
You're hiding something
from me.
What do you have to gain?
- A home.
♪
I saw my planet, Kalanor,
overrun by evil.
I was forced to see the people
I love suffer and die
under the fist of a despot.
Then I was chosen to lead
a band of rebels,
attempting a coup.
Both sides suffered
heavy losses.
But we were triumphant.
However, when the time came
to cut the head
off the snake...
I chose to spare
the oppressor's life.
♪
But my mercy was misguided.
Because it allowed that madman
to rise again
and rain down horrors
a thousand times worse.
♪
I was spared.
Because he knew for me,
the only fate worse than death
would be losing my home world.
♪
So he banished me here.
That's how I came to adopt
Earth as my new home.
Only to watch you destroy it.
- I've been through
a crisis before.
Whatever's coming,
I can handle it.
- Crisis and tragedy
are like fires, Flash.
Some are strong enough
to endure them.
But others are destined
to be consumed by them.
♪
Soon we'll find out
who you are.
♪
- Okay.
This is the last of your...
whatever this stuff is.
What's this thing?
- Uh, nothing.
Yeah, no, it's just
a--a project...for Frost.
That's all.
- Uh-huh.
Chuck, you know how we've been
spending more time
together lately?
- Oh, yeah,
our weekend D&D sessions are,
like, my new favorite thing.
Why?
- Well...and I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but the way you just said
"nothing"...
is exactly how you sounded
right before the raid
on Shavak's Tomb.
-
- And we all knew
you were bluffing then too.
- Yeah, okay.
Uh...
Frost asked me to build...
a weapon.
To hurt Despero.
- But you're...
- A pacifist.
Yeah, I know.
- How do you feel
about doing this?
- Allegra...
you know I still remember
the exact moment
that I decided
to be a pacifist?
I was ten.
And I had just seen
Marvin the Martian's ray gun
on Saturday morning cartoons.
♪
So I decided to make one
of my own.
When I demoed it
for my best friend,
it malfunctioned.
And, well...
I burned
his parents' house down.
Him and his family
barely made it out alive.
♪
After that...
I made a vow.
No more weapons.
No matter what.
So by going back
on that vow now...
I feel like by building this,
I'm not just gonna
hurt Despero.
I'm gonna hurt myself too.
- Look, I...
I know you wanna do right
by Barry and by the team.
But you can't do that if you
don't do right by yourself.
It's not your job
to make weapons.
It's to...
find a way to protect Barry
and stay true to yourself.
♪
- Yeah, yeah.
- What's that?
- Uh...
okay, I built
a temporary comms system
by piggybacking
off of cell towers.
And I'm also using it
to scan for CCPD chatter
about criminal activity, right?
- Right.
- Okay, okay.
Flash?
We got trouble.
- Chester?
What's happening?
♪
- Miss, step aside.
- But if I did that,
then how would I grab
all the priceless art
you're transporting?
Officer, you sound insane.
-
Xotar. Xotar. Xotar.
♪
- Central City Museum,
you shouldn't have.
It's like you read my mind.
♪
- You're done messing with
other people's minds, Xotar.
Including mine.
♪
- If it makes you feel like
less of a failure,
I dug my claws into your mind
long before you even arrived.
♪
- Apologies for not mentioning
the telekinesis.
Didn't take a crystal ball
to know I'd eventually have
to catch you by surprise.
You know, back in the day,
my specialty
was bending spoons.
♪
- Okay, guys,
now CCPD is reporting
that Flash is getting
his butt kicked downtown
by some meta-magician
that's got him suspended
in midair.
- It's gotta be Xotar.
- Barry, Frost is on her way.
- But she's all the way
across town.
She'll never make it in time.
- I can stop Xotar!
I just need to generate
enough lightning.
- But Barry,
you need friction to build up
that kind of kinetic energy.
If you can't run...
you can't throw lightning.
Barry?
♪
- Sounds like Barry is
generating lightning.
How is that possible?
-
Holy Granville T. Woods.
Okay,
if he's vibrating his cells
on a microscopic level...
that might be enough movement
to build up
an electrical charge.
- How would he
throw lightning, then?
- I don't think he's going to.
My guess...
is, he's letting it build up
inside of him
on purpose.
- Caitlin, what happens
if his body can't hold in
his lightning anymore?
- I think we're about
to find out.
♪
- That was the hospital.
The guard that Xotar attacked
recovered as soon
as she was meta-cuffed.
So did everyone else
she attacked.
- How you feeling, Barr?
- Like it's barely
past lunchtime, already feels
like the longest day
of my life.
- But it also feels like
it's gonna be a good one.
Now that we got Xotar,
we don't have to worry
about the rest of the day
or you losing your sanity.
- Well, in that case,
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm starving.
- Oh, yeah.
- Why don't we meet up
with Iris at Joe and Cecile's?
See if we can talk Joe
into whipping us up
a pot of his famous jambalaya.
- That's...not funny, Barry.
- Okay, I'll ask him to grill
some burgers instead.
- Why are you doing that?
- Doing what?
- Acting like Joe's
still alive, man.
♪
- What are you talking about?
-
You don't remember?
♪
Barry, Joe died six months ago.
You know that.
- What?
No.
I don't believe you.
-
Barry, look.
Maybe you're still
processing this or something,
I don't know.
But we'll--we'll figure it out.
Okay?
Why don't you just sit down
and let Caitlin take a look
at the ol' noggin?
♪
- Where is he?
- Barry, you're scaring me.
- Who?
- Joe!
♪
- You gave the eulogy
at his funeral.
- No way.
No, no, this is wrong.
Iris, this is wrong.
We have to investigate this.
We have to find out
what really happened to him.
He's not dead!
He can't be!
- Damn it, Barry.
Joe is gone.
Why can't you just accept that?
♪
- Cecile.
- Barry, why are you saying
all these things
all of a sudden?
It's like the last six months,
this...
living nightmare
never even happened.
- Six months.
- What are you doing?
I can't do this with you.
Barry, I can't do it.
- Cecile, listen to me.
Joe's not dead.
- Yes!
Yes, he is.
He's dead.
And I am trying to move on.
Why won't you let me do that?
- Cecile, please.
- Barry.
You're all over the news.
- What?
- What did you do?
- Nothing. I...
- After apprehending
a criminal earlier today,
the Flash,
for reasons unknown,
committed a crime of his own.
this footage may
be disturbing
to some viewers.
-
- Our camerawoman was barely
able to escape with her life.
And luckily,
there were no deaths today,
despite what
city officials estimate
are millions of dollars
in damage.
But other members of our crew,
along with dozens
of innocent civilians,
were injured
in the Flash's brazen attack.
Once again,
the hero who has saved
our city countless times
has turned against us.
More on this unprecedented
breaking development
as we head to our reporter
on the ground.
♪
- I don't remember doing that.
- Caitlin said
you didn't remember
destroying the loft.
Or almost killing her
and Chester either.
♪
- Barry, we can blame Xotar
for the loft.
But she was in meta-cuffs
when you destroyed City Hall.
- Do you see?
It's been you all along, Flash.
Now do you believe me?
- No.
This is one of your illusions.
That's it.
Iris, Cecile,
you have to believe me.
- Enough!
This ends now.
♪
- Barry!
- It's fitting
that I end your life
with the undying fire
of my home world,
the Flame of Py'tar.
♪
- Get out of my house.
The empath.
Your power's no match for me.
So for now...
Sleep.
♪
- Stop!
If it's me you want,
get it over with!
- Gladly.
♪
- That's--that's all I got.
Barry, run!
- Good move, Chuck.
- What's wrong with you people?
You saw the destruction
he'll bring to the world
with your own eyes.
Why am I fighting
this threat alone?
Stand in my way again,
any of you,
and suffer the consequences.
I will find the Flash
and end him
before he brings about
Armageddon.
♪
- So is Barry gonna be
all right?
- Honestly, we don't know.
- Can you tell us anything else
about Despero's planet
or his freaky flame?
- Well, actually, the pieces
are starting to come together.
For years, we had heard
rumors and whispers
from the dark corners
of the galaxy
about the Flame of Py'tar,
which is an energy source
that was supposedly
the sentient heart
of the planet Kalanor.
But just when we started
to think that this was
a pan-galactic urban legend,
you guys are the first to meet
an actual Kalanorian.
Lucky us.
- Yeah, but thanks
to you guys,
we've opened an official file
on Despero.
Kara and J'onn,
they're off-world,
but we'll keep investigating,
and I'll call
if we find anything
that can help take him down.
You guys stay safe, okay?
- Yeah, thanks. You too, Alex.
- Well, we may not be the Tower
or have access
to S.T.A.R. Labs,
but Chester P can still
roll up his sleeves
and see what I can come up with
to help track down Barry.
- Assuming he wants
to be found.
- If you and Allegra hadn't
shown up when you did--
- Hey, hey, it's all good.
Okay? We'll figure this out.
We always do.
We'll get Barry back.
- Yeah, but what will he
be like when we do?
♪
- You look like
death warmed over.
- I need your help.
- Barry, what the hell is
going on?
- Injustice.
♪
- Greg, move your head.