All right, remember,
loose shoulders,
let your diaphragm do the rest,
and don't tense up
when you hit the high notes.
Mom, I can't. It hurts.
- It's just a little tummy ache.
- It's not my tummy.
- It's my side.
- What am I gonna say to you?
Pain is weakness
leaving the body.
That's right. We are winners.
And that means that we do
whatever it takes to win.
So you go out there
and just keep smiling.
Okay, baby?
All right.
You look beautiful.
Next up,
from Des Moines, Iowa...
...contestant 15,
Starlight.
My whole life,
rich people, powerful people
tried to muzzle me, cancel me,
keep me-me impotent
and-and obedient,
like I'm a puppet.
- You know what? It worked.
- Hey, Ashley,
what's crisis management
saying about this?
Sorry, Starlight, not now!
And guess what.
If they can control me,
then you can
bet your ass
they can control you.
They're already doing it.
You just don't realize it.
I'm done.
I am done apologizing.
I am done being persecuted
for my strength.
...done being persecuted
...persecuted for my strength.
...persecuted...
persecuted... persecuted...
You're up!
- No knock?
- Oh, fuck, I'm sorry.
Um, I'm... Yeah,
I'm gonna come back later.
Wait.
What do you mean, I'm up?
21 points with your base.
What did you just say to me?
21 points.
They loved your speech.
A massive 44% uptick with
white males in the Rust Belt.
- Yes.
- I know.
Fuck yes. Yes!
They're saying you're confident
and unapologetic
and that you're not afraid to...
Keep fucking going, Ashley.
Don't stop.
- Um, I'm sorry, sir.
- What?
Um...
Uh... That's got
nothing to do with you.
Just keep going.
Not afraid to what?
Not afraid to be yourself.
They want me to be myself?
Now, um...
...you did slip seven points
with urban-area adults 18 to 34.
But it's not bad. It's good.
Because ultimately, everybody
loves you and Starlight
as a team.
Together, you have
a Q Rating of 98%.
No one's ever been that high.
Not Soldier Boy, not anyone.
Ninety-eight.
♪ I get straight,
meditate like a Buddhist...
I'm-a be back,
you got to police your shit.
This is the Flatiron Building.
It's a historic
motherfucking building.
We got to put some respect
on the building's name.
- Look at this.
- Uh-uh-uh.
Use a plate.
But I don't use
a plate when I eat
your mother's
sweet and savory vagin.
What is Kimiko doing?
- Are you kidding me? Come on.
- Oh, hey, hey. Come on.
Come on.
She's been suffering
the dreary sting of ennui, okay?
You give her some space.
- The prodigal son returns.
- What the fuck?
Hey, man.
Yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you t... Are you back?
We'll see.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm happy, but are-are you sure?
What the fuck
happened here, kid?
You jacking off
with razors again?
You know, you should
see the other guy.
Other guy's my penis.
- I missed you, kid.
- I missed you, too, man.
Come on, man.
Look, I know what
you're gonna say, and I just...
No, no, mate. I'm just chuffed
to have all the Boys back
under the same roof, all right?
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, there he was, right?
In his fancy pants,
lording it over us like the
viceroy of Vought Square, eh?
And that whole time,
he weren't nothing
- but a Supe's boot lick, eh?
- Yeah.
That,
my son, is a Lifetime Achievement
- at the Cunt of the Year Awards, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
- Yeah.
- It is a Lifetime Achievement.
- Are you done?
- No, mate,
I am just getting started,
believe you me.
Great, listen, we need to get
Ryan somewhere safe.
Vicky knows where he is,
because we fucking told her,
which means
Stan Edgar knows, too.
Yeah, one step ahead.
Colonel's already done
a runner with the boy.
They're well out of sight.
In fact, we were gonna
pay them a little visit.
We are?
Uh, Monsieur Charcutier,
uh, I cannot go.
- I have a matter of great importance.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I must've forgot to run it
by your bleeding secretary.
- It's an emergency.
- I-I'll go instead.
Nah, you skive off today,
and that congresswoman might
split your pretty little buns.
Yeah, thought of that.
Uh, Kimiko.
Kimiko? Hi.
Uh, can you please...
uh, break my arm?
Vicky will smell it
if I fake being sick,
so it's got to be real,
and it's got to last for days.
Fucking hell, Hughie.
At least
take something for the pain.
I got opium.
Government employees
can't fail a piss test.
Let's just get this
over with, okay?
Just do it pretty fast.
H-Hold, hold, hold up.
Have a seat, please.
Only been here three minutes,
and it's already
The Bold and the Batshit.
All right. Go ahead.
Okay.
Right here.
Clean break.
No permanent damage.
Yeah?
One, two...
What the shit?
I'm the first Super
in a hijab, aren't I?
So if I can get myself
into The Seven, lit, man.
So, we're thinking slot one
goes to Supersonic.
For girls 11 to 14,
he's a real panty-dropper.
That's horrifying.
Please never say that again.
He's also a slam dunk
for the Latinx market.
We are desperate to get
into Central and South America.
Did you know that salsa
is more popular than ketchup?
Is Supersonic
an ambitious second-generation
Mexican American
chasing his lifelong sueño
- of joining The Seven?
- Or is he chasing
a rekindled pasión
with Starlight?
Okay, you do know that I have
a boyfriend, right?
Love triangles,
they generate a 47% surge
in trending topics
on social platforms.
Fans will ship the fuck out of you.
Let me talk to him first.
Amazing. Uh, what do you think
of our second choice?
- Moonshadow.
- She's body positive
- but not too body positive.
- Still fuckable.
So fuckable.
No one asked you, Ashley.
Sorry, Ashley.
Okay, that's also horrifying,
but I'm thinking Silver Kincaid.
But she's, uh...
She's from Afghan...
- She's from England.
- ...is tan?
And she has the highest
rescue stats
of any of the finalists,
and she's
a UNICEF ambassador.
She's the most qualified.
Well, we're gonna have to run
all of this past Homelander,
- of course.
- Of course.
Actually, according to
my contract with Mr. Edgar,
I get final say
over the two slots.
So, why don't you run that
past Homelander,
hmm?
Bonjour, Cherie.
Did you bring the passports?
Hey.
What is wrong?
Serge, I fucked up.
I went back to work
for Little Nina.
Merde, Cherie.
Some of us can't get
cushy jobs at the CIA.
I was moving weight for her,
and these fucking assholes
boosted it.
Can you find them?
They wore masks.
I don't know who they were.
And I was high.
Okay.
How much?
Eleven kilos.
We pay her back.
We pay her back. We beg...
No, you know it's the principle
of the thing with Nina.
You remember Olivier?
How many pieces did she cut off
him while he was still alive?
Come with me.
We can go someplace warm.
Just you and me.
Huh?
Sorry.
Oh, Marvin.
What are you doing here?
Poor judgment, ma'am.
Butcher!
Hi.
Oh!
Oh, easy does it, lad.
Bloody death grip you got there.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Right as rain.
Come on in.
The fuck was that?
Didn't know he had it in him.
So, why did you come back?
Soldier Boy killed my family.
Are you sure
this place is secure?
We'll have to keep moving,
but for now, yes.
The only thing that
might give us away
is this clown show of yours
shambling onto my driveway.
Well...
I wouldn't be here
if this was just a phone call.
- Hey, Alex, just, um, come here for a second.
- Hey.
Um, why are you playing
my shitty song?
So he can't hear us.
They want to pick you
as one of the winners tonight.
♪ I first saw you...
- Are you serious?
- Mm-hmm.
And you need to say no.
- What? Why?
- Okay, listen.
I really wish someone told me
what I'm about to tell you.
There's something wrong
with Homelander.
Something broken.
He's threatened to murder me
more than once.
He's murdered other people,
and it's only getting worse.
And you're just gonna be
putting yourself
and your family in danger.
And pretty much
the rest of them, too.
They're so fucking cruel.
Trust me,
you don't want this.
Just say that you can't do it.
Say that your family is
having an emergency.
- Don't do it.
- Annie, Annie, Annie, stop... Annie, Annie, stop.
You just told me that...
all the shit I swallowed
for years... I mean, the band,
Vought's racism, it's all for,
it's all for nothing, right?
- Look, I'm so...
- Look, I need a second.
I'm really sorry, but, please,
you need to promise me
that you will leave
and you'll never look back.
Please.
So they chauffeuring you
around now, huh?
Like you Rihanna.
Never needed a license,
always just ran.
- How'd you know I'd be here?
- I'm your brother.
And I still know a few people.
So...
how bad is it?
Doctors say it's like playing
Russian roulette.
If I ever run again,
maybe nothing,
but maybe my heart...
You still on that blue shit?
That shit'll probably
kill me even faster.
Good. Then we can skip to the
part where I accept your apology
and you can come back
to the crib with me.
Sure the boys would love
to see you, man.
Butcher said you have powers.
Me, too.
Do you like yours?
Do you ever get scared of them?
Me, too.
Aunt Grace wanted
to get me a dog, but...
I told her no.
I was afraid I'd hurt it.
I'm sure you didn't mean it.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Neuman's head of the bureau
because I said so.
I tried to save her from
the attack on Congress
that she fucking caused.
Well, at least you
didn't spend the last year
getting her oat milk lattes
and every piece of intel
she asked for.
I would very much like to know
the plan to eliminate her.
Well, that depends
on what you can tell us
about your little holiday
down in Nicaragua.
- I've never been to Nicaragua.
- Really?
'Cause a little birdie told me
you were Payback's
case officer down there,
on a classified job
that Soldier Boy
never come back from.
Colonel?
Whatever it is William
thinks he may have heard,
he's mistaken.
Is he?
You know that safe
you got in your home office?
The one behind the picture
of Bush number one?
Well, I borrowed
a ledger from it,
the one with all your assets
around the world.
How long do you think them
and their families will last
when I put every one of their
fucking names on Facebook?
You'd sign the death warrants
of dozens of innocent people
who had nothing to do with this?
I'm embarrassed for the both
of us that you're asking.
Nicaragua's ancient history.
Not to mention I could be killed
just for telling you.
And all your agents
will get killed if you don't.
Blimey.
What a pickle.
It was part of Operation Charly.
Operation...
Charly?
Reagan's pet project,
off the books.
Help the Contra rebels fight
the Russian-backed Sandinistas,
but we needed a way
to pay for it.
Some of the cash
came from selling arms to Iran,
Oliver North's epic fuck up.
But the rest?
If there's one thing that
the Contras had plenty of,
it was cocaine.
I was in charge of trafficking
the coke into the U.S.
and then using the profits
to buy more weapons.
In the fight against the Reds,
whatever it took.
That's some
self-justifying bullshit.
Were you part of that
other thing, too?
What other thing?
She knows.
Tell him.
The unwritten policy
was to sell the cocaine strictly
to minority neighborhoods.
Destabilize, demoralize,
while staying out of white ones.
Late in '84, we were gearing up
for a major offensive,
so the higher-ups,
in their infinite wisdom,
decided it was the perfect time
to throw a wrench in the works.
- ♪ My body is burning...
- Fucking Payback.
Each more ridiculous
than the next.
Crimson Countess, Mind storm,
Swatto, the TNT Twins,
Noir, Gunpowder,
and the most idiotic
of them all...
What do you say, Gunpowder?
Give them the Fourth of July?
Let's light them up,
Soldier Boy.
Please put that down.
Ah, well,
didn't realize they made
case officers as pretty as you.
We're just having some fun.
Our munitions dump
is in that direction.
You're about to blow up
half the camp.
Put it down.
Now.
I do like the assertive type.
You know,
with a figure like yours,
you are wasted down here.
♪ Here I am,
rock you like a hurricane...
My humblest apologies.
I'm sure this is...
disorienting.
Let's start over.
Officer Grace Mallory, isn't it?
- Mm.
- Stanford Edgar.
I'm an associate
with Vought American.
Do you want to explain
what the fuck
this freak show's all about?
Vought American has entered
into a partnership
with the U.S. government in the
global war against communism.
- Oh.
- Payback will embed themselves
and fight alongside
the Contra rebels.
Think of it as a trial run.
A trial run for what?
Superheroes in the military,
of course.
For the first time
in over 30 years.
Just imagine how dominant we'd be.
Jesus Christ. Get down!
What's the problem?
The... problem
is that the enemy might spot
a fucking flying man
above the tree line
and find our position.
She's right, Swatto.
No flights without
Officer Mallory's clearance.
Is this a joke?
Supes aren't soldiers.
They're undisciplined dip shits.
Untrained and untested.
They do not belong
in a war zone.
They belong
on That's Incredible!
Tell that to Soldier Boy.
He's a living, breathing
American hero.
I'm not allowing this.
I'm sure Director Casey
will address
any concerns you may have.
Oh, and, uh,
we need a couple of your men
to fetch water for our tents.
Thank you so much.
Claudio.
Mets don't stand
a chance in hell this year.
Señorita, fuck the Yankees.
Will the others go along?
Everyone but Gunpowder.
Good luck, Earving.
Can you please stop eating those
in front of me. I'm allergic.
So, listen,
if I'm gonna take a more
central role on the team,
then I want to lose the mask.
Silent ninjas score
extremely high
with boys seven
to ten years old.
The mask lends
a certain mystique.
Well, fuck mystique.
People don't even know
it's me under this thing.
I got to wear it
just to get a cab.
Payback is the country's
premier superhero team.
The whole country.
Sadly, a Black member's
still a nonstarter
below the Mason-Dixon.
Well, I could be
bigger than that.
I could be Eddie Murphy.
I'm not wearing the mask.
Your choice.
Though, once you're farmed out
to Minneapolis-St. Paul,
you'll want the mask
simply for... warmth.
You should smile more.
- I bet it's a beautiful smile.
- Okay, look,
as an ambassador
from Planet Actual Woman,
I just... I got to tell you,
- I know that you think these lines work, but...
- Oh, they do.
- Just ask Loni Anderson.
- They don't,
and they never have.
The women are either humoring
you, or they're scared of you,
but none of them like you.
You know, if you were
a little nicer,
maybe you'd find a man,
instead of out here
playing Captain Lesbo.
Hey, Señorita Mallory...
Hold that thought.
What the hell
is going on with him?
Ah.
- There she is.
- You mind?
- I'm just grabbing a bite...
- Nope.
- ...to eat.
- I do not mind at all. So...
Ashley tells me that you chose
Silver Kinca...
- Kincaid.
- Mm-hmm.
I have notes.
- I mean, I'm a cocaptain.
It's only fair I have a say
in the new recruits, right?
No, actually,
I choose the new members.
But I am pitching
the craziest twist.
The audience will never
see it coming, right?
Well, I've made my decision.
Oh, come on.
You haven't even heard it yet.
Seriously, you're-you're
gonna love it. Ready?
Return of the Deep.
- Hey.
What's up, guys? How are you?
No, no, no, no, no, Starlight,
before you say anything,
doesn't Christ tell us
to turn the other cheek?
I really want us to be sisters.
Mm.
I had something
made for you, Starlight.
It's a peace offering.
It's 24-karat gold
with certified
conflict-free diamonds.
I've put in the work,
and I realize that when you've
made an unforgivable mistake,
the first person
you have to forgive
is yourself.
What makes you think
that I want a daily reminder
of the guy who fucking
mouth-raped me?
I need a word.
Let's let these two chat,
shall we?
Okay. I'll just...
Absolutely not.
Do you really think
I'm gonna let
a... Muslim in The Seven?
Captain Al ...?
We're Americans.
- I'm taking this to Mr. Edgar.
- My speech last night?
Thirty-eight-point-six rating
and a 59 share.
Oh, and they're saying
that the live-plus-threes
are gonna be even bigger.
Edgar said it himself,
popularity is power.
He won't die on this hill.
Do I need to remind you
of the Flight 37 video?
Go ahead.
Release it.
Let's light this candle, huh?
I mean, sure, I'll lose
everything, but then...
I'll have nothing to lose.
First,
I'll take out
the nerve centers...
White House, Pentagon...
Then any domestic
defense capabilities,
and then critical
infrastructure...
Like cellular, Internet,
that kind of thing...
And then,
well, I think then...
I'll just wipe New York
off the fucking map...
for fun.
I'll even throw in Des Moines
and that little
cousin-fucker hick town
that Maeve's from,
'cause why not?
See, Starlight,
I'd prefer to be loved.
I would, but if you
take that away from me,
well, being feared
is A-one okey doke by me.
So...
Go ahead, partner.
Do it.
No?
You don't want to do it?
Well, then I would have to say
that you have absolutely
no fucking leverage
because I am the Homelander.
And I really can do
whatever the fuck I want.
Okay.
- Okay, so tomorrow...
- Uh-huh.
...you have the
"Re-Contextualizing Feminism"
panel with Rose McGowan
and Alyssa Milano.
Ooh, I love Charmed.
- Hey, babe, I'm serious.
- Yeah?
We need to cover your ass...
...in case that bitch Starlight
comes after you again.
Thanks, babe. I couldn't have
done this without you.
You're telling me.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, you like that?
- Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
- You're so fucking wet.
- Oh, it's all you, baby.
It's all you.
Oh, yeah? Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Gonna jerk me off
with all your arms?
All my arms?
Yeah.
Butcher, are you okay?
Yeah, mate.
It's all good.
Just give us a minute, yeah?
Do you need any help?
Don't come in.
- Hey, Annie.
- Homelander's had a breakdown.
He's lost his fucking mind.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Slow down, slow down. What?
He's bringing the Deep
back into The Seven,
so I brought up the video,
and he said to go ahead
and release it. You were right.
Cocaptain was a bad idea.
I have to leave.
Look, I-I know I should
tell you to run out of there
like a house on fire,
and I want to...
...but you got to stick it out.
- I'm sorry?
- Listen,
I'm-I'm-I'm back with Butcher.
Why?
We're onto something
that could kill Homelander.
What? What is it?
Some kind of weapon. Uh...
I'm not sure,
but you got to buy us some time.
Keep your eyes on him.
How much time?
Uh...
You don't know.
So, for God knows how long,
I have to paste on a smile,
with Homelander
growing more unstable
by the hour,
hoping that he doesn't
kill me or worse.
If that's what it takes,
then yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Just...
Homelander and-and Vicky,
they-they're running laps
around us because...
because we keep trying
to do it the right way.
The high road just doesn't work.
W-We have to be as mean
and fucked-up as they are.
- Now you sound like...
- Like Butcher, I know,
but, Annie, he's... he's right.
He's been right all along.
I'm just so...
tired of losing.
Okay.
You better pull this off,
Hughie, but...
okay.
I used to destroy you
in slapsies.
You had super speed.
Ow!
Khamari.
Put another hand
on your brother,
- you see what happens.
- Hey, Uncle Reg,
- what's up with that suit?
- Oh, you like it, huh?
- That shit's corny.
- Hey, Khamari, that's not
- how you talk to your uncle.
- Nah, it's-it's all right.
Young men just don't understand
the history.
Oh, no, the suit's ridiculous.
But he shouldn't be using
that kind of language.
All right, inside. Both y'all.
All right? And wash your hands.
For real this time.
I didn't want to say nothing,
but...
Just trying to show
the community
I'm down for the cause.
Since when you been down
with any cause?
Come on, man.
I mean, I can't run,
I can't do shit.
So I got to rebrand.
- Stay in the game somehow.
- Or you don't.
You could just be
my pain-in-the-ass
little brother Reg.
- Yeah.
- Let me tell you, man,
I'm happier coaching these kids
than I ever was
working at Vought.
You should come down
to the track.
They'd love to see you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Since you want to be down
with the cause so much...
- Hmm?
- I was walking home,
and this mugger
came up behind me.
I was terrified.
And that's when
Dana Whitmyre says Blue Hawk
came to her rescue.
At
Approximately 7:15 p.m.,
I spotted a Black male
following the victim
southbound on Marin Boulevard.
I intercepted him,
at which point
the suspect became aggressive.
Brother lived
a few houses up the street.
Three kids.
He was just walking home
from work.
Blue Hawk
curb-stomped him so hard,
it cracked the pavement.
- That's fucked-up.
- Yeah.
Maybe I can throw his family
some cash or something.
They don't need a handout.
They need you to speak up.
You're in
The motherfucking Seven.
Yeah, but, I mean...
I... Listen, I'm Michael Jordan.
I'm not Malcolm X.
Everybody loves
the A-Train, right?
Sergei.
- Nina wants to see you.
- Yevgenny.
How's your wife?
She still enjoy getting
her salad tossed by a Frenchman
while her husband
tosses nothing?
Another time.
Get in.
Come on. Fucking knock it off.
All right, mate?
Are you sick?
No, no.
I had a dodgy kebab, didn't I?
Went straight through me.
Try these.
Well, I'll be.
Your mum used to give me these
when I was under the weather.
Same.
- I hated them.
- I used to crush them up
and put them in the bird feeder
when she wasn't looking.
Well, I don't blame you.
They done off leave your mouth
drier than a nun's...
You were gonna say "vagina."
Yeah. Something like that.
It's not just your stomach,
though.
Your heart's racing.
I can hear it.
And your blood
smells funny, too.
Don't you worry, son.
Nothing a good night's kip
won't sort.
Sorry about that.
What the hell
did you drink last night?
Right.
Where were we?
To the surprise of no one,
that moron Swatto
went for another joy flight,
giving away our position.
Even better, the Sandinistas
brought Russian special forces
with them.
Though that didn't matter much
to the Supes.
Those are my men!
You, stay with me! Go!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh, yeah!
Gunpowder!
Will you please fucking stop?
Oh, God.
They killed Soldier Boy.
- What? Who?
- The Russians.
They had some kind of gun
or-or weapon or something.
- That's impossible.
- No!
We saw it. We saw it.
They took his body.
I lost 116 men.
And Vought got full immunity.
That was the day
I decided to make them pay.
Well, ain't that
a wonderful story.
Tell me, Grace,
where did the Ivans take this...
Supe Gun?
The trail went cold
behind the iron curtain.
It's the truth.
My reach only goes so far.
You knew what Soldier Boy did
to my family,
but you didn't think
I needed to know the truth?
It wasn't that simple.
Marvin, Hugh, give us the room.
You came to me
after Becca disappeared
and promised me
Homelander's head.
And all this time,
you knew there was something
that could do the job,
and you never said
a fucking word.
Whatever this weapon is,
it probably won't work
on Homelander.
- And what if it does?
- Even worse.
Because it wouldn't end
with him.
You'd go after another Supe,
then another, then all of them.
If you'd have told me
about this sooner,
Homelander
might already be dead.
Ryan wouldn't be running
from one safe house to the next,
wondering when his nutter dad's
gonna drop out of the sky.
And Becca...
Becca might still be alive.
And for that...
...I'll never
fucking forgive you.
This was never about Ryan
or Becca.
It was always selfish.
Always and only for you.
For the hate inside that you
want to let loose on the world.
I thought maybe you changed,
but I was wrong.
You are your father.
Always have been.
- What happened?
- We're off.
Butcher, wait up.
Where-where are you going?
- The city.
- When will I see you again?
You won't. Ain't safe for you.
Wait!
- What are you talking about?
- I got to go.
- Ryan, let go.
- No.
You said you'd always
watch out for me.
- You promised!
- Ryan, let go.
- I won't let you!
- Well, maybe I don't want to look at you.
After what you done to my Becca.
Did you ever think about that?
I hate you.
Sorry if Yevgenny
got a little rough.
He's still a bit bitter
you ate his wife's anus.
Why am I here, Nina?
Do you remember Mikhail Petrov?
You wait for him to come home.
He step out of his minivan.
You attack. He knocks
the blade from your hand,
so you slam this Honda Odyssey
minivan sliding doors
on his neck over and over
until he's...
...decapitated.
Art. Who can define it?
Then you discovered
his young bride
in the passenger seat,
and my Sergei
does not leave a witness behind.
Where is Cherie?
I don't know.
She had a place in Bayonne
last time I saw her.
Why?
'Cause nobody stole heroin
from her.
She stole it from me.
I will give her
a quick death, pazhalsta,
and I will make this
worth your while.
I don't do that shit anymore.
Nobody changes, hmm?
What was your safe word again?
When I used the dog collar
and the strap-on? What was it?
Vincent Cassel.
You are like rabid little doggy
but loyal to whoever
holds this chain.
Before William Butcher,
it was me.
Before me, it was your daddy.
But you always heel, Sergei.
Not Sergei.
Serge.
And that was a long time ago.
Who I am now is someone
who works for the CIA, Nina.
So unless you want
the full weight
of the government up your ass...
...I'm leaving.
We both have had bigger things
than the government
up our asses.
Just think about my offer.
Go on, scamper away,
little doggy.
Deep,
- welcome home, brother.
- Hear! Hear!
Oh, thanks, Homelander.
This literally means
everything to me.
- To us.
Ah! Here we are.
- Ooh.
- Excellent. Okay,
so, I took the liberty
of ordering for all of us,
but I'm pretty sure you're
gonna love my selection. Okay?
Thank you, gentlemen.
Yes, sir.
Mmm.
- Could I just get some... some bread?
- Come on, now.
You're back
in the big leagues, buddy.
Nothing but the best for you.
I'm so hungry.
Know who
I've been reading up on lately?
Dr. Martin Luther King.
Well, my relationship with King
has deepened of late.
He was, uh, villainized.
Persecuted.
Spoke truth to power.
Just like me. It's crazy. But...
we've both been
to the mountaintop,
and we've seen
the promised land.
I showed people the real me,
and they loved me for it.
I mean, they fucking loved me.
If only I'd known that sooner.
There's always been
so, so many things
I want to do, and now
I can do them all, finally.
And no one can stop me.
Nobody.
Free at last.
Oh! Excellent.
Deep,
- that's for you, big guy.
- Me?
- Thank you, sir.
- Mm-hmm.
Wonderful.
Chef's specialty.
It is a South Korean delicacy.
Holy shit, it's Timothy.
Oh, my God.
That's Timoth... He's my friend.
I, uh, I can't eat him. I'm not
gonna eat him. I can't...
- Oh, yes, you can, Deep.
- No, I'm not gonna...
Timothy is fucking delicious.
He's-he's begging for his life.
He has kids.
Hey, Deep?
What?
Eat fucking Timothy.
I'm so sorry.
He's praying. He's praying.
Mmm.
Wasn't that delicious?
Come on.
You should have seen him today.
Monsieur Charcutier?
How do you work
for a man like that?
You work for him, too.
I'm only here because you are.
But let's just leave.
We can go to Marseille.
Wouldn't that be nice, huh?
All right, let's have it.
Where the fuck you been all day?
I was, uh, detained
by Little Nina.
Who's that?
Little Nina?
And what does that Russian slag
want with you?
It's a long story.
Hang about.
This is a fucking
gold mine, Frenchie.
Set up a meeting
with you, me and Little Nina.
No, no, no. This is a very,
is a very bad idea.
No, Frenchie, it's
a very fucking good idea.
Go on. Get on the phone,
give her a call right now.
Oui, monsieur.
And what are we doing this for?
'Cause, my son,
we're going to Russia.
- Hey. Do you have a sec?
- Hey. Hey.
Yeah, yeah. Come in.
Thanks. Um...
So I went to talk
to the producers,
to tell them that I had
a family emergency
and I have to bow out.
Good. That's-that's really good.
But, uh, you know,
when I got there, I...
I told them I was
thrilled to join the team.
No. Alex, Alex,
that's-that's a mistake.
I was in rehab, would've
killed my mother for some oxy.
Manager bailed on me,
Vought, everyone.
But you didn't leave.
So do you really think
I'm gonna bail on you now?
I'm an asshole,
but I'm not
that much of an asshole.
Are you sure?
Someone's got to have your back.
Come on, then.
Let's hear it.
I'm a fucking monster
for what I done to the kid.
No.
The others don't get it,
but I-I do.
The gloves are off.
If there's anything
that I've learned...
What the fuck?
Well,
this has been quite
a long road for all of you.
You've shown us the best
of what heroes can be.
The first of the two selections,
and the newest member
of The Seven is...
Supersonic.
♪ Baby, rock my kiss,
got such a crush on you...
Welcome.
Thank you, sir.
Amigo, el honor
es todo mío, hermano.
Well... this is it.
The final new member
of The Seven is...
...Lord of the Seven Seas,
the Deep.
Get up here, you.
All right.
Welcome back.
- Good to see you.
- You, too.
- Congratulations, bro.
All right, well, unfortunately,
it won't be either of you two.
I'm sure you understand,
you just can't put a price
- on experience.
- Please hang up your capes and go.
Now, Deep, I got to say,
I am, uh,
well, frankly,
I'm moved and inspired
that Starlight here has
chosen to forgive you.
I accept your apology, Deep.
You deserve a second chance.
Thank you, Starlight.
Looks like we've all grown.
Just to be clear,
it wasn't my idea
to bring you back, buster.
Not at all.
Starlight here insisted on it.
But you keep your distance, pal,
because, uh, well...
...she's my girl now.
Sorry, I-I can't keep it
a secret anymore.
It's time we let the world know.
Starlight and I are in love.
#Home Light.
- Cut! Incredible.
- Huh?
- That fucking plays, man.
- Oh, my God! - That plays like hell.
- That was perfect. Yeah, yeah.
- People are gonna love it.
Incredible! Yes!
Okay, that was perfect, uh,
but, Starlight,
I need you to be not so shocked.
All right, well,
uh, let's go again.
Starlight?
We good?
We ready?
Yeah. Let's, uh, let's go again.
- Okay. Going again.
- Yeah, one more. Great.
Uh, take it
from your line, Homelander.
You got it.
All right.
- That a girl.
- And... action.
I just can't
keep it a secret anymore.
- Hmm.
- Come on, it's time we let the world know.
Hmm?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Um, everybody,
Starlight and I are in love.
#Home Light.
♪