My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Is that what you think I am?
- Some sort of evil secretary?
- You tell me.
I am now and forever will be
my husband's partner.
Pleased to meet you, Dominic Lanse.
- Hello, Mr. Allen.
- DeVoe?
If you hurt my family...
I have no interest in your family.
Besides, you're gonna need someone
to miss you when you're gone.
What did you do?
I left something for you.
I don't have need for it anymore.
Barry Allen, you're under arrest
for the murder of Clifford DeVoe.
My name is Barry Allen.
And I'm an innocent man.
I know that you'll find
my fingerprints all over his body.
And I know that
you'll find his DNA on mine.
But I don't know who stabbed him,
or how he ended up in my loft.
All I can tell you is
I'm being framed
for something I didn't do.
I didn't kill Clifford DeVoe.
All right, Allen, let's run it back
from the beginning.
This is exactly
what DeVoe wanted,
and we all played
right into his plan. Especially me.
Why would DeVoe wanna
orchestrate all of this?
I don't know.
But we know that this started
when I was still in the Speed Force.
But why target Dominic?
Dominic's power must have
allowed DeVoe to inhabit his body.
We should have been
on top of this earlier.
What about the other metas
on the bus? Why create them?
Part of a larger plan.
How are you even here
right now, Allen?
Aren't you on house arrest?
- Yeah. Well...
- He's at Joe's actually.
Either that or at the courthouse.
I managed to hack into
the ankle-monitor GPS.
That's not the only thing
Cisco hacked.
When you came out of the Speed Force,
you were talking gibberish
at C.C.P.D.
You said something about
not wanting to kill anyone.
I digitally scrubbed the video.
Last thing we want is
somebody hearing something
we don't want them to hear.
Your Honor, I'm innocent.
I didn't do this.
I didn't kill anyone.
Yeah, I mean, I don't remember
saying any of that.
- You don't?
- No.
We should look at
everything Allen said
when he first came
out of the Speed Force.
- Might give us a clue.
- That's a good idea.
Okay, guys, but remember,
I mean, considering all the evidence
they have against me,
this trial is not even gonna
last very long.
Okay. But with Cecile taking
a leave of absence to represent you,
you got the best lawyer in town.
Yeah.
And even if they did find you guilty,
it's not like any prison
can hold you.
Well, I'm not gonna run.
I won't be a fugitive.
If I'm convicted,
I have to go to prison.
We're not gonna let that happen.
Right.
Let's get to work.
- We should get to the courthouse.
- Yeah.
How are you doing?
They say the first year of
marriage is always the hardest.
But I never thought my husband
being on trial for murder
would be one of the challenges.
We have been through so much.
We'll get through this, too.
Will we, Barry?
I know the Speed Force gave you
a new outlook on life, but...
I don't know if being positive
is enough right now.
I'm just trying to be strong
for the team and for you.
Remember, we're the Flash.
We're the Flash.
Ralph, hold up.
Listen, I'm not gonna let
Barry go to prison.
I failed his dad,
I'm not gonna fail him.
I need your help.
My help?
As in, the stretchy kind?
As in "the underhanded
private investigator" kind.
Oh, uh...
- No offense taken.
- Come on.
Science has long pondered
what would be required
to successfully transfer consciousness
from one living being to another.
But we've accomplished far beyond
a simple transfer of consciousness.
We've extracted that which elevates
our humanity, and added upon it.
I am both who I was before,
and who I desire to become.
Yes, you are, my love.
My hand still feels foreign
upon your flesh.
And you don't care for it.
No, I do.
As I said, I inherited
my host's ability to read thoughts.
We have never lied
to each other before.
Let's not begin now.
Okay.
Marlize, my love,
see past this body,
see past these eyes.
See me, Clifford.
Clifford.
I am nothing without you.
Your Honor,
ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
for you to understand what it is
I'm about to tell you today,
you need to do something.
I need you to believe
in the impossible.
As children, we're taught
that the police are there
to protect us, to serve.
We're told that
our tax dollars go toward
training them to be
the champions of the city.
But for some of us,
it still seems impossible
that a police investigator,
one of Central City's finest,
could betray that trust.
And even worse, under the guise
of upholding the law to commit
the most heinous act that one person
could carry out against another.
But that is exactly
what Barry Allen did.
And the prosecution
will prove beyond any doubt
that he stood among us
a wolf in sheep's clothing.
But here's the thing.
Barry Allen wears a mask.
He used his connection to the law,
his experience as
a police investigator,
especially as
a crime scene technician,
to stalk a beloved professor, husband,
and murder Clifford DeVoe
in cold blood.
All right, Mr. Borman,
just sign on the dotted line
and your savings account
is all set up.
I appreciate you helping me out.
I wanna get this right.
It's my first savings account.
You okay?
Yeah. Just a little light-headed
before lunch, I guess.
Have a great day.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Ladies and gentlemen,
the document in my hand
is a court-issued restraining order.
It's issued to Marlize DeVoe,
the wife of the victim,
on behalf of her husband,
against a Mr. Bartholomew
Henry Allen.
Now, if you'd like a better look,
I have a bigger copy.
But if you allow me to call out
what's written underneath
"reason for order issue..."
"Harassment."
Defendant was seen just days earlier,
illegally breaking and entering
into the victim's house,
searching through
the victim's effects.
A man obsessed.
Barry Allen's skin cells were found
under the nails of the victim.
Now, imagine that if you can.
Mr. DeVoe, a man in a wheelchair,
desperately trying to defend himself
as Mr. Allen sought to overpower him.
And finally, this is the knife
that was used to kill Clifford DeVoe.
If it looks new,
that's because it is.
It was a wedding gift to Mr. Allen.
Now, let's just let that
sink in for a moment.
This was supposed to commemorate
the most joyous moments
in a couple's lives.
But instead, Mr. Allen used it
to forever separate a couple
from one another.
He used a wedding gift
as a murder weapon.
That is a special kind of evil.
But it showed an absolute disregard...
Cisco.
There's a meta attack downtown.
We gotta go.
I'll stay here with Barry.
When you're done here get some
coverage of the workstations.
Detective, would you get
a statement, please?
- Mr. Ramon.
- Captain.
What happened here?
Vintage Central City.
Meaning, another weird one.
No data breach, nothing stolen,
everyone just collapsed.
I have officers at the hospital
interviewing people now.
But so far, no one knows anything.
Oh.
Dark matter city.
Yeah, we're definitely
dealing with a meta here.
You wanna see what kind of perimeter
we're dealing with?
You read my mind.
Hey, Joe, are you sure
you're okay to run this case?
Because I totally understand
if you need a little more time...
I'm fine. Really.
I may have to go over
to the courthouse later.
Yeah...
I'm actually heading
over there myself.
The prosecution called me to testify.
I'm sorry, Joe.
You know how much I care about Barry,
but I have to tell them what I know.
I get it.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
Yeah.
Do I need to repeat the question?
No, I heard it.
The person standing over
Clifford DeVoe's body
was Barry Allen.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Captain Singh, you stated that
you interviewed Barry Allen
five years ago for the job of CSI.
I wonder, what was
your first impression of him?
He was young.
Had half the experience of
everyone else I interviewed.
Hmm. Why'd you hire him?
It was really something
he said in the interview.
Everyone always talks about
going after the criminal, the guilty,
but Allen said
he wanted to help the victims,
the innocents.
I thought Central City
deserved someone like that.
Allen is one of the good ones.
"One of the good ones."
No further questions, Your Honor.
I'd like to redirect,
Your Honor.
Proceed.
Would you cover for Mr. Allen
if you had to?
No, of course not.
No? It says here
in his personnel file
that he took a six-month sabbatical
to the Czech Republic.
Did he get approval from you first?
Not exactly.
He said it was for
something personal.
I'm sure he had a good reason to go.
Is "saving the world" a good reason?
It also says in here that he was late
seventy-two times in the past two years.
Did you ever ask him why?
No.
Because regardless of
what time he got in,
he always did his job.
I was just curious to imagine
what he does with his time
instead of being at work.
It's almost like
he has this secret life.
So in spite of all these infractions,
you never thought to discipline him?
What are you suggesting?
That whether you realize it or not,
you've been covering the ugly truth
about Mr. Allen for years now.
That is not true.
Is it true that he was targeting
and harassing Mr. DeVoe?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Which is why I granted DeVoe
the restraining order
and told Allen to stay away.
But that didn't stop him, did it?
He kept going after him,
right up until the night
that Mr. DeVoe was killed.
Objection. Conjecture.
Withdrawn.
Captain, now you said that
Mr. Allen wants to help the victims
and the innocents.
But disappearing for months
at a time, being late 72 times...
Doesn't sound like he wants to help
or care for anybody but himself.
Now, do you still think that he's
"one of the good ones"?
I hope you're right about this.
Oh, trust me. I'm very good
at reading body language.
Right now, you're tense.
Now, you're annoyed.
Oh. Here we go.
- Yahtzee!
- Did you get that?
Ralphy got it.
I smell an acquittal.
As we thought might happen,
we are in trouble.
David's testimony hurt us,
but we still have a few options.
What are they?
I can go to Slater.
I can ask for a plea deal.
Maybe get you a shorter sentence.
Or we could use an insanity defense.
No. Both those options
are admitting I'm guilty, and I'm not.
Fine. Then the only other way
out of this is for you to testify.
Cecile, I'm sorry. I won't do it.
All of the evidence, every bit of it,
it points to you.
If you're not willing to take that stand
and defend yourself,
then this is an impossible case.
I'm not taking the stand.
Barry, even if that means
turning this case around
and not going to jail?
Iris, if I testify, I have to lie.
I commit perjury.
I become exactly who they think I am.
- Then don't lie.
- What?
Tell the truth.
Tell everyone you're the Flash.
Barry, if the court knows
you're the Flash,
then you can explain everything
and they'll believe you.
Prosecution is gonna wrap up soon.
I need your answer today.
This is the only way, Barry.
Tell the city you're the Flash.
This is all we got?
This isn't a lot to go on.
I know, okay?
We're lucky we even got this footage.
For some reason,
all the security cameras were fried.
Hey, guys, I was just at the hospital
going over the medical records
of everyone who was at the bank.
- I know why they passed out.
- Why did they pass out?
Well, they all suffered from fatigue,
vomiting, abdominal pain,
skin rashes.
So, everyone ate a bad burrito?
No. Radiation poisoning.
That's why the security cameras
are fried.
Mmm-hmm. We gotta find this guy
before he poisons the whole city.
- Yeah, or worse.
- Hmm?
Guys, if this meta can cause these
levels of radiation in these patients,
it means this meta has a similar
make-up to a nuclear bomb.
So, like, enough to blow us all up?
What are we talking here?
The fallout from a nuclear explosion
could be catastrophic.
Exactly.
- "Fallout."
- Great name.
Terrible power.
Okay, I'll see if the satellite
can track his radiation signature.
Mrs. DeVoe, when did you
first meet Mr. Allen?
Um...
Mr. Allen showed up at my house
almost two months ago,
claiming to be investigating
one of Clifford's former colleagues.
We reassured him that we didn't have
information to help him.
But Mr. Allen persisted
and continued to harass my husband.
And what prompted
the restraining order?
My husband has...
Had advancing ALS.
I was alone with Clifford
most of the time.
But something about
Mr. Allen's aggressive manner
just made me feel unsafe,
so we went to the authorities.
And we thought the complaint
would dissuade Mr. Allen.
But it didn't.
Psst.
Could you please
describe for the court
the last time that
you saw your husband?
It was Christmas.
And Clifford wanted to
confront Mr. Allen.
He had hoped that
in the holiday spirit
he could convince him to let us be.
And I...
I begged Clifford not to go.
But even with his disability,
Clifford insisted that it was his job
as my husband to protect us,
to protect me.
He didn't wanna live in fear, so...
He left.
And I wish I could have stopped him,
and stepped in,
and told him not to do this.
But I let him go.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Your Honor, I would like
to enter Exhibit F into evidence.
Objection, Your Honor. Why wasn't
this entered into discovery?
Oh, I've only recently
received this new evidence.
May we approach?
Your Honor, there are protocols
that need to be observed.
This is my courtroom, Mr. Slater.
I'll run it any way I see fit.
I'll allow it.
These photographs
were taken earlier today.
Mrs. DeVoe...
Could you tell me, please,
who's the man that you're kissing
in that photograph?
It is most certainly
not your husband, correct?
His name is Dominic Lanse.
And how long
have you known Mr. Lanse?
A few months.
So it appears to me that perhaps your
marriage was not quite as perfect
as you've portrayed.
Maybe you were ready
for a life without your husband.
So you ran into the arms
of another man.
Another man you convinced
to kill your husband.
Clifford and I met Dominic Lanse
at an ALS charity gala months ago.
He was there to honor his father,
who had recently passed away
with the disease.
Clifford noticed the bond
that Dominic and I
shared, long before I did.
My husband was happy that
I found someone to talk to,
and he urged me to turn to Dominic
for the needs
and comforts
he could no longer fulfill.
My husband wanted me to be happy.
Clifford didn't see
my relationship with Dominic
as a tool to pull us apart,
but to bring us together.
And it did.
My heart will always
belong to Clifford.
No further questions, Your Honor.
You're excused.
Okay, that did not go well.
What's your decision, Barry?
I'm not gonna do it.
Marlize...
Mrs. West-Allen,
I don't think it's appropriate
for the two of us to be seen talking.
Oh, please.
No one is watching, so you can
drop that ridiculous act already.
If you insist.
Why are you doing this?
What is wrong with you?
It's not about what's wrong with me,
it's what's wrong with the world.
There are problems
bigger than your husband.
Such as?
Whatever it is that you are up to,
it will come to an end.
Such passion.
I had that, too, when Clifford and I
first got married.
But passion fades.
And what remains, if you are
fortunate enough, like Clifford and I,
is something deeper than ardor
that cannot be destroyed.
Then why are you so hell-bent
on destroying our lives?
I am doing what I have to do
for my husband, Mrs. West-Allen.
The question
you should truly be asking
is what are you
willing to do for yours?
Hope you enjoy the rest of the show.
Still no word
from the courthouse.
That's good news, right?
No news is good news?
No. Good news is good news.
No news is miscommunication.
The satellite was able to track
a spike in radiation
downtown on Main Street.
- We found him.
- Fallout's on the move.
We gotta get down there now.
I'll monitor him from here.
- Harry, time to book it.
- Yeah.
- I've got two rads.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey, stop!
- Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
What's going on out there?
Nuclear waste tanker.
Sorry!
Idiots!
- Okay.
- Move along.
Mr. Slater...
Call your next witness.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Your Honor...
There's something you need
to know right now
that will alter
the outcome of this case.
Ms. West-Allen,
I have no idea
what you think you're doing.
Explaining what my husband won't.
Barry Allen is...
The...
What's happening?
We're moving so quickly
that everyone else is still.
How are you able to do this with me?
I actually don't know.
Iris... Hey...
I already decided
not to tell anyone else who I am.
Barry, if the jury knew
that you were the Flash,
there's no way
that they would convict you.
I'm trying to protect you.
Okay? If everyone knew my secret,
we would never stop running.
I would rather run forever with you
than stand alone without you.
It wouldn't just be us running.
Everyone that has stood by us
the last four years
would have a target on their back.
If criminals knew my name,
they'd know my weakness.
I'm trying to be strong, but I...
I know.
I can't anymore.
How can you...
My dad...
He went through this too.
The trial is not over, Barry.
Yeah, it is.
All the evidence points towards me.
You can't tell them, okay?
Okay.
Yes, Ms. West-Allen?
Um...
Your Honor...
Barry Allen
is innocent.
And...
I just thought
you all should know that.
Thank you for your time. Okay.
If there was an award
for Best Crocodile Tears
by the Most
Emotionally Manipulative Widow...
Marlize, definitely in the top three.
Let's snap something
more damning than a lip-lock.
We're not here for that.
Can you do your gross stretchy thing
and slip inside and open the door?
Those are carpet fibers.
Those are from Allen's loft,
aren't they?
You're gonna plant evidence
to frame Marlize.
She was the only one
that could have planted DeVoe's body.
Fibers on the treads of her shoes
places her at the crime scene.
This is the right thing to do, Ralph.
Just open the door. I'll do the rest.
Okay.
It's a solid plan, Joe.
Subtle, but it's crafty
with a touch of pathos.
After this, you're gonna sit back
and kick up your feet
and sleep as sound as a millennial
after Burning Man,
because you did the right thing.
You took down a bad, bad chick.
Ralph, could you hurry up?
And you're gonna ride that feeling
like it's Space Mountain.
And then, when they catch you and
they take your badge and your gun,
that self-righteous indignation
is gonna keep your chest puffed
and your chin up,
because you did the right thing.
Sure, you're gonna be mad
for a few years, but that fades,
evolves,
turns into self-pity.
A few more years
and your life is gonna be a shell
of its former self.
And then, one night,
it's gonna dawn on you that
you did the wrong thing,
and it ruined everything.
Your colleagues won't talk to you,
your friends have vanished,
and your family...
It'll be like...
Like you weren't ever born.
Because you turned into
the very thing that you swore
to protect them from.
Anyhoo...
Good luck with that.
Mr. Slater?
Prosecution rests, Your Honor.
Ms. Horton,
are you ready to present your case?
The defense rests, Your Honor.
Should've gone
with the insanity plea.
Oh! Excuse me.
What's wrong?
What is going on?
There's a massive spike in radiation
downtown at Prentis and Rollins.
The driver
of the nuclear waste truck.
Radiation signature's
already at 3,000 rads and climbing.
We need to stop this guy
before it hits 10,000.
What happens at 10,000 rads?
Hiroshima.
Barry Allen has dedicated his life
in service of Central City.
He's helped
to solve countless crimes.
His testimony has led to the
conviction of dozens of criminals.
Barry Allen is a good man.
He's an innocent man.
And frankly,
Central City is lucky to have him.
Dare I say,
few men in this city are as honest,
upstanding and dependable.
Mr. Allen?
Your Honor, I...
I have to go.
Barry, what are you doing?
I have to.
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
this is an emergency.
Someone needs me.
And I need you
to respect my courtroom.
I will not stand
for theatrical disruptions.
Your Honor,
my client is still free on bail.
And there are no laws that require
him to be present
during closing statements.
Be advised, Mr. Allen,
you are required by law
to be here for sentencing.
Yes, Your Honor.
Stay where you are!
What is happening to me?
Hold it right there!
I didn't do anything!
You need to stop.
I don't wanna hurt anybody.
I understand,
but your radioactivity is dangerous.
- Guys?
- Seven thousand five hundred rads!
Barry, don't get too close to him,
all right?
The radiation he's emitting
is too hot to allow you to self-heal.
Yeah, thanks for the heads-up.
What am I supposed to do?
How do I stop him?
I can't stop this!
Damn!
We need to cool him down.
Killer Frost.
- Great.
- Well...
Go! Turn!
Well, that's not how it works.
I can't just snap my fingers
and make her appear.
It only happens
when I'm scared or angry.
- Oh, good Lord, Caitlin!
- Caitlin!
The city's about to explode!
Everyone! Everything you know
and love!
The birds, the trees, the fish,
the puppies!
Puppies are going down
because you didn't wanna
- show up for work!
- Show up for work!
Thanks.
- That was pretty good.
- Yeah, pretty good.
- Now go already!
- Okay!
Okay, there you go.
What's going on?
Is this business or a social call?
Business, I see.
- Is she okay?
- She's gonna be okay, yeah.
You have any more ideas?
What if I breach him?
Ramon, no, you... You drop him
in a breach, he could explode.
And Fallout's fallout
would kill us all.
Do you think?
Wait, what if I create a vacuum
around him?
That way, even if he does explode,
at least we contain the blast.
Yes. Allen, yes.
That could work.
That could contain it.
Whatever you're gonna do, though,
do it fast.
Falloutjust went above 8,000 rads.
- The vacuum's containing his energy.
- Good.
But he's still getting stronger.
Allen, I don't know how long
you can take this much radiation.
I don't have a choice.
We have to contain his energy.
Allen, 9,000 rads.
Ten thousand rads! Critical mass!
Ramon, you need
to send that energy somewhere.
What? To where?
Earth-15. Earth-15 is a dead Earth!
Breach it there now!
You did it.
Oh, man, you did it.
You saved the day.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
you've reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
All rise.
For docket number 5677-B,
in the matter of The People
v. Bartholomew Henry Allen,
we, the jury,
find the defendant guilty
of murder in the first degree.
Thanks to your meta-metabolism,
your radiation burns should disappear
in the next few minutes.
What about Fallout?
He's unstable,
but we sent him to Tracy's lab.
She's gonna analyze his DNA,
see if it's the same
as the other metas
and be able to neutralize him.
...Superior Court,
where minutes ago, the jury found
Bartholomew Henry Allen guilty
in the murder
of Professor Clifford DeVoe.
Mr. Allen has been a CSI with
the Central City Police Department
for the last five years.
In just a few short hours,
the judge is expected to announce
Mr. Allen's sentence.
Prosecutor Anton Slater
made a statement.
He hoped Mr. Allen
would receive a life sentence,
given the brutal nature of the crime.
I wanted to be the one to tell you.
I can't believe this is happening.
Come on, guys,
we just saved the city today.
We knew this wasn't
gonna go my way in court.
That doesn't mean that DeVoe beat us.
Whatever happens,
we're gonna keep fighting.
I know.
We need to get you back.
You need to be there for sentencing.
Yeah.
I'll see you guys later, all right?
I'm gonna be okay, all right?
Come on.
You know, you got your strength
from watching your dad be your rock.
I got mine because...
You're mine.
And I'll be strong for you.
I love you.
Come on.
Mr. Allen, are you going
to appeal the verdict...
Step back.
Hey, I need a minute, all right?
Mr. Allen...
DeVoe.
Did you know there was a 12% chance
that you were gonna tell the world
you're the Flash?
I'd recheck your math.
There's no need.
Because no matter
what path you chose,
all avenues led to my triumph.
Why do you want us distracted?
Why do you want me
out of the picture?
What are you planning?
That you think that you could
understand the breadth
of what I'm about to do
is almost humorous.
Yes, I think you will miss Iris.
That's right, Mr. Allen.
I didn't just take Dominic's body.
I took his ability.
I know what you're thinking,
right now.
I want you to hear me say it.
I'm gonna figure a way out of this.
And when I do,
I don't care
whose face you're wearing.
I'm coming for you.
You haven't beaten us yet.
Haven't I?
Have a nice life, Mr. Allen.
Your Honor, I'm innocent.
I didn't do this.
I didn't kill anyone.
And I know that one day
the truth will come out.
Thank you.
Rise for sentencing.
In my 30 years behind this bench
I have seen my share of criminals.
But I confess, this defendant
stands apart.
Thank you all for coming
on such short notice.
A few hours ago,
the very existence of our city
came under the threat
of nuclear destruction.
But one man rose
to meet that challenge.
The defendant
was in a position of authority.
Our city trusted him
to bring the guilty to justice.
He ran into danger,
knowing he would suffer
burns all over his body.
He used that trust to take
an innocent and vulnerable life.
This man was not thinking
about himself.
He was thinking about you,
the first responders
on the front lines...
Never have I seen
a defendant more unmoved.
Never have I seen a man
with more bravery.
Never have I seen such inhumanity.
Such heroism.
Such a lack of regard for human life.
It is my great honor
to present Central City
Police Department's Award of Valor
to this city's finest hero.
The fastest man alive...
The Flash!
The court hereby orders
that Bartholomew Henry Allen
should be incarcerated
for the rest of his natural life,
without the possibility of parole.
And that Mr. Allen
be immediately remanded
to Iron Heights Penitentiary.
And may God have mercy on your soul.
Filthy cop!
Badge ain't gonna
help you now.
Be seeing you around, B.
Gonna break you, string bean.
Get comfortable.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::