[door opens]
[clears throat]
[sighs] Babe, you home?
[chuckles]
Well, the Speed Force
is definitely fixed
because the loft did not
look like this a second ago.
You like it?
I love it.
Like the trip to Maui yesterday,
and the fresh crepes
this morning from Paris.
You, Barry Allen,
are the most romantic husband ever.
- [rumbling]
- [objects clattering]
[phone beeps]
[sighs] Satellites say it's just
a small, everyday earthquake.
Usually we have to kiss first
to make the ground shake.
[thunder rumbling]
[Arielle] After Mirror Monarch's
brutal attack
on Central City last week,
construction areas
like the one behind me
have popped up all over the city.
Volunteers from local businesses
and everyday citizens
are working hard to repair the damage
Eva McCulloch left behind.
And here's the person
we've been waiting for,
the hero of Central City, the Flash.
An earthquake hit Central City
last night.
A city already on edge.
How is morale?
Well, the sign says it all.
Central City Strong.
I let down this city...
by failing to prevent Mirror Monarch
from tearing our community apart.
But I will make it up to you.
I promise.
Together we're rebuilding
our community,
our homes, our lives.
It'll take time,
but I believe in this city.
Its resilience.
Most of all, its people.
That's how we'll survive this.
Central City Strong.
[sighs] Thank you, Flash.
For The Arielle Atkins Hour,
this has been Arielle Atkins.
Wow. Flash's speech has me wanting
to sign up for double shifts today.
Yeah, he knows
what the people need to hear
to get back on our feet.
Yo, this is epic.
I didn't know S.T.A.R. Labs
did volunteer work.
Mm-hm. And not just us.
Kord Industries is showing up
for their shift in an hour.
Hey, you got any more nails?
Yeah. I got your box nail,
finishing nail,
casing nail, masonry nail...
All the nails.
- [Cisco] Uh...
- [Caitlin] Whew!
You got a latte in there?
Because I'm as fried as these wires.
Oh. Runkadelic,
are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- Yeah, we gotta...
- Jitters run.
Jitters run. I like Jitters.
We should do Jitters.
One latte coming right up.
Make it a double.
[Caitlin straining]
You okay?
After our fight with Eva,
I have just been exhausted.
And now I've got this headache.
You need to recharge.
Can't you just, like, frost out?
No, not out here.
You and I know she's reformed,
but technically,
there's still a warrant out
for Killer Frost's arrest.
- [phone vibrating]
- [sighs]
Who's that?
Iris. Wants notes
on a Citizen article.
Kamilla's been spending all her time
photographing the destruction
in the city.
It's great that she's so inspired,
but now I'm the only one
that can give Iris any feedback.
Maybe I'll stay here a little longer.
It sounds like you're avoiding her.
Fine. I'm going.
[sighs]
- Hey, got your texts.
- Great.
Sorry to drag you away,
but I need those notes
on the Mirrorverse article.
We need to go to press ASAP.
Online viewership is down 73%,
and I think that my article
could be what The Citizen needs
to pull us out of the financial hole
that Mirror Me put us in.
- Ooh. Did you get me a T-shirt?
- Yes.
Thanks. Cute.
Okay, so stop burying the lede.
Tell me what you think.
Good, huh?
Well, it was really well-written.
Okay, come on.
Pretend you're my editor.
Lay it on me.
It stinks, okay?
This part about the explosion
at McCulloch Tech
is straight out of CCPN's report.
This section on Eva's
framing of Sue Dearbon
was already covered to death
by CC News Network.
And was this quote
from that Maurice guy
even fact-checked?
Okay. Is there anything else?
Yeah.
You were in the Mirrorverse
the longest
and knew Eva the best.
You're the expert.
So where's anything
about your experience?
'Cause what's missing
from this is you.
I'm the reporter, not the story.
This time you're both.
Look...
There are people out there
just like you
who wish they hadn't been
a part of this story.
But they were.
You're their voice, so try again.
For them.
[clattering in distance]
Who the hell are you?
I'm the greatest magician
of all time.
Which is why you should
be more than just afraid.
You should be terrified.
Boo.
[man screaming]
Abracadabra.
Now for my greatest trick yet.
Absolute suffering.
I feel like usually I'd be like
"Holy Arthur C. Clarke,"
but it's just so cute.
Mm, don't let it fool you.
It may be collectible size,
but this little guy is heavy.
Two tons?
That's like 20 baby elephants.
Which is also kinda cute.
I mean, what do you think
this thing's made of?
And how does a shed just disappear?
None of it makes any sense.
Barry, I know
this all seems bad, but...
Chester, this city's
been through hell.
Can't take another emergency.
Not now. Not this soon.
- We got this, Barr, don't worry.
- We just started rebuilding.
I'm not gonna let anything
tear us down again.
Please tell me you boys
found something we can use.
[Cisco] I think I just did.
It looks like this whole crime scene
is infected with
serious temporal energy.
Like the kind carbon-dated
43 centuries from now.
[Chester] As in the future?
Wait, hold on.
Is this thing like a time capsule?
Or maybe like a TARDIS?
P. Runk, you picked a hell of a day
to start your CCPD
consultant internship.
Yeah, this is definitely
a time traveler.
[Chester laughs excitedly]
Barr, there's something
you need to see.
He's not just a time traveler.
He's a guy who has
a theatrical flair for killing.
Abra Kadabra is back.
[sighs] Oh, great.
That explains all the shaking
and quaking yesterday.
Wait, Timequakes, too?
Oh. Okay, so what's
this Abra dude's deal?
Oh, you know, he's just your
standard time traveling,
murdering, thieving
64th-century magician
who uses embedded nanotech
and calls it magic.
[Barry] Four years ago,
the Collectors Agency
took him to be executed
for his crimes.
Somehow he escaped.
Last time, he was hellbent
on stealing tech
to build a time machine.
This time he goes out of his way
to kill an innocent person,
doesn't steal a thing.
That's a pretty vicious escalation.
And what's that thing back there
got to do with it?
[Barry] You know,
it doesn't matter.
Kadabra picked the wrong day
to come back.
I'll put out a BOLO right away.
You wanna help me analyze
some of this stuff?
I'll search the city.
Central City Strong.
[Stephen] When I was inside
that other place,
I watched that mirror version of me
spend time with my wife.
They ate meals together,
talked about their day.
I remember screaming,
"That's not me,"
but I was helpless.
Barry! That's not me!
That's not me!
[Stephen] I thought everything
would be okay once I was back.
It's not.
I'm trying so hard
to get back to normal.
I'm trying so hard to be fine.
But the truth is that things
are not normal and I am not fine.
And I won't be for a long time.
Thank you so much
for coming and listening.
Stephen, Alice,
thank you for agreeing
to do this interview with me.
Are you sure I'm not intruding?
Of course not.
We're all in this together.
Central City Strong.
Yeah. [clears throat]
Um, are you all right?
You seem upset.
Me? No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Were you abducted as well?
[gasps]
You know, if you ever want
to sit in with the group...
No, I'm fine, thank you.
You don't seem like it.
Yeah, I just... I have a deadline
for another article.
Do you mind if we reschedule?
- Sure, no problem.
- Thanks.
[breath trembling]
We could do release date order...
Or machete order...
- Prequels after Empire?
- [Chester laughs]
You're a wild man and I love it.
- Then the Jedi Council has spoken.
- It has!
Get anything
on your scans over there?
[clattering]
[sighs] No.
Think it might be time
for a Jitters run.
Well, thank God,
'cause Chester P. is running on E.
- [rapid beeping]
- Hold the cappuccino.
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
That's the same temporal scan
from this morning.
Only now there's a second one
downtown, which means...
That's where Kadabra's headed next.
Two is always deadlier than one.
Flash.
- I knew it was just a matter of time.
- Bad timing for you, Kadabra.
[Vibe] Yeah, those would be
nanotech nullifying cuffs.
So no hocus pocus this time.
Hey, what's up
with all your new toys?
A magician never reveals his secrets.
- I see you're finally Mecha-Vibe.
- Mecha-Vibe?
I know he did not just name me.
I know more than just your name.
I've seen your future.
[Barry] It's over.
- You've lost.
- Have I?
Seems you've forgotten
the art of misdirection.
Ah.
Oh, shoot.
You know what? I'm doing you a favor
by killing you now, Flash.
This way you'll never have to face
the wrath of the Chronarch.
Alas, you can't run forever.
What was that you were saying
about the art of misdirection?
Look at me. I'm A.R.G.U.S.
I'm gonna let two young,
handsome devils
do all the work
while I reap all the benefits.
And I'm going to pick up
the obelisks. That doesn't bug you?
Kadabra's caught.
The job's finished. You really
want to argue over who gets credit?
Yes.
[clangs]
No.
I just want to know what the plan is.
All right, knock yourself out.
I got to do something
important for Iris.
Hm.
Hey! Hold up there, chief.
My classification is
Director of Technology and Science
for A.R.G.U.S.
I've never held the rank of chief.
Okay. Hey, I just want to know
what your plan is
for keeping David Copperfield
here contained.
David Copperfield is not currently
under A.R.G.U.S.' custody.
Are you for real right now?
If you're asking if I'm a hologram,
I can neither confirm nor deny
A.R.G.U.S.' use of such tactics.
Oh, you just missed Lieutenant Literal.
Where were you?
Hiding from A.R.G.U.S.?
No, A.R.G.U.S and I are cool.
They know I'm innocent.
I was trying to get rid
of this stupid headache.
But look what I liberated from one
of the transport guards.
Ice ice bandit. What is it?
I don't know,
but it was on Abra Kadabra
when they took him down.
Maybe it has something
to do with the obelisk.
- Yeah, maybe...
- Uh-uh.
Before you nerd out completely,
I need a favor.
What's wrong with me?
So much.
I'm kidding.
You're fine.
Every dark matter reading I'm seeing
is completely normal.
What does Caitlin have to say?
She says it's just a headache.
Hm. She's probably right.
[Caitlin] I told you so.
I know something is off.
[Caitlin]
We can't find anything.
Well, then look somewhere else.
I don't know
what else you want me to do.
Sorry, that was yelling at Caity.
Yeah. Okay. I'm going to let you two
work this out.
Chester and I are going to break open
Abra Kadabra's mysterious tech-cuff.
Missing those fancy trophies?
What's that? You're still looking
for the third one?
It's already here.
Picked it up last week.
Hey, keep it moving, Houdini.
What are you trying to pull?
Nothing.
It's already done.
[automated voice speaking]
Access granted.
And then there were three.
- Hey, save your work.
- Hey.
You can finish writing
in the beach villa
I just rented us in Monaco.
Oh. You mean leave right now?
Yeah. For a romantic villa in Monaco.
Barry.
Look, you're working.
I get that that's important.
But you were just staring
at a blank screen when I...
- Fathwoomed in.
- Yeah.
And you know what's great
when you're stuck?
Clearing your head in Monaco.
Cool breeze,
waves crashing on the white sand.
Barry, we have traveled the globe
nonstop all this past week.
Yeah, 'cause you deserve the best.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just...
I'm trying to sweep
my wife off her feet
for a romantic getaway.
Which I appreciate, but...
Iris, sweetie, please just let me
make this up to you. Please.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
All right, you know what? No.
I'll think of something else.
Yeah. Yes.
Yeah. Let's go.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Zoop me to paradise.
Don't you wanna pack your laptop?
Uh... No. You know what?
I need to take a break.
You're right. Surf and sand
sounds perfect right now.
[phone vibrating]
Kadabra's just escaped custody.
He's loose somewhere in A.R.G.U.S.
Go. Go!
[sighs]
[grunts]
Stand down. It's your last chance.
Flash being ruthless. I like it.
As much as I enjoy
the stink of desperation on you,
I'm afraid you're too late.
You're trapped
in a constrictive metallic halo.
The more you try to escape,
the tighter it gets.
So please try to escape.
The last time we met, you begged me
to find a glimmer of light in myself.
Well, I found that light,
that hope...
and then you stole it from me.
Now I'm going to take
something from you.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Let me make it
crystal clear for you, Flash.
You cannot defeat a man
who has lost everything.
[The Flash] What are you doing?
[Abra Kadabra] Creating a masterpiece.
Now, for my last trick...
I'm going to make your whole city...
disappear.
[grunts]
Do we have eyes on Kadabra?
Yes and no.
He's teleporting all over the city
with that obelisk ball thing.
I'm scanning.
We're picking up readings
of anti-matter energy.
[rapid beeping]
He created an anti-matter bomb.
That kind of power,
it could take out another Earth.
Or another universe.
Wait, what?
Are we about to have Crisis part two?
No, no. There's not enough
anti-matter energy for that,
thank the sequel gods.
But the core is roughly
the size of a baseball.
A baseball? Barry, a trace amount
nearly took out your leg.
Is it enough to destroy the city?
I'd say there's exactly enough.
Abra said his last trick
was to make the whole city disappear.
Destroying Central City
must be his plan.
- But why now?
- [Chester] I don't know. But guys...
Every time he teleports,
that bomb gains kinetic energy.
I think he's charging it.
And if I'm reading this right,
his bomb's already at 47%.
At this rate, it'll be fully charged
within the hour.
Okay, what do we do?
There's got to be a way
to disarm it, right?
I could use one of
my Atlantean plug-ins
to analyze the bomb's outer hull,
determine its density,
see if you can phase
through its surface...
and disarm it.
That's not your happy face.
[sighs]
The bomb is made of the same material
as the obelisks.
Pure Valorium.
[Chester] An Nth metal alloy? Not good.
It's impenetrable to anything
but the anti-matter itself.
Which means you can't access
the core and disarm it.
So no phasing.
Even if we could figure out
a way to catch Kadabra,
his teleportation pattern
is completely randomized.
So there's no way to catch him
until he stops moving
and detonates the bomb.
I should have known
Kadabra was up to something
when we caught him so easily.
He wanted to be in A.R.G.U.S.
We helped him get
the last piece of that weapon.
I just let it happen.
Barry, it's gonna be okay.
How? He has anti-matter,
the most dangerous substance
in existence.
And now,
if we can't figure something out,
the entire city,
millions of lives will be lost.
Because I got tricked. Again.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm just...
struggling with everything lately.
I tried to find you and...
Cisco told me what happened.
What did you mean when you
said that you were tricked again?
From the very first moment
that imposter walked into our home,
I should have seen it.
I should have known
that she wasn't you.
[sighs]
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
What happened with Mirror Iris
is not your fault.
Then whose fault was it?
I'm the one that didn't realize
I was living with a stranger.
And if I had, not only could
we have brought you back sooner,
maybe we could have stopped
Eva before she attacked
and the whole city
wouldn't be suffering right now.
When we got married,
I promised to always be by your side.
And I wasn't.
And I know it's stupid to think
if I buy you enough flowers
or make you the perfect dessert,
that's going to make up
for what I did, 'cause it won't.
But honestly,
I don't know what else to do.
Barry, you don't have to do anything.
You've got me,
and I'm never gonna leave.
And I need you to hear me
on this, okay?
Something terrible happened to you,
not because of you.
And that kind of trauma,
that doesn't go away
in a day or a week.
You have to...
[sighs]...face it.
Mirror Iris took
the best part of you,
your heart, and she used it
as a weapon against you.
She lied to you.
Being emotionally manipulated
by someone everything in your being
tells you to trust?
That is not your fault.
Every time I think
I couldn't possibly love you more...
You have a family, friends,
people that you care about.
Somewhere inside of you,
there must be a glimmer of light,
of hope.
Well, I found that light,
that hope...
and then you stole it from me.
- What?
- I know why Abra's doing this.
This is what we found embedded inside
Abra's annoyingly secure tech-cuff.
It's a Martian Memory Restorer.
It helps people get their pre-Crisis
memories back with a single touch.
How do you know that?
- 'Cause Cisco designed it.
- Whoa. But why?
So Laurel Lance and Mia Queen...
Okay, you know what?
It's not important.
The important thing is
I think Kadabra stole the MMR
in the future
and something in those pre-Crisis
memories brought him here.
So the reason he wants to
blow up the city could be in there.
Even if it is, it doesn't matter.
We don't have time to find it.
I mean, the human brain
is essentially capable
of storing trillions of bytes
of memories.
It would take us years
to find the one we need.
No, it won't.
I know how to stop Abra.
[Chester] Flash, Kadabra stopped
at Tagaloa Plaza.
Perfect timing, Flash.
You're just in time to witness
the complete annihilation
of Central City.
Now you'll finally understand
what it's like
when everything you love dies.
You were right, Kadabra.
We can't defeat you.
Which is why I'm not gonna try.
What happens if this doesn't work?
Then it's game over.
Trying to pull a trick of your own?
I wouldn't.
Your 21st-century brain
comes in a distant second
to my 64th-century intellect.
No, no tricks.
Just listen.
I know why you're doing this.
I know why you're hurting.
You don't know a damn thing about me.
Yes, I do! Yes, I do!
I also know killing innocent people
isn't the answer.
And it's not gonna change anything.
Destructions is the ultimate catalyst
for change.
See, people in my century
understand that.
You may be from the future...
but the reason that you're here?
You're trying to change the past.
No, leave that alone.
This is your family
from another timeline.
Only they're gone now, aren't they?
Thirteen months ago,
I started having dreams
of a life I never lived.
One where I was so...
happy.
I had to know what was causing them.
I ran every test on myself possible
using 64th-century technology.
What I found was
that somehow I'd experienced
a sudden increase
in my somatic memory cells.
Your memories were expanding.
More backwards 21st-century thinking.
I'd been exposed
to neuro-temporal displacement.
The kind that's created
when Speedsters disrupt time.
With my clue for the cause,
it led me to the Flash Museum.
You're obsessed
with the future, Flash.
Not now, but... oh, you will be.
I found so many
interesting things there,
including, to my surprise,
Cisco Ramon's archaic memory device.
It was damaged beyond repair.
I fixed it easily.
Ugh. This guy sucks.
You used it on yourself
and it gave you those memories back.
From a time before
everything changed.
With my memories restored,
I had proof
that the family from my dreams,
a wife and son
that I never knew existed, were real.
They were erased from existence
by what you did.
You were supposed to vanish
in your Crisis, Flash, not them.
But when you didn't,
my future changed.
They ceased to exist.
And I lost everything,
just like you will now.
Wait!
[powering up]
- [rapid beeping]
- Kadabra's weapon is 97% charged.
We have less than 90 seconds.
You can do this, Barry.
Crisis destroyed countless lives.
And yes, some of us survived.
It's not fair.
Now we have to carry on
for those who didn't.
I lost someone, too.
He was like a brother to me.
And ever since,
I've tried to honor his sacrifice.
You can do the same for your family.
I'm betting
you already tried to go back
before Crisis started
and you couldn't, right?
That's because that past
is from a multi-versal world
that no longer exists.
Killing me won't reset the timeline.
- That future is gone...
- Liar!
I will bring them back.
And if I can't,
then I'll take everything from you
the way I lost everything.
My pain is yours.
That's why you want
to destroy the city.
So you can make people
suffer like you.
Because you already know
killing me won't work.
Shut up.
You've run all the calculations.
You can't comprehend what I've done.
Yes, I can. I'm a scientist, too.
So tell me, what are the odds
that doing this will bring them back?
Barry, it's about to explode.
I haven't run a calculation
on the timeline yet
where they return.
How would they feel
knowing you annihilated
an entire city in their name?
Making other people hurt
won't erase your suffering.
The only way for you to heal
is to face your trauma.
[Allegra] He did it!
Without throwing a single punch.
Yeah. The Flash
doesn't need big fists.
He's got a big heart.
Luca.
That was my son.
Amelie, my wife.
And your friend?
His name was Oliver.
My name's Philippe.
What am I supposed to do now?
I can't go on without them.
The people we love never leave us.
Let that love help you
find hope again in this world.
I don't get it.
We're mortal enemies in the future.
Why are you doing this?
So the next time we meet,
maybe we won't be.
Fair enough.
[rumbling]
This isn't me.
[rapid beeping]
I'm picking up
enough seismic activity
to rattle us back to the Stone Age.
Detecting a massive biosignature.
Barry, whatever's causing
these tremors,
it's headed right towards you.
Barry!
[roaring]
Barry, get up.
Get up, Barry.
You are an ugly one.
I've got this, Flash.
Stand down, beautiful...
or I'll use every ounce
of this anti-matter bomb
to blow you to kingdom come.
[roaring]
That's impossible.
[rapid beeping]
Fine, let's see
how you like this trick.
[clattering]
Philippe?
What have you done?
[roars]
[yells]
[roaring]
[groans]
Barry!
[Caitlin] Respiratory distress,
elevated blood pressure.
He's crashing.
- [bones cracking]
- [groans]
[roars]
[Barry] Philippe was trying to heal,
just like the rest of us.
This isn't right.
He died a hero.
That means something.
What was that thing anyway?
Death itself, maybe.
Whatever it was,
it absorbed the full power
of an anti-matter bomb.
- That means it's...
- Unstoppable.
But hey, you're...
You're okay, right?
[phone vibrating]
Yeah. Yeah, since we rebooted
the Speed Force,
I'm faster than ever.
So's my speed healing.
Thank goodness.
Great. The brass are dumping
a liaison from the Governor's Police
Compliance Commission in my lap.
I got to go figure out
how to explain all this to her.
Well, I have lots of meta-clients
that need my legal expertise.
How about I drop you at the station?
So what do we do now?
Same thing we always do.
Get to work stopping that thing
before it kills again.
Allegra... [clears throat]
What you said about my article...
If you're going to say I came off
kinda harsh, you're not the first.
I'm glad you told me
what I needed to hear.
But it's still hard to take
from an intern.
Which is why I'm making you
a staff writer.
Wait. You're what?
Congratulations.
You earned it.
Thanks, boss.
You're amazing.
You helped me
get through to Philippe,
and that saved the city.
It's called teamwork.
We're Barry and Iris.
It's the strongest superpower
there is.
So I was thinking tonight
maybe we just go home,
have a normal dinner,
maybe eat a frozen pizza
on the couch?
Sounds perfect.
But...
Nothing, I just...
I was thinking of something
I have to do tomorrow.
Come on, let's go.
Hi.
Um...
I am no stranger to trauma,
but when Eva McCulloch
threatened our city, I was...
taken against my will
to a terrifying place.
A place that you all know.
Somewhere filled
with loneliness and dread,
the same dread
that you all felt, too.
And that is where I spent
the next three months.
Three months where I couldn't be
with my loved ones.
And yes, I feel...
angry, and I feel...
sorry for myself, and I hate
that I feel both of those things,
and I wish that all of that
was yesterday's pain
and that today I could feel
healed and whole.
But I now understand
that I can't heal
if I don't allow myself permission
to feel what I'm feeling.
What happened to us...
was not right.
And...
if you are hurting,
if you feel angry,
if the constant presence of those
emotions is exhausting you...
you are not alone.
I am with you.
You know, my dad once said that
there is as much beauty in this life
as there is pain.
You just have to look for it.
But most of all...
we have to look for it
within each other.
And that's gonna take some time.
But it is time
that we can spend together.
[sighs]
Thank you.
- Boss, that was...
- Everything that I needed.
Thank you.
Well, I guess you know what
you're gonna say in your article now.
I'm not sure that's big enough.
I think I have to reach people
on a whole different level.
I owe them that.
Come on.
- [beeping]
- [sighs]
Chester, if you're going to be
a part of Team Flash,
then you have to stop
beating me at Fortnite.
Cisco. Thank God you're here.
There's something I need to show you.
You still having those headaches?
Nope.
Not anymore.
Okay. Why...
Hello, Cisco.
How great is this?