- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present,
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- I'll deliver it myself.
- That is Eobard Thawne,
the Reverse Flash.
He killed my mother.
- I didn't know that.
- My life is a million times
better
and it's all because of you,
Gracie.
- She may never wake.
- Every meta will die.
- This is a DNA sample
from Cicada.
- We can make
a meta-human cure.
- What if the key to defeating
him is appealing to his heart?
- How do we do that?
- By saving his child.
We need to wake up Grace.
- I want you to think about
the biggest secret
in your life.
The one you keep from
the people that you love
or even from yourself.
I want you to imagine
what would happen
if that secret got out.
Remember when you asked
me that?
I've been using all of
your training.
Studying my pulse,
managing micro-expressions,
limiting non-congruent
gestures,
destroying any piece
of evidence.
I don't know how much longer
I can keep this up.
And not just because of
the risks.
[indistinct chatter]
But because the closer
I get to my parents,
the more I feel like
I'm hurting them.
Data entry complete, Gideon.
- Thank you, Nora West-Allen.
Shall I send this
to the usual recipient?
- Yes.
Send it to Eobard Thawne,
priority level urgent.
[dramatic music]
- You ready for this?
- Dad, I'm just...I'm not
fast enough yet.
- No backing out now, this is
the biggest race of your life.
Get ready, set, go!
- Not really. Dad, Dad...
Wait, wait!
Oh, God.
[yelps]
- Whoa, whoa.
Gotcha.
- This is so embarrassing.
I'm really good at the ice
skating game on my Pocket Pal!
- Okay, you're just gonna bend
your knees...
- Kay.
- And lead forward a little.
Just, yeah.
- [gasps]
- Yeah.
- I'm doing it.
- You're doing it.
- I'm skating.
This is like schway city, Mom.
Thanks.
[laughs]
- Look at you guys.
Such a mom.
- What? What about you?
You're the one who sprang
for ice skating and game night.
- Yeah, well,
I know when Nora got hurt,
I got a little frustrated.
And now, I mean, we have
an actual plan to stop Cicada.
- Waking up his niece to appeal
to his heart.
- I know Dwyer's a killer,
but he's still a person,
and he loves Grace
just like we love Nora.
So I don't know.
I just feel like
everything's heading
in the right direction.
- Here I come. Coming in.
Here we go.
- I'm sorry,
why are you wearing a helmet?
I thought you were made
of rubber.
- Somebody's gotta set a good
example for these kids.
- Well...I thought you grew up
on the ice.
- Well, I did, basically,
my mom dated a zamboni
operator, so...
- And I tell you where I'm from
we don't date zamboni drivers.
Why is that?
Because there are no zambonis.
How do we clear the ice?
All winter long,
we are on our hands and knees
with a squeegee in hand.
Let me tell you.
Best eight months of
the year for this guy.
- It's a really great story,
Sherlock.
- Sherloque.
- You know,
speaking of squeegeeing,
you know who could use
a good squeegeeing
is Larry Blumenthal.
He's dead.
- Larry Blumenthal is dead?
- Yeah.
- The patent registrar across
the hall from you
with the 400 square footage...
both: And the courtyard views?
- Yeah, dead as a doornail.
You can have that place
if you want it. Yours to rent.
- What? Oh, my God.
This is perfect.
I mean, my ad revenue has been
up this quarter, so...
- Yeah, with the extra space
you'd be able to hire
editors, photographers.
- I could turn my blog into
a real newspaper.
- Oh, my package has arrived.
- What package?
- This is the solution
to all our problems.
Allez, les amis.
We must go.
[upbeat music]
Madames et monsieurs,
may I present to you
La Machine à Mémoire,
or as they say in Amérique,
you know...
- The Memory Machine.
Oui, Iris. Memory Machine.
Many times...
I have entered into
people's minds
using this very technology.
From the unfortunate
comatose victims
of the Summerholt Institute
to, yes,
Jervis Tetch himself,
the Terrible Mad Hatter Killer
from Earth-221.
- I come back from Tannhauser
for one second,
just borrowing a splicer
for the meta cure
and what do I find?
This, this...
- Machine à Mémoire.
- Whatever. How did you even
get this here from Earth-221?
- Well, I used the Forerunner
Multiversal Delivery Service.
You don't use it? You don't
have a gold card like me?
Maybe I'll get you a discount.
- We don't need a discount.
All right,
we just need to wake up Grace.
This'll wake her up, right?
- So in most coma patients,
high traffic areas
of brain activity
go dormant and the low traffic
areas spring to life,
but unfortunately,
Grace isn't normal.
Not only has her coma lasted
longer than the average,
but her consciousness
has isolated itself
into one specific region,
her long-term memories.
- It will be so facile,
easy peasy for you.
All you do is you transmit
your brainwaves
into Grace's memories, right?
And then you'll lead
her consciousness
out of a neural nexus portal.
[snaps fingers]
And Grace awakens.
- It's sort of like when
Barry woke me up
when the Thinker trapped me.
- Surprisingly, that sounds
kind of easy peasy.
- As long as Grace's
unusual brain damage
doesn't cause any
unforeseen risks.
- This is why I suggest
you travel in pairs
when you're using
this technology.
Every time I enter into
someone's memories
when I use this I went
with my partner for sure.
- Your partner's name didn't
happen to be Watson, did it?
- [scoffs]
- No, his name was not Watson.
His name was Watsune.
Yes, together we went through
dozens of minds, together...
until one time I found myself
in a memory of a motel room
in Montreal
where what do I find
but Watsune inflagrante deli
in interpersonal relationship
with my wife,
fourth wife, but still.
- You're saying you could see
your partner's memories?
- It's a possible side effect
of traveling in pairs.
And speaking of which,
which pairs would like
to volunteer for this mission?
I suggest the speedsters
for this to be accomplished
so quick.
- Yeah.
- Elected.
- Hey, if you see a memory of
me stealing blank Scrabble tile
it's not what it looks like,
all right?
- [laughs]
That's a good one, Dad.
- All that is left is to
connect this transceiver disc
to Grace's EEG
and we can transmit.
- Great.
- Right.
- All right,
first thing tomorrow,
we save Grace.
- Any big plans for
the night off?
- [groans]
I'm gonna crash.
Killer Frost was up
all night watching movies
from her two favorite Johns,
Woo and Hughes.
- Huh, I'm more of
a Ford and Waters man myself,
but I will be up all night
yet again working with
the radiated meta-human
sample you guys got me.
There's something missing with
this cure.
- All right,
I'll see you guys later.
- All right.
- Night.
- You know, there's something
that I'm missing too.
Your freshly healed hands.
- Odd choice of words.
- Well, I'm meeting with
an informant tonight
and he might have a lead
on Dwyer's location,
but I'm not sure
if I should trust him.
- So you need me to vibe him.
Look, man.
I should really be working
on this cure.
But my splicer algorithm
won't technically
be done until 3:00 a.m.
- Thanks, man, this is,
this is really important work.
- Okay.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Okay, Gideon,
how do I hack this thing
so that Dad won't see
my memories?
- In any configuration,
if you and Barry Allen
go in together,
you still risk exposing
your memories.
- So I can't do anything.
♪ ♪
[machine warbles]
[dramatic music]
Gideon, is that...
- Grace Gibbons' brain waves.
It would appear
Sherloque Wells
has planted
the transceiver disc.
- So I can go in alone.
And I'll be back before
anyone notices,
but by that time Grace'll be
awake anyway.
♪ ♪
- Activating brain wave
transmission.
In three, two, one.
[ethereal whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
- CCPD?
[suspenseful music]
- Okay, Jones,
here's the kid.
- We found her in the car
hiding under the seat.
Her parents were at the ATM
when the meta attacked.
- Damn.
We located her next of kin?
- Maybe an uncle.
Still tracking down
his last known address.
- Well, she can't sleep on
this bench.
We've gotta get her
out of here.
- God, poor kid.
- Who are you?
- You can see me?
Oh, right,
you're Grace's consciousness
in her old memory.
I'm Nora.
- Can you take me
to my parents?
- No, um, I can't,
but if you come with me,
I can help you feel better.
♪ ♪
You know,
when I was your age,
I had a friend just like this.
I bet he'd like
to feel better too.
Yeah.
[tender music]
Okay.
All right, Gracie,
let's get you through
this portal and out of
your coma
before anyone notices
I snuck in here.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[tense music]
Oh, no.
I'm trapped.
- We're gonna find
a way out of here, I promise.
- I feel like I've been in this
police station for a long time,
and now I'm gonna be here
forever, aren't I?
Just leave me alone.
- You know,
when I was your age,
I had to come to this
very same police station
all by myself too.
It's kind of scary in here.
- I'm not scared.
- Well, I was.
I'm scared all the time.
In fact, once, there was
this really bad guy
and he wanted to hurt a whole
lot of people on a plane.
- A meta?
- Mm-hmm.
- But I helped stop him.
- Whoa, really?
- I was terrified, though.
But you know what my secret is?
I just imagine what will happen
after I do the thing.
Do you want to try it?
Okay, close your eyes,
and think about what will
happen once you're out of here.
- I'll see Uncle Orlin.
[tender music]
- Let's find our way
out of here, okay?
- So I can't use "Gazette"?
"Chronicle"?
So the only name that's cleared
is "Central City Citizen."
[door squeaking]
Uh, yeah, yeah, thanks.
- Hey, who was that
on the phone?
- Um, a lawyer, she was
helping answer some questions
about me starting a newspaper.
- That's cool.
What'd she say?
- You know, it doesn't matter.
I-I'm actually not sure
that the timing is right,
and I really just want to focus
on team Flash
and stopping Cicada.
- Yeah, but...
[cell phone buzzing]
Oh, hold on.
Hey.
Slow down, slow down.
It's Sherloque.
Nora did what?
- Why would Nora go in alone?
- And why isn't she out yet?
- My working theory is that
Grace's unique brain damage
has caused her brain
to act defensively,
so when it sensed
an outside presence,
it moved all of its
neural nexus pathways
to seal the exits like
a-a quarantine procedure.
- Grace's brain thinks
Nora's a pathogen.
- Yes, we can expect its
synaptic defense mechanisms
to try and eliminate her.
- Remember I told you about
the Mad Hatter?
He was also brain damaged,
so after my dispute with
Watsune and my fourth wife,
Watsune pursued the case
on his own
until the day I found him
hooked up to the
Machine à Mémoire brain-dead.
- You knew this was
a possibility?
What happened to easy peasy?
- That's why I say go in
in pairs.
- Barry, we have to go in
after her.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I looked all over CCPD.
There's no sign of the portal.
- How could you have looked
everywhere?
You were gone for about
two seconds.
- Well, I'm really fast.
I-I used to run track
in high school.
Go CC Squirrels.
Look, Grace, is there anywhere
else you can take me?
Another memory?
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
Where are we?
- My house.
- [growling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Uncle Orlin!
- Hey!
Aww. Hey, kiddo.
How you doing?
How was your day?
- Let me run through
this again.
So Mr. Truck, you said.
You've seen Cicada here?
- Dude's been up in here like
a mean fungus.
- I see, and how is
the White Russian Hacker?
- You wanna focus up here?
So can you tell me
was he violent?
- Hell yeah, every Thursday,
comes in and assaults
anyone in here
- Unnecessary.
But okay.
[heavy metal music]
- ♪ Running, screaming ♪
♪ The bad clubs in sin ♪
♪ Take me up, terror ♪
♪ ♪
- You're talking about
a band named "Sickada"?
- Yeah, bro.
- You said "that dude"
assaulted people.
- He assaults everyone in here
with that terrible music.
- Dibs.
- Well, that didn't pan out
the way that I hoped.
We will have two
Mother-In-Laws, please.
- No, no, no, no. Truck,
thank you for your time.
I think we're done here.
- One drink.
I'm paying.
- [scoffs]
One drink,
but only because
you never pay for anything ever
and I'm really curious
to see what hell looks like
frozen over.
- We can't warn her
we're coming?
- We wanted to install
an emergency beacon,
but it didn't work.
- So once you enter,
it'll create a new portal.
You'll only have a few moments
to find Grace and Nora
before Grace's brain tries
to seal it off.
Remember,
if you die in there...
- We die out here.
I remember from DeVoe.
We're gonna save her,
I promise.
- Commencing brainwave
transmission.
♪ ♪
Good luck.
[dramatic music]
[futuristic warbling]
- CCPD.
[tranquil, inquisitive music]
♪ ♪
All right, come on.
- We found her hiding in
the last car under the seat.
- And her parents?
- No idea.
She was on the Red Line
headed downtown.
Must've jumped the turnstile
at Fourth and Waid.
- We can't just let her sleep
on this bench.
- Oh, my God. Barry.
- Wait, is that Joe West's
granddaughter?
- Nora? Hey, Nora.
Someone get her.
- I don't think we're
in Grace's memories.
We're in Nora's.
[ethereal whooshing]
- There's been no changes
in Grace's brain activity.
- [snaps fingers]
But look.
Nora's brain activity
has tripled.
That means...
- Barry and Iris are
in Nora's memories.
- How did we end up in Nora's
childhood memories?
- I have no idea.
I also have no clue
how we're gonna rescue Nora
from here.
- Okay. Okay, we're in a memory
within a memory, right?
- Yeah.
- So if we went through
a portal, then...
- It should take us into Grace.
Okay, yeah, we just have to
wander through Nora's memories
until we find where
the portal went.
- Okay.
[footsteps pattering]
- Maybe she'll lead us
right there.
[indistinct chatter]
Whoa.
What happened here?
- I guess in Nora's future,
S.T.A.R. Labs is...
- The Flash Museum.
- [laughs]
No way.
Look at this.
Flash toys and Flash phones.
Flash rings.
Are you kidding? Wow.
- This is all gonna go
to your head, isn't it?
- Oh, you know what?
It looks like it might.
- Oh, that is very cute.
- [laughs]
- Hey, I found her.
[tender music]
You think we can talk to her?
- No. I wish.
This might be the only time
I get to see her at this age.
Nora's consciousness
isn't here, though.
It's in Grace.
This is a fixed memory.
We can't interfere.
♪ ♪
- When I was ten, I wasn't
running away from home.
- That's 'cause you were
a good kid.
I ran away all the time.
- Yeah, only 'cause you were
trying to see your dad.
Not 'cause you were running
from someone.
Oh, hey, we should keep trying
to find the portal.
♪ ♪
- Come on, Gracie, no cussing.
- Please, can we, please?
- Okay, fine.
A rare, old bird is a pelican
whose beak can hold more
than his belly can.
both: He can hold in his beak
enough food for a week.
- But I'm darned if I know
how the hell he can.
- [laughs]
- Grace, I was thinking maybe
we could go now
and look for the portal?
Is something burning?
- Oh, crap.
I mean, crud.
- He thinks he takes
care of me now,
but I really take care of him.
[nostalgic music]
- Okay, kiddo,
you better eat up.
We've got a big day.
- This is...
- First we're going
to the zoo...
- This is an interesting
doll house.
- We're gonna get ice cream,
and then...
- Can't forget the fair.
- Fair?
Where you got hurt.
Grace, I-I think that's where
the portal is.
Can you take me there?
To the last place
that you remember?
Okay.
[rock music playing]
- Hey, check her out.
She's right up your alley.
You should buy her a drink.
- Damn.
Look at that hand stitching.
No, no, I did not come here
to admire jackets.
I came here to vibe and inform.
Is it just me
or are there a lot
of ladies in leather in here?
- Yep, singles night.
- It's quite a coincidence.
- Is it?
What is it
you're always saying?
"I smell a mystery"?
- That is trademarked.
- I can vibe the anxiety coming
off of you right now.
This whole thing was a setup.
Of course your informant
didn't know Cicada.
- I mean, he knew of Cicada.
- You lied to me,
you wasted my time
so I could be your
wingman tonight?
- No, no, no, dude,
it's not like that.
- You know, just when I think
you're growing up,
you go ahead and do something
that shows me
you're just as selfish
as the day we met.
That's for the drinks.
Excuse me.
- Wait.
These guys get their own wing?
- Who is Cicada?
Officials believe...
- Barry, maybe we should keep
looking for the portal.
- Yeah.
- But when Cicada resurfaced
in 2024
after the Flash vanished,
some were left to speculate
that Cicada is not a man
at all,
but an immortal monster.
All we know for sure
is his body count,
152 victims and rising.
- Wait, what?
I knew we never caught Cicada,
but he never stops killing?
- Flash did everything
he could,
but Cicada killed more people
than Zoom
or even the Red Death.
And the way the city saw
the Flash, his legacy...
it was never the same.
- Nora West-Allen, you are in
serious trouble, young lady.
- Grace, what are we
doing here?
- You wanted to go
to my last memory.
- Yeah, but I thought that was
supposed to be at the fair.
[EKG beeping]
Grace?
Hello?
- The destructive phenomenon
emanated from a satellite
that had fallen into
a decaying orbit.
Thankfully,
before the satellite
could strike the city...
- How does she remember this?
- A catastrophic event...
- A new meta was last seen
jumping off a building
in order to evade capture
after...
[eerie warbling, metal clangs]
- [gasps]
- I'm gonna make this
right, Gracie.
Every meta will die.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Grace, how did you hear Orlin
that night?
You were in a coma.
- I know.
[whispering]
But I've been listening.
- You have to stop.
- Not until I'm finished.
- Did they come after
you tonight?
- I killed his partner, Vibe,
but there was
a woman there too,
banged me up pretty bad.
She had speed.
I think she's
the Flash's daughter.
[intense whirring]
♪ ♪
- Grace, I don't know
what you think Orlin said...
- You said you looked
everywhere.
I get it now.
You have speed.
You're her, aren't you?
You're the Flash's daughter.
You're the one
who hurt my uncle.
♪ ♪
- Grace, I want to help you.
- No, you don't.
Uncle Orlin told me about you.
You and your dad are trying
to hurt him.
- Only because he's trying
to hurt other people,
innocent people!
[screams]
- No, he only hurts metas,
like the one who killed
my parents.
Like you!
You're a meta and a liar!
- All metas aren't bad.
[glass shattering]
[screams]
- My uncle is a hero.
He protects people,
and I protect my uncle!
[electricity crackles]
- [screams]
[gasps]
My speed's gone.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Did you think that
you could run away
and I wouldn't figure out
where you went?
It's my job to find out
the truth.
I'm a reporter.
- You're always a reporter.
Why not be my mom for once?
- Oh, yeah?
How's this for being your mom?
You are never coming back
to this place again.
Let's go.
Excuse me,
what is in your pocket?
Hand that over right now.
- It's not yours.
- Well, it is now. There are
consequences to your actions.
Hand it over.
- I hate you.
♪ ♪
- Leave it.
Let's go.
[solemn music]
- [sighs]
- Iris, that wasn't you.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, but it will be, Barry.
Nora's gonna grow up
hating her mother.
- No, she won't. You're gonna
make different choices.
If you don't wanna be that
person that we just saw,
don't be that person.
- I know.
I know you keep saying that,
Barry,
and that's what I'm trying
to do.
I had a moment today
and I thought that
maybe if I could change
the timeline now,
that even in the smallest way
that...I don't know.
That everything in the future
would be somehow different.
- This is why you changed
your mind about the newspaper.
- When I talked to the lawyer,
I asked her to check
a dozen potential names,
and guess which one
was the only one that cleared.
The "Central City Citizen."
- I know it's got baggage,
but it's just a name.
- Is it? I mean, we've been
looking at that front page
for four years.
"Flash Missing,
Vanishes in Crisis."
And I'm the one that writes
that article, Barry.
I just thought that,
I don't know,
maybe if I don't start
the paper, that...
- Iris, this is your dream,
and the city needs
somebody like you.
- Yeah, but, Barry,
look where it gets us.
These are Nora's memories
right now in this timeline
after she interfered.
♪ ♪
Let's keep looking
for the portal, okay?
Nora needs our help.
♪ ♪
[dramatic, eerie music]
- I'll have whatever
he's having.
- All I want to order right now
is a Lyft out of here,
but I get no bars in this bar,
so maybe I'll just have to
leave the old-fashioned way
and breach on out of here.
- Look, Cisco, I'm...
Sorry I lied to you.
- Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to all
the meta-humans out there
still waiting for a cure,
for their right to choose if
they want these powers or not.
- Before I was
The Elongated Man,
when I was just nobody
Ralph Dibny,
I could do whatever I wanted
whenever I wanted,
but I didn't have any friends
to do those things with.
♪ ♪
So I just thought if, uh,
we're getting a night off
from stopping Cicada,
we could just
go out and...
have some fun, you know?
- And I want that too,
but after we figure out
this cure.
♪ ♪
- You know,
my mom's friend Doug,
he had a saying.
"If you're always waiting
to live your life,
you're gonna die
before it starts."
And Doug, he would know.
He operated a zamboni.
May he rest in peace.
All right,
I'ma go outside,
see if I can stretch
my arm high enough
to get you some
cell phone service.
- Dark and Stormy
on the house.
- Do I look that pathetic?
- You look like you belong here
about as much as I do.
- Thought I was coming here
for a business meeting.
- What do you do,
sell leather?
- Nope.
- Tattoo artist.
- Mm-mm.
- Gun for hire.
- [laughs]
Trust me.
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
- Well,
I'm a photographer,
so it looks like we're both
a little lost.
- So what's your excuse?
- Taking pictures hasn't made
me rich, yet,
so I bartend to pay rent.
My sister hooked me up here.
Forgot to mention
I'd be working in hell.
- [chuckles]
Sisters.
If I looked at the DNA
of two siblings,
one who became a meta
and one who didn't,
I would have a close enough
genetic match
to isolate the part
of the genome
that controls meta-genes.
[dramatic music]
I'm sorry,
did I just say that out loud?
- [laughs]
Yeah, you did.
- I-I just...that...I...
Cisco.
- Camilla.
- Nice to meet you.
- I can't find the portal
anywhere.
I can't even get out of Nora's
memories of this one day.
- Barry, get down!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[ominous hissing]
[machine beeping]
- Nora's in trouble.
Grace's defense mechanisms
must be attacking her.
- She's not the only one
who's in trouble.
- We need to get them
out of there now.
♪ ♪
- It's Nora's
defense mechanism.
[dramatic music]
[ominous hissing]
[elevator dings]
♪ ♪
- What am I supposed to do now?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- Nora, is that you?
- Caitlyn!
- Yes, I told you
the M.A.D. 2.0
could complete
your emergency beacon.
Uh, Nora, your parents
went into your memories.
Uh, let me conference them in.
- Sorry, my parents went where?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[cell phone ringing]
[both gasp]
- Iris West-Allan.
- Mom? Dad?
- Nora, are you okay?
- So listen.
We made an important discovery.
- To get you out of there.
- The portals are hidden
in perception gaps.
- Things that you remember
the way you want them to be,
not the way they actually were.
- 'Cause you're in denial
or your perception
was colored by anger
or what have you.
- So these defense mechanisms,
they're composed of synapses.
If you can break down the
synapses in the false memory,
that will reveal
the real memory
and the synaptic jolt
will expose the portal.
- Okay, so...okay, well,
how do we do that?
- Well, uh,
we'll have to call you back.
You're burning up.
- [stuttering and whimpering]
- Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Perception gaps.
The dollhouse.
♪ ♪
- How do we know which memories
weren't real?
- Of course... Iris,
it's the Hall of Villains.
You and Nora.
- Barry, I still dampen
Nora's power.
She still grows up hating me.
This is my future.
- No, no, it's not.
It's just a memory,
one warped from the perspective
of a sad, angry, little kid
that ran away from home.
Don't you get it? That person
that we saw in there,
the bad mom
that Nora told us about,
she doesn't even exist
in any timeline.
I told you you had to be
different in the future,
but I was wrong.
You don't have to change
who you are.
You don't even have to change
the name of your newspaper.
I know any future with you
in it is gonna be a good one.
You just gotta believe
that too.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- Please,
this memory isn't real.
Your uncle's house, I don't
think it's really like this.
- Okay, better eat up, kiddo.
We got a big day...
[grunts]
- [screams]
- Grace, get down!
[ominous hissing]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- I don't see
the portal anywhere.
[electricity crackles]
Barry, it's working!
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
- Death. Failure.
Another broken family.
This is the legacy I gave you.
♪ ♪
- Nobody breaks up my family,
you son of a bitch.
♪ ♪
[epic music]
[electricity crackles]
♪ ♪
Oh, no.
You dropped your toy.
- I just wanted to see
the museum.
- I know, honey,
but you ran away.
I didn't know where you went.
I was afraid you could have
gotten hurt.
- You said that the museum
reminded you of Dad
'cause Dad was the Flash's
number one fan.
So I wanted to see it
'cause I love the Flash too.
It's not fair.
- I know, honey.
I know it's not fair.
I love you, Nora.
Your dad loved you too.
So, so much.
♪ ♪
Come here, girl.
[electricity crackles]
♪ ♪
- Come on. We gotta go.
Let's go get Nora.
- Grace, I know you're afraid.
You think that you'll never
be as happy as you were
that day with your uncle.
That's why you try to remember
it as perfect,
but things can be
that good, Grace.
You just have to wake up.
♪ ♪
And then you and me
and my parents,
we can all help
your uncle together.
♪ ♪
- You're a liar.
[tense music]
[ominous hissing]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Grace.
- Maybe you don't have anyone
who cares about you,
but I have someone
who cares about me,
and I'm the only one
who can help him.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[blow lands]
- Mom.
- Hey.
- She's not coming.
- What?
- Hurry!
- Come on. Come on.
♪ ♪
[ethereal whooshing]
- They're okay.
- [whistles]
[placid music]
♪ ♪
- Neural oscillations
are normal.
You three are
perfectly healthy.
Oh, and we think
we've figured out
how you two ended up
in Nora's brain.
- That is a satellite shard
full of dark matter
in Grace's head.
-Mon dieu.
- Sometimes surgeons leave
a piece of shrapnel
in a patient's brain if
it's too dangerous to remove,
and we think that the dark
matter was seeping out
to create a barrier around
her brain.
We can't go back in
as long as it's there.
It's too dangerous.
- Well, we need to find another
way to stop Cicada.
- I think I might be able
to help with that.
[rapid scribbling]
♪ ♪
It's the inside
of Dwyer's house.
- Whoa.
- Damn.
- I mean, that's great.
But why did you go in
without us?
We had a plan.
- No, I know, um...
You know, just with the machine
being ready
and knowing that Cicada
was still out there
I guess I just, um, I got
a little excessive.
- It's not the only reason,
though, right?
It was protecting her secret.
- What secret is that?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Well, her feelings for her
mother when she was a child.
Must be painful memories.
♪ ♪
Is that correct, Nora?
- Yeah, exactly.
♪ ♪
- Okay, um, let's get started
on this lead.
Good job, Nora.
- Thanks.
♪ ♪
- Monsieur Allen, just for my
records of today's events,
what was the defense mechanism
Nora was using?
- It was one of the costumes
from the museum.
- What costume?
- The Reverse Flash.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[peaceful music]
- Surprise!
- Happy first day
in your new office.
- You're so sweet.
[laughs]
- So have you decided what
you're gonna name the paper?
- I don't know.
"Central City Citizen"
has a certain ring to it.
- You sure?
- Yeah, you were right.
Future isn't always
what it seems.
We decide what it gets to be.
- So, um, I just have to
tell you one little thing.
See that ledger down there?
That's the year the paper
was founded in my time.
- 2021.
♪ ♪
That's two years from now.
[futuristic warbling]
- You're changing
the future already.
♪ ♪
- Hey, um, I gotta find Cisco,
but I'll see you guys later,
all right?
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Let's head back.
[chuckles]
- Mom?
- Yeah?
- Dad told me about the memory
that you saw.
- I know it wasn't real, Nora,
but it must have come
from a very real place.
You must have been so angry
with me to see me that way.
- I was angry all the time.
Angry for not getting
to have a dad,
angry 'cause nobody seemed to
understand what I was feeling.
And it didn't matter
what you did or said, Mom.
I was always gonna be angry
at you...
because you were there.
- You're going through
a lot, Nora.
- But so were you.
I mean, I thought
you were trying
to stop me from being me,
but you were trying to stop me
from being Dad.
I mean, ending up like him.
You guys had a whole
life together
and a child,
and he vanished.
I-I can't imagine how hard
that must have been for you.
And from that day, you...
you were protecting me.
I-I get that now.
So sorry for the way
that I treated you,
both back then and now
when I first got here.
You didn't deserve that.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
You're an amazing woman,
Nora West-Allen.
I will always love you,
past, present, and future.
- I love you too, Mom.
It's hard to keep a secret,
but it's a lot easier
when you're reminded
why you're doing it.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
I met someone who told me
that she would do anything
to protect her family.
She helped me see
that... so would I.
My parents can't know that
you're helping me stop Cicada.
There's too much at risk.
And I'll do anything
to protect them.
Even lie.
[siren wailing in distance]
[eerie music]
- Liar.
Liar.
Liar. Liar.
Nora lied to me.
♪ ♪
She'll pay.
They'll all pay.
[dramatic music intensifying]
[electricity crackles]
- Doug was right.
Going out there,
doing the ice skating thing,
that was definitely
the right thing to do.
- Yeah, all Doug,
may he rest in peace.
- Let's pour one out
for the guy.
- Camilla?
The bartender?
- Uh, excuse me.
- Dude, nice.
- All right, all right.
- Yeah.
- Hey, did you guys
make a breakthrough
with the meta-human cure?
- We did.
I managed to locate
a pair
of meta-non-meta siblings,
so this cure,
it's as good as done.
- All right, good,
because I've been thinking.
[suspenseful music]
I want to use the cure
on Cicada.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.