Cleaned, corrected,
dashes removed and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I'm the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother
Killed by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
But secretly I use my speed
to fight crime
And find others like me,
And one day I'll find
who killed my mother...
- Mom.
- And get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously, on the Flash
and arrow...
I'm just not sure I'm like you,
Oliver.
I don't know
if I can be some vigilante.
You can be better,
because you can inspire people
In a way that I never could.
You said you were writing
about me to bring hope
To someone you care about.
How would he feel if doing that
put you in harm's way?
You're giving hope
to a lot of people.
So I'm doing this for them.
Barry, when you met me,
Oliver, and Dig, we were this
well-oiled archery machine,
But it didn't
start out that way.
I'm sorry I wasn't there
for you tonight.
You're worth being on time for.
Everyone on this planet,
at some point in their lives,
Has had a major case
of the feels...
Those days when your heart
is just too small
To hold the big things
you're feeling.
Today's one of those days.
We think of our emotions like
they're these unique,
Personal phenomena,
That no one has ever felt
what we have felt.
There is a basis in science
for every emotion we feel...
Anger, love.
As a scientist,
I know there's nothing magical
About what makes us feel
something for someone else...
But then I see her smile.
Man, that cannot be science.
♪ Whoo, I want it, whoo ♪
Oh, and there's a fresh bottle
in the fridge
When she wakes up from her nap.
Thank you.
Sir?
Help you with something?
Thanks.
I'll be just fine on my own.
Sir, you're not allowed
to be back here.
Nothing to get upset about.
Barry, bank robbery
in progress
- At Cunningham and Sampere.
- I got it.
Wait, that's where I bank.
Once super thieves showed up,
I went mattress.
I've already missed the gym.
Ugh, no.
Five more minutes.
Come on,
we never get to sleep in.
I know.
But your dad hates tardiness.
Buzzkill.
The buzziest.
Another picture of the Flash
came in.
See?
That red blur?
How do you know that wasn't
photoshopped?
It wasn't.
It's not a hoax
or a mass hallucination.
You know, every day, someone new
accepts the impossible
and believes in him.
Why can't you?
I believe in what I can see...
What I can touch...
What I can feel.
- Which means I believe in you.
- Mm.
Do you mind?
Thanks, man.
- Hey.
- Busy morning.
Witnesses reported
seeing a red streak?
Joe, you should have seen it.
It was like everybody in here
Was trying to kill each other.
I got here just in time.
Well, it must've
been a diversion,
Because there's 1/2 million
bucks missing from the vault.
There's a tracer
in the cash stacks.
We're trying to find the signal.
Meantime, any idea what could've
caused such mass...
- This?
- A neurotoxin, maybe.
I'm going to swab some surfaces,
see what I can find,
But I think maybe
they got whammied.
- Did you just say "whammied"?
- I got so angry.
I can't believe I did that.
I would never hurt anybody.
- You have to believe me.
- I do.
Something is happening
in this city
And everyone wants to pretend
like it isn't, but it is,
And I think we should do
something about it.
My boyfriend has decided
we need to eat healthy at home,
So work is now the only place
I can eat what I like.
Oh, I'm sorry, were you saying
something, detective?
The blur, the Flash,
the man in the red suit...
Whatever he's called...
he was spotted at the bank
- this morning.
- You mean the bank
that was robbed
of 1/2 million dollars,
where a dozen people tried
to murder each other,
And you think our attention
should be focused on
catching Santa Claus.
I can't explain how he gets to
and from crime scenes so fast.
We need to figure out who this
guy is and what he wants.
You should
ask your girlfriend.
She writes fan fiction
about him.
Joe, help me out here.
Sorry, partner.
I stopped believing in Santa
when I was about eight.
Hey.
What's going on in there?
I think Eddie's trying
to convince the Captain
That the Flash
is a public menace.
Excuse me?
So after weeks of my trying
to convince you
that the Flash is real, now
that you finally do believe me,
you're trying
to have him arrested?
- What the hell?
- Thanks, Barry.
Sorry.
No worries.
The Captain shot me down.
Look, I'm not feeling
like lunch.
See you later.
He's just jealous.
Of the Flash?
Should he be?
No.
I'll see you later.
Barry,
You need to get
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah, I will.
After I eat.
Anger, hate, aggression.
A Jedi craves not these things.
No one is feeling that quote?
Everyone in the bank
went total savage for,
Like, five minutes.
And then they were fine again.
Anger can be
a powerful emotion.
If this meta-human can engender
irrational feelings of anger
In his victims,
he can do a lot of damage.
Detective west helped get
a copy of the cat scans
The hospital did on everyone
at the bank.
Take a look.
Well, look at this,
The emotion centers
of the brains
Are still showing signs
of being overwhelmed.
Particularly the area that
controls executive function.
That's the part of the brain
that stops people from doing
Whatever random and potentially
destructive thing
That pops into their head.
How do you think the meta
does it to them?
That's the 1/2 million dollar
question.
Hey, if you guys figure it
out, just give me a call, okay?
Is the Flash off to another
rooftop rendezvous with Iris?
No.
Yeah, but she probably just
wants to ask me...
I mean, you know, him... about
meta-human stuff for her blog.
Do you want some advice?
No matter what I say,
I'm getting the advice, right?
Don't get involved.
As the Flash or yourself.
You don't want to be the one
to blame for their breakup.
Okay.
I hear you.
Iris.
Flash.
Be great to call you
by your real name.
You mean like Ralph?
Is your name Ralph?
What did you want
to see me about?
My boyfriend, he's...
Did you guys break up?
- No.
- Oh.
He's a cop and he thinks
that you're dangerous.
And he's trying to convince
his boss that you're a menace
That needs to be stopped.
I thought I should warn you.
Anyways, you should probably go.
You're not going.
Barry, are you there?
- What?
- The police got a ping
From the tracer hidden
in the stolen cash.
Swat team's closing in
on the 1600 block of pass.
Now stop ruining
Iris' love life and go.
I've gotta run.
I bet you say that
to all the girls.
What other girls?
He always paid in cash.
- Never seemed like trouble.
- He's on the move.
- Freeze!
- Hold it right there!
- Hands up.
- Is there a problem, gentlemen?
Certo.
Turn around!
Certo, what are you waiting for?
Cuff him!
You don't tell me what to do.
Get down!
Ugh!
Ah!
Nice mask.
It's kinda comforting to know
that no matter
What city you go to,
Big Belly Burger is always
Going to taste
like Big Belly Burger.
You mean full of grease
and salt?
I thought those were
the secret ingredients.
Oliver's back.
By the way, I gave Oliver,
like, 1/2 hour head start.
- Hi, Barry.
- Hey, Felicity.
How you doing, Dig?
You're fast.
Did you guys not tell him
about me?
Seeing is believing, or...
drooling.
Hey, thanks for showing up
back there, but I had that.
Uh-huh.
What, I was getting ready
to make my move.
What move?
The one to the morgue?
Wait, so what are you guys
doing in Central City?
Working a case.
Suspicious homicide in the
styling where the murder weapon
is a boomerang.
Cool.
I mean, awful.
I found traces
of iron oxide on it.
I know it's a long shot,
but Central City has
The highest concentration of
iron oxide in the country.
Did you know Australian
aboriginals
Use boomerangs to hunt?
Mainly on kangaroo,
Which is a surprisingly
low-fat source of prot...
we were following up a lead
When we heard the S.W.A.T. Raid
over the radio, and I thought
That I would come by...
Watch you make your move.
I had a cousin got hit
by lightning once.
He just developed a stutter.
Huh.
Well, my team and I
Are after a nasty meta-human
who makes people angry.
Cool.
I mean, awful.
Uh, well, since you guys
are here, why don't we team up?
I'll help you find your
boomerang man, you can help me
Find my super rage-a-holic.
We'd love to.
No, we'll handle our business
and head home.
The fastest way to find out
everything we need to know
About the boomerang is to sic
S.T.A.R. Labs on it.
Enough people know
my secret identity.
Fine... I'll go.
They already know who I am.
You can drop me off, and I will
meet up with you later.
- How 'bout I give you a lift?
- Whoo!
Man,
that's not freaking you out?
Let's go.
- Oh!
- So what'd you think?
I think...
My shirt's on fire!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm glad I decided
not to go braless.
You guys remember Felicity?
I'll always remember this.
Hi, Felicity,
it's so good to see you.
What brings you
back to Central City?
Not Barry?
No, not Barry.
This?
Not happening.
We looked down that road
and we said "no, thank you."
They get it.
Actually, I'm here...
Because of this.
Awesome!
What are the wings made of?
Not sure... I'm thinking
some sort of composite
Or high-density plastic...
Reinforced with carbon fiber.
Oh, that's weird.
It almost feels like it's...
vibrating.
- Yeah.
Oh, I wanna run some tests,
- And I wanna run 'em right now!
- Mmhmm.
Hey, you guys come up
with anything new on our meta?
The officer who was affected
tonight says he saw
A flash of red
before he lost control.
I suspect the meta is inducing
rage via the ocular nerve.
Oh, Dr. Wells
wants to see you.
Why do I feel like
I just got called
Into the principal's office?
Starling City vigilante.
He calls himself
"the Arrow" now.
Oh, does he...
"Flash"?
Wait, what's the problem?
We don't trust him.
You guys don't even know him.
I know that he was wanted
for murder
In at least 12 different cases
dating back three years.
I know there's been at least
two major terrorist attacks
In Starling since
he became active.
All right, but the cops there
are cool with him now.
He doesn't kill people anymore.
And what about
all the criminals
That he put arrows through?
Those, what, don't count?
- He's a hero, Joe.
- You're a hero, Barry.
You offer protection,
hope, light.
What that man does is carry out
a dark reckoning for his city.
It is a brutal, violent vision
of justice,
One we do not share.
You truly think
He's a hero, fine, so be it.
But he's not the kind
you should be looking up to.
Aah!
That's my bad.
That's on me.
I want that "arrow"
out of my city.
Tonight.
Tell me, do you think he can
do everything really fast?
I mean, like, how fast do you
think he goes to the bathroom
After he's eaten something?
This is you watching my back?
Well, the Mirakuru soldiers
are one thing, but this...
Whatever he can do now,
he's still the same Barry
- we met last year.
- Well, if you're so adamant
against teaming up with him,
what are we doing here?
He's a good kid,
and it's just a name, Diggle.
The man who rents
this storage unit...
I want... his... name.
Hey.
The bad guy that you're after,
the one who robbed the bank,
His name is Roy G. Bivolo.
Uh, thanks.
How did you find that out?
The guy's still alive, right?
I'm just asking.
I thought you
didn't want to help.
I'm not.
It's just a name.
- All right.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Ooh!
One non-fat latte,
extra sugar for Felicity,
And one coffee, black,
for Oliver.
I brewed you a fresh pot,
so...
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Barry, um, can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Ow.
What are you doing?
You did not tell me
that you knew Oliver Queen.
- I know Oliver Queen.
- Oh, my god,
He's even more handsome
in person.
And his arms are, like,
twice the size of yours.
Technically
they're not twice the size.
He's on my three list.
- What's a three list?
- My list
Of three guys I'm allowed
to cheat on Eddie with.
You usually don't meet people
on your list,
But now here he is, and I just
cannot stop staring at him.
Felicity,
this is me noticing you staring.
We need to help Barry
with his case.
Why don't you want to help?
Because Barry doesn't
really want my help.
He only thinks he does.
Harrison Wells
and Barry's cop foster dad
Both said you were dangerous
and a bad influence.
Barry defended you.
You're going to hock me
about this
Until I say yes, aren't you?
I'm a hocker.
Okay.
- Okay, what?
- Okay, we'll help you
Catch your bad guy.
Great.
Meta-human.
I am not calling him that,
Barry.
Partners?
Partners.
- Hey.
- You're late.
Barry, how can you have
super-speed
and still not be on time?
Sorry, I guess the super-tardiness
kinda neutralizes it.
So how do we catch Bivolo here?
Oh, no, we don't here.
We're here to train.
What?
Like Rocky?
I read your friend Iris'
blog post on the Flash,
And I visited all
the crime scenes you fought at.
- Don't you sleep?
- Last month
You took on a man
named Leonard Snart.
We call him Captain Cold.
We can talk about you giving
your enemies
Silly code names later.
You mean like over coffee with
deathstroke and the huntress?
The point is that you engaged
Snart on a commuter train,
Which he derailed.
Okay, there may have been some
damage, but I got the job done,
- I was the hero.
- Barry, when you approach
a new environment,
do you case every inch of it?
You could.
You have the time.
But you don't.
You just run in blind.
There's a difference, Barry,
between having powers
And having precision.
When I came to you
thinking about
Going out and helping people,
You said
I could be an inspiration.
Living this life...
Well,
it takes more than a mask.
It takes discipline.
And since you are probably
as stubborn as I am...
What is that for?
You're going to run
over there,
You're going to come back at me,
And you're going to get hit
with an arrow.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Okay, fine,
I will humor you.
Ready?
Ready.
Nice try.
Gah!
Ah!
What, you shot me?
I heard you heal fast.
Oh, god!
Hey.
What's up?
Eddie's making his case
for the task force again.
But I thought the Captain
shot him down already.
Well, apparently
he's got a new argument.
The arrow made another
appearance last night.
And you forgot to tell me
that you got Bivolo's name
From shooting that storage guy
in the leg.
Well, technically
I didn't shoot him.
Well, what word
would you use to describe
How you got this info?
I'm gonna go with "torture."
I don't... the Arrow
gets results.
He's a crazy man.
Look, I don't actually
disagree with you at the moment,
But we wouldn't even have
Bivolo's name
If it weren't for the Arrow.
So maybe instead of judging him,
you should just be thanking him.
Two things I won't be doing
in this life...
Playing professional baseball,
and thanking that lunatic.
Stay.
Have you heard
of color psychology?
The theory that changes
in the color spectrum
Can affect emotion.
It is so nice to have
another woman to talk to.
I know.
I was thinking
that if Bivolo uses color
To induce the temporary
psychosis,
Maybe we can use light and color
to reverse it.
Miss Smoak,
a word, if you please.
Hey, what's up, doc?
Sorry, that was dumb.
Remember I went to M.I.T.
Yes, you're smart.
Felicity, I like to surround my
team with known quantities.
That is because I find
the unknown
To be toxic, dangerous.
The arrow is unknown.
I can assure you, Dr. Wells,
he's not dangerous.
To us.
Well, of that,
I have little doubt.
And yet, I find myself
with a conundrum.
How can I completely trust a man
when I don't even know his name?
And so, I was hoping,
Miss Smoak,
That you could help me
trust him.
Who is he under the hood?
That is not my secret to tell,
Dr. Wells.
Of course.
I'll figure it out on my own.
- Hey.
How'd it go with Oliver?
You know, to be honest,
not exactly the partnership
I thought it would be.
Oh, did he really do the thing
with the arrows?
You knew
he was going to shoot me?
Whoa, it is practically
impossible to tell
When Oliver's making a joke.
Hey, we just got a ping from
The facial recognition software
on Bivolo, aka, Prism.
Since when do we have
facial recognition software?
- Happy Chanukah.
- Where can I find him?
Traffic cameras just caught
him entering a residence
At 168 Jarvis.
We should let the Arrow know.
I can handle this solo.
I've done it before.
Barry, I really think
you need to wait...
Felicity,
I don't need his help.
I knew you'd be coming
for me.
I could see it in your eyes
at the bank.
When I turned those people
against each other,
It made you angry.
Have some real anger.
No signs of macular damage.
Your retina and cornea
seem unaffected.
I told you, I'm fine.
You said Bivolo whammied you.
No desire to go MMA
on any of us?
No.
Yeah, I mean,
something weird happened
- with his eyes for a sec.
- Weird thing?
Yeah, everything went red.
You were right.
Okay, next thing you know,
Bivolo was gone.
Look, obviously his powers
didn't work on me, so...
It was stupid for you
to go out there alone.
You take too many risks.
As fast as you are, that's going
to catch up with you.
Caitlin, I'm not Ronnie.
You gotta stop treating me
like I am.
You're right.
You're not.
What?
You are such a lovable dummy.
It's Oliver... he wants
to have another session.
I'm sure he's not going
to shoot you again.
Maybe you should
wear body armor.
Thinking of new ways
to embarrass me?
I'm not trying
to embarrass you, Barry,
But you went after Bivolo
last night alone
And you lost him.
And you've never
had a misstep?
Course I've had missteps.
Barry, I have been living this
life for almost eight years,
Encountering things
that you can't even fathom,
And I am still alive.
Not because super-speed
kept me out of the ground.
It was because I realized
that I needed to keep learning,
Keep training,
keep getting smarter,
And until you get that,
despite your best intentions,
You will do more harm than good.
I finally see it.
You're a little bit
jealous of me, aren't you?
A guy like you, handsome, rich,
Can have any girl he wants,
Jealousy's probably
a new emotion for you,
So you might be a little slow
to get what it is
That you're feeling.
- That's your theory?
- Absolutely.
So you can train, lift weights,
Climb that stupid barn
till your heart explodes,
But you'll never be
as fast as I am.
You'll never be what I am.
And that's gotta hurt
your rock-hard pride, Ollie.
I told Felicity
you didn't want my help.
Yeah. You're finally right
about something.
Allen! Where are you
with the Bivolo case?
I'm working it.
Care to be more specific?
Hey, how 'bout you answer me
when I ask you a question?
Hey!
How 'bout you back off?
Excuse me?
Look, I work just as hard
as anyone in this building.
I don't need you constantly
berating me to do my job.
When it's done,
you will have it, all right?
Sorry, Captain.
He's having an allergic reaction
To some bad medication.
You remind him
who answers to who.
Have you lost your mind?
I'm so sick of Singh talking
to me like that.
He's still our boss.
Now I know you're upset
about losing Bivolo...
Wait, wait...
You're just like him.
Like Wells, and Oliver,
and everyone else my whole life
That didn't think
I could get the job done.
Do you want to help me, Joe?
You want to help me?
Get my dad out of prison.
You helped put him there,
didn't you?
Barry, I need you
to calm down.
Why don't we both
take a ride to S.T.A.R. Labs?
I'm calm!
Okay?
When I am not calm,
you'll know.
Okay.
I'll call you back later.
That was the Arrow.
He says Barry
is acting strangely.
Strangely, how?
He's been whammied.
He was acting angry.
It was scary.
And his eyes...
They glowed.
It's possible that his body
is fighting off the effect,
So it's hitting him slower.
When it comes to rage,
That is not a good thing.
The longer you suppress
your emotions...
The bigger the explosion.
Considering what he can do,
how do we even stop him?
A cold-gun would come in
real handy right about now.
- Hey.
- I'm just sayin'.
None of us can stop Barry.
Fortunately,
Felicity knows someone who can.
I think you better call back
Oliver Queen.
We're gonna need
the Arrow's help.
Is this your way of telling me
That you want satellite radio
for Christmas?
Look, I am not mad at you.
Good, 'cause there's no reason
you should be.
Eddie, both you and the Flash
care about protecting this city.
You would both
give your lives for it.
You're more alike
than you think, okay?
He's not the bad guy.
How do you know
so much about him, Iris?
He got in touch with me
after I started the blog,
And I've seen him
a couple times.
A couple times?
Why didn't you tell me
about this?
Well, given the fact
that I think he's a hero,
And you want to put him in jail,
Do you really need
to ask that question?
How could you ever think
I would be okay with this?
I heard you've been looking
for me.
All this time,
you've been trying to catch me,
And I caught you first.
Guess you haven't read
your girlfriend's blog.
Eddie, no!
Ooh, see I knew the Arrow
was Oliver Queen.
I mean, I had it narrowed down
to, like, a list of 150 people,
But he was definitely
on that list.
Do you have a way to stop
Barry's rage-fest?
I have an idea
about how to do that.
Joe, we're gonna need
your help.
We need to find him first
before he hurts somebody.
I have him.
Facial recognition picked him up
on a traffic camera downtown.
Oh, god.
Eddie!
Who the hell are you, huh?
You think
you can just come along
And get to have
whatever you want?
What gives you the right?
What the hell
are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What has happened to you?
I feel fine.
You are not fine.
How would you know?
Because you write about me?
You don't know me!
You don't know who I am.
You never did.
I know that you have
Risked your life
to help people,
To save them!
Someone who does that
Does not suddenly turn around
and want to hurt people.
Please.
Run!
Eddie, run!
You need to calm down.
And you need to hold on.
I just hope
they can turn Barry back
Before he kills Oliver.
Me, I'd be more worried
about what Oliver
Might have to do to Barry.
Barry has superpowers.
Oliver has a bow and arrow.
Do you have any idea
how many people
Oliver has killed
with that bow and arrow?
Recurve bow arrows can travel
up to 300 feet per second,
So, like, 200 miles an hour.
Barry can run three times
that fast.
Whatever.
Oliver's been doing this
A lot longer.
My money's on experience.
My money's on speed.
Please tell me
you're not actually
Having this conversation
right now.
You missed.
No.
Aah!
2000 milligrams
of horse tranquilizer
Should be hitting you
any time now.
Where you going?
We're not done!
Is that all you got?
Oliver, get up.
Fool me once.
Ah... Ah... Ah!
I still believe in you, Barry.
Is this even going to work?
He just needs to see
the right colors.
Now, Joe!
Barry, you okay?
Oh, this is going to be
a special kind of hangover.
So...
It was a tie.
Oliver...
I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
But we do still have your
meta-human to take care of.
Anything left in the tank?
Well, if not,
there's two of us, right?
Right.
You think this will stop me?
I will make you tear each other
to pieces!
You will all die
screaming with rage!
Blah, blah, blah,
"no prison can hold me."
Heard it all before, pal.
Adios, Prism.
I liked "rainbow raider."
Okay, you don't get
to pick the names.
I have a prison like this.
Mine's on a nearly inhospitable
island in the North China sea,
But this works too.
My identity is a closely-guarded
secret known only to a few,
And if it were to get out,
will endanger my family,
My friends,
and it would embolden
My enemies to retaliate
at me through them.
What Oliver is trying to say
Is that he had a lovely time
working with you
And getting to know each of you,
And he can't wait
to do it again soon.
Right.
You know, it didn't sound like
that's what he was saying.
I may not agree
with your methods, but...
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey.
If I had a DNA sample
I was unable
to fully break down,
do you think you could isolate
the genetic markers for me?
Sure, what's the sample from?
The canary's murder.
Of course.
Mr. Queen,
I met your father once.
Charity event.
One of the things
we spoke of was you.
I think he would be very proud
of the man you've become.
Thank you.
And please, call me Oliver.
There is something off
about that guy.
Captain Singh approved
the task force.
You wanted me to believe
the Flash was real.
Now I do.
I believe he's dangerous,
And I am going to take him in.
How do you feel about that?
All I know...
is how I feel about you.
Hey!
You guys heading home?
Yeah, we could use some Javas
for the road.
I will hook you up.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Um, so listen...
I'm really sorry
for what I said in the field
And then last night
in the street.
I wish I could say it was all
because of whatever Bivolo
Did to me, but I guess I had
More feelings bottled up
than I thought.
You can always talk to me.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And you were right,
I still have...
A lot to learn.
There's one more thing...
And you're not going to like it.
Does it involve
you shooting me in the back?
No.
No, the heart.
That's not going
to work out for you.
You need to let her go,
For both of your sakes.
Guys like us don't get the girl.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- This one's yours.
- Thank you.
Oliver.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good, good.
It's been a long time.
We never spoke after,
and I'm so sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I heard about your mother...
She loved you very much.
She did.
- I should get going.
- All right.
- Who was that?
- Hmm?
Someone that I used to know.
Hi, sweetheart.
Yes, I'm just getting you
a hot chocolate.
Mommy will be home soon.
Got your message.
I wanted you to know,
last night...
That wasn't me.
Sure looked like you.
Yeah. I was affected
by one of the meta-humans.
He messed with my head.
But I'm okay now, I promise.
I defended you.
Everyone told me that you would
bring me nothing but danger.
My father, Barry, Eddie...
I didn't listen to them.
I never listened to them.
But now it's time I did.
Don't contact me anymore,
okay?
Iris...
I'm sorry.
Me too.
♪ Carry your story ♪
♪ Wherever I may go ♪
♪ 'Cause I know it will
be mine ♪
♪ And ♪
♪ Know I still be
on your side ♪
Look at that.
Better than an ATM.
Anyone tell you not to hang out
under the freeway at night?
You're liable to get robbed.
You got the shakes, man?
What are you, tweaking,
or just cold?
I'm not cold.