[Fast Track screaming]
You were dead.
I saw your body.
And yet...
here I am, in the flesh.
How's that possible?
The Negative Forces...
brought me back.
Because they were too weak
without a fourth member
of their merry band.
Didn't I tell you...
that finding ways to kill you
is my life's work?
Here's what's really funny.
Killing your mother
led to the birth of the Flash,
and killing Iris...
led to the rebirth of me.
So I guess you could say
your mother and Iris...
were good for something.
[yelling]
[screaming]
Dad! Stop!
He's not worth it.
He killed your mother!
[laughing]
Dad, if you do this,
you'll be just as bad as him!
[panting]
[Reverse-Flash] Yeah,
what's the matter, Flash?
You can't finish the job?
You better finish the job!
Because if you don't...
they're next.
Dad, don't listen to him, please.
Even if he did kill Mom,
now, in 2022, we're still here.
Don't you see? We're still alive.
[Impulse] She's right. We haven't been
erased from the timeline yet.
Which means Mom isn't dead yet.
They're both hurting.
- Badly.
- Okay, so what do we do now?
We find Iris and we bring her home.
Then we find a way to take down
the Negative Forces,
'cause if they come back
for a rematch...
I don't think they will.
They already got what they came for.
The last Thawne in existence.
What do they need him for anyway?
[The Flash] There's only one way
to find out.
I have to find a way
into the Negative Speed Force.
Dad.
No offense. That's insane.
I don't have a choice.
As long as Thawne's out there,
everyone's in danger.
Chester already ran a satellite search.
Thawne's nowhere on the planet.
The only place left to hide
is the Negative Speed Force.
- So if I can find a way in...
- [Cecile] No.
Look, I can feel
all of the anger inside you, I can.
And I know that you've been
to hell and back today,
but we need to think
our next move through.
He killed Iris!
Barry, how can you possibly be so sure?
Because I am.
[XS] Guys.
We need to talk to our dad.
Fine.
I'll call Joe and tell him
that we're all okay.
[XS] Look.
Assuming we can find our way
into the Negative Speed Force,
let us handle this.
We will make sure
Thawne gets back to Iron Heights.
Dad, we promise.
You weren't there.
You didn't see what I saw.
Iris died in my arms
before her body disappeared.
You say she's alive,
but for all we know, she's already
been erased from this timeline.
Only the changes haven't caught up
with us yet.
It's happened before.
You still want to kill him.
Don't you?
Hello?
Is anybody here?
[Damien] Hello, Iris.
Damien?
If you're here,
does that mean that I'm dead, too?
No, it doesn't.
What happened to you
is far more interesting than that.
We have a lot to discuss.
[The Flash] Going inside
is the only way to end this.
Barry, it sounds dangerous.
'Cause it is.
Fine.
So how exactly do you get inside
the Negative Speed Force?
The first time
I went into the Positive Speed Force,
Harry hit me with a concentrated blast
of dark matter and lightning
that generated a tachyon reaction.
Well, I could rig the tachyon harness
to do the same.
Only if you're trying to get into
a negative place,
you're going to need
a negative source of lightning.
Like me.
[Cecile] Uh...
Meena, I don't think
that's such a good idea right now.
We need to find a way in.
I'm the key.
Chester, go ahead and get started.
You wanna tell me how you're gonna deal
with all of that anger?
Barry,
I can feel it pouring off of you.
What are you planning?
Oh, my God.
You want revenge.
But why?
Bart and Nora said that Iris is alive.
And I know she's not.
[male voice] Cecile. Cecile.
What is it?
Someone's calling my name.
And now I'm picking up desperation.
[Bashir] You have to find us.
You're the only one that can help us.
- [The Flash] Who is it?
- Bashir?
What happened to you?
Where are the other Forces?
He's gone.
- Was it our Bashir?
- Yeah.
And he's in pretty bad shape.
He said that...
I'm the only one who can help them.
I think he wants me to help bring back
the other Positive Forces.
His timeline's gone.
I love you.
[Negative Deon] Well, we wanted you
to feel at home.
You, uh...
You know who we are.
Beings who can do all this.
I'm guessing you're the Negative Forces.
Why am I here?
You never wondered
where your speed really comes from?
I built a machine...
that taps into the Negative Speed Force,
allowing me to siphon it for my own use.
Brilliant.
Oh, you didn't tap into it.
No, no, no. It tapped into you.
It's true.
The Negative Speed Force
has always existed.
It chose you as an avatar
because it feeds off your hatred
for Barry Allen.
[Negative Alexa] The other Thawne
forgot that.
No hate, no Negative Speed Force avatar.
That's why he had to go.
I don't know what you're planning.
But if you think I'm gonna stand here
and play your stupid game...
[Negative Alexa] Relax.
We're not gonna hurt you.
I'm just gonna transform you.
[Damien] So, let me guess.
The last thing you remember is
figuring out that the Negative Forces
used your time sickness
- to rebirth a new avatar.
- Yes.
But if I've had this time sickness
for months, then...
Why now?
The Negative Forces
used your body as an incubator.
And, yes, it's a dastardly scheme.
Reminds me of my bad old days.
Okay, so if I'm alive, then...
Where am I?
You're here inside my Time Stone.
The talisman that you and Barry used
to wipe out anachronisms during...
Armageddon.
I can't feel my connection
to Barry anymore.
And if it's the same for him,
then Damien,
I have to get out of here
and I need your help.
- Even if you're...
- A remnant of my old consciousness
imprinted on a stone?
Bearing witness
to all timelines for eternity.
Wahoo.
Are you saying that
I'm stuck here forever, too?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, that's up to you.
See, unlike me,
you aren't supposed to be dead.
Which is why,
at the moment that the Negative Forces
annihilated your body,
the stone spared you.
It senses that you still have
something important to do.
The question is,
are you up to it?
[Chester] Okay, you all ready?
The harnesses are good to go.
[all grunting]
What is happening?
- Oh, God.
- I'm shutting down remote ignition.
- Keep on going.
- But, Barr...
Do it!
[yelling]
I'm calling it.
Dad!
- Why didn't it work?
- I don't know.
If this won't work, we can't access
the Negative Speed Force.
Then we need to find another way.
Eobard would have known what to do.
But now he's gone.
Because of me...
and that damn machine.
Dad.
Meena...
You don't want to do this.
Yes, I do.
This machine ruined my life.
No, it didn't.
Thawne did.
There is nothing we can do about it!
Not anymore.
Yes, there is.
Look, Meena...
I know exactly how you feel.
You're the only one who understands.
Who knows how this has to end.
That's why you can't destroy your work.
We need it.
What for?
So we can get you charged...
and you can share your speed again.
With me.
Your speed's at 100%.
Promise me when you find that bastard,
you'll never let him hurt anyone else
ever again.
Do you remember what you did
when you shared your speed with Eobard?
You told me I had to share
the most important parts of myself.
Baby girl...
Wherever you are,
please, please,
come back home soon.
Jay? Joan? What are you...
What are you doing here?
We've been following Iris'
particle trail across the timestream,
and it led us here.
When Cecile called,
she said that Iris was still missing.
- [tracker beeping]
- Not anymore.
Come this way.
What is that thing?
[Garrick] It's a time stone.
I've heard about it in my travels.
Where did you get it?
Damien Darhk gave it to me.
He said I might need it one day.
But why is it glowing now?
Those particles that were left behind?
They're Iris' consciousness.
And now I think they've somehow
ended up inside the stone.
How do we get her out of there?
I can't believe we're doing this.
Look, Allegra, we have to bring
the Positive Forces back.
This is the only way
we can help Flash do it.
Who cares about him?
Yeah.
We just want our powers back.
Okay, look,
both of you are now ex-psychics,
but you know exactly the way
that this works.
Now start concentrating
and help me focus in.
I will do all the heavy lifting.
You found me.
[gasps]
Oh...
Oh, my God, are you okay?
This is a nice office.
What happened?
Iris' time sickness, it spread to us.
So we needed to tether ourselves
to someone in this reality.
I chose Cecile.
- Why?
- Because of your boundless potential.
So I opened the floodgates of your mind.
That's how you were able to absorb
the gifts of others.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, wait, wait.
So you're the guy
who gave her all of our powers?
Mm.
Thanks.
You're... welcome.
So you now have the strength
to bring back the Forces.
That is, if you're willing to help us.
Of course I will.
What do you need me to do?
Your biometrics are spiking.
We thought the bad Forces were back,
but now you're going into
the Negative Speed Force without us.
We're too late.
[grunts]
Thawne.
What the hell?
Eobard can't come to the phone
right now.
He's going through some changes.
What are you doing to him?
Helping him reach his full potential.
If this was all about Thawne,
why did you attack us?
Oh, man, you came at us first
for Armageddon.
When you cut off the
Negative Speed Force from his avatar.
[yelling]
Now, see, we...
We've been pulling the strings
ever since.
Finally ready now.
[Negative Bashir] See,
this is on you, Flash.
You tipped the scales.
We're just...
putting things back to normal,
and then some.
[screaming]
This all started the day
that you severed Thawne's speed.
The day that you upset
the cosmic balance.
Something we didn't know was possible...
until you showed us how.
And that was also the day
that we realized...
we could do the same.
Time to tip the scales.
[grunts]
Dad, are you okay?
It's all my fault.
What about Thawne?
The Negative Forces.
They were transforming him somehow.
So he's still alive.
But they already gave him
his speed back.
What more could they want?
[Chester] Guys?
I'm picking up a huge influx
of negative kinetic tachyons.
Where?
Right over downtown.
[people screaming]
There's no point in running.
[distorted] You're all going to die.
[people screaming]
[screaming continues]
[XS] Holy shrap. That's Thawne.
Who's his new tailor?
Satan?
[Chester] Guys, I'm not just picking up
negative kinetic isotopes.
Reading temporal, geothermic,
electrochemical ones, too.
He has the power
of all four Negative Forces now.
Why?
To tip the balance of power
in their favor.
Turn the entire world
into a living hell.
You said I had unfinished business.
What is it?
It's Barry, isn't it?
Where is he? What's happening?
If you want to find out,
you have to get out of here yourself.
How, damn it?
Oh, come on, Iris.
Look at your life.
Look at everything
that has happened to you
since Barry went into that coma.
You were destined to die,
held captive in another dimension.
Hell, you faced certain death
over and over and over again.
And every time you should have died,
only you didn't.
Why?
Because I always had help, I...
[mimics buzzer] Thanks for playing.
Wrong answer.
Come on.
It's right in front of you.
You're a survivor.
You always will be.
I haven't reached my limit.
No, you haven't.
But what about the spark
between Barry and I?
Well...
Just because you can't feel it,
doesn't mean it isn't there.
So, what are you gonna do now?
Spend the rest of eternity
hanging out with Damien Darhk?
No.
Atta girl!
I'm gonna reignite it.
Say hi to your old man for me.
[screaming continues]
You're outnumbered. Four to one.
You're going to pay
for everyone you've hurt.
Especially Eobard.
[screaming]
Bart?
Dad? Is he going to be okay?
If that's Impulse, where is Thawne?
Right here.
What did you do?
I sent them back in time.
A billion years, to be precise.
[Bashir] We only have one chance.
Okay. What do you need me to do?
Put it on.
There's a reason you were given
all these powers, Cecile.
The powers you absorbed were enhanced
by the one thing that I like.
Your ability to care about people.
That's why you were chosen.
So, take it.
The mask will reabsorb your
psychic powers and transfer them to me.
Don't even think about it.
[screaming]
[Bashir] Wait.
She has to go through this.
Cecile, are you okay?
Did it work?
I sure as hell hope so.
[exhales]
Well, well, well.
Who's faster now, Flash?
Oh! [laughing]
How does it feel, Flash?
How does it feel knowing
you could have prevented all this?
If only you'd killed me
when you had the chance.
Believe me...
that's a mistake I won't make.
Who's doing this?
[Deon] I am.
You're too late
because your pathetic avatar
is powerless.
You call that power?
This is power.
This is impossible.
No, this is the end.
We're equals now, Thawne.
Equals?
Never.
I have always been,
I will always be better than you.
This is for Iris,
for everyone you've killed.
[yelling]
[people screaming]
What is it?
Some kind of temporal disruption
coming from inside the stone.
[Iris West screaming]
Dad?
Baby girl.
- Oh!
- Dad!
It's okay. It's okay.
Damien Darhk showed me the way back.
[rumbling]
That felt like an earthquake.
Or something a lot worse.
Again, our top story,
the deadly new speedster
who has already taken dozens of lives
has been engaged by the Flash.
But fallout from the fight
has turned the city into a war zone.
Residents are advised...
Barry's doing more harm than good.
They started Armageddon.
Jay, I need you
to take me downtown, fast.
[Iris West] Barry!
Barry!
Iris?
Barry, you have to stop.
No, I have to finish this.
No, Barry, listen to me.
The city can't take any more fighting.
That's why I have to end this.
You can't!
[Negative Reverse-Flash] She's right.
We'll never stop
until one of us is dead.
Time to tip the scales.
[panting]
Get Iris to safety.
Good luck.
I'm done fighting you.
Do you think I won't kill you?
I'll slaughter you where you sit!
I just need more power.
Do you hear me?
[screaming]
We're not meant to tip the scales.
[panting]
You won't survive, Thawne.
You lie, Flash!
This is the moment.
[people screaming]
[screaming continues]
[breathes deeply]
No.
It's not supposed to end like this.
[screaming]
[panting]
Dad?
What is that?
It's the universe resetting itself.
[Joan] Barry,
your Force particles are gone.
And as for you, Iris,
there's no sign
of your time sickness anywhere.
You're completely cured.
And Gideon says there's no Thawne
anywhere in the timeline.
Then it's really over.
All of it.
Bart, Nora, about the way
I behaved today...
Uh-uh.
No.
Not after all of the things
that you have helped us with.
He's right, Dad.
At the end of the day, all that matters
is you did the right thing.
And on that note, I think we should all
go back to our lives in 2049.
- Great work today, Flash.
- Thank you.
As always.
Thank you.
Bye.
Guys, guys!
Thank you for everything.
Don't sweat it, Pops.
It was all "aster." No "dis."
No idea what that means.
[all chuckling]
You don't need to.
All right, love you, Pops.
- Mom.
- See you, guys.
We love you.
How are you feeling?
Like there is so much I don't know.
[chuckles]
But more importantly,
the B.L.O.C. is no longer working.
It was never my idea, was it?
No, it wasn't.
The Negative Speed Force
used the machine to pick its avatars.
You were a means to an end.
I'm sorry you lost your speed.
Don't be. It was never
my dream to be a speedster.
I know I never got to meet him,
but Eobard seemed like
a very special person.
He was.
I wanted to give you this.
[Barry] We found it at S.T.A.R. Labs.
[sniffles]
Thank you.
For everything.
I should go.
Hey, Meena, look, if you need anything,
just call us, okay?
We're here for you.
I know.
Oh, and if Team Flash ever needs a
helping hand,
as in the technical kind,
you know where to find me.
[Chester] Good news. Your brain's back
to its old empathic capacity.
Dillon has her powers back.
The Queen, too,
who's back in Iron Heights.
I am going to miss being leveled up.
I'm just glad we all survived this.
Yeah, yeah, I guess I should be happy.
We did bring back the Positive Forces,
and then there was
saving the entire city.
That should be good enough.
A humble brag?
Go ahead, girl. I see you.
Look, here's to saving the world,
friends and Team Flash.
Or, as I like to call it,
Team Badass.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Team Badass! Come on!
- Team Badass!
Mm. Mm-mm.
Okay, that is not a decaf latte.
And this does not have three sugars.
Cecile, I'm sorry.
I guess we mixed up coffees.
I already, uh...
No worries, it's fine.
Cecile, did you do that?
Uh...
Yeah?
But...
Okay, all I did was think
I really wish I had the right coffee.
And then I kind of saw it in my head.
And then all of a sudden it was...
Oh, the Force is strong with this one.
Huh.
Well...
that's new.
[Tinya] I never thought
I'd see you again.
I don't mean to be rude or whatever,
but why am I here?
[Renee] Tinya.
Mom?
It's really you?
I didn't know
if I'd ever get out of that place.
I just knew I had to see you again.
How did this happen?
When Iris beat her time sickness,
it cured the Still Force, too.
And then Renee showed up
back at home in Coast City.
We have so much to catch up on.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[laptop beeping]
Chamber malfunction?
What do you mean, chamber malfunction?
Frost, are you okay?
Frost?
Who the hell are you?
[woman] A friend...
I think.
I never want to let you go.
Then don't.
I mean, I could stay like this all week.
- That works for me.
- [chuckles]
Iris, last night,
I thought I lost you forever,
because I couldn't feel our connection.
Yeah, when I was in the time stone,
I couldn't feel you, either.
That's why I knew
I had to get back to you.
So, I reignited our spark.
How?
You're my lightning rod, too.
Thank you.
Seriously?
I mean, I've been gone
for a while, but...
For reminding me
that even the Flash has limits.
Thawne couldn't accept that
about himself.
Which is why he didn't survive.
Barry, you know the Negative Speed Force
will need to find a new avatar.
I know.
Because the universe
is all about balance.
Which means that one day,
the Negative Forces
will have to pick one.
[Iris West] I wonder who they'll choose.
[Barry] We won't know until it happens.
But whenever that day comes,
and whoever that avatar is...
we'll be ready for them.