Doug! Do something!
Move! You gotta be
a man to do that!
I told you to move!
So, move!
Now, get! Get!
Whoo!
What you got under there?
That's it. Give it to me. Whoo! Whoo!
Fuck off!
Come on. Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo.
It's not my Bob!
Come on, Mom. No! Let's go.
No, just come on.
It's not my Bob.
What was that?
Mom, just stay here, okay?
- Help! Help! Help!
Oh, you fat.
Oh. Big, fat...
and juicy.
No. No, please!
Bobby!
Bobby, where you going?
Fucking kill those motherfuckers!
Get back here! Don't do something stupid!
No. No.
Get back to the trailer!
Come on!
Get out the door!
Help! Shoot him! Shoot him!
- Brenda!
- Bobby!
Come on, now.
Look at me. Look at me.
That's it. Look at me.
Shit! I'll come back for ya.
Brenda!
Bitch stuck me like a pig!
Are you okay?
No.
Oh, God!
Don't move! Don't move, honey. Don't move.
Okay. Okay. All right.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay. S-Sweetheart?
Okay.
Honey? Sweetheart?
Lynn, come on!
Lynn!
Come on!
Oh!
Hmm.
Okay.
What are we gonna do? Huh?
What are we-
What are we gonna do
if they come back, Doug?
This trailer is so small.
I clean and clean.
- It's still a mess.
- Shh.
It's a mess.
- Is Big Bob home?
- Not yet.
Every- Everybody went to bed?
- Yes?
- Yeah.
Brenda's right here,
and Bobby's in the back.
Is Lynny sleeping? Hmm?
You need anything?
- A blanket.
- Okay.
- It's cold.
- Shh. Shh. Nice and warm, huh? Nice and warm.
You're so sweet, Doug.
I understand why Lynny
loves you so much.
So-
I'm not gonna take this shit.
- Hey, we're not going anywhere!
You wanna die too?
- I don't fucking care!
You wanna die, huh?
Look what they did to your mother!
Look what they did to your sister!
Huh? You stop and think!
You're not a fucking child anymore!
You won't make it three feet out there.
We need a plan.
We need to think.
- We need-We need to think.
- Think about what?
Think about what, Doug?
They have Catherine!
They have your daughter.
And you're just gonna sit here and do nothing?
That's 'cause you're a fucking pussy
just like my dad said!
- Shut the fuck up! You shut up! Shut your mouth!
- Fuck you.
No! Turn the lights on.
Turn the lights on.
- He said he's coming back!
- Shh! Quiet!
He said he's coming back
for me. Please.
It's them! It's them!
It's them!
Goggle? Goggle?
Goggle? You copy, Goggle?
Where's Goggle?
He stayed back there.
He's keeping an eye on them.
- I told you.
- What?
I told you,
you've gotta kill them all!
Beast! Beast! You're alive!
Oh, good boy.
Good boy. Good boy.
- Good boy.
- Oh, my God.
Jupiter's going to finish them off.
Why are you doing this to us?
Why are you doing this?
You hear me?
Give me back my baby!
What the fuck
do you want from us?
What do you want?
You give me back my little girl.
You hear me?
- Bobby?
- Hmm?
How many bullets
do you have left?
A clip and a half.
What are we doing?
Which way, Beast? Which way?
Come on. Follow the trail.
Come on, big guy.
I hope you're not afraid of the dark.
Where are they, boy?
Which way, Beast?
Good boy.
Bobby?
Bobby, I followed the blood trail.
It leads to a town or something
out here. Bobby?
Who knows?
Maybe someone heard our calls.
Nobody's gonna hear
the fucking calls, Brenda!
Nobody's gonna see the goddamn smoke
in this goddamn desert!
We're in the middle of freakin'-
Ah, shit!
- God!
I'm sorry.
I'm so scared.
Who are these people?
Good dog. Stay.
- Did you push her?
- Yes.
- Did you destroy the furniture?
- No.
Did you call her
trailer park trash?
- So, now, you're saying you still-
- I'm still in love with her.
Okay, but-So, you said
you treasured the marriage...
and you wanted to end it
two weeks after you got into it?
I wanted to end it
because I have-
I had a feeling that things
weren't gonna work together.
She wasn't working as a team player
with me, and I tried coaching her-
- What were you doing coaching her?
- Well, I tried to show-
- Is she your child?
- No, she's not my child, but she-
Shh, shh, shh.
She wanted me
to eat dinner-spaghetti-
and I wanted to do it
before it got cold.
Watch her head, Bobby.
Come on.
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
Answer me!
I don't know where she is.
I never leave this place.
Your people asked our families...
to leave their town...
and you destroyed our homes.
We went into the mines.
You set off your bombs...
and turned everything to ashes.
You made us what we've become.
Boom. Boom. Boom!
Where's my baby?
What's so funny?
It's breakfast time!
Please don't kill me.
"Please don't kill me."
- Please don't kill me.
- "Please don't kill me."
Lizard.
Kill the baby.
Baby. Baby.
Get out of the way, Ruby.
I said get. Now, get!
Mister, would you play with us?
Ruby!
Catherine!
It's okay.
We'll be all right.
No. No.
- Come on. Come on.
- No!
- Come on, Brenda.
- Bobby!
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Come on. Come on.
It's gonna be all right.
It'll be all right.
Careful. Please? Please?
Oh, shit.
Come on out,
you motherfucker.
Look. Look. It's just a tumbleweed.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go back
to the trailer. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- She's gone.
She's fucking gone! She's gone!
Brenda! Brenda! Go get the trailer ready.
- Brenda, go get the-
- Where's Mom?
- Go get the trailer ready. Okay?
- Listen to me. I need you to go get the trailer.
Just go in,
do what we talked about.
Let's go! Get the window!
Get the window!
It's stuck!
Bob! Help me! Bob!
Go! Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get out!
Here.
Ruby!
Ruby! Come back here!
You little bitch!
Give me that baby!
Fuck!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Oh, my God.
Look! Bobby!