[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
- Cisco, what hap...
♪ ♪
- Frost, Frost.
Barry?
- Help her.
Help her.
Iris.
Iris!
♪ ♪
- [beleaguered breathing]
- Help her.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- Is she gonna be okay?
- When you pulled Iris
out of the Mirrorverse
and she resisted,
it created a molecular anomaly.
All her neural pathways
are disjointed.
- Looks like
her brain's been remapped.
- How do we get her back?
- I don't know.
All we can do now
is let her rest
while I run some more tests.
You gonna be okay?
- I remember everything,
hurting my own team...
forcing Iris
through the portal,
leaving Kamilla
and Singh trapped.
I'm sorry.
- That wasn't you.
- Yeah, it was.
- Man, no, It wasn't.
You were not yourself.
Trust me, we get that.
That's why we're
gonna to put it behind us,
and we're gonna move on,
all right?
We're a team.
We've got each other's backs.
- We're going to figure out
a way to save Iris
and Kamilla and Singh.
I promise.
- But Eva's still out there,
and I can't stop her
'cause I don't have
my speed anymore.
- But you will.
I'm running a full diagnostics
on the artificial
Speed Force machine.
It worked before.
It can work again.
All we need to do
is just figure out...
- No.
I'm done with that thing.
You saw what it turned me into.
I'm not Thawne.
Connecting
with something artificial
isn't gonna work for me...
and since the real
Speed Force is dead...
[phone rings]
- woman: CCPD.
- Wait, your wife
tried to attack you?
- Why would you neighbor try
to make you look into mirrors?
Hold on.
CCPD.
- If he's not your uncle,
who is he?
- Let me get this straight.
You want to help
bring your daughter in,
Mrs. Dearbon,
so that I can arrest her?
- Sue's in trouble.
We want to help her
see things more clearly.
- People change,
sometimes overnight.
♪ ♪
- Captain,
can I speak with you?
It's relevant.
- Excuse me.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Oh, damn.
Sue, I thought you and Ralph
were laying low
until we could clear your name.
- Yeah,
Ralph's tracking a lead.
Arrest me if you have to.
I had to come.
- You mind telling me
what's so important
that you would risk
your freedom?
- Those people in there,
those are not my parents.
I know it sounds crazy,
and then Ralph mentioned
pod people a while back,
I thought it was nuts too,
but I'm telling you,
that's not them.
- No, I believe you.
I've gotten over 100 calls
in the last hour,
exact same complaint.
All saying that people
they've known for years
just aren't themselves anymore.
- Do you think
this has anything
to do with
the craziness at McCulloch?
- Damn,
I know what's happening.
- Move.
[bizarre chiming]
- What the hell?
♪ ♪
- news reporter:
Chaos has broken out
in downtown Central City
over another meta attack.
- So after all that, I'm like,
"Well, at least Grandma Runk
is still my grandma, you know?"
'Cause I was at Jitters
ordering a vibaccino.
Next thing I know,
a pair of T2 arms
jumps out of the countertop
trying to grab me.
You know, fortunately,
Chester P. Runk
knows how to mind
his surroundings.
- Yo!
I just heard back from Joe.
Whatever is happening
out there, it's spreading.
- Yeah, Eva is
getting more powerful.
- I'll say.
I analyzed footage
from Eva's live interview.
It's not just mirrors
that she's manipulating.
It's any reflective
surface now.
- Well, I guess
that makes sense.
Light photons
are elementary particles
that exist
everywhere in nature,
so as long as there's light
around from either natural
or artificial source...
- Call Joe back.
We've got to black out
the city.
He can get the mayor to declare
a state of emergency.
- Okay, I'm on it.
- Okay, why is Eva doing this?
I mean, why does she want us
in the Mirrorverse?
- She wants us out of the way.
These aren't just abductions.
[sirens blaring]
It's a full-blown invasion.
- And with every person
that gets replaced,
Eva's army grows.
- Oh, man, body snatchers.
So what are we gonna do?
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- Boss, you have to get better.
♪ ♪
"The Citizen"
doesn't work without you,
so just please come back, okay?
'Cause we're not giving up
on you, especially Barry.
♪ ♪
What you two have is amazing.
No matter how strong
you both are
on your own,
you're even stronger together.
Don't let Eva McCulloch end
what you guys have.
♪ ♪
- The mayor is doing her best
shutting down the power.
Joe said
it won't be 100 percent,
but I told him
we'd take whatever we can get.
In the meantime
initiating shutters
on all windows
in S.T.A.R. Labs.
- We should cover
all the mirrors too
and kill the lights.
- Yes, I'm on it.
- Hopefully everybody
in Central City
does the same thing.
- If I had my speed
I could patrol,
help people keep safe.
♪ ♪
There's got to be a way
to save 'em all,
to get Iris back.
- [ethereal whispers]
There is, there is, there is.
There is, there is,
there is, there is, there is.
[bizarre chiming]
- Hey,
were you saying something?
- Uh, guys, where's Barry?
♪ ♪
[bizarre chiming]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- You're powerless, Flash,
but I can help you...
if you let me.
- You want to help?
Tell me how to save my wife.
- She needs to go back
where she belongs.
All of you do.
Back to the Mirrorverse.
You see, in the last six years
I've watched people like Joseph
destroy the gift around you,
the glorious world
filled with wonder.
You and everyone else
on this planet have failed.
♪ ♪
So now I'm filling it
with my children...
and we will treat it
and everyone in it
with respect.
- And what happens to us?
- You adapt to your new world,
same as I did.
Don't worry, Barry,
I'm not gonna kill anyone.
I'm not your enemy.
♪ ♪
What I am is a mother
to a newer, better world.
- You want me to give in
just like Ramsey.
- Ramsey thought
he was a hero.
He wasn't.
You are.
Lead your people
to the Mirrorverse.
They'll follow you.
They'll be happy.
- Were you?
- Stop fighting me.
- You've been watching me, Eva.
You know I'd risk my life
to save this city.
- Those are brave words, Flash,
but are you really willing
to do whatever it takes
to ensure
the survival of humanity?
The applications of
my reflective chip technology
are endless.
I can grow crops
tenfold in abundance.
I can end starvation overnight.
Why haven't you?
Why haven't you done the work
that really matters?
Why haven't you made this world
a better place?
[dramatic music]
Because you can't.
♪ ♪
I can, and I will.
I'm not human.
♪ ♪
I'm something better.
That is why
I am showing you mercy.
So please consider my offer...
♪ ♪
And make the right choice.
- Satellites have him
at McCulloch.
- Barry,
I am not losing you too.
- Frost is ready to come out.
♪ ♪
[bizarre chiming]
- Oh, thank Tupac.
- How did you escape?
- I didn't.
Eva let me go.
- Why?
What did she want?
- To tell us that we can't win.
- Well, I hope you told her
where to go.
- No, she's right.
We can't.
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
[ethereal whooshing]
♪ ♪
Nash?
- No, my name is Harrison...
Dr. Harrison Wells.
♪ ♪
- Look,
I don't know who you are,
but I saw Nash die.
All the other Wells
died with him.
- Exactly, and when Nash Wells
gave his life
to power
the artificial Speed Force,
he transferred
all the multiversal particles
of all the other Wells
into the fusion sphere
except for 0.01 percent,
and that's me.
[soft dramatic music]
- How do particles
become a person?
- I have a theory
that when Nash
and all the other Wells
were removed
from the timeline,
the universe required...
a balancing act.
One Wells to make up
for all those lost.
Isn't that cosmic?
- Crisis.
There was an event.
It took people
from other planets
and brought them here together
to the same planet
in one timeline.
- A temporal coalescence.
That...could explain this.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Of all the Wells,
you were the one
I wanted to meet the most.
♪ ♪
I'm B...
- Barry Allen.
I know.
The other Wells may be gone,
but they left
an imprint, memories,
and so let me just say that,
whatever is wrong...
♪ ♪
Let me help you
because they would want me to.
- You can't.
This enemy
that we're facing
is all-powerful,
plus my speed is gone.
- Aren't you
the Paragon of Love?
Look, anyone can save the world
with their speed,
with their might,
but it takes a real hero...
A once-in-a-lifetime hero,
to do it with his heart.
- What is that
supposed to mean?
- It means run, Barry.
Run toward love.
♪ ♪
- Nash?
- No.
Allegra.
Nash thought...
very highly of you.
♪ ♪
- A new Wells.
How is that possible?
- Oh, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're here to save us, right?
[chuckles]
Also, which one is he?
- I'm the original.
♪ ♪
- Okay, I had Allegra
put out a "Citizen" e-blast
to warn the city about Eva.
- Good work.
- Thanks.
- [sighs]
[eerie music]
What is it?
- That window was blacked out.
Where is everyone?
- Oh, I'm feeling
an overwhelming sense
of passion, confidence, focus.
Joe, I...
[screams]
♪ ♪
- You may as well
give up, Captain.
- Joe?
- Captain West
requesting backup.
- No one's coming, Captain.
Cecile, run!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
The windows.
- My phone's not working.
- She must have
jammed the signal.
♪ ♪
- Unfortunate.
Wells, Wells,
Wells, Wells, Wells, Wells,
Well, and Wells.
And that's how I got here.
Any questions?
- Uh, I don't get...
- Hey.
- Help!
Guys, we need help.
- Sue?
Ralph?
- [groaning]
- Holy plasmas.
Dibs, where's your face?
It looks like mashed potatoes.
- Don't!
Don't touch him.
- Oh.
- His body temp's
a toasty 500 degrees.
- Wait, you mean something
actually melted Elongated Man?
Holy sweet Hawking.
- Ralph texted me to meet him
at McCulloch Labs.
- He was looking for evidence
to clear your name, wasn't he?
- Yeah, he figured security
would be down
because of the blackout.
He was inside when Eva
blew the whole place up.
I got caught
in the blast radius.
He walked out holding this.
[dramatic music]
Can you fix him?
- Right, I'll get him
in the mobile biogenic
containment unit.
- Okay, we're going this way.
Right this way, Ralph.
- Come with me, Sue.
I'll take a look at your arm.
♪ ♪
- That's looking
a little toasty.
Okay.
- Anything?
- [sighs]
I mean, not real...
[computer beeps]
Wait.
[chuckles]
Yeah, Ralph found evidence
to clear Sue's name.
♪ ♪
- Once a hero, always a hero.
- Amen.
- I know you're still
in there somewhere.
I'll never stop fighting
to reach you.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
I may be
the Paragon of Love, but...
♪ ♪
That's only because
you're my heart.
Please come back to me.
[electricity crackles]
♪ ♪
- Cisco:I don't get it.
How are you supposed
to get your speed back exactly?
- Iris.
Iris is the key.
- Yeah, still not following.
- The Speed Force,
we all thought
it was dead, right?
I just felt a spark
with Iris just now.
- Barry, your speed is gone.
- No, but the Speed Force
is an elemental part
of the universe,
so theoretically...
- Theoretically it could have
never disappeared.
- And you think
it's still in Iris.
- I always wondered why I was
chosen as the Paragon of Love
and how it related to my speed.
I think it's because
of my connection with Iris.
Our love is just as strong
as the lightning bolt
that hit me seven years ago,
plus Iris did have speed once.
- And Nora was a speedster
whose lightning
was purple and yellow.
- That is so romantic.
- If Speed Force energy
is still in Iris,
how do we get it out of her?
- Well...
- We repurpose the ASF
to tap into an organic source
instead of an artificial one.
- I can help with that.
- Okay, well, I'm gonna need...
- Yeah, I got it.
- If this works,
we can all take the fight
to Eva together.
[dramatic music]
[sirens blaring]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Bring them
a new life, my children.
♪ ♪
- Go, go, go!
- No!
♪ ♪
[door thuds]
- Knock, knock.
♪ ♪
- cop:It's too late, Captain.
This is mother's world now.
- Can she get through?
- Yes.
That door wasn't designed
for tactical force.
[door thuds]
- Ah!
Well, it should have been.
- These old buildings still
have the original ductwork.
- Human beings took this world
for granted, Captain.
We won't.
♪ ♪
- I don't want to leave you.
Please, Joe, come on.
- Kiss Jenna for me.
[door thudding]
Now go.
♪ ♪
- Okay, she's breathing.
What's the ETA on
that energy coupling reroute?
- Energy cycle is rerouted.
- And fusion sphere
completely remapped.
I have to say,
is this how you guys operate?
Because that much contact
with that much unrefined power,
this is a huge gamble.
Mr. Allen,
if you're wrong about Iris,
every atom in your body
will be split in two.
- Barry.
[spirited music]
♪ ♪
- We need you.
We need you.
- I'll be okay.
♪ ♪
- Energy's climbing.
- Wells:Run, Barry, run.
Run towards love.
♪ ♪
- Oh, yep,
ain't no A in this SF.
♪ ♪
- Incredible.
- We're at 100% organic speed.
- We need you.
We need you.
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- I knew you'd find
your way back to me.
- You'll always be
my lightning rod.
[dramatic music]
[people screaming
indistinctly]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- Don't be afraid.
You're going someplace better.
I promise.
Take them.
- No!
Flash!
You've made your choice.
Now face the consequences!
♪ ♪
- It's over, Eva.
- Why doesn't Flash
use his speed?
- Well, Eva's body's made up
of quantum protons,
which are capable
of sub-light speed,
so technically...
- She's faster.
♪ ♪
[door thudding]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- You're not Cecile.
- No.
But she's close.
And if you want
to be with her...
♪ ♪
There's only one way.
- Why should I trust you?
♪ ♪
- You have no choice.
Hmm.
[dramatic music]
- You and I
could have worked together
toward a common good.
It's too late now.
Humankind is done.
My children
are taking over the world,
and I'm their queen mother,
and tonight I begin my reign
as Mirror Monarch.
- Actually,
we're just getting started.
[soundwave blasts]
- How do you like
the sonics, my lady?
[YONAKA's "Teach Me to Fight"]
But wait, there's more.
♪ ♪
- Now, Flash.
- ♪ Small town baby ♪
♪ Got his knickers
in a twist ♪
♪ Doesn't like the way
that this car suits my lips ♪
♪ What you think? ♪
- Not fair.
You brought your team.
- ♪ You're trying
to be your best you ♪
♪ Suited and booted ♪
- Maybe I should bring mine.
- ♪ Trying to act a grown-up ♪
♪ Now that's pretty funny ♪
♪ I fired everyone,
now I be making plenty ♪
♪ I'm feeling pretty empty ♪
♪ This attitude's expensive ♪
♪ Take a trip
and you might find ♪
♪ Let's make this public ♪
♪ Let's take it outside ♪
♪ Put down your small talk ♪
♪ And teach me to fight ♪
- Sounds like Iron Heights
on a Saturday night out there.
♪ ♪
♪ Caught in the middle ♪
♪ Karma can raise your face ♪
♪ Trying too hard ♪
♪ Yeah, it's gonna
make you age ♪
♪ Walk into the room ♪
♪ Everybody looks the same ♪
♪ I'm so tired of this place ♪
♪ Yeah, why you scared
of change, yeah ♪
♪ Too many photos
and not enough friends ♪
♪ Waiting on the next fad
and the next trend ♪
♪ Posers in the hall ♪
♪ And they clogging up
the stairways ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Come on, baby, let's play ♪
♪ Let's make this public ♪
♪ Let's take it outside ♪
♪ Put down your small talk ♪
♪ And teach me to fight ♪
- Cover me!
- ♪ Let's make this personal,
stop wasting my time ♪
- If I can't fix
these things in time...
- You better
figure something out...
and fast.
- Let's do this.
- ♪ It's all I seem to see ♪
♪ And it's all
you seem to know ♪
♪ Bet you're itching
to find out ♪
- Frost!
- ♪ But the party's
is going to go ♪
♪ See you turn up at my door ♪
♪ But you don't know anyone ♪
♪ And the party's over now ♪
♪ Can't you see
you're on your own? ♪
- Every big bad has a weakness.
What did we miss?
♪ ♪
- The fact that Barry
needs more than speed
to win this fight.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- [screams]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- Finish him.
- Flash!
No, Eva, please don't.
- It's too late.
Flash has had his chance.
- And so do you.
Eva, you're destroying
this world.
- No, I'm liberating it
from an infestation.
My children deserve this planet
more than humankind does.
I'll deal with him.
Join the others.
♪ ♪
- Eva.
- You just can't give up,
can you?
Fine.
Good-bye.
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
That's impossible.
You're still not strong enough
to beat me.
Not yet.
- Eva.
You told my husband
that you wanted
to bring peace to this world.
You are using brutal force
against defenseless people.
Eva, my duplicate,
she was connected
to this world with herself,
but your other children,
they are filled with hate.
Look around.
Is this your idea of peace?
- Please, no!
No, please!
[people screaming indistinctly]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Is this really what you want?
- Get back.
Now is our chance.
- No, please.
Just wait.
- No.
No, I...
I wanted
to make things better.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I failed two worlds.
- Eva, it's never too late
to do the right thing.
You've told me about
your dream to help people.
You still can right here,
right now by ending this.
♪ ♪
The foundation
for a better world
is compassion, not violence.
A true monarch knows that.
[sirens blaring]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
- Keep going!
Keep going!
[screams]
♪ ♪
- It's not working.
[people screaming]
♪ ♪
They've grown too strong
for me to control!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We did it.
- What about
the people we lost?
♪ ♪
- Chief Singh?
Sir, what happened?
Are we...
- Dead?
No, Officer,
we're very much alive,
and I'm pretty sure
we owe our lives
to a certain speedster
and his better half.
♪ ♪
- Joe?
Oh, oh!
[phone buzzes]
- Is it really you?
- No, it's Chewbacca.
- It's Kamilla, the real one.
If she's back then...
- That means the rest
of Central City is too.
- Where are you?
- I'm back at "The Citizen."
I was in that other place.
I never thought I'd get out.
- Don't go anywhere.
I'ma kiss you
like there's no tomorrow.
♪ ♪
I love you, Kamilla.
- I love you too.
- [chuckles]
- Need a ride?
I'm ice bridging...
safest way to travel.
- Knowing you,
I find that hard to believe.
- So what will you do now?
♪ ♪
- Go back to the Mirrorverse,
do what I should have done
a long time ago...start over.
♪ ♪
This time my children
will be born of love, not hate,
free to choose their own path.
- Good luck.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Any sign of Eva?
- No, looks like Mirror Monarch
was serious
about starting over.
- Iris, what you did out there,
what if you're a meta now?
- I'm pretty sure Eva
took my mirror powers back
with her when she left.
- Maybe when she went back
to the Mirrorverse
it severed the link.
Without it, no powers.
- Well, the pod people
are gone.
We got everyone else back.
Singh, Dearbons, Kamilla.
That's a good day's work,
people.
Oh, wait, where's OG Wells?
- With Cisco and Allegra.
- They wanted to say
their own good-byes.
- Ah.
- You sure you have to go?
I heard Team Flash
always has a Wells.
- Well, that's overrated,
plus Flash has his speed back,
Mirror Monarch is back
where she belongs.
It's time.
- But I need someone
to train me.
- Allegra, you have
your own wavelength to follow,
and, as it turns out,
somehow I have mine.
The universe gave me
my life back somehow,
and now I can see all 92 years
of that life past,
present,
and future simultaneously,
and somehow can travel
to any moment I want.
- Timeless Wells.
That's a new one.
- It's amazing
and utterly useless
unless I can share it
with the woman that I love,
my wife, Tess.
We had 4 brilliant
years together before she...
Before we both were killed,
and so I now have a choice
between moving forward
from this point without her...
Or going back to her.
Well, I'm going to relive
those 4 years we had together
over and over and over again
until I'm out of time.
- Good luck.
- Allegra, good luck to you.
- I get that,
wanting to be
with the person you love.
If Kamilla and I
are lucky enough
to share half of
what you and Tess have...
- You will.
- This is weird.
- Yeah, we just met.
- Right?
It's like I barely
even know you.
- We barely know each other.
- I mean,
you're nothing like him.
- Like who?
Oh, the Harrison Wells
you used to know.
- Or the man I thought
was Harrison Wells.
Of course,
he turned out to be a...
both: A jerk?
- Yeah.
[both chuckle]
- How do you miss someone
you barely even know?
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Before you go, how exactly
do you travel in time?
♪ ♪
- Easy.
Just...like this.
♪ ♪
- Oh, just like that.
- Sue:Well, we spoke
to Captain West.
Actually, I did.
Ralph's voice
would have freaked him out.
- What's not to love
about my silky tones?
- Dude, you sound like a Dalek.
- Yeah, I feel like
the helmet's more Daft Punk.
What?
You know I love to lose myself
to dance every once in a while.
- Baby, do not...do not.
- You love it.
- Don't worry, Ralph.
A few more days
in the BCU,
and you'll be good as new.
- Either way, it's
good to have you back, Caity.
Frost, too.
- So now that my parents
are okay
and CCPD has evidence
to clear me,
thanks to Ralph...
- We should celebrate.
- Sue, did you ever think
about joining Team Flash?
We could use somebody
with your skills.
- Me, teaming up
with Dr. Perfect
and a squeaky clean do-gooder
like Fleet Feet here?
[chuckles]
Not my style.
Besides, Ralph and I
have some unfinished business.
Black Hole is dead, but there's
an organization just like them
in every country in the world
preying on good people
like my parents.
- And we're gonna
pay them a visit.
- And clean house.
- Ralph,
we've been through a lot
since you joined this team.
- Ah, save it, Bar.
This ain't goodbye.
I'll be back when you
least expect it, and then,
Frost, we'll go on
that road trip, okay?
- She says, "Hell, yeah."
- Well, if you ever need help,
just call.
I'll come running.
- Thanks, you do the same.
Come on, slick.
- Stay flashy.
Dibny, out.
- They make quite the team.
[spirited music]
♪ ♪
- So do we.
[electricity crackling]
- Greg, move your head.