- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present,
and now our world is more
dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- So what are you
going to do with him?
- I think our time would be
better served
learning how to cure him.
- You should really talk
to Dr. Lamden.
- Grodd's attacking him
psychically.
He's paralyzed.
- Human weak.
- We could make
a meta-human cure.
- There's gotta be something
we could do outside the box.
- [screaming]
- You shouldn't go
to your office.
Not right now.
- Why?
- How many times
has this happened?
- 52.
- If I want to stop Cicada,
I can't be so precious
about getting
The Flash's hands dirty.
Sometimes the ends
justify the means.
I get that now.
[people shouting, clamoring]
[dramatic music]
- Can't move.
- [roaring]
♪ ♪
- Ladies and gentlemen,
we finally have our hands
on the meta-human cure.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Cool, cool.
It's not like I spent weeks
in the frozen tundra
or anything.
- No, no, no.
I think that just people are
waiting for
the inevitable "but"
that follows
such a big statement.
- Mmm, no, it's done,
and thanks to Caitlin,
we even have a way to deliver
our silver bullet,
so no, no "buts."
- I believe
there is a big "but" coming.
- But we need to test
the cure on a meta-human.
- [speaks French]
There it is.
- What we need is to save
the metas that
Cicada is targeting
because he's not gonna stop
killing innocent people.
- Is the cure dangerous?
- Well, it's an untested serum
that alters biology
on a cellular level,
so until we try it out
on someone,
we have no way
of knowing.
- When we started working
on the cure,
we decided that it would always
be a choice, not a weapon,
so all we need
is a volunteer.
- Well, there's quite
a conundrum, right?
A meta-human volunteer when
the meta-humans in this city
have been chased away by us
or killed by Cicada
or incarcerated
at Iron Heights Prison, so...
- Nobody from either group
is gonna volunteer.
- No, these criminals
are not going to relinquish
their powers, although...
- There's gotta be
somebody somewhere.
- Yes, on another Earth.
- Oh, I'll call Harry, see if
there's anybody from Earth-2
who wants to volunteer.
- Yes.
- Not really what
I was suggesting.
- Hold on,
you don't have to call Harry.
- Wait, why not?
- Because there's already
a meta here from Earth-2,
one who might not
want his powers...
although it might be pretty
difficult to talk to him.
- King Shark...
you really think
you can cure him?
- That's the idea.
- Oh, Lyla, this is, um...
my daughter, Nora.
- Your daughter?
- Yeah.
- I'm from...
- The future, I'm guessing.
- Weird, right?
- No weirder than
waking up one day
to find out that your son
used to be your daughter.
So, why King Shark?
- Dark matter levels vary
from meta-human to meta-human,
but Shay Lamden's case
is the most extreme we've seen,
so we think if we could reverse
the effects of a high level
mutation like his...
- You can help all meta-humans.
- Look, we know King Shark
has limited speech,
but we're wondering,
could we try and talk to him?
If we're gonna do this, we're
gonna need his permission.
- Well, you're in luck, Cisco.
Lately,
he's been quite talkative.
[jazzy music playing]
- Look at these pictures.
- So peaceful.
- Mm.
- So beautiful.
So peaceful.
- It is, isn't it?
- You know, I never understood
why Wally went there.
Now I do.
- Well, it makes me wonder.
I mean, is my baby brother
ever coming back from Tibet?
- Well, all I can say
is that he is more at ease
than he has ever been.
- Hm.
- And if that means
he wants to stay away from...
[sighs] The crazy that
is Central City,
then, you know what?
So be it.
- Yeah.
Well, I am glad that
you're back, Dad.
- We're all glad
that you're back.
Mmm.
Even Captain Singh is glad
that you're back.
[baby crying]
- Wha...
- I'll get it.
- No, no, no.
No, you will not.
You will not.
You have been on
crying baby duty
for far too long, Joe West.
[smooches]
[whispering]
So happy you're back.
- All right,
all right.
[laughter]
- Are we ever gonna talk
about this couch you bought?
- Another day, Joe.
Another day.
- [whispering]
Very expensive.
- I mean, it's nice.
Listen.
So, Cecile...
- Mm-hmm.
- Has brought me up to speed.
Cicada...been very busy.
[soft dramatic music]
- Yeah, well...
[laughs softly]
You know, Team Flash will
figure out a way to beat him.
- But Jonesy was helping him
right under our nose,
and that got me thinking,
Cicada's eluded capture
for so long
that I'm thinking that
he's still getting help
from somebody.
♪ ♪
- I want more coffee.
I'm gonna make
some more coffee.
Yeah, I'll bring you
a fresh cup.
- Normally, we don't bring in
outside help but we got wind
that the top ichthyologist in
the country was doing research
on cases just like
King Shark's.
Actually,
I think you may know her.
- Dr. Lamden?
You're working
for A.R.G.U.S. now?
- Couldn't say no.
And please, call me Tanya.
- What about
Nautilus Laboratories?
- Director Michaels offered me
the opportunity to work
with another Shay Lamden,
one afflicted with the same
dark matter anomaly
as my late husband,
only this Shay system
was causing
his neural pathways to regress.
I'm teaching him how
to communicate effectively.
- Are you saying his mind
is becoming more shark-like?
- It was, but not anymore.
I stopped the regression
of King Shark's mind
using a cerebral interface
that stimulates
his neural outputs.
I call it a telepathic crown.
- Kinda like the
M.A.D. 2.0 we built.
That's brilliant.
- My husband,
the Shay Lamden of Earth-1,
was a wonderful man.
Now, I have the chance to help
another Earth's Shay Lamden,
by giving him back
his human mind.
And since Shay's current state
requires him to be
in the water more,
these earbuds allow me
to hear him
under water and vice versa.
- The telepathic crown
allows Tanya to get through
to King Shark and curb
his violent behavior.
- Can we use the crown
to talk to him?
- Yes, but why?
- We think we can
make him human again.
- [laughs softly]
- It's taken a lot of work, but
we think we figured out a way
to transform
dark matter-infused cells
back to their non-meta state.
- Now, all we need to do
is test it,
so we came looking
for a volunteer.
- That could really work?
- So, can we ask him?
♪ ♪
[machine beeping]
- Shay, a team from
S.T.A.R. Labs is here.
They have something
you may want...
a meta-cure
for your condition.
Trust me,
their preliminary analysis
on reversing meta-gene
transfigurations
proves there is a strong chance
it could work,
especially in
ichthyological prospects.
[laughing]
No, I'm not just showing off.
It's their research.
Shay has
a wonderful sense of humor.
- So, are we supposed to call
him King Shark or Shay?
- Yes, I'm still here.
Uh-huh.
I agree.
Okay.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- You believe
this cure could help?
- Yeah.
- Where do we begin?
[sharp feedback ringing]
- [roars]
- [grunts]
- This is Agent Michaels.
I need every available soldier
at the aquarium now!
♪ ♪
- Dad?
- I'm fine.
- W-What was all that feedback?
I thought he was under control.
- I don't know.
Nothing like that
has ever happened before.
Maybe his neuroregression
finally reached the point
where the crown
could no longer affect him.
Shay could be lost forever.
- No, no, no.
We don't know that.
Why don't you come to
S.T.A.R. Labs with us.
We can use the M.A.D. 2.0 to
boost the crown's efficiency.
- We need to find King Shark
before he hurts anyone.
- A.R.G.U.S. backup protocols
have been activated,
but King Shark
could be anywhere.
- We'll re-task the
S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
to work in circuit
with A.R.G.U.S.
- What's on your mind?
- Just wondering
if we need to rethink
how we're going to catch him.
- [laughing]
- Stop, that did not happen.
- Yes, it did.
- [laughs]
- Look, my lips went numb,
and then they swelled up
so bad it looked like
I had plastic surgery.
- What did Wally do?
- He laughed, of course.
The baby laughed.
- [laughs]
- At least now I know I'm
allergic to Szechuan peppers.
- Dad, do you mind
if I work here today, actually?
Might give us some time
to catch up.
- Well, you know I'm never
gonna turn that down, so...
Uh, but, Cecile tells me
that you have
a fancy new office?
- Yeah, yeah, it's just,
you know, the plumbing
is really lousy and
I can't have water
dripping on my laptop, right?
- Well, hey, uh, the guy that
expanded our guest bath...
he did a really great job
and he's really affordable.
- Let me give you his number.
- No, Dad, it's fine, really.
- Iris, if you don't
take care of this quickly,
it could snowball.
Here.
Let me just send it to you.
- Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
Actually, yeah, you know what?
That's a great idea.
Why don't you send it to me
and I'll head over there
and see what I can do.
Thanks, Dad.
- Okay.
Muah.
- Love you.
- Love you more.
- So, if we wanna
boost the crown's powers,
we gotta get it
to talk to the M.A.D. 2.0.
- What about
a logarithmic code?
- Exactly.
You see, this is why we need
more scientists on the team.
- Shay tells me that
all the time.
- Well, the guy knows
what he's talking about.
All right, so,
why don't you use
my workstation,
and I'll get this going.
- Fascinating, right?
- Yeah, it should be.
- It's the merging
of technology
and human consciousness.
- And shark,
but no, no, no.
I'm referring to your
relationship with Shay Lamden.
- What do you mean,
"relationship"?
- [speaking French]
The way your posture relaxes
when you're speaking of him
and the way
your voice modulates...
it suggests a familiarity...
- Hm.
- Or something more.
- We're both marine biologists,
so we have a lot in common.
I guess you could say
we've grown very close.
But he's just my patient.
- Oh, of course.
- Look at that.
We have liftoff.
They are actually talking.
You see?
I knew these two crazy kids
were gonna make it work.
- They aren't just synching up.
The M.A.D. 2.0 is acting
like an antennae,
amplifying the
crown's psychic signal
beyond anything
I could have imagined.
- We heard geek screaming.
How are things going in here?
- I just need to synch
the helmet to my earbuds,
and we're good to go.
- Left that in the cortex,
in the main console,
by the monitor to the left.
You know what?
Come with me.
I'll show you.
- Great work, Cisco.
- Oh, well, takes a village.
But every village
needs a genius
and that's me, so thank you.
- Now we just have to find
King Shark and talk him down.
- Why don't we get the cure
injector to Caitlin
and make sure it's ready to go.
- Well, remember,
we gotta talk to him first.
- Right.
[alert blips]
- We got a hit on King Shark.
He's at the wharf.
[alarm ringing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Caitlin,
are you sure he's here?
- Oh, he's there.
He's heading
straight right for you.
- [roars]
- Nora, you're up.
- Done.
- Okay, systems are synched.
- Shay?
It's me, Tanya.
These people are
only here to help you.
Please listen to them.
- It's okay.
- [snarling]
- I think it's working.
- I think you're right.
Let's ask him...
[grunts]
- Shay, stop!
Please.
Please. I don't know
what's wrong with him.
- [roars]
- [screams]
- [gasps]
- Barry?
- [panting]
[device beeps]
- [roars]
- [grunts]
[King Shark roaring]
♪ ♪
- Guys, what's happening?
Where's Shay?
- [gasping, grunting]
- Shay?
- What is it?
- What's going on?
- Is Shay okay?
- Yeah.
He's human again.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Where am I?
Who are you?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- No, enough!
Just get off me!
- It's okay.
They're friends.
- [grunts]
Tanya.
- Yeah, it's...it's me.
- I'm...me?
How?
- We call it the cure.
It's a serum that suppresses
dark matter in meta-humans.
You're the first person
to take it.
- Well, except
you didn't take it.
- We, um, we gave it to you.
- My...my head
is still swirling around.
[soft dramatic music]
Are you saying
I'm human again?
Forever?
- Almost.
We developed a cure to work on
the human part of a meta-human.
The animal part of your brain
fought back a little bit.
There's still some dark matter
in your pituitary gland,
but with this new data,
we should be able to
address the cure and the
next dose should be permanent.
- Monsieur Lamden,
I should introduce myself.
Sherloque Wells.
You've probably heard of me.
I have a question.
I've been debating in my brain.
What drives the King Shark?
Is it the shark,
or is it the man?
- If you're asking should
I be held accountable
for my actions,
my answer is simple.
Yes, I should.
♪ ♪
I don't remember
how many people I hurt,
or who,
but that's no excuse.
- What do you remember?
- Fragments.
Glimpses.
One day, I was a scientist.
The next, I was trapped
in that body and
everything felt heightened,
like my emotions
were on steroids.
And the rage...
there was so much rage.
- That makes sense.
A shark's amygdala triggers
a huge emotional response
when it feels attacked.
- Perhaps that's why
you escaped today.
You were frightened.
- I don't know.
Today felt different.
I don't remember much before
I started using Tanya's crown,
but since then,
my mind and memory
have been much clearer.
And I especially remember the
kindness that you showed me.
- [laughs softly]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
- [whimpers]
What...
[ominous music]
What happened?
- The dark matter in
his system is replicating.
- Tanya, I'm sorry.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Shay, I'm sorry,
but until this is over,
we can't let you
leave S.T.A.R. Labs.
♪ ♪
[whispering]
Call me as soon as the cure
is ready to inject him
a second time.
We have to know if this works.
- Barry?
- Yeah?
- When you said
you wanted me to call you
it was so that
we could ask Shay
if he wants to
take the cure, right?
- Caitlin...
- 'Cause you know,
out in the field,
you didn't really give him
much of a choice.
- But that was kinda hard to do
when King Shark
had you dead to rights.
- We had a way
of communicating with him,
and you barely
gave that a shot.
And we could have
tried again.
- I saved you, man.
What did you want me to do?
Risk your life?
- That's not the point.
- It should be.
We're a team.
We're supposed to have
each other's backs.
- And we agreed, as a team,
to wait for his permission,
but you didn't even do that.
- And look what happened.
You're alive,
and Shay seems
to like being human,
so that's a win-win.
- Is that what you think
a hero does?
Forces other people to do
what you want them to do?
- He was gonna eat you, Cisco.
What was I supposed to do?
- We agreed that the cure would
never be used as a weapon.
- Tell me something.
Did you change your mind
in the moment,
or was this always
part of the plan?
♪ ♪
- ♪ If I could turn back time,
I would do it all again ♪
[upbeat pop music playing]
- Dad?
- I went by your office
to talk to you.
- Dad, look.
I, um...
- Don't.
Don't try it.
I heard about this crazy
time loop you all got stuck in.
- Cisco and Nora told me
what happened
in every version,
and although
I don't remember any of them,
just knowing what did happen...
- You weren't scared?
- I don't know.
I mean,
I broke into Cicada's home.
Dad, I fought him.
And as terrifying
as that was, I mean,
at least I could
react to it, you know?
But now...now that he knows
who I am, who my family is,
I mean, he could show up
at any moment.
- I just, I...
I feel...
- Powerless.
- Yeah, I just...
I don't know,
I can't go back there.
- Okay, get up.
- Dad, I just told you...
[stammers]
I don't want to go back there,
you know?
- I'm not taking you there.
- Then where?
- Someplace where
I can show you
how powerful you really are.
Pack it up.
Come on.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We gotta talk.
- Don't you know you shouldn't
interrupt others
while they're brooding?
Trying to get
my Oliver Queen on here.
- I ran some more tests
on Shay.
The reason he doesn't remember
anything that happened
this morning is because he
experienced a severe brain wave
disruption in his frontal lobe.
That's the feedback
that we all heard.
So, that's why he snapped on us
like it was
"Jaws: The Revenge"?
- A frontal lobe that
compromised would of course
result in lack of control
over emotions and judgment.
- So you think maybe the
crown might have done this?
- No, that's the thing.
The crown is not the problem.
The way the neurotransmitters
work in this device
never would have caused that.
- So what you're saying is
the telepathic crown
was working the whole time?
- Yes, so that
begs the question,
what caused King Shark
to go berserk?
- Guys, hey.
Um...
I just wanted
to apologize for earlier.
I was definitely too harsh.
[grunts]
[electricity crackles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
No way.
Caitlin.
- Hello, Flash.
- [growling]
- Cisco's cerebral scan
is clear.
Mine is as well.
We are both back to normal.
- No more strings on us.
- Killer Frost says
she's sorry for that ice blast.
That was Grodd, too.
Now she's ready
for some payback.
- Yeah, me too.
Do we have a 20
on our Simian Svengali?
- Data and company
are working on it,
but Grodd's psychic abilities
are helping him
conceal his location,
so he could be anywhere by now.
- I thought every
square inch of A.R.G.U.S.
was supposed to be
power dampened 24 hours a day.
- It is.
- [laughs] Then how does
an 800-pound gorilla escape?
- Let me show you.
I went through
our security footage.
This is from the night
of May 22nd, 2018.
- That's the night...
- Of the Enlightenment.
[soft dramatic music]
- DeVoe's dark matter wave
took down all tech
in the surrounding areas.
Luckily,
our generators kicked in.
- But not for a second.
- One second.
That's all Grodd needed
to psychically implant
instructions in a guard.
- Instructions
to secretly shut down
the power dampeners
in his cell,
and find out any other
information he needed to know.
- So that's why
King Shark flipped out?
Because Grodd was trying
to mind control him?
- Likely as a distraction.
- Grodd's only ever
controlled human minds before.
- He must have had a hard time
controlling King Shark
because of the animal part
of his brain.
- So King Shark was trying
to resist Grodd's iron will?
Respect.
- If Grodd's had his powers
for a year,
why wait until now
to escape?
- It's probably no coincidence
that the first thing he did
was steal the telepathic crown.
- Tanya did say she's been
working on the crown
for a while.
Grodd probably knew this
was his perfect opportunity.
- And it was thanks
to our tech.
- All right, well,
now that Grodd has the crown,
what's gonna happen
when he uses it?
- It'll amplify his mental
abilities a thousand-fold.
Instead of just
being able to mind control
a few people at a time...
- He'll be able to
control the whole city.
♪ ♪
- Forgive me.
I'm intruding.
Or am I?
I see him out there and I see
you in here in the shadows.
Why is that, I wonder?
- Can you blame me?
You saw his hand transform.
- [laughs] Yes, right.
"Shark Week!"
Not something you see
every day, but no,
I thought your
hesitation occurred
before that moment,
not after.
It was a slight hesitation,
but it was there nonetheless.
Again,
why do you think that is?
- I don't know...
[laughs softly]
- No? Well, perhaps
I could be so bold as to offer
a suggestion that
it is not the hand
of which you were frightened,
but rather,
it was seeing the face
of the man that you love.
- I don't love Shay.
We're friends.
- All right, well, let's take
a look at that too, shall we?
So this is a friend
from another Earth,
for whom you left
a high-paying job
and for whom you have
dedicated every waking moment
of your life trying to help.
It doesn't quite add up.
- I can't love Shay.
He's my dead husband's
doppelganger from Earth-2.
How crazy would I have to be
to fall in love with him?
- No crazier than
marrying the same woman
from five different Earths...
[laughs]
I know.
I'm very good
at marrying people,
but not so great
at staying married.
Along the way, though,
on these countless Earths
and countless doppelgangers,
I learned there is one thing
that makes all of us unique.
And if that
is what you fell in love with,
well then,
perhaps a face
doesn't matter that much.
♪ ♪
- You missed
a beautiful sunset earlier.
- Too bad.
It's my favorite time of day.
- Mine, too.
I almost forgot
what one looked like.
Did you know sharks
are colorblind?
When I was King Shark,
my world was dull and gray.
And then I met you,
and everything changed.
♪ ♪
I thought you were avoiding me.
- I was,
but not anymore.
- Tanya, are you disappointed
in me now that I'm...
- No, not at all.
They say every sunset
is unique.
Do you think that's true?
- Yes, I do.
♪ ♪
- Dad, this is not
going to work.
- You haven't
even tried it yet.
- Look, I get it.
I'm supposed to take out
my frustrations on that bag
and somehow get over it,
but it's not that easy.
- To confront what ails you?
No, it's not.
It's hard.
I had to go all the way
across the world to do it.
- Are you talking about Tibet?
I thought you went there
to see Wally.
- I did, but that's not
the only reason I went.
I went there to heal.
- Is that why you were gone
for so long?
- Wally convinced me
to come east with the baby.
He said it would help me
repair my mind,
my body,
restore this old soul of mine.
So with Cecile's blessing,
that's what I did.
- And did it work?
- I bent, baby girl.
But Cicada
ain't going to break me.
Ain't going
to break you either.
Come on.
[rousing music]
Come on, Iris.
Show Cicada what you got.
- [grunting]
- Break him, Iris.
♪ ♪
- [shouts, grunts]
- Break him!
- [shouts]
- [laughs]
Yeah.
- [panting]
[dramatic music]
- What's happening?
- Our fuzzy friend is
crawling up the Broome Belfry.
What is it with him
and that tower?
- 'Cause it's at the exact
epicenter of the city...
- Making it the perfect place
to broadcast from.
- He's going to use the crown.
- And get inside everyone's
head in the city.
- [roars]
♪ ♪
- Hear your master, Humans.
Soon,
you will only know my will...
the will of Grodd!
- How long before everyone's
under Grodd's mind control?
- A few minutes, maybe less.
We need to dismantle that crown
and get it away from him.
- I can try talking to him.
He's always had
a sweet spot for me.
- Good.
- The hell you will.
- Nope, Killer Frost is gonna
be a hard sell on that one.
- We're immune
to his mind control, right,
because we're speedsters?
- No.
- Okay, The Flash Museum
just straight up
got a lot of stuff wrong.
- Wait,
but do you have any extra
anti-mind control
headsets lying around?
- There's a few
in the workshop,
but it didn't work
so well last time.
- Yeah,
but now there's two of us.
I need you to run at him
as fast as you can
without reversing time.
- Okay.
- That'll get his attention.
- What are you gonna do?
- An old trick.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[people screaming]
[panicked chatter]
- [roars]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Get the crown!
- Dad?
- [heavy breathing]
[sharp feedback ringing]
[roars]
- [grunts]
[tires screeching]
[horns blaring]
- We can't move.
- The mental dampeners
are working,
but Grodd's too strong.
I'm trying to hack into the
crown, but Grodd won't let me.
- He's gonna kill them.
- Not if you turn me back.
I can stop Grodd.
He can't read my mind...
at least, not when I'm a shark.
- Can you do that?
- I mean, if we accelerate
the cell cycle,
do something that
will prompt a return
to the dark matter
cellular form.
- Right, right, perhaps
a vibration or a jolt, right?
- Yes,
if it was strong enough,
but there would be
permanent consequences.
If we re-saturate
your meta-genic cells,
that will eliminate
the possibility
for you to transform them
back into human cells.
- He won't be able
to use the cure.
- Shay, if you agree to this,
you'll never be human again.
- Tanya, I can save Flash,
the people of this city, you,
and make up for some of the
horrible things I've done.
I have to do this.
- I'm afraid of losing you.
- You won't.
- Well, is there
anyone in this room
that can provide
a vibrational jolt?
- I'm doing it.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[grunting]
[roars]
- My mind grows.
Soon,
Grodd will rule this city,
this world.
And you...
gone forever.
♪ ♪
- King Shark?
- Huh?
- King Shark wants you gone!
[both grunt]
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
Guys, King Shark's not moving.
- When a shark
is turned upside down,
it enters tonic immobility.
- He's in
a state of paralysis.
- How do we wake him up?
- Don't sharks have
electroreceptor organs
called ampullae of Lorenzini?
It's how they detect
electromagnetic fields, right?
- Yes, it's how they navigate.
- And it will also
attract electricity, right?
So if we can get enough
electricity to him, we can...
- Electrify his ass back up.
- Electrify his ass right up.
- Barry!
- Yeah, we heard.
Time for another old trick.
- [roars]
♪ ♪
[roars]
- [roars]
- You okay?
- [snarling]
♪ ♪
- Yes!
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Nothing to it.
- Long live the king.
- [roaring]
- I know Grodd almost
turned all of our brains
into scrambled eggs,
but that Kaiju battle
was the stuff of dreams.
- Seriously,
way better than anything
I read in The Flash Museum.
- Now that
Grodd is safely locked up,
what's stopping him
from getting out again?
- A medically-induced coma,
one safely administered
by Caitlin
and the A.R.G.U.S.
medical staff.
- Exposure to the crown
kickstarted Grodd's
mental abilities
into high gear.
They're growing even now.
Fortunately, I realized that if
Grodd's brain remains inactive,
he can't access
his mental powers.
- Add in newly-enhanced
AI power dampeners
that upgrade to keep up
with Grodd's power.
- You're welcome, by the way...
anything it takes
to keep the city safe.
- Speaking of
keeping the city safe,
we couldn't have
done this without Shay.
- How'd you guys convince him
to turn back into King Shark?
- We didn't.
- He volunteered.
- And you can never turn him
back into a human?
- I don't think so.
- So he's gonna stay
King Shark forever?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Well,
the good guys won once again,
and yet you do not seem like
you're really celebrating.
Why that is?
- [huffs]
After all
that's happened today,
I just wonder
how it will effect...
- Your relationship?
Well, that's a big question,
I must admit.
But you know what?
You will figure it out,
both of you, together.
- If so,
we'll have you to thank.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- Me especially.
- No, no, no.
I did nothing.
No, you're right,
I did help quite a bit.
The point here is simply this,
and that is that whether
it's man or shark or...
man-shark,
the heart wants
what the heart wants.
And so,
you must be open to that.
- Sounds like you've solved
life's greatest mystery.
- Well, that's what I do.
- [laughs]
- If so,
I hope one day, you find
what you're looking for too...
maybe in another doppelganger.
[hopeful music]
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- I'll leave you to it.
- Tanya, you look sad.
Why?
- We found each other today,
and now that connection is...
- Still here.
- Shay, what you did...
- I would do it again
for you, my love.
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- Time to bend.
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
- King Shark
versus Gorilla Grodd?
Are you kidding me?
I missed that?
♪ ♪
[laughs softly]
- Are you sure you don't want
something a bit more grown up?
- Um, you take that back.
This snack is a delicacy
no matter how old you are.
- [scoffs]
- Guys, hey.
I just...Swedish Fish?
I love those.
Um, look,
I know today has been crazy,
and I just wanted to
make sure that we're good,
I know Grodd made you
blast me in the face
but I also know
I kinda deserved it...
same with being ice blasted.
I shouldn't have used
the cure as a weapon
and forced it on King Shark.
I promise
it won't happen again.
♪ ♪
- Apology accepted.
Goober.
- And we know something good
did come out of today.
We know the
meta-human cure works.
- And now we can use it
to help all of the metas
in Central City and beyond.
- Maybe we start with Cicada.
- I'm sorry, what?
- I know, I just...
people can surprise you.
Today definitely
reminded me that.
And like you've been saying,
everybody deserves a choice
to be whoever they want to be...
that includes our enemies.
I think we should offer
the cure to Cicada.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.