They want us to believe
Vought superheroes are the answer.
What else do they lie about?
- A-Train, you're out.
- Out of what?
The Seven.
I ended the relationship
when I met you.
Stop fucking lying to me.
And you love her?
We shouldn't feel so calm or safe.
So, what are we gonna do?
Cross our fingers
that Homelander's gonna save us?
- I'm the face of The Seven.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Ain't you supposed to be a hero?
- I am a hero.
That's Liberty.
William Butcher?
I found Becca.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
- I'm not leaving.
- Becca, you and me, we could disappear.
- I have a son.
- He's a fucking Supe freak.
Ruby.
Here. I'm here.
Looks like you saved me, Red.
No, you saved us.
If you hadn't broken
into the DHS mainframe...
True, I am a hell of a hacker,
but I'm no hero.
You are a hero, in lots of ways.
What do you mean?
You're not afraid to live your life.
To be who you really are.
Me, I'm...
I'm afraid to show the world who I am.
Yeah?
So who are you, Maeve?
I'm a lot like you.
I'm gay.
We have to keep moving.
Come on.
And cut!
Brilliant.
Yes, that was absolutely brilliant.
Gang, let's check that.
And, ladies and gents,
it is a wrap for today.
Good job, people.
That was so great.
Let's hit it hard in the a.m. Thank you.
That's a wrap, people.
Hey, Marty, play that back, please.
- You enjoying this?
- Yeah.
This new Joss rewrite really sings, huh?
- When are you gonna stop torturing me?
- Don't know what you're talking about.
If I promise to never see her again,
will you stop?
But, Maeve, you're in love.
It's beautiful.
Elena's good for you.
I won't let you throw that away.
Not now, not ever.
I mean, that would be cruel.
- Come on.
- Can I have a word, sir?
Oh, look at this.
Look at these strong female lesbians. Hm?
I'm inspired.
- You inspired?
- Oh, yeah.
- Girls get it on.
- "Done." Girls get it done.
- They sure do, Ashley.
- In private. It's urgent.
Ooh.
Terrific.
Oh.
Pfft. They're all starving,
but one of them's got a cell phone?
I wish you had cleared this with me
before you went over there.
Jesus Christ.
I don't have to clear shit with you.
I saw a chance for an easy win,
and I took it.
- How many views?
- They posted last night.
We scrubbed it 17 minutes later,
but that's forever.
And there's been some blowback.
Blowback?
All right. Fine, fine, fine.
So, what, uh, I'm down a point?
A point and a half? Two?
- No, nine and a half.
- Nine and a half?
Nine?
Nine and a half?
Homelander kills! Homelander kills!
What, they're fucking protesting... me?
- Oh, my God. They're protesting me.
- They've been at the Tower all afternoon.
Why didn't you fucking say something?
Goddamn it.
Don't these ingrates realise
I killed that asshole for them?
What do they think "Saving America" means?
PR is drafting a response as we speak.
- Acknowledgement, apology, action.
- No, no, no. Apology? No.
You schedule a press conference,
and I'll clean it up myself.
Well, Mr. Edgar...
and Legal would like
your official position
to be "no comment" at this time.
Please, no press,
until the Crisis Team
has an actionable strategy, okay?
Bad day?
Hey, I'm with you.
Fuck these maxi pad-wearing ingrate hicks.
But there's a way to handle it.
I do not need your fucking help.
Sure, you seem
to be doing so well on your own.
Well, I'm here when you want me.
Hello, hello. Hughie?
Hey, hey. Hi, Hi.
Sorry, thought I was
getting your voicemail.
- That why you called five times?
- No, I thought you should know.
Liberty, that Supe
that Raynor was looking into?
Turns out it's Stormfront.
Vought changed her name.
They're moving her around
like a Catholic priest.
- Right.
- Um...
She probably murdered Raynor.
Annie's trying to figure out why.
But, you know, who the fuck knows?
Well, as long as Starlight's on the job,
we're sorted then, yeah?
I'm not...
I'm not mad, you know.
What do you mean?
I just want you to know that, um...
Yes, you are leaving us
holding the bag on this shitshow.
But I want you to know that I get it.
It's, uh, Becca.
I'd do the same thing. I'm not mad.
Well,
wouldn't matter if you were.
How is she?
Lovelier than the day I met her.
Where are you?
Heading off-grid.
Argentina, maybe. Early retirement.
Butcher?
Yeah, what?
Could've said goodbye.
I know we been through some shit together.
You were...
You were always like my canary, I suppose.
Thank you.
- Goodbye, Hughie.
- Your canary...?
Hello?
On your feet, soldier.
Take me home to Lallybroch.
What are you watching?
A show called Eat My Dick.
Okay.
Have you seen Frenchie or Kimiko?
No, no. Not for a while. Why?
Fuck.
Uh, I just got off the phone with Butcher.
I think something might be wrong.
Like, really, really wrong.
What makes you think that?
He was nice.
And...
called me his canary.
Tell me everything he said.
Agent Pearson, sir.
You're a sight for sore eyes.
Agent Cruz, I thought we lost you.
Got by with a little help from a friend.
So? Good news or bad?
I'd say that's good news.
- And now the CG mutants approach.
- And there's the bad news.
There's no way we can restore the grid
if we don't get
that flash drive to the Tower.
- How will you get through all of them?
- Don't worry.
Girls get it done.
And cut on rehearsal.
No one move. No one move.
Starlight, I'm not touching,
but can you take a step?
Keep going, closer. Can you mark her?
Closer to Stormfront. Mark her, please.
And let's just pretend
like you like her, okay?
Okay, if I have to.
Okay. Okay, good stuff.
Let's try one for that. Good.
We should've shot that.
Clearly you like me.
You've been eye-fucking me
like a lovesick stangirl all day.
Why is that?
I don't know.
I think that you're a good actor.
I just feel
like a frigging fembot up there.
You know...
Everybody, can we stand by to roll?
Let's try to make our day. How about that?
Thank you.
Extra. Extra.
And turning now to superhero news:
Former Seven member The Deep
surprised everybody last week
when he married Cassandra Schwartz,
an anthropology professor at Vassar,
in an intimate ceremony.
The couple asked...
Banana saltwater taffy.
- God bless. Ron can't live without it.
- Ha.
- Billy?
- Hello, Judy.
Who's this?
It's my nephew.
For Christ's sake, Billy,
you gotta ring your mum.
Where's my boy?
Your mum and dad are flying over.
Your mum's worried to death about you.
No. You tell them, no.
It'd be a waste
of a perfectly good plane ticket.
Your father's quite ill.
Cancer's spreading fast.
Yeah, well, not fast enough.
I ain't seeing him.
Now where's me boy?
Oi, Terror.
You little rascal, eh?
Look at you, little fucker.
You ain't changed a day.
How's about you and me
go for a little stroll?
Yeah?
Come on.
So this is what it all comes to, eh?
Metamucil and wringing our dicks out
for a few drops of piss.
I used to think that you, me,
and Becca would grow old together.
Bloody stupid.
Turns out she...
What the fuck was any of it for?
Yes, there he is.
There's my guy,
looking spectacular, as always.
- How we doing?
- Good.
- Feel good?
- Yeah.
You ready
for this big fucking scene today?
That's basically
what I wanted to talk to you about.
- Great.
- I did a bit of a rewrite.
I want you to take a look.
Wow.
What a lot of work.
Yeah, I just felt
like the dialogue was a little off.
You know, A-Train would
never say any of this shit.
Right.
And you definitely just don't need
that giant expo dump at the end.
Your big farewell speech?
Honestly, I think it's better
if we just leave it open-ended.
- Okay.
- Know what I mean?
We can just play it in looks
and just not a whole bunch of words.
- Right.
- Maybe make it more of a question.
- Is A-Train really leaving The Seven?
- Yeah.
- We don't know. We don't know.
- We don't know.
Yeah.
I think we'll go ahead
and do the scene as scripted.
Thank you for putting thought into it.
You got a lot of heart.
Take that heart, put it in the scene.
All right, good stuff.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing this shitty scene.
Well...
that is way above my pay grade.
Bring that up with Ashley.
Right? Right.
Oh, by the way,
I got the crew a Vietnamese crêpe truck.
They make a gluten-free bánh xèo.
It is fantastic. You're gonna be great.
- Where are we going?
- They need to see you in Wardrobe.
Deep, you look so happy.
I hardly recognise you.
Katie, I'm in love. You know?
To an extraordinary woman
I'm now blessed to call my wife.
That's really nice.
Well, let's address
the elephant in the room, shall we?
You know, I'm glad you asked,
because, uh, yeah, you know,
Kevin here has
had some issues in the past.
But people grow.
If you could see
the letters that he writes me,
you would know
what a beautiful soul he has.
Thank you. She's only saying that
because I make her breakfast in bed.
- Oh, stop.
- French toast.
So you are both members
of the Church of the Collective.
It's not realistic.
Alexander Hamilton
wasn't no Puerto Rican.
That's the point.
It's a metaphor for the immigrant
experience in America.
But he was a white guy.
You know what's really good?
Can we help you?
She's just a girl.
Show her a picture of kittens
or some shit.
How about I show her
my motherfucking dick?
Bitch ain't right in the head.
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Stop, please.
Oi, Billy, you should've told me
you were bringing company.
Oi, who's this one remind you of?
Isn't he the spitting of Lenny?
No.
Thought you were retiring.
Argentina, right?
I am.
What are you doing here?
Well, Hughie heard a dog toy on the phone.
I know you keep Terror
at your aunt's, so...
Brilliant as ever.
Time to go.
- Come help us with Stormfront.
- Came all this way for that?
No, we came because we're worried.
Your cunt sense tingling, is it?
Well, don't you worry. I'm sorted.
Where's Becca, man?
Becca?
What's he talking about?
Waiting for me at the Hampton Inn, so...
Lots of thanks. Time to piss off.
We're not going anywhere.
Right.
Just so you know,
that's Terror's girlfriend.
What?
His fuck pig.
Black Noir is here.
What?
It wasn't us. We were cautious.
We swapped cars, no toll roads...
It's not you.
It's me.
He must've tracked me from Becca's.
Billy, what's this all about?
It's complicated.
Becca's not with me.
You couldn't get her out?
She didn't want out.
I'll explain everything.
But right now we're in a bit of trouble.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have come.
Okay, maybe...
Maybe we can make a run for it,
just get to the car.
Nah, he moves faster than a car.
But if he wants to kill us,
he'll have to do it with an audience.
This is the fire department.
A natural gas leak has been reported.
Everyone, out of your homes.
I repeat, a gas leak has been reported.
- Nice one, M.M.
- Out of your homes, please.
Let's hope they stay a while.
Ma'am, do you have any nails,
ball bearings, electrical wiring?
Pressurised aerosol products?
I need a can about this big.
Really appreciate it.
Team Britney, 2007.
- Remember the meltdown?
- Oh, mm, yeah, that...
But, you know...
You're a firecracker.
Mom?
Annie.
Oh, you look so pretty.
What... What are you doing here?
I'm in town.
I've been texting you for days.
I wasn't trying to ambush you, I promise.
Did you get any of the Vietnamese crêpes?
Because they're dope.
No, no, no. I'm good, thanks.
Your mom was telling me about
the hero pageants you used to do.
Lucky.
My mom would never let me.
Adele did not go in
for that sort of thing.
I had to do all my speeches
to a brush in the mirror.
I like this one.
Mom, this isn't a great time.
I know you're busy,
but you don't have to entertain me,
I promise.
I wanted to see you, sweetheart. I...
I miss you.
Uh...
I think that this is something
that we need to discuss in private.
- Donna, can I tell her?
- Tell me what?
Look, your mom is so sorry
about the Compound V.
And she understands
that keeping that a secret
really hurt your relationship.
And I used you as a trophy
to make myself feel important.
I know that now.
Why are you talking to a stranger
about our relationship?
She's not a stranger. She's your teammate.
Annie, look, the whole world
knows about Compound V.
I mean, lots of parents did what I did.
I...
I'm hoping that you'll...
That you'll forgive me.
Please, forgive me.
This is not the time
or the place for this.
Look, everyone is upset about Compound V.
I mean, someone was so upset,
they leaked it to the press.
Can you imagine how angry
that person is, whoever they are?
I'll let you two hash it out,
but I just think, if it was me,
I'd be grateful to have a mom like Donna.
Honey, please.
I need to get back to set.
Do you need someone
to drive you back to your hotel?
No, I'll get a cab.
Okay, now, Queen Maeve. A goddess.
But our Empress of the Otherworld
struggles inside.
Questions of identity
rock her to her core.
- Until she meets...
- Elena.
The connection is immediate,
all-consuming.
A sweet Sapphic love blossoms,
raising Maeve's consciousness
and revealing her own inner truth.
She's gay, and it's okay.
- It's...
- Powerful.
She's more than just a superhero now.
She is a symbol.
Representation matters.
She's hashtag "Brave Maeve."
We're recommending
a multipronged image makeover.
- First guest spots on Queer Eye.
- Then an exclusive It Gets Better PSA.
Kimberly Peirce might direct.
Grand Marshalls at New York
and Chicago Pride,
because you are two proud lesbians.
You know Maeve is bi, right?
I just feel like
lesbian is an easier sell.
A bit more cut-and-dry.
Now, for Elena...
- Me?
- You're gonna love it.
Why am I a part of this shit?
We are going with a polished,
tailored look.
That looks like menswear.
Pew Research shows that
two feminine women in a relationship
sends a problematic message.
This isn't Penthouse Forum.
Americans are more
accepting of gays
when they're in a clear-cut
gender role relationship,
like Ellen and Portia.
Okay, let's get one thing straight.
I have no interest
in being in a public relationship.
You will be compensated.
I am not for sale.
Really? You're not gonna say anything?
I'll fix this.
Yeah.
Elena.
Elena, wait.
If they want a lesbian Ken doll,
they can find someone else.
I'm gonna cash in my vacation days
and go stay with my sister.
- No, you can't do that.
- Why? I'm not under contract.
This is Homelander, okay?
And he's fucking with me.
If you go out there...
Elena, there is nowhere you can go
that he won't find you.
Please, stay.
I can't protect you if you leave.
But what are we gonna do?
We're gonna take that motherfucker down.
- You trust me?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Is this right?
Just like Home Alone,
except way less delightful.
Butcher?
No.
It ain't right.
What's going on?
That ninja cunt's here for me, isn't he?
But you can't go out there.
He'll kill you.
So...
So that's it?
Expecting a happy ending, were we?
Well, I'm sorry, Hughie.
It ain't that kind of massage parlour.
Now, I can keep him busy
for a little while, yeah?
Give you lot a chance to leg it.
I'm knackered.
I could use a little lie down.
Fuck you.
Am I supposed to be impressed
by this blaze-of-glory jerk-off?
Guess not.
You don't think I thought
about cashing it in after Robin?
Because I do.
Still.
A lot.
But I don't.
And the thing that kills me
is that your wife is alive.
She just doesn't want you, that's all.
Say that again.
So you don't have shit.
Welcome to the fucking club.
I mean, come on,
what do any of us have besides...?
Who the fuck asked you to come here, eh?
I don't need your help.
Jesus, you're fucking pathetic.
You're so scared of being alone, Hughie.
First you latch on to Robin,
then Starlight, and now me.
Well, you know what, son?
I ain't interested.
Look, just get out of the fucking way.
Don't make me move you.
You can move him.
Good luck with me.
She wanted the job.
You have her doing hits?
The Albanians have her doing hits.
I'm just a girl getting 10 percent.
I'm sorry, pumpkin.
But I told you,
she's no kitten.
She can make her own choices.
Why?
How is this stopping Stormfront?
I know you blame yourself
for your brother.
I know the rage you feel.
But this, this is not the way.
This is poison for your soul. I know.
Come with me, mon coeur.
I got my own baby brother killed!
He was the only thing
that mattered to me!
Stop trying to help me!
I don't want your help!
I don't understand what you're saying,
because you won't teach me.
Fuck this.
Fuck you.
Go be a monster.
Remember when you were young
and the world was full of possibilities?
Before all the mistakes,
heartbreaks, and disappointments?
What if you could go back
to the way things were?
I used to be angry, insecure, and unsure.
But thanks
to the Church of the Collective,
I now know the kind of man I want to be.
The kind of man
who calls out injustice when he sees it.
- Stop.
- Come on.
Hey, dude.
That's not cool.
The kind of man
who stands up for what's right.
Come on, guys. Knock it off.
The kind of man
who sees the potential in all of us.
So join us
at the Church of the Collective.
And be the person
you were always meant to be.
That's a bunch of bullshit.
Didn't used to be.
Church used to mean something.
Are you a member?
- I was, long time ago.
- Hm.
That place used to be pure.
And then they just started
letting all kinds of people in, you know?
I don't know.
So why don't you tell me?
Well, I think you do know.
Some people are quality,
and others are...
garbage.
Oh, by the way,
I heard they're retiring you.
So unfair.
You have a problem?
Of course not. Why would you say that?
Can I have a word, please?
Adam tells me
you don't want to do the scene.
I can't be a part
of something I don't believe in.
I know it's not easy losing your job.
When I got fired,
I Tindered my way through Barcelona.
Everyone in that city ate my paella.
Fucked a guy with elephantiasis.
But I got through it, and so will you.
Yeah, but I'm still making it happen.
My A-Trainers sell how many pairs a year?
Look on the bright side.
You served four years longer
than Mr. Marathon.
- Now, that is something, okay?
- But...
Please.
Let me just talk to Homelander.
We both know that's not a good idea.
I'm sorry.
I'm not saying the lines.
Okay, this can go one of two ways.
One, you leave The Seven with your dignity
and your severance package intact.
Or two, you get fired
for breaching your morality clause
by shooting up Compound V
and giving yourself a heart attack
in the fucking process.
It's your choice.
You know, the truth is,
I've been running my whole life.
I think it's time
that I stay put for a while.
It's time I went home.
I know this is the Dawn of the Seven.
But it's sunset on A-Train.
- It's been a good run.
- Cut!
Hey, dude, that was awesome.
Awesome? A-dog, that was fucking gold.
Buddy, look, I'm ready to move on.
But how do you feel?
Want another one? Let me know.
No, go ahead and move on.
All right, check it. Moving on.
- Tiffany, we need you over at Mocap.
- I'm heading there now.
Yes, it's true,
Vought has all the money and the power.
- And we have, no offence, jack shit.
- We love you, Victoria!
But after Homelander's war crime,
how can I stay quiet
and still look my daughter in the eyes?
I can't. I know you can't.
And guess what.
The House Judiciary can't, either.
Finally, we are going to hold hearings
on Vought and Compound V.
Yes. Yeah.
Hey, everyone.
May I?
Thank you.
Congresswoman Neuman, everybody.
Isn't she great?
Did you love that "Walk Like an Egyptian"
dance she did online?
So fun.
I loved it.
- But fun isn't what we're here for, is it?
- No, no, no...
Let me just start by saying
how pleased I am to see you all here.
Everyone get the fuck out.
Get the fuck out.
Fuck you. Get out.
...all your voices to be heard.
I know that some of you are a little upset
by that video online
of me stopping the terrorist.
And I just want you to know
that I understand.
I'm upset too.
I mean, come on, guys.
Nobody wants innocent people to get hurt.
Of course not.
But sadly,
well, the bad guys,
they don't think like us.
And so,
sometimes,
well, these things just happen.
This happened before?
- How many times?
- Well, no. Hold on, guys.
My point is,
we all have the same goals, don't we?
- To keep our country safe.
- No.
So American lives
are the only ones worth protecting?
Of course not.
But if you've served
with our amazing soldiers like I have,
you would know
that freedom comes at a price.
You don't speak for us.
- Yeah, you don't speak for us.
- You don't speak for us.
You don't speak for us.
Oh, all right.
Everyone, just calm down. Calm down.
Let's not let your hearts
get in the way of your heads.
- You don't speak for us.
- Everyone just relax.
- Calm down.
You don't speak for us.
- You don't speak for us.
- Fuck Homelander.
You don't speak for us.
You don't speak for us...
All right. You guys are the real heroes.
God bless you.
Love you, guys.
You don't speak for us.
- You guys are all good.
- Oh, thank you.
It's time.
Right, lads. To the taffy room.
This is bullocks.
This is the taffy room?
Affordable alternative
to privatised health care.
She's a dealer.
All right.
Everybody, just calm down. Calm down.
Let's not let your hearts...
You guys, you're the real heroes.
You fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
No one ever said the job was easy.
Look, he's just a kid, 17 years old.
You don't gotta look at him in the face.
Look, no one's ever
achieved anything without sacrifice.
The kid's a hero. Think of it like that.
Right, a hero.
Come in.
Where do you get all these?
This is just the first batch.
I'll have Logan punch up the fear.
- Logan?
- My meme queen.
- Huh.
- So...
When you see it
on your uncle's Facebook page,
then you know it's working.
Hm.
Um...
Can I ask you something?
I suppose I got the time.
Who's Lenny?
You said I look like him.
Billy wouldn't want me to say.
Fuck Billy.
Lenny's his little brother.
Butcher has a brother?
Yeah.
Skinny, nervous little bugger.
Like you.
Fourth grade.
Little wanker named Dorian Savory
breaks Lenny's nose.
Well, Billy goes to work on him.
Was bringing the seesaw down
on Dorian's noggin, wham, wham.
Probably gonna top him.
Kids, teachers, trying to drag Billy away,
but no, no good.
Not gonna happen. Dorian's a goner.
Then Lenny steps in,
face all bleeding,
and leads Billy away,
easy, quiet as a lamb.
That was Lenny.
He had a way of making Billy not be...
well, you know, Billy.
I think Billy needs someone like that,
you know?
Where's Lenny now?
Oh, God rest his soul.
What happened?
Whoa, shh, shh.
Easy, Terror. Easy, easy.
Come here. Come on, everybody, out.
Out the side door.
Move.
- Butcher?
- Get them out of here.
Butcher, wait, wait, wait.
What are you...?
Butcher? Butcher?
Butcher, what are you doing?
Butcher, you don't...
Don't do this.
Butcher.
All right, you fucker.
Where are you?
So you want to take me on, do you?
Think you got the bollocks?
Well, come on, then, cunt.
What the fuck are you doing? Get out.
Oi, gimp cunt.
Over here, gimp cunt.
I'm the one you want. Come here.
You kill him,
and you can kiss
your fucking career goodbye.
I got photos
of Vought's dirty little secret,
my wife's son,
Homelander's son.
Now, you lay
one fucking finger on any of us,
and those photos go out of the cloud,
and into Ronan Farrow's inbox.
And then the whole world will know
that Homelander is nothing
but a filthy fucking rapist,
and Vought has been hiding
his little laser-eyed bastard.
Now, you cunts went to a lot of trouble
to keep that a secret.
I reckon you might
want to keep it that way.
Mr. Butcher.
Oh, hello, cunt.
How can I be sure you actually
have the proof of which you speak?
You can't.
Roll the dice, cunt.
I reckon he'd be more popular
than Meghan and Harry's little sprog.
Here's my first and final offer.
That information
never sees the light of day,
and I'll call off Black Noir.
All right.
You got yourself a deal.
Want to shake on it?
Put Noir on.
Oi, missus wants a word.
Jesus Christ, Billy.
M.M., you all right?
I'm okay.
Do you really
have those pictures?
Of course I do.
They said there'd be food.
Well, this is food for your soul.
Go with love.
Hi.
Maeve. Oh, my God. Hi.
- What brought you here?
- Oh.
Wait, are you...?
- You want to check this out?
- Fuck, no.
Listen, uh, we should talk.
Yeah.
If any of these Moonies
are gonna help you get back in The Seven,
and that's a big "if"...
then you're gonna need a woman
to tell everyone
that you're not a complete piece of shit.
I can be that person for you.
- You think I'm a piece of shit?
- Fuck, yeah.
The point is, I can help you.
If you help me.
Yeah, I've got Stormfront. Flying in.
Why are you in my trailer?
You know, you had no right
to talk to my mother about personal shit.
What were you trying to prove?
Okay, sorry. Just trying to help.
She didn't just lie to me
about Compound V, okay?
She lied to me about everything.
So don't try and broker
some kind of peace between us,
because I don't want it.
Wow, that...
I mean, that is a performance.
Oh, my God.
Look, I'm, like, tearing up.
You don't suck, Starlight.
You are Tilda fucking Swinton.
I know you leaked it.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Not as good. Magic's gone.
Lightning really doesn't strike twice.
Whatever. You know what?
I need to get to set, so...
That hack-a-limb, Gecko.
Yeah, he stole the V, and then you,
you leaked it to MSNBC.
What do you think
Vought's gonna feel when I tell them?
Well, how do you think the world will feel
when I tell them
that you used to be Liberty?
Wow, you are a special
kind of poison flower, huh?
Going against your own people?
You mean fucking white people?
Starlight.
Superheroes.
Don't be racist.
Oh, my.
Oh, yes.
That is adorable.
I do like you. You got spunk.
- You're gonna be a big help to me.
- What the hell does that mean?
Come in.
Hello, you two.
Not interrupting, am I?
No, just between us girls,
right, Starlight?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
- See you around.
- Mm-hm.
- Can't wait to shoot our scene together.
- Yeah, me too.
What was that all about?
You girls friendly?
No, just running lines. What's up?
Uh, me.
Five points.
- Ah.
- Mm-hm.
Yeah, people are, uh, checking boxes
like "patriotic" and "unwavering."
I owe you.
Well, what are you
ever gonna do to repay me?
Well, here we are.
I'm sorry.
I almost threw in the towel,
like a bleeding twat.
We're harder than that, ain't we?
I will get your mom back.
I swear to God, I'll get your mom back.
Just take a little bit longer.
You hang in there, all right?
You be a good boy for Judy.
Yeah. Who's a good lad?
Oh.
I almost forgot.
I got you something.
Terror,
Fuck it.
That's my boy.
- You're all right, for an old bat.
- Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
♪ Every time that I look in the mirror ♪
♪ All these lines on my face
Getting clearer ♪
♪ The past is gone ♪
♪ It went by, like dusk to dawn ♪
♪ Isn't that the way? ♪
♪ Everybody's got the dues in life
To pay ♪
Do it. You know you want to.
I'll cut you in half.
Come on.
Right here.
Don't be a pussy. Laser my fucking tits.
Ow.
Oh, God, it fucking hurts.
Don't stop.
See?
I told you I don't break easy.
♪ Yeah, sing with me
Sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter
Sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow
The good Lord will take you away ♪
♪ Dream on ♪
♪ Dream until your dreams come true ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Dream on ♪
♪ Sing with me
Sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter
Sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow
The good Lord will take you away ♪
♪ Sing with me
Sing for the year ♪
♪ Sing for the laughter
Sing for the tear ♪
♪ Sing with me, just for today ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow
The good Lord will take you away ♪