My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
So, one more bus meta out there.
Edwin Gauss. You better
find him before DeVoe does.
This is an intelligence booster.
You're talking about intense
amounts of dark energy
going right into that cap.
I'm gonna help you
finish the Thinking Cap,
- without using dark matter.
- Fine.
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
How can I be of service?
Hello, Gideon.
Good old CCTA, bus number 405,
where I was gifted with pretty
much the best powers ever.
If it wasn't for this old girl,
I'd still have to leave the couch
when I need to use the bathroom,
you know, because I can...
Yes, I know.
All right, this might be our last chance
to find any clues on the final bus meta
before DeVoe catches him.
Yeah, and we know what happens next.
What do we know about this meta?
Other than his name,
Edwin Gauss, nothing.
It's like he disappeared.
Well, that explains the brand new,
beepy, flashy "schmience" thingies.
Yeah, Cisco designed these scanners
to look for dark matter anomalies,
so anything that looks weird, all right?
Waves, ripples, whatever,
log it.
Ho...
- I got something.
- What?
My Big Belly punch card.
I'm only five away
from a free kids meal,
if I even long enough to use it.
Man, don't even joke like that.
We're gonna get DeVoe,
throw him in The Pipeline,
long before he gets to you.
Right. If that doesn't work,
we'll just, uh, take
him out the other way.
What other way?
Eh, we'll put him down with a shovel,
give him his harp and wings,
send him to visit Grandma
Thinker in the sky.
Ralph, you think we're gonna kill DeVoe?
The way that you're saying that
makes me think I'm supposed to say no.
Okay, look...
I've taught you a lot
about being a hero, right?
You ready for what's probably
the most important lesson?
We never have to kill.
For people with our abilities,
there's just always another way.
You understand?
Han, you complete me.
- Bring it in, man. Come on.
- Uh, I'm good.
Just a little bit.
Give me some, come on.
Okay.
What's this?
Wait a second...
I talked to the guy
who was sitting there.
I remember, 'cause I paid his fare.
Uh... uh-oh.
I think I may have left my
wallet in my other pants.
Look, buddy, you either pay the fare
or you hit the sidewalk.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Mr. bus driver dude,
allow me to pay his fare.
Who are we to be the gatekeepers
of whatever path this
fellow traveler is on?
Have a seat.
Uh, thanks.
Oh, namaste, hermano.
Namaste in the back of the bus.
Funny fat dude.
This is crazy.
His residual dark matter reads
as if he was here one second,
and the next, vanished.
It's Harry.
He wants us back at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Says he has something
important to show everyone.
Well... now so do we.
Yeah. All right, come on.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
That's the big news?
You're taking a sculpture
class at the community college?
It's not art. It's science!
And as such...
it is the thing that is
gonna help us defeat...
DeVoe.
Recall, if you will, the one thing
that we've seen... nay, heard...
That can actually harm DeVoe.
Izzy Bowin's soundwave powers.
Well, Izzy was killed by DeVoe,
so whatever powers she
had is in his hands now.
And now, Joe...
they're in ours.
Watch this.
So...
Actually, maybe you should...
take a couple steps back if
you value your internal organs.
I know how that feels.
One strike incapacitates The Thinker.
Two strikes, no more Thinker.
I call it a Sonic Scepter.
Okay.
Points for alliteration.
Basically just a big tuning fork.
My goodness.
Well, like, I mean, it's
not just any tuning fork.
This might be the most powerful
tuning fork in the multiverse.
You must've laser-shaved this thing
- down to the nanometer.
- Shaved it right down
to the last angstrom,
as a matter of fact.
Child's play for me and my Thinking Cap.
The Sonic Scepter mimics Izzy
Bowin's sonic frequencies,
so we can penetrate
a heretofore impenetrable
force field of DeVoe.
And here's the best part.
Because there's no tech involved...
- It's Kilgore-proof. Nice.
- Yes.
So, now we just need to figure out
where DeVoe is gonna appear next.
As a matter of fact,
before you got here...
I scripted a subroutine
on the pocket dimension predictor,
and it's gonna give us
a massive head start.
DeVoe's next location, thank you.
Yesterday, I thought you
said that wasn't possible.
That's right, Snow, I
did say that yesterday,
but today... is a new day.
I've got a million new ideas.
The cap and I, we're......
Firing on all cylinders.
Onward and upward.
Okay, let's get to it.
Cisco, can you integrate
Harry's algorithm
- into the predictor?
- Can do.
Okay.
Hey...
Harry's really loving
that Thinking Cap, huh?
Oh, my God. It's like the
best friend he never had.
I mean, he wears this thing everywhere.
I'm pretty sure I saw him
step out of the shower with it.
I want to know what kinda problem
he was trying to solve in there.
Nope.
Nope, I... I don't wanna know.
- What are you working on?
- My brain, or brains.
I think I finally figured
out the science behind
what activates Killer Frost.
So, in fight-or-flight,
the adrenal glands flood
the body with catecholamines,
uh, AKA the stress hormone,
and guess where the highest
concentration of dark matter is
in my body?
- In your adrenal glands.
- Exactly.
So if adrenaline is what
activates Killer Frost,
- then all I need...
- Is a shot of epinephrine.
No more Harry and Cisco traumatizing me
to get Killer Frost to show up.
I can't wait to tell her.
- Wait, you guys talk now?
- Sort of.
Uh, we leave each other notes.
Um...
"Thanks for the badass new jacket.
"I got some blood on it.
Don't worry, it's not ours."
I guess her humor is
sort of an acquired taste.
Uh-oh.
Pocket dimension's about to open.
It's DeVoe. Get that pen ready.
Okay, stay ready.
Edwin Gauss?
What...
All right, guys, say hello
to our last known bus meta,
Edwin Gauss.
As we know, there's not much on him.
No college history, no known addresses.
Just a couple of backpacking
photos on an old message board.
Old? Flip phones are old.
This site is from the age of dial up.
Try prehistoric. No digital fingerprint.
Everything this guy owns
is strapped to his back.
He was off-grid before
he was even a meta.
That, and his powers are the
reason we couldn't find him.
And why there were 12
heat signatures on the bus,
including the driver.
Cisco, the way he
appeared and disappeared...
Pocket dimension.
What? Like... Like the DeVoe kind?
No, like the Edwin Gauss kind.
You see, pocket dimensions,
like the one you see here,
are unique to their users.
Just like DeVoe can
only enter or exit his,
Gauss too is limited to
his own pocket dimension.
So why does DeVoe need him?
Well, DeVoe uses his chair
to create pocket dimensions.
If he has Edwin Gauss's powers,
he won't need it anymore.
Then we need to catch Gauss first.
And we will.
Little late. Just tweaking the cap.
Now, listen, locating this meta
is not a task that
we have to accomplish.
Why is that, Harry? I'll tell you why.
It's because we already... have.
Yeah, this is the map
that we constructed:
Of all the pocket dimension activity
throughout Central City.
Right, but that's when we thought
all the pocket dimensions
belonged to DeVoe.
Now we don't know whether
they belong to him or to Gauss.
And figuring out those distinctions,
I'm sorry, but that's too big
even for your britches, Harry.
My britches are plenty big, okay?
I fill my britches. Watch this, okay?
By simply tracking the
two lanes of identifiers,
cross-referencing the, uh,
fluctuation migration patterns
and the temporal displacement
in the energy app, and...
I give you Edwin Gauss's
pocket dimension activity.
"Ahhh, Harry.
Harry is amazing."
Yeah, let's all just split up
and search each one for Edwin Gauss.
Barry, you take Caitlin and Ralph,
and I'll go with Cisco and my dad.
- Harry...
- I'll go with you.
No, I was thinking
that you could just...
You would stay here
and hold down the fort.
Okay, I'll tweak the cap.
Detective, are you... Are
you not going after Gauss?
I'm on my way out.
I just wanted to see
if you needed anything
before we left.
- If I need... no, I'm good.
- Hm.
Holding that Thinking Cap real close.
Well, you never know
when you might need it.
Yeah, and you only need it
for DeVoe-related problems, right?
DeVoe-related problems,
science problems,
making-the-perfect-omelet problems.
You make omelets with that cap?
Oh, yeah. Pretty darn good omelet.
I bet. Hey... do you
mind if I borrow the cap?
No, I don't think so. Not a good idea.
Why not? It seems pretty easy to use.
Detective, this easy-to-use thing
is actually a delicate
scientific instrument
that directly alters the
brain wave of the user,
- so I don't think so.
- Mm.
- So it's dangerous?
- Yeah, it's very dangerous.
And yet you risk using
it to make breakfast?
All right.
Okay, you're good,
Detective. You're very good.
How much do you wear that cap?
I'm not overusing it, if
that's what you're asking.
Overusing is one way of putting it.
- Addiction is another.
- I'm not addicted to...
Your concerns are well-founded.
Ramon had the same concerns.
I told him, promised him
I would not use this Thinking Cap...
with dark matter.
Hm. And that's a promise you kept?
Yes.
All right, I don't mean to be paranoid.
I'm...
Sometimes, it's just hard
to turn off the cop brain.
I get it. No worries.
Good luck finding Gauss.
Iris...
where are we?
Looks like some sort of hippie commune.
Yeah, smells like one too.
Guys, I think I figured
out DeVoe's plan.
He means to suffocate
us with BO and incense.
Okay, well, this is the
last pocket dimension hotspot
on our list, so just...
Do you see Gauss anywhere?
Uh...
Unwashed flower child,
have you seen this man?
- Nope...
- Hm.
I've seen the soul that
belongs to this man.
The dude's aura is a trip.
Wait, so, you know Edwin Gauss?
Sure do.
'Round here, we call
him... the folded man.
- Folded man?
- He's everywhere...
and nowhere...
but mostly, he's around here.
Time for the reflection hike, everyone!
Don't forget to leash
your spirit animals!
Literally already smells better.
Okay, let's just search for Gauss.
Uh, stay in touch over the comms.
Yeah, I will leash my
inner-penguin spirit animal
and head south.
Be careful.
Don't touch anybody.
Okay, remember, if we find Gauss first,
we might be able to put
an end to DeVoe's plans.
- Speaking of ending DeVoe...
- Not what I said.
Allen, I'm just saying,
DeVoe's been ahead of us at every turn.
His backup plans have backup plans.
On the off chance that
we can't capture him,
shouldn't we be willing
to do whatever it takes?
We know that he is.
I am willing to do whatever it takes,
except kill DeVoe.
- Even in self-defense?
- It's not self-defense
if you're already thinking about it.
Look, I...
I've been down this road.
I know you're scared.
I understand the temptation,
but you have to hear me when I say
there's always another way.
I really hope you're right, rookie.
Guys, I got eyes on Gauss!
He's fast for a non-speedster!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Easy, narcs. Hey...
- I give up.
- We're not cops.
But you are in danger.
We're here to protect you.
Oh... righteous.
Is that why you're... why
you brought your ninja buddy?
What?
- Caitlin!
- Meet us at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You can't stop me, Mr. Dibny.
I will cut through all of Team Flash
to get what I want.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, I mean, the wound started healing
before I even woke up.
You frosted out for a
sec when we got here.
- It probably helped.
- Yeah.
Hey, uh, shouldn't you rest?
Honestly, I'm fine.
If anything, this has just made me
more determined to get DeVoe.
I'm gonna go help Cisco
with that pocket dimension predictor.
Well, it could've gone worse.
Yeah, all things considered,
we got pretty lucky.
- Yeah.
- Lucky? Are you two serious?
Am I the only one who's
paying any attention here?
Ralph, the mission was successful.
Caitlin's okay, and Edwin
agreed to stay in The Pipeline.
- Edwin will be safe in there.
- Safe?
Because DeVoe's never
successfully attacked metas
in a maximum security facility before.
Oh, wait, he did exactly that.
- Watch it, Ralph.
- I have been watching.
Watching DeVoe ahead
of us at every turn,
watching Caitlin get skewered,
watching the metas drop
like flies, one by one,
because we can't save them.
And why? Because we
won't make the tough call
and end DeVoe when we get the chance.
Look, I'm not doing this again.
Okay, Ralph, I get
where you're coming from,
but that is not the tough
call, that is the wrong one.
Oh, Mr. and Mrs. S.T.A.R. Labs agree.
I swear if I was running this team...
- But you're not.
- Okay, all right.
That's enough. We don't
have time for this, okay?
We need to focus and
stick to the game plan.
Find DeVoe, hit him with the scepter,
and put him in The Pipeline.
No one has to die.
Huh...
same plan again.
And you wonder why
he's always ahead of us.
Yo... Magnum PI.
I am digging this tiny panic room, bro.
It's... it's... it's like...
Like an eggshell for my body...
which is the eggshell for my soul...
which contains the universal myste...
Zesty Ranch.
Right on.
You strike me as a munchies kinda guy.
Guilty.
Oh, wait, wait, wait,
not actually guilty.
It's not like I'm on anything, you know?
You... you... you guys
said you aren't cops, right?
- Nope.
- All right.
But apparently we have to
follow more rules than they do.
Well, whatever rules protect
me from that evil genius dude,
I shall heed.
Even his name is creepy.
"The Ponderer."
It's, uh, Thinker.
Yeah, sure is a thinker.
Makes me think about my journey.
Like, first time I folded,
I was in this white
space for, like, days,
and then another time,
I tumbled down this ramp
in this space agey
room with blue lights,
and there was this bald dude
in a Professor X floaty chair,
with tubes coming out of his noggin,
and there was this... this lady
in a white lab coat,
with such a hot accent. Ah...
Wait, wait, wait, Edwin, do you remember
anything else from
there? Anything at all?
This is important.
Well, I don't know if
this detail is relevant,
but, um, they had one of
those robot samurai dudes.
You were in DeVoe's lair.
Wait, how can that be?
Cisco said that a pocket dimension
can only be accessed
by its specific user.
I mean... You know,
some places are harder
to get to than others,
but if you ascend your mind
to a high enough plane...
You can go anywhere.
And my mind is really high.
Edwin, can you get us back there?
"Fa sho."
- Come on.
- What?
I... I... I got more.
No, I... I got more, I got more.
I cannot do it
any faster, Captain!
If I apply anymore hobby glue,
this ship is gonna blow!
Wow.
This glue's really something else.
I should probably wear a respirator.
Where is it?
Where's what? The exit?
It's right behind you,
please and thank you.
I can't find my Thinking Cap.
I... hey, I don't have
it, Captain Caveman!
I never said you did,
so why would you
volunteer that information
unless you do have it?
- Get out.
- I know what this is about.
You never wanted me to build
this sucker in the first place,
'cause you never wanted
me to be smarter than you.
Well, guess what, that's
funny, 'cause I already am.
What the hell are you talking about?
I want you to...
- What the hell are you doing?
- Give me my cap!
- Hey! What?
Give it to me. It's mine. It's my cap.
- Cut it out!
- It's mine!
Harry! He didn't take it.
I didn't take it.
You definitely have a problem, man.
- Joe, this is fine.
- No, uh, be quiet.
Just listen.
I've seen these signs before
with my late wife, Francine.
Back then, I didn't
intervene so quickly,
because I said to myself,
I needed to be sure.
But I was sure.
I just didn't wanna see those signs
in somebody I cared about.
I can't make you stop using this.
That's up to you.
All I will ask is that
you take a long, hard look
at what it's doing to you,
and how it's making you
treat people you care about.
Ramon...
Uh... where are we going again?
You're gonna open up a pocket dimension
into DeVoe's lair,
and I'm gonna stop him for good.
No, you're not.
Cisco installed motion detectors
in The Pipeline intake.
I thought it was DeVoe coming for Edwin.
Now I kinda wish it was.
Edwin can get me into DeVoe's lair.
I can end this.
All you have to do is let me go.
- I can't let you do that.
- Um...
Um, listen, I... I don't
really do confrontations,
so, uh, can I just go
back to my glass cage?
We're both leaving in a second.
Okay.
Just give me the scepter.
You know I can take it
away from you if I have to.
Yeah?
Well, you're gonna have
to take it out of me.
- Oh
- Whoa, bro.
Wow, okay, I'm actually
glad I stayed for that.
That was trippy.
- Don't do this?
- Do what?
This?
I'm sorry, Ralph.
Olive Branch?
You don't wanna have a
drink with your buddy?
Is that what you call
someone who just went all
"Thor, son of Odin" on you?
You can take it.
Yeah.
Look...
I know you're worried about DeVoe,
about what he might do to you,
but there are some lines we can't cross.
Wow...
You really don't know as much
as you think you do, rookie.
I know what killing
DeVoe would do to you.
You would be throwing away
everything you've done:
to become a better
man, to become a hero.
You gotta realize that.
You... are a moron.
- Ralph...
- I am not afraid of DeVoe
and what he might do to me.
I am afraid of what
he might do to you...
and Iris and Caitlin and Cisco,
Joe, Harry, Cecile.
DeVoe has taken out everyone
who's gotten in his way,
and Team Flash...
they will always be in his way.
This was never about
protecting yourself.
I know that killing DeVoe
would mean throwing away
everything I've done to become a hero...
But aside from my mom,
this team is the only
family that I have ever had,
and I would throw myself into a furnace
to keep them safe.
DeVoe cannot have them.
They are mine.
What about what we want?
You may not care about
losing who you've become,
but we do.
We like hero Ralph.
Please don't take him away from us.
Well, Ralph was misguided,
but... he had a half-good idea.
- Which half?
- We use Edwin Gauss's powers
to create a pocket
dimension to DeVoe's lair.
Yep, that's the half I was afraid of.
It doesn't get more dangerous than this,
so if we go, everybody
needs to sign off.
Look, you two have led this team
through every danger there is,
so if you think this will stop DeVoe
from claiming any more lives, then...
let's go get that bastard.
I mean, damn, Joe, when you put it
all John McClane like
that, of course I'm in.
I'm in.
I don't even need to ask
Killer Frost what she votes.
- We're in too.
- So it's settled.
Tonight, we take on The Thinker.
Open it.
You got it, mega-fast dude.
Open it again in 15 minutes.
If we don't come out with
DeVoe in cuffs, close it.
Don't open it again.
- It didn't work.
- Why would it?
Sound has no effect on a hologram.
If DeVoe's not here, then...
Now, my love...
the real battle begins.
What's happening?
Someone's taken over our
systems and sealed us in.
A second pocket dimension
opened in S.T.A.R. Labs
at the exact same time as ours.
It's DeVoe.
He used that first opening
to conceal his own entrance.
That's why our sensors didn't register.
This is all a part of his plan:
the Samuroid attack, us getting Edwin,
using him to attack DeVoe's lair.
- He wanted us divided.
- Where did Edwin go?
He's back locked in his
cell, and we got DeVoe's
pocket dimension energy
coming from the Cortex.
That must be where his chair
is. I mean, if we can get to it,
we can use it to get our team back.
First, we gotta get
ourselves out of here.
- Harry, can you unhack his code?
- Trying, but it's too complex.
If I had my quantum decryption keys,
I could do it, but they're
stuck in Cisco's workshop.
But we're not stuck in here.
What are you gonna do?
It's a little worst-case scenario
that I had Cisco whip up.
Get back. Get back.
Harry, go get your equipment...
I'll go and hack the computers.
Yeah. Iris, get to that chair.
- Dad, you can't...
- Go.
Ah!
I heard all the
commotion, and I thought,
"If DeVoe was here,
where would he be going?"
Hmm.
A simple deduction for a simple man.
Though I assure you, you are no threat
for an intellect of my magnitude.
Please.
Everyone I fight is smarter than me,
but no bad guy has beaten me yet.
Well, I'm afraid an old friend
requests a rematch.
I really hate sequels.
Ah...
Mrs. West Allen,
I was hoping we'd meet again.
You might change your mind
about that pretty soon.
Ah... there's that passion
from our chat in the courthouse.
But I do remember warning you
that it could easily be destroyed.
And I remember you asking me
what I was willing to do for my husband.
How about I show you?
- Gideon?
- Yes, Dr. Wells?
Increase the Thinking
Cap's dark matter feed.
More.
Warning: Safe zone
parameters will be exceeded.
- Recommended...
- Maximum capacity now!
Come on.
Little closer. Little closer.
Warning: Fists in Pipeline
are larger than they appear.
No.
Even gray matter as unevolved as yours
understands the pain of psychic attacks.
You were born for me, Mr. Dibny,
and now...
you will die for me.
You first!
What's that?
A big old fork to shove up your...
One more strike and you're dead.
I have been waiting
for this a long time,
you and me alone,
so I can make the hard
choice that no one else will.
Ah!
Perhaps you are willing
to do what it takes...
But it seems my love...
is stronger than yours.
Get out of my office.
Where is he?
- Iris?
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
The others are still out there
fighting DeVoe and a Samuroid.
Actually, now it's just DeVoe.
- Hm.
- Iris?
I'm okay, we just need to get DeVoe.
Breach us to him. I'm ready
to get blood on this jacket.
That blow back in the lair
knocked down my breaching.
- I'll find him.
- Mm-hmm.
Did you just...
Beat The Thinker?
Yeah, I did.
You just got out-thunk, punk.
And I see you went with
the same plan, as always.
Eh.
Do you remember when I
visited you in prison?
You said that I could
have a greater life
if I'd just rise up.
Well...
I'm ready for that life.
And for the first time,
I might even deserve it.
Yes...
it appears I have been bested.
However...
a tip, if I may.
Before you cuff a meta,
make sure the light is the right color.
Ralph!
Ms. Betty never understood
the full magnitude of her powers.
You're currently the
same gravimetric weight
as a cement truck, Mr. Allen.
That should hold you long
enough to bear witness.
Ralph! Just fight it,
all right? Fight it!
I'll save you.
You already did, Barry.
No... no...
No!
- Ralph?
- God...
Stand back.
Melt.
All the training,
all the lessons you taught Mr. Dibny
to help him reach his full potential,
this body will be the
greatest gift of all.
Thank you, Mr. Allen.
You were an excellent teacher.
We were supposed to save them.
We tried.
We failed.
I know this isn't the ending
we were expecting, so...
If anyone wants to talk...
Should I track him down?
No.
I think I know where he's going.
- Cisco?
- Hey.
Uh, weather says rain's
coming. Do you mind helping me?
Can you get Harry?
I think something's wrong with me.
Well, your vitals seem okay.
Blood pressure, respiratory
rate seems normal as well.
You're gonna have to run the test again.
There was some feeling.
I... I don't know what it was, but...
You touched DeVoe.
Hand me the dark matter scanner.
The dark matter scanner...
I'll get it.
- Focus, Harry.
- Yeah, focus.
There's no trace of dark
matter anywhere on your body.
He must've used Melting Point's powers
to entangle your meta DNA.
- So, Killer Frost...
- Is gone.
Thought I might find
you at the other office.
Yeah, well, without Ralph
being around to dodge rain,
it's only a matter of time
before the landlord
closes this place up.
I know there's some things in here
Ralph wouldn't want anybody finding.
You know you could just whoosh around
and you could pack up a lot faster.
Yeah, I know.
- Barry, look, I just wanted...
- Iris, I...
I know that you're... You're here for me
and that I can talk to you,
and I love you for that,
but...
right now, I just need to pack up.
That's all.
Okay, yeah.
Um...
I'll leave you to it.
I'll keep them safe.
To our overwhelming success.
Yes, in more ways than one.
- What do you mean?
- Not only is my new host body
immune to the ravages of
my ever-expanding mind...
It also holds an ancillary benefit.
Clifford.
I'm nothing without you...
And now, all of me...
is with you once more.
But we must temper our
celebration with conviction.
Our plans have yet to reach their apex.
- Is that...
- Dark matter.
Siphoned from the room where Dr. Wells
was charging his counterfeit cap.
As I predicted,
his hubris was his undoing.
And so, now,
the fire that burns down Team Flash...
Will also light the path
to the Enlightenment.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --