- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash."
- 12 markers, 12 metas.
- Your body's deteriorating
faster
than the chair can handle.
- I didn't just take
Dominic's body.
I took his ability.
Sylbert Rundine can shrink
objects and return them
to original size.
Deacon controls technology.
Becky Sharpe can
manipulate luck.
- There's nothing keeping him
from going in the meta wing
and absorbing the powers.
- You should be able to change
into anyone you can think of.
- How's this?
- I believe you are
looking for me.
- It's Ralph.
- Barry Allen is hereby
released immediately.
- He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers.
- Why is everyone looking at me
like I'm a dead man?
[calm music]
♪ ♪
[elevator door dings]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
What's he doing here?
- Addie, hey,
what's going on?
- I think you should
talk to Cap.
- About what?
- Just go see him, Allen.
- Okay.
- Tolerate the behavior that
the previous administration...
- Addie said you wanted
to see me.
- Yeah, shut the door.
- I promise you we will root
out all corruption
at all levels and restore
your faith in public servants.
The name Van Buren
is a name that has always
stood for integrity.
I may be the Mayor...
- We've got a problem that
I'm not sure how to fix.
- All right.
- Some people don't think you
should be back on the force.
- Because of DeVoe?
- Mm-hmm.
I was cleared of all charges.
I didn't do anything.
He's alive.
- I know,
and he's been cooperating,
coming in,
answering questions.
- So what's the problem?
- Look...
People nowadays will
believe anything.
Fake news,
social media.
Allegations are treated
as facts.
But DeVoe being alive?
Showing up in the courtroom
at your appeal hearing?
Some people in Central City
don't buy it's actually him.
- Well, who do they
think it was?
- Who the hell knows?
But we live in a city
full of meta-humans.
It's a conspiracy
theorist's dream.
- So, what does this mean?
Are you...you firing me?
- Not firing.
But I have been asked
to request that you take
a leave of absence.
- [scoffs]
By whom?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Thinks it'll be easier
for everyone.
Restoring the faith
and all that.
- For how long?
- Indefinitely.
Look, Barry,
if you want me
to fight this thing,
I'll do what I can.
But this new Mayor,
she's got a lot to prove
since the Bellows debacle.
- When do you think
I can come back?
- When everyone believes DeVoe
is really alive and well.
♪ ♪
- It's not permanent,
is it?
- I mean,
he said it was indefinite.
- They wouldn't have
given you your ID back
if it was for good.
- I mean, maybe this
is for the best, Barry.
I mean, you need to prove
that DeVoe is still alive.
And you can do that
now as The Flash.
- Yeah, maybe.
How are we doing with him,
by the way?
- We know that we still have
four bus metas left to find.
- And that DeVoe has absorbed
the powers of Killgore,
Hazard, Black Bison,
Brainstorm, and Dwarfstar.
- Fallout is safe with Tracy.
- But the Weeper is M.I.A.
- Then DeVoe must have him.
- Well, that just leaves Ralph.
- Ralph is safe with us.
But the other four
metas aren't.
DeVoe will absolutely kill them
and take their powers.
- But why does he
need their powers?
I can't figure out
his end game.
- I don't know.
I just know that these
last four metas are the key.
That's why we need
to find them.
- And find them we will.
- Where have you guys been?
- A little home away from home,
otherwise known as
the bus depot.
But I showed Cisco here
an old P.I. trick
I learned from my mentor,
Columbo.
Lost and found box
from meta bus 405.
- Question for the room,
how did I get stuck
doing the buddy system thing
with Ralph?
- It's the best way to keep
Ralph safe, Cisco.
- Yeah, it's the best way
to keep Ralph safe, Cisco.
- Well, clearly you've never
had to stay over
at an apartment that uses
neon beer signs for lamps
and the kitchen sink
for a shower.
Ralph, I love you.
But you sleep on a futon.
- Futon's not that bad.
- It is when it's damp.
- Why is it damp?
- I sweat a lot
when I sleep.
- You nasty.
[quirky music]
- Oh, hey,
my retainer.
Been looking for this.
- [laughs]
Retainer.
- Okay, you made your point.
Not that the point
needed to be made.
I'll take the next shift.
- You're a good man,
Barry Allen.
- Really?
Who uses CDs anymore?
- A musician trying
to catch their break.
♪ ♪
Izzy Bowen.
[country rock music plays]
- Ugh, country.
Music's tone deaf stepchild.
- All right,
remember anyone on the bus
with a fiddle?
- There was a guy
with a cowboy hat on
sitting behind me.
Maybe it was him.
- Boy, I sure wish we had
a way of finding out.
Izzy Bowen.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Izzy, you wanna give us
one more mic check?
- Check one,
check, check, one two.
- Okay, well, it's a her,
not a him.
And she's playing a gig
at the Busted Saddle.
- All right.
Ralph, let's go.
- No, no way.
I hate country music.
- Well, buddy system.
It's my turn.
Come on.
- [sighs]
If you insist.
[quirky music]
- ♪ Stand on the box
stomp your feet ♪
♪ Start clapping
Got a real good feeling ♪
♪ Something bad
about to happen ♪
[Miranda Lambert's
"Somethin' Bad" plays]
♪ ♪
♪ Pulled up to the church
but I got so nervous ♪
♪ Had to back it on up ♪
♪ Couldn't make it
to the service ♪
♪ I grabbed all the cash
underneath my mattress ♪
♪ Got a real good feeling
something bad about to happen ♪
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- She's good.
- She's improving,
but she lacks refinement.
- So you're not impressed
by her at all?
- The resting face
of my current visage
may be more pleasant than
the one I used to display.
But I assure you,
this is not the look of a man
awed by symphonic greatness.
- Clifford!
Clifford!
- [moans]
This body,
it's deteriorating rapidly.
- The additional dark matter
in your system
from each of your new powers
is wearing down your host.
It's straining too much
of this body's new energy.
- Then I must move
into the next one.
- But you said that Izzy Bowen
wasn't ready,
that we needed
to find another.
- We don't have time.
We must act now.
[beeping]
- We may be too late.
- Izzy Bowen?
- That's me.
- My name is Barry Allen.
I'm with CCP...
[country music plays]
- Is that a label?
- Um...
- Maybe on another Earth.
- Okay, well,
you want an autograph
or a phone number,
something?
- Uh, no, no.
Nothing like that.
- Okay.
Well, if it ain't business
and it ain't pleasure,
then we got nothing
left to talk about,
now do we?
Oh.
Do it again next week.
Great work.
♪ ♪
- Okay, I'm sorry.
Let me explain.
Um...
♪ ♪
Uh...
Someone very smart
and very dangerous
is coming after you.
- Me?
- Yep.
- [laughs]
Okay, now,
why in the name of God
would anybody dangerous
be coming after me?
- Because you have powers.
- Four months ago,
you were on
Central City bus 405.
That bus got showered
with dark matter
and made everyone on it
a meta-human.
- Now the person responsible
for doing that
wants those powers
for themself.
- Okay, and let me guess.
You boys are here
to protect me.
- Something like that.
Look, we can
explain more later,
but now we just need you
to come with us.
- Oh, no,
that's not necessary.
My daddy bailed.
Mama bailed not long after.
And I have been looking out
for myself my entire life.
- This time it's different.
You can't.
Please.
We need to go.
- I ain't going anywhere
with either of you.
- I think you should
reconsider that.
- I don't give a damn
what you think.
[screeching]
- [grunts]
[country music plays]
- I guess now we know
what her power is.
- What?
Yeah!
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You two are lucky.
Barry, your ear
is almost healed,
and Dibny,
yours just stretched.
- Well, I still can't hear
all that great.
- Consider that a blessing
in disguise.
Less twang in your future.
- Give it an hour.
You'll be fine.
- So Izzy Bowen
can control music.
- More like sound waves.
- Soundwave.
That's a great name.
- It would be, if it wasn't
already taken by a Transformer.
- Okay, well, it looks like
billions of tiny shrapnel
ripped through this.
- Exactly.
Sound is just the force of
billions of tiny gas molecules
colliding into one another.
- So if you can harness
and amplify kinetic energy,
you get...
- Molecular shrapnel.
- Okay, well,
we gotta keep searching.
If we can't track
her down soon,
she's gonna fall right
into DeVoe's hands.
- Speaking of tracking
people down,
when's Harry getting back
from Earth Two?
[Bardo &amp; Talia's
"Déjame" plays]
- ♪ You tell me you love me ♪
- DA Cecille Horton.
- Harry, hey.
When did you get back
from the Earth?
- Just got back.
Getting myself a little
pick me up.
- You and me both, kid.
♪ ♪
- Okay, good talk.
- Yeah.
[both clearing throat]
- Actually, you know,
I don't think that, uh,
pregnant people are supposed
to consume caffeine.
- Uh, yeah, doctor says one cup
a day is fine.
And lord knows I need it.
[yawning]
I need it more than you
could possibly imagine.
- Apparently.
Must be exhausting.
- It is.
He's keeping me up all night.
- "He"?
I thought Allen said
you were having a girl.
- Yeah, and I'm not talking
about the baby.
I'm talking about Joe.
Joe is keeping me up.
[stammers]
No, Harry, come here.
[clears throat]
[sighs]
My newfound ability to hear
people's thoughts.
- Oh, see, I thought...
- Yeah, I can hear...
Joe, his thoughts...I can hear
them while he's asleep.
All night long.
- You hear his dreams.
- Yep.
And they are crazy and fast.
And oh so very loud.
It is like living in the middle
of an action movie, Harry.
I love Joe West
with all my heart,
but I am telling you,
I just...I can't...
[yawns]
I'm so tired.
I can't take it anymore.
- Yeah, well, that sucks,
DA Cecille Horton.
- Yes, it does.
- Okay.
Actually, I might be able
to build something
that can help you with that.
- Oh, Harry, thank you.
[dramatic music]
- Satellite's been
running all day,
but it's still not picking up
any irregular sound variances.
- I checked the city.
I can't find her.
- Babe,
you checked the whole city?
- Yeah. Look,
we have to find her
before DeVoe.
Her life's on the line.
- She had
another gig this week.
I doubt she'd skip town.
- How would Dibny P.I.
suggest we find her?
- Well, since you asked,
has anyone checked
her web site?
- "Has anyone checked
her web site?"
Dibs, of course
we've checked her web site.
[quirky music]
No one has checked
her web site?
Iris!
- Yeah, I'm...I'm on it.
I'm looking now.
Um...
[beeping]
Guys, she's still in town.
"I just picked up the first run
of my next single
and love the geniuses
at Saloon Sounds."
- All right, Ralph.
Take two.
Cisco, we might
need Vibe's help.
- Giddy up.
- Come on, let's go.
We're in a hurry.
[thundering]
- Izzy Bowen,
we need you to come with us.
- Flash?
- You're in danger.
- I know, everybody keeps
telling me that.
- And you're gonna keep
hearing it until it sinks in.
- You just have to trust us.
We're not gonna hurt you,
but we know someone who will.
- Who is going to hurt me?
- I am.
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
Y'all came to warn me
about her?
♪ ♪
- DeVoe.
- Hello, Flash.
- You're gonna leave
Izzy alone.
- You know, you really don't
learn from our past encounters,
do you?
You're not smart enough to stop
me from getting what I want.
And what I want now
is her.
♪ ♪
- That's not gonna happen.
- It's three against one,
genius.
- Check your math, Vibe.
It's three against six.
Though I doubt I'll need to use
all of my powers against you.
[rumbling]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
all: [grunting]
- You stay away from me!
[echoing and rumbling]
♪ ♪
[whirring]
- You just hurt DeVoe.
- Who the hell's DeVoe?
[dramatic music]
- So you're telling me that
this three foot tall chick
that tried to kill me is
actually this Clifford DeVoe?
- Oh, yeah.
100% dude.
- Mmm-hmm.
DeVoe is transferring
his consciousness
to the other bodies
of all the other people
who were on the bus and got
their powers with you.
- Wait, this...this little girl
wants my body?
- That's why we're trying
to protect you.
DeVoe's already taken
most of his targets.
♪ ♪
- No, this ain't happening.
Not now.
I only got my powers recently.
And now it's like I've got
a deeper connection
to my music
than I've ever had.
I'm about to record
the rest of my new album.
I'm about to go on tour...
- Izzy, your album can wait.
This threat is real.
- So is my big break.
Do you have any idea how hard
I've had to work for this?
I left my home.
I lost friends and good men,
and I have put up with more
crap than you could imagine
so that one day
I would get my dream.
And now you're telling me that
some pint-sized lunatic
is just gonna take it all away?
- Which is exactly why we want
you to stay here
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Why?
Are y'all gonna protect me
or something?
♪ ♪
- We're gonna train you.
both: We are?
- Guys, her powers
weakened DeVoe.
Izzy, that makes you our best
shot at stopping him.
- No, no, this...
this is all too much.
I don't even know
who you people are.
- We don't have time for this.
- Flash!
♪ ♪
- You're that guy from before.
- Yeah, Barry Allen.
- And so are you, aren't you?
- Yeah.
Ralph.
Ralph Dibny.
- I'm, uh, Cisco.
Cisco Ramon.
It's nice to meet you.
- Okay, thank you.
Look, look, I...
I don't need training.
Especially from you.
All I need is my life back.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I don't know, guys.
I kinda feel like if I just
followed her into that hallway
and just gave her one of
those "Hey, look,"
inspirational talks,
I could probably
get her to stay.
- Then what are you
still doing here?
- Sorry, I don't know if you,
like,
drew straws for this stuff
or something.
- No, go!
- Okay.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
I'd watch out if I were you.
Sometimes killer robots
come out of there.
- Keep walking, Stretch.
I don't talk to creeps
in dark hallways
dressed in purple leather.
- It's actually, uh,
more of a mauve.
And, uh, I'm not a creep.
Look, Izzy,
I know how you're feeling.
That day that you
got your powers,
I was on the same bus.
So that evil chipmunk,
she wants to kill me, too.
- Please.
I think I'd remember
seeing you on my bus.
- Actually I was kind of, uh,
big boned back then.
I was on a strict diet of gin,
donuts, and regret.
But I got another shot at it.
And I worked my tight butt off.
And now I'm the hottest
superhero in town.
- [scoffs]
Please.
- My life,
it's never been better.
Kinda like yours.
- Yeah, but aren't you afraid
of losing it all?
- Yeah, I am.
Which is why I'm a part
of this team.
You said that your family
bailed on you,
so I can understand why you
wouldn't trust someone
to look out for you,
but, Izzy,
I can tell you firsthand that
these amazing weirdoes,
they won't bail.
They created a buddy
system for me.
And if you'll stay,
they'll keep you safe.
♪ ♪
I promise.
[elevator dings]
♪ ♪
- So?
Who's gonna be my buddy, then?
- [laughs]
I may have to pull
some strings,
but I will see
if I am available.
- [giggles]
♪ ♪
- Subject nine's sonic powers
accelerated the deterioration
of your internal organs.
- She merely disrupted
my atrial flutter
and bradycardia.
This body is nearly
drained anyway.
Its palliation
is a waste of time.
- I need these biometric scans
to fully assess your ailments.
- Then you should have built
this to work faster.
[helmet clangs]
♪ ♪
- I'm doing all I can.
- Yet you achieved precisely
the opposite.
♪ ♪
- I couldn't idly stand by
and watch you be injured.
Your plan was failing.
♪ ♪
Is it possible that
the repeated transference
has affected
your cognitive functioning?
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
There is nothing wrong
with my mind.
♪ ♪
- Next time I will keep
a level head.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Izzy, this will help focus
your powers.
- Well, this ain't much help
in a fight,
unless you're
dueling the devil.
- Don't think of it
like a weapon.
Just do what you've always
been dreaming to do.
Make your own sound.
♪ ♪
- Are you my new target,
Stretch?
- Yeah,
'cause I don't break so easy.
- [scoffs]
Please.
You're built like a twig.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- DA Cecille Horton.
You look tired.
- Yeah,
that's 'cause I am tired.
This thing,
it doesn't work.
- It works because I built it.
And this thing, as you so
ineloquently put it,
happens to be
a mental activity dampener
that is ten pounds
of cerebellum proof
anti-telepathy somani steel.
Thank you very much.
- Yeah, that's the problem.
It is...It's ten pounds
of that stuff.
- So?
- Oh, gee...
Okay.
[clanging]
[grunts]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- And?
- I can't sleep like this,
Harry.
Does this look
comfortable to you?
- I guess I was...
While I was pulling
state of the art technology
out of my ass
to help you with your problem,
I forgot to make things
comfortable for you.
Are you kidding me
with comfortable?
You know what else I forgot?
I guess I also forgot
while I was coming up
with a generational
breakthrough...
- [screams]
[clanging]
- And vibrational
brainwave theory,
that I was working for
the Princess and the Pea.
- Stop it!
Stop!
Put it down.
♪ ♪
Harry?
Put it down.
♪ ♪
Oh, okay.
Just...
[thuds]
What the hell
is wrong with you?
- I'm frustrated.
- You're frustrated?
- Yes.
- You start yelling at me
and throwing things?
It is like every awful thought
that you have,
it just comes pouring out of
your mouth totally unfiltered.
I don't even under...
[gasps]
[whirring]
Is this normal
behavior for you?
- Sometimes behavior.
- Okay.
If I wanna hear a grown man
scream like a child,
I will go home and listen
to Joe's stress dreams
about showing up naked
to math class.
- Eww.
- Just...
Take your thing, Harry.
- [scoffs]
- See you later.
- It's heavy.
♪ ♪
[screeching]
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
- You missed.
Again.
- Well, what do you expect,
Ralph?
I've been doing this all day.
I need a water break.
♪ ♪
- Maybe we should
call it a night.
- Not yet.
She's barely landed
another shot on Ralph.
- She needs more time, Bare.
- She held her own
against DeVoe.
Totally on raw instinct.
- Beginner's luck?
I mean, it took months
to train Ralph.
- We don't have months.
Look, this is our chance
to get ahead for once.
If DeVoe shows up again...
♪ ♪
We have to be ready.
All right, Ralph,
I'm taking over.
- Uh, thanks, Bare,
but we kinda got this
covered over here and...
- Gotta push her, Ralph.
All right, Izzy,
I wanna see if you can hit
a moving target.
- Okay.
- You ready?
♪ ♪
[clanging and shattering]
- Nice.
Take it up a few notches.
♪ ♪
[thundering]
[shattering]
♪ ♪
- Ow!
- Barry!
- Whoa!
♪ ♪
- Mmm!
Oh!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- How's Izzy?
- She just needs
a couple stitches,
but she'll be okay.
Ralph won't leave her side.
I think he might
really like her.
- Ralph shouldn't
be bothering her at all.
I mean,
she needs to stay focused.
- Izzy might be scrappy,
but, you know,
it's her first day training
with powers she's had
for a little while.
- I know.
- Barry, don't you think you're
being a little hard on her?
- No, I'm trying to teach her
how to protect herself.
- No, it seems like you're
trying to turn her
into a hero.
And that path just isn't meant
for everyone, Barry.
I mean, Izzy's just trying
to survive.
- Well, she's not going to
if I don't push her.
- You think this is the only
way to fight DeVoe?
- It's not just about that.
Iris, you weren't
at Iron Heights.
I saw up close what DeVoe
did to Becky.
To all of them.
They...
And I...I couldn't do anything
except just stand
and watch it happen.
♪ ♪
DeVoe is ruthless.
He's not gonna stop until he's
taken her powers and her life.
He's not gonna go easy on her,
so neither can I.
♪ ♪
- I am so sorry that you had
to experience that.
But Barry, we can't be
ruthless like DeVoe.
He's willing to sacrifice
anyone and anything.
Just remember that the next
time you're pushing too hard,
okay?
You of all people know that
heroes aren't made overnight.
♪ ♪
[knocking at door]
- Joe's not here.
- Well, I don't
wanna talk to Joe.
- I kind of figured after
our last conversation
you would never wanna
speak to me again.
[rumbling]
You do know I can
hear your thoughts, right?
- Right.
- No, Harry, I'm not gonna yell
at you again.
Just...
- All right, good.
Here.
That's the...
- Mental activity dampener.
♪ ♪
Sorry version 2.0.
- Just adhere it to
your supraobital ridge.
You'll block West out.
Look, I'm sorry about...
[mimics animal noises]
You know, I just recently
can't seem to stop DeVoe,
can't stop my daughter Jessie
from hating me,
can't seem to stop blowing it
when I'm trying to befriend
someone who's my own age.
- Did you just say befriend?
That's what you've
been trying to do?
You've been trying
to befriend me?
- Well, yes,
through transitive property.
I respect West,
West respects you, so...
- Harry,
that was borderline sweet.
- Thank you.
- Okay, well, let's talk.
- When?
- Now.
- Okay.
- I'm not much...
- Come on, Harry.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
What do you wanna talk about?
- Oh, okay.
I'll start.
Um, you wanna tell me
how this thing works?
Like, does it...does it keep
Joe's brainwaves blocked out?
Does it keep my mind reading
waves locked in?
- It mostly disrupts inbound
brain activity,
but I suppose actually if you
were to reverse the polarity...
[whirring]
- Wow, that is interesting.
- Also.
- Yes.
Harry, you have to do that.
- Right.
- Right now.
- Okay, good chat.
- Yeah.
Okay.
♪ ♪
- Should be good to go.
Might be a little scar, though.
- Wouldn't be my first, doc.
Probably won't be my last.
- It will be, if I have
anything to do with it.
- Why would you have
anything to do with it?
- I'm gonna go.
- Wh...What are you doing?
- The way I see it,
I've gotten more hurt here
than I ever did fighting DeVoe,
so I'm not going to spend
another second training.
- Okay, that is
a really bad idea.
- I've already hurt DeVoe.
By myself,
without y'all.
I can do it again.
- Izzy, the only way for you
to stay safe is for you
to stay with us.
♪ ♪
It's the buddy system, right?
- You're not my buddy, Ralph.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
♪ ♪
Don't do this.
[screeching]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Sorry, Ralphie.
- Initially I envisioned
the mental activity dampener
as just disrupting inbound
brainwave broadcasts,
but I talked to
DA Cecille Horton
and we had the idea to invert
the polarity allowing this
to disrupt outbound brainwave
broadcasts as well.
So we...
- We could use this
against DeVoe.
- That's brilliant.
I'm totally on board.
Except...
mental activity dampener?
- Ramon, the name's no good.
Which is why...
drum roll, please...
I have decided to rename this
the cerebral inhibitor.
- This is where we came up
with the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
♪ ♪
- What's that?
What are you guys doing?
What are...What are those faces?
- When Savitar came
to S.T.A.R. Labs,
he said we would build a device
to use against DeVoe.
- The cerebral inhibitor.
- I wish I had known that
before I spent all this time
trying to come up with
the second name.
Naming is hard.
- Okay, so we can use this
on DeVoe
to keep him from projecting
his consciousness
into new bodies.
- Precisely.
- How does it work?
- Just affix it
to his forehead.
It activates.
Simple as that.
I'll make a few adjustments,
you'll be good to go.
- All right.
Okay, when Harry's done,
we go after DeVoe.
I mean, we have Izzy's powers,
the cerebral inhibitor...
I mean, we have everything that
we need to stop him.
- Except that we don't.
Izzy's gone.
- What?
What happened?
- What did you say to her?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Rookie, Homeslice hit
the road because of you.
She's convinced she can
take on DeVoe by herself.
That's what she's gone to do.
You kept pushing
and pushing her.
Pushed her right
out the door, man.
- Okay, that's not fair.
- No, it's all right.
I did, I pushed her too hard.
It's my fault that
she's out there.
But if DeVoe gets to her
before we do...
- That cannot happen.
Cisco, you need to use your
ESPN and find out where she is.
- Give me that thing.
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
- Hey, blondie!
You want trouble?
Here I am.
[thundering]
♪ ♪
Well!
Look who finally decided
to show her sorry face.
♪ ♪
- Nobody likes a peeping Tom.
Good-bye, Mr. Ramon.
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
[crashing]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
Cisco, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
- She's at
the warehouse district.
DeVoe's there.
- I can't go with you guys.
I gotta take care of Cisco.
- All right, Ralph,
it's just me and you.
Come on.
- Bravo, Ms. Bowen.
Of all my subjects,
you're the only one to mount
a credible defense against me.
- Darlin', you talk too much.
[screeching]
[whooshing]
[suspenseful music]
A modicum of bad luck
at a time like this.
How unfortunate.
You're quite the fiddler.
The fiddler,
Mr. Ramon might say,
nailed it in one.
♪ ♪
[thundering]
- Ralph?
You came after me.
- We all did.
- Hey, Ralph,
I'll keep DeVoe busy.
You just get the inhibitor on.
- Hello, Mr. Allen.
- DeVoe, you're
not getting her.
[thundering]
♪ ♪
[high pitched ringing]
- [screams]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- Flash!
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
- Poor Dominic.
He didn't know he could affect
minds as well as read them.
Now I've taught you what
a brain aneurysm feels like.
- [grunts]
- Get out of here.
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Ah, crap!
[thundering]
[crashing]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[groans]
- Thank you, Mr. Rundine.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
[whirring]
- That'll teach you to mess
with a country girl.
[beeping]
- Cerebral inhibitor's
attached.
- Is it working?
- Oh, it's working.
- How did Mr. Deacon put it?
- Ah, yes.
Call me Killgore.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- The hell?
- Did she hack the inhibitor?
- No, no, no,
that's impossible.
There's a kill switch microchip
that prevents the patch from
networking.
- I can hear your radio signal,
Mr. Wells.
You told me once I wasn't as
smart as I thought.
Wrong again.
- [grunts]
[groaning]
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
Izzy!
- [grunting]
[thundering]
[grunts]
Oh!
[electric shocks]
♪ ♪
- Ralph?
- Hey!
[grunts]
[thundering]
- Get her out of there!
- Ralph, we can't.
- Get her out!
[buzzing]
- We can't.
- [heavy breathing]
[whirring]
♪ ♪
- Izzy, just look at me.
[clinking]
- [moaning]
- Izzy!
Keep looking at me!
♪ ♪
- [moaning]
[whirring]
[laughs]
Much better.
[sighs]
Please inform Mr. Ramon
that, while I had no need
for all six of my powers,
I now have a seventh.
I'm afraid I'm gonna be busy
with my wife this weekend,
Ralphie.
- No.
♪ ♪
[buzzing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- How's Ralph?
- Not great.
♪ ♪
- This shouldn't have happened.
DeVoe wasn't supposed
to walk away from this.
- Yeah, well, he did.
Because of me.
- We all tried to protect her.
- I built the inhibitor, Snow.
If it failed, it's my fault.
And I don't even know why.
Maybe I overestimated
the micro-combustion
infrastructure,
or maybe I underestimated
the amount of time between
each synapse router, or...
- Maybe it didn't malfunction
at all.
- Guys, Savitar said
that we would use
the cerebral inhibitor
against DeVoe.
- Yeah, he didn't say
it was gonna work.
- Yeah, well, it didn't work.
'Cause...
♪ ♪
I'm not smart enough
to make it work.
- Harry!
Where are you going?
- Out.
- Guys,
we have to find DeVoe again.
- How?
Cisco tracked down DeVoe
in his Vibe state,
and he almost got
himself killed.
- Actually...
We might have a different way
of pinpointing him.
Check this out.
Space.
The final frontier.
Now you see it...
[beeping]
Now you don't.
- That's exactly what
it looks like
when DeVoe disappears.
- That is the warping signature
of someone moving
into a pocket dimension.
- Does someone wanna explain
what that means?
- Einstein postulated that
it was theoretically possible
for a region-specific fold
in the space time to exist
between the four dimensions
that we typically think of.
- Yeah, that doesn't help.
- It's...
- [groans]
- It's another dimension.
One that you can enter or exit
at any location in the world.
- Like how DeVoe captured
me in that alley
but then he brought me back out
to somewhere above the city.
Are you saying that DeVoe's
lair is in a pocket dimension?
- Cisco, this is great.
- Can we track him?
- That I'm, uh,
still working on.
- Okay, work faster.
♪ ♪
Just do your best, all right?
Let's find him.
- All right.
- I'm gonna go check on Ralph.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
You were right.
As much as I wanna get DeVoe,
get back to our lives,
I can't rush this.
- It's gonna be a little hard
for a speedster.
- Especially an
unemployed speedster.
- Don't worry.
You're gonna find something.
- And until then?
- You can start
by kissing your wife.
♪ ♪
[upbeat pop music plays]
- Someone looks busy.
- Yep, just a
little bit of work.
Why don't you have a...
[clears throat]
Okay.
- Harry.
- Yes?
- I wanted to say thank you.
- For what?
- The MAD 2.0.
It works like a charm.
I am rested.
If you could just do something
about these swollen pregnant
ankles of mine...
- I think that's
a normal thing.
Drink lots of water.
Don't cross your legs
when you sit.
- Okay.
- Thank you for the info.
- Least I could do
after all the...
[mimics animal sounds]
Rage, I have a
problem with rage.
Apparently it tends to crop up
when I make mistakes.
- Makes it tough to be human.
- Well, humans are
a tricky species.
Anyway, I apologize.
- Apology accepted.
You just needed somebody
to talk to.
- Yeah, well,  I...
[whirring]
Are you doing that thing
where you're reading my mind?
You're reading my mind,
aren't you?
♪ ♪
- Maybe.
Yeah, yeah, I am.
You should call her, Harry.
- Jessie's on a different
planet, DA Cecille Horton.
- But this problem isn't gonna
just go away.
- What if she...
♪ ♪
What if she doesn't come?
- You're not gonna know
unless you invite her.
♪ ♪
[classical violin plays]
- [sighs]
[clapping]
That was beautiful.
- And a welcome change from
the derivative pabulum
this body subjected
us to before.
[suspenseful music]
- Our plan is back on schedule.
- Indeed it is.
Only a few more
subjects left to locate.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- ♪ Stand on the bar
stomp your feet ♪
♪ Start clapping
Got a real good feeling ♪
♪ Something bad
about to happen ♪
♪ ♪
[knocking]
- ♪ I pulled up to the church ♪
- Hey, man.
I can come back if...
- No, it's...it's okay.
- [sighs]
[clears throat]
Look, um...
I totally understand if you
need some time away
from the team.
[dramatic music]
- I mean, to lose someone
right in front of you...
Especially someone
you care about...
♪ ♪
- Izzy was very special.
- She was.
♪ ♪
But...But now...
[sighs]
DeVoe's still out there.
And until that threat's over...
We gotta keep
this buddy system going.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I thought you might
say that, Allen.
Which is why I got you this.
♪ ♪
- You want me
to be your partner?
- Oh, hey, come on.
This, uh, this Turner don't
need no Hooch.
But...
I do know what it's like
to get fired from CCPD
when you didn't even
really break the law.
- You absolutely broke the law.
- And I remember after
I lost my job,
felt like I lost a piece
of my identity.
And now you won't have
to deal with that problem.
So the next time
we're out in the field
and somebody asks you
who you work for,
you won't have
to get all stammery.
♪ ♪
- You like me.
You really like me.
- [chuckles]
[groans]
Don't go getting all soft
on me now, rookie.
♪ ♪
You and I,
we gotta stand up,
and we gotta fight back.
- Just like Izzy
would have wanted.
- That's right.
There's three more people
out there who need our help,
and we need to find them
before DeVoe does.
And after we do that...
I'm gonna take DeVoe down.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.