CISCO: Previously on The Flash...
If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
You're from before she dies, aren't you?
You trapped Savitar in the Speed Force.
- Just tell me how you did it.
- I had help.
Her name is Tracy Brand.
She made the Speed Force trap for me.
You're telling me my ideas
about the Speed Force...
I'm right?
In the future.
We need you to build this trap now.
CISCO: Caitlin's after Tracy.
That means she's working with Savitar.
- So you talked to Cecile?
- Told her everything.
JOE: Told her I love her.
I told her that you were the Flash.
Like I told you from the beginning,
I am the Future Flash.
It's like looking in a mirror.
Well, not quite.
You're not so scary without your armor.
What can I say?
I outgrew red.
I know what you are.
You're a Time Remnant.
A temporal duplicate
created when you run back in time
and meet yourself.
SAVITAR: You brought a Remnant to life
last year to defeat Zoom.
Your duplicate died
saving the multi-verse,
and you continued your happy little life.
And it would've stayed that way.
But then you decided to play God.
You created Flashpoint
and changed everything.
I went to the future.
My future self told me that
he created Time Remnants to stop you,
that you slaughtered them all.
All but one.
Me. I lived.
But a funny thing happened when I did.
You, Joe, Wally, Cisco,
you all shunned me
because I wasn't the true Barry Allen.
I was an aberration.
A disposable hero.
Future you failed to mention that,
didn't he?
How did you become Savitar?
I was broken and alone.
I wanted the pain to end.
And that's when
I realized the truth, Barry.
God feels no pain.
All I had to do was become one.
And I only need two more things.
For Iris to die, so that
you are driven so far into the dark
that I can be born.
And the other?
It may sound ironic,
given who I'm talking to,
but I'll keep that one to myself.
What happens if I kill myself?
If I die, then you'll never be created.
Cause and effect's a tricky thing.
Didn't work so well for Eddie, did it?
Shot himself in the chest.
Thawne's still kicking around.
See, that's the thing
about time travel, Barry.
The more you do it,
the less the rules apply to you.
But us having this conversation now,
we're changing the future.
Are we?
My ascendancy is nearing.
When I have control of all of time,
it will be you
who is abandoned and forgotten.
You're gonna die right here!
I forgot to tell you.
My suit's cooler than yours.
It's impossible.
I don't understand.
How could Savitar be you?
He's not me. Not really.
He's all the worst parts of you.
It's like in Star Trek
when the transporter
splits Kirk into Good Kirk and Bad Kirk.
Please tell me you at least
have Star Trek on your Earth?
- Voyager.
- I hate spinoffs.
That explains
why Caitlin was willing to follow him.
JULIAN: He has a face that she trusts.
Half of one, anyway.
So, when the Legends found that message
in the Waverider from old you saying,
"Don't trust Barry Allen," he was talking
about Savitar Barry Allen.
It's all coming together
in the worst way.
You said you made Savitar? How?
Peep this.
Four years from now,
Future Flash creates
a Time Remnant to fight Savitar.
But Savitar lets that Remnant live
so that it can later become Savitar.
So, once Savitar is
imprisoned in the Speed Force,
this Remnant starts to go crazy,
and he goes back in time to the past
and becomes Savitar.
Creating the lie
that he was the first speedster,
spreading the myth and recruiting acolytes
throughout the ages.
That doesn't make any sense.
Which came first,
Savitar or the Time Remnant?
It's a closed loop. No beginning, no end.
It's just one endless cycle.
Classic chicken-and-the-egg scenario,
I think, gang.
A Time Remnant,
it's like a duplicate of you, right?
So he has your feelings, your memories.
So why would he wanna hurt us?
Why would he wanna kill Iris?
H.R., how's Tracy coming
with the Speed Force trap?
Good. Yeah, good. Slow.
Get her to speed up, all right?
H.R.: I'll do that now. Can do.
If Savitar is a version of Barry
from the future,
and he remembers everything Barry does,
how are we ever gonna
come up with a plan to stop him?
What was he like?
Broken.
IRIS WEST: You know,
all this time, I thought
that Savitar is this monster.
It's hard to picture what might happen
and, it being you, that...
I... I know it's not you, I...
Part of him is.
He said it was like looking in a mirror,
and he was right.
But not just the way that he looked.
It was...
It was his eyes,
the pain that was inside them.
I've seen that in myself.
When I think about
how my parents died so violently,
sometimes, I wanna repay
that violence with more violence.
I wanna make someone else
hurt as much as I do.
But you don't ever do that.
You're not him. You're a good person.
No, I know, but it's in there, you know?
That's in me.
That power, that pain.
That's where Savitar comes from,
from loss.
From losing you.
You're not going to lose me.
Do you hear me?
And we are going to stop Savitar.
You are not alone. He is.
And he is not a god.
Jay told me that we're not gods.
He was wrong.
We could be, any speedster,
and it wouldn't take much.
When the love that we feel in our hearts
is drowned in anger,
when the bad memories
outweigh the good ones...
What am I gonna
have to become to stop him?
Hey! Oh, bad time?
No, man, what's up?
I just came up with the best idea ever.
Either that,
or it's the worst idea ever, but...
- It's an idea.
- It's an idea!
You wanna give me a perm?
It's not for your hair, Steel Magnolias.
It's for your brain, okay?
I want to stop you
from making new memories.
What are you talking about?
Savitar knows everything we're gonna do
because he remembers doing it.
He's a future Barry.
So what if Barry can't remember
what we're doing now?
You wanna mess with his brain?
Just a little bit.
It's a minimal procedure.
It'll still be the same Barry
you know and love,
except he just won't be able
to retain new information.
There's two types of memory, Allen,
short-term and long-term.
- Long-term is for your...
- Okay! Julian, this is... Stop.
This is my presentation.
I'm the expert here.
This is the part of your brain
that retains new information
before sending it to the cortex
to be stored forever,
so what if we block that chain
with a magnetic disruption.
So Savitar won't be able to remember
whatever strategy
we come up with to defeat him.
Which means
he can't be two steps ahead of us anymore.
With any luck,
we'll actually put him one step behind.
Beautiful. Cause and effect.
Barry, what do you think?
Let's do it.
Wait. Wasn't Caitlin
the expert on brains around here?
She was. But this is something
we'll have to do without her.
I trust you.
You won't feel a thing.
Okay. Let's get this show on the road.
The disrupter is attached
to your hippocampus, so we're sure.
Okay, ready for zapping.
Can we not call it "zapping"?
Ready to activate in three, two, one.
- Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
- HENRY: Way to go, slugger.
DR. WELLS: Run, Barry! Run!
JOE: I have watched you
be in love with Iris.
IRIS WEST: Maybe,
we were meant to be together.
Okay, that should do it.
All right.
Right.
How do you feel?
I feel fine.
You see? He feels fine.
Barry?
JULIAN: Barry?
Who's Barry?
Not fine.
Who are all of you?
What's going on?
Seriously, who are you guys?
- Okay, Barry, stay calm...
- Who's Barry?
- Cisco!
- Slight miscalculation.
"Slight" wouldn't be a word I'd use.
Where the hell am I?
Is this a dentist office?
No, no, this is S.T.A.R. Labs.
S.T.A.R. Labs? A laboratory?
A laboratory? What do you...
Were you guys experimenting on me?
No one is... Well, yes.
Technically, yes, but it was consensual.
- You were? You...
- Yes.
Why can't I remember anything?
Why can't I remember my name?
Your name is Barry.
My name is not Barry.
I don't know what my name is,
but my name's "Bartholomew Henry Allen."
- That's not a good name.
- Look, Barry...
Are you sure I don't go by "Bart"? Can...
"Bart" feels more natural to me.
Can we go with "Bart"?
- "Bart" is kind of cool.
- Okay.
- Wally!
Hey, let's just get you back in the chair.
No! No, no, no.
- I'm not getting in the chair.
- Let's just get you...
BARRY: No, how do I know
you didn't kidnap me here
to do some weird brain surgery on me?
Or maybe you're like those criminals
who trick people into hotel rooms
so they can steal their kidneys.
Do I still have my kidneys?
We don't want your kidneys!
Okay, Barry, look at these photographs.
We're your friends, your family.
I just wanna help you, okay?
That's a nice ring.
BARRY: Who's the lucky guy?
You are, Barry.
Look, I know you're scared, okay?
You can trust us.
- Cisco, a minute?
- Yes, sir.
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
Wally, stay with him, okay?
Me?
So how do we know each other?
Oh, uh, I'm your brother.
There is no sign
of any permanent structural damage.
Then why can't he remember anything?
Juhan?
He appears to be suffering from some sort
of psychogenic retrograde amnesia.
Amnesia.
What if we didn't account
for Barry's increased neural velocity?
Due to his super speed.
Wait. Do we think he knows he's the Flash?
JOE: That he has super speed?
Hey Barry, catch.
Sorry.
- Oh, my Lord!
- He's, like, god-awful.
- He's pathetic.
- Can we flip a switch, undo it?
Okay, we are not flipping any more
switches until we figure this thing out.
It's Cecile. Hey, babe.
An emergency? All right, bye.
Okay, Cecile needs Barry at C.C.P.D.,
like, right now.
She says it's urgent.
He can't possibly
go out in that condition.
Okay, um, my dad and I
will take Barry to Cecile.
You and Cisco figure out a way
to get Barry's memory back,
and fast, yeah?
Okay. Okay.
TRACY: You don't wanna work?
Well, then I don't need you!
Um, am I to infer, then,
that you've hit a little speed bump
in your quest to build a device
to trap Savitar in the Speed Force? The...
Accelerated matter
micro generator projectile?
No, I know.
It doesn't exactly roll off the tongue.
No, it doesn't. How about
we call this fancy device of yours...
- No, you probably shouldn't...
- Call it the...
Speed Force cannon!
Speed Force bazooka!
Speed Force gun!
- Speed Force bazooka's much better. Yeah.
- Speed Force bazooka's better.
But if the Speed Force bazooka
doesn't start working soon,
we're gonna have to start
calling it the Speed Force Epic Fail.
Why, what's the problem?
Okay, the accelerometer, it sucks
a hell of a lot of air watts,
- which is measured...
- All right, stop talking science!
You need to take a step back
from the Speed Force bazooka.
- But there's not time.
- There's always time!
Because sometimes to move forward,
you have to take a step back.
Step back. You see?
Yes, and shake a little those shoulders.
Shake a little those shoulders.
You know, I feel like...
Oh my gosh, the tension in your shoulders!
Think of something that calms you.
- Coffee.
- Oh, yes!
But not just any coffee.
Piping hot Indonesian dark-roast
with raspberry and coriander...
Raspberry and coriander...
I have never met another person who uses
copious amounts of caffeine to chill out.
I've never met another person, either.
I'm relaxed. Are you relaxed?
- Mmm-hmm.
- You, uh... And I'll...
- Yeah.
Okay. I mean... Okay.
TRACY: Yeah.
CECILE: Good morning, people.
Hi, I'm Barry Allen. You can call me Bart.
Okay.
So you said there was an emergency.
Where is the fire?
Ah, it's funny you should
put it like that. Lucious Coolidge.
- Who?
- Heat Monger.
The worst arsonist Central City's seen
since Mick Rory went off the grid.
That is, until Flash here stopped him.
- What's Flash?
- So what is the problem?
Judge Hankerson,
he's got an opening in his docket,
so he moved Coolidge's probable-cause
hearing up to this afternoon.
Barry was the CSI on the case,
so I need him to testify
in order to hold Coolidge over for trial.
Uh, yeah, no, Barry can't do that.
Why not?
Uh...
What do you mean he has amnesia?
Barr, what's her name?
Uh... Felicia?
Oh my God.
Is this, like, a Flash thing?
Was he battling a supervillain who used
his evil powers to steal Barry's memory?
No, we sort of accidentally
did this to him ourselves.
Why?
That's doesn't matter. What does matter
is you stalling that judge.
Barry is in no condition
to testify in court.
Joe, if Barry can't testify,
Coolidge walks.
And then God help us all.
Okay, we'll figure out something.
Please do.
It was nice meeting you.
Oh, yeah, you, too, Bart.
I got some friends down at the courthouse.
I'm gonna go down there
and see if we can delay
this whole Coolidge situation, all right?
I'm sorry.
For what?
I don't know.
It just seems like everybody's upset,
and it feels like it's my fault.
No, no, not at all.
Look, we just want you to get back
to normal. That's it, okay?
Well, I would,
if I could remember what normal is.
I mean, what have you and I
been doing lately?
Are we planning the wedding?
Like, have we sent out wedding invitations
or picked a honeymoon destination or...
Am I a warm-weather guy
or a cold-weather guy?
Actually, we've been
a little busy lately, so...
With what?
Um, nothing that you need
to worry about, okay?
Okay. You know what's weird?
I know we just ate,
but I'm already feeling hungry.
Yeah, let's get some food in you.
- All right.
- Okay.
What's that saying?
"Man plans, and God laughs"?
Well, men are planning,
and what's the God of Speed doing?
Kneeling. Brooding time is over.
You revealed yourself. Now what?
Any idea what to do
with Flash and friends?
Because we are getting
pretty close to your big becoming,
and if we don't take them down,
neither one of us gets what we want.
Hello? Anybody home?
What are you doing?
SAVITAR: Who are you?
What's wrong with you?
Who am I?
- BARRY: Science club-
- Yup.
- Key club. Astronomy club.
- Yep.
- Yearbook?
- Yeah.
And Anime club?
Oh, yeah, you loved, loved Dragon Ball Z.
I don't know what that is.
Yeah, I couldn't explain that show to you
even if I wanted to, so...
- Okay.
- Sorry.
I definitely had quite
the nerd thing going on, huh?
Yeah, little bit.
I thought you said
we were best friends in high school.
Yeah, we were.
Why didn't you give me some advice,
help me out?
Oh, believe me, okay, I tried.
- Really? You did?
- Yes.
Okay, because I have evidence
that you did not.
Um, I don't remember any of this, but
even I can see how wrong that look was.
This is visual terrorism.
I won't look at it anymore.
What?
You just...
You're so different. You're so light.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
It's like you're not carrying
the weight of the world on your shoulders.
So, what, I was, like,
brooding all the time before?
- Sometimes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Really?
I don't know. It's just... It's really
nice to see you smiling so much.
Well, I mean...
How could I not,
knowing I'm gonna be with you
for the rest of my life?
Uh-oh.
- What?
- I've got to get to the courthouse.
Oh, yeah, of course.
- Yeah, I've got to...
- Okay, yeah.
Uh, um...
I'll... Yeah, later. Okay.
Okay.
Docket number CC-15204.
JUDGE HANKERSON: Evidentiary hearing
for Central City versus the defendant,
Lucious Coolidge. I see the City
- wishes to file felony charges.
- Cutting it real close, guys.
- You ready to testify?
- No. No, I'm not.
Yes, he is.
He just needs one minute, please.
Prosecution may proceed.
Too late. He's up.
Here, just take these.
What... I wear glasses?
You will now.
Just put them on. You'll be okay.
- Just don't get them wet.
- What...
Your Honor, I, uh,
I call Barry Allen to the stand.
JUDGE HANKERSON: Raise your
right hand, please.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
I do, yes.
Thank you. Ms. Horton?
- Mr. Allen...
- Can I sit?
Please, just...
You are a crime scene investigator
for the Central City
Police Department, correct?
Uh...
Oh, this is so cool.
Well, I'm so glad you enjoy testifying,
but, please, just answer the question.
Of course.
Uh, "Yes, I am a CSI at the C.C.P.D."
"under the expert direction
of Julian Albert." Smiley face.
Wanna cut it out with the emojis?
Mr. Allen, can you tell me,
in your expert's opinion,
what substance do you see
in this photograph?
"Shellac is a resin
secreted by female lac bugs"
"found in large quantities
of the trees in Thailand."
That's too fast. That's...
Mr. Allen, are you all right?
Yes. I'm sorry. I'm fine. I just, um...
It's getting hot in here.
What else is unique about shellac flakes?
"It's the fire accelerant"
"used in all of the arson cases
associated with Heat Monger."
Such an embarrassing name.
I like it. I think it's great.
And how would you know
when shellac flakes have been used?
"We calculate flame temperature
and burn patterns,
"and a telltale sign is when shellac is
burned into potassium perchlorate
"or ammonium perchlorate,"
"which is considered
a high-temperature accelerant fire."
Hmm. So then
would you say the fires in these photos
would be considered
high-temperature accelerant fires?
Uh...
"Yes, because"...
Uh-oh.
- Um...
- Mr. Allen, can you continue?
Yes, I can... I can continue.
The... Yes, the fires were
high-temperature accelerant fires
because the flames
were very yellow.
JUDGE HANKERSONI "Very yellow"?
And that's your expert opinion
on accelerant fires? Mr. Allen?
Ms. Horton,
if Mr. Allen is unable to elaborate,
I'll have no choice but to dismiss.
- Mr. Allen?
- That's... Um...
Dismissed.
How'd it go?
Marvelous. They let the pyro go.
- What went wrong?
- Everything.
Barry's memory loss
is starting to become a problem.
It sure is. For more than just him.
I don't have my speed.
Not anymore, and I know why.
If you wanna fix this and help Barry,
you are gonna do exactly as I say.
And now this Heat Monger's gonna go free
because of me, and I feel awful.
Barry, it's not your fault.
Well, it's just that
now there's a bad guy on the streets,
and I can't do anything about it.
What?
Is that not something
I would've said before?
That is exactly something
you would've said before.
There is just something about you
that always wants to help.
This is our place?
How do we afford to live here?
Wow!
You have great taste.
Uh, actually, this is all you.
I find that hard to believe.
Is that me?
IRIS WEST: Yeah.
Who are these people?
They're your parents.
You don't remember anything
about what happened?
Why, did something bad happen?
They died.
It was unexpected,
but they died peacefully.
That's why you came
to live with Joe and me.
And that's when we met?
Uh, no, actually,
we were friends before then.
I remember the first time that I saw you.
You were the happiest boy
that I'd ever met.
I have a feeling
that's because you entered my life.
It's okay.
What the...
Barry! Are you okay?
What just happened to me?
These powers are so cool!
I can literally feel electricity
coursing through my body.
I mean, is it always like this?
This is amazing!
We just walked into a buzzkill.
My presence usually dampens the mood.
- Joe, don't!
- You fire, I'll fire.
- What the hell is she doing here?
- WALLY: She wants to help.
- "Help"?
- With what?
With the fact that I lost my powers.
Barry, why don't you give us a minute?
Sure. Yeah. Are you, like, a supervillain?
Just asking. Okay.
How did this happen?
You got rid of Barry's memories.
What Barry remembers, Savitar remembers.
So Savitar's lost his memories, too?
Savitar loses his memory,
he doesn't go along
with the plan to give Wally powers.
Cause and effect.
But if you let me help you figure out
how to get Barry's memories back,
everything goes back to the way it was.
- Kid Flash runs again.
- And Savitar survives.
And Iris dies.
Life's full Of difficult choices.
Or it isn't.
If Savitar gets his memory back,
what's in it for you?
That's my business.
FROST: You think
that Barry can become the Flash?
Yeah, he can learn.
I still know how to do everything.
I can teach him.
Okay.
Maybe this is how you defeat Savitar.
FROST: But there's still
a lot of villains in this city,
and no Flashes to protect it.
Is that really a chance
you're willing to take?
Hi! I'm still here.
- There you are.
- Because when you left, I stayed.
We've got to talk
about the elephant in the room.
But you know what?
I have a job to do.
We have to build that device!
We have got to focus on the task at hand.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I totally understand.
From here on out, whenever I look
into your azure eyes flecked with gray
like a summer rainstorm
coming to kiss my lips,
the only thing I'm gonna be thinking about
is how I can best inspire
that beautiful, sexy brain.
Sparks.
You felt them, too?
- No.
- No?
- No, I mean, yes, obviously.
- Okay.
Sparks!
Jumping between two parallel wires.
A modified high-voltage climbing arc.
I guess my work here is done.
You should've never tried this
without Caitlin.
Well, we didn't really have
much of a choice, now did we?
Also, don't refer to yourself
in the third person.
CISCO: It's Caitlin. It's you.
It's the same person.
It's just confusing.
Hand me the girard processor.
FROST: It'll help me prime his neocortical
and medial frontal lobes.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, golly! Look at us,
just three musketeers working away.
Just like old times, huh?
Hey, Julian, Caitlin ever tell you
about our time
working on the particle accelerator
with Ronnie?
JULIAN: No. No, she did not.
There was this one time,
we had this very strict deadline,
and Dr. Wells was super hard on us,
all of us, even Hartley.
Who's Hartley?
Oh, he was this guy we used to work with.
Such a dick.
You actually reminded me a lot of him
when you first came on board.
Anyway, so we were working
on the iridium plating for the, um...
What was it called, again?
The syncotron, that's what it was.
So, anyway, we were struggling,
and we were burning the midnight oil,
and we could not get the dubnium capacitor
to hold a single charge.
And so, all of a sudden,
Ronnie just loses all his chill.
CISCO: He turns beet red,
and he starts yelling at the thing,
like, "Come on you dumb-nium capacitor"...
"Take charge."
Yes! Yes.
Oh, my God!
I think about
all the memories I cherish most,
and you're in every single one
of them, Caitlin.
Let's figure this out.
I don't wanna be here
any longer than I have to.
Suit yourself.
Okay! Guys, I still can't believe
I have these powers.
They're amazing. I mean...
I think that I could be a superhero.
What... All right, well,
is it cool if I run some more?
- Have at it.
- All right.
Mmm.
I haven't seen him
this happy in a long time.
Try ever.
It's the first time
he hasn't been weighed down
by the tragedies of his past, you know?
First time he's actually
been free of them.
You don't want
his memory restored, do you?
Dad, I...
I can't say
that seeing him happy and light
isn't something that I have wished for him
because, yeah, it is.
Sweetheart, I wish that for him, too,
but you didn't
fall in love with the Flash.
You fell in love with Barry Allen.
Dad, I know this is
a different version of him,
but he's still Barry.
No, he's not, honey.
Look, until yesterday,
Barry had 28 years of experiences
to define him.
And some of those memories were bad,
but some were good, too.
But without those memories,
the Barry Allen we know and love is gone.
I don't know, Dad.
You know, part of me can't help but think
that this is some sort of gift, you know?
That this is the life
that he was supposed to have.
Maybe this city doesn't need the Flash.
Hey, everybody.
Happy Friday.
So I am a superhero.
Yeah. A real good one.
You're the Flash.
You sure "the Streak"
isn't a better name, maybe?
Turn on the TV.
Uh, okay, yeah.
NEWSCASTER: Eyewitnesses say
the man who set fire
to the offices is
none other than Lucious Coolidge,
a.k. a. Heat Monger...
That's the guy
that went free because of me.
At this rate, it won't be long
before the whole thing burns down.
There's hundreds of people
that work in there.
We need to stop it.
How? I mean, you can't right now.
No, but I can.
Barry, you don't know
how to use your powers.
- Barr...
- You just said I'm a superhero,
and a good one, right?
I mean, memories or not,
I can't stand by and watch people die
if I can prevent it.
Um, forgot the suit.
Barry, you okay?
Yeah, I'm good. Oh, stopping's hard.
How do I save everybody inside?
CISCO: You just run them out of there.
I barely got here myself!
How am I supposed
to run with someone else?
There's got to be something we can do.
There is something we can do.
Jump-start his brain using that thing.
We have not done a test run.
There's no time to test it now.
What is that thing?
This can send electrical charges
through the transmitters in his suit,
and, theoretically,
it should jolt his memories.
You want to electroshock his brain?
Won't that fry it even more?
If we don't do that,
all the people are gonna die.
Life's a game of chance.
Okay, Barry, you're gonna feel something.
It might hurt, might sting, might suck.
Wait. What?
Probably all three. Okay, here we go!
Barry?
Uh, yeah, I still don't remember.
Why didn't that work?
That was supposed to work.
We kick-started his temporal lobe.
Now he just needs to access it.
Gas is in the tank.
We just need to turn on the ignition.
We need a visceral memory
to spark his brain.
Okay.
Barry, I need you to remember.
- I can't!
- Yes. Yes, you can, okay?
IRIS WEST: Okay, listen to me.
The night that your morn died,
I didn't wanna tell you how,
but she didn't die peacefully.
- IRIS WEST: She was murdered.
- What?
And you came to live with us.
My dad brought you inside,
and you were in shock.
You weren't even crying.
And later that night, a sound woke me,
and I crawled out of my bed,
and I realized that
the sound was coming from downstairs.
I peered over the banister,
and I found you crying alone.
And I knew I had to go to you.
I sat next to you,
and you put your head in my lap,
and I held you while you cried.
And I didn't know it then,
but now, looking back,
I realize that
that was the night that we fell in love.
That was the night that we realized
how much we needed each other.
And, look, I so wish
that I could take your dark memories away.
I wish that I could make all of that
pain go away, but I can't, okay?
But what I do know, what I know,
is that for every bad memory,
there is a good one
that will get you through it.
DR. WELLS: Run, Barry! Run!
Barry?
I remember.
SAVITAR: I remember.
I remember everything.
Now, for this fire.
I don't think
I can put this fire out alone!
You don't have to.
Yes!
Looks like you remembered
how to save the day.
Like riding a bike.
JOE: Your mother's maiden name?
BARRY: Thompson.
CODIS is an acronym for what?
Combined DNA Index System.
Okay, in the third grade,
you renamed the class hamster to?
Alexander Ham Bell.
I was eight years old.
So you got your memories back.
Now we can all focus our attention
on stopping Savitar.
Good luck with that.
Please tell me we're not gonna
just let her walk out of here.
Now you wanna fight?
We don't wanna fight you.
Can't really avoid that, now can we?
Yeah, we can. You can stay here with us.
BARRY: We're your friends, your family.
Caitlin, I can fix you.
You already tried.
Well, then I'll try harder.
I don't care what it takes.
I don't care what I have to do.
I swear to you, I will find you a cure.
Caitlin, I love you.
I don't love you, Julian.
I never did.
I never loved any of you.
She's gone?
Yeah.
Maybe too far gone now.
We'll figure out a way to get her back.
Just like we figured out
how to get you back.
You sure this is the me you want?
With all the baggage?
Seeing you without
the weight of everything that's happened,
seeing you happy like you were
before your mother was killed...
Without all of that darkness haunting you,
you were finally free.
It was nice.
I did the same thing months ago.
What do you mean?
That freedom? I had that.
When I was with my mom and dad again
in Flashpoint,
and I could've let it stay like that.
I could've let the memories
of this timeline fade,
but if I'd done that,
I would've lost Joe and Cisco
and Wally and Caitlin and you.
Pain and darkness, it's a part of me.
You know, I need it to fuel me,
to push me to be a better person,
to be a better hero.
Keep me from ever forgetting who I am.
Now that is the Barry Allen
I know and love.
Hey, you guys... Okay!
You guys, you've got to come see this.
You've got to come see this.
What is that?
This is the Speed Force bazooka.
Good, right?
And that's gonna trap Savitar?
There is a tiny little problem.
- What's that?
- It's, uh...
In order to generate enough power
to magnetize Savitar's radial field
and keep him in a state of
perpetual stasis inside the Speed Force,
we need, by my calculations,
3.86 terajoules of energy.
I'm guessing that's more energy
than in a triple-A battery.
H.R.: Yes!
That's more energy than in the sun.
Guys, where are we gonna find
something like that?