[notification chirping]
Guys, I saw the alert.
Meta attack downtown. I'm on my way.
- [woman] Sounds good, Flash.
- Kamilla? Is that you?
- Uh, yeah.
- And Chester P. Runk, sir.
Ready to assist you
in all your superhero needs.
[The Flash] Why are you two on comms?
- Uh, Kamilla let me in.
- We're the only ones here.
Frost is at A.R.G.U.S.,
checking on Bloodwork.
Cisco's off the grid
cataloging post-Crisis metas.
Iris is on a story.
[The Flash] And Ralph is who knows where
tracing down Sue Dearbon.
- Okay, no worries. I'll do this solo.
- Are you sure you don't want some help?
'Cause, I mean, I am... I am ready,
willing and caffeinated, sir.
- Put me in, coach.
- Thanks, Chester, but I'm good.
[all clamoring]
Hartley Rathaway.
Since when are you a diamond thief?
It's Pied Piper, Flash.
And you're really gonna ask me that
after what you and your friends
did to me?
Uh, what did we do?
[chuckles] Wow, Flash, my brother.
That is epically cold.
How do you not remember?
It was really bad.
Oh, great. Another Crisis change.
Apparently, there's something else
you don't remember.
The gauntlets are
just my backup singers.
Wait. What...
[roof shatters]
Great. He can fly now.
No worries, Flash.
P-Runk is all over it.
That sonic boom had
a specific frequency.
If I scan for the same wavelength,
I think we can...
[chuckles, kisses]
- Voilà!
- Flash, Rathaway's at 52nd and Palm.
All right, I'm on it.
I'll take Broadway.
- Uh, I wouldn't do that, sir.
- [The Flash] Why not?
[Kamilla] Because there's a...
[train horn blaring]
[gasps, panting]
- Since when was there a train here?
- [Chester] Since always.
[Gideon] System update complete.
Is there anything else, Barry Allen?
Uh, just one more tweak.
In the meantime, I wouldn't mind knowing
everything that Crisis changed
before I run back into the field.
[Gideon] Calculating. Calculating.
- Calculating.
- [groans]
[Chester guffawing]
Barry Allen is the Flash.
[Chester laughing]
- Yeah, I already knew that.
- What?
Actually, you know what? When I think
about it, it does kind of make sense.
The whole S.T.A.R. Labs super-facility.
Plus the same voice every time
the Flash came to visit me at the MAC.
And that jawline, though?
Very distinctive.
Hmm. Listen, guys, I'm sorry.
I'm kinda... I'm kinda busy right now.
- Well, what are you working on?
- [Barry] Uh...
[Gideon] Analysis complete, Barry Allen.
I've calculated
approximately 3.725 trillion changes.
Would you like to hear them
in order of causality?
[chuckles] Is this a mobile interactive
artificial intelligence unit?
Uh, yeah, it is. I'm...
I'm just trying to upgrade it.
- Really?
- [Barry] Mmm-hmm.
You know, if you just flip
the positronic solenoid right...
Hey! Please. Um, don't mess with that.
It's, uh, sensitive stuff
and you're not on the team, Chester.
Yeah, totally. Uh...
I guess I'll cross the whole
"superhero tech support"
off my list of career possibilities.
[chuckles]
Anyways, uh, if you'll excusez-moi,
I'm Jitters-bound.
[Barry sighs]
- He's just trying to help.
- I know. I know. I just...
So much has changed after Crisis.
[sighs]
You know, this morning
when I got the meta-alert,
I was trying to find my parents' graves.
But there's not even
a cemetery there anymore.
I've searched every graveyard in
Central City. I still can't find them.
[sighs] Just feels like a piece of me
is missing.
And friends like Hartley Rathaway
are enemies now.
Just everything is so different.
I'll bet hearing different voices
on comms doesn't help either.
[Kamilla chuckles]
You want something familiar.
That's not us.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- It's okay, Barry. I understand.
Just maybe take it easy on Chester.
If he seems a little over-eager,
it's because he idolizes the Flash.
You're his hero.
I'll, uh, let you get back to it.
[Iris West] There's gotta be
some sort of logic to it.
Walk me through the night of the
particle accelerator explosion again.
What were you doing?
[sighs] Like I told you...
I was starting R-CEM tests that night.
I'd just finished the prototype.
My life's work was ready.
Wait. You'd finished
building your machine?
- Yeah.
- Can you build one here?
- I did, but we can't use it.
- Eva, we at least have to try.
What are you so afraid of?
I...
Eva, I get it.
I do. But I've read your research.
You were brilliant.
You were the best in your field.
[sighs]
And that is good enough for me.
You're so brave.
I guess we'll be brave together then.
[snickers]
So, this is a Residual Particle Catcher.
It can detect and detain
molecular afterglow of things.
- Okay.
- Mmm-hmm.
And you need me to do what?
Oh, I need you to help me charge it,
so I can catch him.
Them. The particles.
Catch the particles.
Why are you so nervous?
And what are these "particles"
you're trying to catch?
They're just... They're...
[sighs] They're scientific anomalies.
You wouldn't understand.
[scoffs] There's the Nash Wells we know
and can barely stand.
And I'm guessing anomalies
because of Crisis?
Boss lady told me.
[chuckles] You never did like being kept
in the dark, did you?
Why do you always act like
you've known me forever? It's weird.
[sighs]
I...
don't know what you're talking about.
[Sherloque]
Well, that's not true, is it?
You're such a liar.
What? I mean... It's... Yes.
The Residual Particle Catcher is ready.
Thank you.
So, if you would...
Please, can you, uh, help me charge it?
Just blast it with
an ultra-powered UV ray right there.
- Where?
- There. Right...
[sighs in exasperation]
Just aim for the absorption panel
on the front pylon. Thank you.
- Okay. Keep your panties on.
- That contraption is not going to work.
[low humming]
[Allegra grunts]
[groaning]
[panting]
- Hey. Are you okay?
- Who the hell is she?
She...
[stammering]
That's... It's just someone
I used to know.
Well, she looks a lot
like my doppelganger.
- Why do you have a picture of her?
- It doesn't... it doesn't matter.
It does to me. Dude, this is too weird.
You know, I had a feeling something
was off with you from the beginning.
But I kept ignoring it, because I was
just happy to find another person
who actually believed in me.
[chuckling] Okay...
But this whole time,
when you looked at me,
you saw this other person.
God, that is messed up, you know?
[stutters]
Okay. All right.
Let's try this again, Gideon.
[electricity buzzes]
[grunts]
What the hell?
- Oh, good. You're awake.
- Oh, Caitlin.
Thank God. What the hell is going on?
[stammers] One minute
I'm in the speed lab fixing Gideon,
the next thing I know I'm here.
My speed's gone.
Quite the little chatterbox today,
aren't we?
What?
Why are you talking to me like that?
[chuckling] And why am I in a cage?
Caitlin. Let me out of here.
[Eobard] Easy, killer.
- Thawne.
- You're quite the specimen, aren't you?
Go to hell. I don't know how you
managed to drag me back to the past.
Whatever all this is, I will stop you.
Cranky.
Why, did you offer him the B-word?
Hmm. Maybe he just needs some privacy.
I'm gonna go check on Ronnie.
He's working on a new space
he's very excited about.
He's calling it The Pipeline.
[Eobard] Hmm.
The Pipeline.
- I like the sound of that.
- [Barry] Caitlin?
- [Eobard] I'll come with you.
Caitlin! Do not trust him!
[knock on door]
Hey, baby girl.
To what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit?
- Well, a good lead, hopefully.
- Mmm.
I am working on our Black Hole story
and I have reached a major dead end,
and I was hoping
that maybe you found something new
on Joseph Carver that could help.
Ah, as a matter of fact, I have,
but I can't share it with you.
[laughing]
Are you being serious?
Look, this Carver case
has become a RICO investigation.
I have to report directly
to Chief Singh.
We have to do everything by the book.
Barry told me that you were the one
that gave him the advice
to trust me with the Mirror Gun, and now
you can't even trust me with this?
Oh, Iris, that weapon
was Team Flash territory.
This is C.C.P.D. business
and it has to stay that way,
otherwise Carver could skate
with a collusion charge.
Dad, Carver is mine.
You can't just shut me out.
- Ooh.
- [exhales forcefully]
I didn't... I didn't mean that.
I, um...
This just...
It really means a lot to me.
I can see that.
But, baby girl, there is nothing
I can do. My hands are tied. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
[chuckles]
We both have a job to do
and I respect that.
Hmm.
I, um... I'm about to get some lunch.
Do you maybe wanna join me for some
Big Belly Burger? My treat.
Now that, I would love.
But I got few things to finish, okay?
Yeah, no worries.
You wanna meet me there at noon?
That's perfect. See you there.
- Okay.
- All right.
Oh, come on. Come on, just one game.
I just spent the last two hours
at A.R.G.U.S. talking to Ramsey.
I do not want to play pinball.
Besides, I know the only reason
you're hanging around
is 'cause you want to
work things out with Barry.
- So just go do it.
- [stammers] I'm working my way up to it.
It's just, you know, up until today,
the worst thing I'd ever done before
was drown my grandmother's car.
Uh, don't try to build a hovercraft
at age 11. Doesn't work out.
Didn't you create
a literal black hole over Central City?
[chuckles]
Wait. You think Barry's
still mad about that, too?
Would you stop?
No, no. I wasn't even awake
when that happened.
I mean, it's not like you killed him.
[screams]
Barry.
Barry?
[Caitlin sighs] I can't help you
if you won't talk to me.
- Use your signs.
- What are you doing?
[sighs in exasperation]
Nothing?
Well, everybody's got good days
and bad days. Gorillas are no different.
[Barry gasps]
[gasps]
This isn't the past.
It's a mindscape.
- I'm in...
- [Grodd] That's right, Barry Allen.
You're in Grodd's mind now.
[Barry] What's the matter, Grodd?
Get lonely at A.R.G.U.S., so you decided
to break out, come visit me?
[Caitlin and Grodd]
Grodd is still in his prison,
in the mental coma
you and your team put him in.
Hmm.
So what, the cage is payback?
What, you want vengeance?
[Eobard and Grodd]
Not vengeance. Understanding.
Grodd wants Barry Allen
to see what it's like to have nothing.
No powers. No freedom. Only captivity.
[Caitlin and Grodd]
Caitlin used neural inhibitor
to shut down Grodd's cerebrum.
Caitlin betrayed Grodd.
But you gave her the authority.
This is your doing, Flash.
I'd do it again in a heartbeat.
Your mind is a weapon.
[Eobard and Grodd] You take a weapon
from a man, he is still a man.
You took Grodd's mind.
Grodd's greatest gift.
That is not punishment.
That is cruelty. Pure cruelty.
No. No. Not from where I'm standing.
Does that great mind of yours remember
how many people you've hurt?
Huh?
You marched an army of gorillas
through Central City.
You forced me
into a gladiator arena with Solovar.
You weaponized
King Shark's telepathic crown
so you could control
thousands of innocent people.
Face it, Grodd.
You got what you deserved.
[Eobard and Grodd] You are right.
[Caitlin and Grodd] It took Grodd
a year to find the strength
to think intelligently again.
And in that time,
Grodd had many primitive thoughts.
[Eobard and Grodd] And without
the power of higher thinking,
Grodd could no longer lie to himself,
and was forced to confront
the truth of his actions,
his wrongdoings, his crimes.
[Caitlin and Grodd] Your accident
allowed Grodd to enter your mind.
Not to harm Flash,
but to ask for Flash's help.
[scoffs]
[Caitlin and Grodd]
The neural inhibitor put a Gatekeeper
in Grodd's mind.
The portal that Gatekeeper guards
is the only way out of this prison.
Help Grodd.
Grodd is sorry. Grodd has changed.
Says the super-intelligent gorilla
who just kidnapped me.
[scoffs]
Who won't even show his face.
[Grodd] Grodd wants Flash to trust him.
Your powers are returned.
Please, Flash,
help Grodd defeat the Gatekeeper.
Nice try, Grodd.
But you'll never change.
You're exactly where you belong.
[Chester] That's one crazy
cappuccino maker.
Close.
Sherloque's machine was developed
to put one person's mind
into another person's memories.
Wait. You think Barry is in
someone else's mind?
I mean, we've had experience
with this before.
Based on Barry's pulse,
his rapid eye movement and his vitals,
and the two brainwaves
are a dead giveaway.
[Chester gasps]
This is so awesome. Awesome, awesome...
I mean, this is just awful.
- We should fix that. [clears throat]
- Yeah.
When Ramsey decided to take
a little vacation inside Barry's brain,
Cisco and I decided to work
on the Memory Machine
just in case Bloodwork
decided to resurface.
[Chester] How's this all work?
In a mindscape,
the host transmits neural signals
to the guest's primary motor cortex.
If we can sync up
with those neural transmitters,
I think we can communicate with Barry.
- Like sliding into his mind DMs.
- Sweet.
[computer calculating]
Come on, Barry.
Frost. You and me. Outside. Let's go.
- Harrison Wells is alive?
- That's a really long story.
Okay.
Make it fast or I'm out.
So, it turns out that Allegra,
through a, you know, series of
unfortunate events, she has discovered...
That she's your daughter's doppelganger?
Not my daughter exactly.
More like an employee, right?
An ex-employee.
How do you know that?
Whatever. I'm guessing it didn't go well
because she found out
rather than you explaining it to her.
So now it's time
for some good old-fashioned honesty.
Oh, come on.
Whatever happened between
you and your daughter...
Not my daughter exactly, okay?
More like an employee.
An ex-employee who made a bad call.
Just explain it to her.
Yeah, but she said
it was too late for that.
Well, as my life coach, Ralph,
would say, you can't let that stop you.
Ralph is your life coach?
Oh, finally, there it is.
[panting]
Time to get out of here.
Solovar?
You're the Gatekeeper?
[roaring]
Solovar, listen.
We do not have to fight.
As far as I'm concerned,
Grodd can stay in this coma forever.
[Solovar] I am the warden
of this prison, Flash.
None shall escape. Not even you.
[softly] Great.
[roars]
[The Flash grunts]
[monitor beeping]
Barry's body is reacting to
whatever's happening in the mindscape.
So, if he dies in there,
he dies out here, too?
- [Killer Frost] Correct.
- Do you have any sedatives?
- No. Those don't work on speedsters.
- [stammers] No. I meant for me.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[roaring]
[monitor beeping rapidly]
Uh, Frost,
you've got that look Cisco has
before he throws
a bunch of science words at us
that basically means we're fracked.
The signals traveling to Barry's cortex
are moving at a hyper-neural speed.
We've only seen one other brain
whose neurons can fire this fast.
- Barry's in Grodd's mind.
- Gorilla Grodd?
Damn. Yo, he is, like,
my favorite supervillain ever.
He's, like, super strong
and super smart,
and Barry's super trapped in his mind.
Which is very bad.
We modified Grodd's telepathic crown
to keep him in a coma at A.R.G.U.S.
But its neural inhibiting capabilities
can only sustain one mind.
Before long, the mindscape
will overload and crumble.
If that happens
and Barry's still inside...
He would die.
Well, can't we just call A.R.G.U.S.
and ask them to shut it off?
Uh, no. If we do that while Barry's
still connected to Grodd's mind,
he'll be trapped in there forever.
[stutters]
I still don't understand
how this happened.
How did Grodd get inside Barry's mind?
Because of me.
When I tweaked this earlier,
I adjusted its hypothalamic connection.
By a factor of 900%.
Okay, well, that's more
than enough signal
for another brain to piggyback on.
And Barry was wearing that
when he was whammied.
I am so sorry. I...
I never should have came here.
This is all my fault.
Hey.
How is you running away gonna
help us get Barry out of Grodd's mind?
Because if I'm not around,
at least I can't make things worse.
[scoffs] Look,
I hate to break it to you,
but accidentally putting
Barry's life in danger
is kind of a rite of passage
around here.
We've all done it. Cisco, me, Ralph.
Even that janitor who put
too much wax on the floor.
But then,
after we put his life in danger,
we figure out a plan
to get him out of it.
So now it's your turn.
You know, in the sixth grade
I got into the science fair
with a Millennium Falcon that I built
out of used vacuum parts.
[chuckles] I mean, it flew
and everything, like a drone.
But on the day of the fair,
it didn't fly.
Uh, rust in the intake manifold
was preventing air
from getting into the combustion,
which was then causing it to...
Sorry.
Anyway...
I had begged my teacher to let me fix it
and then fly again the next day.
He said no. You know why?
He was an old-school brother,
and he said that in the real world...
people like us...
we don't get a second chance.
[Killer Frost] Hold on.
I'm not gonna pretend like I have
any idea what your life has been like,
and I know that some
of the stuff we do in here
has nothing to do with the real world,
but... I am offering you
a second chance.
[elevator dings]
Because you deserve one.
Because we all do.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
I don't know how I made that mistake.
I... I thought I said 12:30.
[Joe] Not a problem.
I'll order you the usual.
Yeah, that sounds great.
I will be there soon. Love you.
[exhales]
- Ready to do this?
- Yes.
- [device powers up]
- No. I don't know.
Eva, look at me.
[exhales]
- Trust yourself. You can do this.
- It's the machine I don't trust.
The subatomic particles this emits
will penetrate the mirror's surface,
but it won't pierce the barrier
between the worlds. It will fail.
Then we're no worse off
than we are right now.
I made the mirror pieces move.
Let's just go back to trying that.
Eva, we should be trying everything
we can to get out of here, right?
There's another reason why you don't
want me to use this machine,
isn't there?
No. [stammers]
I better go lie down.
- Eva, what are you hiding?
- Nothing.
Why don't I believe you?
[sighs in exasperation]
Trust me. We can't use it.
- Why can't we use it?
- Because of this!
[screaming]
[gasping and sobbing]
Eva.
[panting]
[chuckles]
- You're Joe now?
- [Grodd] Hmm.
[sighs]
When Flash sees Grodd,
he sees an enemy from his past.
Grodd wants Flash
to see a face he can trust.
And having me fight Solovar
was supposed to make me trust you?
Grodd thought Flash could beat him.
You were wrong! He almost killed me.
- But that was your plan, wasn't it?
- No.
What's that?
What's happening? Is that Solovar?
This world is crumbling.
The neural inhibitor can no longer
take the strain of two minds.
What happens
to this mindscape if it fails?
Both Grodd and Flash die.
Together.
You wanted revenge so badly
that you were willing to die
just to take me with you?
No.
Grodd has changed.
Nothing could ever make you change.
Not even the Crisis of infinite worlds?
How do you know about Crisis?
Grodd's mind wasn't affected
by the merging of the multi-verse,
but Grodd can still sense
changes in this reality.
Changes like Gorilla City.
City is here now.
The gorillas are here now.
Grodd knows this.
- Grodd wants to return home.
- Why?
So you can create another army
to attack Central City?
Just destroy everyone in your path?
That is who Grodd used to be.
That Grodd wanted power.
Power didn't bring happiness.
It brought pain.
New Grodd wants a new path.
Grodd wants to live...
in peace, with his own kind.
Gorilla City is the only place
Grodd ever, ever felt happy.
You're telling the truth.
You really have changed.
Flash didn't believe Grodd before,
but why does Flash believe Grodd now?
You let go of the past.
Maybe I should do the same.
Crisis has changed so much.
I've been obsessed with trying to
keep things the way they were before...
but I can't.
[Grodd] Those things don't matter.
If Flash can't beat Solovar,
there's no escape.
This world collapses, we both die.
That's our fate.
No. We decide our fate.
Grodd, Solovar beat me
because I tried to fight him
the exact same way
I fought him three years ago.
To get out of here,
we just have to try something new.
- We have to run forward. Not backward.
- [Grodd] How?
[growling]
By fighting together.
There's our way out.
[distant rumbling]
You ready?
- We can do this, Grodd. Together.
- [snorts]
Grodd is ready.
[crackling]
What is it?
Barry and Grodd,
their cerebral activity is syncing.
[beeping]
Okay, forget sync.
Their neural pathways just merged.
Their brainwaves are literally the same.
[roaring]
[The Flash] How does it feel?
[Grodd] It feels impossible.
[The Flash] I know. Now, get ready.
This time, we're on the same team.
[roaring]
[Solovar] Grodd will never leave.
[The Flash] You have my powers, Grodd,
and my knowledge of how to use them.
- Now get us out of here.
- [Grodd] Grodd understands.
[growls]
[computer calculating]
The neural comm link is working.
- Barry, can you hear me?
- [The Flash] Frost?
Yes. We've been trying
to get in contact with you.
You're in Grodd's mind.
Is he trying to hurt you?
[The Flash] No. We're on the same team.
Grodd and I merged our minds.
Sort of like the mindscape version
of the Firestorm Matrix.
Wait. So you're half gorilla now?
Uh, I'll explain later. We're fighting
a Gatekeeper in Grodd's mind.
We need to beat it to escape.
- And the only way to do that...
- Is by working together.
[both roaring]
[The Flash] There isn't much time.
The world is gonna split apart.
[Grodd] Grodd thinks
lightning can save him.
Nothing can save Grodd.
Uh, Barry, we've got bigger problems
than Solovar right now.
[The Flash] I know.
Grodd's mindscape is falling apart.
Actually, this is worse.
[both growling]
[The Flash] What could be
worse than this?
[roars]
According to my scans,
if you exit the mindscape
with your brainwaves still merged,
you will end up in one body.
Brundle-Flash. Gross.
Yeah. And what's worse
is the resulting physiological conflict
will cause every brain cell
to shut down,
- and the resulting form would...
- [The Flash] We'd both die.
Yeah.
Wait. So we have to somehow
separate their minds
at the exact moment they escape.
And I'd have to be accurate to
the millisecond, which isn't possible.
Not for us, but it's very possible
for a mobile interactive
artificial intelligence unit.
If we sync Gideon's
quantum intelligence network
to Barry and Grodd's bio-analytics,
it'll perfectly time
the neural de-splicing.
But I'd have to do
some more augmenting to this puppy,
and my augmenting
is what got Barry into this mess
and I just really don't want
to mess up again, so...
[The Flash] Chester, listen to me.
That tweak you made to Gideon earlier?
In two seconds,
you improved her functionality
more than I did in two hours.
You're a genius.
Maybe it didn't work out
exactly how you planned,
so here's round two. Try again.
I need you now, Chester. Please.
You can do this. I believe in you.
- Flash believes in me?
- We all do.
Go ahead. Take your second chance.
Show us your moves.
Right.
It's time for the LeBron James
of the junkyard to do his thing, baby.
Oh, watch out, brothers and sisters,
'cause Chester P. Runk
[mimics air boxing] is back.
[The Flash] Great. Now all we have to...
[screaming]
Flash?
[Solovar] Grodd!
There is no escape.
- [grunting]
- [monitor beeping rapidly]
Solovar's winning. Come on, Barry.
- How's it going, Chester?
- [Chester] Please let this work.
[both grunting]
[Solovar] Grodd stinks of fear.
Grodd knows Solovar brings him death.
[The Flash] Don't listen to him, Grodd.
You have too much to live for.
You hear me? Don't let the past win.
Put it all behind you
and show Solovar what you're made of.
[roaring]
[The Flash] That's it. Get the hell up
and run, Grodd. Run.
[growls]
Almost there.
[crackling]
[The Flash] Whatever you guys are doing,
do it now.
[roaring]
[Chester] Here goes.
[roars]
Yes!
[computer calculating]
[crackles]
Come on, Barry. You got this.
[grunts]
[gasps]
- [sighs in relief] Thank Rao.
- You're back.
Yeah, I'm back.
Thanks to the team.
So, do you think Grodd
has gone, like, full hero?
Or is this more of, like,
a Captain Cold,
former-villain-turned-sorta-good-guy
situation?
Uh, we'll see, I guess.
Lyla had A.R.G.U.S. embed
a tracking polymer in his cerebellum.
She agreed to let him out on probation
as long as we know
where he is at all times,
so if he does break bad again,
I'll find him.
Which reminds me.
I'm gonna check in with Lyla
and make sure I understand
A.R.G.U.S.'s protocols.
I want to make sure
they give Grodd a real chance.
[cell phone vibrating]
- Yeah.
- Hey, babe.
You're kidding? That's great. When?
Cisco's coming home.
[sighs]
Hey, um...
I wanted to say, uh,
I'm sorry I wasn't more welcoming.
[stutters] I mean, I was dealing
with this family thing.
I felt like everything
in my life was changing,
and I took that out on you.
And I'm sorry.
No, it's...
it's all good, Flash.
[chuckles]
Um...
By the way...
Kamilla told me about your parents,
and I kinda hacked every cemetery
database within a 700-mile radius.
[Chester exhales]
I found them.
I don't remember...
Thank you, Chester.
[both chuckle]
[alarm beeping]
Do you mind manning the comms?
[guffaws]
I thought you'd never ask.
According to our satellites,
it is Rathaway.
Pied Piper's back, baby. [chuckles]
Okay, I'm gonna need all the help
I can get to take him down.
- Are you ready?
- Oh, hell, yeah.
All right.
Oh, that's never gonna get old.
[chuckles]
[Iris West] Eva, I'm so sorry.
[winces]
Why didn't you tell me
that the machine could hurt you?
I wanted to prove I wasn't lying.
Words are worthless.
Evidence... evidence is irrefutable.
My colleagues ridiculed
my reflective theory.
Even though my research
was bleeding edge,
no scientific journal would publish it
because I hadn't shown it to be true.
I just...
I couldn't have you doubt me like that.
- I just needed you to believe me.
- Eva, of course I believe you.
I saw you move those mirror pieces.
You're capable of great things.
[sighs]
Look, when you're feeling better,
we will...
- We'll find another way.
- Yeah.
I think I have some more, uh,
bandages in the storage room.
- Could you get them?
- Yeah, of course.
What did you do to us?
I bought us time.
But there's no need for you to suffer.
[exhales]
Hmm.
[exhales forcefully]
All right. Easy-peasy.
He is...
[in hoarse voice] coming.
[breathing heavily]