- What have you done?
- [growling]
- [screaming]
[dramatic music]
- [roars]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
- [roaring]
♪ ♪
- Still at it?
- I think I figured out how
to track the thing
that attacked us.
- So...what are we looking at?
- A spectrograph from the scene
of the attack.
That is a rare geothermic
isotope that I reprogrammed
our satellites to scan for.
If we get a hit...
- Then we can track our target.
Nice work.
- Thanks.
- Barry, you've been at this
all night.
Maybe you should take a break
and get some rest.
- I'm not gonna rest while
that thing is still out there.
Besides, with Ralph overseas
for a while,
and Frost still recovering...
- Oh, I'd say she's more than
just recovering.
Check out this frosty twist.
[playful music]
♪ ♪
- Are my back meds still
wearing off?
I'm seeing double.
- Yeah, you and me both.
- I know this is a lot
to take in.
- Told you they'd freak.
♪ ♪
[record scratch]
[theme music]
♪ ♪
[floorboard creaks]
- Cecile.
- [gasps]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[singsongy] Cecile.
[eerie tone]
- [gasps]
Who are you?
What do you want?
- It's time to come home now,
Cecile.
- [gasps]
Get away from me.
- You cannot control me.
- [breathing rapidly]
- You never did learn
your lesson.
[screaming]
[suspenseful tones]
♪ ♪
- Babe!
Cecile, Cecile.
What's wrong?
You were screaming.
- No, no, no.
I saw...I saw someone.
I saw someone, they were right
there and then they...
- There's no one here.
No one else here.
Except us.
You've been working too hard
on those cases,
must have fallen asleep.
- It felt so...
[suspenseful music]
But the...
The danger, it was...
it was so real.
It was so real.
- I'm sure it was, babe,
but nightmares can't hurt you.
- [breathing shakily]
- So, you remember when
Mirror Monarch blasted me
with her gun?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, ever since that blast,
we've had these crazy
headaches.
Last night,
everything gets fuzzy,
Caity passes out.
And then we wake up...
totally fine.
But there's two of us.
- Uh, Eva's mirror gauntlet
contained
a reflective mirror chip.
I think it forced Frost's
cryogenes to rapidly replicate
and create a whole new form
so that she could survive.
- Crazy, right?
- So can you still hear
each other's thoughts?
- Nope.
Just sweet, sweet silence.
And I got to keep my powers.
Caity got to keep
the doctor stuff
and science know-how,
which is fine by me.
- You always have felt like
two different people.
Now, you just have
two different...bodies.
- But don't worry, I'm gonna
figure out a way to get us
back together
as quickly as possible,
because I'm afraid
the longer we wait,
the harder it'll be.
- I mean shouldn't we be
focusing on that berserker
who killed Abra Kadabra
instead?
- Frost has a point.
Where are we with Fuerza?
Fuerza.
Spanish, for strength.
Look,
She-Hulk was taken, okay?
- Well, uh,
still no sign of her,
but Barry has figured out
how to track her.
- Oh, good.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause if Fuerza can survive
an antimatter blast,
that kind of puts her on
a whole other level of baddie.
Like, a "wet your pants"
level.
[alarm sounding]
Satellites detected
an isotopic signature?
- That's Fuerza.
Where's she headed?
- Here, right now.
[thunder booming]
- What's with all this thunder
and lightning?
Is Fuerza a speedster too?
- Barry.
- Who is that?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [ragged breathing]
Help me.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- I just got the Speed Force
restarted, now this happens.
- And what about your speed?
Has it been affected?
- No.
At least not yet.
I'm still trying to figure out
how this is even possible.
- I have no idea.
I have never seen biometrics
like this.
- You've never had a god
for a patient.
The Speed Force took this form
right after H.R.'s funeral.
It's like Zeus coming down
from Olympus,
disguised as a mere mortal.
- Okay, but why would
a god be asking for our help?
- Whatever the answer is,
I need to figure out a way
to accurately monitor
her recovery.
[dramatic music]
- Holy mother.
- You good?
- Yeah, just give me a minute.
- She's wearing my Speed Force
gauge now.
Right now, it's red.
If it changes,
hopefully that'll tell us
her power levels
are recharging.
- And if that's the case,
maybe she entered
a comatose state
to help heal herself.
- Makes sense,
and when she recovers,
she can tell us
who did this to her.
It.
- Maybe it's the same thing
that can rip through
an antimatter bomb
like it's tissue paper.
Those are residual
geothermic isotopes.
They're all over her.
- You think Fuerza did this?
Oh, that must have been
one hell of a fight.
- Not as big as the fight
we're gonna take to Fuerza.
- Okay, but this isn't just
some run-of-the-mill meta
we're talking about here.
Whatever Fuerza is,
she's powerful enough to
hurt the frickin' Speed Force.
And what if she doesn't
wake up?
What happens to you?
- Look, we've faced
big threats before.
Crisis, Savitar, Thawne.
We beat them all.
If Fuerza did do this,
she should be afraid of us.
- All right, I'll keep looking
for isotopes.
- And I'll keep monitoring
the Speed Force.
- You think Fuerza's
gonna come back
and finish what she started,
don't you?
- I already watched
the Speed Force die once.
I'm not gonna let that happen
again.
♪ ♪
- Yeah...yeah, just call me
when you know something,
All right, thanks.
Bye.
Sorry.
- That's okay.
Um, Dad,
what do you know
about the robbery
at CC Mercantile?
- Robber waltzed in and out,
because the night guard
was catching Z's at his desk.
Why the interest in
an open and shut case?
- Well, the guard told
"The Citizen" a different story
this morning and I figure
I can help him get his job back
if I can break
the real story.
He didn't doze off, Dad.
He had a vision
of his abusive stepfather
stalking him in the bank,
realer than any nightmare
he's ever had.
- The robbery went down
at 11:09,
last night.
- Mm-hmm.
- Around the same time
that Cecile was having
a nightmare too.
Damn.
If we've got some kind of
Freddy Krueger meta
on our hands,
we'll find him.
I'll get Korber to pull
any calls about weird visions.
[knock on door]
Ah.
- Kristen Kramer.
I'm with the Governor's
Municipal Logistics Commission.
- I wasn't expecting you
till this afternoon.
It's good to finally meet you.
- Yeah, I like to get
a head start.
In my experience, if you're not
early, you're late.
You must be
the Captain's daughter.
Hmm.
I read about how you survived
the abduction
into that...mirror dimension,
was it?
Sounded terrifying.
- Ah...
I've survived worse.
- Impressive.
Didn't mean to interrupt.
We can chat tomorrow, Captain.
Lunch is on the governor.
- Sounds good.
- Where'd she say she was from?
- State Logistics Commission.
Why?
- Just another hunch.
[buzzing and whirring]
- Dope belt buckle.
- Ha-ha.
Not a belt buckle.
This is the Firestorm Matrix.
- Okay...
- I helped Thawne build it
to combine Ronnie and Stein
into Firestorm safely.
- And...that's gonna help put
me and Caity back together?
- You can thank Caitlin,
she figured it out.
All we have to do is just
reset it to her DNA,
and your RNA...
we're basically just resetting
fusion to fission.
This baby just needs
a few hours to charge
and that's it!
We can get you back
to your normal,
two minds, one body existence...
that's a Tuesday for you.
- Wow, that was fast.
It's not so bad being separate.
For Caity, I mean, you know.
She can finally watch
"This Is Us"
without me screaming
"Turn it off!" in her head.
- Frost, what have I said about
disparaging "This Is Us"?
- They're so weepy.
- That cast is too precious
for this world.
Listen,
based on how relieved Caitlin
was to figure out this fix,
I'm guessing
she actually misses
hearing your frosty tones
inside her head.
Okay, I'm done with you.
Now we wait.
I want to keep checking the
satellites, make sure we don't
get hit with another
isotopic signature surprise.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[video playing over tablet]
[Fuerza roars]
[footsteps approaching]
- [sighs]
- Whoa.
So that's the Speed Force?
Uh, Iris already texted me
about everything.
- [scoffs]
- [sighs, groans softly]
- What's wrong?
- I had a nightmare,
but it was more like a vision.
I don't know, I thought,
maybe with my powers expanding
lately, Caitlin could check
out my noggin.
Ahh...ahh!
Oh!
- Hey...hey, are you okay?
- No, it's happening again,
It...it's like someone's
stabbing my brain.
- I'm gonna get Caitlin.
- No, no, no.
Barry, Barry it's...[winces]
It's not medical.
It's my powers.
It's like they're picking up
raw fear.
[phone buzzing]
- There's a robbery downtown.
- It's okay, really.
I'm fine now.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
You should go.
[adventurous music]
Hey,
I'll keep an eye on her.
Go.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
It's gonna crush us to death!
- [roaring]
- Flash, thank God.
You have to stop that creature,
it's gonna kill us!
- Ah...
[both guards scream]
- There's...
[both scream]
- Where are you...
- [distorted, echoing voice]
Oh, you gotta go so soon?
[eerie tones]
- [laughing] Ooh.
- So let me get this straight.
You made those guards
hallucinate some kind of
Godzilla rip-off
that almost squashed them?
- Well, I suppose
that is an accurate,
if not immensely reductive
assessment of the situation.
So, yes.
I scared the hell out of them.
And that was after
showing them a vision
of a dozen bystanders
getting eaten alive
by a very hungry kaiju.
It's horrifying
when you think it's your turn.
- Okay, um, look.
Whoever you are,
I really don't have time
for this.
- My, my.
How rude.
And from a superhero?
Is that actually allowed?
- Okay, I apologize
for the rudeness.
But I hope you enjoy
Iron Heights.
'Cause I really do have
bigger problems today.
- Not yet,
but you're about to.
- Hey, I just got another
geothermic isotope reading.
[suspenseful music]
It's coming from your location.
♪ ♪
- Scared yet?
You will be.
[high-pitched ringing]
- [grunting]
- You can't stop me, Flash.
And you never will.
- No, I'm not afraid of you
anymore.
This is just a hallucination.
Which means
you can't hurt me!
- Time to repent.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Ah!
- You lose, Barry.
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
- Barry?
Barry!
- Your vitals were spiking,
but they seem to have
stabilized.
Your speed healing
kicked in.
- What the hell
happened out there?
- I...I was hallucinating.
Thawne, Savitar...
they were trying to kill me.
It was like...
- Like a nightmare
come to life?
- Yeah.
Like the guards
in the truck.
Wait, like you.
You had a nightmare last night.
- Yeah.
Someone is broadcasting fear
into their victims,
and I'm tuning into it
like an antenna.
- Fear I get.
Hallucinations can make you
freak out but not bleed out.
- Whoever's doing this
must be inciting
extreme psychosomatic
reactions.
Barry's mind literally tricked
his body into hurting itself.
- So if you die
in the hallucination...
- Then you die in real life.
- Well, he carried traces
of the same isotopes
we linked to Fuerza.
That means
we can track him too, right?
- Right.
And it means that
Fuerza and Psych must be
connected somehow.
- Psych?
- He's a psychic psychopath,
causing
psychosomatic symptoms,
I mean, the guy practically
named himself.
- He's only dangerous
'cause he got inside my head.
Cisco, do we still have
the mental dampeners
we used to fight Grodd?
- We can try and repurpose them
to repel Psych's
hallucinations.
- Do it.
If we can keep Psych
out of our heads,
he can't hurt us.
[sharp humming]
- [gasps]
- What?
- That must have been
terrifying,
being trapped in
that nightmare.
- I mean, I'm...I'm fine.
Really, I'm fine.
I mean,
we beat those Big Bads
already.
Psych's no different.
- Barry, uh...
- You did a background check
on a public official?
- I've only ever heard
of one other person
using the phrase
"if you're not early,
you're late."
"Citizen"'s go-to military
source.
- Kramer served.
- Yes, she served,
but I think
she's also lying about
why she's here.
Dad, I found her file
in the D.O.D. database.
Half of it's redacted.
What if she's
not here to help?
- Iris,
are you sure this isn't
a reaction
to what happened with Eva?
I mean, she lied to you
for weeks.
- Dad, I am not afraid
of being deceived,
I'm afraid of
not trusting my gut.
Something is off with Kramer,
I know it.
Please, read the file.
- Okay, okay.
- These rapids are hardcore.
Can Caity swim?
What if...when she and I split,
I got swimming,
and now she needs floaties?
- [chuckles] No one's gonna
need floaties, all right?
You two are gonna be peanut
butter and jellied again
by the time
we tear up that river.
- Frost!
- Or not.
- The Firestorm Matrix
has been sabotaged,
only someone tried to make it
look like it short-circuited.
- Before you go blaming
Frosty...
- I ran the adapter
through an infrared scanner,
and guess what
the temperature was?
-162 degrees.
- Fine, I broke your
stupid, precious Matrix.
- Oh.
- Why?
Why would you do that to us?
It'll be weeks
before we can even consider
another fusion attempt.
- Because, maybe
I don't want to recombine!
- Why not?
- Well...
- Call me when you
figure it out.
- [clears throat]
[chuckles]
You know,
this actually reminds me
of that scene
where Rebecca and Jack
are fighting...
[alarm sounding]
Oh, look at that.
Let's go, we gotta go.
[computers beeping]
- Satellites picked up Psych's
isotopic signature
downtown at the Clearly Capital
offices.
- Time to put these
mental dampeners to work.
- And kick some psychic butt.
♪ ♪
- [sobbing]
5.3 trillion gone.
It's all gone.
Oh, God. I'm ruined.
[sobs]
- Hey, i-it'll bounce back.
The DOW only dropped
789 points.
It'll bounce back.
It has to.
[eerie tones]
- Oh, I could do this all day.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Oh, it's you again.
Well, that's disappointing.
- We're not gonna let you
hurt any more people.
- Oh, I haven't hurt
anyone today.
I have freed them
from a system that brings
fortune to the fortunate
and dooms the rest.
Pretty poetic,
don't you think?
- What...what is this guy's
deal?
- I think
he's overcompensating.
- I don't like your friends,
Flash.
Also, if you think your
flimsy dampeners can stop me,
perhaps you all could use
some freedom too.
[eerie tones]
- Killer Frost?
You're under arrest for
your crimes against the city.
- What? No.
No, I'm one of
the good guys now.
- Tell it to Judge Tanaka.
We have a witness.
One who told us
everything you've done.
- Who turned me in?
Was it Mark?
- No.
It was Caitlin Snow.
No, no, no.
How could she...
- [breathing heavily] No.
This can't be how it ends.
- How could she?
- [gasps]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Someone's back for seconds.
- You already showed me
my greatest fear.
It won't scare me twice.
- Oh, Flash.
Those Big Bads aren't
your greatest fear.
This is.
[droning tone]
- [panting]
No. No.
No.
No, please...
No, no, no, no...
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
No.
- Sweet nightmares,
people.
♪ ♪
[soft music]
- First Fuerza, then
the Speed Force shows up,
now this too?
- Why can't I stop shaking?
- Your biometrics
are all elevated.
I mean, your amygdalae
are in overdrive.
- Wait, we had panic attacks?
- Extreme ones,
Psych doesn't just manipulate
your fear, he elevates it.
But your cortisol levels
are slowly stabilizing,
which means...
- Psych's powers
have a residual effect.
- And Barry has had
a double dose.
- Where's Frost?
- She wanted to be alone.
[scoffs]
Even the Ice Queen was freaked
out by whatever she saw.
- The mental dampeners
didn't work.
- Psych must have overpowered
their circuitry.
Which means,
the next time you fight him,
we won't be able
to protect your mind.
- The next time?
How are we supposed to
anticipate him?
Stake out the banks?
- No, he's not after money.
Remember, he said
he...he wants to free people
from the power
it has over them.
- So what?
He has an axe to grind
with the system?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It explains why he attacked
the Cleary Capital offices.
He doesn't want cash.
He wants chaos.
- Well, he got it.
- What exactly
did he make you see?
- Just...
Kamilla, in danger.
What about you?
What did you see?
- It doesn't matter.
- What if it does?
What if there's like
a clue or something in
what you saw...
- There isn't.
- Well, you don't know that.
Look, you're gonna have to
face him again, eventually.
- Well, what if I can't,
all right?
What if he's too powerful
and I can't stop him?
- Barry, no one said...
- You didn't have to.
Maybe, Psych's
gonna destroy this whole city
and everyone in it.
There's nothing
I can do about it.
- Trying to reconnect
the transmitter
to the output circuit?
- Turns out I'm better
at breaking things
than I am at fixing them.
- Do you want to tell me
what scared you so much
when Psych whammied you?
Come on,
we used to share a brain.
I know you don't scare easy.
- I was under arrest,
for all the crimes I committed
as Killer Frost.
And you were the one
who turned me in.
- I would never do that.
- I know.
Look, ever since you let me
take the wheel,
I got to live my life,
not just half the time,
but all the time.
And I really liked it.
And I don't want to go back
to living my life
just half the time.
And I was afraid you'd hate me
for saying that.
- I would never hate you.
You're my sister.
You can always tell me
how you feel.
- I don't know how.
I mean...
I may be the strong one,
but...
you're the brave one.
I mean,
you're fearless!
I mean, ever since I got
in touch with my feelings,
I just...
I'm scared,
all the time.
Sometimes
I don't even know why.
- You think you're the only one
who gets scared sometimes?
Ever since we separated,
there's been this
deafening silence
inside my head,
where you used to be.
And it terrifies me.
That's why I've been
so desperate
to put us back together.
Why I got so upset
when you broke the Matrix.
It's 'cause my biggest fear
in life
is living without you.
- Mine too.
- Well, why don't we face
that fear together?
- You mean...
- Maybe two Snows,
really is better than one.
My apartment has
an extra bedroom.
I could use a roommate,
what do you say?
- I say...
"This Is Us."
♪ ♪
- Cecile, I'm sorry.
I just...um, needed a minute.
- Okay.
You do know that you're not
the only one who's been
whammied with more than one
dose of Psych's fear, though?
- You've been picking up his
energy every time he shows up.
- Last night, I saw...
I saw a nightmare,
where I couldn't
control my own powers.
It was terrifying.
It's been really hard to keep
my own fears at bay today.
I spent last year so afraid
of losing everyone I loved
in Crisis, I never thought I'd
have to face that fear again.
Psych showed me...
People I love,
dead.
Fuerza had killed them.
We've taken on the impossible,
so many times.
Something about these new
threats feels different.
Bigger.
And for the first time
since Crisis...
I'm sc...I'm scared.
- Sometimes, when I'm scared
I ask myself,
"What would The Flash do?"
Seriously.
Barry,
you run through fear,
every time
you save this city.
Honey, you just gotta
find some of that courage
for yourself.
[alarm sounding]
- Guys, we just detected
Psych's isotopic signature.
It's expanding,
all over Sandoval Heights.
- Cecile,
you sent your own fear
into Top.
Do you think you could do that
on a bigger scale?
- D...
Me?...No, no way.
Barry, I could barely broadcast
one emotion across a room.
- Then let's get you
some help.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Barry?
Are you insane?
- I know, it sounds crazy,
but,
DeVoe built this chair
to expand his mental capacity
on a massive scale.
- Yeah, yeah,
and it turned him
into a supervillain!
- But you won't,
'cause you're gonna use it
to save the city.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
- I can feel all your fear,
Central City,
and feels exquisite.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Please...please let me out.
Let me out of here, please!
- It's too much.
Too much!
I can't take it!
- Mom, Dad?
Please don't leave me here.
Why won't you come home?
[multiple screams]
- Get away from me!
[multiple frightened yelling]
- Everything's burning!
- Help me!
The walls are closing in!
- Cecile, you good?
- Nope!
Not even close to good.
I...I am sitting in
a death machine.
What if this thing fries
my brain?
Wh...what if this chair
turns me evil like the Top?
What about that?
- As a medical professional,
I promise you will be okay.
- Okay.
- Probably.
- Flash, where you at?
- I'm approaching
Psych's radius.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Do it.
♪ ♪
[machine whirring]
[screaming voices]
- I can't breathe!
Make it stop!
[multiple screams]
- It's working.
I can...I can...
feel people's minds,
thoughts, all over the city.
I can feel Barry.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- His amygdala is spiking.
- Barry, can you hear me?
Cecile is connected
to your mind.
Whatever you're seeing,
fight through it.
[thunder cracks]
- This isn't real.
It's not real.
- You got us all killed,
Barry.
- I trusted you.
Why didn't you save me?
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- When you let me die,
you killed our children too.
♪ ♪
- Barry can't hear us.
He's caught inside
his nightmare.
He's lost.
- I'm diverting all
satellite power to the comms.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Listen to me, Barry.
You have to get through this.
- Cisco,
I don't know if I can.
- Yes, you can.
You are strong enough,
I know you are.
We can't do this
without you.
- You're a coward, Barry Allen!
- You'll lose us again.
- All because
you're too afraid.
Too afraid
to open your eyes.
♪ ♪
- You're right,
I am afraid.
But I won't let
that fear control me.
♪ ♪
- He broke through!
Cecile, now!
- Barry,
I can feel your courage.
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
- You're too late, Flash.
Ahh!
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- Guys, it worked.
Cecile did it.
- I did it.
- You did it.
- [exhales sharply]
I did it!
- You did it.
- [laughing]
Guys,
I think I need
an energy bar.
- Your frontal cortex
is healing,
but the part that controls
motor control
is still falling behind.
- No trace of Psych
or Fuerza.
- Well, either way,
at least now we have proof
they're connected.
When I struck Psych
with my lightning,
he shook it off easy, but
just for a minute,
the lightning...
it stayed with him.
- Was it glowing?
- Yeah.
- Same thing happened
when you fought Fuerza.
- I threw everything I had
at them,
we all did.
They just kept coming for more.
Luckily, your powers
are getting stronger, too.
- Well,
chair did most of the work,
but thanks.
- I don't know,
you kicked some
pretty serious psychic ass
out there.
Might have to teach Martian
Manhunter a thing or two.
- [laughs]
- Ahh!
- Barry!
- [groaning]
- Is it Psych?
- No, no.
This is something else.
- I'm getting the same readings
I got off Nora.
♪ ♪
- I need to heal myself.
Open the cryo-pod.
- No, Barry.
That'll put you in a coma.
- It's the only way.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Logistics compliance.
Is that what you were doing
when you were working
in Gotham?
- I've made a few
trips there.
I'm a big Knights fan.
- And I called my buddy
who'd been working
the Gotham beat
for more than a decade,
pretty high stakes game
you played.
And...
There is this.
So I don't know
what your goal is here,
but, if you're gonna be
in my precinct...
how about we cut the bull,
and you be honest with me.
- Fair enough.
I wasn't planning
to announce this
until I got my bearings.
On the orders of
the governor,
I'm here to locate
and apprehend
a rogue meta-human,
whatever the cost.
And quite frankly,
it's about time someone
address the long-standing issue
this precinct ignored.
- You want to arrest The Flash?
- No...he's clean.
So far.
I'm here for someone
far more dangerous.
The meta-human fugitive
known as Killer Frost.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- How is he?
- Better. I think.
Barry's system
was overwhelmed
with the same strange
signatures
that I found in Nora's system.
His vitals have stabilized
a bit,
which is good news, but
as to when
he'll be fully healed,
it's difficult to say.
- If Psych or Fuerza
were to attack right now,
we're totally on our own.
- Because I wasn't
fast enough.
- Nora.
- [groans]
This physical form
is new for me.
I didn't know its limitations.
I can feel
how weak he still is.
How weak we both still are.
What happened to Barry?
- He was attacked by
a powerful meta-psychic.
- Who showed him
his greatest fear?
That same psychic was
the second of my attackers.
- Fuerza and Psych?
They both hurt you?
- Who are they?
- I think...
they're just like me.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.