My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother
killed by something impossible.
My father went to
prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my
mother and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
You killed my mother. Why?
If you wanna know that,
you're gonna have to catch me.
Not fast enough, Flash.
I love you, Iris. I couldn't
lie to you anymore. I'm sorry.
My name is Barry Allen.
I am not the fastest man alive.
That title belongs
to the man who killed my mother.
But not for long.
That was too close.
- He told me to make it hard.
- He didn't tell you to make him dead.
Remember this is just supposed to be a
training exercise to improve Barry's speed.
Cisco, you gonna
bring it or what?
Bring it.
Why isn't he running away?
Barry, run away.
Very impressive, Mr. Allen. Your reaction to
stimuli at super speed continues to improve.
- It's still not enough.
- It will be.
Keep working like you are.
Stay focused.
You will be ready next time your
man in the yellow suit comes.
I think you mean
the Reverse-Flash.
What? He said it, not me.
And he's right. Yellow suit, red
lightning, and evil. The reverse of Barry.
- Meh.
- Actually, I kind of like it.
I'm so ready for another round.
How many drones do you have?
Two, and they've got lasers.
No.
Told you it would break.
And the shrink says I'm crazy.
- What is this place?
- Customs warehouse.
Imported cars from Europe.
All worth a fortune.
Question. How do you suggest you and
I drive all these cars out of here?
We're not. We're not
stealing anything.
What are you talking about?
Our entrance set off
the silent alarms.
The cops will be arriving
in two minutes and 14 seconds.
Bring them.
That's not for the cops...
as we discussed.
He'll be here.
You do hear that, right?
He's not coming.
We're leaving.
- This better make sense real fast,
buddy. - It will. Let's go.
- You promised I'd get to do my thing.
- I always keep my promises.
Seatbelt.
- Are you sure nothing's missing?
- That's what the supervisor said.
I can check again.
- Bar.
- Hey.
Uh, well...
the breakage indicates
that the door somehow...
had zero viscoelasticity
when it hit the ground.
What does that mean
to normal people?
Sorry. Uh, the steel
shattered like glass.
It was frozen, Joe.
- Snart.
- He's back.
I thought Snart was
some world-class thief.
All these expensive cars, he didn't
take any of them? Doesn't make sense.
- Eddie, put out an APB on Snart.
- Got it.
Snart wasn't here
to steal anything.
- He was setting a trap.
- For me.
- And by me, I mean...
- I know what you meant.
God, you're beautiful.
Mick.
This is a joke. How do you know
this Flash didn't skip town, hm?
Maybe that's why he didn't
show up. Or maybe he's dead.
Or maybe someone
smarter than you iced him.
He's not dead and he
didn't leave town.
You will tell me what we're stealing
this time? We are partners, after all.
This is what we came for.
That's worth money?
It's called Fire & Ice. An
abstract modern-day masterpiece...
said to represent
the dichotomy of being.
It represents to me that people
with lots of money buy dumb stuff.
Osgood and Rachel Rathaway, one of
the richest couples in Central City...
paid 25 million
for it in Paris.
They're flying
home with it today.
Mm.
Captain Cold is back.
For a non-metahuman, Leonard
Snart is quite the nemesis.
He still has the cold gun, the one
he stole from us. The one I built.
What does he want this time?
The Flash.
If Snart wants a fight,
then I'll give him one.
- Well...
- You don't think I should?
I didn't say that. But, Barry, as fast as
you are, you cannot be everywhere at once.
And it becomes then a question of priorities.
In the last month, you have made...
a commitment to increasing your
speed, enhancing your reflexes.
It's working. You're
getting faster.
Okay, but what am I supposed
to do? Just ignore Snart?
The last time you had a fight
with Snart, a train derailed.
You were lucky to get
all those people to safety.
- Now, if you don't give him that
fight... - He may just back off.
And there'll be no casualties.
Look, Barry, Cisco and I will
work with Joe and the police...
and devise a
way to catch Cold.
Yes, I said it. Soon as it came
out of my mouth, I heard it.
We can come up with ways
to neutralize Snart.
Listen, Barry, whether or
not you go after Snart...
that's your choice. We here, we
will do whatever we can to support you.
But after this past Christmas...
after the events with
the Reverse-Flash...
I just think he poses
a greater threat to all of us.
Okay.
T-minus three days and counting.
Until the big move-in. You
know, I've never had a roommate.
But it did occur to me
if we ever get in a fight...
I can't just storm away and go
home because home will be with you.
- Are you predicting many arguments?
- Have you met me?
I remember the night we met. I
stopped a mugger who stole your bag.
My hero.
H9)'-
Eddie, you know where Joe is?
- Uh, I think he's upstairs in your lab.
- Okay. Thanks.
No second thoughts
about moving in together?
None.
- Joe, hey.
- Hey, I'm glad you're back.
- I've been going over Snarfs file.
- Yeah. I need to talk to you.
Um, as CSI, my work
on this case is done.
And as...
the Flash, I don't think
I can focus on Snart right now.
Mind telling me
what brought about this change?
This man in yellow,
the man that killed my mom...
he's still out there. I have to be ready
to face him, which means amping up my speed.
It's a question of priorities.
Your mom's killer isn't the only
reason you've been doing this.
You told me if you could use your
powers to save someone, you would.
Look, Dr. Wells and S.T.A.R.
Labs are gonna work with you.
Cisco thinks he has a way to protect
the police against Snart's cold gun.
I understand if you're scared.
We talked about this.
Of course I'm scared, Joe.
This guy could run into the precinct and
kill everyone in seconds. He threatened Iris.
I won't let him hurt the most
important people in my life again.
If that means devoting every second I have
outside this place to getting faster...
and stopping him, that's what
I'm gonna do. I've made up my mind.
Aw.
McSnurtle the
turtle. How you been?
When did you stop sleeping with
this? He was your favorite.
He was. But if I remember correctly,
you took him away from me...
after I broke your Duke Ellington
Live at the Blue Note vinyl.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mm.
- You can have him back.
- Oh, gee, thanks.
L-leh-
Oh, Dad.
I'm gonna miss you, baby.
- Dad, I'm only 10 minutes away.
- I know.
Ah, don't you worry about me.
I'll be fine. Just like always.
_H6Y- _H6Y-
Came to help her pack?
Oh, no. No, no, no. Iris said
that she had something for me?
Oh. Ahem.
I found this in my closet. Heh.
I haven't seen this in years.
Well, the nerd survival
kit is still intact.
Wow.
Heh. I thought those
might be worth something.
Uh, I am so late for work.
I promise I'll clean
this up when I get back.
- Bye.
- Bye.Yeah.Heh.
Okay.
You mind telling me what's
going on with you and Iris?
- Nothing.
- Hm.
That's funny because I have
these two things called eyes...
and it doesn't look
like you two are fine.
I told Iris.
You told Iris you're the Flash?
No, no, no. I'm sorry.
I told her how I felt about her.
- Oh, God.
- Mm-hm.
What'd she say?
Well, I mean, she's still moving
in with Eddie, isn't she?
I just wanna pretend like it never even
happened. That's what we're both doing, so...
Well, not saying how you feel is what
got you in this mess in the first place.
Speaking of which, we both know she's not
gonna clean this mess up anytime soon.
No.
Sure.
Uh, excuse me. If I could have
everybody's attention, please.
You have our
attention, Mr. Ramon.
Okay, check it.
So Dr. Wells and I, we took
your ballistic shields and...
And we lined them with a pretty
sweet compacted heating ribbon...
designed to repel
temperature attacks...
especially those reaching absolute
zero, like Captain Cold's gun.
That's supposed to keep us from
getting turned into popsicles?
Um, yeah. Yeah, they will.
How are we supposed to trust anything from
S.T.A.R. Labs after you nuked the city?
You're right.
You shouldn't trust us.
What happened a year ago,
that was our fault.
And we can't change the past,
as much as we wish we could.
But tomorrow is a different story.
Tomorrow's a different thing.
We just want the chance
to make things better.
Observe.
Dummies are one thing...
my officers are another.
You seem pleased with
yourself, doctor.
Well, I'm just happy to help
the police catch Snart, Joe.
- Barry might be able to help too. - I think
Cisco's heat shields are up to the task.
Joe, if Barry feels he's gonna
endanger lives by taking on Snart...
and feels he's gonna save lives by
training to take on the man in yellow...
that's his call.
You know what makes
Barry so special?
He wants to help everyone
he can, however he can.
Always has. Until now.
I guess it's just a question
of priorities, then.
You know, Barry said the
exact same thing to me.
I thought, "Doesn't sound like him."
I guess because it sounds like you.
- Hey.
- Aah!
Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you.
- It's okay. I was just kind of focused.
- Gotcha.
What's Firestorm?
One of the last things Ronnie
said to me before he flew away.
My dead fiancé can fly. Haven't
broke that to my parents yet.
- You doing okay?
- Yeah, yeah. I just...
I told Iris how
I felt about her.
- Bold choice.
- I knew where we stood before.
We're best friends and, I don't know, now I
just don't know what's normal for us anymore.
Before I met Ronnie, I knew exactly what
was going to happen every day of my life.
It was predictable.
I like predictable.
But when Ronnie and I started
dating, everything started to change.
He made me try Indian food
and scuba diving.
At first it was scary,
but then it was better.
Things weren't really normal with you pining
after Iris and her being totally unaware.
Whatever happens next,
it will be better.
Wait, Caitlin.
- Scuba.
- What about it?
"Self-contained underwater breathing
apparatus." It's an acronym.
What if Firestorm isn't a word?
"Fusion ignition research
experiment and science...
of transmutation originating
RNA and molecular structures."
It's 800 pages.
There's a lot of stuff in there, but it
mostly focuses on transmutation, which is...
the process of altering the structure
of an element by unzipping atoms...
And rebuilding it to create
an entirely new element.
Yeah. Well, the article
was co-written by Jason Rusch...
a grad student here at Hudson University.
If anybody knows what happened to Ronnie...
Maybe he does.
- Maybe.
- Thanks.
- Pleasant flight, Mrs. Rathaway?
- Yes, quite. Thank you.
Careful, please.
It's worth a fortune.
- Welcome home, Mr. Rathaway.
- Thank you, Ethan.
Sir, your son, Hartley,
he called again.
We don't have a son anymore.
Someone better call 911.
Move! Move!
Snart, freeze.
Mick.
- Aah!
- What the hell?
Why do they call you
people "the heat"?
I'm the heat.
Forget them, Mick.
- Get ready for him.
- It's beautiful.
Mick.
We go. Now.
Is he all right?
Okay.
- Hey. Hey, are you okay?
- I'll call you back.
I'm fine.
Snarfs new partner, he's got
this handheld flamethrower.
Almost everyone was treated on the scene,
but we got two in the Burn Unit though.
- I'm sorry. I should've
listened to you. - It's all good.
Next time Snart and his pyro pal show up, you
make them sorry they ever messed with you.
I gotta call the hospital.
The cop's bullet ruptured the
secondary internal fuel chamber.
Could have been worse. You were right to get me
to learn every part and circuit of this thing.
Repairing it was a snap.
Give me one reason
I don't kill you right now.
It's gonna be hard to find someone
else to listen to your speeches.
You lost it out there just like the last
job. You lost focus, became obsessed.
I'm obsessed? What about you?
You're usually counting the seconds.
Got the whole thing planned out.
Dotting T's, crossing I's.
But all you care about
now is the Flash.
- We have to put him down.
- Why?
We got the finger painting. It's worth
millions. It's ours. We're rich. Job done.
What about the next job?
And the job after that?
With weapons like these, no one can stand
against us. No one except the Flash.
If you want out, take
the painting and go.
But if you want Central City to be our home,
where we can do and take whatever we want...
this is our chance.
Your chance.
Mm.
Very motivational.
How do we get him?
The Flash isn't so
different from us.
- He's got partners too.
- Hm.
- Jason Rusch?
- Yes. Uh, Dr. Snow?
Please, call me Caitlin.
Uh, thank you for meeting me.
Happy to. Although to be totally
upfront, if this is about the résumé...
I mailed to S.T.A.R. Labs, I've
accepted a position at Mercury Labs.
Uh, no, actually. I wanted to
talk to you about FIRESTORM.
I'm sorry. Uh, this was
a mistake. I have to go.
No. Look, someone I care about is in trouble,
and you're the only clue I have to help him.
Please.
What's the line? I never got paranoid
until they started plotting against me?
Why would they be
plotting against you?
Because of our work.
Because of FIRESTORM.
Transmutation. The ability to
alter matter on a molecular level.
We had rudimentary success
with our stage one testing...
working with sand grains.
But Professor Stein said...
Sorry. Professor Martin Stein? He
was the co-author of the paper?
Yeah, he was our team leader. He didn't believe
in baby steps, so we skipped to stage three.
Which was?
We melted a concrete wall.
But the university
threatened to shut us down...
so Professor Stein published his paper
without permission. They went nuts.
He talked to a friend of his
to secure private backing.
- And who was that? - He didn't say.
He just said he'd call me later.
And no one has seen or heard
from Professor Stein since.
What do you think
happened to him?
All I know is that the Army showed up the
next day and confiscated all of our research.
So tell me, Dr. Snow, do you
think I'm being too paranoid...
or not paranoid enough?
Car trouble?
I hope we're not enemies.
What? No, of course not.
I thought you might blame me.
For pushing you to pursue your
training rather than help the police.
Look, I'm an adult.
I make my own choices,
my own mistakes.
And I'm glad you
push me to be better.
It's so weird. There was
a time in my life that...
I would have paid money for
your autograph. And now we're...
Partners.
I was gonna say friends.
In case you doubt it,
you push me to be better too.
Guys, you have to
come look at this.
When the heat gun was fired, it
increased the surrounding temperature...
of the air dramatically. Sort
of like an extreme heat wave.
- Heat Wave.
- Stop doing that.
Okay. I measured the temperature output
of both the cold and heat guns, right?
And while the cold gun
achieves absolute zero...
the heat gun reaches absolute hot, or
the hottest temperature an object can reach.
Planck temperature.
So potentially, these two guns
could cancel each other out.
Yeah, but to do that, you'd
have to make them cross streams.
You mean like Ghostbusters?
That film is surprisingly
scientifically accurate.
And really quite funny.
Hey, Joe. What's up?
- Joe. Anything?
- There's no sign of Caitlin.
Oh, my God.
- We're getting her back. We have
to find Snart. - Damn right we do.
Come on, let's go.
Joe. Joe. We got a hit.
Second pair of prints.
They belong to a Mick Rory.
- Who is he?
- Big-time arsonist.
He and Snart worked a job
last year that went bad.
Half of Rory's body was burned in
a fire that got out of control.
He escaped from an ambulance.
Hasn't been seen since.
Why would they kidnap
someone like Caitlin?
Joe. Thawne. It's
on every station.
Greetings, citizens
of Central City.
I am Leonard Snan',
but you can call me Cold.
I'm gonna make this
very simple for everyone.
That red streak you've been
hearing whispers about.
The one mysteriously saving
people these past few months?
Well, surprise, he's real.
He calls himself the Flash.
Porter and Maine.
Tonight. Sundown.
Come out, come out, wherever you are,
Flash. Show the whole world you're real.
Or this woman dies.
No, don't come for me.
Stay away. He'll hurt...
You're a friend of
his, huh? He's fast.
Like fire.
Fire, it's undefinable.
Heat, light, energy.
It's an evolution
when things burn.
You're sick.
Maybe you're the sick ones.
You ever think about that?
- Not really.
- Mm.
You've got third-degree burns.
Why didn't you get skin grafts?
The fire revealed my true self.
It showed me who I really am.
I wonder what your Flash will reveal
when I burn his suit and skin off?
Do whatever you want to me,
but leave him alone.
Ooh.
Okay.
You and this Flash must be really close
if you're willing to die for him, hm?
You want me to show you who you
really are? That'd be fun. Hm?
Show you who you really are.
Mick.
Time to go.
You better pray the next people
that come through this door is us.
- Hey.
- Okay. You're on.
- Good luck, son.
- Thanks.
Barry, after tonight, everyone's
gonna know that the Flash exists.
Are you ready for that?
I'll see you soon.
Did you see that? That was him.
- That was the Flash.
- I don't believe it.
Believe it.
The scarlet speedster.
Any preference on how
you'd like to die?
The flame? Or the frost?
Not in the mood for chitchat.
Gotcha. Ready when you are.
Cover me.
Run on this.
Barry? Barry, are you okay?
You know what you have to do.
Yeah. Get them to cross beams and
cancel their guns out. I know.
Mick.
Ah! Gotcha.
Yeah, not as easy as it sounds.
- Eddie. Eddie.
- Iris, what are you doing here?
- They evacuated Jitters. I saw your car.
- You can't be here. It's not safe.
Are you sure
Caitlin's here, Cisco?
From Caitlin's car, I pieced together
surveillance footage that lead us to this area.
But there's over a
dozen warehouses.
But only one of them has had the
heat on the last three nights.
And I'm betting Mick
Rory likes it hot.
Okay.
Stay behind me.
- Caitlin.
- Mm?
Caitlin, is that you? Mm-mm.
Caitlin, we're gonna
get you out of here.
Cisco. Cisco, down!
The fight is spreading beyond the evac
area. We need to expand the perimeter.
We can't. We can't
let this spread.
Oh, my God.
- Thawne, where you going?
- Eddie.
I thought I was gonna die.
Not while I'm around. Or him.
Hold on!
I got this. Go, go, g0!
I can't get them to cross streams.
Speed isn't getting it done.
You're right.
Maybe the way to do this
is not by going faster.
- It's going slower.
- Yes.
Okay.
Thanks for playing, kid.
I didn't see that coming.
Mm, I guess you win this time.
There won't be a next time.
Thank you, detective.
We'll burn every last one of
you pigs! Get your hands off me!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Yeah!
- Your partner's a real hot head.
- That's funny.
You know what's hilarious,
Snart? We got you.
- Congratulations.
- Get him out of here.
- Nice work, Eddie.
- It wasn't me.
It was the Flash.
We're not gonna be needing these
for trial. You'll make sure...
They'll never hurt
anyone ever again.
Mr. Ramon.
Thank you.
He was like a lightning bolt through the
streets. He took them both out singlehandedly.
- That's amazing.
- Wonder who he is?
You ask me, he's a hero.
Okay. All right.
I think that's it.
This better be it.
Well, like you said, I'll be 10 minutes
away, so if you forget something...
Okay.
Dad... Heh.
I can't say it
enough. I'll miss you.
You know you can come
around any time, Joe.
- Just give us a heads-up.
- Heh.
Or not.
Come around whenever.
You want a key?
I'm gonna go...
wait in the truck.
Why don't I give
you two a minute?
Well...
I know things have been really
weird between us recently.
Yeah, they have.
Did you know I can
see into the future?
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
Did I forget to tell you that?
You did not mention it, no.
- Wow.
- Ha-ha.
So, what do you see?
I see you and Eddie
being really happy together.
And things aren't weird
between us anymore.
Took a little time, but
everything's back to normal...
and we're still best friends.
The future doesn't sound so bad.
No. And it'll be here
faster than you think.
The Patriots continue their...
Dad, um, is it okay if I...?
Oh. Yeah.
My baby girl.
- Bye.
- See you.
Well...
You Okay?
Mm-hm.
- How about you? - It was
bound to happen sometime, right?
Mm-hm.
Want to order pizza
and watch the ball game?
Make it pizzas, and you're on.
If you ever need somebody to come
and eat your food, I'm there.
Besides, the laundry machines in my
building have been broken for a month.
I don't know why you moved into
that death trap in the first place.
You've got a perfectly
good room here.
- You said you were turning it into a gym.
- We both know I'm not turning it into a gym.
Besides, you've got me
running around enough as it is.
It is getting hard to hide the blasting in
and out of my apartment from my neighbors.
I suppose it would make sense
for me to move back in.
I am a millennial.
That is what we do.
Don't do it on my account.
I'll be fine on my own.
Oh, yeah. Me too. For sure.
All right, roomie. You order
the pizzas, I'll unpack.
Heh-heh. No way.
I wanna help you.
I wanna enjoy this.
All right.
You know this does
nothing to me.
- Just drink it.
- Mm-hm.
I should have burned the entire city block
down, but instead, I listened to you.
We had the painting. We had the
guns. We could have had everything.
But you had your stupid plan.
How's that stupid plan
working out for us now?
Everyone's seen the Flash now.
This changes things, again.
What the...?
- Snart.
- Relax, Mick.
What's going on?
The plan.
Hey, sis.
Nice.