My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Zoom wants you dead.
Do you think he can do
everything really fast?
- How you doing, Dig?
- You're fast.
Welcome to Earth-2.
Dad! No! No!
Caitlin. That is your name isn't it?
I hate the name "Caitlin."
I'm Killer Frost.
Ronnie and Caitlin's
doppelgangers are evil?
If you're coming with us, we have to go.
Cisco!
Get ready to close the breach for good!
Zoom's coming!
No!
He's not dead. He's not dead.
- Caitlin.
- He's not dead. He's not.
- This isn't happening.
This isn't happening again.
Hey, I got you. Come on.
Open it up.
- Allen.
- I need to go back.
I can't do that.
- Open it up!
- Allen!
The breaches are closed.
All the breaches are closed.
Why can't we just open one of them?
The quark matter energy
that we used to seal the breaches,
it prevents them from being opened.
Ever again.
There's no going back to our world.
Wait.
We're trapped here for good?
Yes.
Look, we can'tjust let
Zoom get away with this.
He just murdered Jay right in front of us.
There's gotta be something we can do.
There's not.
Not this time.
It's over.
No.
How's she doing?
Not good.
I tried to get her to go home,
but she refused to leave.
So, you know,
I Just sat with her until she fell asleep.
First Ronnie, now Jay.
Yeah.
I'm afraid of what this double dose
of grief is gonna do to her.
I mean, she's pretty shell-shocked.
She'll be fine.
Snow's strong.
She'll get past this.
In the meantime,
I would not say anything to her
about her counterpart from my Earth.
That goes for Joe and Iris, too.
Why?
Because you don't wanna
influence their reality
in ways it should not be influenced.
Like in the same way
as when Barry time-travels?
Exactly. But also, what's the point?
Those people are not your people.
Their lives are not your lives.
Never were, never will be.
Bury it, move on.
Yes?
Yeah.
That I can do.
Allen?
So that's what we did.
We didn't talk about Earth-2.
We kept what happened there
between the three of us
and got on with our lives
knowing there was nothing
we could do now to stop Zoom.
Instead, we tried to just adjust
to our new circumstances
and cope with our losses.
Jay's death took its toll.
Left scars on all of us.
Some more than others.
And so to try and keep
my mind off thoughts
of the surreal other life
I experienced that wasn't my own,
I kept running.
Waiting for some other meta-human threat
to rear its ugly head
and distract me
from the frustration I was feeling.
And as fate would have it,
I did not have to wait long.
All good.
GUNS COCKING
Hey, ugly. It's time for dinner.
I think Bruce has gone belly up.
Power down the grid.
We're gonna have to fish him out.
So this is where Waller kept
all her secret projects, huh?
One of many sites, I'm learning.
Well, I'm sure the
new Director 0fA.R.G.U.S.
Will clean up the mess
that Waller left behind.
Easier said than done, honey.
Hey.
My wife can do anything
she puts her mind to.
Code seven in aquaria three.
Irepeat, code seven in aquaria three.
There's been a breach in the aquarium.
You have an aquarium? Why?
What the hell?
Are you kidding me?
Seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
- Time!
- Yes!
Ain't nobody faster than me!
Well, I don't know about that.
Earth to Barry.
It's your turn, dude.
Yeah. It's time to show this little punk
who the fastest Stack Attack-er alive is.
One of you guys go ahead. I'm gonna pass.
You're afraid of a little competition?
No. Just not in a gaming mood right now.
Okay, well, I guess
that makes me the champ.
Right? Whoo.
Uh, anyway, I'm gonna go meet up
with some friends.
All right.
- Bye.
Maybe next time.
And I thought you were the
competitive one in the family.
I know, right? What's up, Barr?
Nothing. Just...
I don't know.
I don't think Wally likes me too much.
Well, we need to fix that.
I mean, you've been so busy running
between alternate realities,
you two haven't had a chance
to spend any time together.
Well, what do you want us to do together?
Get to know each other.
I mean, find something
that you guys have in common.
He's part of the family now, Barr.
You're gonna have to give it a chance.
I know.
Um, all right, well, look,
I'm gonna head to bed, all right?
All right.
- Good night.
Something is up with him,
and I don't think it'sjust Jay's death.
He's been acting weird ever since
he came back from Earth-2.
Did he say anything to you about
what happened over there?
No. Nota thing.
You?
Hmm.
Hey, so I've been thinking.
You've been working around the clock,
maybe you wanna get some rest, go home.
You know, a good night's sleep
wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
I'm fine.
Look, I get it.
You're having a hard time
with what happened.
- It's a lot to take so soon after...
- I said I'm fine.
Hey.
- Did you hear that?
- No. What?
Caitlin just bit my head off.
She's been all-business-no-emotion lately.
She's been cold.
Cold? Come on, Cisco.
This could be the beginning
of her becoming evil.
You're not worried about that?
I'm not worried about that.
Caitlin's not gonna become Killer Frost.
You haven't mentioned anything
about Earth-2, have you?
No. 'Cause I know how to keep a secret.
All right, well, look, I mean...
It's going to take some time
for her to heal.
We just got to be there for her.
Keep her busy.
- That shouldn't be a problem.
- Oh...
Hey, Dig, Lyla.
What are you guys doing here?
We came hereto give you
the heads-up, Barry.
About what?
A meta-human who escaped
from A.R.G.U.S. custody.
Goes by the name King Shark.
King Shark?
You mean, the half-man, half-shark
that tried to kill you months ago?
I thought he was dead.
That's what A.R.G.U.S. wanted you
to believe when they snatched him up.
But believe me,
this half-shark is very much alive.
And his biological imperative
is telling him to do one thing,
that's kill you, Barry.
We're gonna need a bigger Flash.
So how do you know about King Shark?
As the new director ofA.R.G.U.S.,
Lyla's job is to clean up
Amanda Waller's messes.
King Shark was one of the
bigger and weirder ones.
And it appears under her directives,
A.R.G.U.S. had been monitoring meta-human
activity for the past two years.
- Why?
- Well, to see if any of those powers
could be exploited.
Weaponized.
How do you know that he's coming after me?
While in our custody,
he kept saying the same thing.
"Zoom wants The Flash dead."
And although he removed
the tracker we had in him,
the readings we did receive show
that he was headed towards Central City.
Let him come.
Barry, this thing is a killing machine.
We just came here to warn you, man.
Let A.R.G.U.S. handle it.
No, I can't do that, Dig.
I'm sorry, but all year,
we've been sitting ducks for Zoom
and all his Earth-2 henchmen.
This is the last one.
I'm not gonna just wait for him to attack.
I'm going after him first.
I owe that to Jay.
Wells, he's from your Earth.
What do you know about him?
Real name is Shay Lamden.
He was a, get this, marine biologist
before my particle accelerator
changed him into King Shark
and Zoom put him under his control.
So how did you track him
when he attacked Barry?
Zoom sent him to this Earth to kill Barry.
I just followed.
Yeah, but you did track Grodd down.
Can you find King Shark, too?
- I can try.
- All right.
Okay, well, all these locations
are next to a body of water.
There must only be a few hours
before he needs to get back into the water
to re-oxygenate his blood.
I can take the waterfront.
Can you have your team handle the rest?
- I'll get them on it.
- All right.
What about Dr. Lamden's doppelganger?
Maybe he could help us somehow.
Or not.
Um, looks like he died when the
particle accelerator exploded.
What about next of kin?
Uh, he's got a widow, Dr. Tanya Lamden.
She's a research scientist
at Nautilus Labs,
and she studies, wait for it, sharks.
Okay, well, maybe the two of you can go
and see if she's discovered anything
in her research that could help us?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
Great.
- Hey, Dig.
- Yeah.
- How's that helmet treating you?
- It could use some improvements.
I'll get to work on it.
Hey, Joe, what's up?
Hey, Barr, ltalked to Wally.
- He wants to meet up with you.
- All right.
He's working on his engineering project
at our place tonight.
He would love some help
from that big brain of yours.
Okay, Joe, look, I'm sorry.
Right now is kind of a crazy time.
Why? What's going on?
Remember that meta-human shark
that Patty was after and attacked me?
- He's back? I thought Wells, you know.
- Yeah, me too.
But apparently, A.R.G.U.S. had him
and he escaped.
And now he's heading for Central City.
I get it. Uh, I'll tell Wally
some other time.
Hey, you know what? Um, it's all good.
I'll make it work.
Tell him tonight should be fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Barr.
- Yeah, bye.
Why?
It's been two years
since your particle accelerator exploded.
Seems a little late to be asking questions
about my husband, doesn't it?
Your husband passed away
from cancer, correct?
I suppose you could say that.
It only took three days for every cell
in his body to grow uncontrollably.
Whatever cancer he had,
it turned him into something not human.
Well, that's why we're here, actually.
There's a meta-human in Central City
whose body seems to be mutating
in the same way as your late husband.
But he didn't die,
he became a dangerous monster.
My husband was no monster.
That's not what she was implying.
What does this have to do with me?
We've read about the research
you're doing here on sharks.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah,
I've had some encouraging results.
Although, still preliminary.
We need to see it.
I beg your pardon?
Your research. All of it.
What my colleague means to say is that
if you could please let us
take a look at your findings,
it could help us stop this meta-human
from hurting anyone.
You're with S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'm just supposed to trust you?
Please, Mrs. Lamden.
This could help save lives.
I'll e-mail you what I have.
Thank you.
A little harsh.
I was being direct.
Yeah, well, that's one way to describe it.
You've been acting differently toward me
ever since you got back from Earth-2.
What's your problem, Cisco?
Nothing.
Let's just go.
Grid one, negative.
Grid four, negative.
Status check, grid two.
Grid two, negative.
- Anything?
- No, man. Nothing yet.
So far, nothing on our end, either.
I just hope Wells is doing
better than we are.
Hey, how's Felicity doing?
I'm not gonna lie, Barr.
It was pretty rough there at first,
but you know Felicity, she's tough.
Yeah. She's just not
returning any of my calls.
She has a lot going on right now.
But hey, I'll ask her if she can give you
a call when this is all over.
I just want to catch this thing, man.
If everything to do with Zoom and Earth-2
are put behind us,
we could just move on with our lives.
You're starting to do that thing
Oliver does, Barry.
Carry the weight of the world
on your shoulders.
You gotta stop that, man,
or it's going to slow you down.
Still nothing.
Status check, grid six.
Hold on,
I think we got something.
So much for cleaning up
after Waller's messes.
We don't find King Shark soon,
someone's going to be
cleaning up after mine.
We'll find him, Lyla.
All right.
I searched the whole area, he's gone.
He couldn't have gotten far.
Still, he knows we're here now.
We lost the element of surprise.
Not if Wells can figure out a way
to track him.
- In the meantime, we'll keep looking.
- All right.
I'll meet up with you guys later.
I gotta go see Joe's son.
Okay. I thought our relationship
was hard to follow.
See ya.
He's fast, John. Get over it.
Never.
Joe thought I should have you take a look.
So, this is what I got so far
for my project essay to get into
CCU's engineering program.
Turbine supercars?
Turbines. Like jet engines?
Yeah. Yeah, it'd use
an engine like the ones
they have in some helicopters,
only it'd run on biodiesel.
- Cool.
- Lt's very cool.
Yeah, you're gonna wanna address
the fuel economy issue here.
I mean, it is ajet, so it's gonna
burn through a lot of fuel.
Yeah. That's why I wanna use biodiesel.
It'll run off of anything
that burns with oxygen.
Okay, we also got a sound issue.
Gonna wake the neighbors for sure.
Anything else?
Um...
Well, I Just want to help, you know.
I'm just trying to make sure
they don't have any reason to say "no."
Okay.
Sorry, Wally, I didn't mean...
I mean, it looks really good.
All right, let's start over, okay?
Why don't we go through it
all together? Work it out.
- Sounds good.
- Cool.
This is a complete waste of time.
We're not gonna find anything
in Dr. Lamden's research
to tell us how to find King Shark.
Maybe I should take a look?
Oh, yeah, 'cause you're the doctor
with a specialty in biochem.
I'm just saying maybe you could use
another set of eyes, considering...
Considering what?
Considering the way
you've been acting lately.
What does that mean?
You are not yourself, Caitlin.
And it's freaking me out
'cause you have this icy look in your eye
just like you did over there.
Over there?
You mean Earth-2?
No.
Uh, no. Um...
What I meant to say was, um...
You met my doppelganger, didn't you?
What? No.
Cisco.
Look, I'm not supposed to say anything.
- Why not?
- Because I'm not supposed to say anything.
Francisco Ramon,
if you don't start talking...
Okay, fine! Yes, I met your doppelganger.
She's a coldhearted ice queen
named Killer Frost.
A meta-human, who enjoyed killing, a lot.
There.
Great. Now Harry's gonna kill me
and throw my stuff across the room.
Cisco, I'm not a meta-human.
Okay, I hear you, but you're acting
just like she did over there.
You're being shut off,
you're being detached,
you're being cold.
Because I have to be right now.
I just watched Jay get killed
right in front of my eyes.
Just when I was starting to
feel normal again.
Just when I was beginning to love him.
So if I let myself feel,
if I let all of that pain and anger out,
it's never gonna stop.
And that's not going to help me, either.
So let's just get back to this research
and figure out how to find King Shark.
Okay.
Here you are.
Yep, just like back home. Always working.
I'm trying to relocate this King Shark.
He's here? On this Earth?
Yes. It turns out, ourfriend
Zoom brought him here
to kill The Flash.
Looks like he's stuck here
just like we are.
Yeah, it looks like he is,
and so I have to figure this out
before more people get hurt, Jesse, so...
- Probability distribution algorithm?
- Partial matching strategies, yes.
- Based on what?
- Semantic trajectories.
Water, Central City, The Flash.
What about mobility behaviors?
Jesse.
Look, you wanted me out of that room,
but now that I am,
you don't want me here.
Just let me help. Please.
Grab a marker.
Yeah, okay.
Hardest pan' was amping the torque
without increasing drag.
A heavier engine would only
slow things down.
But this streamlined version
should optimize
both the torque and the horsepower.
Yeah. I'm just worried
it won't be enough still.
Here, let's do this.
Use a one-to-one transfer gearbox
to drop the output shaft of the engine.
Reverse rotation and send more power
to the torque converter.
I didn't come here for you
to just do it for me.
I thought we were gonna
work on this together.
Yeah, we are.
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to
speed up the process.
Why?
You got somewhere better to be?
No, I'm... Wally.
All right.
Do you have a problem with me?
Who could have a problem with you?
You're Barry, right? You're perfect.
Never do anything wrong.
Always this, always that.
Wally, it's...
I mean, take a look around you, man.
You're in every picture in this room.
You know, thanks for your help,
but I'll just take care of this myself.
Where's The Flash?
I know The Flash is here!
Ican smell him.
Everybody, get out!
Come on, all right, come on.
Where is he?
Right here!
Flash, Zoom wants you dead!
Yeah, I know.
Then you get to go home, right?
Well, guess what, man?
The breaches that Zoom used
to bring you here, they're all gone.
I closed them. For good.
There's no more Zoom.
There's no way back to your Earth.
You're going to be locked up here
for a very long time.
You might be fast,
but not as fast as I am in water.
You're not gonna catch me, Flash!
Okay.
- You okay?
- Oh, yeah, I'm good.
I think he broke a few things,
but I'm good.
I don't suppose my homeowner's insurance
covers a Sharknado attack.
I don't understand you people.
Jaws busts through your house
like the Kool-Aid Man.
The Flash shows up,
and you all just act like
it's no big deal.
Yeah, well, we've had a lot of
weird things happen
In Central City over the past two years.
Weirder than a talking shark
wearing pants?
Man, you'd be surprised.
Hey, hey, you guys.
Everybody Okay?
Yeah. Yeah, we're fine.
What, did you go hide under your bed?
Wally, come on.
You know, Joe and Iris told me
a lot about you.
Made out like you could walk on water
or something,
but they never mentioned anything about
you being a coward.
Okay, enough!
See you guys later.
Dad, you need to talk to him.
No, it's fine. I get it.
Look, I know you guys love me,
but please stop telling Wally
all this great stuff about me.
Start telling him the truth.
I'm not perfect.
I make mistakes
that even The Flash can't fix.
Okay.
What happened with you on Earth-2?
The truth.
I shouldn't tell you guys this, but, um,
I met your doppelgangers.
You were the cop in the family.
A good one, too.
I told you I would've made a good cop.
Don't get any ideas.
- What about me, then?
- You were a lounge singer.
Yeah, you had this
amazing voice, actually.
Um, but you didn't like me at all.
You actually blamed me
for Iris becoming a cop.
Said that she only became one
to help her selfish husband's career.
Wait, we were married?
Mmm-hmm.
We went to go see Joe perform.
And that's when everything went wrong.
Um, some metas that
worked for Zoom showed up.
They were looking for me. They knew
that I wasn't supposed to be there.
And they attacked, and
you got caught in the crossfire and
you died.
I knew that it wasn't you,
that none of that was this life,
but
watching it happen in front of me,
living that?
It didn't feel any different
because it was all still real.
And Jay warned me not to get
emotionally sucked in when I went there.
And then that's exactly what happened.
And now Joe West on Earth-2 is dead,
because I showed up.
Barr, that's not your fault.
Yeah, it is my fault.
It's all my fault.
Zoom,
this King Shark,
Jay's death.
It's all because of me.
And then I Just left an entire world
at Zoom's mercy.
Just when you thought it was safe
to go back in the suburbs,
King Shark shows up at your house.
I mean, I don't even know how he found me.
It's not like I was The Flash
while I was at home.
- Must be a reason.
- Yeah.
Have you figured out a way
to track King Shark yet?
No. I don't have enough information
to create an accurate location algorithm.
What about Dr. Lamden's research?
Anything that can help us?
I didn't think so at first,
but then I found something
that I think might help us.
Sharks are predators.
In order to track their prey,
they use what's known as
passive electro location.
- Passive electro location?
- Yes, it's how they sense
the bioelectric potential
around a fish's body.
King Shark senses electricity
in Barry's system.
Okay. That explains how
King Shark can track Barry.
But how is that going to
help us track him?
We flip it.
Instead of King Shark being the predator,
we make him the prey, and we track him
using active electro location.
We reprogram our satellite to
generate a specific electric field
and then measure any
electrical distortions
that correlate with a one-ton,
walking shark.
That'll help us get him.
- You'll help me out?
- Sure.
Great. Let us know when you locate him,
and we'll take it from there.
Okay.
Let's get the team ready.
What exactly is that?
That, my friend, is bait.
You made a Flash lure?
It's the best I could come up
with given the time frame.
It's rigged to mimic and enhance
the electric field Barry's body generates.
King Shark takes one whiff of that,
cue the Jaws soundtrack.
And I also stuffed it with enough tranqs
to knock him out for a month.
Which should make him
a lot easier to reel in.
And that container, strong enough
to hold him once he's sedated?
It's made of promethium metal.
It's impenetrable.
Meanwhile, we'll be able to keep track
of King Shark with this
and the cameras that are on the lure.
Whatever he does, we'll have eyes on him.
All right, then. Let's go fishing.
Caitlin, I don't understand why I can't be
the one playing Quint in this scenario.
I should be the one out there, not you.
I need to do this.
You know Quint dies, right?
Water is this monster's natural habitat.
He's gonna be a lot stronger here.
You sure about this?
This ends tonight.
Maybe he's not going to fall for this.
He's a shark. He'll come.
Anything, Cisco?
Uh, nope. Nothing that looks like
it could be him.
You programed the
satellite though, right?
- Yes, Harry.
- And you punched in
- the correct parameters?
- You're insulting my intelli...
- They could be waiting for hours. You...
- I know they've been out there for hours,
but you're insulting my intelligence
with this, okay? I know.
And you set the
right distortion scope, right?
Oh, for real?
Okay, you know what?
We're gonna play a game here.
It's called "lf you're from Earth-2,
you're gonna be quiet."
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Hey, Barry, you okay?
Ever since Zoom beat me here
and on Earth-2,
I've been running away from things,
instead of towards them.
That needs to change.
We'll get you back there.
I know.
Think of this as your first step. Or swim.
Uh, hey, guys, what is that?
The big, big kahuna. Guys, incoming.
He's headed for the bait.
Whoa.
He ate the lure!
Hey, reel him in, all right?
Come on.
Where'd he go?
He's headed for the docks.
GO, go:
Get ready to fire!
Those guns won't stop me, Flash.
First, I'll kill you.
Then I'll kill them.
Oh, yeah? Let's do this then! Come on!
- What is he doing?
- He's electrifying the water.
Now we can reel him in.
Hell of a catch, Barry.
Yeah.
Let's just make sure he doesn't become
the "one that got away."
Won't let that happen again.
So what are you gonna do with him?
I don't know yet.
But one thing's for sure.
A.R.G.U.S.'s plans to turn King Shark
into a weapon died with Amanda Waller.
I think our time would be better served
learning how he came to be
and how to cure him.
You know,
you should really talk to Dr. Lamden.
She's done a lot of research,
and I think it could be helpful to you.
I'll do that.
- Nice to see you again.
- Mmm-hmm.
Well, thanks a lot, Dig.
Hey, I gotta thank you, Barry.
Got Lyla her first win.
I got to watch you run on water.
It was biblical.
Look, Barry, when I was in Afghanistan,
I lost a lot of friends.
Brothers.
So losing Jay, I know what it feels like.
Question yourself,
blame yourself for his death.
And that guilt, it can tear you apart.
Trust me, man,
you gotta get control of it,
or it'll rip you up inside.
Use this, man. Let it guide you,
so it never happens again.
- All right, thanks, man.
- You got it.
- Say hi to everyone for me, all right?
- I will.
Yeah, okay, that's kind of freaky.
Yeah, yeah. See? I told you.
Hey, Oliver, what's up?
You're a really slow reader.
- So?
- I want one of these supercars.
I mean, especially if I can run it off
the bacon grease I collect.
Man, Wally, I'm so impressed.
Thanks. But Barry gave me
a lot of help, so...
Yeah, he did, but this was all your idea.
This is all your hard work.
It's all you.
Barry would say the same thing.
Would he?
Look, Wally.
Iris and I took Barry in
when he was 11.
And the reason he came to live with us
is because
his mother was murdered,
and his father was
wrongfully imprisoned for it.
And I have been overprotective
of that kid since that day.
We gave him all the love
and support he needed
to get through that tragedy
and become the man he is now.
So that pride
you see when Iris and I
are talking about him
is because things could have gone
very differently.
But he's not perfect.
And he's not favored
over you, or Iris, or anybody else.
So you have nothing to worry about.
He's my son.
Just like you are.
What are you doing with those?
I'm adjusting the wavelength trigger to
see if I can get these to work over here.
So you can catch some breachers?
Dear God, Caitlin,
your hands are freezing!
"Caitlin." I've always hated that name.
Oh, no!
No, no, no. It's starting.
You're starting to become...
Killer Frost?
That ain't right.
That ain't right. That's just rude.
Who put you up to this?
Barry put you up to this, didn't he?
Oh, I should've known.
- You two are...
- Cold?
Yeah.
You deserve it for thinking that
I could ever become like her.
Cisco, you need to stop worrying about me.
I may be sad, I may want to be alone
for a little while,
but I promise you
Killer Frost will never exist
on this Earth, okay?
Besides, you tested me.
I don't even have the meta-human gene.
So please stop worrying about me, okay?
Okay.
Come on, Barry wants us upstairs.
For real though,
you gotta work on that circulation.
You might have Raynaud's or something?
You know what Raynaud's is?
I'm a doctor, Cisco.
Hail, hail, the gang's all here.
What's good?
Uh...
I need to apologize to you all.
Um...
Last year, I made a choice
to go back in time
and save my mother.
And that choice had
a lot of consequences that will haunt me
for the rest of my life,
just like I know
it haunts all of you, too.
Zoom.
Jay's death.
It's all because of me.
But I own those choices.
We're the ones
who opened the door to Earth-2.
We're the ones who brought Zoom here.
But we are also the ones
who are gonna stop him.
How?
How are we going to stop Zoom, Allen?
I don't know yet.
But those breaches aren't closed forever,
and we're not done with Earth-2.
Jay's death was not in vain.
We will meet Zoom again.
And the next time,
I will beat him.
Whoever that monster is.
Well, this is a complication.