- Previously on "The Flash"...
- My cure will work.
- Or turn them
into meta-humans.
- [yells]
Beginning biopsy examination
on Patient 1-A,
Mitch Romero.
- I want to become a defense
attorney for meta-humans.
- Babe,
do you know how many people
you could help in this city?
- Hi, I'm here about
the internship.
- Welcome to "The Citizen."
- In order
for billions to survive,
the Flash must die.
- I'm gonna go see
this Crisis for myself.
[grunting]
The only timeline where
you all survived was if I died.
- So what do we tell them?
- Whatever we're gonna do,
we can't tell the team
I'm gonna die.
- Add all these
to the inventory, boys.
Tomorrow's bake sale
is gonna be a real treat.
- Who died and made you boss?
- Mitch Romero.
- Still no word from him?
That makes Romero missing,
not dead.
- In our line of work,
what's the difference?
This is my crew now.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[electricity sparking]
Fan out.
Whoever's here, put him down.
[metal clatters]
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
[gunfire]
- [screams]
- [yells]
♪ ♪
- Romero?
- [growls]
- The Monitor?
Where did you see him?
- We went in the Time Vault,
right after putting Chester
in the MAC.
The Crisis that he spoke about
last year,
it's the same one
in the plinth's newspaper.
And it's not coming in 2024.
It's coming December 10th...
2019.
- Are you sure about this?
- The jackass lied to you.
- Yeah, well,
we thought so, too, but...
Barry went to Earth-3,
and Jay Garrick helped him see
that it was true.
- How did he do that?
- Jay projected my mind
forward into the future.
- Okay.
And what did you see?
- I saw a giant wave
of anti-matter
sweeping over our Earth.
Vaporized all of Central City
and everybody in it.
Including you three.
- Great.
I'll go mark my calendar.
- We still have seven weeks
to make sure
none of this happens.
- Guys, Barry's right.
We've changed
the future before.
We can change it again.
- So what else did
our Asgardian cosplayer say?
[phone buzzes]
- That was pretty much it.
- It's Joe.
Needs me at CCPD,
but that can wait.
We...we need to get on this.
- Yeah, we should spend
every minute we have on this.
- No, guys, look,
what we should do
is take a well-deserved
time-out
and come back tomorrow
with clear heads.
- Okay.
If you think so.
- What now?
[ice crackling]
- I have to prepare them
for what's coming.
They have to be ready to go on
without me.
I guess I know
who I need to start with.
[door opens]
- Mom?
- Ralphy!
Ralph, oh, come here, baby.
Those stupid things.
- What happened?
- Last night,
10:00 p.m.,
the Avenue M pawn shop
was robbed at gunpoint.
The shop owner ID'd your mom
as the perp,
so we had to hold her.
Charges pending.
Mrs. Dibny,
this is Cecile Horton.
Ralph, good luck.
- Look, Cecile, yes, my mom
has an eventful past, but...
- Okay, robbery,
larceny, bribery...
- 14 allegations.
Not a single charge,
Miss Perfect Hemline.
- Thank you.
Um...
Ooh, it says here that
the owner of the pawn shop
personally identified you
as the robber.
- Okay, I was in the shop,
but not at 10:00.
I left around 5:00.
- Okay, so the robbery
was, like, five hours later,
so, Mom,
where were you around 10:00?
- Yeah.
- Is it really that important?
- Wait, yesterday
was the second Monday
of the month, so, Mom...
- Yeah.
I was at the Cleaner's Royale
on Oak.
- Okay, dry cleaners.
- It's a little bit
of a gambling front.
- Wow, Mom, the last time
that I was there was when...
when you and Marv Perez
were an item.
May he rest in peace.
- Oh.
- Well, Ralphy,
I really don't think
anyone there
is gonna help with my alibi.
- There's only one way
to find out.
- Road trip.
- Joe thinks
there's a meta-killer
that might be involved,
so if anybody asks,
you're my meta-human
consultant.
- Hey.
- The security guard
from a nearby building
heard the gunshots.
Said it sounded
like a war zone.
We haven't found
enough body parts
to determine
which crew did all this.
- He's covered in claw marks.
An animal did this.
Good to go?
- No, we're not.
This...this isn't animal blood.
- There's two more bodies,
or what's left of them,
and a lot more
of whatever that is.
- I see one arm, two arms.
Hm.
They're from the same person.
- I'll analyze this.
Hopefully, it'll lead us
to our killer.
- Thank you.
Can you analyze
what's going on with her?
- Yeah, I'm trying.
Frost!
Frost, what are you doing?
- There's no ammo in these.
- I know these guns.
They're charged
with dark matter.
They're all empty.
Who would kill for dark matter?
- A coward.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[ice crackling]
- Gotcha.
- What did you do?
- Frost, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be
following my lead, not...
- Getting a damn murderer
to confess?
- There's no evidence
he's involved.
Ease up.
Let him go.
[dramatic music]
- [gasps]
Cait?
You're Killer Frost?
- Actually, she's me,
Sad Coffee Guy.
- I am so sorry.
My name is Barry Allen.
I'm a forensic scientist
with CCPD.
We're investigating a series
of meta-related murders,
and Caitlin and Frost
are my meta-human consultants.
- Dr. Ramsey Rosso.
- What happened to your lab?
- Um, somebody broke in
while I was working late.
- This same substance
was at our crime scene.
I think the meta
that attacked you
is the person
we're looking for.
- The guy we're looking for
stole dark matter
from a stash house.
- [stammers] I did have a small
amount of dark matter here.
- Where'd you get it from?
- From an old colleague.
Ted Kord.
He was actually
willing to help me
with my research.
- Well, someone's out there
hunting for dark matter,
and he's willing to kill
to get it,
so whatever it is
you're working on...
- Look, Mr. Allen, my HLH
research is very important.
I lost my mother
to this disease.
Now, you mentioned you found
a similar substance,
both here
and at your crime scene.
- And, honestly, it's unlike
anything I've seen before.
- Well,
I am a blood specialist.
Perhaps I could be
of some assistance.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You are not actually gonna
trust this guy, are you?
'Cause I don't.
- I'm sorry.
Frost...
People are dying out there,
all right?
If Dr. Rosso can help us
in any way,
then, yeah, I'm open to it,
and you should be, too.
Would you help us, Dr. Rosso?
- Please, call me Ramsey.
- Morning, boss.
I have got the mother
of all scoops,
and thanks to your new intern,
it's gonna be
a CCC Media exclusive.
- Actually, you know,
I was hoping
that you would help me
with the new filing system.
- Alphabetical is great.
So there was a break-in
at McCulloch Tech last night.
Nothing was stolen,
but you'll never guess
who the perp is.
Get this.
Harrison Wells is alive.
- Where'd you get this?
- One of the McCulloch security
guards and I go way back.
- Nice work.
Um, I'll tell you what.
I will look into this,
and in the meantime,
I could use some quotes
on that mayor story.
The city council's
wondering how long
this new one's gonna last.
- Uh...I'd rather do this.
- Allegra, look,
I understand, okay?
I was an ambitious cub reporter
once, too.
You know, this is great work,
but I will take it
from here, okay?
- Fine.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Ralphy boy!
Long time no see.
Looking trim.
- Thanks, Tony.
- Deb.
- Howdy, Tone-Loc.
- I need a favor, Tony.
- Yeah, hi,
the Avenue M pawn shop
was robbed last night,
and the police think
that Debbie was responsible.
- We just need the footage
from your security camera
so we can prove that Mom
was here last night.
- Last night?
Yeah, Deb was here.
- Great.
- But I don't work
with the cops.
House policy.
Besides, you know I don't have
cameras in here, Deb.
- Potted plant.
- Ugly lamp on the bar.
- Smoke detectors
one, two, three.
- I like you, Ralphy.
Guess what?
You can have the footage.
- Oh, great.
- For 5,000 bucks.
- I'm sorry, what?
- Come back and see me
when you got the green.
Good to see you, Ralphy boy.
- [sighs]
That was a bust.
Oh, well.
- Wait, wait, wait,
hang on, hang on, hang on, Mom.
We might not got the green.
We can earn it.
- Right.
- Uh, excuse me, down here.
How exactly
are we going to earn it?
- Watch me, sweetie.
- [gasps]
- So can I talk to Cait?
Can she hear me right now?
- One, it's Frost.
I'm rebranding.
And two, sure.
She can if she wants to.
- Caitlin,
I want to explain myself.
About purchasing dark matter
from Kord Industries.
I hope you understand
if there's any chance
of saving more lives...
- You're gonna take it.
Right.
- I didn't want to go
behind your back,
but you refused to help me.
- Not listening anymore.
- And you never told me
that you were a meta.
I thought we were
closer than that, Cait.
- Huh. Guess you two aren't as
good of friends as you thought.
- Hey, guys, CCPD got back
a DNA match on our meta.
Mitch Romero.
Do you recognize the name?
- No.
- Mitch Romero is the head
of Central City's biggest
gun-running operation.
What?
I have friends in low places.
Romero must've been looking
for dark matter last night
when he went to the only
place he knew he'd find it.
His own stash.
- Why rob yourself and then
kill all your employees?
[phone buzzing]
Someone just broke
into Mercury Labs.
- A facility like that
would have
undisclosed amounts
of dark matter.
♪ ♪
- [growls]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[tires screeching,
car horns honking]
- What did you do?
Frost!
You just killed him!
We're supposed to cuff metas,
not throw them out windows.
- Calm down.
Romero is fine.
He just got up and walked away.
- You had no idea
that would happen
when you shot him
out the window.
You let your anger
get the better of you.
I thought you had
a handle on that.
Frost!
That cannot happen again.
- What, now you're telling me
how to feel?
- Look, I have seven
weeks to teach you
how to handle
this kind of situation.
You have to start listening.
- You have to stop being
such a crappy teacher.
- ♪ Money,
that's what I want ♪
- Make sure she loses.
- Tony's security footage
is on a USB drive
in his office.
Buy me as much time as you can.
- Okay, it's fine.
We got it. Go.
Okay.
[mysterious humming]
- [whispering]
He's nervous.
Go. Do it.
- Pair of tens.
- Can't bluff a bluffer.
- ♪ Money,
that's what I want ♪
♪ Hate to tell you, baby ♪
♪ ♪
- Boom.
- [exhales]
- You're kidding me.
- Debbie's hot tonight.
♪ ♪
[mysterious humming]
- Uh, Debbie.
Oh, Deb.
- ♪ Money,
that's what I want ♪
- All in.
♪ ♪
- Read 'em and weep.
- Ooh, tough break, Deb.
- I'm sorry, Mom.
We tried.
Let's get you home.
Good to see you, Tony.
Keep up the not-so-legal work.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Money,
that's what I want ♪
[knocking on door]
- Hey.
- Where's Killer Caitlin?
Out assaulting another suspect
without cause?
- She's taking a breather.
Did you find anything
helpful from the sample?
- More than I ever imagined.
- Yeah?
- Take a look at the pattern
of these gene transcriptions.
Romero's
dark matter-infused cells
are destroying
his normal cells.
He's more monster now than man.
The more dark matter
he absorbs,
the stronger he gets.
- According to this,
Romero's been dead
for over 24 hours.
That's why he can't die.
He already has.
Um, thank you for your help,
Dr. Rosso.
- Barry.
- Yeah?
- If I could observe
Romero's genes
interacting with dark matter,
I might be able to find a way
to counteract his condition.
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
Working with dark matter
can be really dangerous.
- Mr. Allen, I'm the top
hematologic oncologist
in the western hemisphere.
There's a creature out there
with a metastasized
blood chemistry
with the strength of ten men,
and he's getting stronger
by the minute.
Please, let me help.
- The satellite's facial
recognition spotted
our news Wells
less than an hour ago.
According to Miranda,
it's somewhere in this area.
[loud whirring]
[metal clangs]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Harrison Wells,
welcome to Earth-1.
My name is Cisco Ramon.
[gasps]
- Why are you following me?
- Oh, great.
Another angry one.
- To get your hands
on this priceless beauty?
Is that why?
Go ahead.
It gives nightmare
hallucinations
to all of its victims.
Would you like that?
- No!
[device beeping]
[beeping continues]
- So...
It's you.
- What?
- What's your name?
- Iris West-Allen.
- Well, Iris...
[shouts]
- And don't you forget it.
- I had that.
- And there you are.
- Wait. Oh, no, no, no.
Debbie, um...
that has you leaving at 9:30.
We need to know
where you were at 10:00,
the exact time of the robbery.
- Went out for air.
Oh, well. We tried.
- Hang on, there's another
camera angle outside.
- Ralphy, don't...
[computer chimes]
- Did you find her?
- I did.
With Marv Perez.
Marv's alive?
- Yeah.
- You said he died
in a car accident months ago.
You were with...
Marv when the pawn shop
was robbed.
- Ralphy, let me explain.
- If Marv is alive, what about
your other boyfriends?
How many of them are alive?
- [sighs]
Okay.
All of them.
- Ralph, hey, you know what?
It's okay.
This is...
this is a good thing
because Marv is Debbie's alibi,
so your mom
isn't gonna go to jail.
- Yeah, let's focus on that.
- Marv, Doug, Craig, Nick?
These guys, they...
They were like family to me.
How could you lie about that?
- I don't know why
you're so upset, sweetie.
You always moved on so quickly.
- I was being strong for you.
That doesn't mean it didn't
hurt like hell every damn time.
What really happened?
- What always happens.
You know, we were happy,
but I knew it wouldn't last,
so I ended it.
- What else did you lie about?
Did Dad really leave us?
- Yes.
That one is true.
Ralphy,
I didn't mean to hurt you.
- My name is Ralph.
You need to leave.
Get out.
Now.
♪ ♪
- I can't believe you and Cait
get to work here.
- How will all this help?
- Dark matter
is a miraculous thing.
With gene splicing, I can use
your dark matter samples
to negatively charge
Romero's blood.
That should weaken him enough
for you to make an arrest.
But, um...
I, uh...
I will need
a second centrifuge.
- Oh. Uh, there's
another one downstairs.
I'll get it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I had a feeling about you.
I hoped I was wrong.
But I know a desperate man
when I see one.
Put them back.
- No.
- I can make you.
- Go on, then.
Like you said,
I'm a desperate man.
I have nothing to lose.
- I thought you wanted
to save lives.
- HLH isn't just
my mother's disease.
First it killed her,
and now it's killing me.
- I still can't let you
take those.
Look at what it did
to Mitch Romero.
- I am marking a calendar
every day until I die,
waiting to fall off a cliff,
powerless to grab
onto anything or anyone.
I watched my mother
dive off that same cliff...
with a smile on her face.
She didn't even fight.
- I know what it's like
to lose your mother.
- I know you're angry.
- This isn't anger.
This is the pain
beneath my anger.
It takes courage
to fight death.
- Maybe it takes more
to accept it.
- My mum had that same look
on her face
when she was first diagnosed.
You're a dead man, too.
Aren't you, Barry?
So why don't you fight
for yourself?
- I'm marking my calendar with
the days I have left to live.
And I'm gonna spend them
saving as many people as I can.
- You're not a coward.
You're just naive.
- Mitch Romero's
still out there.
You said you wanted
to save lives.
Prove it.
Help me stop him.
Or get out of my lab.
♪ ♪
- Let's get to work.
You know,
I don't understand you, Barry.
You march towards death
without fear,
just like Mum.
Where is it
you get your strength?
- Probably the same place
she did.
People I love.
- I see.
Well, it must've been
incredibly hard to tell them.
♪ ♪
- You're a dead man, too.
Aren't you, Barry?
Well, it must've been
incredibly hard to tell them.
This isn't anger.
This is the pain
beneath my anger.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- According to
his techno fanny pack,
this belongs
to Dr. Harrison Nash Wells.
[both shouting]
- [groans]
- Easy.
We're not gonna hurt you.
- No.
Let's just try this again.
All right, I'm Iris West-Allen.
This is Cisco Ramon.
- Iris. Cisco.
- And we are friends
of the Council of Wells.
- Oh.
Those idiots.
Okay, now.
- Okay, listen,
I tased you once before,
and I'm happy to do it again,
so just...
- I let you do that.
Now hold still.
- Ah, ah, ah.
What are you doing
on our Earth?
- What am I doing?
I'm searching for an artifact
that just happens to contain
the same particles...
[device beeping]
I'm currently reading off you.
- What?
- Although...
- What...what part...
particles of what?
- Eternium.
- Eternium?
- Eternium is a Multiversal
element, all right?
Although the readings
were stronger in the alley.
- Listen, Indiana,
I don't know how they do things
on your Earth,
but this ain't
"Temple of Doom."
And what is Eternium
supposed to be, anyway?
Some kind of stolen mystical
element from the tiki gods
that you suddenly
have to return?
- Look, there's no such thing
as mystical mumbo jumbo
or gods.
What there are
are meta-humans, aliens,
and false gods worshiped
by simple-minded people
that find comfort in myths.
I dispel those myths.
You people are no help.
- Newsflash, Nash.
We've actually done
this dance before.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- It usually starts off rocky,
especially between you and me,
but eventually,
we bond,
and you learn to embrace
that sensitive side.
So why don't you just
drop the act,
and show me that warm,
compassionate, smart guy
that I know you to be.
- Let me ask you a question.
Do I look like
I want to hold hands?
Interesting.
- If you want your toys back,
you might just have to.
- [chuckles]
[rapid beeping]
[explosion]
- [coughing]
Well, I have to admit.
That was pretty cool.
- Yeah.
[knocking at window]
- Does she know
about the Multiverse?
- She kind of does now.
I'll handle it.
- I got the quotes
for the mayor story,
and I finished your filing.
Everything's alphabetical.
- Great.
- Also, I quit.
- Allegra, wait.
- You know why
I was even out here?
Enjoying the sun.
You don't get much of that
in Iron Heights.
I spent five years
locked up there,
and it taught me how
to tell the difference
between a snitch and a liar.
You're not a snitch.
- Allegra,
it's not what you think, okay?
- Forget it.
I've wasted enough time
behind bars.
I'm not wasting any more
working for a liar.
So be honest with me,
or I'm out of here.
- Okay.
You're right.
I was lying to you,
but I can't tell you the truth
about Harrison Wells,
not yet.
I do believe in you, Allegra.
I think you have
great instincts,
and I think you're gonna
make a great reporter.
That's why I took
a chance on you.
Now I'm asking you to take
a chance on me, okay?
Trust me.
When the time is right,
I will tell you everything.
I promise.
- We're journalists.
It's our job
to tell people the truth,
not control it,
even if it's tough to say,
or hard as hell to hear.
Just saying, boss.
See you in the morning.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Come to lecture me
some more?
- Look, I know you think
that you fight better
when you're angry,
so why don't you try
and hit a real target?
- ♪ I'm burning
all these secrets ♪
♪ I'm burning
♪ ♪
- Stop trying to hit me,
and hit me.
Or why don't you just
admit the truth
about what's hurting you?
♪ ♪
- I don't want to die
when I've just started living.
Okay?
I finally have the chance
to live a life,
and now this stupid Crisis
is gonna take it all away?
- I know it's not fair.
- Do you know
that Baskin-Robbins
has 31 different flavors?
I might die
before I get to figure out
which one is my favorite.
Or what my favorite song is,
or have my first
birthday party.
30 years of existing,
and I have never had one.
That really sucks.
- Frost.
There's always
gonna be a crisis,
or some meta-human
that's threatening
to take away the life
that you love.
Truth is, we're all living
on borrowed time.
- So, what, everybody feels
this crappy all the time?
That actually does
kind of make me feel better.
- It's why you can't let
the threat of losing tomorrow
keep you from making the most
of today.
- I want to spend
the rest of today
making sure that Mitch Romero
doesn't hurt anyone else.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What are you?
[metal creaking]
[grunting]
- [snarling]
- Stop!
Let me go.
[coughing]
[gasping]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Romero!
- [snarls]
- Ramsey, don't move.
You want this?
Yeah?
Yeah, come and get it.
Come on.
Come and get it.
Come on!
- [snarls]
Frost, Romero's heading
to the pipeline.
Hey, there.
Come on.
Yeah.
- [snarls]
- Come on.
- Oh, I miss all the fun.
- Next time we have to lock up
an undead meta,
he's all yours.
- Uh, Barry.
[pounding on glass]
Guess those meta-cuffs
would've been a waste of time.
- [moaning]
- Dark matter fuels his rage.
- All right, get back.
I'm gonna throw
a lightning bolt at him.
- No, no, no,
I have a better idea.
Get me all the dark matter
in Star Labs. Now.
- That's gonna
make him stronger.
- No, it's gonna
make him angry,
and I'm pretty sure
if we give it to him,
he'll overdose.
Trust me.
- [growls]
- Rage on this, Romero.
- [groaning]
- [gasps]
- You were right.
Anger really does
cloud judgment.
- No breaks, just bruising.
You got lucky.
- I must be off.
- Ramsey, hey, um...
I know we didn't
see eye to eye today,
but thanks for your help.
If you ever want to talk...
- Thanks, but I'm fine.
See you in the next life,
Barry.
- Thanks for coming, Mom.
- You kidding?
I'm just so grateful
you would see me.
Can I go first?
When your father left,
you came into my room
every morning for a week
with your hands on your hips,
and you said, "Where's Dad?"
And I did not know how to tell
you he wasn't coming back.
I was so worried
that you would think it
was my fault, or worse, yours.
And then when I did
tell you the truth,
you were so mad.
And so hurt.
You could not believe
that he left
without even saying good-bye.
So a couple years later when my
boyfriend Doug and I broke up,
and he left...
there was no way
I was gonna put you
through that pain again.
You two had become
so close, and...
- You lied to protect me.
But, Mom...
why did you break up
with all the others?
- They always wanted more
than I could give.
- You get scared.
I know because
I'm the same way...
Which is why
I made you something.
An addendum
for "The Book of Ralph."
- "22 steps
to being open
to the love of your life."
I'm open to love.
I'm just picky.
- Mom, give me a break.
Neither one of us have been
open to love since Dad left.
And, Mom,
by keeping that pain away...
we're also closing
ourselves off
from the joy
that love can bring.
- I don't think
I'm cut out for joy.
[laughs]
But I want that joy for you,
Ralph.
Love, happiness,
the whole kit and caboodle.
I want you to go find that.
And don't worry about me.
Okay, Ralph?
- Come on, Mom.
I'll always be your Ralphy.
♪ ♪
- I now have a new theory.
I believe I have found
an effective cure for HLH.
One that would eliminate my
need for dark matter entirely.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Analysis of Subject 1-A,
Mitch Romero's blood,
reveals that dark matter
infused
with healthy blood cells
to create an even stronger
biological substance.
This substance appears
to heal any and all weaknesses
in the human body...
including cells
affected by HLH.
I will now commence
human trials.
[groaning]
I need more.
[upbeat hip-hop music]
- ♪ Where my girls at? ♪
♪ Where my girls at? ♪
♪ Where my...
where my girls at? ♪
♪ Where my girls at? ♪
- What in tarnation?
- Hey, sweetie, we having
a little get-together?
- So Frost has never had
a birthday party,
so I offered to throw her one.
She picked the guest list.
[glass breaks]
- It's my party,
and I'll rage if I want to!
[all cheering]
♪ ♪
♪ I'm everything you want,
I know I got it ♪
♪ I'm everything
you want, I know I got it
♪ ♪
♪ I know I got it ♪
- Hey.
You're missing out
on all the fun.
Thanks for the party.
- [laughs]
- I'm thinking next year,
we go whitewater rafting.
- You should definitely
do that.
- You're not gonna be
at my birthday party next year,
are you?
Whenever you talk
about life after Crisis,
you never talk about yourself.
You're gonna do more than just
vanish in Crisis, aren't you?
- I don't know
how to tell them.
- Try with me by your side.
Barry, keeping this secret
all day hasn't felt right.
Let's tell them together.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Barry and I didn't share
everything that we learned
about Crisis, and...
you guys deserve
to know the truth.
- The Monitor
didn't just warn us
that Crisis was coming early.
There was something else
that he said had to happen.
When I projected
my mind forward,
I saw billions
of possible futures.
The only timeline
where everyone survives...
was the one where I died.
I have to die in Crisis.
None of you
can try and save me.
[device beeping]
[rapid beeping]
- [grunts]
It's here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.