[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- [echoing] Think
about Witness Protection.
- [echoing] Dad, we should do
this way more often.
- [echoing] Wherever I go,
part of me is with you.
- [echoing]
I don't think I can do this.
I have to go.
It's the only way
to keep our family safe.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hands up!
Don't move.
- [exhales sharply]
[groans]
- You scared the bejesus
out of me.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Oh!
- [inhales deeply]
It's Iris.
- [breathing heavily]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Wally warned me that something
was off with Iris.
And then Sunshine
attacked Frost.
I noticed that she was
being weird with you,
cold even.
[sighs]
I just didn't say anything.
- It's not your fault.
- Well, it feels like it.
Well, where are
the other duplicates now?
- Iris' copy is gone.
She...
It...
shattered into a million pieces
right in front of me.
I know it wasn't her,
but right before it happened,
she seemed so...
alive.
Almost like
she was really back.
I'm trying to have hope
that it's all gonna work out,
but I can't help feeling...
[solemn music]
Joe, what if I can't
save her this time?
- And I believe that you can,
but do you?
♪ ♪
- They're just gone?
- What does that even mean...
"Mirrorverse"?
Can we even get them back?
- Oh, my God.
We...we have to warn
David's husband.
- I've been living
with some copy of Kamilla
while the real one's
trapped somewhere?
- Eva said they're safe
for now.
- And you're taking her word
for it?
For all we know,
they're dead already.
- They're not, so just...
you don't even think
about that.
- We have to think about that.
What if creating
Kamilla's duplicate
actually killed
the real Kamilla?
Same thing with Singh,
same thing with Iris.
Hello?
- What do you want me to say?
- Anything, that we have a
plan, that we'll get them back.
- I don't have a plan, Cisco.
Eva can move anywhere
through any mirror
in the universe
in the blink of an eye.
She's faster than I am,
and somehow,
I'm supposed to stop her
and still hope to God that
Iris and everybody else
is still alive in a world
that we don't even understand?
- Hey, hey!
You're both right, okay?
You're both right.
But we cannot fall apart.
We need to work the problem,
not tear each other down.
So here's what I'm gonna do...
I am gonna call
David's husband,
and I am gonna see if he
has seen Singh's duplicate.
- I'll check
the Bentley Building.
Mirror-Iris and Kamilla
were alone there a lot.
Maybe they left
something behind.
- Good.
- You want company?
- Maybe you should find
something else to do.
- You can come with me.
I'm gonna see if I can
dig up any details
on this Eva McCulloch.
- If the Mirrorverse is
just another dimension,
there might be a way
to enter vibrationally.
Caitlin's still on the mend,
so I can't ask her for help.
I guess that means
I'm doing this one on my own.
- Barry, look, I understand
how you're feeling...
- Cecile, I know you're trying
to help me, and...
I appreciate it, but...
right now I'm gonna work
on the Artificial Speed Force.
I just...there's no point
in finding Eva
if I'm useless against her.
[ambient music]
♪ ♪
- I read Eva's secret files,
and now I know that there's
a mirror version of Kamilla,
which means that
the real Kamilla
must be in here somewhere.
[sighs]
I have to find her.
[eerie tones]
I can't think straight.
Eva calls it
"neural dissonance,"
the way that your mind
changes here.
I'm leaving this here for you
in case you find it,
but don't find me.
Barry...
No matter what worlds try
to keep us apart,
I will always be with you.
[ominous music]
[keys clack, computer beeping]
♪ ♪
- How dumb am I, huh?
- Yeah, that feeling's
going around.
- I've been working
side by side with duplicates
this whole time.
Some budding reporter I am.
Wait, does that mean I'm
in charge of "The Citizen"?
How the hell am I supposed to...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Godspeed.
- You're the one
that stopped the others.
I'm not impressed.
- What do you want?
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
I was looking for a reason
to test out this pulse cannon.
- Oh, this isn't over.
♪ ♪
- Didn't you say
all four Godspeeds
were locked up at Iron Heights?
- Those are just cybernetic
drones with modem-speak.
This one was talking.
And by the way,
do you not happen to have
protective protocols
for this place?
- Do not put this
on me. I am trying
to figure out a way
into the Mirrorverse.
What were you doing?
- I was saving our speedster.
- Oh, good for you.
You did something.
- Thank you.
Could I have a parade?
You don't seem to be
doing anything else.
- Stop! Just give it a...
- What?
- [sighs]
What are you thinking?
- I...
[dramatic music]
- Cisco, you're
the schmience-y guy.
You must have some kind
of a plan, right?
- [chuckles]
- Cisco, you still...
still with us, bud, or...
- Ralph, please, I'm trying to
get our friends back right now.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Okay, okay.
Allegra, you said
Godspeed's lightning
caused some sort of blast.
- Yeah, he was like a frickin'
lightning storm in the room,
but it was his thunder
that did the damage.
- Not thunder...vibrations.
- Makes sense.
If you go fast enough,
you create a sonic boom.
Velocity transmutes
into vibrations in the air,
only this Godspeed
figured out a way...
[key clack, computer beeping]
To reverse those vibrations
and use them to extract speed
from a speedster.
- Okay, so he's power hungry.
How do we stop him?
- Well, we'd need a really,
really deep understanding
of vibrational sonics.
- Great.
Do we have that?
- Not really, no.
- I know who could help us.
Hartley.
Hartley Rathaway.
- Who's Hartley Rathaway?
- He is an expert
in psychoacoustics
and sonic vibrations.
He used to work
for S.T.A.R. Labs.
Also, a jerk
who hates us so much
he tried to julienne
your insides.
- It turns out that
he hates The Flash
even more post-Crisis,
only we don't really know why.
- Correction...I know why.
My Crisis research dug up
the answer to that.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- Henchmen?
No, it was only me and Hartley.
- Not in this timeline.
Pied Piper's Band of Merry Men
tried to flank you
while you were distracted
playing musical cars.
Yeah, you clocked them,
but when one of them tried
to shoot at you,
you countered
with a lightning bolt.
That lightning collided with
the weapon's blast, and...
♪ ♪
Turns out, that was
Hartley's right-hand man...
Roderick Smith.
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
- It's Frost.
Sorry, guys, I got to...
I got to check on this.
- Roderick Smith is being held
in an energy containment unit
in Mercury Labs.
Apparently, it's the only thing
that's keeping him
from completely disintegrating.
- I guess that's a no
to Pied Piper's help.
- Well, he did
almost kill us, so...
- Let's not bicker
over who killed who.
We can fix this.
We just make his right-hand man
right again,
this Roderick fellow,
and then maybe Hartley will
agree to a little quid pro quo.
I have a theory.
♪ ♪
- I got your text.
Are you okay?
Is the wound getting worse?
- Ralph, I'm fine.
As fine as anyone with
a chronic light bullet avulsion
can be in their chest, but...
This patch is
keeping me stable for now.
- Then what's the emergency?
- Payback.
I just wanted to say thank you
for everything you've done
for me this year...
for taking me to an art show
and teaching me how to get
in touch with emotions
I didn't even know I had.
- Hey, that's what
life coaches are for.
- Well, I know I've
still got a long way to go,
but I'm leaving soon,
so we might not be able
to finish this.
- You getting better
is our number-one priority.
And your mom is the expert
on all things ice,
so she'll patch up
that wound of yours,
and then we can pick up
where we left off.
- I could be gone
for a long time.
- Okay.
[scoffs]
But you are coming back, right?
- Look, Ralph, forget it.
I-I just...I wanted to say
good-bye to an old friend.
- Look...
[chuckles]
Friends say "so long"
or...or "until we meet again."
They...they don't
really say good-bye.
So why don't you just tell me
what's really bothering you?
- I'm fine.
Stop trying to smell
a mystery or whatever.
- Too late.
The Tannhauser tech...
it's the only stuff
that can fix you,
but you don't really
want to go, do you?
- Just drop it.
- It's not the tech, is it?
It's the person behind it.
Frost, why don't
you want to see Carla?
- Because she's
not my mom, okay?
She's Caity's.
- You don't really mean that.
- Yeah, I do.
Carla doesn't know me.
After all these years,
it's just been her and Caity.
- Hey, you're
her daughter, too.
- I am the cold, dark part
of her daughter
that she tolerates.
- If that were even true,
why would I be sitting here
worried about you?
- 'Cause you're
a good guy, Ralph.
- And you're an equal member
of Team Flash,
just like Caitlin.
And you are just as important.
And if you can't see that
for yourself...
[dramatic music]
Then maybe you're right.
Maybe you do have
a long way to go.
♪ ♪
- Hello, Flash.
I heard you coming
from a mile away.
- Hartley, I know
what happened now.
And I'm sorry.
- [panting]
- Is something wrong
with your speed?
- Look, I'm...
I'm trying to make things
right with you.
- Now you're sorry?
- I think I can help Roderick.
- What do you know
about Roderick?
- I know his condition's
my fault,
but I think I can fix it
if you'll give me the chance.
- And?
- And if you're willing,
I could use your help.
- Hmm, here we go.
- There's a new speedster.
He's a threat
to the whole city, Hartley.
He's using sound waves.
You're the only person we know
that can stop him.
Lives...
- [chuckles] I don't care.
- I swear
I want to help Roderick.
- Well, you can't.
- Let me try.
- I said you can't help him.
Don't you get it?
No one can.
I thought I could stabilize
his molecules
with my sonics, but...
- [grunting, screams]
- [grunting]
- [screams]
- I wasn't strong enough.
- So you sent him
to Mercury Labs.
We think we can help him.
Let us show you.
- Who is this "we" and "us"?
[dramatic music]
Harrison Wells.
- Nash Wells, actually.
Harrison Wells
is my doppelganger.
- Your doppelganger?
- How to explain?
Okay, so there was this big
event we call the Crisis, and...
- He's his twin.
- He's my twin.
- Huh, twice blessed.
- We think that there
may actually be a way
to help Roderick.
I've seen this kind of
molecular disembodiment before,
and...all right, bear with me...
I think that if we combine
concentrated light energy
with an inert gas
with high thermal conductivity,
it may actually slow down
Roderick's molecules
and get him his body back.
- So basically combine light
with helium.
I'm the smartest guy
in the room...I get it.
[sighs]
Fine.
You fix Roderick,
and maybe I'll help you.
♪ ♪
- Kamilla?
Wait, what are you doing?
It's me, Iris.
- You're the one
who sent me here.
- No, whoever she was,
that was not me.
I swear.
- Then tell me something
only the real Iris would know.
- Cisco is the love
of your life.
[stammers]
And you knew it
from the moment you met him...
when you were bartending
at the Liquid Kitty.
He is the most brilliant man
that you know,
and he always makes you laugh.
♪ ♪
You are the only person allowed
to wear his Chewbacca T-shirt,
the one that his parents gave
him when he was 14 years old.
- [sighs]
It's you.
Thank God.
After you...
or whoever looked like you...
shot me with that mirror gun,
I just woke up here
totally alone.
- You never saw Eva?
Eva McCulloch...Carver's wife.
- She's alive?
She's...she's here?
- She's the meta
behind all of this,
and...and now she's escaped
into our world.
- Then we have to get back.
I gathered all the items that
the mirror gun sent here.
I've been analyzing them
for clues,
but the data keeps
getting all wonky
when I try to see the screen.
♪ ♪
- [panting]
- Hey, are you okay?
- No.
No, I'm not.
But you are.
[breathing heavily]
The neural dissonance
hasn't affected you yet.
It's this condition
that affects our minds
in this, uh...
this Mirrorverse.
- That explains the screens.
When I look at them too long,
I get a headache.
- Yeah, that's how
it started for me, too,
with Eva's computers.
Everything was broken
and...and fractured, but...
now...now I can read them.
- [echoing] You can help us
get out of here.
- Ah, you know, I-I can't.
- Shh. The truth hurts.
The truth hurts.
- We...we...we shouldn't be here.
We should not be here.
I should not be here.
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
Not much has changed.
Ugh, S.T.A.R. Labs...
still keeping mediocre
engineers around, I see.
- Do we have to work
with this douchebag?
- Look, I've heard that
you two hate each other,
but let's just focus.
- A few months ago,
I theorized there might be
a mechanical way
to open a breach
to an alternate dimension.
- Looks like an engine for
focusing subatomic vibrations,
or as you would say, "vibes."
Oh, please.
I figured that out ages ago.
The hair?
Dead giveaway, Ramon.
You too, Flash.
There's only three facilities
in the state
that could build a suit with
that much bleeding-edge tech.
But only one of them had
someone brilliant enough
to build it.
- Thanks.
- Harrison Wells.
- There it is.
- What I don't get
is why you need a machine
when you could just
use your damn vibes.
Unless you can't vibe anymore.
Ooh, ouch.
You lost your meta-mojo.
Oh, well, you could try
being a barista maybe.
- I gave up my powers
by choice.
You know, I'm making this
so that I can save
the person I love the most.
But I wouldn't expect you
to understand that, Hartley.
The person you love the most
is yourself.
Come find me when
you're ready to work.
[cell phone vibrates]
- [sighs]
Cecile just got Roderick back
from Mercury Labs.
He's here.
♪ ♪
- Here's what I need from you.
I need you to direct
a concentrated UV blast
into the reception conduit.
Now, this containment unit...
I am going to release helium
into it,
and when those
two things collide, pop.
It should lock Roderick's
molecules back into human form.
Ready?
We'll go on three.
One...two...
three.
♪ ♪
It's working.
- [groans]
- No, no, wait. Stop.
- [groaning]
- Wells, enough.
- [screams]
- Stop, you're hurting him!
- Nash.
[air hissing]
♪ ♪
Hartley, I'm sorry,
but we can try...
- I was stupid
for trusting you.
Don't ask me
for anything, ever.
My world is over.
I hope yours burns.
♪ ♪
- Give me your velocity,
or your city pays.
You have one hour.
- [grunts]
- You're not fast enough
to stop me.
None of you are.
Death will rain down
on your city, Flash,
unless you give me what I want.
Choose wisely.
♪ ♪
[soft music]
- I don't think these equations
are gonna help fix
Roderick that much.
Plus, we simply need
a better bonding agent.
- You do that.
I'm working on the Artificial
Speed Force right now.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Nash!
Hey, Nash, what the hell?
I've been working
on these all day.
- You're wasting time.
Why?
You don't have to tell me.
We don't know each other.
You could talk
to Joe and Iris.
But they're not here.
Whose fault is that?
- It's mine, all right?
Is that what you want me
to say?
♪ ♪
I'm supposed to lead this team.
Now, I-I don't even know
what to tell them.
- When I lost Maya...
every day since then,
I wanted to say,
"Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
It was my fault."
But she's gone.
When I was Pariah
and I watched my mistake
burn down the Multiverse,
I wanted to tell those people,
"I'm sorry,"
but they were gone,
and it was over.
And this is not over for you.
You can find your way
out of this.
All you have to do
is trust yourself.
- How am I supposed to do that?
I just lived with an
impostor for five weeks.
- You forgive yourself.
You showed me that.
Now it's time for you
to do it for you.
And you know what?
If you can't...
do it for Iris.
- I just miss her so much.
Without her here,
it feels like...
♪ ♪
I know why Hartley's world
is over.
♪ ♪
Thank you, Nash.
- [sighs]
[exhales deeply]
- Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, hey.
Look, I know you're hurting.
I do.
But I was with Kamilla
when Bloodwork's
monsters attacked,
and...and you got to trust me
that no matter where she is,
your girl knows how
to take care of herself.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
I know. It's just...
[sighs]
When Kamilla's around,
I want to show her I'm strong.
I want to believe I'm making
the right decisions.
She gives me the confidence
I need, but she's...
[sighs]
She's not here.
And all I can think about
is the hero I used to be.
He was just full of life,
and he wasn't afraid
to do the impossible.
He was...
[sighs]
He was Vibe, you know?
He had all the answers.
Sometimes he was the answer.
If Kamilla's not here
and Vibe is gone...
what if...
- What if you don't have
all the answers
and you're making
the wrong decisions?
Cisco, Kamilla
did not fall in love
with your powers.
She fell in love with you...
you...
and that big,
beautiful brain of yours.
Boo-hoo, Cisco Ramon
isn't Vibe anymore.
You know what he is?
He is a damn
brilliant engineer
who has never backed down from
doing the impossible before.
♪ ♪
You gonna start now?
- No, ma'am.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- You okay?
- I let Eva manipulate me
all this time,
and now the neural dissonance
is getting worse.
How did I let that happen?
My skill as a reporter is
being able to see the truth,
but Eva proved to me that
I can't trust my instincts
or...myself.
- You weren't the only one
she tricked.
Your duplicate tricked me,
everyone...even Barry.
Don't beat yourself up
for not being perfect.
Of course Eva would want you
to see your strength
as a weakness.
That's how she's
kept you trapped.
But if you want to escape,
you have
to trust yourself again.
I do.
So...
where do we start?
- There is one other duplicate
that Eva created...Chief Singh.
We should find him.
If we're gonna go home,
we're all going home...
together.
- [sighs]
[sniffles]
Get out.
- I know why you're so upset.
- You don't know anything
about me.
- I know what it's like
to be responsible
for losing the person I love.
Roderick...
he's not just
another hired gun, is he?
- He's my boyfriend...
[sniffles]
The love of my life.
I put him in the line of fire
when I fought you,
meaning that what happened
to him is my fault.
- You're not the only one
to blame.
I threw the lightning,
remember?
- I gave him the weapon
that made you defend yourself.
- [sighs]
- And then when
I couldn't help him...
- You got him
the help he needed.
- He was better off
at Mercury Labs than with me.
I was useless.
[sighs]
- Someone just
reminded me that...
we're no good to the people
that we love
if we can't find the strength
to move forward
and forgive ourselves.
- Thanks, Oprah.
- Hey, we got a big problem
at Iron Heights.
- You can stay here.
Or you can be the person that
Roderick fell in love with.
It's your call.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- The satellites just picked up
a massive energy surge
in the Meta-Wing.
[alarm wailing]
- It's gone.
Wait, get a video feed.
What happened in there?
- I'm trying.
Oh, crap.
- Every Godspeed
we caught till now...
he took all their speed.
♪ ♪
- Record this.
You have one minute, Flash.
After that, someone dies
every 60 seconds until
you surrender what's mine.
- I have to stop him.
- Wait, wait, Barry.
- What?
- Look, I know
you want to do this,
but you don't have
a lot of speed, okay?
We need to call CCPD,
or A.R.G.U.S., anyone who can...
- Godspeed is
my responsibility.
I have to face him.
- Barry, you don't...
- I have enough speed left
to do this.
Even if I don't, I have to try.
♪ ♪
I have to try.
- Someone dies
every 60 seconds
until you surrender
what's mine.
- Godspeed is
my responsibility.
I have to face him.
I have to try.
I have enough speed left
to do this.
- Someone dies. Someone dies.
- I have to try.
I have to try.
I have to try. I have to try.
- Time's up, Flash.
Have you come
to give me what's mine?
- You have to catch me first.
♪ ♪
- He's running at Mach 5.
He's moving faster than you.
- But I know this city
better than him.
♪ ♪
- Barry!
- You are pathetic.
You don't deserve
the speed you were given.
We do!
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
I didn't think you were coming.
- I didn't save you
so we could chat.
- That's your backup?
It won't help.
- Hartley, I can't
stop Godspeed.
He's too powerful.
- God, how thick are you?
Roderick got hurt when
the lightning you threw
collided with the vibrational
force of his weapon.
The result was
a thermogenic blast
capable of rendering him
unstable at a molecular level.
Just duplicate that force...
- And Godspeed's toast.
- Bingo bango.
- Flash!
Now you'll feel
the real power of speed!
♪ ♪
- You ready?
- Let's do it.
- Where is he going?
Barry, you're going
the wrong way.
- Wait for it.
♪ ♪
- Now, Flash!
- They crossed streams.
- Crossed streams.
♪ ♪
- Hartley, thanks for coming
after me.
- Yeah, don't mention it.
You won another battle
against some speed freak,
and I lost everything.
- I promise we'll figure
something out.
- Okay, I haven't seen
that one before.
- Is that Godspeed's blood?
♪ ♪
- Satellite readings indicate
it could be some kind of
biogenic electrolyte secretion.
- It's charged sound.
- Charged sound.
- Oh, boys...
I do believe we found
the solution we're looking for.
♪ ♪
- How does it work?
- Normal sound waves need
to have a transmission medium
to move through, but
charged sound builds its own.
- Normal sound can temporarily
reattach molecular bonds.
Charged sound
can permanently attach them.
It's like
a permanent bonding agent.
- Hartley, this will
stabilize Roderick.
- If you hurt him,
I'll hurt you.
- Ready?
- Ready.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply]
Hartley.
- I'm here.
- [chuckles]
- I thought I lost you.
- Come on, you know I'm harder
to get rid of than that.
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
So, uh, what happened?
Last thing I remember,
we were at the dam,
and The Flash,
he, um...
- He helped bring you back.
- We'll give you guys
some space.
♪ ♪
- I'm glad we reunited
the happy couple,
but I have to say
I am super relieved
to finally get rid of Godspeed.
And this one talks,
so now we know
we got the real August Heart
behind bars.
- That's not the real Godspeed.
Once he was placed
in a meta-dampening cell,
I questioned him as The Flash,
and all he could say was,
"The one who sent me
wants infinite velocity."
- When you were fighting
Godspeed, he said,
"We deserve your speed."
- Who's "we"?
- Does "we" include
the one who sent him?
- He couldn't tell me.
- Because he stopped talking.
- And started chirping
like a broken modem...
just like the rest of them.
[scraping]
- So...
I, uh, came to apologize.
- So you broke in?
My front door is locked.
- I may have, uh, slipped
under the doorframe,
uh, literally.
So I guess I actually have
two things to apologize for.
Um, listen...
I shouldn't
have been so harsh.
- It's okay.
You were right.
I have a long way to go.
- No, you don't.
- A "Dib-ploma"?
- Congratulations on graduating
life-coach school.
- Ralph, this is ridiculous.
- You know what's ridiculous?
You thinking that you're
not as important as Caitlin.
And being intimidated by
a parent, that...that's normal.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Frost, I was ten
when my dad walked out
on Mom and me.
You don't think
a day goes by where I'm not...
absolutely terrified
that he's gonna show up
at my front door?
- He walked out on you guys.
He's a jerk.
- Yeah.
And a part of me
still wants to see him.
- I guess I'm afraid Carla
might actually want to get
to know me, and then...
she'll see me
for who I really am.
- That is
the ironic part to me.
'Cause, Frosty, you are
one awesome human being.
You were just afraid that Carla
was gonna reject you,
so you rejected her first.
♪ ♪
- Not anymore.
[sighs]
- And that is why
you're ready to graduate.
Damn, I really am
one hell of a life coach.
- Yeah, you are.
- I don't know
how to thank you.
I...we lost everything
when we lost each other...
even hope.
Thank you for not giving up.
You gave us back us.
I owe you.
We both do.
- Good luck.
Just maybe stay out
of diamond stores for a while.
- [inhales sharply]
No promises.
Hey, will you give us
a second?
- Yeah.
- Okay, look, um...
[chuckles]
You know I'm not exactly
the "let's hug it out" type,
so I'll just say this...
- [chuckles]
- You gave me my world back.
You'll get
your world back, too.
But you have to do more
than just forgive yourself.
You have to believe
that your world can change.
That's the part I'd forgotten.
Thanks for reminding me.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
We've all lost
so much this year...
our power, our love,
our family.
At times, it's even felt like
there's nothing left to lose,
like everything that matters
has already been taken
and our lives are empty...
hollow inside.
♪ ♪
Some things can't be taken.
Look around this room.
We still have our faith
in each other
and our will to fight
for those we love.
This is what we'll never lose.
[triumphant music]
Eva McCulloch
has never faced us head-on.
And that's about to change.
We're gonna find her...
beat her...
and get back everyone.
- Amen to that.
- You just tell me
where to stretch.
- And blast.
- Sounds violent.
I'm in.
♪ ♪
- I have an idea...
a way to get our people
out of the Mirrorverse.
We need a lossless,
self-sustaining source
of perpetual energy.
- Sounds like you're talking
about the holy grail
of science...
a perpetual-motion machine.
- That's right.
- [scoffs]
- Hartley had some ideas.
I think
we can actually build one.
We're just missing
one component,
and thanks to my travels,
I know exactly
where to find it...
Atlantis.
- Finally, Crisis pays off
in a good way for once.
- I know time is crucial,
but don't worry.
I'll hurry back.
- Can I come?
- Actually, if you don't mind,
I'd like for you to stay.
Team Flash needs as many hands
on deck as possible.
♪ ♪
Now let's get to work.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[door whirring]
- [inhales sharply]
♪ ♪
I'm coming for you, Joseph.
- Greg, move your head.