- Previously on "The Flash"...
- If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
are in the future,
then that's where
I need to go.
- You're from before
she dies, aren't you?
- You trapped Savitar
in the Speed Force.
Just tell me how you did it.
- I had help.
Her name's Tracy Brown.
She made the Speed Force
trap for me.
- You're telling me my ideas
about the Speed Force...
I'm right?
- In the future.
We need you to build
this trap now.
[glass shattering]
- Caitlin's after Tracy.
That means she's
working with Savitar.
- Did you talk to Cecile?
- Told her everything.
Told her I love her.
I told her that
you're The Flash.
- Like I told you
from the beginning...
I am the future Flash.
[dark music]
It's like looking in a mirror.
Well... not quite.
- You're not so scary
without your armor.
- What can I say?
I outgrew red.
- I know what you are.
You're a time remnant.
- A temporal duplicate.
Created when you
run back in time
and meet yourself.
You brought a remnant
to life last year
to defeat Zoom.
Your duplicate died,
saving the multiverse,
and you continued your
happy little life.
And it would've stayed that way,
but then you decided
to play God.
You created Flashpoint
and changed everything.
- I went to the future.
My future self told me that
he created time remnants
to stop you.
But you slaughtered them all.
- All but one.
Me.
I lived.
But a funny thing happened
when I did.
You. Joe.
Wally, Cisco.
You all shunned me because I
wasn't the true Barry Allen.
I was an aberration.
A disposable hero.
Future you failed
to mention that, didn't he?
- How did you become Savitar?
- I was broken
and alone.
I wanted the pain to end.
And that's when I realized
the truth, Barry.
God feels no pain.
All I had to do
was become one.
And I only need
two more things:
for Iris to die
so that you are driven
so far into the dark
that I can be born.
- And the other?
- It may sound ironic
given who I'm talking to,
but I'll keep that one
to myself.
- What happens if
I kill myself?
If I die, then you'll
never be created.
- Cause and effect's
a tricky thing.
Didn't work so well
for Eddie, did it?
Shot himself in the chest...
Thawne's still kicking around.
See, that's the thing
about time travel, Barry.
The more you do it, the less
the rules apply to you.
- But us having this
conversation now...
we're changing the future.
- Are we?
My ascendancy is nearing.
When I have control
of all of time,
it will be you who is
abandoned and forgotten.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You're gonna die right here!
- I forgot to tell you...
my suit's cooler than yours.
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
- It's impossible.
- I don't understand.
How could Savitar be you?
- He's not me. Not really.
- He's all the worst
parts of you.
It's like in "Star Trek"
when the transporter
splits Kirk into
good Kirk and bad Kirk.
Please tell me you at least
have "Star Trek" on your Earth.
- "Voyager."
- I hate spinoffs.
- That explains why Caitlin
was willing to follow him.
He has a face that she trusts.
- Half of one anyway.
- So when the Legends found
that message in the Waverider
from old you saying
"Don't trust Barry Allen,"
it was talking about
Savitar Barry Allen.
[chuckles] It's all
coming together...
in the worst way.
- You said you made Savitar?
How?
- Peep this.
Four years from now,
future Flash creates...
a time remnant
to fight Savitar.
But Savitar lets
that remnant live
so thatit can later
become Savitar.
So once Savitar is imprisoned
in the Speed Force,
this remnant starts
to go crazy.
And he goes back in time
to the past
and becomes Savitar.
- Creating the lie that
he was the first speedster,
spreading the myth
and recruiting acolytes
throughout the ages.
- That doesn't make any sense.
Which came first, Savitar
or the time remnant?
- It's a closed loop.
No beginning, no end.
It's just one endless cycle.
- Classic chicken and the egg
scenario, I think, eh?
- A time remnant, it's, um...
it's like a duplicate
of you, right?
So it has your feelings,
your memories.
So why would it
want to hurt us?
Why would he want to kill Iris?
- H.R., how's Tracy coming
with the Speed Force trap?
- Good, yeah, good. Slow.
- Get her to speed up,
all right?
- I'll do that now.
Can do.
- If Savitar is a version
of Barry from the future
and he remembers everything
that Barry does,
how are we ever going to come up
with a plan to stop him?
- What was he like?
- Broken.
- You know... [sighs]
All this time I thought
that Savitar is this...
monster.
It's hard to picture
what might happen,
and it being you that...
I...I know it's not you.
I'm...
- Part of him is.
He said it was like looking
in a mirror, and he was right.
But not just the way
that he looked.
It was...
it was his eyes.
The pain that
was inside them.
I've seen that in myself.
When I think about how my
parents died so violently...
Sometimes I want to repay that
violence with more violence.
I want to make someone else
hurt as much as I do.
- But you don't ever do that.
You're not him.
You're a good person.
- But it's in there, you know.
That's in me.
That power, that pain,
that's where Savitar comes from.
From loss.
From losing you.
- You're not going to lose me.
Do you hear me?
We are going to stop Savitar.
- [sighs deeply]
- You are not alone. He is.
And he is not a god.
- Jay told me that
we're not gods.
He was wrong.
We could be.
Any speedster, and it
wouldn't take much.
When the love that we
feel in our hearts
is drowned in anger...
when the bad memories
outweigh the good ones.
What am I going to
have to become to stop him?
- Hey! Oh, bad time?
- No, man, what's up?
- I just came up with
the best idea ever.
Either that or it's
the worst idea ever.
But...
- It's an idea.
- It's an idea!
- You want to give me a perm?
- It's not for your hair,
Steel Magnolia.
This is for your brain, okay?
I want to stop you from
making new memories.
- What are you talking about?
- Savitar knows everything
we're gonna do
because he remembers doing it.
He's a future Barry.
So what if Barry can't
remember what we're doing now?
- You want to mess
with his brain?
- Just a little bit.
It's a minimal procedure.
It'll still be the same Barry
you know and love,
except he just won't be able
to retain new information.
- There's two types
of memory, Allen.
Short-term and long-term.
Long-term is where you...
- Okay, Julian, just stop.
This is my presentation;
I'm the expert here.
This is the part of your brain
that retains new information
before sending it to the cortex
to be stored forever.
So what if we block that chain
with a magnetic disruption?
- So Savitar won't
be able to remember
whatever strategy we
come up with to defeat him.
- Which means he can't be
two steps ahead of us anymore.
- With any luck, we'll actually
put him one step behind.
- Beautiful.
Cause and effect.
- Barry, what do you think?
- Let's do it.
- Wait, wasn't Caitlin the
expert on brains around here?
- She was.
But this is something we'll
have to do without her.
- I trust you.
- You won't feel a thing.
- Okay, let's get this
show on the road.
The disrupter is attached
to your hippocampus.
So it's ready.
- Okay, ready for zapping.
- Can we not call it "zapping"?
- Ready to activate.
In three...
two...
one.
- Sweet dreams,
my beautiful boy.
- Way to go, slugger.
- Run, Barry, run!
- I have watched you be in love
with Iris...
- Maybe we were meant
to be together.
- Okay, that should do it.
- All right.
Right. [clears throat]
How do you feel?
- I feel fine.
- You see? He feels fine.
[nervous laughter]
- Barry...
- Barry?
- Barry.
- Who's Barry?
- Not fine.
- Um, who are all of you?
- What's going on?
Seriously, who are you guys?
- Okay, Barry, stay calm.
- Who's Barry?
- Cisco!
- Slight miscalculation.
- Slight wouldn't be
a word I'd use.
- Where the hell am I?
Is this a dentist office?
- No, no. This is S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Labs? A laboratory?
St...a laboratory?
What are you?
Are you guys
experimenting on me?
- No one is ex...
well, yes, technically, yes.
But...but it was consensual.
- You were?
- Yes.
- You... Why can't I
remember anything?
Why can't I remember my name?
- Your name is Barry.
- My name's not Barry.
I don't know what my name is,
but my name's...
"Bartholomew Henry Allen."
That's not a good name.
- Look, Barry...
- Are you sure I don't
go by "Bart"?
Can..."Bart" feels more
natural to me.
Can we go with Bart?
- Bart's kinda cool.
- Okay.
- Wally!
- Okay, hey.
Let's just get you
back in the chair.
- No! No, no, no.
I'm not...I'm not
getting in the chair.
No, how do I know you
didn't kidnap me here
to do some weird
brain surgery on me?
Or maybe you're like
those criminals
who trick people
into hotel rooms
so they can steal
their kidneys.
[gasps] Do I still
have my kidneys?
- We don't want your kidneys.
- Okay, Barry, look
at these photographs.
We're your friends.
Your family.
We just want to help you, okay?
- That's a nice ring.
Who's the lucky guy?
- You are, Barry.
Look, I know
you're scared, okay?
You can trust us.
- Cisco.
A minute.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm gonna be right back,
okay?
Wally, stay with him, okay?
- Me?
- So how do we know each other?
- Oh, I'm your brother.
- There is no sign of any
permanent structural damage.
- Then why can't
he remember anything?
- Julian?
- He appears to be suffering
from some sort
of psychogenic
retrograde amnesia.
- Amnesia.
- What if we didn't
account for Barry's
increase neural velocity
due to his super speed?
- Wait, do we think
he knows he's The Flash?
That he has super speed?
- Hey, Barry. Catch.
- Sorry.
- Oh, my Lord.
- He's, like, god-awful.
- He's pathetic.
- Can't we flip a switch...
undo it?
- Okay, we are not flipping
any more switches
until we figure this thing out.
[cell phone vibrates]
- It's Cecile.
Hey, babe.
An emergency?
All right, bye.
Okay, Cecile needs Barry
at CCPD, like, right now.
She says it's urgent.
- He can't possibly go out
in that condition.
- Okay, um, my dad and I
will take Barry to Cecile.
You and Cisco figure out a way
to get Barry's memory back.
And fast.
Yeah?
- Okay.
- You don't want to work?
Well then, I don't need you!
- Um, am I to infer that, uh,
you've hit a little speed bump
in your quest to build a device
to trap Savitar
in the Speed Force? The...
- Accelerated matter
microgenerator projectile.
No, I know. It doesn't exactly
roll off the tongue.
- No, it doesn't. How about...
we call this
fancy device of yours...
- You know, you probably
shouldn't...
- Call it the...
- Speed Force Cannon.
- Speed Force Bazooka.
- Speed Force Gun.
[together] Speed Force Bazooka.
- Is better, yeah.
- But if the Speed Force Bazooka
doesn't start working soon,
we're gonna have to start
calling it
the Speed Force Epic Fail.
- Why? What's the problem?
- The accelerometer.
It sucks a hell of a lot
of air watts, which...
- Stop talking science!
You need to take a step back
from the Speed Force Bazooka.
- There's not time.
- There's always time!
Because sometimes,
to move forward,
you have to take a step back.
Step... back.
You see? Yes.
Shake a little...[mumbling]
Shake out those shoulders.
I feel like...oh, oh, my gosh.
The tension in your shoulders...
Think of something
that calms you.
- Coffee.
- Oh, yes.
- But not just any coffee.
Piping hot...
- Yep.
- Indonesian dark roast with...
[together] Raspberry
and coriander...
- I've never met another person
who uses copious amounts
of caffeine to chill out.
- I've never met
another person either.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
- I...
I, I, I'm relaxed.
Are you relaxed?
- Mm-hmm.
- You, uh...
and I'll... okay.
I mean... okay.
- Yeah.
Cecile:
Good morning, people.
- Hi. I'm Barry Allen.
You can call me Bart.
- O...kay.
- So you said there
was an emergency.
Where's the fire?
- Ah, it's funny you should
put it like that.
Lucious Coolidge.
- Who?
- Heat Monger.
- The worst arsonist
Central City's seen
since Mick Rory
went off the grid.
That is, until Flash here
stopped him.
- What's Flash?
- Uh, ah, so what...
what is the problem?
- Judge Hankerson.
He's got an opening
in his docket,
so he moved Coolidge's
probable cause hearing
up to this afternoon.
Barry was the CSI on the case.
So I need him to testify
in order to hold Coolidge
over for trial.
- Uh, yeah, no.
Barry can't do that.
- Why not?
- Uh...
- What do you mean
he has amnesia?
- Bar, what's her name?
- Um... Felicia?
- Oh, my God.
Is this...is this like a...
like a Flash thing?
Was he battling a super villain
who used his evil powers
to steal Barry's memory?
- [laughs]
- Um, no, we sort of
accidentally did this
to him ourselves.
- Why?
- That doesn't matter.
What does matter
is you stalling that judge.
Barry is in no condition
to testify in court.
- Joe, if Barry can't testify,
Coolidge walks.
And then God help us all.
- Okay. We'll figure
out something.
- Please do.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Oh. Yeah.
You too... Bart.
- I got some friends
down at the courthouse.
I'm gonna go down there
and see if we can delay
this whole Coolidge situation,
all right?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
- I don't know.
It just seems like
everybody's upset
and it feels like it's my fault.
- No. No, not at all.
Look, we just want you
to get back to normal.
That's it, okay?
- Well, I would, if I could
remember what normal is.
I mean, what have you and I
been doing lately?
Are we planning the wedding?
Like, are we sending out
wedding invitations
or picked a honeymoon
destination, or...
Am I a warm weather guy
or a cold weather guy?
- Actually, we've been
a little busy lately, so...
- With what?
- Um, nothing that you need
to worry about, okay?
- Okay. You know what's weird?
I know we just ate, but
I'm already feeling hungry.
- Yeah, let's get
some food in you.
- All right.
- Okay.
- What's that saying?
"Man plans and God laughs?"
Well, men are planning.
And what's
the God of Speed doing?
Kneeling.
Brooding time is over.
You revealed yourself.
Now what?
Any idea what to do with
Flash and Friends?
Because we are getting
pretty close
to your big becoming,
and if we don't take them down,
neither one of us
gets what we want.
[tapping]
Hello? Anybody home?
[choking]
What are you doing?
- Who are you?
- What's wrong with you?
- Who... am... I?
Barry:
Science club.
Key Club, Astronomy Club...
- Yup.
- Yearbook?
- Yeah.
- And anime club?
- Oh, yeah.
You loved...loved...
"Dragon Ball Z."
- I don't know what that is.
- Yeah, I couldn't explain that
show to you even if I wanted to,
so...
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- I definitely had quite
the nerd thing going on, huh?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- I thought you said we were
best friends in high school.
- Yeah, we were.
- Then why didn't you give me
some advice, help me out?
- Oh, believe me, okay?
I tried.
- Really? You did?
- Yes.
- Okay, because I have evidence
that you did not.
Um, I don't remember
any of this,
but even I can see how wrong
that look was.
- [laughing]
- This is visual terrorism.
I won't look at it anymore.
What?
- You just...
you're so different.
You're so light.
- [laughs] What do you mean?
- I don't know,
it's like you're not
carrying the weight
of the world on your shoulders.
- So, what, I was like...
brooding all the time before?
- Sometimes.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Really?
[laughter]
- I don't know, it's just...
it's really nice to see you
smiling so much.
- I mean...
how could I not,
knowing I'm gonna be with you
for the rest of my life?
[phone buzzes]
- Uh-oh.
- What?
- I got to get
to the courthouse.
- Oh, yeah, of course.
- Yeah, I got to...
- Hey, yeah.
- Um...
I'll...yeah, later. Okay.
- Okay.
[calm, reflective music]
♪ ♪
- Docket number CC-15-204.
Evidentiary hearing
for Central City versus
the defendant, Lucious Coolidge.
I see the city wishes to file...
- Cutting it real close, guys.
- You ready to testify?
- No. No, I'm not.
- Yes, he is. He just needs
one minute, please.
- The prosecution may proceed.
- Too late. He's up.
- Here. Just take these.
- I wear glasses?
- You will now.
Just put 'em on.
You'll be okay.
- Just don't get them wet.
- [clears throat] Your Honor,
I, uh...I call Barry Allen
to the stand.
[quirky music]
- Raise your right hand, please.
You swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
- I do, yes.
- Thank you.
Miss Horton?
- Mr. Allen...
- Can I sit?
- Please, just...
You are a crime scene
investigator
for the Central City
police department, correct?
- [exhales sharply] Uh...
oh, this is so cool.
- Well, I'm so glad
you enjoy testifying,
but please just answer
the question.
- Of course. [clears throat]
Uh, yes, I am a CSI
at the CCPD under the expert
direction of Julian Albert.
Smiley face.
- Want to cut it out
with the emojis?
- Mr. Allen,
can you tell me,
in your expert opinion,
what substance do you see
in this photograph?
- Uh, shellac flakes.
Shellac is a resin secreted
by female lac bugs
found in large quantities
of the trees in Thailand...
that's too fast, that's too...
- Mr. Allen, are you all right?
- Yes, I'm sorry. I'm fine.
I just, um...
it's getting hot in here.
- What else is unique
about shellac flakes?
- It's the fire accelerant used
in all of the arson cases
associated with Heat Monger.
- [scoffs]
Such an embarrassing name.
- I like it.
I think it's great.
- And how would you know when
shellac flakes have been used?
- We calculate flame temperature
and burn patterns,
and a telltale sign is
when shellac is burned
into potassium perk-er-lorate
or ammonium perchlorate,
which is considered
a high-temperature
accelerant fire.
- Hmm. So, then...
would you say the fires
in these photos
would be considered
high-temperature
accelerant fires?
[exhales] Uh, yes, because...
[zap]
Ow!
- Uh-oh.
Um...
- Mr. Allen?
Can you continue?
- Yes, I can.
I can continue.
The...uh, yes, the fires were
high-temperature
accelerant fires,
because the flames...
were, were...
very yellow.
- Very yellow?
And that's your expert opinion
on accelerant fires?
Mr. Allen?
- [soft whimper]
- Ms. Horton, if Mr. Allen
is unable to elaborate,
I'll have no choice
but to dismiss.
Mr. Allen?
- That's...um...
- [sighs]
Dismissed.
- How'd it go?
- Marvelous.
They let the pyro go.
- What went wrong?
- Everything.
Barry's memory loss is starting
to become a problem.
- It sure is.
For more than just him.
- I don't have my speed.
- Not anymore.
And I know why.
If you want to fix this
and help Barry,
you are gonna do
exactly as I say.
- Now this Heat Monger's
gonna go free because of me,
and I feel awful.
- Barry, it's not your fault.
- It's just that now
there's a bad guy
on the streets, and I can't
do anything about it.
- [sighs]
- What? Is that not something
I would've said before?
- That is exactly something
you would've said before.
There's just something about you
that always wants to help.
- This is our place?
How do we afford
to live here?
Wow.
You have great taste.
- Uh, actually, this is all you.
- I find that hard to believe.
- [chuckles]
- Is that me?
- Yeah.
- Who are these people?
- They're your parents.
You don't remember anything
about what happened?
- Why, did something bad happen?
- They died.
It was unexpected, but...
they died peacefully.
That's why you came to live
with Joe and me.
- And that's when we met?
- Uh, no, actually, we were
friends before then.
I remember the first time
that I saw you.
You were the happiest boy
that I'd ever met.
- I have a feeling that's
because you entered my life.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- It's okay.
[whirring]
- What the...
- Barry! Are you okay?
- What just happened to me?!
- These powers are so cool.
I can literally feel electricity
coursing through my body.
I mean, is it always like this?
This is amazing.
We just walked into a buzzkill.
- My presence usually
dampens the mood.
- Joe, don't.
- You fire, I'll fire.
- What the hell
is she doing here?
- She wants to help.
- Help?
- With what?
- With the fact that
I lost my powers.
- Barry, why don't you
give us a minute?
- Sure, yeah.
Are you like a super villain?
Just asking. Okay.
- How did this happen?
- You got rid
of Barry's memories.
What Barry remembers,
Savitar remembers.
- So Savitar's lost
his memories too?
- Savitar loses his memory,
he doesn't go along
with the plan
to give Wally powers.
- Cause and effect.
But if you let me help you
figure out how
to get Barry's memories back,
everything goes back
to the way it was.
- Kid Flash runs again.
- And Savitar survives.
- And Iris dies.
- Life's full
of difficult choices.
- Or it isn't.
If Savitar gets his memory back,
what's in it for you?
- That's my business.
You think that Barry
can become The Flash?
- Yeah. He can learn.
- I still know how
to do everything.
I can teach him.
- Okay.
Maybe this is how
you defeat Savitar.
But there's still
a lot of villains
in this city, and no Flashes
to protect it.
Is that really a chance
you're willing to take?
- Hi.
- Ah!
- I'm still here.
- Yeah, you are.
- Because when you left,
I stayed.
- We gotta talk about
the elephant in the room.
But you know what, I...
I have a job to do.
We have to build that device.
We've got to focus
on the task at hand.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
- I totally understand.
- From here on out,
whenever I look into
your azure eyes,
flecked with gray,
like a summer rainstorm
coming to kiss my lips,
the only thing I'm
gonna be thinking about
is how I can best inspire that
beautiful, sexy brain.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Sparks.
- [whispering] Sparks.
- You felt them too.
- No.
- No?
- No, I mean yes, obviously.
- Oh, yeah.
- Sparks.
Jumping between
two parallel wires...
a modified high-voltage
climbing arc.
- I guess my work here is done.
- You should never have
tried this without Caitlin.
- Well, we didn't really have
much of choice, now, did we?
Also, don't refer to yourself
in the third person.
It's Caitlin. It's you.
It's the same person.
It's just confusing.
- Hand me the girard processor.
It'll help prime his neocortical
and medial frontal lobes.
What?
- Nothing.
Oh, golly. Look at us.
Just three musketeers
working away.
Just like old times, huh?
Hey, Julian, did Caitlin ever
tell you about our time
working on the Particle
Accelerator with Ronnie?
- No. No, she did not.
- There was this one time
we had this very
strict deadline,
and Dr. Wells was
super hard on us.
All of us, even Hartley.
- Who's...who's Hartley?
- Oh, he was this guy
we used to work with.
Such a dick. You actually
reminded me a lot of him
when you first came onboard.
Anyway, so we were working
on the iridium plating
for the, um... [snaps fingers]
What was it called again?
The synchrotron,
that's what it was.
So anyway, we were struggling,
and we were burning
the midnight oil,
and we could not get
the dubnium capacitor
to hold a single charge.
And so all of a sudden
Ronnie just loses
all his chill.
He turns beet red
and he starts yelling
at the thing like,
"Come on, you dumb-nium
capacitor!"
- "Take charge."
- Yes!
[laughs] Yes.
Oh, my God.
I think about all the memories
I cherish most, and...
and you're in every single
one of them, Caitlin.
- Let's figure this out.
I don't want to be here
any longer than I have to.
- Suit yourself.
- Okay!
Guys, I still can't believe
I have these powers.
They're amazing.
I mean...
I think that I
could be a superhero.
- [laughing]
- All right, well is it cool
if I run some more?
- Have at it.
- All right.
- I haven't seen him this happy
in a long time.
- Try ever.
It's the first time he
hasn't been weighed down
by the tragedies of his past,
you know?
First time he's actually
been free of them.
- You don't want his
memory restored, do you?
- Dad, I...
I can't say that seeing him
happy and light
isn't something I
have wished for him,
because yeah, it is.
- Sweetheart,
I wish that for him, too.
But you didn't fall
in love with The Flash.
You fell in love
with Barry Allen.
- Dad, I know this is
a different version of him,
but he's...
he's still Barry.
- No, he's not, honey.
Look, until yesterday,
Barry had 28 years
of experiences
to define him, and some
of those memories were bad,
but some were good, too.
But without those memories,
the Barry Allen we know
and love is gone.
Barry:
Whoo-hoo!
- I don't know, Dad.
You know, part of me
can't help but think
that this is some sort of gift,
you know...
that this is the life that
he was supposed to have.
Maybe the city doesn't
need The Flash.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, everybody!
Happy Friday!
[all screaming]
- So I am a superhero?
- Yeah. A real good one.
- Huh.
- You're The Flash.
- You sure The Streak isn't
a better name, maybe?
[laughter]
- Turn on the TV.
- Uh, okay.
Yeah.
- Eyewitnesses say
the man who set the fire
to the offices is none other
than Lucious Coolidge,
AKA Heat Monger.
- That's the guy that went
free because of me.
- At this rate, it won't be long
before the whole
thing burns down.
- There's hundreds of people
who work in there.
- We need to stop it.
- How? I mean,
you can't right now.
- No, but I can.
- Barry, you don't know
how to use your powers.
- Bar...
- You just said I'm a superhero.
And a good one, right?
I mean, memories or not,
I can't stand by
and watch people die
if I can prevent it.
Um, forgot the suit.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
- Barry? You okay?
- Uh, yeah, I'm good.
Stopping's hard.
How do I save everybody inside?
Cisco:
You just run them
out of there.
- I barely got here myself.
How am I supposed to run
with someone else?
- There's gotta be something
we can do.
- There is something we can do:
jump-start his brain
using that thing.
- We have not done a test run.
- There's no time
to test it now.
- What is that thing?
- This can send electrical
charges through
the transmitters in his suit
and theoretically,
should jolt his memory.
- You want to electroshock
his brain?
- Won't that fry it even more?
- If we don't do that,
all those people are gonna die.
- Life's a game of chance.
- Okay, Barry,
you're gonna feel something.
Might hurt, might sting,
might suck.
- Wait, what?
- Probably all three.
- Okay, here we go.
- [screaming]
[moans]
- Barry?
- [grunts]
- Uh, yeah, I still
don't remember.
- Why didn't that work?
That was supposed to work.
- We kick-started
his temporal lobe.
Now he just needs to access it.
- Gas is in the tank, we just
need to turn on the ignition.
- We need a visceral memory
to spark his brain.
[woman screaming]
- Okay...
okay.
- Barry?
I need you to remember.
- I can't!
- Yes, yes, you can.
Okay? Okay, listen to me.
The night that your mom died,
I didn't want to tell you how,
but she didn't die
peacefully.
She was murdered.
- What?
- And you came
to live with us.
My dad brought you inside,
and you were in shock.
You weren't crying.
And later that night,
a sound woke me,
and I crawled
out of my bed,
and I realized that the sound
was coming from downstairs.
I peered over the banister,
and...
I found you crying alone.
I knew I had to go to you.
I sat next to you,
and you put your head
in my lap, and I held you
while you cried.
And I didn't know it then,
but now looking back,
I realize that that was the
night that we fell in love.
That was the night
that we realized
how much we needed each other.
And look...
I so wish that I could take
your dark memories away.
I wish that I could make
all of that pain go away,
but I can't.
Okay? But what I do know,
what I know,
is that for every bad memory,
there is a good one
to get you through it.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Run, Barry, run!
- Barry?
- I remember...
- I remember.
- I remember everything.
- I remember everything!
- Now for this fire.
[exciting music]
- I don't think I can put
this fire out alone.
Wally:
You don't have to.
♪ ♪
- Yes!
- [panting]
- Looks like you remembered
how to save the day.
- Like riding a bike.
- Your mother's maiden name.
- Thompson.
- CODIS is an acronym for what?
- Combined DNA Index System.
- Okay. In the third grade,
you renamed the class
hamster to...
- [chuckles]
Alexander Ham Bell.
[laughter]
I was eight years old.
- So you got
your memories back.
Now we can all focus our
attention on stopping Savitar.
- [scoffs] Good luck with that.
- Please tell me we're not gonna
just let her walk out of here.
- Now you want to fight?
- We don't want to fight you.
- Can't really avoid that now,
can we?
- Yeah, we can.
You can stay here with us.
We're your friends.
Your family.
- Caitlin, I can fix you.
- You already tried.
- Well then, I'll try harder.
I don't care what it takes.
I don't care what I have to do.
I swear to you,
I will find you a cure.
Caitlin, I love you.
- I don't love you, Julian.
I never did.
I never loved any of you.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- She's gone?
- Yeah.
Maybe too far gone now.
- We'll figure out a way
to get her back.
Just like we figured out
how to get you back.
- You sure this is
the me you want?
With all the baggage?
- Seeing you without the weight
of everything that's happened,
seeing you happy, like you were
before your mother was killed?
Without all of that darkness
haunting you,
you were finally free.
It was nice.
- I did the same thing
months ago.
- What do you mean?
- That freedom? I had that.
When I was with my mom
and dad again in Flashpoint,
and I could've let it
stay like that.
I could've let the memories
of this timeline fade,
but if I'd done that,
I would've lost Joe,
and Cisco, and Wally,
and Caitlin, and you.
Pain and darkness-
it's a part of me.
You know, I need it to fuel me,
to push me to be
a better person,
to be a better hero.
To keep me from ever
forgetting who I am.
- Now that is the Barry Allen
I know and love.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, you guys...
okay!
You guys, you got
to come see this.
Y-you got to come see this.
- What is that?
- This is the Speed Force
Bazooka.
Good, right?
- And that's gonna trap Savitar?
- There is a tiny
little problem.
- What's that?
- It's, uh...
- In order to generate
enough power
to magnetize Savitar's
radial field
and keep him in a state
of perpetual stasis...
- Stasis.
- Inside the Speed Force,
we need by my calculations...
- By calculations...
- 3.86 terajoules of energy.
- I'm guessing that's more
energy than in a AAA battery.
- Yes. That's more energy
than in the sun.
- Guys, where are we gonna
find something like that?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- Greg, move your head.