Previously on "Crisis on Earth-X"...
- To Barry and Iris.
- ALL: To Barry and Iris.
Are you asking me to marry you?
- I am.
- Just forget about it.
- Felicity.
- I don't want to marry you!
I just called off my engagement.
To making things go away.
Does anyone have just cause
why these two should not be married?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Nazis?
Why would Nazis want
to crash my wedding?
There's a 53rd earth called Earth-X.
Basically our Earth with one difference.
The Nazis won the war.
I call it "Calm After the Firestorm."
No powers for either of us?
The other archer and flying woman
are Oliver and Kara of Earth-X,
and Thawne is working with them.
The general is dying.
All we need is a new heart.
And we found the perfect donor.
I don't think this is our Earth.
- [DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- _
- ♪
[DOGS BARKING]
[MAN YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
- [CRYING SOFTLY]
- Eyes front!
So this crap-hole's Earth-X.
- Wells was right.
- He usually is.
It's hard to believe a place
like this actually exists
on any Earth.
I wish I shared your sentiment,
but in all my travels to distant times,
one thing which sadly remains
constant is men's ability
to feel hatred for other men.
Keep moving.
Move!
All prisoners, stay away from the gate.
Stars and triangles...
Badges used to identify
purported crimes these
people have "committed"
to land in here.
What's the pink triangle for?
What did you do?
I loved the wrong person.
♪
We got to get out of these things.
- Transmute us out.
- With pleasure.
I can't vibrate through them either.
Power-dampening collars.
Well, why are we wearing them, then?
Doesn't matter.
There's too many guards here anyways.
They're gonna kill my sister.
Look, we're not gonna let that happen,
Alex, I promise you.
We're gonna get back to
our Earth before then.
How? We don't even know how we got here.
No, we don't. We're gonna figure it out.
Then we're gonna find a way
to get out of this place,
and we're gonna get back
to the people we love.
I hope everyone else is okay.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
_
[BALL BOUNCING]
Oh!
Rip Van Ramon awakens.
This doesn't look like a wedding.
[MUTED YELLING]
You missed quite a bit, Cisco.
All you need to know
is that you are locked
in one of your fabulous
anti-meta-human cells
with the rest of us.
- We can't escape.
- Of course we can't.
That's what I designed them for, genius.
Good command of the obvious.
- Boys.
- Is that a ball?
Why? Is it bothering you?
Yes.
God. Hey!
[BALL THUMPING ON WALL]
Are they gonna do that the
whole time we're in here?
- Ow!
- Probably.
- It hurts! Cut it out!
- Cut what out?
[SIGHS] S.T.A.R. Labs.
It feels like old times, doesn't it?
You know, I, uh... I built this place...
with my own hands and called it home
for 15 years, and do you know what?
I hated every minute of it.
Where are my friends?
Your friends, they're on Earth-X.
I wouldn't worry about your
friends too much because...
they're not going to
be alive much longer.
- [GRUNTS]
- [CHUCKLES] Oh, honey.
It's because of the red sunlight.
And trust me,
it'll make you weaker than
you can possibly imagine.
[PANTING]
[BREATHES UNEVENLY]
You did all this just... just to get me?
Do you know how many
innocent people you killed?
Their lives to save mine?
Well, they should feel honored.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS MENACINGLY]
It's a strange sensation, isn't it...
feeling vulnerable?
And it's just gonna get worse
because this red sunlight,
it's softening you up
until pretty soon,
I'm gonna crack you open like a walnut.
Then I'm gonna take your healthy heart.
I'm gonna put it in her.
Which means we should
probably get you going.
Good.
That'll give me time to talk to...
myself.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
[PANTING] Did you hear that?
- Everyone else is on Earth-X.
- And Kara only has a few hours
before they go full Mengele on her.
- We gotta stop them.
- Got any ideas?
I don't know. Give
me some time to think.
Iris, I'm all for girl
power and everything,
but how are you and I gonna
stop the meaner, Nazi version
of my whatever he is right now and...
[WHISPERING] People with superpowers?
We don't have to.
We just need to get to
the pipeline and get Cisco.
He could turn off all
the power to the building
and breach us out of here.
Do you know how to get
to the pipeline from here?
[BREATHES DEEPLY] I think so.
Lead the way, McClane.
Move!
[ALARMS RINGING]
- [WHISTLES BLOWING]
- Move!
I don't like the looks of this.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
- Keep moving!
- What are we doing?
- It's roundup time.
- Roundup for what?
Move!
In line, now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪
So these are...
the heroes.
Yes, Sturmbannfuehrer.
[WOMAN VOCALIZING EERILY]
♪
[SCOFFS]
Blonde hair...
blue eyes... This is Nordic perfection.
Why would you align
yourself with the unpure?
Because I like men
and I like women.
[HUFFS]
You know, I had a daughter
who looked just like you,
with similar compulsions.
♪
And I expunged that filth
from my family line forever.
Bring them all.
And him!
Move! Now!
- [GUNS COCKING]
- Go!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Not to be an alarmist, but if
we don't have an escape plan,
I suggest we get one immediately.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
[DEVICE WHINES]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[ALL GROANING]
Up!
♪
Go.
Turn around.
I know you are not him,
but I cannot stomach
the sight regardless.
Ready!
I'm sorry, Kara.
Aim!
[GUNS COCKING]
[BLASTER FIRES]
I hate "fire."
ALL: Snart?
About time!
Kill them all!
[GUNFIRE]
Take cover!
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[GUNFIRE]
Hey, you're cutting it close.
I thought that was great timing.
I really enjoyed the pun.
So you're Leonard Snart's doppelganger.
No, I'm Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Leo.
That is a fantastic outfit.
Did you make that?
- Leo.
- Right.
Time to make you shine, buddy.
Uh, you, uh...
You might want to close your eyes.
Why?
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪
Well, I believe he just
answered your question.
♪
Come on, let's go.
Where are we going?
- To our base.
- Your base?
- And... and who are you?
- I was thinking exactly
- the same thing about you all.
- [GUARDS SHOUTING]
You might have to tell us on the way.
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUNTS]
You're looking more human.
Scared, helpless, pathetic... inferior.
We're not that different from them.
Oh, please. We're
everything they want to be:
blonde, white.
Aryan perfection.
I'm not like you.
I don't think I'm better
than everyone else.
You should.
You are.
You're a god to them.
You could have been living like one.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Like you?
Yes, like me.
They want someone to bow to,
to worship, to lead.
What you're doing is not leading.
It's ruling.
Yes, it is.
They're like ants, Kara.
They shouldn't fear
us for what we can do.
They should rely on
us when they need us.
Oh, spare me the Good Samaritan crap.
I'm not gonna take
advantage of anyone,
just because I can.
The world isn't made better
by protecting the weak.
It's made better by getting rid of them.
You really are pathetic.
You know, I saw you at the wedding.
By yourself.
Poor, lonely little Kara.
Can't even find a date
to a wedding. [LAUGHS]
You don't know what
you're talking about.
It's written all over
that pouty little face of yours.
You spend so much time on your planet
taking care of everyone but yourself.
No wonder you seem so utterly miserable.
It's not going to work.
You're not gonna get what you want.
Really?
Why do you care if I take your heart?
You're not using it.
At least I have one.
We're almost ready.
[PANTING]
Clear.
I know bad guys have inopportune timing,
but this is, like,
the worst timing ever.
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
Barry and I were just
about to get married.
At least you guys left on good terms.
The last thing I said to
Oliver was, "I don't want
to marry you," and now
he's stuck in Nazi world.
I mean, what if we never see them again?
- [GUNFIRE]
- Stop!
Hands in the air!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[GUARDS SCREAM]
[GROANS]
That was extremely badass.
Same to you.
Cisco.
- Cisco?
- Hey!
Guys, we're trapped in here!
We're gonna get you of here!
[POUNDING]
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
- What?
- I can't open the blast door.
You mean they're trapped?
I'll send an SOS to the Legends.
How long will it take
for them to get it?
Depends where they are in time.
We can't wait that long.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
It's up to us to save Kara.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
I guess we're in Earth-X's Star City.
I have to say, that's
one hell of a story.
- You're a speedster.
- Yeah.
Okay, you two turn into the burning man.
Yup.
And you're the good
doppelganger of the Fuehrer.
"Good" might be an oversimplification.
You still haven't told us
which Earth you're from.
Clearly, it's not this one.
We're from Earth-1.
Earth-1? Well...
golly.
Am I missing something here?
I'm from Earth-1 too.
If you're from our Earth,
then you know how we
got here, don't you?
Yeah, I have a pretty good idea.
I think you guys...
came through this.
- A temporal gateway?
- Same physics as a breach,
- just more stable and larger.
- Yeah, much larger.
So we have a way to get back.
So where is this thing?
It's actually not too far from here.
22.3 kilometers, to be exact.
- Well, we'd drive there.
- Good.
So take us to it.
- Can't do that.
- Why?
Because the gateway's
in a facility guarded
by a not-so-small army of Nazis.
Yeah, well, we've faced worse, so...
Look, it's our only way home.
We're going through it.
Nobody's going through anything.
Because we're blowing it the hell up.
♪
- Winn?
- Please,
- Freedom Fighter General Schott.
- General Schott?
Yeah, and who are you?
New friends from Earth-1.
They're on our side.
Except for the part where you guys
want to blow up our only way home.
We don't exactly want to.
Everyone we care about
is on the other side
of that gateway, imprisoned by Nazis.
The Nazis that want
to cut open my sister.
- We have to get back.
- Eliminate that facility,
and you eliminate our only chance
of saving our friends from your enemies.
I'm sorry, but we've been waiting
for an opportunity like this for years.
We cannot wait any longer.
This is our only chance
to separate the Fuehrer from his army.
We are trying to turn this war around.
You are gonna leave
our Earth at the mercy
of the three psychopaths
who have ravaged yours.
Wait, why does this man look exactly
like the Fuehrer I am trying to kill?
Look, fingerless
gloves, all we are asking
is for a little bit of time.
Let us get into the facility
and through that gateway.
The gateway is guarded
by 30 Panzer XIIs,
50 Sturmtigers, and 100
Schutzstaffel officers.
- Not the best odds, maybe.
- I'll take them.
No, you will not.
We are blowing up
that gateway right now.
Final order.
Sorry he's a little
rough around the edges.
But he is the general, and
he's issued his commands.
Hey, hey, hey.
You won't change his mind. No one does.
Look, on my Earth, he
and I are like family.
And he would do anything
to help my sister.
Ray, let her try.
You don't seem to know
how to take an order.
That's because I'm used to giving them.
You can't do this, Winn.
General Schott.
Look, I don't know where
the hell you think you are,
but this planet has been
at war for generations.
We are tired.
There are men dying
for the same causes
their grandfathers did.
[SCOFFS]
We're not asking you to surrender.
Hey, just... just let us get back home
before you destroy that thing.
I-I'm just asking for a little time.
Time is what I can't give you.
They have a weapon...
a doomsday weapon powerful enough
to affect other worlds.
It has to be eliminated.
Winn.
- Please.
- [SIGHS]
The Fuehrer on your Earth,
the people that you hate,
they're going to kill my sister
if you don't let me
get back to save her.
On my Earth, my sister
is your closest friend.
She's saved you countless times.
You would do anything to help her.
You would do anything to help each other,
no matter the risk, without question.
So all I'm asking for is a chance.
Please.
I am sorry about your sister
and about your Earth.
I truly am.
But today I have the chance
to protect my people,
my Earth.
My decision stands.
Winn.
Jefferson?
Uh, Grey, I'm busy, man.
Yes, I can see that, but I was hoping
you might take a moment
away from your ruminations
on dystopian alternative
history to accept my apology.
I may be a learned man,
but I am not always an astute one.
I think I was just so thrilled
with the reality of
my imminent departure
that I neglected to
consider your feelings.
Look, man, I'm not trying to
take you away from your family
- or nothing...
- You are my family.
Long before I unexpectedly
found myself with a daughter,
I found myself unexpectedly with a son.
- Yeah, I know. I ju...
- You know.
You know, do you?
Look around you. We're
standing in one of the...
darkest places imaginable.
Yet somehow I'm
optimistic. Do you know why?
'Cause you're a crazy old man.
- Yes. No!
- [LAUGHS]
Because I'm standing here with you.
You are a better son than
I could have ever hoped for.
And no length of time or distance
will ever change that.
A'ight. Apology accepted.
Come here. [CHUCKLES]
What are you doing?
Looking for a gun...
or knife... anything.
Okay, I don't care how many Sturmtigers
they have out there.
I'm gonna go save Kara,
with or without the
help of these people.
No, you're not.
I'm a government agent
certified in over 30 military weapons.
And you're impressive,
I'll give you that.
But you still can't fight your way
through an army of
Nazis alone and scared.
I'm not scared.
No, not for you. For your sister.
I should've done more.
I mean, if I hadn't
gotten so... distracted.
Well, sorry to be a distraction.
You don't understand.
I can't lose her.
I understand more than you think.
[SIGHS]
I lost my sister.
The anger and guilt that I felt
for not being able to save her
took me down a dark path.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
How could you?
I mean, the only thing we
know about each other is...
what we look like with clothes off.
Beautiful, by the way.
You also don't know
that I protect my team,
and you, Danvers, you're on my team.
And I promise you, we're not gonna let
what happened to my
sister happen to yours.
I'm sorry.
I just want to... I want to save Kara,
and I want to get back to Maggie.
- Maggie is?
- Complicated.
Yeah. I had a Maggie too.
And I think about going back to her...
all the time.
Look, Alex.
You seem like a pretty
thoughtful person.
And if you thought it
wasn't gonna work out
and had to end it,
I'm sure that reason was valid.
Trust your instincts.
Ray, please, let's talk to him.
Look, you said to let Alex try.
I let her try.
- She didn't succeed.
- So that's that?
We just let these poor
strangely dressed individuals
lose their one way home?
Look, it's what Winn ordered,
and I am not in the habit of
defying generals on any Earth.
And what about your
family back on Earth-1?
What about them?
You'd be giving up any chance
of ever seeing them again.
Leo...
why are you pushing this?
- Pardon?
- We have fought
and bled and sacrificed for this war.
And then these strangers show up
and you're willing to throw
everything away for them?
The fate of the world is at stake.
So are the lives of their loved ones.
Come on.
Tease me all you want
for being sentimental.
These heroes would risk everything
for the people they
love, just like I would...
for you.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You know I can't say no
when you look at me like that.
That is why I look at you like that.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
We talked to the general,
and after a lot of arguing,
- he agreed, so...
- We're gonna help you out.
♪
Now, you referenced 100 guards.
I assume most of them
are around the perimeter?
- Correct.
- All right.
We fight through them outside.
We access the main corridor.
What is security like inside the hangar?
I'll do some recon.
So the entire facility
has meta-human dampeners.
Okay, we can't take that
hangar with no powers, man.
These satellites indicate a
control room off the hangar.
That must be where the dampener is.
Okay, well, we definitely can't take
the main control room with no powers.
It's not like we blend in here.
[EXHALES]
[EXCITING MUSIC]
I think I know how to get in.
I'm allowing this mission
against my better judgment.
You have one hour.
[EXHALES] I appreciate it. We all do.
Yeah, I know. I know
what you're thinking.
If you don't make it
through the gateway,
I am not giving you more time.
I will blow that place to kingdom comm.
Red light saturation...
is complete.
- [GROANS]
- She's cooked.
And you will wake up stronger
than you've ever been.
I love you.
[WHISPERING] I love you.
Unfortunately, Miss Danvers,
we need you awake for this procedure.
My... my cousin...
he'll find you.
Your cousin.
Really? Fun tidbit.
I fought your cousin
once. In the future.
He is fast.
I'm faster.
[SAW WHIRRING LOUDLY]
♪
They're starting the surgery.
I'm working on it, and...
[SAW CONTINUES WHIRRING]
[ELECTRICITY POWERS DOWN]
[ALARMS BLARING]
Just have backup power,
and it's not enough.
Well, everyone in the building
has been accounted for.
Where might people be hiding?
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
- [WOMEN GRUNT]
- Take that you, Nazi mother...
Whho!
Hey, hey, hey.
Comm with me if you want to live.
Get me to the sun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
- I got her, I got her.
- Okay.
We gotta go.
[ELEVATOR WHIRS]
[ELECTRICITY ZAPPING]
I don't believe Mr. Thawne
is done with you yet.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Your papers, Sturmmann.
We don't have papers.
This is a special visit.
Your papers. Now.
Suit yourself, but, uh,
I think you better talk to our boss.
As you were.
Mein gott. My apologies, sir.
Let them through!
- [GATE BUZZES]
- Let them through!
Thank you, mein Fuehrer.
♪
ALL: Hail, Fuehrer.
[DARK MUSIC]
♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
Mein Fuehrer, we were...
We were not expecting you.
Nor was I anticipating
being back so soon.
Thanks to your incompetence,
the Earth-1 doppelgangers...
[RAISSNG VOICE] My doppelganger...
[SOFTLY] Escaped his execution.
Yes, he did.
And?
We are exhausting every possible means
to locate them.
Good.
Would you like us to delay
deployment until we do so?
Deployment?
She is inbound and ready.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
The doomsday device.
The Wellenreiter is fully operational
and at the ready, mein Fuehrer.
Shall we send her through?
As scheduled.
Begin!
[WHOOSHING]
♪
The Wellenreiter is on its way.
Hail, victory!
ALL: Hail, victory!
Hail, victory.
♪
- Report.
- Good news.
The Wellenreiter's made the
transition to this Earth.
Kara is all that matters.
That red sunlight
we're flooding her with,
that's burning off.
So pretty soon, her cells
will be so desaturated,
we cannot perform the surgery.
- Fix it.
- I can't.
This is your city.
This is your facility.
So turn the power back on.
I can't because the
system has been encrypted.
By who?
By Miss Smoak.
♪
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
No, that'll be all.
Very well.
Before I go, I have something
for you, mein Fuehrer.
A gift...
to celebrate your return.
Guard!
Well, I know how much you
enjoy executing rule breakers,
and this one has broken many of them.
We discovered this Jewess
handing her rations to
the work camp children.
Strictly against camp rules, of course.
Those children were starving.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
Well, this must be hard.
I hear your doppelganger on Earth-1
loved a woman who looks just like this.
♪
- [GUN CLICKS]
- [LAUGHS]
[GUNS COCKING]
[CHUCKLES]
Did you really think I would
hand you a loaded weapon...
[RAISING VOICE]
Before verifying who you are?
[GRUNTING]
[GUNFIRE]
[MEN YELLING]
♪
Hey, hey, hey, you're okay.
No, no, no, you're fine. You're fine.
Just take this and go.
Why are you doing this?
It's the strong's duty
to protect the weak.
Take it and go.
Go!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Clear.
How did it... Oh.
Barry, we have a problem.
The gateway control's been damaged.
We can't turn it on?
We can't turn it on here,
but there should be a manual
override at the platform.
[SIGHS] All right, we're gonna have
to fight our way through.
What do you mean? Call it back!
Too late. It's been programmed.
There's no changing course now.
You said we'd have an hour.
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
The team hasn't gone
through the breach yet.
That team has nothing to do
with us or saving our planet.
And everyone who can threaten it
is on he other side of that breach.
They are not coming back through.
- General!
- Leo, enough!
I'm not risking any more time.
We are blowing it up.
Guys, we have a problem.
What kind of problem?
A weapon is heading to
blow up the facility.
A weapon? You mean a missile?
Not exactly.
♪
Felicity Smoak.
Turn the power back on.
He said...
[BREATHING RAGGEDLY]
- Felicity!
- [COUGHS]
"Turn the power back on."
Sorry, Eobard. Eobard?
- Eobard.
My Goo, the future sounds weird.
That's funny.
Sometimes we think we're
more clever than we are.
Because where I come from,
the history books are
filled with stories
of this Age of Heroes:
Green Arrow,
Black Canary,
The Flash.
And yet no one...
no one has ever heard
of Felicity Smoak.
Stop!
Stop. Stop.
You came here for me,
so just take me, please.
Please don't hurt anyone else.
Give them the code.
- If I do, they'll kill you.
- It's fine.
Nobody's gonna die because of me.
Latte, Ada, Jonas, 1-1-9-0-0.
Latte?
Cute.
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
Let's go.
In ten minutes, Red Tornado's
gonna bring down this entire facility,
and there's nothing we
can do to stop that robot.
Then we need to reopen the gateway
before that happens.
- Barry, Ray...
- We know.
Stop a flying robot somehow.
Good. The rest of us
will open the breach.
That's the whole plan?
Well, as a Snart we know used to say,
"Make a plan. Execute the plan.
Expect the plan to go off the rails.
Throw away the plan."
Wow. That is... that is terrible advice.
I always have a plan,
down to the second,
so nothing ever goes wrong.
No, no, no, the only plan now
is not to leave this
Earth... without me.
Okay.
Right. Ready for Tornado watch.
Let's do it.
I thought it'd be fun if
we put on our costumes.
Where'd you get the bow and quiver?
The general collects weapons.
Let's go to war.
No one gets to the gateway!
No one!
[GUNS COCKING]
[EXPLOSION]
[MEN GRUNTING]
♪
[GUARDS YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
Move! Move!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
♪
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
Here we go.
♪
[GRUNTS]
[TRAIN HORN BLOWING]
♪
Okay, we're Nazi-free. Let's go.
Hold on. That's an automated power cell.
We need to activate it before
using the control console.
I can hot-wire it, no problem.
Then I'll turn on the console.
You want to split up? You sure?
It's our most favorable odds.
Let's kick some ass, Jefferson.
♪
Grey, we got power.
[GUNFIRE]
Whoa! Hey!
Ray!
A little help here!
♪
[YELLING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
BOTH: Oh, crap.
[GUNFIRE]
Well, that's not very fair.
I'm pinned down!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GASPS]
Grey! No!
♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...