Previously on The Flash...
The disappearance
of Sue Dearbon.
I don't think I've ever seen you
this devoted to a case.
I want to become
a defense attorney for meta-humans.
Meet Chester P. Runk.
He opened a black hole by accident.
What up, party people!
Also, where am I?
His molecules need to re-stabilize
at the sub-atomic level.
And when he does get out, that boy knows
exactly what he wants to do.
Gonna ask Natalie out.
You cannot avoid the coming crisis.
Just tell me what I can do.
The Flash must die.
Nash, if you would just tell us
what you're looking for down there,
we might be able to help you.
So this is
where you've been hiding.
I know how to save Barry Allen.
This is what I do.
I don't just solve mysteries.
I bust myths.
I bust them wide open.
You said you could save Barry.
Tell us what you meant. The truth.
Do you know what you're dealing with?
The Monitor, Mar Novu.
Or whatever he calls himself.
- Are you saying the Monitor's here?
- That's right.
You tracked a multi-verse god
down into a hole?
And he's going to do here
what he has done
on all these other Earths.
Create fear.
Because the Monitor is a fraud.
He's a false god.
One that I intend to take down,
thereby saving your husband.
If my calculations are correct,
behind these rocks
there's an inter-dimensional portal,
and that portal will lead us
directly to Mar Novu.
He's been here all along.
He has nowhere to run.
Back up.
Yeah, no, I wouldn't do...
Barry! Barry.
- Did you know that would happen?
- Yeah.
But this is just another one
of Mar Novu's tricks.
These rocks are infused with Eternium,
and that creates
an anti-vibrational force field that...
- No phasing.
- No phasing, correct.
So, how do we get through?
I got a jackhammer in my car.
Uh, no. Any contact with the Eternium
in the sediment
could cause
a catastrophic molecular blast.
Everybody dies.
No, instead all I need is
an artifact.
One that will illuminate the Eternium
so I can know what rocks
to dig around. Simple.
And I know where to find that artifact.
What up, party people!
Uh...
Hello!
Where is everybody?
Chester P.
Chester P., my brother.
You have a multi-billion dollar
bleeding-edge tech facility...
all to yourself.
Whoo!
It has everything!
Incoming!
Sonic wrench!
Good morning, guv'nor. I'm the Doctor.
Ooh.
They have a multi-array private
global satellite surveillance system?
Oh!
Gotta check my emails.
Disabled?
I'm going again. I'm going again.
Uh-oh.
Killer Frost.
Wow.
The one day I get watch duty.
Uh...
What does this mean?
Looks like, technically, you're dead.
- Oh. Can I touch it?
- Mmm-hmm.
An official Elongated Man emblem?
He's going to scream.
He's going to be so surprised.
I've been preparing the whole team
for life after Crisis.
But Central City also has to be ready
for a world without Flash,
and Elongated Man should be
its sole protector once I'm gone.
As far as Ralph knows,
he's coming to C.C.P.D.
for a routine deposition tomorrow when
it's really a press conference to...
pass the torch.
Hey, guys.
Yo! Got your message, Joe.
Hey, Ralph.
I talked to an old friend
about your Dearbon case.
I got the address you were looking for
in Midway City.
If I were you, I would go check it out
after the deposition tomorrow.
Why put off tomorrow
what you can do today, right? Thanks.
Wait, wait, wait. Um...
You're going to be back from Midway
by tomorrow morning, right?
It's a routine deposition.
You can handle it.
Why don't I tag along?
I'll speed things up a bit.
You want to help me with a PI case?
Yeah, definitely. It'll be fun.
I'll follow your lead.
Okay.
This looks like it's gonna take a while.
Not if you know how to work the system.
I spent the whole summer hobnobbing
with the rich, famous, and the infamous.
Relax, I got this.
I can't imagine spending the whole
summer undercover with this crowd.
What does a gala event have to do
with Sue's disappearance, anyway?
Right before Sue vanished,
she was seen wearing
a one-of-a-kind
Victoria Veil dress in Milan.
This photo was taken three weeks ago.
It's the exact same dress.
Sue was here,
and either she's still here,
or somebody in there
knows why she isn't.
Time to suit up.
Lose the ring, pal.
This is how we suit up tonight.
So, if anyone here knows where Sue is,
it'll be the party's host.
There's hundreds of people in here.
How do we narrow it down?
Golden tile, sir? Thank you.
VIP lounge.
That's where anyone who's anyone will
be going to kiss the proverbial ring.
We need to get in there.
Here. Mine was tight, too. Just...
Now I have ten selfies
of inside Barry Allen's nose.
- A camera tie?
- Mmm.
What, do you have a knife shoe
and a grapple-hook belt, too?
Maybe.
Time to charm.
Wait for my signal.
Ralph, what's this...
And here I thought the paintings would
be the most beautiful thing tonight.
I was wrong.
Ralph Dibny.
January Galore.
I haven't seen you
at one of these events before.
That's because I spent the last year
on my island in Dubai.
My partner and I sold our corporation.
Barry?
Gingold martini. Shaken, not stirred.
Congratulations on selling
your corporation, Barry.
I do hope you reinvested your profits
in collateralized loan obligations.
Yes. We recently sold our company
for many millions of dollars.
Do you know our host?
Mr. Meyers?
Yes, Mr. Meyers.
The host of this event is
Remington Meister.
You both crashed this event, didn't you?
Would you like some free advice?
I'd leave before someone scary
comes and finds you.
Well, that did not go well.
Yes, it did.
Our VIP ticket.
Finesse.
Harrison Wells?
Ah!
- Okay. Who are you?
- Allegra.
You're the intern. So, maybe
you can help me with something.
Uh, I'm looking for a UV emitter,
and my scanner tells me
there is a UV emitter right around here.
You're supposed to be dead.
What happened?
Did you fake your own death?
Oh, no. So, you, uh...
No. You think I'm Harrison Wells.
I'm not Harrison Wells.
My name is Nash.
Nash Wells.
You look just like him.
Yeah. Well, doppelgangers are like that.
This stupid Earth.
- Okay. Accelerant.
- Allegra.
I'm doing a dig. All right?
I need UV rays to complete my dig.
You, according to my gauntlet...
are a meta-human with UV capabilities.
You see where I'm going here?
You want me to use my powers
to help you?
- Yes!
- I can't help you.
- What? Why not?
- Never mind. The answer is no.
Allegra, I will make you a deal.
You help me with the UV thing,
and I will give you the...
scoop of the century.
Doppelgangers, multi-verse,
and potentially...
the end of all life...
as we know it.
Now, how does that sound to you?
Tell me more about this multi-verse.
The bank unfroze your accounts,
and maybe I erased your parking tickets
when I got
your driver's license reinstated.
Thanks, Cecile.
Oh, your clients are lucky to have you.
Hey, speaking of, I should let you
get back to doing your job.
Thank you so much
for everything that you've done.
Wait. You know what? Hey, Chester...
I got... I got a little time.
Is there... is there anything else
that you could use some help with?
Mmm, nope.
All is good in Chester-hood.
Don't go. Don't go.
Are you sure?
Like, are you sure, sure?
Anything at all
that I could help you with?
I mean, think hard.
There is something.
I knew it. Okay, sock it to me.
Jitters is gone. Right?
Which means that I'll never see...
uh, their coffee again.
Yeah. I'm thinking
that by "coffee" you mean Natalie?
I was gonna ask her out after
I filled in my Vibe-acino punch card.
But...
it's too late now.
So...
Sorry. I know this isn't
a lawyer problem at all. I...
No, it's not. But...
it is a meta-empath problem.
You got... you got powers?
Oh, I got powers.
Oh, that's so cool.
That's so cool. Ah!
That must have been a major conflict
of interest as a DA, though.
It was. Yeah.
But those powers are about
to help you ask out Natalie.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Let's do it. Okay. We're doing it.
Very few of my guests have the
Tapferkeit to challenge me like this.
After all...
I am the master of this ring.
Strict rules of mah-jongg?
But of course.
Oh, so, gentlemen...
I don't think we have been introduced.
I'm Remington Meister, your host.
And you are?
The name's Dibny. Ralph Dibny.
Allen... Barry.
Well, nice to meet you,
Allen Barry and Ralph Dibny.
Mmm.
And what brings you
to my wonderful grosse Feier?
Sue Dearbon.
Sue?
A, uh...
fiercely intelligent young woman.
She's a friend of yours?
Um...
I'm an admirer of hers.
A-ha.
You have taste, Mr. Dibny.
And I wish I could be a more
auspicious host and introduce you.
But I'm afraid Ms. Dearbon isn't here.
In fact, I don't think I have seen her
at any social event in over six months.
Perhaps she'll attend an event
in your vicinity soon.
And, uh, where was that nochmal?
- Paris.
- Dubai.
We run
a multi-city import-export company.
Mmm.
Maybe she's still on the guest list.
You know, just in case.
You think I should check?
Sure. Yeah.
Idna!
That's a beautiful dress.
Is it a one-of-a-kind?
Two-of-a-kind, actually.
Even the most stubborn designer's
one-of-a-kind outfit has a price.
So true. So true.
I'm impressed.
You have quite the eye for fashion.
Oh.
- Sue Dearbon is not on the list.
- Oh.
And strange...
Neither are you.
Well, when an auction
like yours pops up,
no list can keep us away.
I like you.
Him? Nicht so viel.
Ah!
Mah-jongg.
Sik wu.
I win.
Such a pleasure to meet you both.
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
I'm sorry, man. I thought I had that.
We should get back to Central City.
Put our friend above on high alert.
I tracked down the woman who designed
Sue's dress in Milan.
- Yeah?
- Turns out that Idna
did commission her to make another one.
So, I think
what we got to do next is probably...
But, Ralph, Sue's not here.
We just got made,
and we just hit a dead end.
We should head back to Central City.
Barry, if Meister wanted us out of here,
we'd be gone already.
Take a whiff, would you?
Something doesn't smell right here.
Ralph, I know you care
about this Sue case.
But we're grasping at straws.
I'm not even sure
there's a mystery here.
Really? You're not sure?
You see that guy
with the eye patch right there?
That's Riggs Wellington.
He's a shady Bratva counterfeiter.
And January Galore?
She's an underground weapons dealer.
That guy right there,
he's a drug kingpin.
The woman he's talking to is a mob boss.
If this is a party for criminals,
then the Flash and Elongated Man
need to take over.
Pump the brakes, would you?
There's a time and place
for masks and cowls. But this is not it.
This Meister, he's up to something.
We need to find out what it is.
No matter how long it takes.
Ralph, tomorrow we have...
we have the deposition...
Lay off the whole deposition thing,
would you?
C.C.P.D. can wait.
I can search this whole place
in seconds.
Barry, I realize that you want to help
and I appreciate that.
But this is not Central City.
These people are not metas.
This is a time for our human identities.
Finesse. Remember?
- I just need some time. Okay?
- Okay.
Here's the deal.
I made a coffee order
with the new Jitters-To-Go service.
That's where Natalie works now.
So when she arrives,
- I am going to read her emotion...
- Mmm-hmm.
...and then
I'm going to tell you what to say.
What if she says no?
She's not going to say no.
Not with my help.
And I'm here, too.
My good deed for the day
was to help somebody
and I couldn't find
anyone less annoying.
Really?
Hey, I have a delivery
for Chester P. Runk.
Yeah. That's... That's, uh...
That's me. Yeah.
Wow. Twelve Vibe-acinos.
Yeah.
Chester, she's feeling impressed.
Big order like that, it shows her
that you are a man of means.
Yeah, well, you know, I'm, uh...
kind of a big spender. You know?
Can't take it with you, right?
Sure. I guess.
Do you need a receipt?
Are you sure you're reading her right?
Yeah. Of course.
Um...
Hey, Chester.
She's yearning for validation.
So, pay her a compliment.
She's feeling very strong
positive feelings about her shoes.
Uh...
I really like your shoes.
These old things? Yuck.
I lost my favorite kicks
to a black hole.
That's, uh... that's rough.
You are totally missing the mark.
You... You're not helping.
Uh, Chester, be assertive.
Don't let her leave
without asking her out.
Natalie, before you go...
I was wondering if...
If we could, you know...
I... I could carry this crate for you.
Oh.
It's not a problem.
Yes, it is.
She wants you to be chivalrous.
Help her, now.
Pardon moi!
I can pay for those.
Yeah. I think you've done enough.
I'm no expert,
but The Book of Ralph says
that when you ask someone out,
you should just be yourself.
How is he supposed to be himself
when he doesn't even know
who he is anymore?
And these different Earths have
existed simultaneously since...
Well, since, uh... Let's see.
Oh, the dawn of time.
How come nobody knows about this?
I mean, stuff this big?
The public should be made aware.
People know. Just the right people.
The general public, no. No.
No, that would not be good.
They would lose their minds.
Right. I mean...
It's all so...
- epic.
- Yes. It's epic.
Doppelgangers, anti-matter events,
and speedsters juggling dual identities
like the Flash and Barry Allen.
Wait. What?
What?
My boss's husband is the Flash?
Mmm-hmm.
God. Nobody tells me anything.
But then, of course, let's not forget
the villain of the story.
The Monitor. Hmm.
Yeah. Cosmic imposter
with delusions of grandeur.
That is why
I want to take that fraud down...
permanently.
You're going to kill this... Novu guy?
Enough story time.
Time for you to hold up
your end of the bargain.
Wait. Can you, uh,
explain doppelgangers?
Sure, absolutely, I can. But first...
let's have you zap this
with your meta UV light
so I can find out
what rocks to avoid when I excavate.
And... go.
I... I can't.
Yes, you can.
You're a meta. It's who you are.
- No, it's not.
- It is. And also...
we had a deal.
- Well, the deal's off.
- What?
I... I'm not gonna be some weapon
you use to hurt others.
I'm not asking you to be the weapon.
It's not who I am.
All right, let's see what we got here.
Something tells me
that ain't a Johnny Cash song.
Damn it, Ralph. She's not here.
They're all here to bid on this.
Come on. Come on.
Meta target acquired.
Wunderbar.
Hey, hey.
Don't bother. It's meta-dampened.
I must say,
I did not expect Central City's
resident superhero
to crash my little gathering.
I must say, I'm surprised
by all the Bond villain clichés.
I mean, you've got the accent,
the diabolical scheme.
Even the silent-but-deadly henchperson.
Ultraviolet? I sent you to Iron Heights.
Luckily, she has friends in low places.
Well, let me guess.
You're gonna add my unmasking
to your little auction.
Oh.
I could care less about
your secret identity, Flash.
My interests are global.
And to think, Mr. Dibny,
that it was the Flash that set off
my meta-activity monitor,
that then triggered the security
protocols that got you caught.
Danke schön.
I am very curious, though...
as to why you are really here.
Do you expect me to talk?
No, Mr. Dibny...
I expect you to die.
Oh, come on! That line is
literally from Goldfinger.
And so is this.
Behold!
A state-of-the-art
industrial laser cannon.
It will shoot a deadly beam...
through the both of you
the moment Central City is destroyed.
You're gonna kill millions of innocent
people just to sell your weapon?
Ja.
Enjoy the show.
Got lost, didn't you?
What? No.
- No?
- Maybe.
Shut up.
I freaked you out, didn't I?
Watching Rag Doll eat
while in Iron Heights is freaky.
Sure it is.
So, why the disappearing act?
Actually, let me posit a theory on that.
I think you're afraid
to use your powers,
because if you do,
you think you'll become like...
someone... someone...
someone you know.
Someone you...
hate.
How am I doing?
My cousin, Esperanza,
she has the same powers as me,
only she uses them to murder people.
You're not your cousin.
But if I start using my powers,
what's to stop me
from becoming like her?
Because, Allegra,
in this life we choose.
We choose who we are.
So if you choose
to use your incredible powers,
that does not make you
anything like Esperanza,
unless you choose that.
I'm not Esperanza.
Who are you?
- I'm Allegra.
- Yes.
Allegra Garcia.
Yes.
Well, that was anticlimactic.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Did I do it?
Yes.
I think you did.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
Mmm...
Like Alderaan on a bad day.
You look pretty
emotionally vaporized, too.
Okay, Chester. I...
I think that I was using your problems
as a distraction
from my own feelings,
and my internal compass
was completely off,
and that made me sense the opposite
of what Natalie was feeling,
and I'm so sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
I've had these powers for two years now
and I'm still figuring them out.
How are you feeling now?
Oh, uh...
Honestly, I don't know.
Well, let's pretend I'm the empath.
What kind of feelings would
you be putting off?
Now, now...
- Stare into my eyes.
- Okay.
And imagine my pupils are swirling...
and swirling, and swirling.
Okay, honey, that's a hypnotist,
not an empath,
but I really appreciate the effort,
yeah.
- Okay, right. Yeah.
- Uh...
How am I feeling? I'm...
Oh, my God. I'm freaking out.
You know, I was a DA for 20 years
and they just, boom,
replaced me overnight,
and now I feel like I don't exactly know
who I am anymore,
and if I fail at this meta-attorney
thing, I can't go back.
Yeah, but you didn't fail me.
You know, I think the two of us
just need to trust
that the real us will always
shine through.
Which is why I will embrace the new me
by finally asking out Natalie.
You know, seize the moment and all that.
Yeah.
And maybe you should, too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Maybe I should, too.
I should have
listened to you.
If we'd done things your way,
we wouldn't have gotten caught.
Maybe I should be handing Central City
over to Ralph Dibny
rather than Elongated Man.
What are you talking about?
There's no deposition.
I planned a press conference
to present you as Central City's
official protector.
Because of this coming Crisis,
I have to prepare the city
for a world without Flash.
Wow.
I'm, uh...
I'm honored...
that you think
that I could help fill your shoes.
Look, tonight's job was for Ralph Dibny.
Because both parts of my identity
have value.
The same is true for you.
Only tonight I could have used
your civilian half.
What I'm trying to say is,
Barry Allen...
is just as important as the Flash.
Try to remember that.
I know I will.
Now, can you reach my cufflink?
- What?
- Grab my cufflink.
Yeah. Got it.
All right, I got it.
Okay, on three,
I want you to flick it
at that laser cannon.
One, two, flick.
I got it. It's down.
Uh-oh.
- Whoa, watch out.
- What was that?
- Okay. Uh, what do we do?
- I don't know.
Uh, what do we do?
Ahhh!
How do we stop that?
- There's a pattern.
- Really?
All right, when I say "now..."
fling ourselves to the left.
- Right.
- The left.
Now!
We have to stop Meister.
He's got Ultraviolet protecting him.
Her powers could kill us both.
Let's do things your way.
With a little finesse.
Time to suit up.
Good evening, meine Freunde.
The moment that you've
all been waiting for is here.
Let the auction begin.
The EYE-3C9 satellite system...
or as I like to call it,
"The Ring of Fire,"
is equipped
with 15 dioptric long-range missiles.
Simply use this console to enter
your desired coordinates,
and then sit back
and watch hellfire rain down
on your enemies.
Perhaps a little demonstration now.
Yes?
This isn't the bathroom.
Sorry. Sorry.
Mr. Allen Barry.
I see you have found the open bar.
Keep her busy till I can get
to that console.
I'll bid on your stupid laptop.
Five hundred million.
Five hundred million and one... dollar.
Price is Right rules.
Ultraviolet,
gently escort Mr. Barry out,
but don't burn his money.
I love Mortal Kombat.
Mr. Dibny, we meet again.
You got to take it easy on
the Bond quotes, man.
Know what my favorite part is?
"Finish him."
You know, usually,
I allow Ultraviolet to do the killing...
but for you, I'll make an exception.
Come on.
Fire in the hole.
Thanks for dropping in.
Really? Adjusting your tie?
Adjusting the flash.
Nice job, man.
- Shocking.
- Your performance...
Wunderbar, Mr. Barry.
The name's Allen.
Barry Allen.
Remington Meister's crime ring is over.
Glad we got Remington,
but I'm sorry we didn't find Sue.
My nose tells me there's more
to that case than I imagined.
- You'll find her.
- I will.
And in the meantime,
I'll be busy keeping Central City safe.
- Still on for that ceremony today, Joe?
- Oh, yeah. See you there.
So did you do it?
Did you embrace your new identity?
Did you see Natalie?
Did you ask her out?
Did she say yes?
Yes. Yes. And... no.
Chester, I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
I've actually never felt better.
The last time I went to ask Natalie out,
I was scared as hell.
Today, I conquered that fear.
You know, she said no,
but I said "yes" to me.
All right, well,
I am very happy for you.
I think.
Hey, you're...
you're marketing your firm.
Yeah, yeah. It is the first step
in embracing the new me.
Ah.
You know, I wanted to thank you
for your encouragement.
And speaking of encouragement,
you know,
you'd fit in nicely at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Don't be a stranger.
That... would be so...
epic... epic... epic...
Epic.
Here you go.
Ah.
Better?
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Yeah. You're welcome.
Why are you being so nice today?
Let's just say you remind me of someone.
- Another doppelganger?
- Something like that. Hey, um...
Good job.
For the last five years,
I've tried to keep Central City safe.
But as new threats arise,
you'll need more than me.
Which is why I'm proud
to recognize a hero
who's put his life on the line
for this city time and time again.
A hero who deserves our recognition.
The Elongated Man.
Now, Central City has
another symbol of hope.
To every woman, every man
and every child listening today,
I have wanted to protect Central City
since before I ever even got my powers.
This is my home.
And I love it here.
And so today I hereby promise
that I will defend Central City...
with my dying breath.
Before we wrap up, there is someone
that Captain West and I
would like to bring up here.
CSI Barry Allen, please come up.
What are you doing?
Uh, those who wear capes and costumes
aren't the only ones that keep us safe.
There are some unsung heroes as well.
Like this man.
This man has solved crimes
to give mourning families justice.
He's a C.C.P.D. team member
who's never given up
on a single case.
This man has saved Central City
more times than anyone knows.
So it's time that we thank him.
It's time that... that I thank him.
So, without further ado...
Officer Barry Allen,
on behalf of C.C.P.D.,
we present you with their highest honor,
the Medal of Honor.
Thank you for your service.
Pretty cool, huh? Look how shiny it is.
Yeah, that's great, Ralph.
- Um, is this why you wanted to meet me?
- Yes.
And I want to show you this.
I took it at Meister's party.
I recognize that pin.
Guess who else showed up in Midway City.
Ultraviolet?
Thanks, Ralph. The Citizen's on it.
Great press conference.
I have a follow-up question.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::