- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
- Previously, on "The Flash"...
- The night that Savitar
kills you, you didn't have
a ring on your finger.
- We weren't engaged yet.
So you thought
that if we were...
- That it might
change the future.
- Now there's always gonna be
a part of us that's tainted.
- Why is Savitar hiding
in the Speed Force?
- That's where
the future you trapped him.
- That's right.
- I have what I need
to escape my hell, Wallace.
- Not everything; we still have
a piece of that stone.
- It's gone?
- If Savitar gets
ahold of the stone...
- He'll escape for sure.
- You can't get rid of
that stone, Wallace.
You're not fast enough to
throw it into the Speed Force
by yourself.
♪ ♪
Wally has taken my place
in the Speed Force.
- [grunting]
- We have to bring him back.
We have to save him.
- My fear is the reason
for all of this.
Savitar was right.
This is all because of me,
because of my weakness.
Flashpoint.
And because of it,
everyone's lives have changed.
Everyone I love is suffering.
This has to stop.
I can't let anyone hurt anymore
because of me.
No one else should
have to pay for my sins.
And they won't.
Ever again.
Cisco.
Get the breach room ready.
- Okay, for what?
- I'm gonna save Wally.
- How exactly are you
going to do that?
- I'm going back
into the Speed Force.
♪ ♪
- I'm just trying
to wrap my mind around
you going into
the Speed Force again.
The Savitar said he was
there for years.
You said it was like
being in space.
- I know.
- So what are you gonna do?
You gonna run in there and
run around till you find him?
It's endless.
- I know.
And this is the
only way to save Wally.
- Yeah, yeah, I just...
We need a plan.
I...I...
I don't wanna lose both my sons.
- Look, gang,
I don't understand
the Speed Force, but there are
plenty of people
in this room who do.
- Am I correct in assuming
there's a point coming?
- My point is why can't you use
your knowledge to fashion
some kind of safety precaution
for young BA right here so that,
while he's in the Speed Force,
he doesn't get lost.
- Oh, so you're saying
I can just whip up
some kind of
inter-dimensional tether
to just anchor him
to the Universe?
- Yeah.
- That's exactly what I can do.
- Yeah!
Now we're cooking with helium.
- Yes, and I can...I can add
a biological component
that will measure his vitals
when he's in the Speed Force.
- That's a great idea.
- Thank you, Caitlin.
- Because if we can
monitor Barry's vitals,
we'll know if they fluctuate,
and we can pull him out.
- You mean "pull us out."
Yeah, if you're going in there
to save Wally, so am I.
- Jesse, you're gonna stay here.
- Because if your father
finds out you're lost
in some negative world,
the first person
to get a broken schnoz is me.
- There's a negative world?
- Yeah, negative world.
- Really?
They have Super Mario
on Earth-29?
- Oh, yeah, challenge me.
- Barry, you need my help.
Your shoulder is still broken.
- It's okay.
It's almost healed.
- No, look, I can do this.
- I know, but I need you
to stay here.
Keep the city safe
while I'm gone.
And this is something
I have to do alone, okay?
- Fine.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Okay, let's go to work.
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna find Wally.
Whatever's holding him,
whatever's keeping him
trapped in there,
I'm gonna get him back.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
Iris...
Did I lose you?
♪ ♪
- Bar.
What's going on?
- Nothing, nothing,
I'm just trying to make her
not worry so much.
- About Wally or you?
- Joe, now's not
the time, all right?
- Look, you are about to risk
your life to save her brother.
I think now is the perfect time.
- She's having doubts about us.
About marrying me.
- Did she call off
the engagement?
- Guess I changed the future
one too many times.
♪ ♪
- I think that's gonna do it.
- We should be able to use this
to keep track of Barry's vitals.
- He'll play astronaut,
and we'll play Houston.
- Right, but how exactly are you
gonna track his location
when he's in the Speed Force?
- Well, this is just
a simple modification
from what we used to
get Barry out last time,
so the electrode halo?
- Julian wasn't part of
the team last time.
- Not yet.
- Oh, right.
You know that thing we used
to talk to Savitar?
- Yes.
- Meet the electrode halo.
So basically these two
are linked electromagnetically
via Goldtooth.
- Goldtooth?
- Yeah, it's kind of
the Cisco Ramon
interdimensional equivalent
of Bluetooth.
Kind of proud of it.
Anyway, it gives us all
the relevant locus information
no matter what corner of
the multiverse Barry's stuck in.
- And, if Barry needs our help,
it'll stimulate
Cisco's prefrontal cortex.
- And I'll open a breach and...
[pop]
Send him back in.
- Good Lord, multiverses,
breaches, halos,
easy bloody peasy.
- By George, I think
he's got it.
- Cisco, you about ready?
- Born ready.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Here's winging it.
- Winging it?
Wait, what do you mean?
- Well, I mean, I don't really
have a map of the Speed Force,
so when I vibe Barry into it...
- You have no idea
where I'm gonna land.
- But the good news is,
if he gets stuck
on the wrong side of the tracks,
now we can fish him out.
♪ ♪
- Find my boy.
- I'm gonna do
whatever it takes.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- I love you, Iris.
♪ ♪
- I love you too.
- Are we ready?
- Good to go.
♪ ♪
- To infinity and beyond.
Okay, once I let go,
you're on your own.
- Do it.
♪ ♪
- Good luck.
[thunder rumbles]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[thud]
- Wally?
[thunder rumbles]
♪ ♪
[thud]
Wally?
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbles]
Hello?
♪ ♪
- Hey, Bar.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Why are you here?
Why did you come back
to this place?
- I'm here to save Wally West.
- Ever the hero, huh, Barry?
- It's my fault that
he's trapped here.
- Is it?
- Where is Wally West?
- He's not exactly here, per se.
He's in the prison you created.
Well, your future self, that is.
- How do I get him out?
How do I get him out?
- I think you'll find
we're not gonna be
as accommodating as we were
the last time you visited us.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It means things have changed.
We gave you your speed back
because you said you'd
come to terms with
your mother's death,
but you lied to us.
- I...
- You went back in time
and saved her.
And, in doing so,
you created Flashpoint.
- Zoom had just
killed my father.
- We know, and we understand,
which is why we allowed you
to do that,
but choices have consequences.
And I'm afraid we can't let you
make any more choices like that.
- Wally is just a kid.
- He's a Flash.
He made his choice.
Now he has to live with it,
just like you do.
- I'm not going anywhere
until Wally's free.
- Then be prepared to spend
an eternity in here.
♪ ♪
- Why would you order
a single espresso?
It's gotta be at least
a double espresso.
I can go triple.
[slurps]
Doesn't affect me at all.
- Frightening.
- I can have
a quadruple, a sextuple.
Oh, there you are.
I'm gonna get us all coffees
'cause we got a lot
of work to do, you know?
A lot of...
A lot of stuff to do.
It doesn't affect me though.
It doesn't affect me at all!
- Okay.
He scares me.
- Yeah.
I was wondering,
do you think you could use this
to track Savitar's location?
- That's not a bad idea.
You know, I couldn't before
because he was
in the Speed Force, but,
now that he's out of it,
feeling footloose
and fancy-free, I'm sure...
I'm sorry, you know what?
That was insensitive of me.
- It's fine.
- Okay, so let's say
I find Savitar, right now.
What are you gonna do about it?
- I'm gonna go after him.
- Jesse, are you
out of your mind?
- No, okay?
I can't just sit here waiting.
- You can, and you will.
We all will.
And, soon enough, Barry's
gonna get Wally
out of the Speed Force.
- You don't know that, okay?
We don't know anything.
The only thing we actually know
is that Savitar is out there,
and, if we can,
we have to find him
and send him right back
where he came from.
- You're staying here.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- Iris.
- I wrote that article.
That used to be my byline,
but not anymore.
♪ ♪
- Well, 2024
is a long ways away.
Things could still change.
♪ ♪
- What if it's too late?
What if some things
can't be undone?
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- You having second thoughts?
- I guess I'm just worried
that I made the wrong decision.
- And what?
You think that calling
things off sent Barry
running into the Speed Force?
Please, we both know
that he was gonna
go save Wally no matter what.
- Yeah, that's just
the kind of hero he is.
♪ ♪
- Sweetheart, I know...
I know how you're feeling.
You can't figure out which way's
up right now, can you?
♪ ♪
Do yourself a favor.
Look deep inside that big,
beautiful heart of yours.
You'll find the answer
you're looking for.
♪ ♪
- Eddie Thawne's life
was almost so different.
Iris was about to be his wife.
Joe was about to be
his father-in-law.
But things didn't turn out
that way, did they, Barry?
[gunshot]
[thunder rumbles]
♪ ♪
Instead of that life
being his legacy...
This is.
♪ ♪
So the only reason you came back
is to save Wally.
- Yes.
- There's no other reason?
- No.
- All right then, Bar.
If you want Wally,
all you need to do
is go through those doors.
[ding]
♪ ♪
But you're gonna have to
outrun that thing first.
- [snarling]
- Time Wraith.
- [roars]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [shrieks]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[baby crying]
- ♪ Hush, little baby,
don't say a word ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you
a mockingbird ♪
- Caitlin.
[baby crying]
♪ ♪
- ♪ And if that mockingbird
don't sing ♪
♪ Mama's gonna buy you
a diamond ring ♪
- That baby...
♪ ♪
Is she...
- Beautiful.
Just like her mother.
- Ronnie.
- Hello, Barry.
We need to talk.
♪ ♪
- Perhaps some sort of new metal
akin to a Luttinger liquid?
What do you think?
- Man, I don't know
what this is.
All I know, it just came off
the armor of some
Hindu speed god, so...
- It's like the box
the philosopher's stone came in.
It simultaneously exists
and doesn't exist.
- Like Schroeder's cat.
Remember Schroeder?
Guy with the cat in the box
both dead and alive
at the same time, dun, dun, dun,
which, by the way,
seems like cruelty
for animals half the time.
- Okay, I think you're thinking
of Schrödinger, maybe?
- Schröding...no.
- Yeah, 'cause Schroeder's
the guys from "Peanuts."
- I don't think so.
- Yeah, the one with the piano.
- The...Charlie Brown
has the piano on my Earth.
That's the whole gag 'cause
he can't play the piano.
He's terrible.
- No.
- Oh, my God, who cares
about cats or pianos
or the freaking "Peanuts"?
- It's not "The Peanuts."
It's just "Peanuts."
- You have been
studying this thing for hours.
Can we or can we not use it
to track Savitar?
- Okay, all right, wind it in.
- As far as we can tell,
the shard is made
of near-frictionless material
that's in a constant
state of flux.
- So while it's utterly
motionless on the outside...
- It's constantly moving
on the inside.
- Yes, it's as if it's being
affected by some sort
of external source,
much like the tides are affected
by the phases of the moon.
- Okay, okay, then it
has to be Savitar.
I mean, this was
part of his armor.
Maybe it's trying to reconnect
with its other pieces.
- That's it.
It's just like
"The Iron Giant."
If this is true, then this shard
could lead us right to him.
- That's an idea.
- Okay, all right,
so what are we waiting for?
Let's...
[ping]
- Hold your roll, Jesse Quick.
This hesitation that you feel,
on behalf of the group,
is our realization that
this "go for broke" attitude
is the very attitude that
got Wallace in his predicament
in the first place.
Am I right?
- I can't believe
I'm uttering the words,
but I actually agree with H.R.
- Ditto.
- Thanks, boys.
- A lone speedster...
It's just no match for Savitar.
- Yeah, but...
- Jesse, we're gonna find him.
- When?
- When the real Flash gets back.
That came out wrong, um...
- Wow.
- Put my foot in it.
Jesse, Jesse!
Oh, Jesse, hey, Jesse,
quick question:
Merlot or Cabernet?
- What?
- What wine do you think
would go best with a big, old
men's size 11 shoe
stuffed in his mouth?
- H.R.?
- Yeah?
- Just leave me alone.
- I get it, I get it.
I get...
Savitar...Savitar hurt
the one you love,
now you wanna hurt Savitar.
- Yeah, bet your ass, I do.
- No, I get it.
I...I love it.
I respect it.
I'm a little worried though
that, in your zeal for payback,
you might be the one
who ends up getting hurt.
- On my Earth...
- Yeah.
- I am the real Flash.
- I know.
That's why I...
[gagging]
I should've said what I said.
- No, no, you
shouldn't have, okay?
'Cause I've fought
plenty of monsters before.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Like Savitar, though?
'Cause, look, here's the thing.
If your father
were here, he would...
- Do everything in his power
to stop Savitar.
And that is exactly
what I'm gonna do.
- [laughs]
Okay, okay.
I mean, hats off to you.
You really are Hard-Hat Harry's
little girl, aren't you?
- Yeah, I am,
and you're not him.
So just do us both a favor
and stop trying to be.
♪ ♪
- This troubles you.
Another life that
could've been and never was.
♪ ♪
- Caitlin and Ronnie
should've had that.
A family, a future.
- The future doesn't always
turn out as we want it to.
♪ ♪
- I see what you're doing.
First Eddie, now Ronnie,
showing me all of the people
who sacrificed themselves
for the greater good.
- No, Barry, their sacrifices
were for you,
as was Wally's when he
attempted to stop Savitar.
- No, Savitar tricked Wally.
And now he's trapped.
Wally doesn't belong
in the Speed Force.
You have to let me
take his place.
And that's why I'm here.
- Or the other reason, Barry.
- I wanna sacrifice
myself for Wally.
- We can't allow that.
- Why not?
- Because where Wally's gone
is a hell all his own.
- Savitar said, "One will suffer
a fate far worse than death."
- And it's not for you.
Leave, Barry,
while you still can.
♪ ♪
- No.
Whatever hell
Wally's trapped in,
I'm gonna set him free,
and I'm not leaving here
until I do.
- Very well,
but you were warned.
- [snarling]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [roars]
- Hunter Zolomon.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Come on, come on.
- [shrieks]
[ding]
♪ ♪
[roars]
- Is it Barry?
- Did something happen to him?
- We don't know.
One second, the telemetry
was perfectly normal, and...
- Then his vitals,
they just started crashing.
- We warned you.
- Why are you doing this?
- You speak of sacrifice,
yet you still let others
bear the burdens that
should be on your shoulders.
- [gasping]
Okay, okay, you're right.
You're right.
I never should've
asked Wally to save Iris.
It should've been me.
[yells]
Please, let me save him.
- There's only one way
to free Wally West
from his eternal torment.
You must free yourself first.
- [roars]
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
I love you, Iris.
- [roars]
[beeping]
- No.
- Cisco, is he...
- I don't know, I don't know.
- Find out!
- I can't.
The tether's gone.
- What?
That was him and Wally's
lifeline out of the Speed Force.
- How are we gonna
get them back?
- I don't know that we can.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Hello?
♪ ♪
Wally?
Wally, Wally!
I'm gonna get you out, okay?
Just hang on.
[zap]
- Visiting hours
are over, Flash.
♪ ♪
- So...
That's not yours.
- Get out of my way.
- I can't do that.
Not if you're planning on
using that to fight Savitar.
I can't.
- You're not gonna
talk me out of this, okay?
I already told you you're not...
- Not your dad.
That message was received
loud and clear.
Now hear mine.
Taking on Savitar
all alone
is not gonna bring
Wallace back, Jesse.
It's just gonna get
you killed, and that,
my friend, that is
not happening.
Not on my watch.
- You done?
- Yeah, said my piece.
And guess what?
I'm still not...
[smack]
Moving...
[thud]
♪ ♪
- That was oddly satisfying.
- What's happening to him?
- Wally West is caught
in an endless temporal loop,
just like Savitar
after you imprisoned him here
in the future.
No wonder he hates you.
♪ ♪
- What's he seeing?
- He's reliving the single
most painful moment of his life
over and over again.
His mother's death.
- Wally.
He doesn't deserve this.
- Let me guess.
You do?
- I know what my hell is.
I've already seen it
in the future.
- You don't like
the future, Flash?
Change it.
- I can't.
Don't you get it?
I can't!
I'm not fast enough.
He is.
♪ ♪
That's why you have to
let me take his place.
Wally can save Iris.
- Not learning
your lesson, Barry.
You keep telling us one thing
and then doing another.
♪ ♪
You wanna know what
inspired Leonard Snart
to sacrifice himself?
It was you, Barry Allen.
You inspired him to be better.
You inspired him to be selfless,
to sacrifice himself for others,
to be a hero, just like you.
- I'm no hero.
Not lately.
- So what?
You've had enough,
Scarlet Speedster?
Time to hang up the cowl
and give it all up?
Well, if you're out...
You're out.
- I'm done fighting.
- We know, and that's
exactly the problem.
[zap]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- You think seeing
Iris' death is hell?
You ain't seen nothing yet.
[zap]
♪ ♪
- Let's get you out of here.
- All right, you stupid
piece of metal,
take me to your leader.
♪ ♪
Gotcha.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Jesse Quick.
I knew you would come for me.
♪ ♪
- How'd you know
I was coming here?
- Because I know everything
that happens.
I've already lived it.
- I'm not afraid of you.
- You should be.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[electric crackling]
- [grunts]
- Jesse.
- H.R.?
It's a little late to talk me
out of this, okay?
- I'm not gonna try
and talk you out of anything.
I learned that lesson.
- You have something
that belongs to me.
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
I need a little help here, H.R.
- Bum, bum, thinking.
- Think faster.
- What do we got?
We're fighting Savitar.
Savitar is a speed god.
He's omnipotent.
He's invulnerable.
Then why does he need
a suit of armor?
- [grunts]
- Jesse, he's vulnerable
somewhere under the suit.
Find a gap, find an opening,
and go for it.
- [grunts]
- I have such plans for you
in the future, Jesse Quick.
- And I have plans for you too.
This is for Wally.
- Ahh!
- Yeah!
- [roars]
♪ ♪
- Jay.
- Yeah?
- Is this really you,
or is this just
another Speed Force test?
- Yeah, kid, it's really me.
- How?
- As soon as the team
lost contact with you,
Cisco came to my Earth
and told me what was happening.
I came here to help.
Let's get Wally.
[zap]
- [grunts]
- 'Fraid I can't
let you do that.
Getting a little slow in
your golden age there, Garrick.
- Stop.
- Can't do that either.
[zap]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[zap]
- Enough!
I'm taking Wally.
- We can't let you
do that, Barry.
- Yeah?
Try and stop me.
♪ ♪
[vibrating]
Wally?
♪ ♪
Hey, Wally.
[machines beeping]
Hey.
- Barry, Jay.
[sniffling]
I saw my mom.
- I know, I know.
- My mom.
- I know.
Look at me now, okay?
It's over.
You're free now, okay?
We're going home, all right?
It's okay.
We're going home.
♪ ♪
Jay, let's go.
- Sorry, kid, this is
where I stay for a while.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- We both know that a speedster
needs to take Wally's place.
That's why I'm here.
- No, no, Jay, you already
lived your hell
when you were Zoom's prisoner.
- And you set me free,
and I owe you for that.
- Jay...
- I've run a hell of a race,
but every marathon
has a finish line.
Time's finally come for me
to cross it, but you...
You, Barry, need to put
an end to this once and for all
and stop Savitar.
♪ ♪
- How?
- Do what you do best.
Be The Flash.
[thunder rumbling]
♪ ♪
Cisco said that he could
use this to track you
and bring you home.
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna get this
back to you again
when I break you out of here.
♪ ♪
- See you soon, Flash.
[electric crackling]
- What's happening?
Do you think you can
reel them in?
- I don't know.
I've never felt this much
harmonic feedback.
It feels like
the Speed Force is about to...
♪ ♪
- Wally!
- Barry!
- Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
- We will be.
♪ ♪
- Hold on a second.
Three speedsters go in,
and only two come out.
- Jay...
Jay stayed back to save Wally.
♪ ♪
- Come on, Wally,
let's get you checked out.
♪ ♪
- I thought I lost both my boys.
Thanks for bringing him back.
- You're welcome.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- I thought I'd lost you too.
♪ ♪
- I'm right here.
[dramatic music]
- The Speed Force.
And it just appeared to you
in the form of Eddie Thawne?
- And Ronnie?
- And Snart.
All to teach me another lesson.
- Which was what?
- Saving Iris
is my responsibility
and mine alone.
It's why the Speed Force didn't
let me take Wally's place,
why Jay sacrificed
himself to do it.
So I could finish this.
- Jay, hero among heroes.
- Yeah.
- We can't just
leave him in there.
- We won't.
I'll beat Savitar.
We'll get him out.
- Good, 'cause it seems to me
the Speed Force
is a little bit
of a crazy place.
Just ask Wallace.
- Yeah, yeah, what...
What Wally saw...
It's gonna haunt him
for a while.
So until he can get past it,
and he's really ready
to go back out there,
Kid Flash is gonna
need to take a break
for a while.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
You okay?
- Are you?
- Right, you should see
the other guy.
Caitlin said I'll be fine.
- Jesse, I can't believe you
went after Savitar by yourself.
What were you thinking?
- I mean, the same thing
you were when you did it.
- Yeah, that was a mistake.
One that I will
never make again.
- Yeah, yeah, me either.
Not on this Earth, anyway.
- Wait, what?
You're going back
to Earth-2 already?
- Earth-3, actually.
- But you just got here, Jesse.
- I know, I know, and
I want to be with you.
It's just Savitar said he had
plans for me in the future.
And I can't let that happen.
Besides, until Barry can get
Jay out of the Speed Force,
Earth-3 needs
a Flash to protect it.
♪ ♪
- I love you, Jesse.
- I love you too.
♪ ♪
- You show those villains
on Earth-3.
Nobody messes
with our Jesse Quick.
- That's right.
You give them hell.
- You know I will.
- We're here
if you need us, all right?
Safe travels.
- Thanks.
Sorry for the, uh...
- Yeah, yeah, me too.
Good left-hook.
- Thanks.
- I shouldn't be surprised.
Us Wellses...
We are forces
to be reckoned with.
- That we are.
Thank you, H.R.
- For what?
- Just being a friend.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
- You ready?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- This isn't good-bye.
- No, it's more like
"see you later."
- I can't wait.
♪ ♪
- So, fun fact uncovered
by our intrepid Jesse Quick,
in her latest dust-up with
the so-called "God of Speed,"
guess who feels pain.
- What...what exactly
are you saying?
Are you saying that underneath
the suit of armor that's he's...
- Yes, James.
He's not a god.
He's just a man, baby.
- A man?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- [sighs]
- Thank you for saving Wally.
- Of course.
Um, so, I just...
Look, you told me that you only
wanted to marry someone
because they love you
and not because they were
trying to save you,
and I get that.
I just...
You know, I've lived with a lot
of death, tragedy in my life,
and seeing you die...
♪ ♪
It's impossible not to be
consumed by that.
- Yeah, no, I get that.
I do.
It just...
It made me question
if you were asking me
for the right reasons, you know?
If it was out of love
or responsibility.
♪ ♪
But, hey, look,
while you were gone,
I realized something.
I don't have to doubt
why you wanna marry me.
It's the same reason
that I wanna marry you.
I wanna be your wife, Barry.
♪ ♪
- Um...
I love you.
♪ ♪
But, uh...
You were right.
I proposed because
I thought it would save you.
I thought Wally would save you.
I...I was wrong.
I alone have to save you
in the future, and I'm going to,
but not by changing it.
By embracing it.
- Okay, um...
What...what does that mean?
- It means that I...I think
we need some space
for a while.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, but...I...I don't...
I don't know how we can
move forward like this, with...
♪ ♪
- Um...
Okay.
♪ ♪
I guess I'll go to my dad's.
- No, you stay here.
I'll...I'll stay with Cisco.
♪ ♪