BARRY:
I'm getting faster. Faster than I've ever been.
I wonder if it's because lately
something's chasing me.
I know what it is that's stalking me.
It's my past.
It's getting closer. And as fast as I am...
...I can't help but feel like my past
has almost caught up with me.
EDDIE: Where's Barry?
-Should be here any second.
-I sent him out for...
-Pizza.
-What?
EDDIE: From Coast City?
Supposedly the best in the west.
Why did I not think of this before?
-Come to papa.
-Caitlin?
I'm not hungry.
Okay. Six months of investigating
Harrison Wells has led us nowhere.
So we're going back to the beginning
to see what we can find out.
-What does that mean?
-Road trip, baby.
Joe and Cisco are gonna go to Starling City.
-What for?
-To investigate the car accident...
...Dr. Wells was in
with Tess Morgan 15 years ago.
I don't understand. Why?
Dr. McGee said that after Wells's accident
he became, like, a complete stranger.
-Just a different person entirely.
-Because the love of his life died?
You, of all people, can understand
how grief can change a person.
Caitlin, we believe that Dr. Wells is the
Reverse-Flash and killed Barry's mother.
He may have done
the same thing to Tess Morgan.
We have to learn everything we can
about that night. See where it leads us.
Oh, um, can you cover for me?
With Dr. Wells?
You mean lie?
Yeah.
I need some air.
BARRY:
Caitlin.
Doesn't look like Caitlin's with us.
No. She's with us. I'll talk to her.
What do you want us to do here?
-Business as usual while we're gone.
-Copy that.
Come on.
I wanna wish you good luck,
but I'm also scared of what you might find.
Scared is a good thing.
Scared keeps us alive.
WOMAN:
Can you get the door, Nina? Nina?
Oh. Sorry.
Wrapped up in my own little world.
Late night?
Just one more thing to do
before I make my escape.
-See you tomorrow.
-Night.
EDDIE:
So let's go over this again.
This is you on
the surveillance footage, correct?
It looks like me.
But it's not me.
I left work early yesterday.
Ask my husband.
Footage doesn't lie. Your husband might.
NINA:
That's not me.
No priors. No arrests.
Not even a speeding ticket.
Everyone who knows this woman,
co-workers, neighbors...
...say she's the kindest, nicest,
most honest woman they've ever met.
So unless she woke up this morning...
...and out of nowhere,
decided to become a criminal...
Maybe we should be looking
for a metahuman.
-Yeah.
-One that can control people's minds.
Coerce them into becoming thieves.
Is that possible?
-Is that a real question?
-Hi, Barry.
Hey.
Have you, um, seen my dad?
Captain Singh says he took a couple days
off, and he hasn't been home.
I didn't ask. Apparently,
he's taking a couple of personal days.
Like father, like daughter, I guess.
I'm sorry.
When are you coming home?
When it starts to feel like a home again.
Better pray Joe and Cisco find something
on Wells at that accident site, Barry.
Because I am just about done lying to Iris.
About all of this.
Yeah.
MAN:
I recently inherited the entire collection.
Beautiful.
-Let me grab my microscope.
-Of course.
WOMAN [ON PHONE]: 911 emergency.
-This is Dominic over at Abbot Jewelers.
I've got a guy in here
trying to sell stolen diamonds.
BARRY: Good morning.
CAITLIN: Hey.
Hey, look, uh, can we talk about last night?
-There's nothing to talk about.
-There is, actually...
Caitlin, look. I know after everything
Dr. Wells has done for all of us...
...it's hard to wrap your head around this,
but I need you to see the truth.
The truth?
The truth is that he saved
your life multiple times.
Look, I know, but if I'm right about this...
If, Barry. If. And before I can believe any
of this, I'm gonna need to see some proof.
Proof? Proof of what?
We may have another metahuman case
on our hands.
We are always happy to help, Barry,
as you know.
Have you heard from Cisco?
He hasn't arrived yet.
Uh, he has to help Dante, his brother.
He might need a few days off.
WELLS:
Ah.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
All right.
-Eddie.
EDDIE [ON PHONE]: Hey.
I got a call about a guy selling
jewelry stolen from the bank last night.
Could be the teller's partner.
I think he's made me.
I could use the Flash's help.
Be right there.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
You can't outrun me.
I won't have to.
[WOMAN GASPS]
Well, that was new.
-A shape-shifter?
-Yeah. I literally saw a grown man, like...
...morph into a teenage girl.
WELLS:
That's fascinating.
Today's physicists have always
regarded programmable matter...
...as nothing more than a theory...
...but I guess your shape-shifter
proves it can be done.
Wait, so he or she or...
Whatever, this person can actually...
...transform into anyone they touch?
Yes, it appears so.
That includes you Mr. Allen.
Dr. Wells is right. If you're touched
while you're the Flash and he transforms...
...we run the risk of him exposing that
Barry Allen is the man behind the mask.
We don't know if the shape-shifter
is capable of absorbing more...
-...than just physical characteristics.
-He might be able to copy my speed.
That would be bad.
Got it. Hands off the metahuman.
Hands off the metahuman.
So how do we find someone
who can transform into anyone?
I guess like any problem,
go back to the beginning.
Find the first person
the shape-shifter morphed into...
-...when they discovered their powers.
-Pull up the C.C.P.D. records of cases...
...where the perpetrator plead innocent
when they were on camera...
-...committing the crime.
-You're good, Barry Allen. You're very good.
Look at this.
Multiple crimes of this manner.
All dating back to a month
after the particle-accelerator explosion.
And the first one was?
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Jacob Fisher,
a teller at the federal credit union.
Claims he was innocent
and was framed by his best friend...
...a Hannibal Bates.
I'll pass this on to the C.C.P.D.
See if they can track him.
-Good.
-Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Always here to help, Barry.
LANCE:
There it is.
-This is all you have?
-It's a pretty cut-and-dry case, detective.
Harrison Wells,
Tess Morgan are on a Sunday drive.
The tires blow.
Wells loses control,
and, uh, sadly, Tess dies on the scene.
Couldn't imagine carrying that kind of guilt.
So, uh...
...what are you two hoping to find?
-We're not exactly sure yet.
-All the way from Central City.
-You don't know what you're looking for?
-Following a hunch.
Uh, can you take us to the accident site?
It's been 15 years.
The pictures would serve you better.
Still, we'd appreciate a look.
Whatever you need.
Captain, I need those witness statements
for the Joshua Brown trial.
Um, yeah, well, like I told you. End of day.
Sorry. Uh, Detective West, Cisco Ramon.
This is ADA Laurel Lance.
Related?
Daughter.
Hi. Hi.
Hey there.
You work at S.T.A.R. Labs
with Barry Allen, right?
-Uh, yeah.
-Can I talk to you privately for a minute?
Sure.
LANCE:
So, uh, how is Allen?
Not too messed up from getting hit
by that lightning?
Uh, no.
No.
How do you know Barry?
Are you guys friends or something?
Not really.
We met last time he was in Starling City.
Visiting my friends.
John Diggle, Felicity Smoak
and Oliver Queen.
Three people who have
absolutely nothing in common.
-As far as I know.
-Cisco.
I know Barry's the Flash
and Oliver's the Arrow.
Pfft. Heh.
How do you know that?
[SOFTLY]
Because...
...I'm the Black Canary.
Stop playing.
-It's true. Heh-heh.
-You stop it right now.
No.
[LAUGHING]
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
I love you.
I mean, I love the way that you...
...beat up criminals.
[LAUGHS]
Wait...
...why are you telling me this?
Because I need some technical expertise.
I've been using my sister's sonic device.
I was hoping you could help...
...modify it.
Yeah.
I think I got some ideas.
Great.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
[EXHALES]
[TRANQUIL PIANO MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
What?
Are you spying on me now?
-What were you doing at Wells's house?
-I was gonna talk to him...
...and get some answers of my own.
You can't. You cannot talk to him.
Oh, so I'm just supposed to stand by
and watch all of you ruin this man's life?
Ruin my life?
What are you talking about, "your life"?
Those nine months...
...that you were in a coma...
...were the worst of my life.
I lost my reputation, my fiancé...
...and through all of that...
...Harrison Wells stood by my side.
He told me everything was gonna be okay.
If Dr. Wells is who you say he is...
...everything I've done since the minute
I stepped foot in S.T.A.R. Labs...
...has been a lie.
Caitlin.
If I am right about all of this...
...and you tell him what's been going on...
...I'll never be able to get my dad
out of prison.
-Barry.
-Look, if not for me, just do it for him.
I can't believe you're pulling the "dad" card.
[CHUCKLES]
It's dirty pool, Barry.
Just until Joe and Cisco get back.
Please.
Turns out Hannibal Bates
hasn't been seen in well over a year.
The only remaining relative
is his grandmother.
She took out a missing-persons report...
...a couple of days
after the Jacob Fisher arrest.
I figured we could ask her a few questions.
Like why anyone in their family thought
that naming a kid "Hannibal"...
...wouldn't mean he'd grow up
to be a criminal.
Have you heard from your grandson
Hannibal recently, Mrs. Bates?
-Recently? No.
BARRY: Uh-huh.
Why do you ask?
Oh, please.
Um...
Because you filed
a missing-persons report...
...over a year ago.
Oh, yes. I certainly did.
You'll have to forgive me, detective.
My memory is not quite as it used to be.
Of course.
And neither apparently are my manners.
May I get you two something?
Coffee? Tea?
No, thank you, ma'am. We're fine.
Oh, please.
It'll only take a minute.
It's nice to have visitors.
Coffee would be nice.
Thanks.
Ma'am, would you happen to have
a recent photograph of Hannibal?
[CLOCK CHIMES]
Ma'am?
She's gone.
I'll take the front.
Hey, we located Bates.
He was impersonating his grandma.
Barry, do not let him touch you.
-Or let him see you use your speed.
-How am I supposed to catch him?
WELLS:
The old-fashioned way.
Run like a normal person.
Okay, all right.
Oh, man...
[SIREN WAILING]
-What do you want us to do, Thawne?
-Die.
[BOTH GRUNT]
Barry, call 911.
[SIREN WAILING]
COP: What do you want us to do, Thawne?
-Die.
[GUNSHOT ON TV]
I know what this looks like, Cecile.
It looks like one of your detectives
shot two of your cops.
-Both are fighting for their lives.
-That's not what happened.
I am the district attorney. I can't ignore
what I watched because you want me to.
There are things going on
in this city that can't be explained.
Come on, David. Until you show me
something incontrovertible...
...the best I can do...
...is promise to keep him out
of gen pop at Iron Heights.
Do you have any way
of explaining this, Allen?
I'm working on it.
-Barry.
-Iris.
What is going on?
Everyone is saying Eddie shot two cops.
-How is that possible?
-Not sure yet.
-You don't think he did this?
-No. Of course not.
-I need to see him.
-Hey. You can't see him, all right?
They're not gonna let you.
I'm gonna do everything I can to help him.
-Okay.
-Okay?
Okay. I'm so sorry.
-It's gonna be okay.
-Okay.
I promise. All right?
JOE:
This is definitely the place.
Cisco, let's see what we can find.
What is that, a metal detector?
Uh, essentially, only instead of listening
for metal objects...
...I'm listening for anything
that emits an abnormal sound wave.
Right.
-Where'd you find this kid?
-It's a long story.
So it must be interesting having a daughter
who's also the DA.
Yeah, interesting is the word.
-I have a daughter.
-Same line of work?
No. I wouldn't let her near this nonsense.
-Ha-ha. Smart guy.
-Overprotective.
LANCE:
You two get along?
We don't always see eye-to-eye,
but no matter how mad she gets at me...
...or how mad I get at her,
there's a strong bond.
Why? You two have a bit of a rough patch?
Yeah, she, uh...
She kept something from me.
You know, something important.
Lied to me about it for months.
Hard to come back
from something like that.
Did she give a reason?
Not one I could accept.
Ah. Well, sometimes, we lie for love.
Especially when it comes to family, right?
CISCO: Joe!
-Yeah?
I think we got something.
-Tachyons. Little bits of time travel.
-You sure?
[RUMBLING]
Pretty sure, yeah.
I didn't shoot those officers.
The captain certainly pled your case.
The results of the GSR swab.
Detective Thawne's hands are free
of lead, barium, and antimony.
Yet no one can seem to explain
how the surveillance video clearly shows...
...Thawne firing his weapon.
-It only looked like Detective Thawne.
-Mr. Allen, no.
Aren't you supposed to be the scientist
around here?
It's hard to blame her.
That video is pretty damning.
No, no, we just have to convince her.
Seeing is believing, Barry.
They're gonna put me away.
Okay, look. Get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
They'll set you with a burner phone.
-I'll contact you...
-No.
I run now, that video is the least
of my problems.
No way I don't smell guilty.
No way they'll let me stay.
You said it yourself. If we don't find
Hannibal Bates, you go to prison.
For a crime you didn't commit.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
This isn't like your dad, Barry.
Eddie, look.
When your dad was put away,
you were a kid.
There wasn't anything you could do.
But you're not a kid anymore.
You're a scientist. Hell...
...you're the Flash.
You are gonna find Bates,
and you are gonna clear me.
So go do it.
All right.
Get me out of here the right way.
BARRY:
I promise, Iris.
I'm just here to shower and change,
and then I'm going to my lab.
I swear I'm gonna get Eddie
out of this. Okay?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'll call you later, all right?
Eddie? What in the world?
How did you get out?
Captain Singh called in a favor.
Got a judge to sign my release.
I was on the phone with Iris.
Why haven't you called her? Hold on.
[BOTH GRUNT]
I have no idea who she is.
Heh.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Barry, it's me.
Hello...
...you.
I figured a way to stop our shape-shifter
from morphing into other people.
Oh, really?
What if I create a serum that will terminate
the polymerization reaction?
Essentially forcing the bonds
to revert to their original form.
Stop him from being able
to control his power.
You can do that?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Look, about last night...
...I can't imagine how hard
this must be for you.
I mean, I know how desperate you are
to solve your mom's murder.
But...
...let's just bury the hatchet,
and we'll go back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Figure out how to catch this "Everyman."
"Everyman"?
Bad nickname?
No.
No, I kind of like it.
Okay, good. Me too.
[CISCO GRUNTING]
Wait. Hold up, Cisco.
Please tell me that's not what I think it is.
LANCE:
Okay, that is definitely a hand.
Okay, see, I thought it was a foot,
but a hand is just as bad.
That is freaky.
-That is proof, Cisco.
-I'll need to test it to be certain.
I'm gonna grab my kit.
I'm gonna have to call this one in.
I can't let you do that.
And I'm asking you, cop to cop...
...keep this under wraps.
Forget you ever saw it.
-West, I can't do that.
-Listen.
Lance. If this is who I think it is...
...anybody that knows about this
is in a lot of danger.
Including my daughter.
As mad as you are at Laurel...
...I can't imagine you wouldn't do
anything to protect her.
[LANCE SIGHS]
Hey.
Good to go. Just need to...
...give it a little spin.
Oh.
Right.
Yes, spin.
So this, uh...
...serum that you're making,
is it a temporary fix?
Or will it take away
his power permanently?
Not permanently.
Just long enough so we can stop him.
And how long is it going to take?
Not long.
We just need...
What are you doing?
Something...
...I think I should've done...
...a long time ago.
Barry. Uh...
[BEEPING]
Oh, my God.
Look who's here.
Yes. Her.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Here I am. What's up?
Whoever is framing Eddie, I got to thinking.
What if they've done this before?
I went through CCPN's crime archives...
...and in 11 months, there have been
six crimes committed by people...
...who later swore they were innocent.
None of them had priors.
All of them had rock-solid alibis.
-All right.
-So...
...I hacked into my dad's C.C.P.D. account...
...and went through the footage
of Eddie shooting those cops.
-Look.
FAKE EDDIE: Die.
What's wrong with you?
Huh? Nothing, I didn't do anything.
FAKE BARRY:
I don't know.
Seems pretty convincing to me.
Look again.
Eddie is not left-handed.
Look, Eddie is being framed.
And we need to figure out
who's behind this.
Believe me, when I get my hands on them,
they are going to be...
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING
AND FAKE BARRY GRUNTING]
Oh! What did you do?
Your observations about the shooter
were spot-on, Miss West.
He was indeed left-handed.
As is this man.
Our Barry...
...is right-handed.
Oh, I knew it.
-Never mind.
-Then this is him.
It is indeed.
I need to take him in to the police.
If they can see what he can do,
they'll let Eddie go.
Perhaps it might be best
if Dr. Snow and I handled this.
What are you two going to do?
No, no, no. I'm taking him in.
Of course.
Well, at least let me help you.
There is a reporter at work who kept a file
of these sorts of things.
You know,
all the unexplained events in the city.
This guy...
...definitely belongs in that file.
That's gonna be a pretty big file.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You know who else is in that file?
The Burning Man.
Really? What about him?
I thought he was just some urban legend.
GIRL:
Help me!
-Help me! Help me! Help me!
-Oh, no.
Someone please help me!
Help me!
These bad ladies have kidnapped me.
-What's going on here?
GIRL: I need help.
I need help!
These mean ladies kidnapped me!
We did not kidnap her.
-Iris, drive.
-I can't.
-Call the police.
-No.
No, no, no. She's dangerous.
MAN: Hey.
-She's dangerous. No!
Where are you going?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Oh. Barry.
[BARRY GROANING]
Agh! For real?
-Why did you slap me?
-You were unconscious.
Smelling salts work just as well.
Sorry. Are you okay?
I think so, yeah.
Wait, Caitlin. Bates, he was here.
-Yes, I know.
-Okay, let's go.
You sure there's nothing else
I can do for you, detective?
You have done more than enough.
Thank you for everything, captain.
I should be thanking you
for getting me out the office for a day.
Pushing papers, reviewing budgets,
public all over my ass. It's a nice change.
I'd still be detective if I could, but you know,
body just can't take it anymore.
What you gonna do
when you got a bad heart?
I can think of something
that might make things better.
Cisco.
Laurel, hey.
Uh, we're just about to head back
to Central City.
Were you able to make that item?
I think this will do the trick.
I bumped up the specs.
Quadrupled the range,
tripled the resonance.
Should be able to do
some serious damage with this thing.
I can't believe you were able
to make it so quickly.
Eh. I've had some practice
with sound waves recently.
I think you should call it the "Canary Cry."
I like it.
Thank you.
As promised.
Hey. You show this to anyone, I'll kill you.
Heh. It's just an expression, right?
Nope.
Cisco, you good?
Oh, I'm good.
Hannibal Bates has turned
into quite the metahuman. Take a look.
His cells have the ability
to transmogrify at quite the rate.
BARRY:
Which is how he can become anyone.
How he can look like anyone.
Because he cannot appropriate...
-...your memory or your powers.
-Got it.
-Hands on the metahuman.
To help you do that, Dr. Snow has concocted
a solution we believe will stop him.
Yes, I've made a serum that will create
a cortical reaction around his cells.
Deprive those cells
of their electrical charge...
...his shape-shifting days are over.
-Wow, that's great work.
-Ah!
Thank you. Um...
No need for a hug or anything like that.
Okay.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Barry, we got a ping
from your cell phone. Looks like...
...Hannibal Bates is at the airport.
Payback time.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Are we sure he's at the airport?
According to your phone. He's there.
Yeah, but...
...he could be any of these people.
I'm not seeing him.
Gotcha.
Hannibal Bates!
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
Wait, it's me.
Please, don't hurt me.
[FLASH GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Not so hero-like.
You treat all your women like that?
Look at that.
I'm the Flash.
You may look like me...
...but you're not as fast.
You're done imitating innocent people.
[SHRIEKING]
CAITLIN [OVER COMM]: Barry?
-Yeah.
The one and only.
Detective Thawne has been released.
CECILE: I have to admit,
this is new territory for me.
This is new territory for all of us.
I certainly don't think the law is prepared
to deal with this kind of criminal.
Hopefully, we can catch up fast.
It's hard to believe we live in a world
where this kind of impossible even exists.
Luckily, it's also a world
where the Flash exists.
Uh, speaking of...
...he left this list of all the robberies
that Hannibal Bates was involved in.
That's a long list.
With just as many innocent people
whose names need to be cleared.
You know, I saw the Flash once.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
I was on my way to the courthouse.
He blew past me.
It was just a blur of red and a gust of wind.
But it was pretty damn cool.
Heh.
Iris.
All charges have been dropped.
I'm clear to go.
Oh, thank God.
Iris...
...I need to tell you something.
You know what?
It can wait until we get home.
You were right.
I was hiding something from you.
You deserve to know the truth.
The reason I've been so distant lately...
...I've been working with the Flash.
Let me out of here!
Hey, cutie. Wanna let me out of here?
Like anyone would be dumb enough
to fall for that. Heh.
[SIGHS]
I've seen a lot of things
that you can become, but...
...who are you, Hannibal Bates?
I, uh... Heh.
I can't remember.
Well, let's lock up shop.
Good night, everyone.
What about Dr. Wells?
Come here.
I need to show you something.
This isn't possible.
Caitlin...
...I ran the DNA test twice.
It's a perfect match.
This body is the real Harrison Wells.
CAITLIN:
If this is Dr. Wells...
...then who have we been working for
this whole time?
BARRY:
Dr. McGee said that after the accident...
...Wells became
a completely different person.
It's because he is a different person.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Dr. Wells.
-You here on business?
-Business? No.
I came to give my regards
to Detective Thawne.
I'm glad it all worked out.
Yeah. A crazy day for him.
Yeah.
Crazy day for us all.
Oh.
Detective, did you enjoy
your time in Starling City?
Not much time for sightseeing.
I was working on a case.
-You used to live there?
-I did.
You ever go back?
No.
Too many memories of Tess.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
You, detective...
...are one of the few people I know that...
...truly understands that kind of loss.
Iris's mother.
You never talk about her, do you?
No.
I don't.
You and I, detective...
...are members of a rather exclusive club...
...I suppose.
One whose membership is too expensive.
Maybe we should have
another drink sometime.
Talk about it.
Yeah.
Yeah. We should do that.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
What are you doing?
After the accelerator exploded,
I built a 3D model of S.T.A.R. Labs...
...so I could pinpoint
what caused the malfunction.
BARRY:
And you never ran this test?
Of course I did. I just never had
a reason to look at any areas...
...outside of the pipeline or the cortex.
It's a big building.
Lots of places for Wells to hide something.
What is that?
That shouldn't be there.
I'm picking up more activity...
...around here.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
Tachyons.
There.
[SCANNER BEEPS]
CAITLIN:
Oh, my God.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
BARRY:
Guys.
What the frak?