- Previously on "The Flash"...
- The disappearance
of Sue Dearbon.
- I don't think I've ever seen
you this devoted to a case.
- I want to become a defense
attorney for meta-humans.
- [yells]
- Meet Chester P. Runk.
- He opened a black hole
by accident.
- What up, party people?
Also where am I?
- His molecules need
to re-stabilize
at the subatomic level.
- And when he does get out,
that boy knows exactly
what he wants to do.
- Gonna ask Natalie out?
- But you cannot avoid
the coming crisis.
- Tell me what I can do.
- The Flash must die.
- Nash, if you could
just tell us
what you're looking
for down there,
we might be able to help you.
- So this is where
you've been hiding.
I know how to save Barry Allen.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
This is what I do.
I don't just solve mysteries,
I bust myths.
I bust them wide open.
- You said you could
save Barry.
Tell us what you meant.
The truth.
- Do you know what
you're dealing with?
The Monitor, Mar Novu,
or whatever he calls himself.
- Are you saying
the Monitor's here?
- That's right.
- You tracked a Multiverse god
down to a hole?
- And he's going to do here
what he has done on
all these other Earths...
create fear because
the Monitor is a fraud.
He's a false god.
One that I intend to take down,
thereby saving your husband.
If my calculations are correct,
behind these rocks there's
an inter-dimensional portal,
and that portal will lead us
directly to Mar Novu.
- He's been here all along.
- He has nowhere to run.
Back up.
- Yeah, uh, no.
I wouldn't do it...
[zap]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Barry!
- [coughs]
- Barry.
- Did you know
that would happen?
- Yeah.
Look, this is just another one
of Mar Novu's tricks.
These rocks are infused
with Eternium, and that creates
an anti-vibrational
force field that...
- No phasing.
- No phasing ,correct.
- So how do we get through?
- I've got a jackhammer
in my car, so...
- Uh, no.
Any contact with the Eternium
in this sediment
could cause a catastrophic
molecular blast.
Everybody dies.
No instead,
all I need is an artifact.
One that will illuminate
the Eternium
so I can know what rocks
to dig around.
Simple, and I'd know
where to find that artifact.
♪ ♪
[machine whirs]
[pulsating]
[powering down]
- [laughs]
What up, party people?
Uh, hello?
Where is everybody?
Chester P.
Chester P., my brother.
You have a multi-billion dollar
bleeding edge tech facility
all to yourself.
[laughs]
- ♪ Only thing I gotta say ♪
- Whoo!
♪ It's the vibration,
the good sensation ♪
♪ Everybody wanna dance ♪
- He has everything.
Incoming!
A sonic wrench?
[British accent]
Good morning, guv'nor!
I'm the Doctor!
Phew!
They have a multi-rigged
private global
satellite surveillance system?
Ah!
Time to check my emails.
♪ ♪
Disabled?
I'm going again.
♪ ♪
Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh.
- Killer Frost.
Wow.
- The one day I get watch duty.
- Uh, what does this mean?
- Looks like technically
you're dead.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Oh!
Can I touch it?
- Mm-hmm.
- The official Elongated Man
emblem.
He's gonna scream.
He's gonna be so surprised.
- I've been preparing
the whole team
for life after Crisis,
but Central City
also has to be ready
for a world without Flash,
and Elongated Man should be
its sole protector
once I'm gone.
As far as Ralph knows,
he's coming to CCPD
for a routine deposition
tomorrow,
when it's really a press
conference to pass the torch.
[knock on door]
- Hey guys.
- Yo!
- Got your message, Joe.
- Hey Ralph, I talked
to an old friend
about your Dearbon case.
I got the address you were
looking for in Midway City.
If I were you,
I would go check it out
after the deposition tomorrow.
- Why put off tomorrow what
you can do it today, right?
Thanks.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Um, you're gonna be back
from Midway
by tomorrow morning, right?
- It's a routine deposition.
You can handle it.
- Why don't I tag along?
I'll speed things up a bit.
- You wanna help me
with a PI case?
- Yeah, definitely.
It'll be fun.
I'll follow your lead.
- Okay.
[soft electronic music]
♪ ♪
- This looks like
it's gonna take awhile.
- Not if you know how
to work the system.
I spent the whole summer
hobnobbing
with the rich, famous,
and the infamous.
Relax, I got this.
- Yeah, I can't imagine
spending a whole summer
undercover with this crowd.
What does a gala event
have to do with Sue's
disappearance anyway?
- Right before Sue vanished,
she was seen wearing
a one-of-a-kind
Victoria Veil dress in Milan.
This photo was taken
three weeks ago.
It's the exact same dress.
Sue was here.
And either she's still here
or somebody in there
knows why she isn't.
Time to suit up.
[funky music]
♪ ♪
Lose the ring, pal.
This is how
we suit up tonight.
♪ ♪
[light music]
- So if anyone here knows
where Sue is,
it'll be the party's host.
- There's hundreds of people
in here.
How do we narrow it down?
- Golden tile, sir.
Thank you.
- The VIP lounge.
That's where anyone
who's anyone
will be going to kiss
the proverbial ring.
We need to get in there.
- Here, mine was tight too.
Just let me...
[camera shutter clicking]
- Now I have ten selfies
of inside Barry Allen's nose.
- A camera tie?
What, you have a knife shoe
and a grapple-hook belt too?
- Maybe.
- ♪ You like it better
with my lips... ♪
- Time to charm.
Wait for my signal.
- Ralph, what's the...
- ♪ Against the wall ♪
- And here I thought
the paintings would be
the most beautiful thing
tonight.
I was wrong.
- ♪ You know you like it... ♪
- Ralph Dibny.
- January Galore.
I haven't seen you at one
of these events before.
- That's because I spent
the last year
on my island in Dubai.
My partner and I sold
our corporation.
- [coughs]
- Barry?
- GinGold martini.
Shaken, not stirred.
- Congratulations on selling
your corporation, Barry.
I do hope you reinvested
your profits
in collateralized
loan obligations.
- Yes, we recently sold
our company
for many millions of dollars.
Do you know our host?
- Mr. Meyers?
- Yes, Mr. Meyers.
- [chuckles]
The host of this event
is Remington Meister.
You both crashed this event,
didn't you?
Would you like
some free advice?
I'd leave before someone scary
comes and finds you.
♪ ♪
- Well, that did not go well.
- Yes, it did.
Our VIP ticket.
Finesse.
[rustling, clinking]
- Harrison Wells?
- Ah!
Okay, who are you?
- Allegra.
- You're the intern.
So maybe you can help me
with something.
Uh, I'm looking
for a UV emitter,
and my scanner tells me
there is a UV emitter
right around here.
- You're supposed to be dead.
What happened?
Did you fake your own death?
- What?
Oh, no.
So you, uh, no.
You think I'm Harrison Wells.
I'm not Harrison Wells.
My name is Nash.
Nash Wells.
- You look just like him.
- Yeah, well,
doppelgangers are like that.
[electronic beeping]
Oh...
Stupid Earth.
Okay, Accelerant.
- Allegra.
- I'm doing a dig, all right?
I need UV rays
to complete my dig.
You, according to my
gauntlet...
Are a meta-human
with UV capabilities.
You see where I'm going here?
- You want me to use
my powers to help you?
- Yes!
- I can't help you.
- What?
Why not?
- Never mind.
The answer is no.
- Allegra,
I will make you a deal.
You help me with the...
UV thing,
and I will give you
the scoop of the century.
Doppelgangers, Multiverse,
and potentially
the end of all life
as we know it.
Now how does that sound to you?
- Tell me more about
this Multiverse.
- The bank unfroze
your accounts,
and maybe I erased
your parking tickets
when I got your
driver's license reinstated.
- Thanks, Cecile!
Oh, your clients
are lucky to have you.
Hey, speaking of,
I should let you get back
to doing your job.
Thank you so much
for everything
that you've done.
- Wait, you know what?
Hey, Chester.
I got...I got a little time.
Is there...is there
anything else
that you could use
some help with.
- Hmm, nope.
All is good in Chester-hood.
- Wait!
Don't go!
Are you sure?
Like are you sure-sure?
Anything at all that
I could help you with?
I mean, think hard.
[gasps]
There is something.
I knew it!
Okay, sock it to me.
- Jitters is gone, right?
Which means that
I'll never see Na...
their coffee again.
- Yeah, I'm thinking that
by coffee, you mean Natalie?
- I was gonna ask her out
after I filled out
my Vibe-acino punch card.
But it's too late now, so...
Sorry, I...I know this isn't
a lawyer problem at all.
- No, it's not,
but it is
a meta-empath problem.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
You got...you got powers?
- Oh, I have powers.
- Oh, that's so cool!
That's so cool!
That must've been
a major conflict of interest
as a DA though.
- It was.
Yeah.
Uh, but those powers are about
to help you ask out Natalie.
- Yeah!
- Let's do it.
- Okay, we're doing it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Very few of my guests
have thetapferkeit
to challenge me like this.
After all,
I'm the master of this ring.
♪ ♪
Strict rules of Mahjong?
- But of course.
- Oh, so gentlemen,
I don't think we
have been introduced.
I'm Remington Meister,
your host.
And you are?
- The name's Dibny.
Ralph Dibny.
- Allen.
Barry...
- Well, nice to meet you,
Allen Barry and Ralph Dibny.
Hmm, and what brings you to
my wonderfulgrosse feier?
[suspenseful music]
- Sue Dearbon.
♪ ♪
- Sue?
A, uh, fiercely intelligent
young woman.
♪ ♪
She's a friend of yours?
- Um...
- I'm an admirer of hers.
- Ah, you have taste,
Mr. Dibny.
- [chuckles]
- And I wish I could be
a more auspicious host
and introduce you,
but I'm afraid
Ms. Dearbon isn't here.
In fact, I don't think I've
seen her at any social event
in over six months.
Perhaps she'll attend an event
in your facility soon.
And, uh, where was that?
What?
- Paris.
- Dubai.
We run a multi-city
import/export company.
- Hmm!
- Maybe she's still
on the guest list.
You know, just in case.
- You think I should check?
♪ ♪
- Sure, yeah.
- Idna!
♪ ♪
- That's a beautiful dress.
Is this one-of-a-kind?
- Two-of-a-kind, actually.
Even the most stubborn
designer's one-of-a-kind outfit
has a price.
- [laughs]
So true!
I'm impressed.
You have quite the eye
for fashion.
- Oh.
- Sue Dearbon
is not on the list.
- Oh.
- And strange...
neither are you.
- Well, when an auction
like yours pops up,
no list can keep us away.
♪ ♪
- I like you.
[chuckles]
Him?
Nicht so viel.
♪ ♪
Oh!
Mahjong.
Sieg.
I win.
Such a pleasure
to meet you both.
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, man.
I thought I had that.
I...we should get back
to Central City.
- Put our friend above
on high alert.
[click, beeping]
♪ ♪
- I tracked down the woman
who designed Sue's dress
in the Milan.
- Yeah.
- It turns out that Idna
did commission her
to make another one.
So I think what we gotta
do next is probably...
- Ralph, Sue's not here.
We just got made
and we just hit a dead end.
We should head back
to Central City.
- Barry, if Meister
wanted us out of here,
we'd be gone already.
Take a whiff, would ya?
Something doesn't smell
right here.
- Ralph, I know you care about
this Sue case,
but we're grasping at straws.
I'm not even sure
there's a mystery here.
- Really?
You're not sure?
You see that guy with
the eye patch right there?
That's Riggs Wellington.
he's a shady
Bratva counterfeiter.
And January Galore?
She's an underground
weapons dealer.
That guy right there,
he's a drug kingpin.
The woman he's talking to
is a mob boss.
- If this is a party
for criminals,
then the Flash
and Elongated Man
need to take over.
- Pump the brakes, would ya?
There's a time and a place
for masks and cowls,
but this is not it.
This Meister,
he's up to something.
We need to find out what it is,
no matter how long it takes.
- Ralph, tomorrow we have...
we have the deposition...
- Lay off the whole deposition
thing, would ya?
CCPD can wait.
- I can search this
whole place in seconds.
- Barry, I realize
that you want to help
and I appreciate that,
but this is not Central City,
these people are not metas.
This is a time
for our human identities.
Finesse, remember?
I just need some time, okay?
- Okay.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[Cecile]Here's the deal.
I made a coffee order with
the new Jitters-To-Go service.
That's where Natalie
works now.
So when she arrives,
I am going to read
her emotion,
and then I'm gonna tell you
what to say.
- What if she says no?
- She's not gonna say no!
Not with my help.
- And I'm here too.
My good deed for the day
was to help somebody,
and I couldn't find
anyone less annoying.
- Really?
- Hey, I have a delivery
for Chester P. Runk?
- Yep, that's...that's...
that's, uh, that's me.
Yeah.
- Wow.
12 Vibe-acinos.
- Yeah.
- Chester,
she's feeling impressed.
A big order like
that, it shows her
that you are
a man with means.
- Yeah, well, you know,
I'm a...[chuckles]
kind of a big spender,
you know?
Can't take it with you, right?
- Sure.
I guess.
Do you need a receipt?
- Are you sure
you're reading her right?
- Yeah!
Of course.
Um, um, hey Chester,
she's yearning for validation.
So pay her a compliment.
She's feeling very strong,
positive feelings
about her shoes.
- Uh, I...man.
[exhales]
I really like your shoes.
- These old things?
Yuck.
I lost my favorite kicks
to a black hole.
- That's, uh, that's rough.
- You are totally
missing the mark.
- [stuttering]
You're not helping!
Uh, Chester, be assertive.
Don't let her leave
without asking her out.
- [stuttering]
Uh, Natalie.
Uh, before you go,
I was wondering if...
if we could, you know,
I...I could carry
this crate for you.
- Oh, it's not a problem.
- Yes, it is.
She wants you
to be chivalrous.
Help her now!
- Girl, I got it.
- [gasps]
- Pardon moi?
[chuckles]
[stuttering]
I could pay for those.
- Yeah,
I think you've done enough.
- I'm no expert,
but the Book of Ralph says
that when you ask someone out,
you should just be yourself.
- How is he supposed
to be himself
when he doesn't even know
who he is anymore?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- And these different Earths
have existed
simultaneously since...
- Well, since, uh...let's see.
Oh, the dawn of time.
- Well, how come nobody
knows about this?
I mean, stuff this big?
The public should
be made aware.
- People know.
Just the right people.
If the general public knew?
No. No, that would not be good.
They would lose their minds.
- Right, I mean...
it's all so...
Epic.
- Yes, it's epic.
Doppelgangers,
anti-matter events,
and speedsters juggling
dual identities,
like the Flash
and Barry Allen.
- Wait, what?
- What?
- My boss' husband
is the Flash?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ah, nobody tells me anything.
- But then, of course,
let's not forget the villain
of this story...
the Monitor.
Hmm, yeah.
The cosmic imposter
with delusions of grandeur.
That is why I'm gonna take
that fraud down permanently.
♪ ♪
- You're gonna kill
this Novu guy?
- Enough story time.
Time for you to hold up
your end of the bargain.
- Wait, can you explain
doppelgangers?
- Sure, absolutely.
I can, but first...[mimics zap]
Let's have you zap this
with your meta UV lights,
so I can find out what rocks
to avoid when I excavate.
And go.
- [sighs]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I...
I...I can't.
- Yes, you can.
You're a meta.
It's who you are.
- No, it...it's not.
- It is,
and also we had a deal.
- Well, the deal's off.
- What?
- I'm not gonna be some weapon
you use to hurt others.
- I'm not asking you
to be the weapon.
- It's not who I am.
♪ ♪
- All right,
let's see what we got here.
[keys clacking, beeping]
♪ ♪
Something tells me that
ain't a Johnny Cash song.
♪ ♪
- Damn it, Ralph.
She's not here.
[yells, groans]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[whirring]
♪ ♪
- They're all here
to bid on this.
♪ ♪
Come on, come on.
[groans]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Meta target acquired.
- Wunderbar.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- [groans]
- Hey, hey.
Don't bother.
It's meta-dampened.
- I must say, I did
not expect Central City's
resident superhero
to crash my little gathering.
- And I must say,
I'm surprised by all
the Bond villain clichés.
I mean, you've got the accent,
the diabolical scheme,
even the silent
but deadly henchperson.
- Ultraviolet?
I sent you to Iron Heights.
- Luckily, she has friends
in low places.
- And let me guess,
you're gonna add my unmasking
to your little auction?
- Oh, I could care less about
your secret identity, Flash.
My interests are global.
And to think, Mr. Dibny,
that it was the Flash
that set off
my meta-activity monitor
that then triggered
the security protocols
that got you caught.
Danke schon.
I am very curious, though,
as to why you are really here.
- Do you expect me to talk?
- No, Mr. Dibny...
I expect you to die.
- Oh, come on.
That line is literally
from "Goldfinger."
- And so is this.
Behold, a state-of-the-art
industrial laser canon.
It will shoot a deadly beam...
zap!...
through the both of you
the moment Central City
is destroyed.
- You're gonna kill millions
of innocent people
just to sell your weapon?
- Yeah.
Enjoy the show.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Got lost, didn't you?
- What?
No.
- No?
- Maybe.
- [chuckles]
- Shut up.
- I freaked you out, didn't I?
- Watching Rag Doll eat while
in Iron Heights is freaky.
- Sure it is.
So why the disappearing act?
Actually, let me pause
at theory on that.
I think you're afraid
to use your powers
because if you do,
you think you'll
become like someone.
Someone.
Someone you know,
someone you...
hate.
How am I doing?
- My cousin, Esperanza,
she has the same powers as me,
only she uses them
to murder people.
- You're not your cousin.
- [sighs]
But if I start using my powers,
what's to stop me
from becoming like her?
- Because, Allegra,
in this life we choose.
We choose who we are.
So if you choose to use
your incredible powers,
that does not make you
anything like Esperanza
unless you choose that.
[dramatic music]
- [sighs]
I'm not Esperanza.
- Who are you?
- I'm Allegra.
- Yes.
♪ ♪
Allegra Garcia.
- Yes.
- Well, that was anti-climatic.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[pulsating]
[yells]
♪ ♪
[beep]
[pants]
Did I do it?
- Yes.
I think you did.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
How you holding up?
- Hmm, like Alderaan
on a bad day.
You look pretty
emotionally vaporized too.
- Okay, Chester, I...I think
that I was using your problems
as a distraction
from my own feelings,
and my internal compass
was completely off,
and that made me sense
the opposite
of what Natalie was feeling.
And I'm so sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
I've had these powers
for two years now,
and I'm still
figuring them out.
- How you feeling now?
- Oh, uh, honestly,
I don't know.
- Let's pretend I'm the empath.
What kind of feelings
would you be putting off?
No, no.
Stare into my eyes.
- Okay.
- And imagine my pupils
are swirling.
And...and swirling,
and swirling.
- Okay, honey, that's
a hypnotist, not an empath,
but I really appreciate
the effort.
Yeah, uh...
- Yeah, you're right.
- How am I feeling?
I'm...
oh, my God.
I'm freaking out.
You know,
I was a DA for 20 years,
and they just...boom,
replaced me overnight.
And now I feel like I don't
exactly know who I am anymore,
and if I fail at this
meta-attorney thing,
I can't go back.
- Yeah, but you didn't fail me.
- [sighs]
- You know,
I think the two of us
just need to trust
that the real us
will always shine through.
Which is why I will embrace
the new me
by finally asking out Natalie.
[chuckles]
You know, seize the moment
and all that.
- Yeah.
- And maybe you should too.
[chuckles]
[somber music]
- [sighs]
Maybe I should too.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- I should've listened to you.
If we'd done things your way,
we wouldn't have gotten caught.
Maybe I should be handing
Central City
over to Ralph Dibny
rather than Elongated Man.
- What are you talking about?
- There's no deposition.
I planned a press conference
to present you
as Central City's
official protector.
Because of this coming Crisis,
I have to prepare the city
for a world without Flash.
- Wow.
[chuckles]
I'm, uh...I'm honored
that you think that
I could help fill your shoes.
Look, tonight's job
was for Ralph Dibny
because both parts
of my identity have value.
The same is true for you,
only tonight I could've used
your civilian half.
What I'm trying to say
is Barry Allen
is just as important
as the Flash.
[dramatic music]
Try to remember that.
I know I will.
♪ ♪
You know,
can you reach my cufflink?
- What?
- Grab my cufflink.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
- Got it.
All right, I got it.
- Okay, on three,
I want you to flick it
at that laser cannon.
One, two, flick!
[zap, pulsating]
- All right, I got it.
It's down.
[machine whirs]
Uh-oh.
♪ ♪
Whoa, watch out.
- What was that?
♪ ♪
Okay, uh, what do we do?
- I don't know.
- Uh, what do we do?
♪ ♪
Ah!
Jeez!
How do we stop that?
- There's a pattern.
- Really?
- All right,
when I say now...
fling ourselves to the left.
- Right.
- The left!
Now!
♪ ♪
We have to stop Meister.
- He's got Ultraviolet
protecting him.
Her powers could kill us both.
- Then let's do things
your way,
with a little finesse.
Time to suit up.
[suspenseful music]
[applause]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- Good evening,
meine freunde.
The moment that you've
all been waiting for is here.
Let the auction begin.
The EYE-3C9 satellite system,
or as I'd like to call it
the Ring of Fire,
is equipped with 15 dioptric
long-range missiles.
Simply use this console
to enter our desired
coordinates,
and then sit back
and watch hellfire
reign down on your enemies.
Perhaps a little
demonstration now, yes?
♪ ♪
[machine whirs]
[beep]
♪ ♪
[machine whirrs]
- This isn't the bathroom.
[confused chatter]
Sorry, sorry.
- Mr. Allen Barry, I see
you have found the open bar.
- Keep her busy till
I get to that console.
- I'll bid on your
stupid laptop.
- $500 million.
- $500 million and one dollar.
"Price is Right" rules.
- Ultraviolet, uh, gently
escort Mr. Barry out,
but don't burn his money.
- I love "Mortal Kombat"!
[click, whirring]
- Mr. Dibny, we meet again.
- You've got to take it easy
on the Bond quotes, man.
- You know what
my favorite part is?
"Finish him!"
- You know, usually I allow
Ultraviolet to do the killing.
[Muse's "Supremacy"]
[concerned chatter]
But for you,
I'll make an exception.
♪ ♪
Ha!
- Come on!
♪ ♪
[groans]
[both grunt]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[both grunt]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[zap]
♪ ♪
[click]
Fire in the hole.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[zapping]
- ♪ The time it has come ♪
♪ To destroy ♪
♪ Your supremacy ♪
♪ ♪
- Thanks for dropping in.
[zapping, groaning]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Really?
Adjusting your tie?
- Adjusting the flash.
♪ ♪
[zap, yelling]
[click, beep]
[panting]
- Nice job, man.
[both chuckle]
- [laughing]
- Shocking.
- Your performance...
Wunderbar, Mr. Barry.
- The name's Allen.
Barry Allen.
- Remington Meister's
crime ring is over.
- Glad we got Remington, but
I'm sorry we didn't find Sue.
- My nose tells me there's more
to that case than I imagine.
- You'll find her.
- I will.
And in the meantime, I'll be
busy keeping Central City safe.
We still on for
that ceremony today, Joe?
- Oh yeah, see you there.
♪ ♪
[Cecile]So did you do it?
Did you embrace
your new identity?
Did you see Natalie?
Did you ask her out?
Did she say yes?
- Yes, yes, and no.
- Oh.
Chester, I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
- I've actually never
felt better.
- Uh, the last time
I went to ask Natalie out,
I was scared as hell.
Today, I conquered that fear.
Yo, she said no,
but I said yes to me.
- All right, well,
I am very happy for you.
I think.
- Hey, you're...
you're marketing your firm.
- Yeah, yeah, it is the first
step in embracing the new me.
- Wow.
- You know, I wanted to thank
you for your encouragement.
And speaking of encouragement,
you know, you'd fit in nicely
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
[somber music]
Don't be a stranger.
- That...
would be so epic!
Epic.
- Epic.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Here you go.
- Better?
- Yeah, thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Why are you being
so nice today?
- [chuckles]
Let's just say you
remind me of someone.
- Another doppelganger.
- Something like that.
Hey, um...
Good job.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- The last five years,
I've tried to keep
Central City safe.
[sighs]
But as new threats arise,
you'll need more than me.
Which is why I'm proud
to recognize a hero
who's put his life
on the line for this city
time and time again.
A hero who deserves
our recognition.
The Elongated Man.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Now Central City
has another symbol of hope.
♪ ♪
[applause]
[zap]
♪ ♪
- To every woman, every man,
and every child
listening today,
I have wanted to protect
Central City
since before I ever even
got my powers.
This is my home
and I love it here.
♪ ♪
And so today,
I hereby promise
that I will defend Central City
with my dying breath.
♪ ♪
Before we wrap up,
there is someone
that Captain West and I
would like to bring up here.
CSI Barry Allen,
please come up.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
- Uh, those who wear capes
and costumes
aren't the only ones
that keep us safe.
There are some
unsung heroes as well,
like this man.
This man has solved crimes to
give mourning families justice.
He's a CCPD team member
who's never given up
on a single case.
This man has saved Central City
more times than anyone knows.
So it's time
that we thank him.
It's time that...
that I thank him.
So without further ado...
- Officer Barry Allen,
on behalf of CCPD,
we present you with
their highest honor...
the Medal of Honor.
Thank you for your service.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Pretty cool, huh?
Look how shiny it is.
- Yeah, that's great, Ralph.
Um, is this why you wanted
to meet me?
- Yes.
And I wanted to show you this.
I took it at Meister's party.
- I recognize that pin.
- Guess who else showed up
in Midway City?
- Ultraviolet?
Thanks, Ralph.
"The Citizen" is on it.
♪ ♪
[squishing, snarling]
- Great press conference.
[ominous music]
I have a follow up question.
♪ ♪
[roaring]
- Greg, move your head!
[electricity zaps]