- [sighs] It feels like my
shift started 100 years ago.
- Drink more coffee.
[distorted warping]
You're around it all day.
Duh.
Besides,
that place is so boring.
- [yells]
- Wait.
What's that?
- Yeah.
Just some guy cosplaying.
- What's he doing now?
- I don't know.
Must be some sort of
Comic-Con thing or something.
[distorted warping]
[foghorn blares]
What in the world?
- Natalie?
Natalie, what's that noise?
[loud thumping]
- [dramatic music]
- Natalie, what's that noise?
Natalie?
[growling]
- [screams]
- [roars]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- My beautiful boy.
I'm giving him all the strength
I can to heal him,
which means I'll be weak
for a bit longer.
- Because Psych and Fuerza
attacked you?
- Exactly.
♪ ♪
- Do you remember
what happened?
- Only some of it.
When I was reborn,
I was surrounded
by light and love.
Then came the pain.
I could feel
these Forces of Nature
were like me, only evil.
- If they're like you, then why
are they trying to kill you?
- I'm not sure,
but I think it's to feed.
That's why I had
to find Barry Allen.
I thought he could keep me
safe until I fully recovered.
But if the other Forces find me
in this condition,
I wouldn't survive
another attack.
- Don't worry.
We are gonna figure out a way
to keep you safe.
Somehow.
- Holy Henry T. Sampson.
Wow, so you're the actual,
all-encompassing,
immeasurably interstellar,
and mind-bendingly
cosmorrific...
- Yes, Chester P. Runk.
I am the Speed Force.
- Whoo-hoo, Chessman.
How's that isotope
detection system coming along?
- Yeah, actually...
[quietly] She knows my name.
- I think she does.
- Okay.
Behold, believers.
This puppy I designed
can boost isotopic signals
for our satellites to scan.
Now all we need to do
is build a few units,
place them around the outskirts
of the city, and eureka.
- And then we would get
an early warning
if Psych or Fuerza
decided to come back.
- And they can detect
foundational isotopic
signatures,
so we won't just know
they're coming.
- We'll know whoever it is,
Psych or Fuerza,
which one is headed our way.
Chester, that is amazing.
- Could we use this
to follow the other Forces?
Perhaps find them
before they find us?
- Not yet.
Right now,
they only work
in close proximity, so...
- But at least now
we have a way
to help protect you.
- Cisco, how long would it take
to make enough amplifiers?
- We have everything we need
in the S.T.A.R. Labs van,
so we could build them
as we go.
- So let's do this, baby,
'cause...
both:
Team Chesco's on the case.
- Let's get it.
- [sighs]
Separated at birth.
[hip-hop music]
- Hey, what's all this?
- Norvock finally brought
the rest of my stuff over
from one
of Amunet's stash houses.
I was gonna throw everything
away, but then muse struck.
♪ ♪
- Oh, wow.
It's great.
- Yeah, this'll really give
the place some attitude
when I'm done.
- I'm sorry.
You want to hang that in here?
- Yeah.
That empty wall behind you.
It's been driving me crazy.
- Well, you know what they say.
♪ ♪
Great minds.
What do you think?
♪ ♪
- Um...
It's missing something.
♪ ♪
Huh.
Much better.
You know, art should always
provoke a strong reaction.
- Oh, it does.
- And sensor is ready.
- Excellent.
Once the amplifier goes live,
then our early warning system
will be a go.
And that means it's time
for coffee and a cronut.
- Coffee and a cronut.
Actually, you know, there's
a Sip-n-Dash in Masonville.
Or was, back in the day.
Oh, I used to live there,
but Grandma Runk
and I moved to Central City
when I was done
with high school.
- All right.
Looks like we're ready to go.
- Okay, cool.
[sighing]
[electrical static]
What?
- Why?
- [sighs]
- Look at this.
What do you think?
You think
it's the neutrino filtrations
glitching on it?
- Cisco, Cisco, Cisco, Cisco.
[dramatic music]
What?
[both screaming]
[both heavy breathing]
- We're okay?
We're okay.
What was that?
- I have no idea.
Well, looks like
the sensor's working.
- Huh.
- Did I give you my phone?
- No.
Mine's gone too.
Okay, hold up.
Where's the van?
- It was just here.
What...
- Uh.
Does the van have
a secret cloaking mode
that I don't know about?
Asking for a friend.
- That's no van.
[echoing boom]
- Whoa.
- Chess, we've just been
under-the-domed.
- Nora?
[somber music]
You all right?
- Yeah.
Just making sure
nothing happens to Barry.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
How do you deal with all this?
- Well, it's never easy
dealing with a threat,
especially when it affects
someone that you care about.
But don't worry, okay?
By this time tomorrow, Barry
will be back to his old self.
Healed, wrapped up
on the couch, full BBB-style.
BBB...Barry's blanket burrito.
It's um...
[laughs]
It's hard to explain.
- No.
I understand.
It's something
between the two of you.
- Actually, you know what?
It doesn't have to be.
I want to show you something.
Come with me.
- We made it.
Now, we can find a phone
and call S.T.A.R. Labs
before...
[quirky music]
- Tell me you're seeing
what I'm seeing.
- Does it have anything to do
with "Space Jam"
being back in stock?
- At that Blockbuster Video
that doesn't exist anymore?
- Yeah, and get this.
I saw a Sip-n-Dash
store back there
that got torn down
when I was in high school.
♪ ♪
- I think we
just time traveled.
- Really?
So tonight we're gonna party
like it's 1998?
[laughs]
- None of the payphones work,
we don't have cell phones,
and we're trapped
in an invisible barrier.
We are stuck
in the 90s?
[laughter]
- This is so epic.
Epic.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
It is off the heezy fo' sheezy.
Heezy fo...
- Okay, cheesy.
Why don't you calm down?
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
- Look, is this
freaking awesome?
Yes.
- [laughs]
- Do we desperately need
to figure out a way
to get back home?
Also yes.
- Well, how are we supposed
to do that
without a DeLorean or hot tub?
- By looking at
what brought us here:
a green energy wave
that looks like it came
straight out of Turtle 2.0
White Whale's Revenge.
Coincidence?
I think not.
- Look, I know you and Turtle
2.0 kind of have this thing.
- I'll say.
Maybe we're not dealing
with a meta at all.
The amplifier showed
an isotopic surge
when the wave hit.
- So it's one of our Forces.
Wait.
Check the signatures.
Was it Fuerza or Psych?
- Neither.
The sensor detected
a temporal energy.
- So there's a new Force
in town, and...
- And it can control time.
- Yeah, okay.
We gotta get out of here
and warn the team.
The Speed Force isn't safe.
- Not so fast.
We need to know
exactly who we're up against.
You remember how
the Speed Force asked
if the amplifiers
could track the Forces?
If we added a transmitter diode
to the sensor...
- It could localize
the isotopic circuits enough
to detect a new Force
within a 20-yard radius.
- Right, but we need the kind
of maxed-out receiver
that just doesn't exist yet.
- [sighs]
Time to go shopping.
- Man, there's a Tech Station
right here.
[metal clanging]
Chess, hurry up.
This is embarrassing.
- [grunts]
See?
One man's trash
is another man's...
- Another man's reason
for a tetanus shot?
- I already got
my tetanus shot.
- I can't believe you just
used junk to fix our sensor.
- Ah, just think of it as one
repurposed Force finder.
[laughs]
Aw.
Rest in peace, UltraFax 4000.
Damn, they don't make them
like you anymore.
- All right.
Let's find ourselves
a time god.
[bell rings]
To high school, huh?
The sensor seems to think
they're in here somewhere.
Let's do this.
- Yo, yo, yo.
For real?
Masonville's principal
suffers zero fools, feel me?
- All right.
Then we just sneak in.
Simple.
- Uh-uh.
We gotta blend in.
We gotta kick it up a notch.
[Montell Jordan's
"This Is How We Do It"]
♪ ♪
- ♪ This is how we do it ♪
♪ Check it out,
once upon a time in '94 ♪
♪ Montell made no money
and life sure was slow ♪
♪ There lived a D.J.
and Paul was his name ♪
♪ He came up to Monty,
this is what he said ♪
♪ You and Oji
are gonna make some cash ♪
♪ Sell a million records
and we're makin' tha dash ♪
♪ Ohh, I'm buzzin' because
this is how we do it ♪
- All right.
Here's the plan.
We ask people questions,
see if anybody
has any diabolical plans
to alter the future...
- Yes.
- And then we check the sensor.
If it spikes...
- Then we found our time god.
- Let's get it.
- This for the yearbook?
- Yeah.
"Future Falcon Forecast"
section.
- What's the question again?
- Where do you
see yourself in 23 years?
- Mm.
- ♪ Shorties always be running
when I start to flow ♪
♪ Balling on the stage,
but my boo's a no-show ♪
♪ My girl complains
my verses be weak ♪
♪ She takes the 8-ball.
See? ♪
♪ Outcome looks bleak, yeah ♪
- 23.
Yeah.
- In 23 years,
I'll be like everyone else
in this dumb high school.
A zombie.
Totally dead.
- ♪ But I'm the bomb ♪
♪ I'm gonna kill,
in the future ♪
♪ Blowing all them rap minds,
you'll be needing a suture ♪
- Dead inside, from slaving
away at a thankless job.
both: Oh.
- Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
- Jobs are bad.
- That'll be all.
- Yeah.
Keep going.
- Keep spitting.
Yeah, you got it, boy, hey.
- ♪ Blowing all them rap minds,
you'll be needing a suture ♪
♪ Boom, and that's
my "Falcon Forecast" ♪
It's Reggie Q, I'm out.
The past.
both: Oh!
- Dropped the mic.
- Yes, yes.
- Aw, no, he was spitting.
- No.
- No?
Okay.
- Carry the two...
- No, you don't carry the two.
- Hey, dog, check it out.
Parents got it for me.
Said they want the NFL to be
able to hit me up anytime.
- It's hella cool, right?
- Yeah, yeah, nice, Deon.
- Yeah, man.
[whistle blows]
You know, in the future,
I want to be just like Deon.
You know, he's gonna kill it
in the state championship
tomorrow.
- Yo, K Swizzle.
it's time to bounce.
[beeping]
- [sighs]
Well...
That's not him.
- [sighs]
[beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Wait till those dumb jocks
see what the future
has in store for them.
- [sighs]
- Yo, Parker, right?
Listen, do you have
a couple minutes to spare,
so we can ask you
a few questions?
- Who are you?
- We're students.
- Students.
- Just like you.
- Yeah.
You guys talk like my dad.
- [laughs]
Parker.
What?
- Come on.
Don't be wack, all right?
We are 17.
- I'm 16.
- We love "The Real World".
We like Beanie Babies
and "The Matrix".
- "The Matrix" hasn't
come out yet.
- Ah, shoot.
See?
I had a feeling.
Wait a second.
How did you know that?
- This isn't right.
You gotta help me, please.
We're trapped in the same date.
No, wait.
[beeping]
It knows I broke free.
It's gonna start over.
Oh, God.
- Oh, not again.
Okay.
That was freaky.
You all right, dude?
- Who are you?
Where am I?
Did you take my headgear?
- Dude, it's me.
Chester.
- No.
No, I don't know you.
Stranger danger.
- Stranger danger?
Uh.
Cisco, how old are you?
- I'm seven, you predator.
- Because you still think
it's 1998.
Oh, no.
- Please, sir.
-Cisco.
Don't chase after me.
I don't want
to get in your van.
- I'm not trying to hurt you.
Listen, just listen okay?
You're not seven.
You're 30,
and you're a scientist
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Remember?
What about visiting Atlantis
or King Shark versus Grodd?
[laughs]
Oh, God, please tell me
you remember "Game of Thrones".
- Littlefinger.
- Yes.
- The Iron Throne.
- "The Rains of Castamere."
Yes.
- Chester.
- [sighs]
How did we get here?
Last thing I remember, Parker
was going all "Get Out" on us.
- Oh, no.
Parker is not our Biff Tannen.
A modern reference jolted him
awake, just like you.
- But we're back
on Main Street.
Right before the wave hit,
Parker said it's gonna...
both: Start over.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Gotta go.
both: It's a time loop.
- This isn't about
changing the future.
It's about reliving one day
over and over.
- When Parker woke up,
it reset the loop,
but why didn't
you get whammied?
- I think the sensor absorbed
the temporal energy
and shielded me.
Only, by the looks of it,
that's not happening again.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to fix this.
Otherwise, if the loop resets,
we won't be shielded.
We won't remember
that we're stuck in the past,
and we'll be trapped here,
like everyone else.
We have to fix this now.
- Okay, you know what?
I think I have the parts
to fix this at Grandma Runk's.
- Perfect.
Let's go there right now,
and while we're on our way,
maybe we can figure out
what's so special
about December 4, '98.
- Uh.
You know what?
These parts ain't
at Grandma Runk's.
Someplace better.
- Please don't go
dumpster diving.
- This blanket is
quite well-loved.
[laughs]
- He's had it for years.
- How does swaddling
himself help?
- Well, it's not
about the blanket.
It's more like wrapping himself
in the memories
and the comfort
associated with the blanket.
- [sighs]
[laughs]
It's like being hugged
by warm, loving arms.
[somber music]
- His mother made it for him.
He doesn't really talk
about her much, so...
- Not even with you?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
They were so close.
Being reminded
of what happened,
he's forced
to think about that night.
[grunts]
The violence of it all...
it stays with him,
and I wish I could take that
away from him,
but I can't.
[electrical whooshing]
- TI-82.
Girl, you still fine.
- Stop flirting
with the calculators.
We've got a problem.
- What?
- The X-76 power converter.
They just sold the last one
to that guy.
- [sighs]
[beeping]
Okay, chill.
It's not that big a deal.
He actually looks
pretty reasonable.
I say we just offer
to buy it back from him.
- No, no, no.
We can't go after him.
- Okay.
Why not?
Chess, what's going on?
- We can't go after him
because
he's my dad.
I'm the last person
he'd want to help right now.
[bell rings]
- Chess, you wanna tell me
what's going on?
- [sighs]
Look, my Pops was
a very smart guy
who traveled all the time
trying to get rich
off of his latest invention,
so he never had time for me.
[somber music]
It was always, "Sorry, son.
I don't believe in quitting."
♪ ♪
- Look, whatever happened...
- Tomorrow, my dad dies
in a car accident
on his way to some big meeting
in Coast City.
Today's the last day
I see him alive.
- I'm sorry.
That's heavy for anyone,
let alone a kid.
What if...
What if you're here
for a reason?
[dramatic music]
This could be your chance
to talk to your dad.
- What good would that do?
I can't save his life.
That would just reset
the time loop, so...
[sighs]
Now I just gotta...
just gotta stay firm.
Keep doing my thing.
- I understand.
Don't worry about
the converter, all right?
I'll get it from him.
- Wait.
You're gonna go talk to my dad?
- Just long enough
to get the X-76.
Then I come back here,
we fix everything,
and it all goes back to normal.
That is what you want, right?
- [sighs]
Oh, thank God.
I thought you might go
somewhere Barry knows,
but you weren't
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and CCPD seemed unlikely.
- Yes, and I know
how he loves the coffee here.
[somber music]
I never took into account
how much his mother's death
might still weigh on him.
What have I done?
♪ ♪
I'll change my appearance.
Appear in my true form
to all of you,
from now on, as lightning,
because I can't keep
hurting him like this.
- You're not causing him pain.
You're giving him a gift.
- How?
- It's like how his blanket
reminds him of his mom,
and that memory gives him
comfort and peace.
It's the same thing with you.
- So I'm not
a painful reminder?
- No, not at all.
You are a happy one.
I may be his lightning rod,
but you are his lightning.
- Thank you.
[beeps]
[computer beeping]
- [clears throat]
- Can I help you, kid?
- Me?
Uh, yeah.
I'd like to buy
your X-76 converter.
- What makes you think
I have one, Mr...?
- Boyega.
John Boyega.
The clerk at the tech shop said
that you bought the last one,
and they don't get another
shipment for a week, so...
- Look, I'd like to help you,
but I need
this X-76 power converter too.
- You need it for some
important invention right?
- Nope.
I'm throwing it away.
- Uh...
Ha, my son Chester
is working on a project.
I've looked at his plans.
Two days from now,
he's gonna need that part,
but I'll be back
on the road by then.
I'm throwing it away now
so that he can find it later,
when he needs it.
Do you have kids, Mr. Boyega?
If you do,
someday you'll understand.
- Wait, so why not just
give it to him?
- It's my way of teaching him
to be resourceful
and a problem solver.
- It's kind of brilliant.
- I know.
Plus, he gets the joy
of learning to see treasure
where other people see trash.
- Do you do this kind of thing
a lot for him?
- Everything I do is for him.
He's the reason I get
out of bed in the morning.
- [sighs]
But don't you ever resent
having to work so hard 24/7?
- I'm the boy's father...
And Chester's worth
any sacrifice I have to make.
Besides, when it
comes to him...
I don't believe in quitting.
- So you don't care
about your work
more than your son.
You care about your work
because of him.
- I'm just a man trying to do
the right thing.
Make my son proud.
Yeah.
This is weird.
- Sorry.
It's pretty inspiring.
And I hope I can be
a great dad too someday.
- Something tells me
you will be.
I'm still not selling you
that part though.
But if you really need one,
I think I have an idea.
[mysterious music]
Hold that.
[laughs]
- Cisco, my Pops
is pretty cool, man.
- Yeah?
It sounds like it.
- I'm just really glad
we had a day to hang out.
[somber music]
It made me realize
that my Pops isn't just smart.
[scoffs]
Dude's a genius.
Check it.
[dramatic music]
Pops and I built it together.
[both laughing]
- [sighs]
- Wow.
You know what this means.
Now, we can disrupt
the temporal isotopes...
both: And go home.
- Yes.
- Yo, nerds!
Been looking for you.
- Hey.
Yo, Deon.
We were just going to...
thinking of going to...
both: Blockbuster.
- You ever see "Space Jam"?
- Four times, man.
- Oh, man, it's so good.
- Now, it's time to kick you
wannabe Urkels to the curb,
because whoever you two are,
you don't belong here.
This is my time...
And you two gotta go.
- Time god.
- Thanks for ruining
my perfect day, not.
- Yo, Deon.
Why bum around 1998?
Man, I thought you left
the small-town life
for college and the NFL.
- That wasn't me!
[both grunting]
[dramatic music]
- You will have 30 minutes
to create...
an amuse-bouche
that will tickle...
[energy wave whooshes]
[Pulse's "Another Woman"]
♪ ♪
- Oh, crap.
- ♪ Could make you see ♪
- Katie, I think
we got a problem.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- What do you mean?
Grandma Runk said
that after you won state...
- It was
the second-string quarterback
that led the team to victory.
Not me, dumbass.
I got injured and taken out
in the first quarter.
He got all the victory.
Me?
I got four pins in my knee
and a job selling used cars.
I came back to the past
because I have no future!
- That's weird,
'cause your future
looks bright to me.
- [grunts]
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
You dweebs really think
you can stop me?
You tripping.
- Oh, not good.
- Oh, snap.
I just erased it from time.
My bad.
[jazz music]
♪ ♪
- Could somebody please tell me
what this green energy
is doing to my city?
- There are geothermic isotopes
all over the city,
which means we know
it's one of the Forces.
We're just trying
to figure out which one.
- This used to be a tablet.
[funky music]
♪ ♪
- So it's not just me?
- Baby girl.
You look incredible.
- So do you, Dad.
Frost.
Caitlin.
- Thanks for trying.
[sighs]
- Nora, Iris told me
you were here,
but it is so good to see you.
- It's good to see you too,
Captain.
[alarm blaring]
- Scans show the isotopic
foundation is unstable.
The green wave is spreading
and heading toward downtown.
[foghorn blares]
- What's that noise?
- [growling]
- Natalie?
Natalie!
Natalie?
- [screams]
- [roaring]
Oh, my God.
- [roars]
[computer beeping]
- I was able to trace
the energy to a nearby town.
- Masonville?
- Cisco and Chester
were installing an
early warning system by there.
- Looks like
something triggered
the amplifier's sensor.
- If I can access
the data drive,
I might be able to figure out
what set this off.
- Temporal, as in time travel?
- Yeah, but this energy
doesn't match Psych or Fuerza,
which means...
- Which means that
we're dealing
with a new Force of Nature
that can alter time.
- Buckle up, fools,
'cause once
I reset my time loop,
you'll forget everything.
- We gotta get out of here.
He's too powerful.
We can't fight him on our own.
Come on.
Chess?
- I don't believe in quitting.
- These isotopic signature
are moving at speeds
that should be impossible.
This new Force
is rewinding time at random,
and we can't stop it.
- What happens if we get stuck
in one of these time pockets?
- We could end up
in the Stone Age.
- Oh, my God.
It's up to
Cisco and Chester now.
- Hey.
Yo, Deon.
Listen to me.
You can make us
forget our futures,
but there's no power
in the world
that'll make you forget yours.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
I've tried to rewrite
that night 100 times.
No matter what I try to do,
I can't change what happens.
- What happened to you
must be a fixed point.
You can't change it.
So maybe you should
stop trying,
and instead choose to see
the possibilities
in every new day.
Look, your future's
still not written, Deon.
- I hate my future!
- [roars]
[both screaming]
- I'm supposed to be
the next Patrick Mahomes, man.
- Look, I know it's easy
to hold on to the bad stuff.
Ever since I was a kid,
I thought my Pops cared more
about his job than me.
- Boo-hoo, man.
- And I carried the hurt
around with me for years.
But today,
when I looked at my past
with fresh eyes...
I saw that my dad worked hard
to give me a better life.
And once I saw that, it helped
me let go of that pain, Deon.
And you can do the same.
But not until you stop letting
one moment in your past
define all the moments
in your future.
[thunder rolls]
- [roars]
- [screams]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- The future's on me?
- Yeah.
- So I get to figure out
what it looks like.
So I get to decide
what happens from now on.
Not just for me...
But for everyone.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Time to bounce.
- Well, Barry, looks like
your vitals have stabilized.
How you feeling?
- I feel fine.
So no luck finding Deon yet?
- So far,
satellites haven't found
any traces of his
temporal energy signature.
- And he's a time god,
so who knows where
or when he might be hiding?
- Plus, I think Deon's only
just now starting to realize
the full scope of his powers.
But I don't get it.
Not once did he mention
chasing after you.
- Well, unlike the others,
he might not know
that I survived.
- That makes sense.
- You know, it's weird.
Every time you and Chester
talk about Deon,
he sounds a lot
more reasonable than Psych
and a lot less lethal
than Fuerza.
- Even so, being able
to control time
makes him
the most powerful Force yet.
- He could stop you in
your tracks anytime, anywhere.
That's his power.
It's like he's the opposite
of the Speed Force.
He's the Still Force.
Which I guess would make Fuerza
the Strength Force.
And that would make Psych
the Sage Force.
- [laughs]
- If this new Force is
more powerful than me,
then how did you
defeat him, Cisco?
- [laughs]
Uh, I didn't defeat him.
Chester P. did.
- Uh, I got lucky.
Yeah, I'm gonna leave
the going mano a mano
with big bads to the Flash
from now on.
[cell phone dings]
- Oh, that's Kamilla.
Supposed to meet up at Jitters.
Caitlin, you still in?
- Absolutely.
Let me grab my bag.
- How about you, Chess?
You still down?
- No, I actually have
an errand to run,
but bring
a brother back a Vibe-a-ccino?
- Duh.
[both laughing]
Hey, you didn't get lucky,
all right?
What you did out there...
I'm proud of you.
- Yeah.
I guess I'm just a man
trying to do the right thing.
Make my Pops proud.
- Caitlin, hurry up.
I'm trying to get this coffee
and a cronut.
- Iris, thanks to you,
I'm seeing things
a lot clearer now.
Well, I imagine you two
are anxious to get home,
so I'll see you in the morning.
- Wait.
You're staying here tonight?
- Well, I want to know
right away
if the satellites
find the other Forces.
- Yeah, no, I get that,
but we'll get an alert
if that happens.
Nora, we have clean sheets
in our guest room
and plenty of blankets.
- Sounds cozy.
- Yeah, it is.
You should stay
with us tonight.
Right, Barry?
- Um, sure.
Yeah, of course.
- [laughs]
You have no idea how much
that would mean to me.
Really.
- It's our pleasure.
Thank you.
Come on.
- I got you, Pops.
Time to finish
what you started.
Okay.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is that damn time bubble back?
- Oh, no.
I just liked the look,
so I decided to swing
by a thrift store.
Picked up these bad boys too.
- Listen, we need to talk.
- Ugh.
Nothing good ever starts
with, "We need to talk."
- This new state liaison
that's auditing CCPD,
her name's Kristen Kramer,
I just found out
that she's here to catch
a dangerous
fugitive meta-human.
- Hmm.
- She's here for Killer Frost.
- That's not who I am anymore.
- I know.
I just got to find a way
to make her see that.
In the meantime,
you need to lay low.
- Yeah.
That's not gonna happen.
- She's former
Army Intelligence, Frost.
- I don't care if she's
Xena, Warrior Princess.
I am finally free
to live my own life,
and no one is gonna take that
away from me.
So if this Kristen Kramer
wants to come after me,
then I say bring it on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.
[thunder rolls]
[electricity surges]