Najid, cut
the horses loose!
We have to turn back.
We have been riding
for six months.
And we've lost 20 men.
But we survived.
Yes. By chance.
Any one of us could
have met that same fate.
We were the strongest.
Remember why you're here.
In the West, we would be enemies,
and I would have to kill you.
At least here,
we have a common goal.
Oh, yes.
This black powder.
It turns air into fire.
And kills a dozen men
at one time.
It is the weapon
of our dreams.
And what if
it's just a myth?
Men have sent word
that it's real.
And those men are dead.
And we are next.
We have no maps,
no medicine
and no food.
No one is going back.
We take inventory
of what we have left
and finish
what we started.
There's not much here.
The moon is strong.
When the horses
are fresh, we move.
- To where?
- North.
If they keep after us, we'll
kill them in the mountains.
The magnet.
Too heavy.
Useless.
I'll have it.
It's all yours.
Amigo, only you would carry a
stupid magnet through the desert.
I can use it
to make a compass.
Rizzetti won't make it.
The wound is festering.
We'll be dragging
a corpse.
I heard that.
He's earned the right
to die where he wants.
I've been left
for dead twice.
It was bad luck.
For who?
The people who left me.
Maybe Rizzetti's right.
Where are they?
Hill tribes?
It's no man.
Then what is it?
Whatever it is,
it's hunting.
What was that?
I don't know.
I took its hand.
- We need to move.
- Agreed.
I'll take the hand with us.
What the hell for?
So someone can tell me
what I just killed.
Persistent bastards,
aren't they?
We'll take the rise,
make a stand there.
What a long shitting
way to go to die.
Mother of God.
I have no need
to go down fighting.
Agreed.
I say we take our chances with
the gents in front of us.
I haven't surrendered
in a while, eh?
It'll come back
to you.
Follow my lead,
we'll be fine.
Of course,
my friend.
Where you go,
I follow.
You're doing such
a great job already.
They know what it is.
And they don't
look happy to see it.
All the more reason to get
the hell out of here.
Our weapons
are on that table.
Have you lost
your mind?
I can take out the guards on
the perimeter with my bow.
You cut the legs out
from under the officers.
I must confess, this is
not my favorite plan.
Where was this found?
You speak English.
Fantastic.
Where was this found?
It wasn't found.
It was taken.
That thing killed three men
before we took it down.
Where?
Two days' ride.
North, in the mountains.
Two of you,
you did this?
Well...
I killed it.
Alone?
Tell me how.
A swing of the sword.
The hand,
it came away clean.
The beast fell back
into a chasm.
Why are you here?
We came to trade.
We were ambushed.
You are soldiers.
Mmm.
Are you killing us, sister?
Two lost travelers?
I think she'd like that.
If it is death, my dear,
we need time to pray.
I'm trying here.
Sister, I know a siege
when I see one.
What comes at you so hard
you need a wall like this?
What the hell
did we kill out there?
Tao Tei.
You killed
a Tao Tei scout.
You killed it alone.
You're correct.
We are under siege.
But we did not expect the
attack for another nine days.
Attack?
Tao Tei.
What the hell
is a Tao Tei?
Many things about your
story have importance.
You are not to die today.
The black are
the foot soldiers.
And the red?
Those are the archers.
And the blue?
They're all women.
What the hell
do they do?
Look at this army.
Have you ever seen
anything like this?
Incredible.
They look nervous.
It's a big wall
to be so nervous.
Do you hear it?
William, over there.
Why isn't he tied up?
There's our escape.
We need to move!
We need to move
or we die!
Go, go!
Go and fight!
Cut me loose!
Fight or run?
Run where?
Aim for the eyes!
William!
Hey! Bitch!
William.
I need a shot.
What god made
those things?
None that we know.
Think they'll
hang us now?
I could use the rest.
You've earned
General Shao's praise.
Will they come back?
Yes.
All we can do
is prepare.
Who are you?
Easy.
I'm Ballard. Hmm?
William.
This is Tovar.
What are
you doing here?
We came looking
for black powder.
I bet you did.
I came with mercenaries
for the same thing.
Twenty-five years ago.
And did you find it?
Finding it and leaving with it
alive are two different things.
You saved the west turret.
That was extremely diplomatic.
We weren't
being diplomatic.
We were trying
to stay alive.
You smell like animals.
Thank you.
Clean up
and they'll feed you.
He knows where the powder is.
Then why is he
still here?
He needs help
getting out?
Right.
We play our part,
take the powder
and go home.
I didn't sign up for this.
Which part?
Well, all of it.
But mostly the monsters.
There's a lot of them.
We really do smell.
General Shao welcomes
you as honored guests
of the Nameless Order and thanks
you for your skill and courage.
We are honored
to be honored.
Is that the best
you've got?
Commander Chen thinks your bow
is not worthy
of your skill.
Tell him there's no
better weapon here.
They wish
to see you shoot.
In here?
What was that?
He thinks you have fear.
Too many people.
Get one of the cups.
Now?
I want to eat.
You remember
how to do this?
Last time didn't go so good.
We were drunk.
How high?
Ten yards.
Six hands to the right.
Turn around.
No, I'll do it this way.
On my count.
Amigo...
One.
Two.
Three.
Pull.
Good luck with that.
I want food.
Who taught
you English?
Sir Ballard.
English and Latin.
Heard he's been here
for 25 years.
You won't
let him leave.
He must stay here.
What about us?
Pace yourself.
The meals
are regular here.
I hope not
to stay that long.
I like your thinking,
but I suggest you keep
your plans private.
You aren't
the first Westerners
to come here looking
for black powder.
We'll discuss it tonight.
Bring your partner.
How long
have you been here?
Always.
I was not five years old
when I came here.
I have no other family.
We're the same.
I was given to an army
before I can remember.
As a soldier?
Worse.
As a gleaner.
Packs of children, we'd
clean the battlefields.
After, when the
fighting's over.
I became a page,
a pikeman's boy...
For your country?
No. I fought for food.
You fight to eat.
You live long enough,
you fight for money.
How many flags
do you fight for?
I don't know.
I fought for Harold
against the Danes.
I saved a Duke's life. I
fought for him until he died.
Fought for Spain
against the Franks.
Fought for the Franks
against Boulogne.
I fought for the Pope.
Many flags.
We are not the same.
Meet me on the Wall. I have
something to show you.
He should be
careful with her.
She's very powerful here.
Then it is a fair contest.
Come.
Hmm.
You wish to try?
She says men
have so much to teach us.
I don't think
that's what she said.
You know what I think?
I think you're afraid.
You said that
this morning.
And yet,
here I am.
Yes.
Here you are.
Will you jump?
Or not?
These men know
what they're doing?
Wrong question.
Whether or not
the cable is attached,
that is the question.
And the answer?
Xin ren.
Xin ren means trust.
To have faith.
Here, in this army,
we fight for more
than food or money.
We give our lives
to something more.
Xin ren is our flag.
Trust in each other.
In all ways,
at all times.
Well, that's all well and
good, but I'm not jumping.
I'm alive today
because I trust no one.
A man must learn to trust
before he can be trusted.
Then you were right.
We're not the same.
My God!
A taste, a glimpse.
A few pilfered grains from Strategist
Wang's supply of black powder.
He's mastered the transmutation
of these elements.
People speak
of a weapon.
There are many
weapons here.
Why have we
not seen them?
There are many
things you have not seen.
And many things you should
pray will not be needed
before the siege
is through.
The Tao Tei will return.
When the drums
call to battle,
the guards leave their posts and
take their positions on the Wall.
That is our moment.
We want to be
riding away
as the battle rages.
And the armory doors?
You have keys?
I have black powder.
Enough for
several doors.
He brings us in.
We get us out.
As you fought,
where was this stone?
In my bag.
Its unseen force
is powerful.
I believe this strange
stone could help us.
We try everything.
Where are the
Tao Tei now?
The mountains, regrouping.
Where do they
come from?
About 20 centuries ago,
there was an emperor whose greed brought
deep suffering to all of China.
The heavens sent the meteor
that struck Gouwu Mountain,
turning it green
and releasing the Tao Tei.
From that day on, the Tao
Tei rise every 60 years
to scourge
the north of China.
They come to remind us of what
happens when greed is unchecked.
They eat anything,
alive or dead,
and take food
to their queen.
She depends on her
soldiers to feed her.
Only with the food they provide
is she able to multiply.
The capital, and its two million
people, is only 800 Ii away.
If the Tao Tei ever had
that much nourishment,
no corner of the world
would be safe.
You can't hunt them?
Men try.
They disappear.
We never find
their bones.
This is envoy
Shen from the palace.
He has brought important records
to help with the coming battle.
A 900-year-old
battle report.
At the Hansha gates,
three beasts
mounted the Wall.
They killed many men
as they went forward.
Then, by the grace
of the ancient gods,
the beasts stopped...
...and sat peacefully
as we slaughtered them.
At the Hansha Gate,
was a magnet just like this one.
I believe that magnet was the
reason that two of you Westerners
killed the Tao Tei
so easily.
I believe the magnet
makes the Tao Tei deaf.
Without instruction,
they fall still.
How can we be sure?
Why not try it?
Capture a Tao Tei.
See if it works.
How?
No net is strong enough.
Hunt them.
Like a whale.
You know what that is.
Uh... A water beast.
Hundred times
the size of a Tao Tei.
A spear that grabs. Hook the bone.
Pull them up.
I've seen
it done in Spain.
What the hell
are you doing?
We need to be free
when the attack comes.
How many chances do you
think we will get?
Be injured. Be missing.
Be a coward.
Get out of this.
We did enough.
He'll be here.
When?
When it's over?
We start
and he will find us.
Start?
We're jumping
off a cliff here.
I have everything.
Powder, tools, maps.
It's all hidden and
arranged along the route.
Once we start,
there's no going back.
I'll find him.
Forget him.
He'd rather die trying to
impress the new general
than grab the key to every counting
room and brothel in the world.
Good God, man.
The time is now!
I can't go
without him.
More the spoils for us!
We need his bow!
No, no, no. Stop!
There's too much tension.
Chain will break.
That way. That way.
Let him run!
Stop! Stop!
We need longer for the
sleeping potion to work.
That way. That way.
We need to isolate it.
Separate it from the others.
The chain won't hold much longer!
William, wait.
These arrows will
scream as the Tao Tei run.
Aim for the sound.
I'm only saving
you so I can kill you myself.
Grab an ax,
we're fighting blind.
Not yet.
I know what to do!
The fire's not
holding them back.
Die well, brother.
What the hell
are you doing?
She's listening.
Did it work?
Yes. The beast
was captured.
My friend...
He was unharmed.
Why did you go
over the Wall?
Did I say it right?
Thank you.
Black powder.
It is a terrible weapon.
It would be better if
you had never seen it.
I know very little
of the outside world.
But it seems to me,
the greed of men is not that
different from the Tao Tei.
Is that true?
The strong take
what they want.
Forget what you have seen.
Hmm?
You're much
braver than they think.
You wounded?
I was looking for you.
To say thank you.
You feel good, huh?
Maybe you sing
a little song, eh?
I will join you.
We can sing together how you
saved the grateful chinos.
You saw what happened out there
and that's what you say?
I see black powder.
I see a man
forget his friends.
The black powder's
not going anywhere.
What goes nowhere is you.
You'll never get
what you want from this.
You think they see you
as some kind of hero?
A man of virtue?
Maybe you can fool them,
but I know what you are.
You know what you are.
A thief,
a liar,
and a killer.
And you can never undo
the things you have done,
and you will
never be anything.
Good to see you again,
amigo.
Nothing?
No.
How do you know
he won't betray us?
I don't.
They'll kill him. They'll
kill him no matter what.
The time they spend
killing him
is time they are
not chasing us.
Careful with that.
There's powder here.
Tovar.
Have a look.
See if it's gone out.
Is it safe?
Of course it is.
Shake it off, man.
To work.
I thought
you said it was safe?
We're in, aren't we?
You're here.
We've come
to our senses, eh?
Ballard has
planned well.
Getting out is easy.
There's a gate.
20 miles west.
We dodge
the hill tribes.
We can make it.
They need us here.
They need more than us.
These people are doomed.
Don't be a fool.
I've been a fool.
I'm done with it.
Brother, please.
We've been fighting
for nothing.
For greed.
Amigo,
after all the blood,
and cold, and pain,
with this black powder
in our saddle bags,
we win.
You come with me.
I can't do that now.
Stay and fight.
William...
Think he's dead?
It'd take a lot
more than that.
Come on.
Hyah.
I tried to stop them...
You dare to speak to me?
I didn't do this.
And you came here
to trade.
And you knew nothing
of black powder.
What a fool
you must think I am.
If I was with them,
why would I be here?
I tried to stop them.
I tried...
You lie.
Some part of you knows
that's not true.
If I were not the General,
I would kill you myself.
Which way,
left or right?
Go up and take a look
from the high ground.
Hyah!
No!
No! Bastard!
What happened?
We have failed.
The Tao Tei
are in the Kingdom.
You are free to leave.
Take what you wish and go.
This was the
General's final order.
Where is she?
To do what?
To fight?
Is there a chance?
There's only one.
Kill the Queen.
Kill the Queen,
or we all die.
Leave.
Tell the world
what you have seen,
and tell them
what is coming.
I'll need my bow.
If I'm to join you,
He wishes
to join us.
No.
No, don't throw
that thing near fire!
Above you!
Behind you!
I set you free.
And here I am.
There's the Queen!
They will not attack
while the Queen is feeding.
We have a chance!
Hold on!
There is
an underground canal here.
Has it been breached?
The Tao Tei should
all be above ground.
And the one we captured?
We load it up.
We feed it.
And it will return
to its Queen.
Good.
You'll have one hell of
a scar, but you'll live.
We'll come back for him.
They've broken through!
Patience, William.
And it will go to the
Queen when it's done?
It should.
It Will.
Let it in.
I can get a shot
from above.
Go! I'll hold them back.
Wait. Not yet.
Hit.
Go higher.
I'll get
a better shot.
General!
It's up to you now!
We have one black
powder weapon left.
Give me the spear.
I've trained for
this my whole life.
I'll get you the shot.
I've got you.
So, how's life
without me?
A little slow.
You're a hero after all.
Well, it looks that way.
You seem pleased
with yourself.
And what are they giving you
for all of your troubles?
A bag of gold?
A victory parade
along the top of the Wall?
All the black powder
I can carry.
And a cavalry escort
to get me home safely.
Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
So what is this? You're
here to rub my nose in it?
Well, would you
blame me?
The last time I saw you,
you left me for dead.
And the time before that,
I saved your life.
True.
You know, the Emperor
gave me a choice.
I could take
the black powder,
or I could take you.
Please tell me
you chose the powder?
I don't even
know you anymore.
The horses are
saddled and waiting.
Best we ride
before nightfall.
I'll be inside.
Don't leave
without me.
I came to say goodbye.
I understand congratulations
are in order.
General of the
northwest territory.
That's quite
an honor.
Seems you've made
your choice.
Him?
Believe me, I'm already thinking about
trading him back for the powder.
I heard that.
Perhaps we were
both wrong.
We are more similar
than I thought.
Thank you, General.
Are you sure you don't
want to go back?
Of course I do.
I just don't trust you to
make it out of here alone.