- Previously on "The Flash"...
It's the city, they're
responding to my article.
- This guy says he saw DeVoe
on 5th and Knoll
two days ago.
- Yeah.
- This means DeVoe can't
hide from us anymore.
- The injection of dark matter
from the thinking cap,
which overwhelmed
my synapses.
The more I try
to use my brain,
the sooner
I'm going to lose it.
- DeVoe plans to position each
of his five satellites
around the globe.
- And when the satellite
link up...
- He'll use that network
to emit a series
of dark matter bursts.
- It will reboot
the pre-frontal cortex
of every man, woman,
and child on this earth.
We know we need
a tech-free projectile
to stop DeVoe's satellites.
We've been looking
for an object
when what we really need
is a person...
Amunet.
- It will deliver
one savage concussive blow.
But you only get one shot.
- Initially we set out
to enlighten the world.
Now you want to rule it.
I am leaving you, Clifford.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Agent Diggle.
Good to see you, sir.
We have the specimen ready...
- The specimen?
That's a man in there
that we are supposed
to protect.
- Of course, sir.
Our most powerful
meta-dampeners
are set on the building,
I assure you.
- Elvis Banana.
- Hendrix Spaghetti.
Eye scan?
- DNA sample, sir.
Central City branch
had some trouble with
a transmogrifier
this time last year.
You're good to go, sir.
- Good.
Now drop the dampener.
Got caught in a blast.
Slugger's microchipped now,
Dampener scrambles
the frequency.
- Technical,
this is Castlellan.
Lower the drawbridge.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
[tinny pop music plays]
♪ ♪
Modern music.
So lacking in the harmonic
resources necessary
for expressiveness.
["Hallelujah"
by George Handel play]
For profundity.
[muted choking]
Timpani in Handel's orchestra
weighed 140 pounds,
the exact gravitational force
that I am now exerting
on your lungs.
- ♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
Music Appreciation 101.
This evening's recital will
be conducted by your...
beloved professor.
chorus: ♪ Hallelujah ♪
[blasting sounds]
- Who goes there?
Oh!
- My wife...
cared very little
for violence.
- Stay where you are!
- Me...
- [screams]
- Not so much.
- [yells indistinct
command]
- What's going on?
- Oh...
[bullets whizzing]
- Go!
[chorus singing]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
[electricity surges]
[beeping]
- Get out of my mind!
- Move, move, move!
[choir continues singing]
[men shouting]
- Ahh!
[groaning]
[bone cracks]
♪ ♪
[gunshots]
- [whispering in
foreign language]
[chorus continues]
[men grunting, yelling]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hallelujah,
Hallelujah ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ And he shall reign
forever ♪
♪ And ever ♪
[bodies thudding]
["Hallelujah Chorus" stops]
[chorus resumes singing]
- Hey!
Oh!
[crack]
[alarms blaring]
- Come on, come on!
♪ ♪
[magnetic thrumming]
chorus: ♪ Forever and ever ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
- [murmuring under breath]
- ♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
[alarm blaring]
- [screams]
- And God said,
"Let there be light."
[end chords]
[dramatic music]
- Okay we've got eyes
on Cape Canaveral,
Space X,
and the Xichang Space Center.
- And Blackhawk Island.
That's every launch pad
south of the 39th parallel.
- Good man.
- Okay, are we sure
that DeVoe is gonna
launch the machine
from an airfield?
- If he's shooting
five satellites
into synchronous orbit,
that's the latitude he needs.
And whether or not
he's still moping around
about his wife ditching him,
he's gonna resurface.
And he's gonna do it soon.
When he does, I whoosh.
You whoosh.
She bangs.
- If I can get there
in time.
I mean, I'm still not
fast enough
to make it to DeVoe's
pocket dimension.
- That's why we split up.
Yeah.
Each one of us stakes out
a different launch pad.
- You're serious?
I mean you've seen DeVoe
in action.
- Yeah, the guy's a one man
Legion of Doom.
So send the Super Friends.
- Okay, but we're not at full
super strength right now.
I mean Joe's got the baby
on the way
and Caitlin's looking
for Killer Frost.
Harry's...
- [grunts]
This chair came
out of nowhere.
So hey, Allen.
West-Allen.
Ramon.
- Cisco.
- Cisco Ramon.
Guys.
Check this out.
Okay?
Somebody has been blogging
about the Thinker.
About DeVoe and the bus metas,
all of it, okay.
And if we find this blogger,
we can stop the Thinker.
- Hey, buddy.
- That's...that's my blog.
- Look at the byline.
It's not written by
Iris West-Allen, okay?
It's written by
Anonymous Central City Citizen.
[mimics explosion]
Mic drop.
- Hold on to that mic.
- It's imaginary.
- I asked you to proofread this
for me, remember?
- You asked me
to proofread this when?
This morning.
That's when.
When you said, "Harry...
will you proofread,
will you proofread..."
- Yeah.
- Let's start by finding him
a room with less chairs.
- Okay.
Good.
Is that powder on the floor?
- Ay-ay-ay.
- You have 400,000 new views.
That's amazing.
- [chuckles] I know, right?
I mean, people have been
writing in from all over
sharing their theories
and reporting DeVoe sightings.
- And Marlize sightings?
- Yeah.
I've been trying
to track her down for days.
I know Harry thinks
that they split up,
but she's still
just as dangerous as DeVoe.
- Right, so wh...why would
we send citizens after her?
I'm all for telling people
the truth, but...
- Yeah, I mean
after I convinced you.
- Yeah, I just...I don't know.
I don't know
if it's the best idea
to send people out there
to do our jobs for us.
- No, we're inspiring them,
Barry.
I mean, we could be
the ones to show them
how to do the right thing.
[cell phone buzzes]
Oh.
I just got a new lead.
- Hmm.
- Fallout...
- So you think
your psychosis made
a friend of yours disappear?
- Yeah, I mean, she's
a really good friend of mine.
Almost like a part of me.
- So your friend, is...
she with us here right now?
- Oh, no,
I'm not schizophrenic, um...
she's more like
another personality.
- Dissociative
identity disorder.
That is usually caused
by trauma,
and from your history
you've had quite a bit.
- Yeah, I did see
my fiancé die.
Twice.
And then my next boyfriend
turned evil.
- I actually meant
childhood trauma.
Tell me about your father.
- My dad?
He was the best.
Loving, supportive,
always pushed me
to get smarter.
- And how did you feel
when he passed?
- I...He had ALS, he...
was always hiding
his symptoms from us.
He never wanted us
to see him suffer.
- Sometimes when we're young
we repress things
that scare us.
- Oh, I'm not repressing
anything from my childhood.
My missing friend just appeared
a couple years ago.
[phone buzzes]
It's my adult life
that's got me like this.
I'm so sorry.
I have to go.
Do you charge by the hour?
- For you and your friends,
the quarter-hour.
- I got a tip about Fallout,
but it's been scrambled
by Kilgore's code.
- Hmm, not anymore.
Consider it unscrambled.
- Devoe.
Where's A.R.G.U.S. keeping
Borman? Do we know?
- I-I can't ping Lyla,
but I can try Dig.
- I'll just go get him.
- Uh...
- Trash can.
- Ooh, how about the recycling?
- Nope.
- I got it, I got it.
- Really?
- Seemed like a good idea
at the time.
- Sorry, man.
- [vomits]
- I'm sorry.
- Mm-hmm.
- [groans]
- Can we just...
I'm sorry.
- I hate you.
What is this about?
- Neil Borman,
the man we left with you,
with A.R.G.U.S.
Where you keeping him?
- Barry,
that's classified information.
I'm not the director of
A.R.G.U.S. I...
- Dig, we don't have time.
Please.
- He's at a place
called the Castle.
It's a thousand miles away
from anything.
- Please.
Can you check it?
[dark music]
[computer beeping]
- Okay, looks like
everything's fine in A.R.G.U.S.
except for me.
Um... Says I checked
in six hours ago.
- DeVoe can shapeshift.
With Melting Point's powers,
he can trick a DNA scanner
and take over the building.
[alarm blaring]
- [screaming]
- Hey, Diggle.
Diggle, Diggle.
- 10,000 rads and climbing.
Borman's body's gone
critical already.
We can't save him.
- If that chamber hits 100k,
it'll start generating
nuclear fusion.
Like core of the sun fusion.
- Infinite fuel.
- He's using Borman's body
as a battery.
- That's the last piece
of the Machine.
- Wait. A battery?
Borman's containment cell
is 10 feet tall.
- And DeVoe has the power
to shrink it down.
He'll charge the satellites.
All he'll have to do
is launch 'em.
- How long do we have?
- At this rate of fusion,
we have...
12 hours until
the Enlightenment begins.
[dramatic music]
- Okay, Dig's back
in Star City.
Now, I'm going
after DeVoe.
- Don't go storming
the Castle just yet.
You're looking at motion-
activated electro-shock plates
that A.R.G.U.S. installed
in the facility.
- 70,000 volts?
You hit one of those,
you'll be knocked out for sure.
- So I'll avoid them
when I go in.
- Okay.
Genius idea,
if their placement didn't
randomize every couple hours.
- So DeVoe's basically charging
his battery for 12 hours,
completely protected
by A.R.G.U.S. defenses.
- And then he'll probably just
jump into a pocket dimension,
and he's out of there.
- What if I don't
avoid the plates?
What if I hit 'em?
All of 'em.
I'm serious. I mean,
if I go into Flash Time,
I could use each plate's
electric current
as a fuel source.
Then I'd be fast enough
to follow DeVoe into
his pocket dimension.
- You would get
a serious boost.
- Again, another genius idea,
if hitting the plates didn't
cause an electrical explosion.
- Yeah, but I'd be through
the pocket dimension
before the blast wave,
ready to blow up the satellite
on the other side.
[electronic beeping]
- Satellite results came in.
Okay.
Oh, frell me.
- What?
What is it?
- We got six plates
and six heat signatures
above them.
- There are A.R.G.U.S. agents
still alive in there.
- He has hostages.
- You can outrun
an electrical explosion.
They can't.
- How's he keeping
them suspended like that?
- I think I know how.
- Do you know what
my favorite thing
about teaching is?
Having a captive audience.
[electricity crackles]
- I haven't moved
from this spot in three days.
Baby, you're gonna have
to carry me into the hospital.
- Okay, so I got snacks.
I got clothes for you.
I got clothes for the baby.
Damn, I forgot something.
- Joe, we are not gonna need
a katana at the hospital.
- Okay, so you're
in my head again
and it's entirely possible
that we get attacked
by a samurai
at the hospital.
- You have already repacked
that bag five times.
You've read ten different books
on birthing methods.
- By the way, I love the one
about Lamaze.
- Yeah, but...
- Damn, where is this boy?
- You have already left Wally
a dozen voice mails.
- He's literally
on a time machine,
so he has no excuse
not to show up on time
to meet his new baby sister.
- [sighs]
- I'm sorry.
It's just nerves.
- We've both done this before.
Not gonna be any surprises,
okay?
This is gonna be...
totally sick.
[inhales]
- Sick?
[stammers]
Are you feeling sick?
- Nah, brah, nah.
This delivery
is gonna be sick.
Having this baby
is gonna be like
one epic wave.
[laughs]
- You okay?
You're scaring me.
[door knocks]
- Far out!
That's the 'za I ordered.
'Chovies and pineapple.
Tubular.
- Tubular, brah!
There's your 'za!
That'll totally be 8.50.
- Thanks, brah.
- Hey, this house is...
- Bitchin', yeah,
everybody says that.
- No.
Hard to find.
Those are some
gnarly bushes outside.
both: [laughing]
- Let's crush some 'za, brah.
Dude!
Dude?
- Where is she?
- Where is...?
Ahh, where is she?
I don't see her.
- No, Harry, I...I'm talking
about tracking down Marlize.
If DeVoe has popped back up
then she might too.
And we need to put her
in the Pipeline
before she causes
any trouble.
- How are you tracking her?
- Well, my readers
have sent in hundreds
of tips.
Plus there's
facial recognition
and credit card checks...
- Facts.
- Right.
- Wrong.
- What?
- You're looking at facts
when you should
be focusing on feelings.
You remember
the Council of Harrisons?
- I do.
- Handsome but annoying.
Well, they kind of taught me
that if you wanna...
if you wanna follow
DeVoe's actions
you gotta focus
on DeVoe's motives.
Which is basically
DeVoe's feelings,
and so feelings,
if you're Marlize DeVoe...
where are you gonna
feel safe?
- So if I dig into her past,
maybe I can figure out
where she is now.
Harry, that's really helpful.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Iris West,
for saying that, I...
I-I don't feel helpful
that much anymore.
So thanks.
- Hey, um...
Are you busy, Harry?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
Would you maybe wanna
help me investigate?
- Yes.
- Okay, cool.
- [chuckles]
- When...
- We're gonna...Right now.
- Hey.
Did you guys send an alert?
- We did.
We think we've figured out
how to stop DeVoe
and save the hostages.
- What...what is it?
- Us.
- You bring us
into Flash Time with you.
- Look guys, that's great,
you know,
you want to help, but
we can't split up in A.R.G.U.S.
if I'm holding onto you
the whole time.
- Well, survey says...
you don't have to.
- Have you guys been
researching me?
- At first we thought you
were vibrating our molecules
when we were in Flash Time,
but that didn't
explain why we were conscious.
- Which gave us
this brain blast.
When you run, you don't
just tap into the Speed Force.
You generate Speed Force
around you.
- It's like you're
creating lightning
to protect you
from the friction
Like an aura.
- So when I bring you
into Flash Time
I'm actually extending
my Speed Force aura to you.
- And what if physical touch
just focuses those powers?
- I could let go.
Share my speed.
- We'd only be able to last
a few moments
before we burnt out.
Like 55 milliseconds
of real time.
- And thanks to relativity,
that gives us just enough time
to rescue the hostages
while you chase DeVoe
down the rabbit hole.
- Guys, I mean...
you know everything
looks normal to me
when I'm in Flash Time,
but it took me months
to learn how to operate
like that.
- Exactly.
That's what makes you the
perfect candidate for training.
Train us.
- I know it's a leap, Barry,
but we're running
out of time
and I just think it might work.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Okay.
Ready?
One second on the clock.
Go.
- Oh, Flash Time,
how I've missed thee.
- Here we go.
- Is that lightning
about to hit me?
- You wanted to do this.
- It's working.
- Thank you, Speed Force.
- Okay, here we go.
Just remember,
when you're moving this fast
it's not about
running with your legs.
It's about staying calm,
focused, centered.
Otherwise you're gonna fall
on your ass at Mach 3.
- Yeah, okay, sensei,
I'm just opening a breach.
- You good?
- It's a little harder
than I thought.
Maybe if I shift my weight.
- You know,
you're burning up already.
You okay?
- I...
I-I can't move my leg.
- What?
- My leg's not working.
- All right, stay calm.
Remember, concentrate.
You're slowing down.
- I can't really concentrate...
I-I gotta, gotta keep it loose.
I gotta keep moving,
I've got to breach, I mean...
- You gotta stay calm.
- Okay, well,
I gotta get the leg to move.
Now both of my legs are stuck.
- What?
- My...my legs are stuck.
[stammering] I'm working with
two frozen drumsticks here.
- Okay, just relax.
- Okay.
Now I'm falling.
Ah...
- You okay?
- Yep. Yep.
My leg's just asleep,
but I'm gonna get this.
I'm telling you.
- Okay.
- [exhales]
[phone rings]
- It's Joe and Cecile.
Do you think
I can spare a minute?
- Just gotta walk it off.
- Yeah, we could use a break.
- Good news is
you're totally healthy.
- [sighs]
- Thank God.
[psychic pulsing]
- Oh, no, Caitlin,
please don't think "relax."
If you were
nine months pregnant
and you suddenly started
craving Master Kush and surf,
I don't think
that you would relax.
- Actually,
I was thinking relaxin.
The hormone?
As we get closer
to your due date,
your body releases relaxin
to loosen the ligaments
to make it easier
to deliver the baby.
It's like
you're literally stretching.
- So you think this hormone
is stretching her meta powers?
- Yes, I think instead
of just reading people's minds,
she's now inhabiting them.
- Great. That's great.
I mean that's just
one more thing for me
to talk about in therapy.
I mean can you believe what
Dr. Finkel said this morning?
- Babe, we didn't see her
this morning.
- Uh, I did.
- She thinks that
I'm repressing something.
I mean, repressing something?
How crazy is that?
Oh, my God.
This Erlenmeyer flask
is covered in water spots.
- Yeah, she's definitely me.
Here why don't
I give you this.
It'll help you take
some deep breaths and focus.
- I'm familiar with an
albuterol inhaler, thank you.
[light music]
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
- Don't worry about it.
You're just going
off my instincts.
- How do we stop this
from happening again?
- I don't think we can
until you give birth.
So I think
the best thing to do
is actually keep you isolated
and use this.
- Come on,
we can handle that.
- Okay.
I'm gonna get back to training.
- Thank you, Caitlin.
Hey, Caitlin?
For what it's worth,
when I was you back there
for like 20 seconds,
it seemed like you were trying
to ignore something.
Something really big.
And if there's anything
that I've learned
from having these powers,
it's that you cannot hide
from anything forever.
You just be careful,
okay?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Marlize Malan.
Born in Cape Town.
- Cape Town.
Summers by the sea.
Picking grapes in the vineyard.
- Got a PhD in inflationary
theory and engineering.
- Cute little button nose
always buried in her book.
[chuckles]
So nice.
- Tenured as a professor
of engineering at Oxford
where she met Clifford DeVoe.
- Where she met
her husband to be.
Isn't that romantic?
A continent apart,
yet they find each other.
So romantic.
I mean, it's beautiful
when you think about it.
It's...it's...what?
- Beautiful. What is that?
What are you doing?
- I'm empathetic.
I'm being empathetic...
Council says be empathetic.
I'm empathetic.
You know?
I'm putting myself
in Marlize's shoes.
[snaps]
I should see  she's got
a pair of shoes,
put myself in 'em.
- No, Harry.
This?
This is not a love story, okay?
She married a psychopath.
- Psychopath now,
not then.
Back then he had feelings.
They loved each other.
He had feelings.
She had feelings
then he...
Lost the feelings,
and that's why she got out.
That's why she left.
She left.
West-Allen.
We should turn Marlize.
- Harry, no.
I don't think you even know
what you're saying right now.
- I know what I'm saying.
I know.
I have...I have bad days.
Dumb Harry.
But I'm not dumb today.
Today's a good day.
We should turn Marlize.
Marlize can help us.
- And why would she want
to do that?
- To stop the psychopath.
Right? Protect the man
trapped inside the monster.
Marlize can save everybody.
Marlize is the key.
- Harry,
we've tried that already.
With Savitar, remember?
It didn't work.
You can't save monsters.
- Marlize isn't a monster.
- [sighs]
- And besides...
the clock's ticking.
It's like ten hours
before the Enlightenment.
What do we have to lose?
- She stabbed me
with a katana, Harry.
Our lives are what
we have to lose.
We can't save anyone
if we're all dead.
- Right.
- We're going to bring her in
and we're gonna stop her
so she doesn't hurt anyone
ever again.
- Okay.
- I left some of my files
at home.
I'll finish
my investigation there.
- I'm gonna come with.
- No I'm fine, Harry.
You stay here, okay?
- I'll come with.
- Harry!
- I'll just stay here.
Just stay right here.
[suspenseful music]
- All right, just remember
to stay calm this time.
- Why are you looking at me...
- I wasn't...Both of you.
[sighs]
- All right.
Take two.
- Yes!
- Nice!
- Brrrrat!
- A little baby breach.
- That's right, Barry.
A baby breach.
And in time,
she'll blossom into maturity,
but for now, in
Flash Time, she's...
my little breachling.
- Okay.
Cait.
- Cold Gun's still not working,
just like Killer Frost.
- We gotta find a way to
off-set the friction.
- Ah, damn it.
- Oh...
- My leg's stuck.
- All right,
just stay calm.
Hey, watch out!
- Ah...
[dramatic music]
[bicycle bell dings]
- Dad!
My leg's stuck.
[tires screeching]
- Caitlin, watch out!
- Caitlin!
- Cait!
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- What happened?
- Training.
You came out of Flash Time
in midair.
I think you got
concussed.
- Then again, I'm not
the team doctor.
- I mean, I don't feel
nauseous.
Just hand me some
acetaminophen,
and get back to training.
- No, hold on.
We have to talk
about what happened.
- What do you mean?
You just lose focus, right?
- Yeah.
- No, it was...
I don't know.
Something pulled your focus.
- No, I'm fine.
- If this were the real thing,
you would have died.
- I'm not a liability.
- I know.
I am. I'm putting
you guys in danger doing this.
I mean I-I realize
you guys want to help,
but I've got
to stop training you.
- Barry, come on.
Those hostages...
- I'll find another way
to save 'em.
- You have to let us help you.
I mean, after everything
DeVoe did to us...
Killer Frost.
- She's right.
We're running out of time.
It's worth the risk.
- I'm not training you guys
just to get you killed.
I'm sorry.
[soft rock plays]
♪ ♪
[knocking on door]
- West-Allen!
[knocking]
West-Allen!
- Of course
he followed me home.
West-Allen!
[knocking]
West Allen!
- West-Allen!
- Apartment five.
Hi.
- Five...Oh, you moved.
- No.
- This...
This is apartment four.
- Four.
- You're in apartment five.
- Yes.
- So, look, I just came
to say you were right.
Trying to put myself
in Marlize's shoes,
and I forgot I should also try
to put myself in your shoes.
- Thanks.
It's very big of you to admit
that you were wrong, Harry.
- I'm not...I don't know
if I was wrong...
the word you said.
It's more like I'm dumb.
I'm dumb now.
- Harry.
- Yeah?
- Marlize is not
gonna help us
fight her husband
out of love.
- Love.
Exactly.
Look, she...look...
the Enlightenment was not
born out of love.
She's always been an activist.
Look at that.
Even before she met DeVoe,
she was trying to save people.
- Yes, her earlier papers were
very optimistic.
She thought
that technology could...
could liberate humanity.
- Humanity. Right.
- But she's not
saving anyone now.
- Not according to your
perspective.
What about her perspective?
Put yourself in her shoes.
- Come in, please.
- You know?
Just put yourself in her shoes.
Okay?
- Harry.
- Yeah?
- Take your shoes off.
- You put on my shoes,
and I'll put on your shoes.
We'll both trade shoes.
- No.
No, Harry, I don't
want try your shoes on.
I want you take your shoes off.
You're tracking mud
all through my house.
Please.
- Oh. Right. Sorry.
[murmuring]
It is kind of...
more of a loft.
- This is my home, okay?
This is the first place
that I've lived in with Barry.
It makes me feel loved
and safe,
and so we are going
to keep it nice and...
clean.
- What? What is it?
What are you thinking about?
- I think I know where
Marlize is hiding.
- Apartment four.
- No, not apartment four.
- Babe.
Babe?
- [sighs]
- What are you doing?
- I gotta get
this bag ready. Uh...
I got, I got snacks.
I got water.
I got a change
of clothes for the baby.
Forgot a change
of clothes for me.
[laughs]
- You're me?
both: [laughing]
- This a whole new level
of weird. Stop.
Give me this...
Sit down.
[light music]
Okay...
Better?
- Who the hell are you anyway?
- Okay, not better.
I'm calling Caitlin.
- What are you doing
in my house?
- Cecile, this is our house.
- Cecile? Why do you keep
calling me Cecile?
My name's not Cecile.
I'm Joe West.
- Um...
Okay don't! Joe!
Joe.
Joe, sit down.
Sit down.
Okay. I need you to take
a deep breath.
In through your nose.
Out through the mouth.
Close your eyes.
Imagine that you're sitting
in a big, beautiful sea.
The waves are cresting over
you, back and forth.
Those waves...
that's Joe.
Now look up.
Big, dark, beautiful sky
with one shining star.
That star is you, Cecile.
- [ exhales]
- Great.
How do you feel?
- Joe?
- Oh, God.
- You pulled me back.
How did you pull me back?
Lamaz?
- I-I had to switch
some things up
in my head, but...
Hey, am I crazy,
because you were...
- Babe, trust me.
There are far worse
heads I could have been
stuck in.
I love you.
- You figure it out yet?
- [sighs]
No, I-I shut down the
generator.
I can save the hostages,
but DeVoe still gets away,
and then, you know.
- Actually, I meant...
Have you figured out
how come...
you lost your damn mind?
- Okay. Look, I'm sorry.
I'm just...
- You're just trying
to keep us safe.
I know.
It's starting real familiar
coming out of your mouth.
- You're not ready to use
Flash Time.
Not like that.
- We will be ready
if you train us.
- It takes more than ten hours
to learn Super Speed.
Okay? You guys
could do in there.
- And if you don't
take us, we'll die anyway.
Our brains get wiped,
and that's it.
That's the end of our world.
- No!
Losing both of my best friends
and it being my fault...
that's the end of my world.
You may think it's worth
the risk,
but I couldn't live with
myself.
- Barry.
You cannot sideline
us because
of what happened to him.
- All right.
I don't need another therapist.
- Look we all lost somebody,
okay.
But that never
gives us an excuse
to shut each other out.
- I said drop it, all right?
- You think you're the only
one who feels bad
about Ralph dying?
- Guys...
- You know he came to see me
at Iron Heights?
He told me he was afraid.
He warned me he wasn't ready.
But I pushed him anyway.
I said go back out there
and do my job.
My burden.
- We made the bus metas.
We gave Ralph his powers.
You wanna talk about burdens.
I started this.
I shot that bazooka.
I opened up the Speed Force,
and I didn't do it
so you can stand here
and tell me you're going
to save the world alone again.
- I...I know that.
And I know we're running
out of time and...
I can't do this by myself,
but...
Everybody I've tried to teach
has ended up worse
than when I found them.
- And what about Ralph?
Was he worse?
You taught him
that when his back
was against the wall
and the world was ending
around him he could
always make the choice.
Make the choice
to be a hero.
We deserve that same choice.
All we need is someone
to show us how.
- You guys really
want to do this?
- It's not a burden
if we shoulder it together.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- We found her.
- You found Marlize?
- I think so.
She's in England.
- [sighs]
All right.
This is our last
extrapolator.
- You set the coordinates,
it'll breach you there.
We have to stop DeVoe.
By the time you get back...
- Hey.
I love you.
Go save the world.
- I love you.
[electronic beeping]
Where're we at?
- Borman's almost
at 100,000 rads.
- All right, we got to go.
come on.
- [screaming]
- Thank you, subject seven.
[continues screaming]
Now your fire will
light up the world.
- Perimeter's secure.
Once we're inside,
we'll have less than a second.
I'll activate the plates,
draw their charge.
- I'll lay the breachlings.
- And I'll protect
the A.R.G.U.S. agents from
the blast using this...
ice shooter.
- Ice shooter.
- Do I have to call it
an ice shooter?
- I thought Frostbite
sounded good.
- Guys, it solves
the friction offset problem
by shooting ice,
therefore it's an ice shooter.
You call it an ice shooter.
- Relax.
- It's just not
that hard.
- DeVoe must be shrinking
Borman's chamber.
- We can do this.
- Catch me if you can.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I've got the charge.
- Breachling is go.
- He's iced.
- Five more to go.
Remember, stay focused.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[sinister music]
[exhales]
We did it.
- "Once upon a time
in some remote corner
"of that universe,
there was a star
upon which clever beasts
invented knowing."
- You're quoting Nietzsche
at me?
- You destroyed a satellite.
Top marks, quick boy.
You can destroy a thousand more
and you will still
march closer to
the Enlightenment.
- I forget what Nietzsche said
about wiping minds.
I must have skipped
Philosophy class...
- Did I teach you nothing
this year?
Has nothing pierced
you thick cowl?
Think of it?
Or rather don't.
You'll just end up
hurting yourself,
so let me explain.
A world enlightened.
Within a day, all soldiers
will lay down their arms.
Every nuclear weapon
will be disarmed
within six months.
Poverty, famine, disease...
eradicated.
We will clean up the streets.
People will put down
their idiot phones
and become curious again,
and I will be there
to teach them.
I...not you...
will save this
godforsaken world.
- No, you'll just control it.
You want to take away
free will.
- A pittance for humanity
to pay
to know peace.
- But we wouldn't
know each other.
Parents wouldn't
remember their kids.
Husbands wouldn't
remember their wives.
- Good.
You hit upon
precisely the point.
Emotion is the father
of all error.
Chemicals in our brain
that distract us,
impede progress.
And the most destructive
and ridiculous imbalance
of all is that thing
you feebles call love.
I learned this
from experience, Mr. Allen.
And soon...you will too.
- What happened in there?
- All that matters
is that you're all safe.
- But DeVoe? Where's DeVoe?
- Hey.
Hey, don't worry.
Flash is on it.
- Thank you.
- What's wrong?
- I need your help.
Back when we were training,
I had this fragment
of a memory.
I think it's something
that I've been repressing
for a long time.
I don't remember much,
just that I was young
and I was terrified.
- Caitlin, are you sure
you want me to vibe you there?
I mean, maybe your brain
kept this memory
under lock and key
for a reason.
- I need to know
what it was.
I can handle it.
- Then focus on it
and hang on.
- Caity!
Oh, no! Caity!
Caity, are you okay?
Stay still!
We're gonna get you help!
- That's me.
Right there.
- Caity...honey, don't!
- [screams]
- [panting]
[whispers]
Killer Frost.
She was part of you
even then.
- The particle accelerator
hadn't exploded.
How is that possible?
- Empty.
- But this is their first
place together.
She would come here.
I can feel it.
The pot's still warm.
That means...
- We can have tea.
- No!
Marlize!
- Iris, she's not here.
- Come out.
- Iris.
- It's rude to breach
into a person's home uninvited.
And dangerous when
that person is holding
a grudge and a katana.
Why are you here?
- I got this.
We're here, Marlize...
we're here because you...
because...
Wait, uh, you...
You have...You...you've...
I can't. I can't.
- He can't verbalize it.
Not anymore.
Just like we hypothesized
but never observed before.
You're experiencing
the penultimate stages
of the Enlightenment.
You mind is being rebooted.
Soon you will be
without memories,
without relationships.
Just a blank slate
so that Clifford
may re-educate you.
Soon we'll all be
just like you.
- Marlize,
we have to stop him.
Your husband has gone too far,
and I think you know it,
or you'd be with him
right now.
- Yes, I left my husband.
But that doesn't
change the fact
that he's right.
If anything, his betrayal
proves his very point.
Man corrupts even
the best of ideas.
- Pessimism...
isn't smarter than optimism.
In this life
the bravest thing you can be
is optimistic.
- Familiar words.
- You said them when
you were at Oxford.
Two weeks before you met
Clifford DeVoe.
- I gave a speech
on technology and the
elimination of world hunger.
I truly believed it
could be done.
- He tried to change you,
Marlize.
But I think deep down,
you are still an optimist.
You still believe
in humanity.
And I believe in you.
You asked me
what I was willing to do
for my husband.
And now I'm gonna ask you.
What are you willing to do
for the world?
[intense music]
- Barry shot down
one of his satellites.
- He did...
- DeVoe didn't
seem to care.
- I'll try and see
if I can track it.
[alarms blaring]
I don't like that sound.
- This says a Star Lab
satellite's been activated.
- It's DeVoe.
- He's using our satellite
to replace
the one you destroyed.
- Well, can you stop him?
[electronic whining]
- He's here.
- Hello, professor DeVoe.
- No, no, no.
DeVoe!
[pounding]
[dark music]
DeVoe!
- Initiating Enlightenment
protocol.
- Let there be light.
♪ ♪
- He did it.
- The Enlightenment.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
- God saw...it was good.
[dark, sinister music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.