- Eddie?
- Iris, I've missed you so much.
This is not possible.
You were...
Are you okay, babe?
You look a little flushed.
Yep, that's a fever.
Can I get you something?
Some water?
No, I'm fine.
No, I know what you need.
Your favorite, chamomile tea.
Oh, and don't worry.
I know I've been gone a long time.
But I'm not leaving
until you're all better.
Okay?
Iris? Why is there an attractive
blond man in your kitchen?
Oh, hey, I'm Eddie.
Eddie Thawne.
Iris's fiancé.
[kettle whistling]
[news anchor on TV]
C. C.P.D. has ordered a city-wide curfew
after the shocking massacre
that happened earlier tonight.
The mysterious assailant
remains currently...
No sign of Deathstorm anywhere.
- How's it going here?
- Good.
The Mental Augmentation Chamber's
just like I remember.
Not that I could forget six weeks
of living inside this thing.
So, we're seriously going to turn
Frost into an anti-Deathstorm?
We know Deathstorm is made up
of pure thermodynamic energy.
So we use the MAC to harness particles
from its home dimension
and then beam them
into your consciousness.
The reaction should transform Frost's
body into a being like Deathstorm.
You'll be able to create fire,
defy gravity...
And consume Deathstorm's fuel source.
Once you absorb all that grief energy
out of Deathstorm...
I'll be able to snuff him out, for good.
Well, it's official.
This is the craziest plan
we've ever had.
[Frost] Then, let's get crazy,
'cause I'm not letting that Skeletor
put another bony finger on my sister.
I just got to finish
the MAC's cryo-circuits
and it should be good to go.
[Cecile] Guys, I need you
in the med lab. It's Caitlin.
Is she okay?
I don't know.
Her biometrics are stable,
but I just felt another
huge wave of grief from her.
I just keep picturing Dad die.
It's all I can see over and over again.
- Him on the floor.
- What is wrong with her?
Remember when Deathstorm took Caitlin?
It was trying to change her
into something else, its bride.
But it still needs her
to experience more grief
before the transformation is complete.
Must've dialed up
one of her worst memories.
You're going to be okay.
We've got a plan.
What if it doesn't work?
What if I'm stuck like this forever?
Don't even think like that.
Just get some rest
and I'll be here when you wake up.
How much longer till Chester
has the cryo-circuit ready?
I'm not sure. Maybe an hour.
We don't have that kind of time.
I'm gonna call backup.
- We still need to find Deathstorm.
- I know.
Can you feel anything?
No. It's like he's disappeared.
[singing] Capacitor's connected
To the inductor
Inductor's connected
to the cryo-circuit
[chuckles]
The cryo-circuit's connected
to the...
Frak me.
[ominous wind rustling]
[Gideon] I still haven't
identified the cause
of Iris West-Allen's temporal ailment.
Okay. Keep trying, Gideon.
In the meantime, could you run a search
for any extra-dimensional energies
or cold fusion anomalies in the area?
Of course, Barry Allen. Search...
Gideon?
[alarm blaring]
He's here.
[distorted] Actually, I'm everywhere.
And nowhere.
I was born a long time ago.
Before Maltus, before the stars.
During that lonely blackest of nights.
I was there when the first gas cloud
sank and collapsed.
I was there when the first beings
drew their final hissing breaths.
I am decline. I am entropy.
I am the master of death
and all of its inhabitants.
My beautiful boy.
[Chester] Guys, it's my dad.
He's back.
[Allegra] Esperanza's here.
I need backup...
That's better.
Where I'm from,
there's not so much noise.
If you take one step toward Caity,
I will send you back
to the hell you came from.
My home is much further than hell.
It's a lonely place.
At least it was,
until Ronnie died in a Singularity.
His mind found me.
His grief became my hunger
and his love became my guiding light.
So you're trying to take my sister
'cause you're lonely?
Ronnie's feelings
showed me how to end my suffering.
I'll show you suffering.
You can't hurt me.
You're still fighting back,
just like your father intended.
So what? You got my dad
hiding in some other room
so you can sic his grief ghost on me?
My phantoms only appear to those
who can grieve them.
Which is why you won't be
having any visitors.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It's simple.
You don't have anyone to grieve,
because your grief isn't real.
I wish
I knew that all those nights
I was drinking away my pain
at O'Shaughnessy's.
The sadness you've experienced
in your existence
is just a copy, an echo of real emotion.
Like all of your feelings. Like you.
You are so full of it.
Then why can't I sense
any loss inside your mind?
Why can't I smell those hormones
dancing along your neural receptors?
It's because when Thomas
built you in his lab,
he gave you everything
you need to protect Caitlin.
Cryo-kineticism, healing, rage.
But as for the rest of you,
he just copied what was inside her.
He cloned a few scraps of her feelings,
tinkered with her personality traits.
But he never gave you
any authentic emotions.
He never built you
your own consciousness, your own soul.
- That's not true.
- Grief and pain,
those are the things that make people
truly alive, and you don't have them.
Shut up.
Because you are not a real person.
You're a faulty experiment,
a broken mirror who can't
aid me in my cause like the others.
I said shut the hell up!
Come on, come on! In here.
[gasps]
Let me guess,
your ghost dad's back, too?
Yeah, I lost him in the hall.
I don't get it.
These things can walk through walls.
Why the hell aren't they coming in here?
I don't know. But is it getting
kind of toasty in here?
Yeah.
Oh, crap! The doors.
There's no way out.
They chased us in here on purpose.
No, this isn't real.
You're not my mom.
Argh! [panting]
Please, sweetie, stop.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
This is just another manipulation.
Just some part of Deathstorm
trying to screw with my head.
Why would you say this about me?
I'm your mom.
No, you're not.
I came here to help you
because I love you so much.
You have to believe me.
I've been watching you, your life,
what's happening to Iris.
There's no cure
for her temporal sickness.
No secret answer.
You're going to lose her forever.
That's not true.
Her condition's stabilizing.
I can still save her.
Like you saved me?
I'm trying to warn you, Barry.
You can't have a family.
Your father died.
I died.
And now your poor, sick wife
is going to die, too.
And there's nothing you can do
to stop it.
Sure I can't get you a cup?
Oh, no, thank you.
Eddie.
You know what sounds great right now?
Some soup.
Soup? Really?
Why don't I whip up some of
Uncle Robern's famous chicken noodle?
Oh, yeah. Yummy, babe.
Okay, I'm gonna need some chicken stock.
Um, uh...
You know what would be great
with that, too?
Some chipotle chilies.
Yummy.
Do we have any?
Yeah, I'm sure they're in there.
Just keep looking.
Nope, not seeing any chilies.
But I do see you, Sue Dearbon.
- Argh!
- Come on. Let's go.
[groans]
Come on, guys.
You know nobody's leaving
till Iris is all better.
[Frost] The team's trapped.
How's Caity doing?
It feels like she's getting worse,
and I have no idea why.
Oh, God!
There's something coming.
It's more grief.
Caity, no.
[Frost] Her vitals are spiking
and she's burning up.
She keeps changing,
and Deathstorm is nowhere near.
No...
It's not Deathstorm.
I have felt this grief before.
It's the team's. It's Barry's
- and Allegra's and Chester's and Iris.
- [voices chattering indistinctly]
I can feel all of their pain
and their sadness
flooding out of them
and pouring into Caitlin.
That's why he sent the ghosts
after them.
The more grief they feel,
the more goes into Caity.
And the sooner she becomes his bride.
- [deep voice] Burn.
- [gasps]
Burn.
War. Home.
Please tell me you can do something
to stop this grief.
Or you can use your powers
to help her somehow.
Frost, I am sure as hell gonna try.
[Mark] Everybody decent?
Finally. What took you so long?
The cryogenics department
at Fast Track Labs
has really improved
the security recently.
Just not as much as they thought.
Et voilà, madame.
Your very own cryo-circuit.
Well, you must be the infamous Mark.
This baby here
should modify the MAC no problem.
And then we can temporarily
transform you into...
I'm sorry.
What are we transforming you into again?
The anti-Deathstorm.
Right. Man, you kids on Team Flash
do some crazy stuff.
[wheezing]
- Is Caitlin gonna be okay?
- Yes.
As soon as we get the MAC working.
Let's go.
I got her.
[groans]
Okay.
Trying to blast a hole in the door
is out.
What the frak
is this thing made of? Titanium?
Actually, yes.
And all my tech just bricked
from the heat.
And then the thermostat died at...
137?
Great. So not only
are we trapped in here,
but we don't know how hot it is?
Humans don't go hyperthermic till
200 degrees Fahrenheit, give or take,
- which means that...
- You've got about 20 minutes.
When your internal temperature
reaches 105 degrees,
blood flow starts to decrease.
At 107, organs fail
and brain function slows.
By about 109...
you'll believe in quitting.
[Allegra] Don't listen to him, Chuck.
Nothing he says means anything.
"Chuck"?
You let her call you that?
No, no, she's right.
You're not real.
I'm getting that door open.
Why do we love science, Chester?
Because regardless of who's
conducting the experiment,
the results are right and wrong.
Black and white.
Just like this situation.
Whether I'm real or not,
you care about each other.
And here you are, trapped in a room.
Forced to watch each other die.
And when you do...
[speaking Spanish]
I'm done with your games.
You could burn me alive right now.
But you won't.
So tell me, what do you want?
I want to prepare you, Barry.
Iris' impending death
won't just mean that she's gone,
it will mean that Nora and Bart
will never exist.
I'm not trying to be cruel.
But the truth is,
your legacy isn't heroism.
It's heartbreak.
You know what people like you
will never understand?
Love is a strength, not a liability.
The heartbreak
that I've suffered,
the people I've lost,
they don't hold me back.
They make me fight that much harder.
And I'm going to fight for Iris.
Then why didn't you fight for me?
Why did you stand by
while Thawne stabbed me in the gut?
Thawne didn't kill you!
He killed my mom.
And as much as it hurt,
I have accepted her death.
And what about the rest of them?
Thank you for everything.
[grunts]
- Have you accepted all their deaths too?
- [screams]
Barry told us about Deathstorm and
the ghost that he sent after Chester.
You're one of those apparitions,
aren't you?
And where's your precious Barry now?
Nowhere to be found, as usual,
while you're laid up in here,
waiting to die.
Iris is not going to die.
[Eddie] Trust me.
As a dead man myself, she's toast.
And she knows it.
Just like I knew.
I thought my sacrifice
would mean something.
That I could erase
the Reverse Flash from existence.
That finally... I could be a hero.
[Iris West gasps]
But then Eobard Thawne came back.
Again and again, and again and again.
What I did...
it didn't matter at all.
I died for nothing.
And now you've made the same mistake.
You sacrificed yourself for nothing.
I saved Barry...
and I helped stop Armageddon.
Then what happened?
The timeline got reset, but you're
still suffering the consequences.
Can't you see? Your death
is gonna be just as pointless as mine.
Something's wrong.
Why are you... happy?
Who? Me?
Oh, well, that's easy.
I'm young, I'm rich.
I'm a total dime.
And before you so rudely destroyed
another one of my brand-new phones,
I hit the panic button.
Hey, Detective Pretty Boy.
Come on, before it wears off. Come on.
Nana?
No, please don't go.
Chyre...
Chyre, hold on, man, please. Chyre.
What did you do to them?
I showed them the deaths
of the people they love.
And now, with the help of their grief,
the bride's transformation
will be complete.
All right. Cryo-circuit's functional.
Ready to merge your cold fusion cells
with Douchestorm's
dimensional particles.
This has to work.
Hey, master cryogeneticist over here.
Not just a pretty face.
Trust me.
Okay.
Cryo-circuit is alive.
Activating augmentation receptors.
[machine whirring]
Deploying dimensional particles.
[groaning]
[exhales]
Hey, are you okay?
Did it work?
- Are you anti-Deathstorm?
- Only one way to find out.
What's wrong?
I'm just me.
No fire powers, no nothing.
This stupid machine didn't work.
I mean, that doesn't make sense.
It should work on anyone, any organism
or sentient being with a consciousness.
Or anyone who's truly alive.
I guess we know
what the issue here is then.
It's me.
[Mark] How can you be the problem?
- It doesn't make sense.
- You said it yourself.
The reaction depends on the MAC
being able to put particles
in someone's consciousness.
What if that person doesn't have one?
What are you talking about?
I mean, of course
you have a consciousness.
Not according to Deathstorm.
He and I had a little chat
about why everyone on Team Flash
got visited by a ghost except me.
He said that I couldn't experience grief
because when Thomas created me,
he just gave me a copy
of all of Caity's emotions.
He's obviously just messing with you.
Don't let that fire freak
get in your head.
What if he's not?
Do you know what my earliest memory is?
It's not of Carla singing me a lullaby
or Thomas throwing me on his shoulders.
It's of Caity being hit by a car.
[screams]
'Cause that's the first time I woke up.
To take the hit.
And then I just drifted back
into her subconsciousness,
locked away there for years.
Watching Caity live her life
and have friends.
You know, so when I finally
started coming out more,
I wanted to make up
for lost time, you know?
Finally live a life.
Boy, was I stupid
for ever thinking that was possible.
'Cause it doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter how many
life coaches I get,
or if I get my own body
or do a bunch of art,
or get my own boyfriend.
Because I'll always
just be a copy of the original.
An echo.
'Cause I've never been really alive.
And now that's gonna get Caity killed.
Frost...
If you are not really alive,
where does that leave me?
You're the only person I've ever
cared about more than myself.
Or at least equal to myself.
I guess we're both screwed up, then.
Yeah, that's definitely true.
But the way I see it, you and I
have been through a lot, right?
And through all of those ups and downs,
I, for one, have seen you have
loads of emotions, all kinds.
Especially when it comes to Caitlin.
You love your sister like crazy.
And wherever that love came from,
whether you were born with it,
or your dad gave it to you,
or you put it together yourself
over time,
built it with pain and heartache...
That love is as real as it gets.
Believe me.
Then why didn't Deathstorm
use any of my grief?
He said he couldn't even find it in me.
Maybe he couldn't find it
because you've got it
buried so deep
in that foxy head of yours.
Maybe because you love so damn hard,
and you know the flip side
would totally suck.
Yeah, I mean,
I have been a little closed off lately.
I'm sorry, Snowflake.
Grief is a necessary part of life
and you are very much alive.
That's it.
Yes!
Frost, the MAC's been
working fine all along.
But the chemical reaction
was missing a necessary ingredient.
Frost, I think I know how to finish
your transformation.
Sue, Dad, it's not real.
You guys, you're stronger
than this bastard.
That's no way to talk about your fiancé.
I know you want our grief.
But you're not gonna get an ounce
from me.
I know you are not the real Eddie.
No, I'm not.
Because he died.
Just like you're gonna die, too.
No, it's not real.
[Eddie] Yes, it is.
Now you're gonna lose everything, Iris.
Your family, your future.
Everything you worked so hard for.
It hurts, doesn't it?
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] You and I, we had history.
But you and him had a future.
And that's so much worse, isn't it?
Because you're not just
watching him die.
You're watching everything
you could have shared die, too.
You can try all you want,
but you'll never get out of here, son.
And neither will she.
She's gonna die...
because you're not smart enough
to find a way out.
All that time tinkering with machines,
building countless gadgets,
and the one time you need
to come up with a big idea,
the one time it really matters...
you can't do a damn thing.
Chuck... I got you.
It's okay.
It's... It's not okay.
It's not okay. I'm so sorry
I couldn't fix this, Allegra.
No, don't feel bad.
That's how they want us to feel.
But Chuck, the truth is...
right now, with you,
I feel happy. Happy I met you.
Me, too. Me, too.
[screams]
Oliver traded his life for yours.
Stop! Stop it!
No! You stop fighting, Barry.
Give in to the pain.
The pain you still feel.
Let your sorrow wash over you.
So the bride may be reborn.
[deep voice] I can see them.
Stars, endless stars.
Hey, Caity.
I'm not even sure if you can hear me,
but there's something I need to say.
You know, I used to be afraid
that because we shared a body,
I was only gonna get to live
half a life.
That I was only gonna be half a person.
I realize now that isn't true.
You didn't take anything from me.
In fact, it's just the opposite.
You make my life complete.
And I got to be honest,
I'm a little worried
we're not going to make it out of this.
And that I might lose you forever.
And I can't handle that.
I would die.
I love you more than anything.
[groans]
Is that what's supposed to happen?
Argh!
The MAC's been working fine all along.
But the chemical reaction
was missing one ingredient,
the spark that gave Deathstorm life.
Grief.
Frost just had to let herself feel it.
[groans]
Damn! I've never felt this warm before.
It's all that power.
Frost, I can feel it
radiating off of you.
That's 'cause I'm not just Frost...
I'm Hellfrost.
[gasps]
[panting]
Sue, Dad, are you guys okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. We're okay.
The team...
They're all okay.
So, hot stuff...
what do we do now?
We kick some ass
and save my sister.
You look totally badass.
Thanks. I feel badass.
But Caity's not okay.
In fact, Cecile says she's worse.
Then this isn't over.
Deathstorm is back
in his home dimension,
which means he can still
put guilt inside of Caitlin.
Or send more ghosts after you guys.
Yeah, I talked to Iris.
Deathstorm sent one to the loft.
You saved the whole team.
And now I'm gonna save Caity
by extinguishing this son of a bitch.
Hey, when that thing comes back,
you're gonna need some backup.
No, I'm the only one who can do this.
Even Barry's lightning can't stop him.
- And if anything goes wrong?
- You'll get me out of there in a flash.
Okay, wait. Flash, lightning...
Are you saying that he...
Whoa.
[chuckles]
But if he can't help you,
you've got to let me try
adjusting my gauntlets.
- I can pump up the cryo-kinetic outputs.
- There's no time.
Then maybe we need to make some time.
Look, I told you. I was born for this.
But I'll give you something
to remember me by.
- Damn.
- There's more where that came from.
I...
Did I break you?
No, I...
Go save your sister.
I'll be here when you get back.
[Mark] Okay.
You guys do this all the time?
Yep. That's the gig.
How do you stay so calm, man?
It's nerve-racking as hell.
Welcome to Superheroing 101.
This is it.
I can sense all that precious grief
inside you, Cait.
You're almost ready.
I've waited so long to end my solitude.
It's time to start our honeymoon,
my bride,
because I want forever
to start right now.
Surprise!
What have you done?
Now let's party.
Are you sure she can do this?
We have to trust her.
I will burn you to ash.
You first!
Come on, Frost. Give him hell.
You can't keep me from my bride.
Who do you think you are?
More than you can handle.
Go to hell!
[groans]
Now it's time for me to feed.
[grunts]
That's it, party people.
All traces of supplemental cold fusion
and barometric anomalies are gone.
What happened?
Frost saved you.
Hellfrost, you did it.
Hell yeah, I did.
That's my gal.
[Frost] How's Caity?
She's doing fine.
Thank God.
Hey, I have a bourbon straight up
waiting for you when you get back.
Sounds great.
Guys, I'm not feeling so hot.
- Her vitals are crashing.
- What?
Frost.
You just woke up from a coma.
Are you sure you're up for this?
I have to be.
- What the hell happened?
- Mark, hey, hey...
- Why isn't she moving?
- We don't know.
We don't know. But Caitlin is working
on her, and she is going to save her.
- Okay, I can help.
- No, you can't.
I'm sorry, but you need to leave.
- I can't...
- Mark, hey, it's going to be okay.
Caitlin has to focus.
Hey, let's just give them
some space, yeah?
Okay, her pupils are dilated.
Her heart rate's spiking. Talk to me.
Tell me what happened out there.
We manipulated her cryo powers
in the MAC
so that she could absorb
Deathstorm's energy.
It's what saved you.
But Deathstorm's been doing this
for a millennia.
So I'm guessing he can
handle a lot more power than she can.
- [machine beeping]
- She's going into cardiac arrest.
Okay, I'm gonna inject her
with cold fusion.
That'll bring Frost back
and that'll kick in her ice healing.
Come on, Frost, come back to me.
You did it.
[machine flatlining]
No. No, no, no, that's impossible.
Her ice healing, it's not kicking in.
She's flatlining. Get me the paddles.
Here, here.
[paddles powering up]
Clear.
[imperceptible]
Caitlin.
Caitlin, Caitlin.
C. C.P.D. has lifted the citywide curfew
after confirming that,
as of an hour ago,
the mysterious mass murderer
plaguing our city is no longer a threat.
Citizens are cleared to fully resume
their normal...
Well, Deathstorm's finally gone.
Frost is a real hero.
Caitlin and Barry have been
in there forever.
Frost is gonna pull through.
You doing okay, Mark?
Yeah, thanks.
I've been doing a lot of thinking,
you know.
Frost and I had a lot of plans.
Like I scored this trip
to the Himalayas,
where you jump out of a chopper
and snowboard down,
and at the bottom, at base camp,
they have this cute little restaurant
where every dessert is made of ice.
I know she's probably gonna say
it's stupid,
but then secretly not hate it at all.
Kind of like how she feels about me.
I just wanna make her smile.
There's nothing better than that.
Well, she's lucky
to have you in her life.
We all know I'm lucky
to have her in mine.
Barry.
Something happened.
Where is she?
Come on, where is she?
Frost died.
That's not possible.
I'm sorry. She didn't make it.
She's gone.
[sobbing]