[Iris West] Previously on The Flash...
[the Monitor] Vibe must live again.
I am no longer Nash. I am... Pariah.
I freed the Anti-Monitor.
And now I am forced to bear witness
as he destroys world after world.
[Rene] Oliver sacrificed himself
to create this new world.
[Barry] Our earths must have merged
when we helped Oliver
reboot the universe.
We all live on the same Earth now.
[Iris West] This is the same guy
that kidnapped your cousin Esperanza
and turned her
into a meta-assassin.
The guy you questioned was killed
in the same lot you questioned him,
on the same day.
There's a major UV energy
coming off this thing.
Looks like Team Citizen
has a new mission.
[pop music playing]
Come on in, folks.
After five months of Vibaccinos to go,
welcome to the new Jitters.
Here you go.
And remember, folks, CC Jitters
is here to stay, rain or shine...
Hands in the air,
you foam-loving fascists.
Are you kidding me?
We're already being robbed?
Jitters just reopened and was
immediately attacked by terrorists.
Why am I not surprised?
I'll go bail out those latte sippers.
[The Flash] Guys, I got this.
You, open the register!
Give me everything inside.
Dude, we just reopened.
There's barely anything in there.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh.
Well, I'm gonna start
blowing stuff up, then.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Oh, crap.
Sorry, I'm late.
I love what you've done with the place.
[all applauding]
[all] Flash! Flash! Flash!
Oh, stop.
Stop, you guys.
[Killer Frost] I'm sorry.
Crisis is over. We beat the bad guy.
And you're still worried because...
Because...
an infinite number of earths
experienced a cosmic heat death
from which only one Earth was rebuilt.
Hmm.
So now, not only do Superman,
Supergirl, and Black Lightning
live here,
but, now, our entire timeline
has been rewritten
so that they've always lived here,
and I don't remember owning this shirt!
Great shirt.
Besides, isn't that a good thing?
We're all one big happy family now.
No!
No! No, it is not.
Not when these guys...
...are crashing the reunion.
Not a single one
of our doppelgangers survive
to make it to Earth-Prime
as far as I can tell,
but we did manage to pick up
a butt-ton of bad guys, and aliens,
and more metas,
and you know the best part?
[chuckles] The best part is a bunch
of our old villains are back
with fresh paint jobs.
When did you have time to do all this?
Eden Corps, the Top,
Rainbow Raider...
Our Earth has more threats than ever,
and we don't even know
where they're coming from.
[knock on door]
What the hell was that?
Pipes. Bad pipes. The heating.
Don't worry about it.
[man] Let me out.
Are you sure?
'Cause it looks like
you locked Nash in the closet.
No.
[knocking continues]
[Nash] Let me out.
Okay, one of the auxiliary pipes
was leaking,
so he's patching it up in exchange
for a crypto-circuit.
Fine! Don't let me out.
I'll let myself out, actually,
thank you very much.
I'm gonna put
an Atlantean shoulder check
into this door and bust right through.
- In three, in two...
- Okay.
...in one! [grunts]
What's up?
[sighs]
Killer Frost.
It's just Frost now.
Give me my crypto-circuit,
or I'm gonna punch you in the throat.
I have your crypto-circuit,
and I could give it to you,
[chuckles] but I'm not really sure
what you'd need it for because...
you're an adventurer, so shouldn't
you be off somewhere adventuring?
Preferably, not here?
Yeah, I mean, Gorilla City
is part of Earth-Prime now.
Don't you wanna go myth-bust it?
No.
Gorillas are atheists.
[laughs] Are you kidding me?
No, I'm gonna run tests on my dig site
to ensure that nobody ever accidentally
reopens the anti-matter universe.
Run your tests.
But I've already run tests,
and that cave is staying shut,
so you're not really needed here.
If you ran the tests,
then I'm really needed.
- [sighs]
- What happened to Magenta? I liked her.
[Iris West] Isn't it great?
It's still our number one story.
Thanks again, friend.
- Iris, hey.
- Hi.
I was running back from a car fire
on route 119, and look who I found
on the way back.
- Hey.
- Digg, hey!
[chuckles] How's the fam?
Oh! Everyone is very busy.
Lyla just accepted a new posting.
So, next week, we'll be taking the kids
to Metropolis.
I heard.
So shouldn't you be at home,
helping to pack boxes right now?
Right.
But...
Ah!
Oliver's last will and testament
was read yesterday,
and he left something...
for you, Barry.
Oliver's mask.
It's the original.
This is the one I made him.
Yeah, it's interesting because Oliver
was never a man given to sentiment.
Hey.
Do you see this?
Right above the left eye.
Oliver hasn't worn this in years.
Why is there a mark on it?
I don't know. Felicity skimped
on the dry cleaning?
Or he left it on purpose.
I mean, you just said it.
Oliver wasn't sappy.
What if the mask is a clue
to some new threat out there,
- something too dangerous...
- [cell phone chimes]
...to put in writing?
[Diggle] Barry, you got all that
from a smudge mark? I don't...
Iris, what do you think?
Um, that you two will have
to figure this out on your own.
I'm so sorry, babe. I gotta go meet
with this source right now.
Yeah, no, that's fine. Do your thing.
Write your story,
and Digg and I can work on this.
We can?
- [door opens]
- Can't we?
[door closes]
Were you followed?
- No.
- You sure?
Yes.
No. No recordings.
The people you're after,
they know my voice.
These people, you say you've learned
quite a bit about them,
so you should recognize this, right?
[man breathes shakily]
I spent 20 years working
for McCulloch Technologies.
R&D department, classified division.
And then this guy showed up.
He said his name was Malcolm Strombard.
He'd been promoted into our group,
but he had no technical know-how.
And last fall, I came in late one night,
and I found him
with the infrared photon rifle
we'd been developing for years.
The next day...
- [rifle cocking]
- ...he and the prototype were gone.
So I started looking into it.
And this man, Malcolm Strombard,
he doesn't officially exist.
Of course, no one at McCulloch
believed me, so they fired me.
The group that sent him
to steal that rifle,
they found out I was after him.
How they kill their own men.
They have destroyed
way too many innocent lives,
and they will not stop
unless someone helps us
bring them to light.
Someone like you, Mr. Huskk.
And I can stay anonymous?
No one will ever know your identity.
I will do whatever it takes
to keep you safe, I swear.
These people, they will not be
brought out of the shadows easily.
They live in the darkness.
In the absence of light.
[clanking]
[pants]
- I didn't talk.
- [weapon powering up]
I didn't talk. I swear.
[Huskk] They call themselves...
[man 1 screaming]
...Black Hole.
[speaks in Japanese]
[Cecile speaks in English]
You're telling me that
a secret organization has been operating
in Central City for seven years now?
Yes, and, according to my source,
they have a name.
[Iris West reading]
[Kamilla] We've been
building a timeline.
It looks like Black Hole's
activity started
just after
the particle accelerator exploded.
They've been abducting
and training meta-humans
like my cousin Esperanza,
and potentially others.
And Black Hole's reach goes far beyond
theft and training meta-human assassins.
They are also involved
in international arms deals.
And they kill anyone they believe
has been compromised,
including our mystery man.
He's now crispier
than the chicken strips
Allegra insists on ordering for dinner.
Better than your vegan donuts.
[exhales] Iris, have you told
Joe about this?
Yeah, I have, but Dad would have
to launch a RICO investigation
to pursue a conspiracy like this.
This is reporter territory now.
Okay, okay. Look, guys.
I get it.
There's nothing stronger
than a reporter's drive.
I literally can feel it
coming from all three of you,
but as your legal advisor,
I gotta tell you...
I think that running this story
is a mistake.
Iris, if McCulloch doesn't like
what they read,
they can sue you for defamation.
I know. My dad was worried
about the same thing.
But that's a risk
that I'm willing to take, Cecile.
Guys, we don't even know
who's running Black Hole.
We're gonna find out.
[Iris West] Yeah, she's right.
Reporters don't walk away
from the truth.
Now I have a meeting
with the CEO of McCulloch Technologies,
Joseph Carver, in an hour.
So, let's see if he's willing to comment
on what's been happening.
But, either way,
be prepared to go to print.
We are running this story
with or without his comment.
[whooshing]
I know it's sort of like asking
the ocean to be less wet,
but, Barry, do you think you could...
[clears throat]
slow down?
Digg, you wouldn't let me speed you
to the crime lab,
so I had to speed the crime lab here.
[chuckles]
Look, man, if Oliver really wanted you
to look into something,
don't you think
he would've left you a note
instead of some secret code?
Oh, because Oliver never kept
a secret from you before?
[laptop beeping]
There are sediment traces on the mask
usually found on islands
in the North China Sea.
- Like Lian Yu.
Barry, there's more than one island
in the North China Sea.
Yeah, but only one with Mirakuru.
Does that mask
really have Mirakuru on it?
Anton Ivo's super soldier serum.
You really think there's
any of this stuff left on the island?
Yeah, Oliver always thought
that some samples
could have survived on Ivo's freighter.
And we don't even know what the state
of Lian Yu is post-Crisis.
If somebody got their hands on Mirakuru,
they could become a living weapon
or replicate it
and build an entire army.
Digg, this is...
This has gotta be
why Oliver left me the mask.
He wants me to find
the last stash of Mirakuru
on Lian Yu
before it threatens the world.
Look, I know you don't want me
to run you there,
but it's a 20-hour plane ride.
That's too much.
What you got?
My wife and I started this company
with three employees.
Now we have almost 3,000,
but I still know
each one of their names.
It's what Eva would have wanted.
It's very thoughtful, Mr. Carver.
Joseph, please.
I'm a huge fan of The Citizen.
How can I help?
Well, I have a source who can prove
that one of your classified
photon rifles was stolen last fall,
and it's now in the hands
of a secret organization
linked to terrorism,
kidnapping, illegal arms deals,
and... murder.
Do you care to comment?
Maurice, tell the board
I'm running a little bit behind.
Ms. West-Allen and I need to speak
some place a little more private.
Great.
[beeping]
Your source, it's Gene Huskk, isn't it?
I completely respect your need
to protect your sources,
but there's something
that you should see,
off the record, for Huskk's sake.
Just a sec, please.
[sighs]
[door opens]
Someone did infiltrate
the R&D division here at McCulloch,
but it wasn't a secret organization.
[inhales deeply]
It was Obsidian Tech trying to steal
one of our prototypes.
But Huskk couldn't accept that.
He became convinced
there was some larger conspiracy.
And the paranoia consumed him.
He became troubled,
started scaring other employees.
I had no choice but to let him go.
Mmm.
But I can assure you that we have dealt
with this problem internally.
We just completed our investigation,
and we're getting
a whole new security system
starting tomorrow,
new badges, new cameras, the works.
There's no story here. [chuckles]
Well, with all due respect, Mr. Carver,
I think that there is.
Maybe it's just one that you won't like.
Hmm.
Ms. West-Allen, everything that I do,
I do in my wife's honor.
To protect her legacy.
A story like this could really damage
our company's reputation,
not to mention scare our investors.
I'm asking you,
please, don't run this story.
I understand.
You have an obligation
to your shareholders.
Thank you.
But...
I have an obligation to the truth.
You were robbed, Mr. Carver,
and I get that that's embarrassing.
But the public deserves
to know what happened
before anyone else gets hurt.
So...
if you wish to withhold comment,
that's fine.
But I'm running the story either way.
One hundred thousand views in one hour.
That's gotta be a record.
Citizen just fired
its first shots at Black Hole.
This is a cause for celebration.
- Ooh.
- Are you even 21?
I'd hold off on the balloons and bubbly.
McCulloch Tech just sent a memo.
They are suing The Citizen
for defamation.
[powering up]
- [scoffs] This is ridiculous.
- Iris...
"Fabricated statements,
deliberate omission
of exonerating evidence..."
Iris, something's not right.
Carver is just trying
to bury us in legal fees.
He's just trying to scare us.
Everybody down!
[sizzling]
Why is someone shooting at us?
It's them. It's Black Hole.
Okay, we gotta go.
So they can kill us outside?
Okay, look, it's me that they're after.
Okay? So you guys get to S.T.A.R. Labs,
I will make my way out
through Nash's tunnels.
No way. We're not leaving you.
Look, I have to make sure
that my source is safe, okay?
Once I do, I will meet you there,
I promise.
Now we need to go.
On my count, okay?
One... two...
three. Go.
- [gunshot]
- [sizzling]
[camera clicking]
Go, go, go.
[exhales]
You're okay. Oh!
- What happened?
- Black Hole tried to assassinate Iris.
She went to go find her source.
- Cecile went to Joe's.
- Where's Barry?
He's in Lian Yu.
I've been trying to radio him,
but that place is a total dead zone.
What about those clicky things
you guys use?
The extrapolators don't work.
Now that the multiverse is gone,
the physics behind breaching
has changed entirely.
But don't worry. Frost is out there
looking for the shooter.
She should be careful.
Do you see these burn marks?
Whoever tried to kill us
was using high-intensity light.
[Cisco] Holy crap.
I'm glad you two made it out alive.
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You're fine.
[sighs] Good.
Why didn't you tell me
that they're in danger?
I could've gotten them outta there.
Don't come at me, Nash.
I'm not here to keep you in the loop.
You're not even a part of this team.
Oh, that's so hurtful.
How's your little team doing in the
standings? How's your little team...
Okay, see, this is exactly
what I'm talking about.
No, you don't care about the team.
You only work with us
when you want something from us.
No, keep me out of this.
So what is it this time?
You got a couple glyphs
you need Allegra to X-ray for you?
Or maybe you just want to open up
another Pandora's box of hell.
Are you kidding me?
I was the only one
trying to stop Crisis.
A Crisis you started!
Billions of worlds,
trillions of people gone.
- Like they were never even born!
- And I paid for it.
As Pariah, I paid for it
and still managed to help
defeat the Anti-Monitor.
Which did nothing
for the people who died.
Oliver, Harry,
Jesse.
An infinite number of Harrison Wells.
And we're stuck with the one
who killed the multiverse.
Babe, what the frak was that?
Just making sure we learn
from our mistakes.
Iris is still out there, guys.
And we need to figure out
who this assassin is
before they get to her first.
[breathes shakily]
Thank God you're safe.
I'm not. Neither are you.
Black Hole isn't what we think.
[gunshot]
- [groans]
- Oh, my God!
Mirror.
[breathes heavily]
[weapon powering up]
[tires screeching]
[engine revs]
[weapon powering down]
- Iris.
- Boss, you're okay!
Yeah, no, I'm fine, but my source isn't.
The person that tried to kill me
got to him first.
Hey, Cisco, where's that binder?
- Right here.
- Thanks.
Where is it?
Her. Dr. Kimiyo Hoshi.
[Cisco] Hoshi?
She went missing four years ago.
She's an astronomer out of Tokyo
with the power to fuel Starlight,
but her meta powers
aren't precise enough
to do the kind of damage
you showed me in those photos.
What if she used
the photon rifle to focus them?
Good thinking. Maybe the reflector chip
could condense her UV photon emissions.
The rifle is the weapon.
Now she's the ammunition.
So Black Hole turned her
into some kind of evil light doctor.
So we've got a brand-new,
more powerful, murder-happy Dr. Light
on our hands. Another new meta-surprise,
- courtesy of Earth-fraking-Prime.
- [Iris West] Actually, you know what?
Hoshi killed my source,
but I managed to save some evidence
he gave me. Ow! [winces]
Dammit.
Hey, you should sit down.
I'm fine.
- Did you get hurt out there?
- I said I'm fine.
Whoa, whoa! Call Frost, now.
- [Diggle] That was on the freighter?
- [Barry] Yeah.
If there's anything left, it's in here.
Open it up, man. Let's see what's in it.
All right.
This can't be right. I searched
the whole island a dozen times.
[chuckles] Take the win, man.
- There's no more Mirakuru left, Barry.
- No,
Oliver's mask, it's a warning.
Or...
maybe this is exactly what it was
intended to be in the first place.
- A gift.
- No, man, no. It can't just be a gift.
There's gotta be
something we're missing.
What if somebody got
to the Mirakuru first?
- Really? And left the box behind?
- I don't know.
Okay, I need to run more tests.
Or why don't we bring in the DEO
or call Felicity or Thea?
We can't just let somebody
create another Deathstroke.
We have to stop this threat, man.
- I have to finish what Oliver started.
- Barry.
[crackling]
Are you all right, man?
Yeah, I'm...
That's never...
I'm just frustrated, I guess.
[Diggle] Yeah.
Yeah.
Look, I think I know exactly
what went on here.
Oliver and Thea came to this island
a couple of years ago,
and they faced off with the man
who used to live in this cell,
Deathstroke himself, Slade Wilson.
Oliver brought his uniform with him.
Which is how he could have soil
and Mirakuru on his mask.
It wasn't a warning at all.
You're searching for a mission
that doesn't exist, Barry,
but no amount of search
is gonna bring Oliver back.
[Diggle sighs]
That man sprinted
from crusade to crusade.
But, Barry, life is more
than just the mission.
Unfortunately,
Oliver learned that too late.
He wouldn't want you going down
that same path.
Oliver died
so this Earth could live, Digg.
I have to do everything
I possibly can to protect it.
Oliver died for more
than this Earth's survival.
Oliver laid down his life
so the people he loved
could live theirs.
That includes you.
Life's a marathon,
not a sprint, Barry.
Slow down and enjoy it.
[Caitlin] So,
Kamilla asked me to check on you.
What are you watching?
So my latest experiment jump-starts
my neurons. They're currently...
- Harry.
- ...firing at 120 times per second.
I think we can get to 200.
So, this is... [chuckles]
It's progress. It's real progress.
I'll let you know. Anyway, miss you.
He was regaining his intelligence.
All of Earth-2...
wiped out.
And he doesn't even know it.
But that wasn't your fault.
Wasn't it?
When the Monitor gave me
my powers back for Crisis...
I remembered how powerful I used to be.
I can't help thinking that
if I hadn't stopped being Vibe,
maybe I could have sensed
that first anti-matter wave.
Maybe I could have saved them.
And that's why you've become so obsessed
with all the new threats.
You want to protect everyone
who did survive on Earth-Prime.
Cisco, do you regret
taking the meta-human cure?
No.
Do you miss being Vibe?
Caitlin, it's not that simple.
I don't know.
You know...
I think you might be
onto something over here.
With all these new threats...
changes to our reality...
we need someone whose job it is
to compile all of them.
Somebody who remembers
the difference between...
the way it was and the way it is.
Yeah, but...
what you're talking about,
that can't just be done in a day,
and it certainly can't be done
in some room
in the middle of Central City.
I know.
But I still think
you're the man for the job.
Besides, maybe some time
away from Central City will
allow you to figure out
who you want to be
in this post-Crisis world.
Yeah.
Maybe.
[imperceptible]
There you go.
Thanks.
So, you gonna tell me?
You're thinking...
of running the story.
I know what I was doing, Dad.
Really, Iris?
Frost told me.
You have fifth-degree burns.
My forensics guys have been
in your office for hours,
and they've found nothing.
There's no bullet holes.
There's no casings.
If that assassin would have...
murdered you today,
I would have no evidence
to bring her in.
Black Hole attacked my office.
Dad, they nearly killed my friends.
They murdered my source
right in front of me.
He's dead because
I asked him to speak up,
and I have to honor that
by exposing each and every person
behind this organization.
So, I'm sorry, Dad,
- if you want me to give up, I...
- You know I wouldn't say that.
But this organization
has been in operation for years,
and their roots run deeper
than you have dug, Iris.
You can't win this war in a day.
Look, when you and Barry told me
that Crisis was coming,
I was determined to solve
as many cases as I could
because God knows
how many days I have left
to make a difference,
but then Crisis came.
Barry survived.
So, now, I have to remind myself
every single day
that we don't live
in Crisis mode anymore.
We have time now.
So what am I supposed to do, Dad?
How am I supposed to fight these people?
First things first,
don't go charging to the front line
like you have nothing to lose.
[exhales]
Now... Okay, your source...
Are you sure...
he hasn't told anyone else
about Black Hole?
No, no.
[sighs]
Actually...
someone else did know.
[speaks in Japanese]
- [in English] Did you sleep?
- No, I'm okay, Dad. Thanks.
- How about a glass of water?
- Yeah, okay, sounds good. Thanks.
[rifle powering up]
[groans]
Got you.
[gun cocking]
Lower your weapon now.
We got you surrounded.
Put it on the floor.
Pretty good Iris, huh?
Uncanny, babe.
Now it's up to the real one.
Mr. Carver. Hello.
Ms. West-Allen.
- What a surprise.
- I know.
Reports of my death
were greatly exaggerated.
Oh, careful.
There's a scrum of reporters
20 yards down the hall.
Might not be the most convenient time
to call up your meta-assassin.
That's quite the allegation to make
without any evidence.
Oh, no, there's evidence.
You gave it to me.
Your McCulloch ID.
It uses a microchip
that reflects ultraviolet radiation,
and as your former employee
tried to tell me...
...it's the same microchip
inside your company's reflector gun
and inside Black Hole's badges.
Black Hole has been using
your optics technology for years,
all while abducting metas,
like Esperanza Garcia,
who have light-based powers,
your area of expertise.
You placed Malcolm Strombard
in Gene Huskk's division
so that he could obtain the rifle
before it went to market
and then place that rifle
in the hands of the one person
who could power it,
Kimiyo Hoshi,
your personal assassin.
You weren't robbed by Black Hole.
You are Black Hole.
And you've been using
McCulloch's resources
to power a global conspiracy
in meta-human trafficking, weapon sales,
and murder for hire.
Now, would you care to comment?
I would...
but I don't think you have
the whole story yet,
because, if you did,
why would you be here trying to scare me
while your family risks
their lives for you?
Weapon down now!
[rifle powering down]
[grunts]
- [Carver chuckles]
- You're right.
I can't stop Black Hole tonight,
but I can't let you hurt anyone else...
which is why I've set up
a dead man's switch.
If I, my employees, any of my sources,
my loved ones die,
all the information I have
tying you to Black Hole
will be immediately released.
[groaning]
Come on.
[breathes deeply]
[Hoshi speaking Japanese]
[in English] Screw you.
So...
tell your friend to stand down.
[rifle powering up]
[cell phone ringing]
[Carver speaks Japanese over phone]
[rifle powering down]
[in English] That's it?
You're just leaving?
I follow orders.
[sighs]
- [reporter 1] Mr. Carver.
- [reporter 2] Mr. Carver.
[reporter 3] Mr. Carver.
- Mr. Carver, a couple of questions.
- [reporter 1] Mr. Carver.
- Mr. Carver.
- Just a few questions.
- A couple seconds.
[Carver] Hi, thank you all so much
for coming. Here...
Given new information
that has come to light,
I have decided
that McCulloch Technologies
will be dropping its lawsuit
against Central City Citizen Media.
[indistinct chatter]
Any questions?
Thanks for coming.
- Hmm.
- I'm going away for a bit.
I might not have my vibe powers anymore,
but at least I can still do
some good old-fashioned footwork,
so I'm gonna go...
suss out whatever brave new threats
we might have
to our brave new world,
and I was thinking, in the meantime,
maybe you could hold down the fort
here at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Ah!
Oh, you got cameras here?
There's no cameras.
- This is some kind of trick, right?
- No.
It's not a trick.
It's more of an olive branch.
Oh.
I'm sorry I said those things.
I should have held myself accountable
for what happened in Crisis,
but instead I chose
to take it out on you.
Anyway... [clears throat]
So...
Hitting the road?
Yeah.
So, while I'm gone,
do your best not
to break anything, will you, Nash?
Break everything
while you're gone, got it.
It's like you're literally not listening
- to what I'm saying.
- What's that?
- Nash.
- Hmm?
I hope you find what you're looking for.
[Iris West] How was Lian Yu with Digg?
I thought Oliver...
left the mask as a reminder
to keep fighting.
But with all the danger
we've been through,
I guess, I kind of forgot why I made it
for him in the first place.
It was so Oliver would
always remember
to protect the people he loved.
That's why he left it to me.
He wanted me to take my own advice.
I have been in overdrive
ever since we learned
that you were gonna die in Crisis.
I have spent the last month
trying to live every day
like it was my last, hell-bent on...
trying to make the most
of the limited time
I thought we had left together...
but Crisis is over now,
and you didn't die.
And I think I just...
- I forgot to...
- To slow down.
So are you also thinking
that tonight maybe we just...
take it easy?
Great minds.
Beautiful minds.
Oh, my God!
Mirror.
Eva.
[door unlocks]
What were you up to, Eva McCulloch?
[computer beeps]
[gasps]