I thought we had a truce.
I thought as much.
Your bravery strengthened
by the reassurance you gain
from enhanced healing.
Oh, it doesn't mean it hurts any less.
Pain is the debt we pay for change,
and I'm here to change the future.
Thanks to this experiment,
I now know the force required
to kill you when the time comes.
Oh.
I've seen your destiny, Flash.
I've watched you use your power
to destroy everything and everyone.
You still haven't told me
why I would do this. Huh?
What would cause me to turn my back
on everything I've sworn to protect?
Madness.
Many times in the past,
the pain you suffered
nearly crushed you.
But soon, a new despair will befall you
and it will create
an unbroken chain of sorrow so great,
your mind will crack.
And with it, the world ends.
You see, your power
has recently accelerated,
but so too has your ability
to descend into madness.
Tragedy is coming for you, Flash.
What remains to be seen
isn't whether or not you break,
it's when.
I have seven days.
I'd worry more about tomorrow,
if I were you.
I don't know the details
of what will happen,
but I know tomorrow
is the beginning of the end.
Your end.
I've granted you a chance
to defy destiny.
But I'll be staying close by.
As soon as I sense
your mind turning mad,
I'll find you.
Good luck fighting fate, Flash.
I'll be watching.
Okay. Uplink to the Tower
mainframe is secure.
You now have access
to our alien database...
...including any intel
we have on this Despero.
We appreciate you helping, Alex.
How long will it take to download?
Well, this new algorithm
works at light speed.
In fact, Caitlin,
that guy, Marcus,
that I connected you with,
he designed it.
If the world's still here in a week,
I'll be sure and give him a call.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys, I'll keep digging
and see what I can find out.
But if this Despero
has managed to stay off of our grid,
then he is a greater threat
than any alien we faced.
Keep your guard up.
Well, you heard her.
We have to protect Barry.
There's no way
he would destroy the world.
What if he's right?
I mean, look, we all saw
how a massive boost of speed
affected Barry before.
Oh, crap. You're right.
Remember the ASF?
He gained speed thinking
but as a result...
I turned on the people I love.
Look, uh...
that's not gonna happen this time.
But, Barry, what if you
just leveled up too much, too fast?
Barry isn't a threat to us.
Despero is and his story doesn't add up.
I mean, come on.
Doesn't anyone else think it's weird
that an alien cares so much about Earth?
He's not even from here.
Wherever he's from, here's what we know.
I ran a bio scan on Despero
the minute he entered S.T.A.R. Labs.
His anatomy is unlike anything
I've ever studied before.
He has strength and invulnerability
that rivals Kryptonians.
How are we gonna stop him
from killing you?
Prove him wrong.
Despero says tomorrow,
my mind starts to break.
So all we have to do
is make it through the next 24 hours
without that happening,
and he'll have to back down.
I like that plan.
Let's get some rest.
Tomorrow, we'll need
to be on the lookout for anything.
And if something does happen,
then we need to be ready to stop it.
Protecting this city
is still our top priority.
Even from you?
It won't come to that. I promise.
These are the bio scans
Caity did on Despero's brain.
Study them and let's
figure out a way to stop him.
Oh, I heard that.
I was already planning
on pulling an all-nighter.
You know, I was thinking maybe
we can find a way to restrain him or...
I'm not talking about restraining him.
Look, we need to level up our offense.
And I'm not talking about
some containment unit
like we did with Bloodwork
or taking out his lair with an EMP.
We need to hit him hard.
You're... You're asking me
to build a weapon.
Frost, I've never built something
to hurt someone before.
Think of it this way.
You're gonna help save Barry's life
whatever it takes.
Couldn't sleep, either?
Something bad
is supposed to happen today.
All I keep thinking about is you.
I'll be fine.
We can't take any chances.
I promise I have a very safe
and boring day planned.
Cecile's working on a big case.
So, after some work, I'm gonna
stop by and help her with Jenna.
They both have been having
a pretty hard time lately.
Iris, if anything happens to you...
Hey, baby, we're gonna be okay.
Look, how many times
in how many timelines
have we found each other?
Doesn't matter what
anybody says about your fate.
Our destiny is to be together.
C.C.P.D.
Allen, just in time.
How bad is it?
Just your typical "makes no sense"
bank robbery in Central City.
No one's hurt,
but the on-duty security guard
is being hospitalized
for some sort of breakdown.
Wait. Like a mental breakdown?
The witnesses said
the guy lost his mind,
and started babbling nonsense.
Then he fired his weapon into the air
and everyone ran out.
By the time anyone got back inside,
the vault was empty
and the guard was stark raving mad.
It took four officers to restrain him.
I'm on it.
Allen, I need you to stand down.
What, is Gibson working the case?
I'll... I'll just help him investigate.
I need you to turn in your badge.
You've been suspended.
- What?
- I just came from the mayor's office.
You're under investigation
for federal crimes.
Your badge, Allen, now.
You're
under investigation for federal crimes.
Your badge, Allen.
Allen, I know this must be a shock.
Captain, hold on.
What... What am I supposed to have done?
Two years ago, Joseph Carver
had a mole
manipulating evidence at C.C.P.D.
Yeah. Millie Rawlins aka Sunshine.
We caught her.
And the DA was reviewing her case
as a part of an internal audit.
Now, I don't know what exactly,
but he also found new evidence
that points to Carver
having a second inside man. You.
That's crazy.
I mean, why would I help Joseph Carver?
That's for the DA to suss out.
I'm sorry. It's above my pay grade.
Now please leave the scene.
I have to find out what happened here.
I mean, I think you'd have
other concerns right now.
I just...
Korber said a guard lost his mind.
What if that happens to
somebody else?
People could get hurt.
Look, Captain,
I know you only have my word,
but you got to believe me,
I'm innocent.
So, please, just let me do my job.
If Joe were here right now,
he'd say I should learn
from last year and keep an open mind.
Which is why I promise you,
I will get to the bottom of this
and find out the truth.
But until I do, I'm sorry, Allen,
you have to leave.
This is insane.
Your C.C.P.D. record is stellar.
Everyone knows that Rawlins
was nothing but Carver's lackey.
Can you find out what evidence
they have against me?
Oh, Barry, I'm gonna do
a hell a lot more than that.
I am about to slap C.C.P.D.
with the biggest wrongful termination
lawsuit this city has ever seen.
I am gonna bleed them dry
for doing this to you.
Are you feeling all right?
No.
I'm sorry. It's just been hard lately.
I mean, you know why.
What's wrong?
We're not alone in here.
I can feel another presence
in this room.
Why are you here?
I'm not.
This is a psychic manifestation
of my consciousness.
Appearing only to you
in order to assess
your mental stability.
Barry, who are you talking to?
There's nothing wrong with my mind.
That's him, isn't it? Despero?
Your mind is suffering
due to this tragedy.
But, no,
it hasn't broken...
yet.
His energy...
his energy, it felt like...
the whole room was flooded
and we were both drowning.
Well, Despero's watching me now,
waiting for the proof
he needs to kill me.
Are you sure he is not
what drives you insane?
No. I'm not.
But I do think there's another
explanation for what's happening.
Korber said a security guard
at this morning's robbery lost his mind.
That can't be a coincidence. Not today.
No. It has to be connected
to what Despero said
happens in the future.
I need to talk to that guard.
Xotar.
Xotar. Xotar. Xotar.
Xotar!
Xotar.
Caitlin, hey, good timing.
I think I've got a clue
to run through the S.T.A.R. Labs
search satellites.
Barry, we need you here right now.
The city is shutting down S.T.A.R. Labs.
Okay, lock this place down.
I want that radiation leak found.
Get here fast.
Xotar.
Xotar. Xotar. Xotar.
You can't just come in here
and kick us out of our own offices.
Public Safety Act?
Passed four years ago
after the meta fallout
nearly took out the city.
Means we can do whatever
we have to do for the greater good.
Post teams at every entrance.
- No one gets in without clearance.
- Right away.
Excuse me. I'm Barry Allen.
I own this facility.
Mr. Allen, we've detected
dangerous levels
of radiation within your facility.
This lab's a day away from a meltdown.
That's impossible.
We would have noticed
if things were that bad.
Uh, maybe not.
I just checked out the safety logs.
Our radiation scanners
haven't updated in over a week.
It doesn't make any sense.
What happened?
This is part of our
early detection array
that monitors radiation levels
inside the place.
But it's corroding.
It hasn't been functioning for a while.
Sensors in the subterranean power core
currently read over a thousand rads.
Consider yourselves lucky.
Another day, you'd all be in ICU.
Seal off that power core.
Yes, sir.
And get an external
containment team, stat.
What kind of containment?
We need to construct
a concrete and steel encasement
around this entire facility
in order to contain
the radioactive material.
Then we'll demolish S.T.A.R. Labs
and move the debris
to a nuclear waste site.
You're gonna demolish it?
Safety board makes the final call.
This looks pretty bad.
Now, gather your people and say goodbye.
You got five minutes
to make like a banana and split.
Fan out and search all levels
for additional leaks.
Excuse me.
Okay. This place is already
swarming with city workers.
If they get to the inner levels...
They'll find out it's Flash HQ.
Aka our home base.
That's why I need you to grab
what you're able to,
conceal the lab's critical areas
and get out as fast as you can.
Hello, Barry Allen.
Gideon, can you pull up the controls
for the holographic emitters
and set them to manual?
Understood. Preparing task.
What do you need, Ches P?
Where are you?
Yes.
Instruction set received.
Holographic emitters reconfigured.
Initiate.
Must be old plans.
All clear.
Okay, let's head back.
Sequence complete.
However, Team Flash data
on internal servers
will compromise your identity
if discovered.
Standing by for emergency data wipe.
Gideon, is there any other way?
No, Barry Allen.
All information within S.T.A.R. Labs
must be erased
in order to assure your safety.
This includes myself.
This is the best option.
I'm so sorry, Gideon.
It has been an honor working
with you, Barry Allen. Farewell.
It has been an honor
working with you, Barry Allen. Farewell.
Frost ice-bridged a bunch of stuff
out of here.
- She's gonna bring it to Caitlin's.
- Okay.
It's time to go.
I can't believe this is happening.
This was our home.
This...
This is so unreal.
I've spent more time in that lab
than anywhere I've ever lived.
Guys, I know how much this hurts,
and I know what you're thinking.
But these setbacks aren't proof
that Despero's right about the future.
They're not proof he isn't either.
I know, but, I mean,
we gotta have faith.
Not just in me, but in each other.
Barry, we're with you.
I think we all just wished
that there was some other explanation
for all this.
I think there is.
Something caused a security guard
to lose his mind
at a bank robbery this morning.
Uh, you mean, exactly like what
Despero said would happen to you?
This has to be related.
I was going to use the S.T.A.R. Labs
satellites to follow a lead.
But luckily, we have someone on our team
who is an expert at exposing the truth.
- The Xotar story is priority one.
- Got it.
Okay, the word's out.
If there's anything
to this "Xotar" lead,
my people will find it.
Despero said I'm gonna
destroy the world.
If that's true, I'm the reason
everyone I love is gonna die.
Barry, do you remember the last time
that something messed with your head
when you had speed thinking?
It was like I was on auto-pilot,
my mind just took over.
Yeah, but you snapped out of it
because you saw
that your friends were in danger.
I mean, you could never really hurt us.
Even so, if something
does happen to someone I love
because of my leveled up speed,
I don't know how I'd react.
It's Taylor.
She found out that "Xotar"
is the name of a meta criminal
in National City.
Xotar's a meta?
A psychic meta who controls
her victims' minds
and drives them crazy.
You know what this means.
Xotar could be the real reason
I lose my mind today.
And catching her will prevent it.
All I have to do is find her.
Xotar...
Flash, you found me.
Yes.
Let me guess. You're psychic, too.
Not psychic, just patient.
I knew if I ran around the city
long enough,
eventually you'd show yourself.
How very underwhelming and basic of you.
So what's next? We fight?
How passé.
Actually, what do you say we take
a quick trip to Iron Heights?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
What's going on?
You zooped in out of nowhere
and started destroying the place.
- What? No, I...
- You almost lightning-blasted Chuck.
I...
I don't remember doing any of that.
Okay, listen. Hey, I don't know what
just happened, but I didn't do this.
And I'm... I'm not going insane.
- Barry, we saw you.
- No way, I...
Dude, she's right. You came in here
all lathered up out of control.
- Allegra had to blast you, man.
- Okay.
All right, look, whatever happened,
I can prove I'm myself now.
Or at least Caitlin can.
Cover me.
Your amygdala activity
and cortisol levels are elevated.
But within normal parameters.
Even if you're really you again,
it doesn't explain what just happened.
Now I know who's responsible for this.
Right before it happened,
I intercepted a meta called Xotar.
She controls her victims' minds.
What are the odds a meta who commits
telepathic assaults on people
shows up the same day Despero claims
I'm going to lose my mind?
It does make a lot more sense.
Okay. We need to find Xotar
and stop this from happening.
And keep Despero from killing you.
Back at S.T.A.R. Labs, you could scan
for Xotar's energy signature
and find her,
but those satellites are blind.
I can search the city.
I found her once, I can find her again.
Frost needs help setting up
a portable med lab at the apartment.
Me and Allegra can set up
a comms/Cortex type sitch in my garage.
All right, do it. And look, guys,
I know today started with a loss,
but we can end it with a win.
We got this.
Sorry.
Sorry. It's all right.
Search for Xotar all you want.
The answer you're looking for
has been with you all along.
Enough.
No more cryptic prophecies.
No more games.
Why do you care so much?
You said yourself,
this isn't your world.
You're hiding something from me.
What do you have to gain?
A home.
I saw my planet, Kalanor,
overrun by evil.
I was forced to see the people I love
suffer and die
under the fist of a despot.
Then I was chosen to lead
a band of rebels attempting a coup.
Both sides suffered heavy losses.
But we were triumphant.
However, when the time came
to cut the head off the snake...
I chose to spare the oppressor's life.
But my mercy was misguided...
because it allowed
that madman to rise again
and rain down horrors
a thousand times worse.
I was spared...
because he knew for me,
the only fate worse than death
would be losing my home world.
So he banished me here.
That's how I came to adopt Earth
as my new home,
only to watch you destroy it.
I've been through a crisis before.
Whatever's coming, I can handle it.
Crisis and tragedy
are like fires, Flash.
Some are strong enough to endure them.
But others are destined
to be consumed by them.
Soon, we'll find out who you are.
Okay.
This is the last of your...
Whatever this stuff is.
What's this thing?
Uh, nothing.
It's just a... a project for Frost.
That's all.
Uh-huh.
Chuck, you know how we've been
spending more time together lately?
Oh, yeah. Our weekend D&D sessions
are like my new favorite thing.
Why?
Well, and I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but the way you just said "nothing,"
is exactly how you sounded
right before the raid on Shavak's tomb.
And we all knew
you were bluffing then, too.
Yeah. Okay. Uh...
Frost asked me to build...
a weapon to hurt Despero.
But you're...
A pacifist. Yeah, I know.
How do you feel about doing this?
Allegra.
You know, I still remember
the exact moment
that I decided to be a pacifist.
I was ten.
I had just seen
Marvin the Martian's ray gun
on the Saturday morning cartoons.
So I decided to make one of my own.
When I demoed it for my best friend,
it malfunctioned and...
I burned his parents' house down.
Him and his family
barely made it out alive.
After that, I made a vow.
No more weapons, no matter what.
So, by going back on that vow now,
I feel like by building this,
I'm not just going to hurt Despero,
I'm gonna hurt myself, too.
Look, I know you want to
do right by Barry and by the team,
but you can't do that
if you don't do right by yourself.
It's not your job to make weapons.
It's to find a way to protect Barry
and stay true to yourself.
Yeah. Yeah.
- What's that?
- Uh...
Okay, I built a temporary comms system
by piggybacking off of cell towers.
I'm also using it to scan for C.C.P.D.
chatter about criminal activity.
- Right?
- Right.
Okay, okay, uh...
Flash, we got trouble.
Chester, what's happening?
Miss, step aside.
But if I did that, then how would I grab
all the priceless art
you're transporting?
Officer, you sound insane.
Xotar. Xotar.
Central City Museum, you shouldn't have.
It's like you read my mind.
You're done messing with
other people's minds, Xotar.
Including mine.
If it makes you feel
like less of a failure,
I dug my claws into your mind
long before you even arrived.
Apologies for not mentioning
the telekinesis.
Didn't take a crystal ball to know
I'd eventually have to catch you
by surprise.
You know, back in the day,
my specialty was bending spoons.
Okay, uh, guys,
now C.C.P.D. is reporting
that the Flash is getting
his butt kicked downtown
by some meta magician
that's got him suspended in midair.
It's got to be Xotar.
Barry, Frost is on her way.
But she's all the way across town.
She'll never make it in time.
No, I can stop Xotar!
I just need to generate
enough lightning.
But, Barry, you need friction
to build up that kind of kinetic energy.
If you can't run,
you can't throw lightning. Barry?
Barry?
It sounds like
Barry is generating lightning.
How is that possible?
Holy Granville T. Woods.
Okay, if he's vibrating his cells
on a microscopic level,
that might be enough movement
to... to build up an electrical charge.
How would he throw lightning then?
I don't think he's going to.
My guess is he's letting it build up
inside of him on purpose.
Caitlin, what happens if his body
can't hold in his lightning anymore?
I think we're about to find out.
That was the hospital.
The guard that Xotar attacked
recovered as soon as
she was meta-cuffed.
So did everyone else she attacked.
How you feeling, Barry?
Like it's barely past lunchtime,
it already feels like
the longest day of my life.
But it also feels like
it's going to be a good one.
Now that we've gotten Xotar,
we don't have to worry about
the rest of the day
or you losing your sanity.
Well, in that case, I don't know
about you guys, but I'm starving.
Oh, yeah.
Why don't we meet up with Iris
at Joe and Cecile's?
Let's see if we can talk Joe
into whipping us up
a pot of his famous jambalaya?
That's not funny, Barry.
Okay, ask him to grill
some burgers instead.
Why are you doing that?
Doing what?
Acting like Joe's still alive.
What are you talking about?
You don't remember?
Barry, Joe died six months ago.
You know that.
What?
No, I don't believe you.
Barry, look,
maybe you're still processing this
or something? I don't know.
But we'll... we'll figure it out.
Okay? Why don't you just sit down
and let Caitlin take a look
at the ol' noggin?
- Where is he?
- Barry, you're scaring me.
- Who?
Joe!
You gave the eulogy at his funeral.
No, I...
No, this is wrong.
Iris, this is wrong.
We have to investigate this.
We have to find out
what really happened to him.
He's not dead. He can't be.
Damn it, Barry.
Joe is gone.
Why can't you just accept that?
Cecile.
Barry, why are you saying
all these things all of a sudden?
It's like the last six months,
this living nightmare,
never even happened.
Six months.
What are you doing?
I can't do this with you.
Barry, I can't do it.
Cecile, listen to me.
Joe's not dead.
Yes.
Yes, he is.
He's dead and I'm trying to move on.
- Why won't you let me do that?
- Cecile, please.
Barry.
You're all over the news.
- What?
- What did you do?
Nothing...
After apprehending
a criminal earlier today,
the Flash, for reasons unknown,
committed a crime of his own.
Warning. This footage
may be disturbing to some viewers.
Our camerawoman was barely able
to escape with her life.
Luckily, there were no deaths today,
despite what city officials estimate
are millions of dollars in damage.
But other members of our crew,
along with dozens of innocent civilians,
were injured
in the Flash's brazen attack.
Once again, our top story,
the hero who has saved our city
countless times
has turned against us.
More on this unprecedented
breaking development,
as we head to our reporter
on the ground.
I don't remember doing that.
Caitlin said you didn't remember
destroying the loft
or almost killing her
and Chester either.
Barry, we can blame Xotar for the loft.
But she was in meta-cuffs
when you destroyed City Hall.
Do you see?
It's been you all along, Flash.
- Now do you believe me?
- No.
This is one of your illusions.
That's it.
Iris, Cecile, you have to believe me.
Enough!
This ends now.
Barry!
It's fitting that I end your life
with the undying fire of my home world.
The Flame of Py'tar.
Get out of my house.
The empath.
Well, your power's no match for me,
so for now...
Sleep.
Stop!
If it's me you want, get it over with.
Gladly.
That's all I got. Barry, run.
Good move, Chuck.
What's wrong with you people?
You saw the destruction he'll bring
to the world with your own eyes.
Why am I fighting this threat alone?
Stand in my way again, any of you,
and suffer the consequences.
I will find the Flash and end him...
before he brings about Armageddon.
So is Barry going to be all right?
Honestly, we don't know.
Can you tell us anything else about
Despero's planet or his freaky flame?
Well, actually, the pieces
are starting to come together.
For years, we had heard
rumors and whispers
from the dark corners of the galaxy
about the Flame of Py'tar,
which is an energy source
that was supposedly
the sentient heart
of the planet Kalanor.
Butjust when we started to think
that this was a pan-galactic
urban legend,
you guys are the first to meet
an actual Kalanorian.
Lucky us.
Yeah, but thanks to you guys,
we've opened an official file
on Despero.
Kara and J'onn, they're off-world.
But we'll keep investigating,
and I'll call if we find anything
that can help take him down.
You guys stay safe, okay?
Yeah. Thanks. You too, Alex.
We may not be the Tower
or have access to S.T.A.R. Labs,
but Chester P.
can still roll up his sleeves
and see what I can come up with
to help track down Barry.
Assuming he wants to be found.
If you and Allegra hadn't shown up
when you did...
Hey, hey. It's all good. Okay?
We'll figure this out. We always do.
We'll get Barry back.
Yeah. But what will he be like
when we do?
You look like death warmed over.
I need your help.
Barry, what the hell is going on?
Injustice.