- Elisabeth!
- Here Elisabeth!
- We love you!
- Elisabeth!
- We love you, Elisabeth!
- Please!
- Over here!
- We love you!
- Wanna get something to eat?
- Yeah, get a pretzel or something...
- Remember her?
- She was in that movie, uh...
Agh...
We're gonna have to let her
know we're gonna be late...
Yeah I'll shoot her a text.
- Yeah, he owes me twenty bucks.
- Oh, you're kidding?
Shit!
You got it!
Feel that power, ladies!
And march, get those knees up!
You got it!
Come on!
Front!
Kick!
Oh yeah, you got it!
Square.
Think about those bikini bottoms
you wanna look like a giant
jellyfish on the beach?
Come on!
Cross!
Push!
Kick!
Come on, you've got it!
Hang in there, ladies,
you've got it!
You've got it!
Woah!
Ah, thank you.
Great workout, ladies!
Alright, I hope I see you next week
for Sparkle Your Life.
We're gonna work
on the lateral abs
you know the most difficult part to sculpt.
But in the meantime
take care of yourself.
- Back to position one.
- Great job ladies.
You got it!
- Happy birthday
- Oh, thank you.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
I don't care if we see
every fucking young girl
in this fucking town
in the next few weeks.
Look, I'll make it simple.
We need her young.
We need her hot.
We need her now.
How the old bitch has been able to stick
around for this long.
That's the fucking mystery to me.
Oh, Oscar winner, my ass.
When was that,
back in the 30s?
What, for King Kong?
No, I don't give a
fuck what we promised her.
This is network TV,
not a fucking charity.
Find me somebody new.
Now.
Hey, did you know
that a woman's fertility
starts to decrease
about the age of 25?
How old is Jennifer?
You better get busy.
It's like when you see
someone fart on screen.
People just love that.
I mean, that's just the way it is.
So you know what I mean?
People are just people.
And I have to give people what they want.
That's what keeps the shareholders happy.
And people always ask for something new.
Renewal is inevitable.
And at 50, well...
it stops.
What stops?
What?
Um, you know, the um...
The um...
Oh, George!
Oh, oh!
I'm sorry, I gotta run.
Harvey!
George, those ratings are insane!
You're a genius!
Oh, what a mix. You're a genius.
Let's buy you a drink, come on...
Well, it's your lucky day, Miss Sparkle,
because we have
X-rayed you from head to toe,
and you don't have so
much as a cracked molar.
So, you are good to go.
Uh, vaccination, okay...
Not going on a vacation.
By the way, I just want to say,
my wife is a huge fan.
Um, blood type...
Oh, hey, it's your birthday.
Happy birth...
Oh, uh, that's an emergency,
I'm sorry.
I, uh, had to..
Have a...
Bye.
One moment.
There's just one last exam to perform.
I thought he said I was good to go.
Is there a problem?
No, it's perfect.
You're a good candidate.
I mean, you're good to go.
I wish you the best.
Lizzie?
Lizzie Sparkle?
Oh my God, I can't believe it.
Fred!
Fred, from 10th grade homeroom!
Oh, Fred, of course...
You haven't changed a bit.
You're still the most beautiful girl in
the whole wide world.
You know, I followed your career.
What a success.
I mean, wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
Hey, why don't we go out maybe for a
drink sometime now that we're,
you know, reconnected?
Um...
Oh, of course, I'm stupid.
You're super busy.
But you know what?
Why don't you give me your card?
I mean, you never know.
Um, sure, what I...
This will do.
Oh.
Don't look at my cholesterol levels.
They're a disaster.
Oh, God.
There.
Now you've got it.
Have you ever dreamt of a
better version of yourself?
Younger.
More beautiful.
More perfect.
One single injection unlocks your DNA,
starting a new cellular division
that will release another
version of yourself.
This is...
the substance.
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you.
And everything is you.
This is simply
a better version of yourself.
You just have to share.
One week for one
and one week for the other.
A perfect balance of seven days each.
The one and only thing not to forget.
You are one.
You can't escape from yourself.
Yes.
Hello.
I'd like to order.
Address.
1057 Beverly Canyon.
Write this down.
35 North Byron Alley.
35 North.
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you
and everything is you.
This is simply
a better version of yourself.
Hello.
Thanks.
We'll let you know by next week.
Thank you so much.
I'm just dying to get the part.
Great dancer.
Hmm, too bad her boobs
aren't in the middle of her face
instead of her nose.
Next!
Looks like everything sure is in the
right place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
I'm Sue.
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue,
Sue, Sue, Sue,
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
Where is she?
What a gorgeous little angel.
You're hired.
We want a show that's just like you.
Beautiful and happy.
People want to be happy.
We air in two weeks,
so let's get to work.
I'm gonna let you organize
the rest with my assistant,
uh...
Isabella?
Is-is-is.
Who has time to say that?
We're gonna make you Cindy.
It's shorter, it's better.
So, I'm gonna let you organize
everything else with Cindy.
Oh, um, before you go,
I just have to mention
a small scheduling issue.
I have to be out of town every other week
to take care of my mother
who's very sick.
I want you for this show
and we will work around
any mother, brother, fucking sick,
puppy you need to take care of.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Gorgeous, with a pure heart.
People are gonna love that.
Perfect.
So you jump out, touch your elbows,
head down, contract.
And five, six, seven, eight, elbows.
Where have you been?
We've all been wanting
to have a drink with you
for your departure.
Anyway, we all chipped in
and we got you just a little
something to keep you busy.
It's French.
My wife, she swears by it.
Oh, I love my wife.
Oops, I gotta run.
But it's always great to see you.
The antelope and the deer moving about
a hunt through the...
God damnit lady,
come on
I haven't slept in three nights!
Open up.
Goddamnit,
are you gonna open the...
Ah uh, sorry...
I thought that Ms. Sparkle.
She moved out.
I'm the new tenant.
Sue.
Oliver.
- Oliver.
- You wanted to complain about something?
Oliver?
What?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think it's like awesome
when there's stuff
going on in the building,
you know what I mean?
Um, I'm actually,
quite handy if you ever need
need me to be of aid in any way.
I got a sack of tools and...
I got a big hammer.
You know what I mean.
Anyways, I live right here,
so you know where to find me.
Anytime.
Day or night.
Later.
Hi everybody.
I'm Sue
and it's time to pump it up.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Thank you so much everybody.
I'll see you next week.
And in the meantime,
take care of yourself.
Where is she?
There she is!
Wonderful, wonderful!
That's what I'm talking about!
I won't be out late, so just wait for me.
Don't eat too fast.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'll be right back.
What did you do?
You've seen me the more
beautiful than before.
No.
Yes.
Yes, hi.
This is Elisabeth Sparkle.
I'm 503.
Yes.
Yes, hi.
There's been a slight
misuse of the substance.
A few extra hours were accidentally used
causing, um...
an alteration.
So I'm just looking for
the procedure to reverse it.
What has been used on one side
is lost on the other side.
There's no going back.
No, I don't know what she was thinking.
And obviously she was drunk.
Remember there is no she and you.
You are one.
Respect the balance and you
won't have any more inconveniences.
Sue!
Sue?
I just saw you on TV.
Holy moly.
Makes me want to join your class.
Hey, you don't give
private lessons, do you?
Hey, what about a
drink at my place tonight?
Come on, don't be shy.
I see you standing behind
the door there, gorgeous.
All right, take your time
but it's a date.
You know, pump it up
You got to pump it up
Sue.
What can I get you?
Moka Latte.
It's long, isn't it?
Excuse me?
Seven days.
Did you follow me here?
I was just curious
to find out how things were going for you.
Each time you feel a little more
lonely...
don't you think?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
It gets harder each time
to remember that
you still deserve to exist.
That this part of yourself
is still worth something
that you still matter.
Has she started yet?
Eating away at you?
Fuck!
Watch out!
What?
Hey!
Move!
You're still the most beautiful girl
in the whole wide world.
Hello?
Hi, Fred.
It's Lizzie.
Hello?
Sorry, I mean, I'm in shock.
- Oh.
- Wow.
Wow, wow.
I thought I'd never
hear from you again after--
Oh gosh, no, no, not at all.
I've just--
I've just been really busy lately.
So listen, I was thinking that
maybe we could get
together and grab a drink.
Are you still there?
Sorry, I'm in shock, again.
Um, I could book Luigi's,
at eight?
Eight at Luigi's, it is.
I will see you tonight.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
Hi everybody.
Hi.
Okay, here we go everyone.
Clear the set please.
First positions, thank you.
Roll cameras.
And in three, two, one.
Squat, squat, squat.
Circle those hips.
Contract, contract, contract,
contract, contract, contract.
Head between your legs.
Cut.
I'm sorry, I thought uh,
thought I, I...
I just got distracted.
Not a problem, let's
get right back to it.
Back to one please.
Sorry, it's the control room now.
The director said he saw something
bizarre on the monitor.
Bring up the replay on camera two.
Camera two.
Forward.
Can I have my dressing gown?
Sorry, it's in your dressing room.
Well then go and get it.
Let's just take this frame by frame.
I need five minutes.
- Yes.
- This balance is not working.
I barely have any time to enjoy myself
while she wastes seven days
stuffing her face in front of the TV.
Remember there is no she and you.
I love everybody...
What's happening?
Where is everybody?
The taping's been cancelled.
What, why?
Sue.
Harvey wants to see you
in his office immediately.
Okay.
- I'll go change--
- No, he said now.
I'll get right to the point.
We can't keep you on the morning show.
But why?
I just started.
Ratings are through the roof.
We started at 42.
Now we're up to like--
216.
It's phenomenal.
People love you.
They adore you.
They want more and more and more of you.
That is why we have decided
that we want you
to host the New Year's Eve show.
You mean the--
The network's biggest show.
50 million viewers live.
You can't go higher than that.
That's gonna be intense.
We only have a few months to pull it off.
So are you in?
If you don't open the
door when opportunity knocks,
you won't get another chance.
You of all people know this.
Just one more day and
then I have a whole week off.
We can switch.
We're doing the cover of Vogue.
Just one more day, okay?
- Yes.
- She didn't respect the balance.
She's stealing more
and more time from me,
completely without
consideration of the consequences.
She's a selfish bitch.
Would you like to stop?
Stop?
You are the Matrix.
If you are not satisfied,
you can put an end to the experience
and go back to being
just you on your own.
Would you like to stop?
Will it go back to the way it was before?
What has been
transferred won't come back,
but you can stop the experience.
As of now, would you like to stop?
To go back to being just you on your own?
No.
No, no, no.
I can't stop.
She just--
I'm...
The balance just needs to be respected.
So respect it.
Stop it, stop it, stop it
stop it, stop it.
You are the winner!
Well,
congratulations, you've won $25,000.
Now you'll have one final chance
to answer a simple question
in our big question round
and play for $250,000.
Now you'll have just 45 seconds
on the clock
to give me as many
correct answers as you can--
Just a little something to keep you busy.
Fuck.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, she is here.
The superstar of the moment, Sue.
Are you ready? Let's welcome her...
Sue!
You popped up out of nowhere
on our screens like a tornado.
I don't think anybody was
really prepared for this whirlwind.
It all started with the morning show
and rumor has it that you are
up for Tom Grant's next movie.
Wait, just a moment.
I'm being told that you are going to host
the New Year's Eve show.
Can you confirm this?
Yes, that's right.
Oh my God, that is huge news.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
Where are you from?
How did you get discovered?
I want, we want to know everything.
Well, I mean, there's
really not very much to tell.
I'm just a girl from a
very small town in Indiana.
I'm sure that you've never heard of it.
In fact, it's not even a town.
I'm not sure you could
really even call it a village.
It's a farm, perhaps?
But ever since I can remember,
it has always been my
dream to be on screen.
This is my dream.
As a child, I used to
put on shows for my family.
Mm, your family.
How sweet.
So, everyone is aware that
you replaced Elisabeth Sparkle.
And no doubt about it, you stepped in,
you turned up the volume,
and you rocked their world.
Were you a fan of her show?
Um, well, well, I can't, uh,
I can't really say that I
actually watched her show.
You do know that we're not exactly from
the same generation.
And you have to admit
it was a bit old-fashioned.
Jurassic Fitness, really.
- Jurassic Fitness...
- It needed a change.
I'll fucking show you.
You really wanna see
some Jurassic Fitness?
You want it?
Come on, come get your
fucking Jurassic Fitness!
But my mother was a huge fan of hers.
So, every morning, rain or shine,
"Sparkle Your Life" was on TV.
So, in a way, I grew up with her.
Whether I liked it or not.
I guess that's why you could say
we have some sort of connection.
Some sort of connection.
You wouldn't exist without me.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum...
It is time, ladies and gentlemen,
for our final question.
The question that we ask each
and every one of our guests.
Okay.
Would you share one of your
little beauty secrets with us?
Just one little trick of yours
that helps you look
so incredibly stunning.
I mean, look at you.
I don't know.
Say it!
Let me think.
Tell them who your
little beauty secret is!
I guess, I would just
show them right here.
Here's your little beauty secret.
I guess I just try to be myself.
To be sincere and
grateful for all that I have.
And to always remember
to lead with my heart.
Oh, I'm hearing this sweetheart.
We'll be back...
I just, oh, I try to be myself.
Stop it!
Stop it.
You're taking it from me.
That's your little secret.
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
You have to--
Control yourself!
I can't go back inside her.
Oh!
Gross old rat.
Stop it!
Coming to bed?
Yes, I'll be right there.
- Yes.
- Hi, hi, this is an emergency.
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
Hello?
It's fucking 503.
Yes.
Fuck!
I'm telling you, this is urgent.
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
It means you've reached the end.
What do you mean the end?
You've drained it all out.
If you want more, you must
let the fluid regenerate.
Tell me how to do it.
I need to stabilize myself right now.
You simply have to switch.
Excuse me?
The switch reboots the
fluid secretion process
so you can continue to
enjoy the experience.
No, no, no, no, no.
I can't switch, I can't.
Especially not now.
There is no other option.
Sue?
Babe?
You alright?
Stressed out about tomorrow?
Babe?
Sue?
Is something wrong?
...a little cranky because of your
lady business?
Sue, open the door.
Come on, Sue.
Sue, it's not funny,
I need to take a piss!
Sue, open the door.
Open the door, Sue, come on.
Babe.
Sue, open the door.
Sue!
Open the door, come on!
Sue, open the door.
Sue!
Open the door!
Get out!
What the fuck?
Get the fuck out!
Who's this? Who the fuck is this?
And leave me alone!
What the fuck?
Yes?
It's 503.
I want to stop.
Are you sure?
Once you stop, you can't go back.
I want to stop!
I want to fucking stop!
We'll deliver.
- Sue, I was...
- Fuck off!
Are you sure?
Once you stop, you can't go back.
You will simply remain on your own.
Just on your own.
On your own.
- On your own.
- Shut the fuck up!
On your own.
Okay.
I can't do this.
I need you.
I need myself.
You gotta get ready.
It's our big night.
Come on.
They're gonna love you so much.
You're the only lovable part of me.
You have to come back.
You have to come back. Come back.
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Oh, don't!
You've got an hour and
a half in makeup... hair...
Then we gotta get you over to
the pinning room. Get you dressed.
After that, we have one final test on
stage for lighting and sound.
We have a bit of downtime
before the show starts.
- You got it? You good?
- Mmhmm.
Okay, let's go.
The dress...
...is wonderful!
Perfect!
There you go.
Good.
You get the dance lights.
I'm gonna be right back, sorry.
They need to see you on stage
to set the lights.
Have you ever dreamt
of a better version of yourself?
More beautiful, more perfect.
Sue?
Yes, let me meet you there.
Okay, so I'll wait for you on stage.
Oh!
Sue!
Sue?
Let me introduce you to the shareholders.
They have been dying to meet you.
Is everything okay?
So smile.
That's what we want tonight.
Pretty girls should always smile.
Feathers, feathers, feathers!
Hey, you ready for tonight?
I just need a better version of myself...
Please give me a better
version of myself, please!
Please.
Come on.
Looks like everything sure is in the
right place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
Pretty girls should always smile.
At last, we were starting to worry.
Hurry up, you're up in five.
There she is, so beautiful.
We love you.
This is where you belong.
You'll always belong here.
We can't do without you.
We could never do without you.
You're irreplaceable!
Oh.
Girls, come on, let's go.
What are we waiting for?
Okay, come on, everybody...
let's go, let's go, let's go.
You will not be disappointed.
She's my most beautiful creation.
I have shaped her for success.
Five, four, three, two, one...
The monster!
Shoot the monster!
It's a freak!
Monster!
Freak!
- Freak!
- Monster!
Monster!
It's me.
Too bad her boobs aren't
in the middle of her face
instead of that nose.
Hmm.
Next!
Pretty girls should always smile.
At 50.
It stops.
So beautiful!
We love you.
You're irreplaceable!