Almost at the goal line.
Look, I know I've been stable
for a few months,
and I'm not due for
another treatment quite yet,
but I appreciate you checking.
Hey, gotta check yourself
before you wreck yourself.
All right.
Well, you're all good now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, it's--it's just that...
um...
lately, I've been
forgetting things.
For instance, there was this
dinner at my dad's and I...
Dad? Weren't you just upstairs?
Yeah, and then I went to the
garage because you asked me
to get the files from
the old Scarpulla case.
Remember?
Um.
Yeah, I-I I must've just--
checked out or something
for a couple of minutes,
and then I have this
hazy memory of--
of a train station.
And for some reason,
I feel like you were there.
You forget we had
an appointment in the books?
You're gonna start moving
in and out of timelines again.
It's news to me
'cause I'd remember
something like that.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Of course.
Hey, how does someone
catch a time sickness, anyway?
No idea,
but I intend to find out.
Whoa, hold up now.
What is it?
I'm picking up mutations
like ones
I've never seen before.
Well, that sounds bad.
Actually, it could
mean a lot of things,
might even be a side effect
of my treatments.
Tell you what, I'm gonna go
hit up my Force sibs
to see if they can help me
figure this out.
- What do I tell Barry?
- Nothing.
I don't know what this is yet,
so for now, just chill.
Trust me, all right?
As soon as I find out
what's up,
I'll come find you
wherever you are.
♪
This case gives dead ends
a bad name.
At least no one else
has been hurt.
Yet.
Barr, what's wrong?
I just can't shake
the feeling
that there's something
we missed.
Well, look, I'm gonna
dig into the evidence
you gave me
from last week's crime scene.
All right, thanks.
Hey, where's Caitlin?
We need all the help
we can get.
Ever since she decided to go
all in with Marcus,
it's open season
on spontaneous getaways.
So one minute,
they're listening to showtunes,
getting all weepy on the couch,
and then next,
they got last minute tickets
to "Dear Evan Hansen"
in Metropolis.
Well, good for her,
but where does that leave us?
One step closer
to the truth, y'all.
Okay, so I stayed up all night
building this cold fusion alarm
module for our satellites.
♪
Chester?
- I...
- You all right?
Yeah. Sorry, sorry.
This all-nighter's got me
zoning out.
Here's the deal.
So we know that this meta's
fire powers are cryokinetic,
meaning that their power output
would read
as extreme cold pockets.
This alarm
I just finished building,
it's gonna alert us as soon as
there's any rapid drops
in barometric anomalies
anywhere in the city.
Only downside is, we won't know
where our baddie actually is
until "flame's on."
Or someone else
gets burned up.
No, the moment we get a hit,
I'll be fast enough
to get there in time,
and we can end this
before anyone else gets hurt.
♪
Sue Dearbon,
loving the non-catsuit look.
Why the change?
I got restless, so here I am.
Iris?
Hi, you good?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm great.
Yeah, so what brings you back
to Central City?
Oh, well, now that
Black Hole's gone
and my parents are
in white collar prison,
I am in charge of revitalizing
the family business.
So I'm just here showing face
at all the business holdings
and reassure everyone personally
that things
are gonna be different.
And added bonus, I get to
pop in on my favorite tenants.
Well, we are
eternally grateful
for your help
in expanding our office.
Hey, you guys are the ones
doing all the work.
All right, I have got to jet
to Coast City.
We own a string of luxury
hotels I have to go inspect.
- Sounds fun.
- No, no. It's boring as hell.
Yeah, but if I'm lucky,
maybe I'll catch a glimpse
of the CCP while I'm there.
Oh, you guys haven't heard.
Apparently there's been
multiple sightings
of someone
walking through walls.
It's popping up on socials
as #CoastCityPhantom.
It sounds like a new meta.
I wonder how they got
their powers on the West Coast.
Actually, I have run into
quite a few metas
around the world.
Turns out there's folks
all over the place
with latent meta genes.
All it takes is the right set
of circumstances
for their powers to manifest.
Maybe that's what happened
in Coast City?
Yeah, giving them
their first meta.
Iris, this could be
a great story.
Yeah, you should
come with me.
I would love the company.
You don't mind staying in posh,
five-star hotel suites, do you?
I'll go.
- You will?
- Yeah.
Allegra can cover things
while I'm gone.
I can?
Yeah, don't you have a
blossoming media empire to run?
Well, I can run things remotely,
and besides, Allegra's right,
I mean, this is a huge scoop,
and if this story pops,
it could lay the groundwork
to a West Coast expansion.
I am sold.
Great. That's that.
Road trip.
- Oh.
Let's go.
Hey.
Is that a cold spot?
Our fire meta just turned up
at 138 South Devon Road.
♪
What the hell?
Flash, did you find them?
Barry, what's happening?
I'm too late.
- Black fire?
- Yeah.
It was like nothing
I've ever encountered.
And it put itself out.
How is that even possible?
I don't know,
but I'm telling you, man,
I mean, it was there
one second, the next nothing.
So what else do we know?
The vic's name,
Parker DeStefano.
She teaches classes here
at the studio.
♪
Hey, are you seeing this?
Holy "Fahrenheit 451."
Okay, we need a way
to preserve it.
Maybe we can try using
the micro-catalyzed
containment unit?
The what?
Ray Palmer and I
designed it together
in collaboration
with the foundation
that he named after my dad.
The MCCU preserves the
vaporized integrity of gases,
but it's back at my workshop.
- What's it look like?
- It's like an 8-inch
vacuum-sealed
borosilicate canister
with an ionic-fused
base and cap.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
That's gonna take some time
to get used to.
Is this it?
Yeah, yeah, that's--yeah.
Okay.
♪
Okay, try to determine
its molecular properties
then reprogram
our satellite module.
To detect whatever
meta-data I find.
Yeah, then match it
to a city-wide search.
That way, if we're lucky--
We can catch this murderer
before they kill again.
I triangulated the last few
Coast City Phantom sightings
posted to social media,
and all of them
occurred downtown.
Wow, you're really
pulling out all the stops.
So how's tricks?
Everything okay at work?
Yeah, better than ever.
I mean, CCC Media is evolving.
How about you and Barry?
You guys still
the couple of the century?
You say that
like it's a bad thing.
- Lady, it is the best thing.
- Agreed.
Uh, yeah, no,
Barry is leveling up
and firing on all cylinders
with Team Flash.
And...hold on.
What's with all the prying?
It's nothing.
I mean, I get it.
Life's grand, and you're busy
as all get out.
But with all that going on,
you're still really eager
to help this new meta
become the Streak part two.
And Allegra could've
handled this story
and taken some of this
off your plate.
Is there anything
you want to share?
Oh.
Oh, look at that. We got a hit.
Let's go.
Okay, not them.
♪
Hmm, could be either one.
We should probably get closer.
- Uh, uh.
Give it a minute.
♪
Yahtzee.
Hi, I'm Iris West-Allen
with "The Central City Citizen"
Media.
Never heard of it.
- Fair enough, and this is--
- Her landlord.
Yeah, still not caring.
So if you don't mind.
Okay, well we were
hoping that you could help us
with a story
that we're researching.
Not interested.
It's about
the Coast City Phantom.
You ever heard of him? Or her.
Look, we don't want to cause
you any trouble, okay?
We really just want
to talk to you
and see if there's any way
that we can help you.
What's your name?
- I'm not telling you that.
- Order for Tinya.
- Oh, Tinya.
Triple espresso,
that's a lot of caffeine
for a teen.
Okay, I'm gonna be honest.
When we heard that
there was a possibility
of a meta in Coast City--
- What's a meta?
- People like you with powers.
And what?
You think
I'm your next headline?
No, no, it's not like that.
It's just in Central City,
we have experience
working with metas.
To do what?
Well, to help others.
Have you heard of the Flash?
Okay, well eight years ago,
I was the reporter
that who helped break his story
and if you let me,
I can help do the same for you.
How'd you guys
find me anyway?
Well, metas like you
are made up of dark matter,
and this app helps us
find just that.
Really?
♪
Well, good luck finding me now.
Yeah, that went well.
I've triple checked
the who's who binder.
Nothing on
a "Tales From The Crypt" meta
who can conjure up black fire.
With no chemical signatures
to program into our satellites,
we're still flying
pretty blind.
All right,
keep working the science.
I'm gonna pay Kramer a visit.
Now that she's part
of the team,
she needs to know
what we're really dealing with.
Plus, maybe she can help us
find a connection
between all three victims.
Just call me
if you find anything.
Yeah...
No problem-o.
Just me
and the scary black flame.
Nothing weird about that.
Okay, relax, Chester P. Relax.
You got this.
♪
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey.
There's a fire!
There's a fire. Help!
Help me!
Someone help!
Chuck, Chuck.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's just us.
You were shouting
in your sleep.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I just--
just a bad dream.
Must've been a doozy.
Are you sure that's it?
I can feel how frightened
you still are.
Yeah, no, no, no, I'm...
I'm good, I'm good.
Really, I've just been
working way too much lately.
Maybe I just need
some coffee to power up
the old mental hard drive.
Sorry.
♪
Okay, I can feel him struggling.
Anybody else notice
that he's been having
a hard time lately?
- Yeah, I definitely have.
If something's bothering him,
why wouldn't he say so?
I mean, he's the most
touchy-feely person I know.
It must be
super personal then.
To keep us out, Team Flash?
I mean, that's just wrong.
He'll talk to me.
Since your phone's toast,
I'm downloading
Chester's dark matter app.
Only seven hours
and nine minutes to go.
Okay, I really need
to upgrade my service.
I can afford it.
No, Sue, we don't have
that kind of time.
I mean, Tinya can
walk through walls.
I mean, she could be anywhere.
Well, until this downloads,
we have the rest of the day
to come up with a better idea,
and this looks like the
perfect place to strategize.
Okay, well, we need
to narrow down all the places
that we think that she might be
and search them.
Great, and we can talk about
the real problem
while we're doing it.
Come on, Iris,
what are you really doing here?
It's--it's far out, so...
Try me.
Last year,
I started feeling...
weird, and so the Still Force
took a look at me
and discovered that I had
contracted a time sickness.
Now, what that means and how
I got it is still a mystery,
but I don't know.
Recently, I feel like
I'm starting to lose time.
Okay, okay.
I see why you're freaking.
Yeah, and then this morning,
I checked in with Deon,
and he found something
that he had never seen before.
And even though he told me to
relax while he looks into it,
I mean, I can't help
but feeling that
something is really wrong.
And that's why you
threw yourself into this story?
Yeah, I needed a distraction.
Believe me, I understand.
I did the same thing when
I found out that my parents
volunteered to work
for Black Hole.
At first, I was so mad
I just looked the other way.
I mean, seriously,
I did everything to avoid
facing the consequences
of their actions.
But I had to stop running away
and face my parents.
And Iris, you have to do
the same thing
about this fear around
this time sickness thing.
Yeah, but I mean,
what if Deon shows up tomorrow
with bad news?
Yeah, that could happen.
You could also be fine.
Either way,
you have to stop running
from the fear of the unknown.
It's--it's a race
you can't win.
What?
- Tinya.
What if I'm not
the only one running?
I think I know
where to find her.
Got enough for a second cup?
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
I'm not gonna lie,
you look more stressed now
than you did during the
"Trials of Gyntarri" campaign.
Yeah.
That was a tough one.
Wow.
Even D&D talk
isn't gonna perk you up?
I'm sorry.
I'm a little out of it.
I know this new fire meta
case is pretty intense,
and as our resident
science guru,
you're in it pretty deep.
I mean, you have to
examine victims
and run tests on bodies.
That's a lot of pressure.
I guess what I'm saying is,
you're not alone.
I mean, we're all
in this together.
Right?
So if you need to talk about
something, anything...
♪
- It's happening again.
- How'd it get out?
It didn't trust me.
I know you're not really here.
This is just another dream.
No, it's not.
Doesn't S.T.A.R. Labs have
a fire suppression system
or something?
The fire's cold fusion.
It doesn't produce
carbon dioxide.
Our sensors wouldn't pick it up
as real fire.
Please, please, not like this.
It's here.
♪
I can't put out these flames.
All right, just stay behind me.
♪
I don't get it.
First, Chuck has a dream
about this weird fire,
and then the meta
who created it attacks us?
And why would anyone
want to hurt Chuck anyway?
I don't know,
but we're gonna keep you safe.
I promise.
- Thanks.
Chester, what about your
barometric detection thingy?
Why didn't it go off?
When I programmed
the search parameters,
I used the default setting
that establishes
a tracking grid
outside of S.T.A.R. Labs.
Right.
Maybe you should fix that.
Yeah, I just did.
I also doubled checked
to make sure that S.T.A.R. Labs
was clear too.
It's like this
black fire meta
can appear and disappear
at random.
Plus, their fire
leaves no trace.
Like a ghost.
♪
I gotta get some air.
He's hurting
really bad inside.
Can you blame him?
First, two bodies show up
at O'Shaughnessy's...
Then the yoga instructor,
DeStefano, this morning.
Yeah, and now the same person
is hunting Chuck,
a guy who would
never hurt anyone.
It doesn't make any sense.
If this meta can get inside
S.T.A.R. Labs undetected,
they could be anywhere.
What if they're controlling
the flames remotely?
I mean, the shape
that we saw in the fire,
it had no face,
no identifying marks.
Maybe it was
some kind of projection?
I mean, it could explain why
you haven't
been able to catch them.
The killer's
never actually been
at any of the crime scenes.
But that doesn't explain why
our black fire meta
is going after Chester.
Put S.T.A.R. Labs
on lockdown.
Nobody except for me
gets in or out
until we figure out
what's going on.
Where you going?
If somebody is controlling
the fire remotely,
I'm gonna search the city
until I find them.
Stay on comms.
On it.
♪
She's not here.
How did you get--
I don't know how you found me,
but I'm out of here.
How about you stay?
All right, you do know that
I can walk through walls,
right?
Well, we have friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and when I told them that
we had a ghost meta on
our hands, they gave me this.
It's called a
molecular destabilizing matrix.
Apparently all I have to do is
turn it on, and it destabilizes
any folks like you
within a three-block radius.
What do you say
we give it a try?
Yeah, I thought
you two helped people?
Oh, she does.
Me, it depends on my mood.
So why don't you relax?
Let's hear Iris out.
Why do you even care?
We know that you're looking
for your mother.
It was your backpack.
At Jitters, it looked like
your whole life
was jammed inside of it.
I started looking
through Coast City's
missing persons database,
and that's when I found out
that you had run away
from foster care.
And that your birth mother
worked at that Jitters,
and that this apartment
was her last known address.
Yeah,
she's a damn good reporter.
Okay, well then you also know
that my real mom
abandoned me when I was born
and hasn't tried
to contact me since.
Not once.
Not to see how I'm doing
or if I even survived,
but I did.
And it's been hell recently,
but now that I suddenly have
these new powers,
I have a chance to be somebody.
So you wanted to show
your mom who you've become.
Yeah,
because maybe she'll think
that I'm something special.
And take me back.
Latent meta powers manifested
by intense emotion, check.
Let us help you find her.
♪
It's just a paperweight.
Like I said,
Iris is a great reporter
and if there's anyone that can
help you find your mom,
it's her.
- If you'll trust me.
♪
We're gonna find out
what's behind all this...
And you're gonna be fine.
I'm starting to wonder
if that's still possible.
We've got your back.
Trust me, you're more than
just a part of this team,
you are a part of my life,
and I'm not letting you go
anytime soon.
Got it?
Allegra, I--
Never mind.
It's just--
you just a really good friend.
So are you. The best.
Which is why
I gotta tell you this.
Okay, that person in the fire.
I know who it was.
And it wasn't
some new fire meta.
It was a ghost.
You seriously think
you're being haunted?
For real?
By my father.
That's who's in the fire.
And I know that
because that's how he died,
but for some reason,
he's--he's come back.
But I was there,
and whatever it was,
it didn't have a face.
It was just a shape.
No, no, no,
it was more than that.
I wasn't with my dad
when he died.
Okay, but when
that fire appeared,
that thing inside of it
made me feel like I was.
Right there on the road
where it happened 24 years ago.
It's was like
I could see the wreckage
and feel the heat
from the engine burning.
And I could hear my dad
shouting for help.
But no one came.
Allegra, no one came.
He just--no one came.
He just--he died alone.
I don't know what you saw,
but that wasn't your father.
It couldn't have been.
Yes, it was! It was.
Chuck, you told me
what happened
last year when you met.
How much he loved you,
what a great dad he turned out
to be all this time.
Chester,
a good father would not
do something like this.
It had to be.
Look, I get--
Allegra, I can feel it.
Okay, I can feel it.
Like I was right there
at the crash site, I can--
You said,
"Quincy P. Runk loved his son
more than anything else."
Which means whatever you felt
or thought you saw,
it was a lie.
Allegra...
I hated him my whole life.
Okay, what if this
is some kind of, like...
Some kind of messed up
afterlife payback?
No.
I don't believe in ghosts,
and neither do you,
which is why we have
to figure out
what's really going on.
♪
He's--he's back, isn't he?
If so, he's gonna have to
go through me first.
Let's go.
What's going on?
- We're not sure yet.
We got cold fires
on multiple levels,
and it's spreading.
And they're all headed
our way.
If it's cold fire,
how come it's getting hotter
in here?
These flames form
in a subzero state,
but they still give off
high levels of kinetic energy.
Which means they can still
burn the hell out of us.
That was a router junction.
They're in the walls too.
He's after me.
This is all my fault.
No, it's not.
Chuck, you need to concentrate.
Okay, we're gonna need
your help to survive this.
Oh, no, no, I can't.
I can't.
The fire's already
burning through
our structural supports.
Once they're done--
Every volatile resource in
S.T.A.R. Labs will meltdown
and contaminate Central City.
So what do we do?
Chester, look, I know
this is hard right now,
but we need your help
to stop this.
That means we need you
to initiate a search protocol.
Look for anything that could
create cold catalyzed reactions.
We'll buy you
as much time as we can.
Okay. Okay, I'm on it.
Tracking muon-catalyzed
heat signatures.
Barry, the flames are
converging on the speed lab.
I don't know why,
but maybe there's some sort
of epicenter forming there
or something?
Let's do this.
♪
- Frost.
- I'm on it.
Our heat index
is off the charts.
Chester, I just felt
a massive wave of despair.
I told you I can't do this.
He thinks
he's being haunted by his dad,
and that's the reason
all of this is happening.
That's not the reason.
Chester...
The despair that I'm sensing,
it's not just from you.
It's like I can feel the pain
of thousands of people,
maybe more.
What the hell is this?
- Cecile?
- All right, listen to me.
You guys need to evacuate
while you still can.
No, we're not
leaving you behind.
It's here.
All that pain and sadness.
All that grief.
♪
Dad?
Take my hand.
It's time to come home, Chester.
I'm so sorry
I couldn't save you.
Chuck, that's not your dad.
It's true.
Chester, all of the sadness
that I'm feeling,
it's...
it's coming from that thing.
Allegra's right.
That's not your father.
Chester, we belong together.
No, no.
Chester, everything
that's inside of you,
it's moving from you into it.
Becoming a part of it.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
it's feeding on your grief.
Chester, you have to let it go.
I love you, son.
It's lying.
No, no, that thing is lying.
It's lying to you, honey,
it wants you to stay trapped
inside of your sadness
because it's...
Hungry.
Chester, honey,
you have to let it go.
I cant. I can't.
Chuck, listen to me.
Think about the last time
you saw your dad
and what you remember
most about him.
That's what
you have to hold on to.
Okay?
Yeah 'cause
if your real dad was here,
he would be the first to say,
"Remember how much I love you."
Hold on to that, Chuck.
That's what matters.
♪
Take my hand.
My dad...
He never asked me to turn
my back on my life here.
♪
Oh, no, he would love the life
that I've built here.
He'd freak...
If he saw my workshop.
And he'd love that I'm working
with an actual superhero.
Helping him
save the world every day.
No, my dad...
He'd be proud of his son.
And the man that I've become.
I said take my hand.
No.
No, I'm gonna stay here
with my friends because they--
they're my real family,
and you're not my dad.
So why don't you
just go to hell!
♪
Chester, the cold flames
are gone.
What happened?
I sent them packing.
With a little help
from my friends.
Chester, seems like you had
a pretty close call, huh?
You too, Barr.
Yeah, well thankfully,
I was able to phase myself
and Frost long enough
for Chester to do the rest.
Oh, it wasn't all me.
If it wasn't for
Allegra and Cecile,
I'd be just another
burnt corpse right about now.
Hey, what about
the other three victims?
Joe, did you find anything?
I did some digging,
and I called in a few favors.
Turns out our first victim,
Stan Mullen,
recently lost all
his belongings to foreclosure.
Then Donna Winters,
her sister died last week.
Let me guess, our yoga vic
was suffering some loss too?
Fiancé and
childhood sweetheart to cancer.
That's a grief pattern.
Which fits with where
I've been at lately.
So this new meta,
whoever he is,
eats grief and sorrow
to survive.
Yeah, that's not terrifying.
It gets scarier.
We thought we were looking
for a meta serial killer,
someone that was
controlling the black flames
like the figure
I saw in the fire.
But the fire created that.
And when I spoke to it,
it heard me
like it could understand
or something.
Chester's right.
With all of that sorrow
that I felt coming out
of that thing,
I also felt other emotions:
determination, passion, desire.
It's almost like
whatever that thing is,
it's got a mind of its own.
So we're not looking
for a separate fire meta?
No.
The will to seek out
victims to kill,
need to satisfy
its hunger at all costs...
The flames have
a survival instinct.
Which means the flames aren't
being used by the killer.
They are the killer.
Because they're alive.
♪
We're not interrupting,
are we?
No, no, no, it's good.
Just trying wrap my head
around all this.
You know, every member of
this team has dealt with grief.
Me with my own mom
back in Houston.
Nash and Esperanza.
And Barry,
all that he's dealt with,
and with both of his parents.
It's weird,
but I guess dealing with loss
is just another thing
that makes us human.
When we help each other
deal with it...
It's what makes us family.
Yeah.
♪
So I have some filing
I need to do back at my office.
- Right now?
- Yup.
You guys stay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, I know we have,
like, D&D plans for tonight,
but honestly,
I just I--I can't.
Yeah, I'll text Marco
and the gang.
Maybe we can pull
an all-nighter this Saturday?
I'd like that a lot.
Me too.
And Chuck...
You know I'll always
be there for you.
Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
And for the record,
you're a very big part
of my life too.
♪
- How's Sue?
- A life saver as always,
and it turns out that
the Dearbon Corporation
owns an entire city block
in downtown Coast City.
Oh, she rich-rich.
Yeah, you forget about it
until she puts all three of us
in a place like this and
you're like, yeah, billionaire.
- So Tinya's there too.
- Uh, yeah.
She's sleeping
in the suite next door.
She has no place
else to go, Barry.
I--I really want to help her.
That's what I love about you.
You make a real difference
in people's lives
with everything you do.
Yeah, you too.
Speaking of,
I was thinking that
with powers like hers...
She could be a hero too.
Like the Streak?
I mean, why not?
That worked out.
Yeah.
Babe, what is it?
No, I'm...
I'm just--I'm glad
you decided to stay
in Coast City a little longer.
The black fires?
Yeah, it's just not safe
here right now.
Um...okay.
I mean, is there anything
that we can do?
No, it's okay.
I mean, we don't even know
how to locate it,
let alone stop it.
If anything happened to you...
Yeah, no, I get it.
Okay, well, I love you.
- I love you too.
- Get some rest, okay?
- Yeah, you too.
♪
You found out
what's wrong with me.
And it ain't good news.
♪
Greg, move your head.