BARRY: I know I'm moving pretty fast, but
stop me if you've heard this one before.
Boy meets girl. Happens every day.
Except this boy was struck by lightning
and became the fastest man alive.
So, nothing is ever that simple.
-(EXCLAIMS)
-Oh, my... Oh, uh... Careful.
-Ho! Sorry. It's all good. It's all good.
-(CHUCKLING)
Those... Those weren't
for me anyway, right?
They were. I didn't realize
roses were so flammable.
Oh, my God.
Well, it's the... It's the thought
that counts.
And, you know, proper fire safety
management, that counts most.
Yes. I have spent most of my life
feeling very unlucky.
Yeah, and now?
Feels like I've been
struck by lightning twice.
No!
(PANTING)
Help!
(CHOKING) Help.
Flash, everything you have will be mine.
-No!
-No! No!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Okay, so, there's my desk.
Upstairs is Anti-Crime and the CSI lab.
That's where Barry works.
And we have the open files...
And that is a pencil. That, stapler.
Okay. Sorry, Wally. Obviously,
your sister got the funny genes.
Captain, I want you to meet somebody.
This is my son. Wally West.
Handsome young man, Joe.
Hey, he's a West. He can't help that.
Your pops here is a hell of a detective.
Obviously not.
Pleasure to meet you, Wally.
Anyway. I'm glad you're here, Wally.
Yeah, I've always wanted a baby brother.
What about the White Shadow?
You're joking but,
yeah, we did call Barry that.
He's been pretty busy. He's doing
a whole lot of running around.
But, why don't we do dinner?
The whole family?
I... I got plans.
Iris will cook.
Dad, we just met the kid.
We don't want to kill him.
All right. We do take-out.
Chinese, whatever. Come on.
Where are your cuffs, Tail Lights?
Come on. Let's go.
You know that kid?
Uh, no, no. You know, it's just
what they say. I got one of those faces.
I'll see you guys at dinner.
Okay.
Any chance I could chat with you
for a minute?
Yeah. What's up, Detective?
Oh, I... I meant Iris.
Yeah. You're not needed.
I am needed. Somewhere.
I'm gonna go there.
(CHUCKLES)
What can I do for you?
Uh, I just wanted to talk with you...
About Barry.
I know that Barry's, you know,
practically your brother
so I understand that your loyalty
is obviously to him, not me,
but I was just hoping that maybe
you would think I'm good for him,
so you'd want to help me figure him out.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I mean, if you did that,
you would be the first.
-Wonderful. That gives me tons of hope.
-(BOTH LAUGH)
It's just... Um...
He's being... Not "distant" but...
"Guarded."
Yeah. He's being guarded.
And he's waking up from these bad dreams
and not telling me about them.
And I know that we got close really quick.
It's just... It's like
there's something holding him back.
Here's the thing about Barry.
He has a bad habit of carrying
the weight of the world on his shoulders.
Burdens that aren't even his to bear.
But he doesn't have to do that with me.
Which is exactly what you should tell him.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(CLATTERING)
Hey! No. Absolutely not.
You don't get to throw somebody else's
stuff when you're pissed off.
(CLATTERING)
Thank you.
What is this?
Wrong answers.
Maybe you're asking the wrong questions.
What does that mean?
I've been thinking about this a lot
recently.
We keep trying to come up with ways
to make Barry faster,
but I still think we can figure out a way
to make Zoom slower.
We tried that already, remember?
Those darts didn't slow him down at all.
Yeah, I know. I'm not
talking about the darts, okay?
The darts clearly didn't work.
They just pissed him off.
I'm talking about something else.
A way we can steal Zoom's speed.
How?
The Turtle.
As some of you may well know,
I've been deeply embroiled in a secret,
one-sided battle with an invisible enemy.
No. Not the Turtle again.
What? What is the...
Who is the Turtle?
It's Cisco's white whale.
Half whale, half turtle.
Mmm, no. Do you see what you're doing,
Caitlin? Everybody's confused now.
Get to it.
I stumbled upon a few of these cases when
we were looking for the Reverse-Flash.
Robberies that were seemingly
committed at high-speed.
People holding their beloved items
one second,
those items were gone the next.
Tell me what you see.
So he can, what? Stop time?
No, no, no. Look at the time code.
It's still running.
Yeah, okay. So if he's not stopping time,
what is he doing?
He's slowing down everything around him.
And that is why we call him The Turtle.
Why have you never
mentioned this guy to me before?
Oh, I don't know. I think we've just been
a little distracted, you know?
What with Captain Cold, and the
Weather Wizard, and Gorilla Grodd.
Do I need to go on?
Okay, so, if we can catch him,
figure out how he uses his powers...
Maybe we can show Zoom
what life is like in the slow lane.
How would you even know where to find him?
Well, the robberies in the videos
all correspond with police reports
that were dismissed as
"lost or missing items" instead of thefts.
The suspect's MO being?
Items of immense personal value.
Huh...
Oh! It appears that there's
a press conference at CCPD
because the Vandervoort diamonds
have just been recovered.
From hell's heart, I stab at thee.
The perpetrators who committed this
heartless crime have been apprehended,
and are now in our custody.
And we're happy to report
that the famed Vandervoort diamonds have
been returned to their rightful owner.
The real gem is the return
of my great grandfather's ring.
Getting that returned to the family
is what's most priceless to me.
Gotcha.
The ring is gone. What happened to it?
Lock this place down. No one
leaves this room. Sweep the Precinct.
Well, the good news is,
whatever the Turtle did,
it only affected you temporarily.
Yo! What was it like?
Being in Turtle Time?
Yeah. No, it was weird.
It was like waves of inertness.
Like all the energy was suddenly sucked
out of my body, and then it would return.
That's because
that's exactly what was happening.
He has the ability to transfer all the
surrounding kinetic energy into himself.
Leaving everyone else
in a temporary state of potential energy.
That's right.
So why could I still move?
Your speed. Your speed allows you to
change positions faster than anyone else.
So you can convert your stored
potential energy back to kinetic energy.
Excuse me. Where are you going?
Trying to figure out how to use this
against Zoom.
You remember Zoom?
"Cisco, please join me.
"We'll use your idea, and take it to new
scientific heights and save the world."
"Yes, I'd love to."
Okay! Facial recognition software
found us a match
from the press conference footage.
The Turtle's name is Russell Glosson.
He was a small-time thief,
who stopped thieving
after the particle accelerator explosion.
All right, I'm gonna head to work.
Catch Joe up.
Let me know if you find out
anything else.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah. It's just... (CLEARING THROAT)
It's hard to look at that and not think
about how I can't help people anymore.
Well, we have lots of technology here.
Why don't we figure out
how to get your speed back?
(INHALES) I'm a scientist too, Caitlin.
And when I first got here, all I did was
work on how to get my speed back.
Believe me, whatever test you could run...
I've already done it.
JOE: The Turtle?
Cisco's been looking for this guy forever.
Singh just put an APB out on him.
Um... How did everybody know
about Glosson before I did?
Mmm. Cisco's got a whole list of
unidentified metas.
The boys around here are calling him
Cisco de La Mancha.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, are you good?
You seem a little jittery.
A little anxious.
Let's be honest.
I'm really nervous about
this whole dinner tonight with Wally.
Come on. Why are you...
Why are you nervous?
You're, like, the best dad ever.
He'll see that.
(SIGHS) It'll be a whole lot easier
with you being there.
Joe, I wouldn't miss it.
-See you tonight.
-All right.
-Hey, you.
-Hey.
-You got a sec?
-Yeah.
I just...
I just want to make sure
everything's okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm... I, uh, don't want to nag.
That's not, you know, who I am. I just...
I don't want you to feel burdened
by anything.
No, I don't.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, wait, Patty. The New Years
is always a hard time for me.
It's when my mom died,
so just those memories all come out
and they're hard to put away.
So if it feels like
I haven't been communicating...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry. I didn't know.
No, no, no.
Look, um, we haven't had a romantic night
in a while.
What do you say, tomorrow night,
we get some dinner and drinks,
and maybe a little kissing...
That sounds like what we need.
Okay. All right, I'll see you later.
Okay.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Okay, I think we can call it.
Wally is not coming.
I'm sorry, Joe.
I know how much this meant to you.
He's a kid, right? I get it.
He could have at least called.
Well, there could be a number of reasons
why he didn't.
Thank you for being here. I love you.
-I love you.
-(BOTH GROAN)
See you in the morning, Barr.
Yeah.
Well, West family 2.0
is not really off to a great start.
You've been quiet all evening.
The Turtle?
How do you know about him?
(CHUCKLES)
No, erm. No. Just had a lot on my mind.
Patty? We... We may have met for coffee.
Iris...
She really cares about you, Barry.
And she's just wondering
why you've been so "guarded."
And what did you tell her?
I told her to talk to you.
Oh, that's not cool.
You know, she did mention
that you've been having nightmares.
About Zoom killing her.
Look, I know that things have been
moving pretty fast between you two.
But you realize you can't keep things
from her forever, right?
One day, you're going to have to
tell her the truth.
That I'm The Flash? I can't do that.
Barry... I wish a year ago,
you had told me the truth.
So, what?
You think that I should just tell her?
I think that if you are serious
about being with her,
you have to.
All right. Then that's what I'm gonna do.
I'll tell Patty I'm The Flash.
Hey. You guys got anything?
I think we found the next target for
our 30-something
metahuman-not-a-ninja Turtle.
How long did it take you
to come up with that one?
It just came out of my mouth.
Did you see that? That was amazing.
Central City Museum is hosting
a special black-tie event tonight
showcasing The Crystal Ball.
It's a famous painting, apparently,
recently recovered from Markovia.
The painting is on loan to the museum
from the Silverberg family.
Jacob Silverberg, himself, said, "The
painting's safe return means more to us
"than all the money in the world."
It's like they're begging Turtle
to rob it.
Okay, yes. This is a plan.
So, the Turtle will make his move, and
we can be there waiting to take him down.
How do you look in a tux?
Come on. He's 6'2", he's square-jawed
and he's jacked. I think he looks fine.
I'm 6'4".
Oh, crap.
Problem?
No. No.
An opportunity. Maybe. Hold on.
Hey, you. I'm excited to see you tonight.
Yeah, me too. Actually, about that, um...
So I know I said let's have dinner, but,
uh, you've been wanting me to share more.
So, I thought that I would share
that I love art.
Okay. Interesting.
Yeah. No, it's just, you know,
I can't get enough of art.
Anyway, there's this event
at the Central City Museum tonight.
They're showing this really famous
painting that I've always loved.
Actually, I don't know anything about art.
But, what's the saying? I know what
I like, and I like you, so count me in.
All right, great. I'll see you at 8:00.
ALL: 7:00.
Or 7:00. I'll see you at 7:00.
Okay. 7:00 it is.
Bye.
You know, you're a really great superhero,
a really great superhero...
Thanks. Thank you.
But, do you think it's a good idea, when
you're fighting crime, to bring a date?
I'm gonna tell Patty that I'm The Flash.
What... Is that a bad idea?
What do we think?
I will say, she put bullets
in King Shark and Harry.
So, as far as I'm concerned,
that's Team Flash material to me.
All right. Yes. Thank you, Cisco.
Yeah. Thank you.
-Cool.
-Mmm...
I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna tell her.
Don't tell her.
Huh?
You care for this woman?
(CHUCKLES)
That's nice. Then keep her
as far away from this as possible.
And here's why.
If Zoom finds out who you care for,
who you love, who you live for,
he'll take them from you.
(SIGHS) All right. Keep your eyes open
for the Turtle.
A sentence I never thought I would say.
Cisco, are you and Harry in position?
CISCO: I'm in the security feed. I've got
the facial recognition software running,
so we'll be able to spot Turtle
before he makes his move.
(WHISPERS) Turtle.
Why do you insist
on giving them ridiculous nicknames?
Me? Who's the genius
that came up with "Zoom?"
Yeah, well...
I'll tell you.
About two years ago,
this was on Earth-2 now,
the CCPD there, they got a 911 call
about a hostage situation.
But when the S.W.A.T. team got there,
there were no hostages.
It was a trap.
Zoom set a trap in order to show
the police that they could not stop him.
And he killed 14 officers. Men and women.
Slaughtered them.
Left one alive to tell what happened.
That officer described blue lightning
zooming all about
as his comrades,
brothers- and sisters-in-arms,
were murdered.
That officer considered himself
to be a lucky one,
spared in order to tell the tale,
until Zoom went to his house that night
and killed him, too.
Anyway, that's how
we got the nickname Zoom.
If you ever need me to vibe,
so you can know if she's still alive...
She's alive.
Right.
-(SCREAMING)
-No!
You have a really weird look on your face.
Do I look weird?
No, no. Um, you look like a dream.
(CHUCKLES) You look very handsome.
I can't wait to see this painting.
What painting? The painting. Uh, yeah.
Me too. Um, yeah.
How about we talk first?
I thought you'd never ask.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I can't figure you out, Barry Allen.
That is because I work hard
to hide who I really am.
You don't have to hide with me.
I just have to really trust someone,
if they're gonna know the truth.
Do you?
I trust you, Patty.
I trust you, too.
Patty, um...
After I was struck by lightning,
when I woke up...
We've got eyes on Turtle!
Barry, you were saying?
I have to go. I'm sorry.
What? What? Barry!
CCPD! Freeze!
-(CROWD MURMURING)
-(PATTY EXCLAIMS)
How are you as fast as The Flash?
Oh, no. He is much slower.
What's this, a trap? I'm slow, not stupid.
CAITLYN: Oh, my God!
(GRUNTING)
JAY: Okay, I got him. Come on.
Your pupils are normal.
Your heart rate's a little low.
But other than that,
no concussive symptoms.
I really do feel fine. What about Turtle?
No sign of him.
Or the painting.
He must have gotten away with it
in the chaos.
Yeah. Things went a little sideways
after your girlfriend decided to go all
Lethal Weapon I through IV on Turtle.
Oh, my God. Patty's gonna think
I ditched her. No. I gotta go.
Where are you... Finding Turtle
is what's important right now.
Yeah. This is important to me, too.
But we need to see
if your speed still works.
(STUTTERS) I think it still works.
We still have to find out
how Turtle drained him of it.
Can I talk to you for a second?
You never got your champagne.
(CHUCKLES)
I couldn't find any flutes.
I hope that's okay.
Of course.
Here you go.
Mmm...
(SIGHS) Let me go see if I can
make myself useful.
Mmm!
(KNOCKING)
I was right. I thought
that you would look mad and you do.
What happened?
Um...
I don't really have a good excuse.
Nothing? Nothing? I mean, come on, Barry.
Anything is better than nothing.
I mean, come on.
Holy crap, I've been a really, really
cool girlfriend.
Most girls don't have the self-esteem
to handle the...
"Plans? Oh, no plans. That's cool."
Or the waking up in the middle
of the night screaming again?
Fine. Whatever. And then,
and then the really, really fancy plans?
Which were awesome, and then
you ditched me right before I almost died.
I mean, when you put it that way, it's...
I'm actually really upset.
Yeah, I know.
Look, we've been having fun.
And fun has been so great.
But I'm moving past fun to the close part.
That's what I want, okay?
That's where I'm going.
You need to figure out
what it is that you want.
And do it fast.
Fast is my specialty.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
-(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
-(CROWD CHEERING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Tail Lights! Tail Lights!
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah!
Yo, pay up.
(CHUCKLES)
What, you got someone tailing me now?
Why didn't you show up for dinner
last night?
Couldn't make it.
You tell someone you're gonna
be somewhere, you show up.
Guess I didn't have my dad
to teach me that, huh?
Is this why you came to Central City?
Not to get to know me or your sister,
but this nonsense?
You know, no one in Keystone
will race me anymore.
But I don't actually have
to explain myself to you.
Actually, you do.
This is illegal. I'm a cop, remember?
Oh, yeah. Yes. The detective
who didn't know he had a son.
And who doesn't know anything about me.
I am trying to get to know you, Wally.
These races, that car that I won,
that's the only way that
I can pay for my mom's hospital bills.
Get her the help that she needs.
You don't have to do this. I have money
saved. I can dip into my pension.
I don't need your money. I can take care
of myself and my mom, okay?
I'm the man of our house.
That position has been filled.
Go home to your family, Joe.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCKING)
Barry?
Hey.
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
What do you want from me?
The thing most precious to The Flash.
You.
Patty?
No, no, no, no, no.
Joe, Joe!
Um, I think the Turtle has Patty.
Look, just meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs,
all right?
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
(PATTY PANTING)
What do you want from me?
I want you to stop moving...
Forever.
What do you get out of killing me?
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you.
That's much too fast and messy.
I like to take things nice and slow.
You don't have to hurt me
to try to prove a point.
This isn't about hurting you.
This is about hurting someone
who values you.
Who, Barry?
No. The Flash.
What does he have to do with this?
I saw the way he saved you.
Yes, that's what he does. He's a hero.
He saves people who need saving.
It's a waste of time saving people.
They take everything for granted.
So you take the things
that matter most to them.
My wife, Rosalyn, took me for granted.
She wanted to leave me,
the thing I valued most.
So that's what this is about?
You're hurt because your wife left you.
I couldn't let that happen.
So I made her mine.
Forever.
(GASPS)
I do hope I spelled your name right.
JOE: Barr, we'll find her.
I'm not getting any leads on this guy.
It's like he's totally
fallen off the grid.
(STUTTERS) You know, any of the stuff
he's stolen, I can't find it.
He keeps them. He keeps them
the way a serial killer collects trophies.
He's stolen a lot of stuff.
Which means he needs a lot of space
to store it, right?
That's where we start.
See if he rented any storage spaces.
No, no... I'm not getting anything.
Wait a minute. His ex-wife used to be
an archivist
for antiquities at the Naydel Library
before it shut down.
And it shut down three months
after the accelerator exploded.
That place is big enough to hold
Turtle's stuff?
Okay, all right.
Wait, Barry, we haven't even figured out
how to neutralize the Turtle's power.
Well, I'm gonna have to power through it.
(PANTING) All right.
I'm outside the library.
Barry, the only way to save Patty
is if you grab her
in between each of the Turtle's pulses.
You'll only have two-tenths of a second
to make your moves.
I got it.
(GRUNTING) No!
(SHUDDERING)
(GROANING)
I guess he doesn't care about you
as much as I thought.
No!
No! No! Please...
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Patty. It's all right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, whoever you are.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, Turtle.
So you want to know
my new definition of "irony"?
Now you are our most prized possession.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCREAMING)
Patty okay?
She is. Yeah.
CAITLYN: Jay.
Yeah?
I know. Why didn't you tell me
that you're sick?
The champagne...
You took my DNA off the glass.
You know I lost my husband.
How hard that was for me to move on.
How could you let me get close to you
knowing that soon, I'd lose you, too?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
I just... I didn't expect this.
I didn't expect you.
Then help me find a cure.
There is no cure.
The only way to save me
is to get my speed back.
And the only way to do that
is to stop Zoom.
Then let's stop him.
Yeah.
(KNOCKING)
Hey.
I think I left my sweater here
the other night. It's green.
Oh, yeah.
I thought that didn't look like Barry's.
I'm heading back to Keystone tonight.
That's a fast trip.
Yeah, well, it's getting a little hot
in Central City for me.
Don't worry, I'll try not to run
too many lights on the way there.
You know, if you're waiting
for an apology, it's not coming.
No, no. I'm...
I'm the one that should be apologizing
to you.
I felt bad not being there
while you were growing up,
and I was pushing
this whole father-son thing.
I'm sorry.
Let's just slow down a bit.
I won't try to be your instant dad
and you won't have to pretend
that you want to be my son.
Deal?
All that food for you?
Doesn't have to be. You like chow mein?
No.
But I like kung pao chicken.
PATTY: Initial and sign.
There you go. Thank you, guys.
Crazy night.
-Patty. Hey.
-Hi.
Um, can we talk? Like, really talk?
Yeah, uh...
No. Now is not really an awesome time.
I have a mountain of paperwork on my desk
I need to finish, so I'm sorry, I can't...
Okay, no, no. Okay. Really quick.
Um, so you were right.
You were right about everything.
Um, I've been closed off and weird
and all the things that you said I was.
But mostly, I have not been honest.
Barry?
I'm leaving Central City.
What?
Before Mardon, and before my dad,
before everything
I always wanted to be CSI.
And four years ago, I was accepted into
the Forensic Science program
at Midway City University.
That's a really great school.
Yeah. Yeah, I know. I just... I didn't go.
You know, I deferred to become a cop
and catch my dad's killer.
And I've done that.
So, uh...
So it's time to move on.
From the job.
From everything.
Patty, Patty, Pat...
Journal log entry number 113.
Jess, I'm coming for you.
Soon. I promise.
I was thinking earlier today
about the time that you were four,
I took you to the planetarium,
just you and me.
I remember because it was the first time
I took you out all by myself.
The planetarium was crowded,
you held my hand for dear life.
Or maybe it was the other way around.
But it was in the Mars exhibit
that I lost you.
Panic. I had that place locked down.
And in one minute, I had
every security guard looking for you,
and I could feel the fear rise
in the back of my throat,
and something else rising also.
Some dark instinct inside me
about what I would do
to the person who had taken you.
The things I would do...
Unspeakable things.
And it was in that moment that I realized
for certain
that I would do anything to get you back.
(PANTING)
Gideon.
Yes, Professor Thawne?
Where the hell am I?