Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created
the alternate timeline,
Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline
to how it was,
only to find
things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats
to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- Caitlin, I'm sorry, honey.
These powers you have...
the more you use them,
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
- I took your cuffs.
- Is this some sort
of fashion choice?
'Cause you're not a meta-human.
- Am I her?
- Yeah.
They saw the both of us.
Like, full-on
Vibe versus Killer Frost.
- The time has come
to set you free.
- Wally, don't!
[energy blasts and whirs]
[energy blasting]
- [snarling]
You may serve the speed force,
Flash,
but I rule it.
You are only a man,
but I am a god.
Your god.
I am Savitar.
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Shoot him!
- I can't see it.
- Just do it!
[Savitar screeching]
- Alchemy!
- Let's go for a run.
[energy blasts]
♪ ♪
- Barry!
[Savitar smacking,
Barry grunting]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- What's happening?
- I don't understand.
The suit's tracker must be
malfunctioning.
It says he's appearing
and reappearing
all over the city at once,
and that's impossible.
He can't be moving that fast.
- Well, if he can't,
maybe something else can.
♪ ♪
- Had enough?
- Not even close.
♪ ♪
[Barry gasps]
[computer beeping]
- Look. It stopped.
He's at the waterfront.
- Okay.
We have to get to him.
- And do what?
He's fighting an invisible force
that's too fast to track.
- If I may, I have a plan.
- No. No.
- Pretty good plan.
- Put your hand down.
- It's a question of numbers.
'Cause right now,
it seems to be one against one.
What if there were three
against one?
Do you know what I'm saying?
- Cisco, you can open a breach
and get you both
to the waterfront.
- Guys, I can't.
It's too dangerous.
- I'm begging you. Please.
- Still alive down there?
You are only a shadow
beneath my throne.
You are the past,
whereas I...
I am the future Flash.
- I can't see it!
- [snarling]
- Just do it!
[crackling]
[Savitar roars]
[ice crackles]
[ice crackling]
[ice crunches, Savitar whooshes]
- Whoo-ee!
Ahh. Oh, boy.
I'm gonna feel that tomorrow.
Ah.
That was a new and painful use
of my powers.
Ugh. You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Just cold.
[breathing heavily]
Thanks for coming.
♪ ♪
- Barry, you're already healing.
You should be fine soon.
Um, Cisco, the MRI I did
of your brain shows changes
in the capillary morphology
similar to that
of a mini-stroke.
I wouldn't try an
intra-dimensional breach
like that anytime soon.
- Okay, okay. Mini-stroke?
You can't just gloss over that
like that.
Okay? What does that...
what does that mean?
Am I gonna have this migraine
for the rest of my life?
- It means you should take a few
aspirin and you'll be fine.
- Oh. Well,
just lead with that next time.
- Cait, I know what a risk
you took using your powers.
Thank you.
- I didn't do anything.
- Well, you saved my life.
- You've saved mine
plenty of times.
I'm gonna go
check on Wally.
- Okay.
[tense music]
- What was that?
That frozen thing
at the waterfront?
- I don't know.
But now we know Alchemy is
just the lackey.
Whatever that thing was, it's
what we're really up against.
- Question: you're the only one
who can see him?
Why?
I mean...why?
- You're both speedsters.
Maybe it has something to do
with that.
- Maybe. But I think he's
more than a speedster.
I mean, when he had me,
it wasn't
like we were even moving;
it was just like,
"bam," we were instantly
somewhere different,
even from my perspective.
- Did he say
anything else?
- He said his name was Savitar.
- Mm.
Hindu god of motion.
- What?
How do you know that?
- Crossword puzzle wizard.
On two planets, I might add.
12 across, 7 letters.
Savitar. Bam.
Hindu god of motion.
- He said he was God.
- That's...that's nice.
That's not scary...at all.
[computer beeping]
- Hey.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
How are you?
- [sighs]
- Can you tell anything?
- Wally's alive in there,
but his vitals are
really subdued.
His brain function
is low.
Something like you'd see
in a coma patient.
- I was in a coma
after I got my powers.
Maybe it's a
similar process.
Can we take him out?
- When a caterpillar is
in its chrysalis,
it literally breaks its body
down into enzyme soup
before rebuilding
as a butterfly.
If this cocoon is
doing the same thing to Wally,
I just...I don't know.
- You're right.
You don't know.
None of us knows a damn thing
about what's going on in there.
And I feel like a fool
just standing here listening.
- Dad?
- Look, I've said it before:
I don't have the education
most of you had.
The science of what we do here
is mostly lost on me.
But what I do have
is my detective skills
and my instinct,
and time and time again,
I don't use them
because you guys all tell me
that everything is
gonna be okay.
Everything is not okay.
- I'm sorry, Joe.
- I know you are.
But I can't just stand here.
My gut is telling me
I need to do something.
- This is not
your fault.
- Yeah, it is.
[door opens]
- Not so tough without your
friends and your fancy robe.
I want to know about Alchemy.
What he does,
how he does it...
- His powers are
beyond human understanding.
- Try me.
- Oh, you will be tried.
All of you.
When my master rises,
the human race will be judged.
From where I'm sitting,
you will not fare very well.
[dramatic music]
[groaning]
- You think I'm playing
with you?
My son is
in one of those cocoons,
and you're gonna tell me
how to get him out.
Now talk!
- [whimpering]
[knocking at door]
- Go away!
- [panting]
[groaning]
- Caitlin, what is it?
- It's Wally.
He's out of that thing.
He's fine.
- And he's okay?
- Yeah. He's fine.
I promise.
- Oh, thank God.
Thank you, Caitlin.
- You should probably
go see him.
- Uh, yeah.
[lock clinks]
♪ ♪
- Where is Alchemy?
- Tell me where Alchemy is.
- I sense great fear in you.
You fear your power,
your own greatness.
- I don't fear anything anymore.
Where is Alchemy?
- The only one I fear is
that whom Alchemy serves,
the dark lord Savitar.
- Maybe it's time
you started fearing me.
- [screaming distantly]
No, no, no...aah!
[banging on door]
- Who's in there?
[whooshing]
[dramatic music]
[pounding on door]
- Frozen?
♪ ♪
Hello?
[coughing]
[ice crackles]
- [stammers]
Excuse me?
- Hey! Anybody out there?
[pounding on door]
Somebody open the door!
[pounding on door continues]
- Let us out of here!
- I need you to come with me.
- Wait.
What is going on?
- Hey, Joe.
- What do you mean?
- Caitlin came by the precinct.
She said that Wally was out
and that he was okay.
- What?
I didn't even see her leave.
[whoosh]
- [sighs]
- SWAT needs to establish
a cordon at 6th and Fairmont
all the way down to Gleason.
Move. Move!
Let's go!
- Detective Patterson?
Hey. What's...
- Just the man I want to see.
Your little friend's in big
trouble, Allen.
- My f...
- A female meta-human
attacked the precinct,
took Julian Albert hostage.
- Julian? Wait,
do you know who the meta is?
- Uh, no. But she's smart.
I'll tell you that.
Took out our security cameras
so we couldn't ID her.
I thought
maybe you'd recognize her.
- No.
Why would she take Julian?
- She's a meta.
They're all crazy.
But don't worry.
We'll get her.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing, Cait?
♪ ♪
- Bit chilly in here,
isn't it?
- Shut up.
I need to think.
- Look.
I know who you are, okay?
You're...you're...
you're Allen's friend, right?
Dr. Snow?
- I said be quiet.
- Are you going to kill me?
- I need to find Alchemy.
- Alchemy? What?
- What do you want me to do?
- Alchemy has disciples,
followers.
I need you to create
an algorithm
that will allow you
to locate anyone
who has searched
for a specific keyword
in the last six months.
If we find one of his followers,
they can take me to Alchemy.
- Okay. But "alchemy" is
a relatively common phrase.
It'll have hundreds of hits.
- Then search
for an uncommon one.
- Such as?
- Savitar.
- Savitar?
[sizzling]
[grunts]
- Get searching.
♪ ♪
- So, they don't know
why she took Julian?
- No, they don't.
But more importantly,
they don't even know
that it's Caitlin yet,
so we need to find her
before they do.
- Savitar.
Now, what about this Savitar...
- We find Caitlin.
Then we can worry about Savitar.
- You know what, guys?
I'm...I agree with Barry.
Let's find Caitlin.
- Okay. You're right. And when
we find Caitlin, then what?
- I don't know. I mean, she's
not thinking straight. She's...
- She's becoming Killer Frost.
It's just like in the Vibe.
- We don't know that yet.
- Her mother said
the more that she uses
her powers,
the faster she's gonna go.
And saving you from Savitar...
that must have put her
over the edge.
- How do we find her?
- I don't know. I tried
pinging her cell and Julian's,
but she must have
ditched them both.
- Ahem!
If I may proffer a notion...
- Oh, great. More suggestions
from the genius over here.
- You don't call the genius.
The genius calls you.
Question:
how did you catch
your Captain Cold?
I've been reading about him
in your files.
Seems like a wily fellow.
Slow talker.
But his MO...strikingly similar
to our dear Caitlin's.
- What? No. We tracked him
using the satellite
to scan for ultraviolet
cold signatures.
[clacking]
Got it.
♪ ♪
No. Nothing near the precinct.
- Wait, what's that?
- Frozen food warehouse.
- There she is.
Okay, I'm gonna isolate the feed
so that no one else can see it.
[sticks clack]
- All right, figure out
what she's making Julian do.
I'm going.
- Okay.
[whooshing]
- That...is cool.
- I found two individuals
that have searched
for the name Savitar.
Here are both their addresses,
both of them in Central City.
What exactly
are you gonna do to them?
- I don't know.
♪ ♪
What am I doing?
[keys clacking]
[phone buzzing]
- Son of a...
Sergeant, we got a location
on Albert.
Let's move.
- What part of
"I'll freeze you to death"
did you not understand?
[whooshing]
- Stop.
- Get out of here.
- You know I can't.
- What are you doing?
Take her out. Take her out.
- You don't want to do this.
You don't want to hurt anybody.
- She's willing to hurt someone.
Knock her out.
- Caitlin...
- Leave me alone.
- What are you doing?
- I have to find Alchemy.
- We will find him.
All right? Together.
- No. You don't understand.
I don't want to lock him up.
I need him to help me.
- Help you what?
- I need him to get rid
of my powers.
- Oh, Caitlin.
- I don't know
if it works that way.
- You don't know
that it doesn't.
- I know that we love you.
And we will do everything
that we can to help you.
You and I...we've been
through too much together
to let each other down now.
Please.
Let me help you.
- Like you helped
your mother?
- Caitlin.
- Or Wally?
Or me?
You keep messing
with everyone's lives,
wrecking everything,
and we're left behind
to pick up the pieces
from your mistakes.
Some things you break can't be
put back together.
- I can fix this.
- Oh, like you fixed
Cisco's family?
You didn't tell Cisco that you
screwed him worst of all,
did you?
You hear that, Cisco?
Dante was alive,
healthy and happy,
until Barry created Flashpoint.
When he reset things,
that's what killed him.
Barry is the reason
your brother is dead.
[guns cock]
- Albert's down. Shoot her!
[gunfire]
- [cries out]
- That severed
your triceps surae.
Even with your healing
abilities,
it'll take four hours
to regenerate.
Don't follow me.
- Caitlin.
Come on...gah!
[grunting]
♪ ♪
- How much does it hurt?
- As much as I deserve.
- Okay. Let me know.
They took Julian
to County General.
He's still out cold.
How hard did you hit him?
- I don't know.
I didn't mean to knock him out.
Or maybe I did.
[grunts]
Cisco.
Hey, man, um,
what Caitlin said...
- Was she lying?
- No. Um...
- You're sorry?
- [sighs]
- That you killed my brother?
'Cause he was here.
He was alive...
until you created Flashpoint,
until you did this.
- I know, man.
- I don't even know
how to feel right now.
All I know is
Caitlin is out there,
and we need to find her.
Can we do that?
- Yeah.
- I hacked Julian's computer.
Caitlin had him look up
two addresses:
16 Hawthorne Avenue
and 1104 Truman Place.
- She's trying to find the
acolytes, I was trying to say.
- What exactly would she want
with Alchemy's followers?
- She must think
that he can take her to Alchemy.
She wants him
to take her powers away.
- We know.
We heard everything.
Well, two acolytes,
two addresses.
Which one's she gonna hit first?
- We got to watch both.
- You're gonna stay here.
You can barely walk.
I'll take Hawthorne.
- I'll take Truman.
- I care about Caitlin,
but I don't want to leave Wally.
- Dad, Barry and I will stay
with Wally.
You go with H.R.
- Oh, yeah,
I would love that.
Hey, you and me...
all-star team, huh?
All right, you know what?
I'll make a couple cappuccinos
for the road, right,
so we're ready
for tonight's adventures.
Hey, not to worry, Barry.
Right?
We'll help her.
- Cisco.
If you find her...
- I won't call you.
You've done enough.
- [sighs]
- The acolyte's
on the second floor.
- Cup of joe, Joe?
- No.
- No? All right.
You're a tea drinker, I bet.
- If you want to talk nonsense,
I'm gonna need you
to stop talking to me.
- You're worried
about your son.
- Do you have kids?
- No.
- Then I don't think we could
possibly have a conversation
about how I'm feeling right now.
- Okay, but...
as an interested observer,
I can tell you
Barry admires you.
- Yeah.
Well, he needs to listen to me.
- Yeah, well,
the reason he doesn't is
Barry's real superpower
isn't speed.
It's hope.
- Mm.
- Kid's got
an endless reservoir.
Believes everything's gonna
work out.
- Well,
he's wrong about this one.
They all are.
I said it before:
when my gut tells me
something is off,
I trust it.
And I need them to trust me.
- The next time your gut tells
our team what to do,
I'll trust it.
- How do I know you're not just
telling me what I want to hear?
- [laughs]
Well,
what does your gut tell you?
[beeping]
- What is that?
- The satellite.
[grunts]
It's programmed to detect
rapid temperature decelerations.
[beeping continues]
That's the house
Cisco's watching.
- Oh, God.
- Honey? Craig?
It's freezing in here.
Go check the thermostat.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
[ice zings]
- Both of my parents are
doctors.
It's all I ever
wanted to be.
Growing up, I used to practice
the Hippocratic Oath.
I was obsessed
with it.
If anyone was
even gonna step on a bug,
I would say, "Do no harm."
It's built into my DNA.
Unfortunately,
my DNA isn't what it used to be.
So, believe me when I say
answer every one
of my questions,
or I will harm you
and your family.
- [breathing shakily]
- Who is Alchemy?
- I don't know.
I've never seen him
without the mask.
- I know he can
give people powers.
Can he take them away?
- Yes.
But you can't make Alchemy
do anything.
He's just an acolyte, like me.
We both serve the speed god,
Savitar.
He's shown us the future.
I saw you there.
You were glorious
and powerful.
My lord has special plans
for you,
Caitlin Snow.
Or should I say...
Killer Frost?
♪ ♪
- Caitlin!
- [panting]
- Really?
You brought your toys?
- I'm hoping
it won't come to that.
- It won't.
- Look, I'm not leaving you
out here.
I want to help you.
- There's only one person
who can help me.
- Really?
You really think
seeking medical advice
from someone named Dr. Alchemy
is the way to go?
- Why not?
My name is Killer Frost.
- Your name...
is Caitlin Snow.
- Can Caitlin Snow do this?
[icicles blasting]
- [panting]
Caitlin, please!
[beams blast]
[whooshing]
- Aah!
[groans]
- How's the leg?
♪ ♪
[both groan]
- I'm sorry, Caitlin.
- That was cold, Flash.
But this is colder.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- [breathing heavily]
Start vibrating.
It'll warm you up.
- [labored breathing]
[groans]
[sighs]
- Whew.
Guess I just needed
a little sleep.
[grunts]
Thanks, guys.
I'm feeling much better now.
It's okay.
You can let me out.
I promise
I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
Hmm.
Guess you're all smarter
than I thought.
You know, that was some blast
there, Vibe boy.
It kind of hurt.
- I didn't want to hurt you.
- You're pathetic.
- Alchemy can't help you.
But we can.
I promise.
- Oh, like you promised Eddie?
And like you promised Ronnie?
You know, for a hero, Flash,
you sure let a lot of people
around you die.
- This isn't you talking.
It's the powers.
They're messing with your mind.
You're sick.
- I'm broken, Barry.
But what do you care?
'Cause you've got Iris.
You got your happy ending.
Everyone else be damned.
So, I'll tell you what:
you guys let me go,
and I will leave you to your sad
and miserable lives.
- No. We're not abandoning you.
- You did this to me!
[dramatic music]
- Do you have any idea
how we can reverse this?
How we can get her back?
- It's like Caitlin said:
sometimes when things
get broken,
they can't be fixed.
- My son's not gonna end up
like Caitlin.
Help me get him
out of this thing.
- Oh, no, no. Joe, no.
We don't...we don't want
to touch that thing...
first off, we don't know
what that's gonna do to Wally,
right?
Maybe this is
the kind of situation
best left to the people
with the science.
- You mean Caitlin?
- [sighs]
- Please help me.
- What are you doing
down here?
- We should all be working
to find Alchemy and Savitar
and figure out how to stop them.
Instead, we're fighting
each other.
- Yeah. Team Flash is not
at its finest.
- Why didn't I just follow you
inside the house?
- Because you were hurting.
You would do anything
to make the pain go away.
That's why Caitlin is so lost.
And Cisco.
We will do anything
to make the pain stop.
That doesn't make you
a bad person.
That makes you human.
- Tell that to my friends.
My best friends,
one of them is locked up
like a villain;
the other one hates me.
- You can not take this all on
yourself.
- Why not?
- How do you know
that Caitlin wasn't
already affected
by the accelerator explosion,
or that Dante wouldn't have died
in a car accident anyway?
You are not God, Barry.
- That's what Jay said.
- Jay's a smart man.
You can not keep doing this
to yourself,
constantly going over
the what-ifs.
You'll go nuts.
Everyone in this building needs
The Flash right now:
my dad, Wally...
even Cisco and Caitlin.
So, be strong
like I know you are.
I know you don't want
to be the leader right now,
but you have to be.
- I told you I couldn't do this
without you.
- And you'll never have to.
[lights buzzing]
Wally.
- Yeah. Come on.
[buzzing, whirring]
- There's an energy surge
coming from the Cortex.
- What?
Joe! Hey!
What are you doing?
- Hey, Barr.
- Hey, stop!
You can't cut him out!
- I have to.
[saw buzzing]
- Joe, don't!
[whooshing]
[crashing]
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- Wally.
- Wally?
♪ ♪
- Joe.
- What did I do?
- Was this your idea?
- No.
Joe...I was helping Joe.
- No sign of Wally.
I've got the satellite
scanning the entire city
for rapid movement.
If he's a speedster,
he could be
halfway across the country
by now.
- Barry, we have to find him.
- I'm more worried
about what happens
when we do find him.
He didn't seem like he was
all there, Iris.
- I shouldn't have cut him
out of that thing.
- Joe, I...what we need right now
is a biochemist.
- You've got to go talk to her,
Barr.
- [exhales deeply]
All right.
[beeping, whirring]
We need your help, Caitlin.
Wally...he's...
he's out of the cocoon,
but his biochemistry
is all out of whack.
He went AWOL.
- So?
- So, when we find him,
he's gonna need your help.
He's gonna need
your medical expertise,
your experience with metas.
What he needs is
Caitlin Snow, MD.
- So, you came to try
and talk some sense into me.
- No.
I came to let you go.
[beeping, whirring]
- For a smart guy,
that was an awfully dumb move.
- Like I said,
you're free to go.
- What's the catch?
- You have to kill me.
- What is he doing?
- I don't know.
It's gonna be all right.
- You want to fight, Flash?
- No.
I'm not gonna fight you.
But if you want
to leave this room,
you're gonna have to kill me.
- Don't think I won't.
- Then do it.
[energy surges and ice crackles]
What are you waiting for?
What's the big deal?
Come on.
Live up to your name,
Killer Frost.
I want to see some killing.
You want to be the villain?
This is what they do.
They kill their friends,
because nothing matters to them
anymore, right?
Right?
Come on.
Kill me, Caitlin.
You can't do it.
You can't,
because underneath
all that cold,
you're still you.
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply]
Barry!
- It's okay.
I got you.
It's okay.
- I think extracting Wally early
from that cocoon
left him in a fugue state.
His synapses aren't used
to functioning at superspeed,
so his mind and muscles
are misfiring.
- I mean, will this stuff help?
- I've synthesized
a neural compound
that I think will get his mind
and body
running at the same speed.
- We just have to find him
first.
- Where'd he go, Joe?
What's your gut tell you?
- The house that he grew up in.
He used to go there
when he missed his mother.
- In Keystone.
Thank you.
[insects chirping]
- Wally! Wally!
It's your dad, son.
You're gonna be all right.
We're gonna take care of you,
okay?
[whooshing]
- [gasps]
Dad.
- Ooh!
[whooshing]
- Damn.
How fast is he going?
- Faster than Barry could
at the beginning.
- I, uh...
I just wanted to...
- It's okay.
You scared me for a second,
getting all Mother of Dragons
on me with that hair.
[both laugh]
- Thank you.
[whooshing]
- That is the greatest feeling
I've ever felt.
Barry, it's unreal.
- Yeah, it is.
- How fast was I going?
- Too fast.
- Dad, don't look so worried.
I'm fine. I feel fine.
In fact, I feel kind of awesome,
like everything is buzzing,
electric,
like I could do anything.
- That is what it feels like.
Got the Speed Force coursing
through you
giving you power.
You're a speedster now.
- [laughing]
Cool.
Um, so, what next?
- Caitlin is gonna run every
test she can think of on you.
I mean, if you're up for it.
- Being a doctor?
That, I'm always up for.
- Yeah, um, but when do I get
to go out, Barry,
with you?
- Uh...
- Okay, let's just take it
one normal-speed step at a time.
[phone buzzing]
- Slow down, Wallace.
- Barr, it's the hospital.
Julian's awake.
- He knows it was me.
He knows what I did.
- Don't worry.
I'll talk to him.
You'll be fine.
I promise.
[knocks on door]
Hey, man.
I just wanted to see
if you wanted to talk about...
- I don't.
- All right. Um...
Look, Cisco,
you're my best friend, man.
Are we gonna be okay?
You and me?
- You want me to be honest
with you?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I don't know.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Hey, Patterson.
- Barry Allen,
don't you ever work?
- I just wanted to make sure
that Julian was doing okay.
- Well, I'm about to take
his statement, yeah.
- Would it be okay if I talked
to him before you went in?
I just...we're pretty close,
him and I.
- Yeah. Go ahead.
Just make it quick.
- Always. Thank you.
- Oh.
- Hey.
- A hospital visit. I didn't
think you missed me that much.
- What did the doctors say?
- Concussion and frostbite,
but I'll be dandy in a few days.
- That's good news. I'm glad
you're gonna be all right.
- Yes, and as much
as I appreciate
your outburst of emotion,
I think we both know
the real reason you're here.
Your friend Caitlin Snow.
She's a meta,
and not one
of the friendly ones.
Did you know?
- She's sick, Julian.
- She is a bloody menace.
- Julian...
Man, I know that you think
that getting powers is
this binary game,
that you're either good or evil,
but life isn't like that,
even for metas.
Look.
Caitlin...she's a good person.
I'm begging you:
don't turn her in.
I will do anything you want,
but please don't do this to her.
- [scoffs]
I got hit pretty hard,
and I don't have the foggiest
who even kidnapped me at all.
- [sighs]
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
- There is one thing
you can do for me, mate.
- Anything.
- Quit.
- What?
- Tender your resignation
from the Central City
Police Department,
effective immediately.
I can overlook
the unexplained absences,
the constant disregard
for the rules and regulations,
but your moral compass is
broken, my friend.
I point-blank refuse
to work with someone
whose sense of right or wrong is
as flippant as the weather,
someone who thinks friendship is
more important than justice.
You are unfit to be CSI.
Barry Allen has no place
in law enforcement.
Now, do we have an agreement,
or would you like the detective
to meet that girl?
- All right.
- [sighs]
- He's all yours.
- Hey, Albert.
- Hey.
- So, what can you tell me
about our...our meta friend?
- I don't really remember
anything.
To be honest with you,
it's all a bit of a blur, so...
- [sighs]
- Hey.
- We just heard from Singh.
You quit?
What...what is going on?
- I, um...
didn't really have a choice.
- What do you mean,
you didn't have a choice?
- Julian.
You quit, he keeps his mouth
shut about Caitlin.
- That son of a bitch.
- I don't know.
I mean, he said I couldn't
do something
like protect Caitlin
and still be a good CSI,
and maybe he's right.
- No, he's not.
Barry, you are
an incredible CSI,
and no one
in this building cares more
about helping people
find justice than you.
And that was
long before you were The Flash.
This lab...it's your life.
- You're my life.
Both of you.
And Wally and Caitlin,
Cisco.
[sighs]
If these past few months
have taught me anything,
it's that I would give up
everything I have
to keep you all safe.
No regrets.
- Every time I think you've
run out of ways to be a hero,
you show me another one.
You hungry?
- Yeah.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbles]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Julian.
Julian!
- No.
Stay away.
- No, Julian.
You can't get away.
There's nowhere
I won't find you.
♪ ♪
Only together can we bring about
my return.
[thunder rumbles]
♪ ♪
Become my servant once more.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Become Alchemy.
[thunder crashes]