She's dead.
You killed Alexa.
[Speed Force as Nora Allen]
Barry and I did it together.
That was the only way.
She was the strongest.
I needed every ounce of power,
including your strength, to kill her.
I'm supposed to protect lives,
not destroy them!
I'm helping you clean up
your mess, Barry. This is your fault!
The night you brought me back,
you created these monsters.
You and your lightning rod.
When you regained your speed,
I wasn't the only thing
you two willed into existence.
- That's impossible.
- Really?
Alexa was afraid to come here,
but she trusted you.
Why?
Because deep down,
she could feel a connection with you.
The same connection
that you feel with me now.
But these new Forces,
the way they've merged with
the people they chose as avatars,
it's corrupted them.
Because it's unnatural.
But once the other two were gone...
I won't help you kill again.
Oh.
My beautiful boy.
You have no choice.
Because if you don't,
those things will kill everyone
you've sworn to keep safe.
Is that what you want?
Then please, Barry...
help me.
No.
You have to help me, damn it!
Nora, stop!
I will destroy
those other Forces, Barry,
with or without your help.
Then you'll see that I'm right.
[Caitlin] What a day.
First Frost is sent to Iron Heights
for life, and now Alexa's dead.
We can't let this happen again.
[Caitlin] I'll get to work.
I need to figure out
how Nora was able to...
Kill a god?
She could because she had help.
Barry, she tricked you.
No, she manipulated me.
Just like she's been doing
the whole time.
Honey, I know how you feel...
but not everything she did and said
was a lie.
I mean, there were moments
that felt real, too. That must mean...
Iris, we can't trust her anymore.
What about what Nora said about
you two creating the other Forces?
I mean, there's no proof.
Well, what if we find out
if Nora is telling the truth?
If she is, then that means
the other Forces would have been born
the same day she was.
I'll pull satellite scans
from the night we fought
Mirror Monarch.
Please and thank you.
Okay. You see that cluster
of kinetic energy readings?
Pretty sure that's the Speed Force
being reborn in the Speed Lab.
Whoa. There they are.
Three brand-spanking-new
isotopic signatures.
Nora was right.
We created the Forces.
[Cisco] Fuerza's dead.
Nora killed her.
She killed the Strength Force?
And now she wants to kill
the other two Forces.
Maybe I should go to San Francisco.
What?
My series of photos on Eva's attacks
got accepted at a gallery there.
Babe, congrats!
Well, I was thinking of going
to help them install the exhibition.
I'd ask you to come,
but I know you have your perfect job
at S.T.A.R. Labs
and your amazing friends.
I mean, you're an OG member
of Team Flash.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
This is an Isotopic Scanning Lens.
It can detect the signatures
of all four Forces.
Even kinetic signatures
from Speed Force Nora.
And if one's nearby...
[Kamillia] It lights up
like an overexposed landscape.
In which case, you run the other way.
Okay? I'm serious.
I just want you to be safe.
Are you sure you're okay?
[phone rings]
Oh, it's Barry. I gotta get back.
They could have found Nora,
or worse, she's come back on her own.
How bad is it?
Okay. Did Nora kill somebody else?
No. And I have a way to make sure
she never does.
Okay. How?
I'm here. What's going on?
I spent all night
coming up with a way to fix all this.
Okay. What's the solve?
We need to wipe the new Forces
out of existence.
Barry, what are you saying?
I want to go back in time...
and uncreate them.
Barry, you're talking about
creating another Flashpoint.
You know we can't do that.
Not if I can figure out
a way to go back
that doesn't affect the timeline.
Which would be impossible.
Barry, look, I know
that you're devastated about Alexa.
But uncreating Forces?
That crosses a line.
I convinced Alexa to come here.
Her death is my fault.
If we don't get these new Forces
out of Psych and Deon,
Nora will kill them, too.
So it's on us to fix this.
By killing Deon and Psych?
No. I'm not killing them.
I'm saving them from the Forces
that took over their lives.
Whoever they were before this,
they can go back
to being those same people again.
And what about the other Force
that was born that night?
Nora. If you uncreate...
We're only going to target
the new Forces,
not Nora. That's the plan.
But if something goes wrong,
Barry, you might lose your speed.
Then I lose my speed.
All right? It's worth the risk
to keep everyone safe.
And what about the risk to Nora?
Does her life not matter at all?
Nora's not a person, Iris!
[sighs] She never was.
Look, if we uncreate these Forces,
we can put everything back to normal.
Hopefully, that'll fix her, too.
Hopefully?
Barry, do you hear yourself
right now?
Iris, I'm trying to save people.
I mean, how do you not see
this is the right thing to do?
The right thing to do would be trying
to get through to Nora.
Just like how we beat Eva.
Just like how we talked down
Abra Kadabra. That is what we do.
We tried talking to her.
All Nora did was double down.
- [sighs in exasperation]
- There's no reaching her.
Obviously, we disagree on this.
Yes, we do.
I have to do it.
Then you'll be doing it without me.
Wait. You want
to go after a Force of Nature?
Yeah. If I can convince Nora
not to kill Deon and Psych,
then Barry will see
that she can be reasoned with.
But how do we find her? I mean,
she's the frickin' Speed Force.
Well, if she finds us first,
at least we'll know she's coming.
Holy crap, you guys gotta see this.
You see that bright spot
at the center of you?
I think that's kinetic energy.
Guys, this is gonna sound
really wild, but...
Yeah, 'cause a ghost-hunting lens
isn't weird enough?
But if Barry and I
created these Forces,
what if there's a little bit
of each of them inside of us?
Like you're all connected.
Wait. Iris, when you're
over by the door,
your glow was brighter.
Like there's something
in that direction
that was intensifying it.
- What if...
- That something is Nora?
Guys, we can use me as a divining rod
to track her down.
Yup, that's weirder.
Elemental Force Particles?
They're the particles
that created the new Forces.
The lightning bolt
that re-birthed the Speed Force
was full of 'em.
Now, if we can extract a sample
of these Force Particles
from the lightning,
then we can send out
an electromagnetic pulse
that'll seek out
those same particles,
wherever they may be
along the temporal spectrum.
And you can erase
the new Forces from existence.
That's not bad.
But small detail, though.
How in the world are you supposed
to extract these particles
from a giant bolt of lightning?
A few weeks ago,
when Barry was Spock-Flash,
he modified the Tachyon Enhancer
to siphon
Mirror Monarch's dark matter photons.
So all we have to do
is tweak the enhancer
to siphon Force Particles
instead of photons.
Tweaking the Tachyon Enhancer...
and then send out an EMP
to 86 the Forces. That's genius.
I mean, it's foolproof even.
But it still doesn't answer
how we're supposed to do this
and protect the timeline.
I'll figure it out, somehow.
I will. I'll figure it out.
Man, I wish Nash Wells was here.
I mean, he came up with most of these
equations for the ASF machine.
I feel like he'd crack this
easy-peasy.
Modify the Particle
Harness Collector.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Roger that, but where are you going?
To get the one person
who could help us pull this off.
Oh, no. Tess!
[laughs] President Bartlet
just mixed up his meds.
That's not gonna be good,
but great TV. Whoa.
[sighs, laughs]
Allen. Allen.
I'm guessing
this isn't a social call.
Not exactly. We need your help.
Well, how bad is it?
- That depends.
- On?
Whether or not you can
help us do the impossible.
Well, well, well. Honey, I'm home.
Holy deus ex machina. Timeless Wells.
- Perfect timing.
- Always.
So, apparently,
there's danger in Central City.
- Apparently.
- Well, then let's get busy.
Well, do you really think
we could do this
without affecting the timeline?
I know we can.
As long as we use me as your guide.
Harrison was there
when the Forces were created,
so if we use the other him
from that night
as a beacon to lock on to...
Hopefully, I can go back
to that exact moment...
but also bring Allen along
for the ride,
and he'll collect the particles.
Wait. So you can travel through time
with a plus one?
It should work.
When Allen and I go back
to that exact moment that those
dangerous Forces were created
17 days ago,
I will create
a protective time-bubble.
All right?
From that moment until now.
Preserving those days
in this timeline
and preventing
anything from changing.
Which would also allow us
to wipe out the new Forces
without altering any of the events
that have happened since then.
Yo, that is trippy.
Cisco, this'll work.
What about Iris?
When she sees everyone's safe,
she'll come around. She has to.
You're not convinced. I wasn't either
when Allen told me about this,
but then I thought of Tess.
I thought of my wife,
and how my future with Tess was...
ripped from me.
Until this gift,
which has allowed me
to relive every single day...
with Tess.
But only...
because I took a chance.
All right. I'm in.
It's brighter.
We must be getting close.
[sighs]
She should be here.
Maybe it was a false positive?
Or maybe since
Nora is the Speed Force,
her isotopic signature
is all over the city by now.
So what do we do?
I don't know,
but we are running out of time.
Well, Cisco always says
you can't solve a problem
till your asking the right question.
Isn't "Where's Nora's kinetic energy
leading us?" the right question?
No. The right question is,
"Where's Nora?"
We've been trying
to find the Speed Force
when we should be looking
for the person.
So where would
the real Nora Allen go?
Home.
Come on.
[exhales] Harness
modifications complete.
Let's get some time particles.
Actually, you know what? Um...
Let me just run one more diagnostic
on the collection disk.
[mumbling] I just need one more...
Oh, frak.
Yo, Deon. [chuckles nervously]
What's...
- What's good, man?
- You tell me.
Something drew me here.
Was it you?
- I don't think it was...
- Who's this?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Who am I? Who are you?
Who is he?
Look, guys. All's good in the hood,
all right? Look.
Barry, this is Deon.
Still Force.
And Deon, this is Barry,
who's actually the...
owner of this
fine establishment.
So you're the landlord.
What's that got to do with anything?
Deon, it's good to meet you.
[Cisco] Actually, you remember me?
I was with him.
You called us wannabe Urkels.
- Oh, yeah. Cornballs.
- [nervous laughter]
- Yeah.
Corn... so funny.
Who's the egghead?
Harrison Wells.
I'm a fellow...
visitor to Barry's place.
You know, y'all are being
real friendly right now.
But I think
y'all are acting like that
because you're afraid of me.
Now why is that?
No. We're just making a...
We're just doing an experiment...
Shut up!
Now,
why do I get the feeling...
that you're the reason I'm this way?
Because that's true.
And I'm sorry.
I never meant for this to happen.
So please let me fix it.
Fix it? Fix it?
So I'm a mistake?
- I didn't say that.
- You didn't have to.
I can feel it.
You wanna destroy me.
No. I want to save you.
Deon... Deon.
There are three other Forces.
People like you.
One of them, she wants to kill you.
Now, she's already killed
one of the other Forces.
The Strength Force.
And she didn't care
when the person
containing that Force died, too.
So, I need to make it
so the Still Force never found you.
It's the only way to keep you safe.
[softly] Nah.
I like being me.
I get it.
Oh, I get it.
Deon?
No, I get it. I get it.
This is what you're gonna use
to do it, huh?
This is what you're going to use
to make it like I never existed?
Not you. Just the Force inside...
Man, I am that Force!
Do you have any idea what it's like
to be told
that you shouldn't be here?
Well, I never asked to be born.
Deon, listen to me.
Look at what you're doing.
Okay? You don't understand
what you are.
Yeah, I do.
I'm a god.
Maybe it's time you understood that.
Deon, wait...
Time to bounce.
[Timeless Wells] Right?
What the hell just happened?
[Timeless Wells] I think your friend
Deon just stopped time.
Yeah, he does that.
Hey, why'd he leave?
Because I couldn't stop him.
[Barry] Deon just aged the harness
1,000 years.
How bad is it?
[Timeless Wells] Pretty bad.
But not hopeless. See,
I figured if we can find some way
to somehow create some sort of...
I was working on the collection disk
when Deon showed up.
I figured I'd better hide it
just in case.
[chuckles] Chester, you're a life saver.
As for the vest,
I'm used to working with junk.
I'll just need a bunch of
replacement parts from my garage
and she'll be up-and-running
in no time.
With a little help, that is.
I'm with you.
What's up?
I think Deon's right.
We can't just uncreate
these Forces like that.
So, what, we should just give up?
On this? Yeah, we give up.
Doesn't that feel like
the right thing to do?
Cisco, Nora will kill him
if I don't do something
to prevent it.
Just like she killed Alexa.
'Cause she's not gonna stop
until all the Forces
and the people
connected to them are dead.
Why can't you see
I'm trying to save him?
He doesn't want to be saved by you!
He just wants to be given
the chance to be himself.
[sighs]
And Iris understood that.
Look, every second
that we leave these Forces
inside Deon and Psych,
people are in danger.
It's only a matter of time
before someone dies
in one of Psych's nightmares
or gets killed by some kind of
Deon time anomaly.
Not to mention Nora declared war.
She doesn't care
how many people she kills,
as long as the Forces die.
You're right.
Yes, you're absolutely right.
And something needs to be
done about that.
And I don't have all the answers.
All I know is...
this can't be it.
You guys understand, right?
I have to uncreate these Forces.
Like I said,
I am Team Flash all the way.
But Cisco has a point, man.
Harrison?
If uncreating these Forces is what
you feel in your heart is right,
I'll take that voyage with you.
But all I ask is that you think,
truly think...
about the choice you're making.
Please fix the harness.
Good luck.
- [device chimes]
- [Kamilla] Iris, you were right.
These isotopic readings
are off the chart.
[Allegra] Where are we?
[Iris West] The old Allen house.
This is where Barry's mom was killed.
He also said this is where
the Speed Force went when she died.
Whoa. That old car is hella vintage.
Almost looks brand-new.
Must be a collector or something.
You can ask him when we're done,
assuming we survive.
[Joe] Caitlin called me about Alexa.
So, it turns out
when Iris and I brought back
the Speed Force,
we also created three new Forces.
It's our fault that
they're out in the world,
hurting people, killing them.
So I feel like I have to be
the one to take them out.
These Forces,
you think they're above saving, too?
I think it would be
safer for everybody
if they didn't exist.
You remember
when Wally first showed up?
Man, it wasn't just that
I found out I have a son.
I found out I have a son
who kept getting his butt in trouble.
But he was mad at the world.
There was one point
he said to me that he wished
he had never been born.
So I tried
to get close, and he pushed me away.
And I tried to give him space.
Then he felt abandoned.
No parent is perfect.
But one thing
I never stopped doing...
was trying.
And look at the man he grew up to be.
Strong,
kind, good.
Yeah, I get it. I do. But...
I mean, these Forces,
they're not my children.
You sure?
You said it yourself.
You brought them into this world.
Look, I know they've all
done terrible things.
But what if they could change?
You never judge your kids
for who they are now.
You help them become
who they know they can be
when they grow up.
So lead with love.
After that, it is up to them.
[door creaking]
[electricity crackling]
[Iris West] This is Barry's old room.
[door creaking]
Nora?
[tense music playing]
Psych.
[Psych] Hi, Mom.
Esperanza, don't kill me!
They're everywhere.
We need to keep them out.
Psych, stop.
You're hurting them, please.
Oh, they're hurting themselves.
Sure, I pull back the curtain,
but what they see is up to them.
Now before I show you
your worst fear,
why were you looking for me?
I wasn't.
No.
You were looking for the Speed Force.
Nora.
Why? Why are you so desperate
to find her?
Is it to hurt her?
I want to talk to her
so I can help her.
Are you sure?
Because I'm feeling the pain
that she has inflicted upon you.
[inhales sharply]
How deeply she's torn apart
your relationships your whole life.
Actually, the suffering she's caused
is quite beautiful.
That wasn't Nora. She's lost control,
just like you have.
But if you let me,
I can help you both.
[laughs] I don't need your help.
Besides, I can feel
what you fear most.
It's the person you seek.
Well, your wish is my command.
[screams]
[gasps]
Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
[distorted voice]
You'll never measure up.
[Chester] Okay, it's working.
Now, when you're close enough
to siphon particles,
the disk'll light up.
Guys, I appreciate you helping me.
Make sure the proton collection
housing's double fused.
[Timeless Wells] We did.
And it's good to see you.
What changed your mind?
Look, this is dangerous.
And it doesn't feel right...
but I'm always going
to have your back,
no matter what.
Ches, let's get it going.
Okay. So, Barry.
All you need to do
is get close enough
to the Speed Force lightning
to collect a sample of each Force.
The PHC
and timeless Wells' time-bubble
- should do the rest, theoretically.
- Yeah.
Ready?
[clears throat]
Nothing's happening.
- You gotta...
- Wait for it.
Wait for it.
[Chester] Ain't no "A" in this SF.
Incredible.
We're at 100% organic speed.
We need you.
I need you.
[electrical crackling]
I remember this moment.
This is where it all started.
We should get to the roof.
[distorted voice]
You think you can be a good wife,
a good mother...
but you never will.
Everything you do
pales in comparison to me.
Besides, how could you be
a good mother?
You never even had one.
I'm not listening to you.
You don't have to.
You already know it's the truth.
No, you're not real.
There's no escaping your own fear.
I know you're still here, Psych.
[Psych] Very good. Hm.
It is not every day
that someone can sense my presence
in their nightmare.
I'm not just someone.
We have a connection.
I know you can feel that, too.
Perhaps. It's not going
to help you though.
Escape one nightmare
and I'll just serve up another,
because there's always
more terror to unlock.
Come on.
[Iris West]
But before you had those powers,
before you became a Force,
you were a person.
I'm talking to that person right now.
I have friends.
I have a team that can help you
fight this monster
that's inside of you.
We can help you
regain control of your body.
[Psych] What makes you think
I'm not in control?
I know you didn't choose
to have these powers,
and you shouldn't have
to go through this alone.
I know that
we're not flesh and blood,
but in a way,
I'm...
I'm like a parent.
So please, let me help you.
[grunts]
[Psych] Then there's something
I should tell you, Mother.
I hated my parents.
[screams]
[grunting]
Isotopic energy readings
are going down.
The Forces are dying.
- [Psych laughing]
- [Iris West screaming]
[screaming]
[Deon] Those fools are gonna learn.
You mess with Deon,
you get dealt with.
[screaming]
[Chester] Another 20 seconds
and they'll be gone forever.
Barry did it.
Look at it.
Wait, wait.
What is that?
[thunder rumbling]
I think that is an act of creation.
[Barry] I have the particles.
Shouldn't the Forces be dying?
Perhaps they are, somewhere.
In time. But right here, right now,
they're being born.
[Psych] What are you doing to me?
I wasn't able to get through to him,
and now it's too late.
Boss, we can't stay here.
[Psych groaning]
[gasping]
Allen,
you okay?
[Joe] You neverjudge your kids
for who they are now.
You help them become
who they know they can be.
They're almost gone.
[Chester] Five percent.
Four...
three...
two...
[Cisco] What's happening?
Everything just stopped.
[Chester] Look,
the numbers are going back up.
It's as if the Forces are still here.
Iris was right.
Hey, you all were.
I couldn't do it.
Iris...
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
Barry, I um...
I went looking for Nora.
I thought that
if I could just talk to her
that I could fix everything.
But I ended up finding Psych instead.
You were right.
I couldn't get through to him,
and it probably would have been
the same with Nora.
I should have listened to you.
No, I'm the one
who should have listened.
Harrison told me about
the birth of the Forces.
Sounds incredible.
It was.
I can't believe
how close I came to erasing them.
And what changed your mind?
You.
Joe.
Everyone.
Even the Forces themselves.
I could feel
how they would affect the future.
All the speedsters' and heroes'
lives they'd shape.
Some of them were family, Iris.
Our family.
Barry, we both know how dangerous
these Forces can be.
I mean, if you couldn't uncreate them
and I couldn't get through to Psych,
what are we supposed to do?
Try again. Together this time.
Joe helped me realize
that we can't judge Psych and Deon
for who they are now.
We have to help them become
who they can grow up to be.
Because that's what parents do.
[rumbling]
- Alexa.
[rapid beeping]
What happened?
There was a tremor,
and Alexa sat up and looked at me.
Alexa's alive?
She was for a second,
but she's not anymore.
Which doesn't make any sense,
medically speaking.
What if us being back in sync
is what woke her up for the moment?
Yeah, then she reconnected
with the Strength Force.
Is it crazy to think
that we did this?
No.
Because we're all connected.
And if we woke her up once...
Then we could
bring her back permanently.
[gasps]
Why is everyone looking at me?
Listen, I'd ask you to stay,
but I already know the answer.
Man's gotta be where his heart lies.
He's just got to learn
to listen to it.
One more thing before I go.
Whether it's me or...
any of the many Wells predecessors,
I want you to know that you taught us
every inch as much as we taught you.
Maybe more.
Yeah, I'm never going to
get used to that.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
For the first time in a long while,
yeah, I feel okay.
Good, because I've been
thinking about something,
and after tonight,
I know I have to do it.
Okay, that's just weird.
I was literally about to say
the exact same thing to you.
- I have to leave Central City.
- Thank God.
- Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God.
Babe...
What are you gonna tell Team Citizen?
What are you gonna tell Team Flash?
[hip-hop song playing on headphones]
Let a dog roam
And he'll find his way home
Home of the brave
My home is a cage
Hey, yo, I'm a slave
'Til my home is a grave
Stop, drop
Shut 'em down, open up shop...
[sniffles] You're the one
who's after me?
You don't look so tough.
What are you?
A reckoning.