Previously on "The Flash"...
You're no longer you.
You're a part of a negative force.
Thawne's Speed Force is
fueled by negative emotions.
- What do you do?
- Trust me,
you wouldn't believe me if I told you.
You're not super satisfied
with your secret identity.
Are you saying I don't want to be Vibe?
There won't be any future for any metas
if we don't get rid of that dagger.
If anything's gonna destroy that dagger,
it's this Mirror Gun.
It works.
Follow my instructions
and we'll defeat Cicada,
destroy her dagger,
and save your father.
Thawne is manipulating her.
He's on death row, how
is he manipulating her?
Something doesn't add up.
The dagger is Thawne's plan.
Don't shoot it!
I always wanted to be a hero,
to use my extraordinary
abilities to help people.
That's why I came here.
To meet my family, to stop Cicada,
help fix the Flash's legacy,
and save him from
disappearing in the future.
I believed I could do the impossible,
but I never imagined it
would turn out like this.
No, no! What's he doing?
Cicada... Thawne, dagger.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
How's Ralph?
I've never seen anything like it.
I can't quite figure it out.
His cells are kinetically inverted.
It's like they're the
reverse of themselves.
Should've spent more
time trying to figure out
how this thing works.
I just don't understand
why he would jump
in front of that blast.
I mean, why would he do that?
That's the question, isn't it?
That's the question.
In other news, Cicada
deuce is still MIA.
All right, we should get to CCPD,
see if we can find anything
that could help us track her.
What?
I'm supposed to meet
up with Kamilla later.
I thought things were going
really well for you two.
They are.
I just haven't told her about
my vibratory alter ego yet.
Cisco, if you're serious
about being with her,
you have to tell her the truth.
I know.
All the metas that we couldn't cure,
we got safely evacuated
and they're waiting
at a protected holding facility.
Nice work, both of you.
Well the work's not done yet.
I mean, the metas are safe for now,
but Cicada's still out there,
so the people are still in danger.
Fill me in on the details.
I'm ready for this nightmare to end.
It should've been over already.
Nora, look,
I'm sure Ralph had a good reason.
Until we figure out what
it is, we just gotta
concentrate on this, all right?
Wait a second.
What is that?
Looks like wood.
From what?
I mean the floor is marble,
furniture's untouched,
and the skylight's made
of glass and metal.
Well if it didn't come
from Cicada's point of entry...
She must've brought it
from somewhere else.
What do we do now?
You know what to do.
Hit them when they least expect it.
When they least expect it.
The Time Sphere.
If I repair it,
I can bring the last of the virus back
to the night of the
Particle Accelerator.
When meta-humans first
appeared in Central City...
And the Flash becomes a hero to stop me.
Destroy the meta-humans
before they destroy the world.
They'll be born only to die.
Definitely some kind of wood fragment.
And you think those will lead
us to where Cicada's hiding?
We can find out.
We can cross-reference this,
see what kind of wood it is,
then see where we end up.
Is there any progress on Ralph?
No, he's still unconscious,
and I can't figure out
a way to reverse his cells.
So I guess that means
we still don't know why
he jumped in front of
that Mirror Gun, do we?
We do.
We do...
because Dibny solved the
greatest mystery of all.
The Flash legacy, how to stop Cicada,
repentance for his past sins...
all the reasons Eobard
Thawne was helping you.
And stopping Dad from
disappearing in the future.
Disappearing in the
future is part of it, hmm?
But this has nothing
to do with your father.
The real reason that Thawne
wishes to defeat Cicada
and destroy Cicada's dagger
is because this dagger
is the only thing keeping
the Reverse-Flash in prison.
Guess this is it.
Looks like it, doesn't it?
Mm.
I almost forgot.
I contacted the Flash Museum,
had them send something over for today.
I thought it should
be buried for good...
along with you.
Consider it a parting gift.
Destroying Cicada's dagger in the past
will save Thawne from
dying in the future?
That's right.
Cicada's dagger has been dampening
Thawne's powers all this time.
So if we get rid of the dagger now,
it disappears in the future?
And Thawne gets out of Iron Heights.
A reverse time hack.
Everything you said
about Thawne is true.
The only person he
ever helps is himself.
Nora, this is not your fault.
Yes, it is.
Now the question we have to ask...
do we stop Cicada or do we stop Thawne?
No, we're not gonna let
thousands of meta-humans die,
now or in the future.
We find Cicada.
We destroy the dagger once and for all.
You gotta get out of here.
No, we gotta wait for the results...
We can handle it until you get back.
Go see Kamilla.
How do you choose?
That's more of a question
for Iris than for me.
Hey.
She seems to be happy with my photos.
I was kinda hoping she'd
send me over to CCPD
to take photos of the meta-humans
when they were getting that cure.
Can you imagine being there
when that Cicada guy attacked?
Cicada woman, actually.
A woman?
Her name's Grace Gibbons.
Her uncle was the first Cicada.
She killed him after he
took the meta-human cure.
The cure that I made.
The cure you made?
You're serious.
That's the scientific project
you've been working on?
At S.T.A.R. Labs.
You never told me your
lab was S.T.A.R. Labs.
There's a lot I haven't told you.
What is that supposed to mean?
You're Vibe.
Look, Kamilla,
I've seen firsthand how hard it is
to have two lives like this.
And I tried to separate you from that,
but I don't want to keep
this from you anymore.
I can't keep lying to you like this.
I'm sorry.
Cisco, wait.
I totally get it.
I've read a lot of comic books.
I know all the tropes that go with
revealing secret identities.
But in real life, I
would never expect you
to tell me something
like this right away.
You're amazing, you know that?
Cisco, this isn't about me.
It's about you.
If being Vibe is a part
of the life you want,
I would never get in the way of that.
You know you really are a lot like me.
Trusting.
And you always blame
yourself when things go wrong.
How do I fix this?
I don't know if you can, Nora.
You made a mistake,
you know?
A big mistake.
Sometimes in life, all we can do is just
live with the consequences.
So what you have to ask yourself is
what kind of hero are you gonna be?
One who takes a do-over
after every mistake,
or one who lives with
it and moves forward?
Nothing?
Nope, I still cannot
figure out how to reset
his cells back to normal.
He's till Humpty Dumpty'd, huh?
Yep.
He hasn't been this much of a mess
since he first got his powers.
Since...
And what did you do to help him then?
We introduced a stabilizing
enzyme that reset
his body back to its original
form using vulcanization...
and muscle memory.
Muscle memory.
Well then it appears
all that we need to do
is wake him up.
How would you suggest we do that?
Simple.
We blast him.
We blast him?
If you blast him, the vibrational jolt,
it will be more than enough to
kick-start his consciousness.
I'm sure of it.
Can't we just play some Gaga
and hope he wakes up?
Gaga is not the solution to everything.
You have to blast him.
Allez, young Ralph Macchio, please.
Be careful. This could
get a little ugly.
Okay.
Sorry, deuce.
WrestleMania!
Voilà! Good as new.
Blasted why you happen what?
Hmm?
B-b-blasted why you happen what?
Except for the language skills.
Those will return, probably.
Everybody going, where is?
Everybody going where... every...
What is it?
It's the wood particles you guys found.
"Swish ash".
Part of the flowering ash
trees indigenous to Europe,
but also make up our biggest wood space
not 12 miles from Central City.
Kolins Woods.
That's where Cicada almost killed me.
That's also one of the largest
wooded parks in the country.
- We need a better plan.
- I've got one...
that can stop Cicada and Thawne.
Out to sniff? So really
we're using her Cecile?
Well, she is a highly sensitive empath
and Cicada emanates hate.
DA Cecile Horton will serve
as our early warning detection system.
If we're lucky, Cicada
won't see what's coming.
Then once we find Cicada to entrap her,
we give Young Grace the
choice to take the cure.
And hopefully, when
she's no longer a meta...
That bitch will cease to exist.
That way we can stop
her without destroying
the dagger and Thawne never goes free.
Now all you have to do is help Grace
make the right choice.
What do I say?
Whatever's in your heart. She'll listen.
What a bunch of sentimental crap.
You two sound like a
friggin' Hallmark movie.
I hear ya, sister.
I think we're close.
You good?
Oh, yeah, jeez, sorry.
Uh, this way.
Here we go.
The Sphere is ready.
We can leave.
Guys, we found her. Get ready.
I'm actually glad you
found me before we left.
Now I can end your lives twice today.
Not on my watch.
- We got her.
- Nora, you're up.
If you can connect to Grace as an adult,
you can connect with her as a child.
You just have to tap into her anger.
You can do this.
You shouldn't have come back here, Nora.
I had to, Grace,
because a lot of people are
gonna die unless you help me.
If I can help it, you'll
be the first to die.
Uh, the force field's integrity
just went down to 86%.
Grace, I know you think your
uncle wanted all metas dead,
but he was a meta.
That's why he took the cure
and why he wants you to have it too.
You're a meta, just like your uncle.
No I'm not! Take it back.
70%... 52...
Don't listen to her, Gracie.
This hate. It's consuming you,
turning you into a monster.
And what's worse, you're all alone.
Uncle Orlin wouldn't leave me.
He had no choice.
Take the cure just like your uncle did.
No.
40%.
Nora's gotta convince Grace now.
Metas killed your parents, Gracie.
They all deserve to die.
Don't believe him, Grace.
This is just in your mind.
She's right, Gracie.
It's why you created him.
He's the man who took care of you.
19%.
I know a part of you
knows that this is wrong.
But the other dark part
of you is out there
in the real world
killing innocent people.
You can make a choice to stop it.
How?
Wake up and take the cure.
Shut up.
You can do this, Gracie.
Get ready.
Grace.
- Gracie.
- Grace.
- Grace. - Grace.
Grace!
Okay, I don't want people to die.
I'll take the cure.
Thank you.
Here she comes.
Okay.
Did it work? Guys, what's happening?
Joe, no!
Now I'll finish what I started.
It didn't work.
That shard in her head.
It's still part of the dagger.
Its dark energy is enough
to counteract the cure.
If we want to cure Grace,
we must destroy that dagger.
You took my family away from me, Flash.
Now watch me take yours.
No!
Barry!
Just in time.
Gentlemen.
I hate to inform you, but...
You're all dead.
Thawne...
I... I can help you.
Isn't this ironic?
Time to repent.
Consider this a parting gift.
Just... in...
Well, well.
It appears as if someone has figured out
how to reverse time.
Clever girl.
We figured out everything.
Oh, really?
What have you figured out?
We figured out why you sent Nora back,
why you had her punch
DeVoe's satellite...
to create a Cicada we could stop.
Right?
A dagger
we could destroy.
It was the dagger that was keeping you
in prison all along, wasn't it?
That's right.
15 years.
The second time I've
been stuck somewhere
against my will for 15 years.
Boring.
Except for your visits, of course.
You're leaving out the
most delightful part:
how you both helped me escape.
We helped you?
That's right. When you traveled
to the Time Vault, remember that?
Oh, we need help trying to figure out
how to drain dark energy
from the "one who got away".
Cicada!
Remember that? When you blurted that out
in the middle of the Time
Vault, so that years later,
when I ended up with
Cicada's dagger strapped
to my chest, I knew
exactly what I had to do:
get Nora Allen to trust me.
Easy.
Just like when I got you to trust me,
and then everything
starts falling into place.
Why?
Because I am the only speedster
that knows how to
manipulate the timeline
to get what I want,
orchestrate the changes that I need,
some of which...
are happening right now,
to ensure one thing:
that I go free.
We don't need a dagger to stop you.
Well then,
let's just see how much
your father taught you.
I guess you're not as
good a teacher as I am.
You can't save him, Nora.
No matter what you do,
no matter what you try, the
Flash will always vanish.
That is his legacy.
Isn't this nice?
Team Flash, back together again...
with a new guy.
Ralph Dibny.
Welcome. You should be dead.
Yeah, I guess we have that in common.
We'll take care of that in a moment.
Iris.
Always a pleasure.
Frost.
Cisco.
It warms my heart to see you again.
I want to apologize for...
But had I not done that,
you never would've had the
means to become extraordinary.
I don't need powers for that.
Now!
It's not my father's legacy
that's gonna disappear, Thawne.
It's yours.
- Nora!
- Hey!
So close, Little Runner.
It was never going to work anyway.
Mom? Dad?
- No, no, no, no.
- Mom, what's happening?
- A new timeline is setting in.
- What?
A new timeline that you created
when you destroyed the dagger!
I'm sorry, Little Runner,
for trading you in like this.
But I had to be sure
that I could go free.
You can still save her, Barry.
There's still time.
You can still save her.
How?
The Negative Speed Force.
She has to go there.
It's the only place immune
to timeline changes.
But you have to go now.
You have to go, Barry!
Or we lose her forever.
That's right. I've
grown fond of her too.
In many ways.
She's shown me what it's
like to have a daughter.
See you in our next crisis.
I can't do this.
Yes you can, yes you can.
You have to, all right?
Just hold on a little longer.
No, Dad, I can't.
Nora!
I can't.
- Nora, what are we doing?
- It's too late.
No, it's not. We gotta go back.
- Dad, no.
- Barry, you have
- to take her back.
- I know, I know.
- Mom, Mom.
Nora, you have to go back now.
No!
If I go back in, the
Negative Speed Force
will be a part of me forever.
No, we'll get it out of you, Nora.
We can get it out. We can save you.
- Please, I promise.
- Mom, you can't.
Mom, you can't.
None of you can.
It's making me like Thawne.
Full of anger and hate.
I... I don't want that to be my legacy.
- This is all on me.
- No.
All of it.
My mistake.
And I'm not gonna make another one.
Sometimes all you can do is
live with the consequences.
Oh my God.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
We love you.
Thank you for everything.
We're so sorry.
We have to believe that
we'll see her again.
We will.
Nora...
made sure that we didn't
lose everything tonight.
She saved every meta in the city.
And she gave Grace a new future.
Gave all of us, right?
Especially me.
Without Nora, I never would've met
the love of my life, Renee.
And you wouldn't have
stopped your 38th Cicada.
Or your 39th.
Right.
It's been quite a journey.
Plaisir.
An honor, Flash.
We never could've solved
this mystery without you.
Well, don't be too sure.
You already have a master
detective in your midst.
Congratulations, Adult Giraffe.
Well done, Sherloque.
Sherlock.
Well, all right then.
Without further ado.
Mes amis.
Good luck, Team Flash.
It's Singh.
Yeah, he, uh... he wants
us to meet him in CCPD
and bring Barry.
Yeah, go.
I kinda want to be alone anyway.
Is everything okay?
What Thawne said...
I don't want that.
I don't want the extraordinary thing
about my life to be my powers.
No one feels that way.
Here's the thing.
I do.
All these years I thought that Vibe
was the person I was supposed to be.
I think it's time Cisco
finally got his turn.
So what does that mean?
It means I want to take the cure.
- If you do this...
- There's no going back.
I know.
Killer Frost and I are
really gonna miss Vibe.
Me too.
How do you feel?
Scared.
But I'm hopeful.
Before I forget,
I left you something in the workshop.
Just, you know, my way
of saying thank you.
For what?
Being a great friend.
Well, Grace Gibbons
is currently scheduled
to meet with our county counselor.
And as soon as possible,
we'll get her in with
a good foster family.
Look, I won't keep you long,
but I just want to thank you
for being at the forefront with Cicada.
Just doing our job, sir.
Well, you went way beyond
just doing your job.
And I know you did it
because of how much
you care for the people of this city,
which is how I know I can
leave it in your capable hands.
What do you mean, leave it?
The mayor's offered me the job
as the new chief of police.
What?
- Dave.
- David.
- Congratulations.
- That's great.
Thank you, thanks.
Of course that leaves me
responsible for finding
my own replacement.
And, uh...
I would like that to be you, Joe.
Re... replace you?
As... as captain?
Captain Joe West.
Oh, I like the sound of that.
And don't worry.
If things get dicey, as
they tend to around here,
you'll have plenty of help.
Isn't that right, Flash?
Oh come on, Barry.
I'm a detective too.
Sir.
Congratulations.
I'll do my best.
Hey.
Now I know what my
dad meant when he said
being a parent is like
wearing your heart
on the outside of your body.
Yeah.
Thawne got away.
Again.
Nora's gone.
Should feel like a loss but,
I also feel...
- Pride?
- Pride, yeah.
She did good.
Yeah.
She was the best of both of us.
She was my legacy all along.
And us, together, as a family,
that's how I want to be remembered.
As a good man,
a loving husband...
A supportive father.
You're already all of those things.
Nora felt that way too.
- Time language.
- Mm-hmm.
No matter what changes
with the timeline,
that'll never change.
We'll always have this to remember her.
Hi, Mom and Dad.
If you're watching this,
it means that something went wrong.
But I don't want you guys to be sad.
I'm not.
I always wanted to be a hero,
to use my extraordinary
abilities to help people.
That's why I came here:
to meet my family, stop Cicada,
help fix the Flash's legacy,
and save him from
disappearing in the future.
I believed I could do the impossible,
but I never imagined it
would turn out like this.
I'm glad it did.
I wouldn't change anything
about my time with you,
my sweet parents,
the most important people
to me in the world.
I wish I could be there to
celebrate every new chapter,
to witness every success.
Just know...
that no matter where I go in my life,
you'll always be my side.
Because of you,
I know I will never,
ever, truly be alone,
and I will feel your love
and support like a warm hug
comforting me,
wishing me to be the
best person I can be.
Thank you for everything...
For making me a hero
and for loving me even
if I wasn't perfect.
Please remember that I love you both
and I always will,
no matter what the future brings.
Incoming time flux.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --