- Previously on "The Flash"...
- My time on this earth
is coming to an end.
You're part of something
different now.
Part of a negative force.
Pain racing through your mind.
- Thawne really got her.
Her lightning. It was red.
- Renée Adler.
- Sherloque Wells.
You're a meta.
- You're from the future.
- The mission can succeed.
- What mission?
- To kill every last
meta-human.
[clang]
- Cicada's dagger
can dampen powers.
- If anything's gonna destroy
that dagger,
it's this mirror gun.
- Cicada has a lethal virus.
- She stole the atomizer
so she could spread the virus.
- Cicada is gonna kill every
meta-human in the city.
[beeping]
[alarm pinging]
[door slides open]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- 15 years, Thawne.
Tell me, how's it feel to know
you're about to become extinct?
- I guess time will tell.
- [chuckles] I'm gonna miss
the hell out of you.
Especially our
rehabilitation time.
How about a taste
of what's to come?
♪ ♪
- [yelling]
- Ironic, isn't it?
The same thing that gives you
your powers
is gonna end you.
- It's time.
♪ ♪
- [evil chuckling]
- [panting]
♪ ♪
[soft dramatic music]
- We need to stop this plague
from spreading.
- We will.
- We can't just purge
the meta-humans in this city.
We need to wipe
every one of them
off the face of the planet.
- We will.
- You need to promise me
this will work, Gracie.
- I said it will.
♪ ♪
- It's time we finish this,
Gracie.
It's time to ensure our legacy.
[pulsating]
- Here's what we know
about the cryoatomizer.
Tannhauser originally
developed it
to combat land fires
caused by droughts.
So the cryoatomizer can
disperse cold air particles
into the atmosphere
that triggers rainfall.
However, if Cicada can replace
the cold particles
with the cure prototypes
she stole from Cisco...
- Which doesn't cure
so much as it kills.
- She could infect
the entire city.
- And every meta-human in it.
♪ ♪
- Not great but this dark cloud
does have a silver lining.
Which is if Cicada
had everything
that she needs to carry
out her plan...
would've already done so.
- He's right.
She must be missing something
or else we'd be done.
- Yeah, but not for long.
She's not gonna waste any time.
Whatever it is that she needs,
she's out there
looking for it right now.
- Well, then we move
right away.
We get the cure to everyone who
needs it as soon as possible.
- So we just up and release
some game-changing wonder drug?
- We tested it.
We know it works.
People need a choice
now more than ever.
Do we have enough of the cure?
- Not nearly enough.
- Caitlin, how fast can
you make more?
- Guess we'll find out.
- Okay, okay, good.
Now we just need to find
someplace to distribute it.
- Well, what about CCPD?
It's public. Everybody
feels safe going there.
- Yeah but gathering
that many metas in one place
is gonna make it
one big target, right?
- Cicada has the virus
and the atomizer.
That makes every meta
everywhere a target.
- Well, how about this?
You guys make up as much
of the cure as you can
and Cecile and I
will talk to Singh.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- I'm going to warn Renée.
- Yeah.
All right,
let's track Cicada too.
Get ready to face her
when we find her.
- Let's take it one step
at a time.
Follow me.
♪ ♪
- Is that the satellite core?
- That's right.
The reflective panels
on the mirror gun
aren't the only thing
we got from the satellite.
We also have the core and,
of course, the dagger.
- So they're all composed
of the exact same alloy
and contain
the same dark matter levels?
- Yup.
- So if the Mirror Gun
works on the core,
then it should work on
Cicada's dagger.
- [sighs] Only one way
to know for sure.
♪ ♪
You might wanna step back.
I mean, you don't know
what this gun's gonna do.
I mean, we shouldn't be firing
this in such a small space
but what's life if you don't
pull down your shorts
and slide on the ice every
once in awhile?
Here we go!
- Hm.
[firing up, pulsating]
- Um...
- Is something supposed
to happen or...
- [chuckles]
- Where did it go?
- It doesn't matter.
This thing works.
- It works!
We can finally destroy
Cicada's dagger.
If we do that,
we have our powers.
- And we can stop her.
- N...Nora, are you okay?
- Yeah, why?
- Nora, earlier today you had
red lightning like Thawne's.
We want to make sure
you're okay to get out there.
- I'm fine, okay?
Caitlin ran every test
in the book.
My lightning's back
to its normal color.
And besides,
Thawne's Speed Force
is fueled
by negative emotions,
and right now I feel
pretty dang positive.
- Okay. We're your parents.
It's our job to worry.
- The only one that should be
worrying is Cicada II.
- You want me to open
the doors to the CCPD
to every meta in this city?
- David, these people need
our protection.
- And not all metas
are criminals.
You know, some of them are
doctors and students and cops.
- I know but this is
a police station, not a clinic.
- S.T.A.R. Labs says that
the cure is safe
and it's as easy to give
as a flu shot.
- Well, S.T.A.R. Labs
isn't exactly the FDA.
- Look, we have to do it here.
Red tape alone, it would take
weeks at a medical facility.
If we do nothing, there's
a whole bunch of citizens
who could've been saved
that will die on our watch.
I'm not having that.
- [sighs]
Well, you clearly believe
in this.
So I'm willing to as well.
But that means
there's going to be
a lot of
political navigating.
So I'll go down to city hall
and brief them in the morning.
While I'm away,
you're in charge.
♪ ♪
[message chime]
- [chuckles]
Oh!
Sherloque,
you scared me to death.
- Well, I apologize.
But when you don't answer
my many emoticon pictograms,
no, I fear the worst, huh?
- I was in the library.
What could've happened to me?
- Stacks collapse.
Livid librarian.
- Really?
- Death by Dewey Decimals?
- Yeah, life lost by late fees?
- Ha-ha! There you go.
- Yeah. Oh.
- Shall we?
- I'm sorry I didn't...
I didn't check my texts.
I mean, well, actually
I haven't checked
my phone all day, so...
- And yet the average person
checks their phone
110 times a day.
- That's not true.
- That is true. Look it up.
- Well, also the library's
right next to the tech lab.
So, you know, I get
terrible reception in there.
- And yet that built
a cell phone tower
less than a mile away.
- Hasn't made a difference.
I don't know,
Maybe my phone's just crap.
- Or maybe you don't want
to respond
because then you would have
to discuss your secret.
- My secret?
- Yes, your secret.
[alarm ringing]
[zapping]
Run. Run!
- What?
[alarm blares]
- It's Sherloque.
Cicada's at CCU.
[people screaming]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- So at Jitters, I saw you open
the door without touching it.
I know you have powers.
what are they?
[pulsating]
[clattering]
- That.
♪ ♪
[pulsating]
- [breathes heavily]
I see you too.
[clang]
[explosion]
- [groans]
[sighs]
Are you okay?
- I think so.
- Nora.
[static cracking]
- Hey, you find anything?
- Confirmation that She-cada
hasn't stolen everything
she needs.
So we have some time.
- [sighs]
Finally some good news.
- Except what she did steal
was a Quantum Tunnel Converter.
The first working prototype
of its kind.
- Yeah, that's the same face
Cisco made when he heard.
- The converter can transform
dark matter energy
to practical energy.
- Cicada's gonna use her dagger
to superpower the atomizer.
- If she wants to connect it
to the atomizer,
the last piece she'll need
is a hyper-conduit,
and those are pretty hard
to come by, to say the least.
She'll be lucky to locate one
in the CC area at all.
- Well, we better
find it first.
- We'll get to it.
- [speaking French]
- Thank you.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
small sips, huh?
- The second she saw me,
she wanted me dead.
She tried to kill me,
Sherloque.
- Because of what you are.
A magnokinetic meta-human!
[chuckles] That was something,
your powers, huh?
- I wanted to tell you, but...
I didn't know what you'd think.
- I...I think...
The world of you.
[soft music]
Nothing is ever going
to change that.
♪ ♪
- Do you think Cicada's
gonna come back again
to try to find me?
To try again?
- Yes.
I don't think she'll stop.
- What am I gonna do?
- Well, you know what?
♪ ♪
I believe I can help you
with that.
- Hey.
- Guys okay?
- Yeah, uh, I need
to tell you something.
When we were running over here,
I connected to Grace's
mind again.
I could see through her eyes.
- Wait, like
the same thing you did
when Cicada attacked
Alice Bolan's birthday party?
- Yeah, we must still be
psychically connected
from when I was
in Grace's mindscape.
- That's what caused
the red lightning.
The anger that you felt,
it wasn't yours.
- It was hers.
We can use this.
If I can see where she is
just for a second,
we can run to her.
Guy, this is the key
to stopping Cicada II.
- No.
No, Nora, it's too dangerous.
We don't even know
what the side effects are.
- No.
- We just got the stuff
out of you.
We're not risking
exposing you to that again.
- Mom, I want to do this.
- We'll find another way.
We'll find
another way.
- [both sigh]
♪ ♪
- The dizziness
should subside shortly.
Make sure he gets lots of rest.
- Hey, we know
you're feeling anxious.
But I promise you're safe now.
Head out that way.
I'm gonna go see
if there's anyone else.
- Should we reopen
the Cicada tip line?
And Dupree's asking where you
want the security checkpoints.
- Uh, yeah.
Uh, yes. Open it and, uh,
checkpoints should be
two blocks on either side
of the CCPD.
Okay?
Uh, actually,
three...three blocks.
- Hey, you. You good?
- Yeah, yeah. I'm good.
Look.
They are airing
Iris' story again.
- New updates
on the meta-human
serial killer Cicada,
who recently attacked
Central City University.
Now in response
to these attacks,
The Central City Citizen
reports that CCPD,
in conjunction
with S.T.A.R. Labs,
is offering a groundbreaking
meta-human cure,
entirely free of cost.
[pulsating]
- Maybe I should call
the night shift in earlier.
- Oh, my God.
- Or not.
- Joe, I just felt
a huge wave of panic.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
We're about to get
slammed in here.
[elevator bell dings]
♪ ♪
- Everyone, please be patient.
We'll get to you.
- Far enough.
[crowd clamors]
- Okay.
- Stagg, Mercury, Ivo.
- None of them have
a hyper-conduit
compatible with
the converter Cicada stole.
- You know, now that
I've actually experienced
this whole time travel thing,
I think I understand it
a little bit better.
Which makes me understand
Thawne's plan less and less.
Why would he send Nora back
to create a new Cicada
only for a newer Cicada
to appear who's harder to stop
than the one Nora created?
- Ralph, can we get away
from Thawne's plan
and try to stick to our own?
- Yeah, yeah, I...I just...
I feel like there might be
an answer
in this timey-wimey crap
that could help us solve this.
Nora, where would you find
this hyper-conduit in 2049?
- Probably Ollins Laboratory.
Ollins won a Nobel Prize
for quantum engineering.
- Ollins?
As in Sebastian Ollins?
- Yeah, do you know him?
He's a true genius.
- [chuckles]
A genius, you say.
The guy couldn't even
stay awake
through a single
physics lecture.
In fact, I'm pretty sure if
it wasn't for his very smart,
very considerate college
roommate
lending him notes,
helping him study,
he wouldn't have made
it through his finals!
Nobel Prize my ass!
- Yeah, he knows him.
- You know what?
It doesn't even matter.
Life's too short and I'm not
about to spend my life
worrying about
little Sebastian Ollins.
Found him.
Looks like he's been renting
a warehouse
somewhere on the Southside
and then he retrofitted it
with fiber-joules technology
to test out his experiments.
Including one bleeding-edge
hyper-conduit.
- I'll go get it
before Grace can.
- Right behind you.
- I, um...
I...I think you should sit
this one out.
- What? Why?
- Nora, your connection
with Grace.
It puts you in too much danger.
I mean, we don't...
I think it's best for you
to just stay out of the field
until we stop her.
- So what? Now I can't help
the team at all?
- Nora, please understand.
Look, you would be
much safer here.
[zap]
All right, I'm here.
No sign of Cicada.
- Great. Grab the conduit
and get out of there.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I think I got something.
[beeping]
[gasps]
- Barry!
- She's already got
the conduit.
And she blew up Ollins'
warehouse.
[pants]
Grace has everything she needs.
- It's just like we thought.
- Great.
- What?
- [sighs]
With all the pieces
that she's stolen,
Grace can now use the dagger's
dark matter energy
to supercharge the atomizer.
Apparently it wasn't enough
for her
to just kill all the metas
in Central City.
- With this super-charge,
she'll kill every meta
in the country.
- All right, look,
I know you guys want me off
this whole Thawne thing,
but you've got to hear this.
- Ralph.
- No, you've got
to look at this.
You've got to hear this.
So just...just give me a second,
all right?
- All right.
- Please.
All right, so, this is
the original timeline
with the original Cicada,
David Hersch.
This is the night of
the Enlightenment,
when Nora interfered
with the satellite,
giving us our Cicada,
Orlin Dwyer.
That's also the same night
that Grace goes into a coma.
This is where it
gets complicated.
At some point in the future,
Grace wakes up, she becomes
her own full-fledged Cicada.
She goes back in time,
she kills her Uncle
with his own dagger.
What happens to all the metas
that Dwyer killed?
Do they get un-killed?
What about all the metas that
Grace killed in the future?
What did she kill them with?
And most importantly,
what happens in the timeline
where Grace never killed Dwyer.
[soft dramatic music]
Something doesn't add up.
- You might be right.
But right now, there won't
be any future for any metas
if we don't get rid
of that dagger.
Now. This is our last chance.
We have to figure out
how to find Grace.
Or we lose everyone.
- We'll go see what
the satellites can do.
Maybe we're due for a miracle.
♪ ♪
Hey, come on.
- [sighs] Hey.
Do you think we made
the right decision
leaving Nora out of this?
I mean, the whole reason
she came back
was to fight Cicada
in the first place.
- We're her parents,
all right?
- It's our job to protect her
from harm.
The best way to do that is just
to keep her far away from it.
♪ ♪
[vibrating]
- [sighs]
You worked for Caitlin
and Killer Frost's connection.
Let's see what you can do
for me and Grace.
♪ ♪
- What's taking so long?
- Look, how much more cure
do you have left?
- Listen, we have plenty.
Please, uh, we will administer
the cure
as fast as we can, people.
Okay?
- Detective West,
we need additional squads
to aid the crowd control.
- Uh, yeah, take...take two.
No...no, no. Take three.
Two, two, two.
- Joe, we need more
alcohol swabs.
- [sighs]
- Babe, you okay?
[elevator bell dings]
- Hey, oh! Hey, oh!
- Sherloque?
- So, Dr. Caitlin Snow.
This is Cecile Horton
and Detective Joe West.
This is my...
this is Mademoiselle
Renée Adler.
- Hi. Adler.
- Adler. And Renée,
these are the people
that can help you.
- So you can actually
just remove my powers?
- We can if you want us to.
- And...and this would
be permanent?
- Oh, it's permanent, yes.
But better than Cicada
permanently killing you.
Am I right?
Tell her detective.
That's right? Right?
- Yes.
- Uh, you're feeling nervous,
I can tell.
But Cicada really
is trying to kill
every meta-human in this city.
- Hey, what's your problem?
Back off!
I'm standing here.
Is something wrong
with your eyes?
- They're fine.
- [deep, eerie voice]
Then get out of my way.
- All right, all right.
Break it up.
We need to keep this line
moving.
- Want us to detain them,
Detective?
- Just give me the cure
and I'll get out of here.
- No way! I was here first!
You know that!
- Sir, what should we do?
- Detective, we've got
one squad left.
- Give me the cure
and I'll get out of here.
[all clamoring]
- Ah-aah! Enough!
[clamoring fades]
I need a minute to think.
[elevator dings]
- [sighs] I'm so...
Renée?
There she is. Hey, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey! Hey, oh!
- That was Cecile.
CCPD is flooded with
a lot of really scared people.
Are there any signs of Grace's
dark matter signature?
- No. Nothing. Not even a...
[alarm blaring]
- Is that her?
[pulsating]
Nora!
- Barry, she can't hear you.
- I don't think
she can see us either.
Nora! Nora!
[lightning zaps]
♪ ♪
Nora!
- What were you thinking?
- Nora, you almost gave
yourself an aneurysm.
- I was trying to find Grace.
- Opening yourself up to Grace
and her rage
also opens you up to
the Negative Speed Force.
We don't know anything
about it.
Don't you get
how dangerous that is?
- Yeah, I do.
And I still wanna try.
I have to try.
- Nora, you trying almost
destroyed Cisco's workshop
and almost got yourself killed.
- Not to mention, what if
Cicada saw through your eyes?
You could've given away
our location.
- No, I made sure there was
nothing in my eye line
that said S.T.A.R. Labs.
Guys, listen.
I saw Grace and I almost saw
where she was.
Right now she is putting
her pieces together
and when that is done,
thousands if not hundreds
of thousands of people
are going to die.
I can't stand around
and do nothing.
- Yes, you can because that's
what we're telling you to do.
- [sighs]
[soft dramatic music]
When I first got here,
I would rush in to fix things
and by doing that, I always
ended up making them worse.
But I am not
that person anymore
because of you.
You showed me
how to use my powers.
You taught me how to make
the right choices.
And right now, I am choosing
to face this risk.
- Nora, this is
a terrible idea.
- I know you feel that way.
But I don't.
I'm an adult capable
of making my own decisions.
I've made up my mind
about this.
So I am asking you, please,
as my parents,
stop trying to keep me away
from this danger
and start helping me face it.
♪ ♪
- No, no, no, no, no.
Don't worry. I can handle it.
All right.
- Hey.
- Uh, hey.
- What are you doing?
Those people are overwhelmed.
They don't know what to do.
They need you and you just...
you walked away?
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
It's just...
- Okay, did I just catch you
on the phone with Singh
trying to find out how fast
he was gonna be back?
- Cecil, I...I...I'm not used to
being in charge
of all this managerial
and logistic stuff.
I'm just not cut out for that.
- What are you talking about?
Babe, I have seen you
take charge
in the field a million times.
- But that's in the field and
I always knew that I had Singh
to go to if I had
any problems this way.
Now everybody's coming to me
and I can't answer
all these questions.
- Joe West.
How many times has Barry,
Iris, Nora,
even Ralph Dibny come to you?
Specifically come to you to get
answers to their problems?
- [sighs] More times
than I can count.
- Exactly.
And that is because everyone
of them knows
that when they come to you,
they're gonna get
an honest answer
straight from the heart.
Babe, that heart of yours,
that is a moral compass.
It's one of the many reasons
why I love you.
♪ ♪
Right here.
That's all you need, babe.
As long as you speak
from there,
I promise you, you will never
lead anyone astray.
♪ ♪
- Hey, oh!
[panting]
- Sherloque.
- Yes.
- Sherloque,
I'm sorry I ran.
I was...[sighs].
Just feeling so overwhelmed.
- All I wanted to do...
make you feel safe.
And then I put you
in a position where you
feel overwhelmed and not safe.
But look, we'll go to
S.T.A.R. Labs, quiet and safe.
We'll administer the cure.
It will be great.
- Look, Sherloque,
that's...[sighs].
That's not why I ran away.
- It's not?
- No.
- I don't wanna take the cure.
- You don't?
- No.
I love having my powers.
- You do?
- Y...yes and yes,
is it scary knowing that
there's a killer out there
that's targeting people
like me, but...
I don't want
to change who I am.
I don't want to give into fear
just because
there's danger involved.
You know?
I want to live my life
on my terms.
As a meta-human.
[soft music]
- No, but you're brave.
I just worry that Cicada
won't stop
until she kills every
meta-human on this...
- [sighs]
- On this earth.
There is a way.
For you to still have your
powers and be free of Cicada.
- How?
- On a different Earth,
where'd you be safe.
In your travels in your career
as a librarian,
have you ever heard of the
theory of the "Multi-verse"?
♪ ♪
- So...so this a device
that opens
a portal to another world.
- Yes.
Right.
- Any world I choose?
- Right. You're so smart.
You catch on so quickly.
You know, some people,
they just don't believe.
- Well, a few weeks ago
I saw a giant shark
fighting a giant gorilla
on the 6:00 news,
so...
- That's a good point.
Now look, this Earth that
I'm going to send you to,
it's...it's my Earth.
I'll have some friends there
to meet you,
but secret, huh?
This trip, you must not tell
anyone because if Cicada
were to find out
there's multiple Earths
and each one of these Earths
contains meta-humans,
no, they would be
her next target. Hmm?
What?
- Come with me.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- No, I must stay.
Now knowing Cicada is
a threat to this Earth,
I must fight
alongside my friends.
You know, Team Flash,
they're like...
They're like a family to me
but when I am done...
I will come find you.
You are the woman
I have been waiting for.
♪ ♪
So...
- I know.
♪ ♪
- Okay, you ready?
- Yeah.
- All right. [clears throat]
Allez.
♪ ♪
- You were right.
We taught you
how to be a hero.
So we shouldn't be angry
at you when you act like one.
- I know you're just afraid
I'll get hurt.
- There's always going
to be danger
that you're going
to face, Nora.
And we can't hold your hand
through all of it.
- As much as we want to.
You're our daughter
but you're not a kid.
You're right, you are capable
of making your own decisions.
[dramatic music building]
You really think you can
control your connection
to the Negative Speed Force,
find Grace for us?
- Yeah, I do.
All I need is for you guys
to keep our home safe
while I do it.
- I think I know how.
♪ ♪
Let's find Cicada.
- Man, this thing brings
back memories.
- Good ones? Bad ones?
- Thawne ones.
We trapped the Reverse-Flash
in this thing
before we even knew
he was Thawne.
- But we actually ended up
trapping his Speed Mirage.
while his real self
just sat there chilling
in his wheelchair.
- Man, Thawne's plans
got plans.
- But fear not, true believers.
The Thawne Trap 2.0 is smaller,
sleeker, and stronger.
I've gone ahead and sharpened
the inflexion points
to account for your
Negative Speed Force energy.
So if you go full
"Dante's Peak" in there,
we'll be safe out here.
- It also means I can't phase
in there if you need me.
- Your dad and I will
be right here the whole time.
- You always are.
- You got this.
- Let's go catch our big bad.
♪ ♪
[crowd clamoring]
- Excuse me! Excuse me!
People, please! Please!
[clamoring fades]
Thank you.
- For all of you I haven't met,
I'm Detective Joe West.
Now I am not a meta-human.
I don't know what that's like.
But I do know what it's like
to be afraid and overwhelmed.
You all came here
because you wanted answers
and you needed help.
Myself and everybody else here
at CCPD are here to help you.
So I swear to you,
with a little bit of patience
from all of us,
we will get through
this together.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Officers, let's start moving
the line again.
- We're gonna get to everybody.
[quietly clamoring]
[rousing music]
- Hold onto your butts.
[click, beeping]
♪ ♪
[pulsating]
- They're connected.
- I can see
the completed atomizer.
But I can't see
where she's taking it.
- Remember Nora,
that's not your anger.
It's hers.
[electricity zapping]
- Ah-ah, Nora.
I see what you're doing.
- Okay, something pissed
her off.
[zapping]
[eerie, high-pitched music]
♪ ♪
- Is your memory machine
letting you back into my head?
- No.
This is all me.
I can't let you
release that virus, Grace.
Thousands will die.
- Thousands today.
Even more tomorrow.
The world I wake up in
is overrun with people
with impossible powers.
Destroying innocent lives.
Ripping families apart.
Just like mine was.
And all of this is
because of you!
[glass shattering]
♪ ♪
- Uh, is that bad?
- Well, it's not good.
I'm pulling her out.
- No, no.
No, she'll get control.
- Your Flash family
created meta-humans.
The Particle Accelerator.
The bus metas.
The Enlightenment satellite
which you shattered!
[clattering]
[grunting]
- This isn't my anger.
It's yours.
- [grunting]
- You may look different,
Grace.
But you're still
the angry little girl I met
the first time I came here.
- [yelling]
- I'm sorry you have
to carry that anger.
But you're gonna have
to carry it alone
because I make
my own decisions,
and I've decided not
to be like you.
- [yelling]
[pulsating]
♪ ♪
- Nora! Nora.
- Hey!
- [panting]
She's...she's at CCPD.
[pulsating]
- Get everybody out of here
right now!
Cecil, go. Go!
- Move, move, move!
♪ ♪
- And now their end begins.
- Cicada's at CCPD
but she could use the atomizer
to spread the virus
from anywhere.
- There are hundreds
of metas there.
She's going to try
and take all of their lives.
- Not their lives,
their dark matter.
- She's going to use
all those metas like a battery.
What are we gonna do?
- Reach in, lose our powers,
destroy the dagger,
stop Cicada
from Supergirl-ing away,
then regroup
for the emotional fallout.
- Fallout.
Cisco, where did you send
Fallout's energy
when he was going nuclear?
- Earth-15. It's a dead Earth.
- Let's breach
the atomizer there.
- I'm coming with you!
- Nora, look.
You've already helped.
More than enough, all right?
- Okay, just do me a favor.
Blast that dagger to hell.
- Absolutely.
- Get out of my precinct.
[gunshots ring, pinging]
[zap]
- Hey, Cricket freak.
You and I have
some unfinished business.
- Nice hit.
- It won't keep her down long.
- Why do we have our powers?
Did we already win?
- Not yet.
The dagger's in the atomizer.
- Wait, wait, wait!
If we shoot the dagger
while it's still in there,
it could detonate the virus.
- Guys, she's waking up.
- All right, figure out
a way to stop it.
I'll keep her off your back.
- All right.
- This will help.
[ice cracking]
- Cisco, remove the dagger and
then breach the atomizer away.
- [grunts]
Yeah, there's a slight
problem there.
Breaching this thing
anywhere could set it off.
My powers are useless here.
- Then use your other power.
Your mind.
[dramatic music]
- Bring up
the atomizer blueprints.
I'm gonna have to science
the crap out of you.
- Good morning, sunshine.
A little different without your
power-dampening dagger, huh?
- Oh, I don't need
a dagger to kill you.
I never had it
before I came to this time.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- You wanna kill me?
Come get me.
- What she said.
♪ ♪
- Once you remove the plate,
you should be able to see
the control processor plane.
- I see it.
It's not gonna work.
I need a quantum computer
to hack this thing.
- [gasps] Wait! I have one.
Yeah.
[pulsating]
- Your gauntlet!
Damn, I love the future.
Okay, if I can connect
to the three nodes inside,
I'll override the system.
If I touch anything else,
hasta la vista, baby.
[grunting]
[panting]
Okay.
[beep]
There. I got it.
- Yeah, great. Um, how long
for the other two?
[beeping rapidly]
- However long we have left.
♪ ♪
[thud]
[pulsating]
Two down.
- Well, you're not great at
the Operation game, are you?
- You suck at
constructive criticism!
- [groans]
- Cisco, get out of there.
- Almost there.
It's in.
Cisco:Oh, shrap.
Iris: Cisco, what's going on?
- It's too late.
[powering down]
- Gotcha.
- [yelling]
- [grunts]
- The Atomizer's off.
- Flash!
- The dagger.
- If anything's gonna destroy
that dagger,
it's gonna be the mirror gun.
- Something doesn't add up.
Thawne's plans got plans.
She didn't have the dagger
in the future.
[clicking]
[dramatic music building]
♪ ♪
The dagger is Thawne's plan.
Don't shoot it!
- Greg, move your head.