- Previously on "The Flash"...
I'm Cisco, by the way.
You must be Gypsy.
It's nice to meet you.
Who are you?
- Daddy?
- You're a warrior
who would fight to protect
the only person I love.
- I want to take the cure.
- You're the person that I want
to run this team when I'm gone.
- Sorry I went
all ice dagger-y on you.
I still don't like you.
Ramsey, don't do this.
- As long as I feed,
I could live forever.
- So this is where
you've been hiding.
- Sometimes the truth
is the hardest lie
to see through.
And when you can't put
your faith in the truth...
all you have left is yourself.
- You're under arrest, Ramon.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Barry,
we don't have to do this.
- It's Tahiti,
not Iron Heights.
- I know, but we've got
too much going on right now
to be taking a vacation.
- Okay, look.
It's two days.
All right?
Ramsey's been off the grid
for two weeks.
And Crisis is coming.
No matter what.
Let me take you
someplace special,
where we can have
fruity umbrella drinks
and get sand between our toes.
- I do like us.
And we're even better
with Mai Tais.
- You gotta take a look.
It's in a book.
[laughs]
Hey, I thought you guys
fathwoomed out of here.
- We just wanted to make sure
you guys were okay
holding down the fort
while we were gone.
- We're good.
Rest easy, lovebirds.
Team Leader
is my new middle name.
- What was it before?
- Baracus.
- As in Barracas, Argentina?
- No, as in Mr. T.
My mom was a big "A-Team" fan.
- Wish mine was.
Could've been Hannibal Dibny.
- Hannibal?
Please. You're Murdock
on your best day.
You guys have fun.
I'm gonna hold it down
with a little help
from my friend,
the Barry.
- The Barry?
I'm standing right here.
- Not you, Barry.
B.A.R.I.
Barry Allen
Replicated Intelligence.
- Aww.
- It's my decision-making
algorithm.
- So if there's a problem,
this is gonna tell us
what to do?
- Yes, and since it's based
on his past leadership choices,
it'll tell me
how to handle any situation
exactly like he would.
- I mean, I'm flattered,
I think.
- Huh.
What is Barry's favorite thing
that I make him for breakfast?
- Uh...
banana?
[computer beeping]
- Huh.
- Who's next?
- Okay, computer,
what's Barry's favorite movie?
- "Empire."
- Oh, thank God.
- Actually...
I mean, I've loved,
loved "Empire Strikes Back"
my whole life, but...
now that I think about it...
oh, my God.
My favorite movie
is "Jurassic Park."
- There it is.
- How does it do that?
- Fuzzy logic,
and AI intuition, my guy.
With the B.A.R.I. by my side,
it'll be like you never left.
- Well, okay.
I guess we should get going.
- Yes, we should.
- Send me a post card.
- Look, remember,
I'm leaving you in charge.
- I'll see you
when you get back.
- Bye.
- So you got
any marching orders, boss?
- The B.A.R.I. wants me
to stay here
and you to go with Frost
to stake out Ramsey's lab.
- I love it when a plan
comes together.
♪ ♪
- Just so you know...
I let you follow me here.
- I let you think that.
Captain Joe West.
CCPD.
- So...
what brings you down here?
- People with your face
usually have something to hide,
so when my son Barry told me
that there was a new Wells,
I started keeping taps on you.
- I don't know how new
a Wells I am, and second,
keeping tabs, that's what
you mean by spying on me
from that nondescript sedan
parked up on Lake Avenue?
- Well-observed.
So why are you...
digging holes in the city?
- Well, perfect stranger...
the reason I'm digging holes
underneath the city is...
oh, wait...
you couldn't
possibly understand.
- Try me.
- Nah.
No, no, no, no, no.
♪ ♪
- You need some rest.
All those late nights
working on the B.A.R.I.,
you've barely slept this week.
- Tonight,
I'm gonna sleep like a child
'cause I got the B.A.R.I.
and I got my white noise
and I got my boo.
Goodnight.
[disquieting music]
♪ ♪
[screams]
- You okay?
- No, not really.
I just almost went
Sweeney Todd on myself.
Why would I do that?
Maybe I was sleepwalking?
- Yeah,
that's kind of your new thing.
- Huh?
- Yeah, you woke me up
last night, too.
I heard the front door shut,
and you were standing there
with your keys in your hand
and your shoes on.
I was half-asleep,
so I just put you back to bed.
- Okay,
why didn't you say anything?
- Well, I didn't think
it was a big deal.
I...just like a one-off,
'cause you're so exhausted.
- Well, it is a big deal,
and it's not a one-off anymore,
is it?
That's twice now
that's happened.
- Babe, relax.
Okay, you just launched
the B.A.R.I. today.
You need time to rest
that sexy brain of yours.
- My brain is the Ryan Gosling
of genius intellects.
Okay.
Will you please let me know
next time that happens?
- Yes.
- And hide
those scissors from me.
Okay.
- Goodnight, babe.
Goodnight.
I love y...I look...
forward to spending time
with you tomorrow.
- Uh...thank you.
- You're welcome.
[playful music]
- Yeah, okay, babe.
Goodnight.
♪ ♪
[loud humming]
Oh, my God.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- It's okay.
I know him.
He's my ex's dad.
Hey, Breacher...
long time no try to kill me.
What brings you
to my bedroom...
again?
♪ ♪
Breacher?
Hey.
Josh.
- It's Cynthia.
She's dead.
♪ ♪
- I can't believe she's gone.
And I never get
to see her again.
- Cynthia was tracking
a high-level hacker.
Goes by the name of...
Echo.
- She mentioned him before.
Nobody's ever been able
to figure out
who he really is, right?
- We think Cynthia did.
How he got the jump on her,
we don't know.
- I don't see her
losing a fight to anyone.
[mournful music]
- She won the fight.
Dying here just...
triggered her Collector QT-net.
- The quara-temporal
containment barrier?
Gypsy once said
these barriers
were like supersized
vibe fields
around the planet.
The Collectors put them up
so a suspect
can't breach their way
to another world.
- And only the Agency
can lift it.
- Meaning her killer
is still here.
- I'm going to avenge
Cynthia's death.
And Vibe
is gonna help me do it.
[dramatic music]
- Cisco isn't Vibe anymore.
He decided to take
the meta-human cure.
- Weren't you worried
about breach psychosis?
It happens sometimes
when you suppress your powers.
It's...
it's really gnarly.
- How gnarly?
- Hallucinations,
weird blackouts...
dry mouth.
- My powers weren't suppressed.
They're gone.
- Well,
even without his meta-powers,
Cisco can still help you.
He's a genius.
[gentle synth music]
♪ ♪
- What would Barry do?
The B.A.R.I. wants us
to go to the crime scene.
Listen, you don't
have to go back there.
I'll go.
- I'll come with you.
- Kamilla,
this could be dangerous.
I mean, we're dealing
with a killer here.
I can't ask you
come to with me.
- You didn't.
I volunteered.
[musical crescendo]
♪ ♪
- I knew you wouldn't
let me down.
[both coughing]
- Okay.
[groans]
[electronic beeping]
[laughs]
You can dance around
with that thing all you want.
This place is a dead zone long
before that wall came down.
- Well,
it might eventually go through.
At least I'm trying to help.
What are you doing?
- I'm getting us out of here.
That's what I'm doing.
Stupid.
- Well, I have a team
that could help us
get out of here.
- How?
How are they gonna help us?
No one knows we're down here.
- I am a precinct captain.
I have dozens of cops
and a whole support staff
that depends on me 24/7.
If I don't show up
for a couple of hours,
they're coming looking for me.
- All right.
Somebody's over-confident.
You know what you don't have?
You don't have
cell phone service.
You don't have Wi-Fi.
You have no way
of telling anyone...
- What are you doing?
- That we're down here.
Right?
- Put it away.
- This is our only option.
I'm gonna get us out of here.
- What are you doing?
Stop!
[both groaning]
both: What is wrong with you?
- Why did you not tell me
that this Earth vibrational
frequency
is calibrated
at a molecular level?
- You're supposed to be
the expert.
- Shh!
- Shush me one more time.
We gonna have a problem.
- We already do.
It turns out that
that fireball sapped 80...
87% of the oxygen
in this chamber,
which means that you and I have
42 minutes left to breathe.
♪ ♪
- You know,
the idea was you'd call me
before he started
killing people.
- He showed up out of nowhere.
Rat and Pops
tried to run for it.
They didn't get far.
Frost,
that guy is next-level creepy.
I wouldn't go looking for him.
- Smart move.
Especially without a partner.
How's business, Snake-shack?
- Had better days.
- You mind giving us a minute?
Need to have
a little chat with Frosty.
- What are you doing here?
- Looking for you.
What happened
to staking out Ramsey's lab?
- Norvock texted me.
He said he saw Ramsey here.
- Frost, as your life coach,
going after Ramsey alone
is probably gonna put me
out of a job.
- This isn't a joke.
This is a fight.
My fight.
So stay out of it.
- We're a team.
Your fights are my fights,
so why don't you
just take a breath
and try trusting a friend?
- I knew from day one
not to trust this guy.
But we did.
And now people are dead.
So I've gotta fix this.
- It wasn't that long ago
that I felt the same.
Blamed myself,
never asked anyone for help,
and you know where it got me?
Eyeball-deep
in Gingold and self-pity.
So believe me when I say
that life is better
if you have faith
in the people around you.
♪ ♪
What?
- I know who Ramsey
has faith in.
I gotta go.
- Did you hear
anything I just said?
You can't go alone.
- I know what I'm doing.
And don't worry.
I won't be alone.
- Listen, Kamilla...
there's something I've been
wanting to say to you.
I've been trying to figure out
how to say it,
but I don't know.
I think I should just
come right out and say it.
Kamilla, I...
- Holy crap.
[radios squawking]
I thought CCPD's crime scenes
were serious.
- Yep.
Earth-19 Collector agents
take investigations
to a whole other level.
- Agent Zak Zeal.
Kamilla Hwang,
Cisco Ramon.
Yeah, I heard you'd be coming.
I thought you'd be taller.
You know, from the way
Gypsy talked about you.
- That's funny.
She never mentioned you at all.
- [scoffs] Hi.
Make sure Walker
is updating
the dimensional output report.
Thanks. You gotta keep
on them constantly
when you're in charge.
Breacher understands.
Where is he, anyway?
- He already saw everything
he needed to see.
We're here in his place.
- Well, the Agency authorized
you to join this investigation,
so I guess I'll just
have to let you.
- Is there a time of death?
- Due to multi-dimensional
signal speed,
our best guess is that
it happened some time
between 2:30 and 4:30 a.m.
- That's a pretty good guess.
- Yeah, I know.
And we found this.
301-H energy cartridge.
Standard issue.
No prints.
Combine it
with the Sigma Baryon residue
we also found,
and it looks like...
- Echo killed Gypsy with
a transonic-demolecularizer?
Show us.
Now.
- Her body, clothes,
even her communicator
were all vaporized.
♪ ♪
- Me being like this...
I don't want you to think
I'm still hung up over Cynthia,
or something.
- Cisco.
Someone you cared about died.
I'd be worried
if you weren't sad.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
So earlier,
when we first got here...
you were gonna say something?
♪ ♪
- Kamilla...
- We're locking down the area.
- For the love of God.
- You two need to leave.
Ramon.
- I just wanted to say again
how much I truly admired Gypsy.
I've got some big shoes
to fill.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- We're not seriously just
gonna give up, are we?
- No, we're not.
Have you noticed
he's the only one who benefits
from Cynthia's death?
- So what's the plan?
- The B.A.R.I. suggests
a dual course of action.
First, we use the
satellites to track
the weapon's unique signature.
Can you...
- On it.
I've been paying attention.
Second?
- We're gonna have to do
the impossible.
- [panting]
- Man, sit down.
Relax.
We may live longer.
- What evidence
do you have that anyone,
literally anyone,
is coming down here
to rescue us?
- I don't have any.
- No?
- But I do have faith.
- Ha! Well, then, Captain,
at least you haven't lost
your sense of humor.
Whoa.
Ouch.
- Uh-huh.
Got light-headed, didn't you?
- No.
- You selfishly don't believe
in anything or anybody.
I used to be like that.
When my ex-wife
left me and my daughter...
I was broken.
So much so
that I went somewhere
where I almost never go.
Church.
I didn't go there
to pray or anything.
I went there
to yell at the universe
for destroying my life.
Next thing,
I'm at home.
I'm so hurt
that I can't even...
cook dinner for my...
for my daughter.
Doorbell rings.
I open the door to what looked
like my whole neighborhood
standing on my lawn
who had cooked food for us.
You can have faith
in anything, but...
it was then
I realized that I...
I have faith in people.
♪ ♪
- According to B.A.R.I.,
we can use low-level
delta wave vibrations
to stimulate harmonic resonance
in my prefrontal cortex.
If I think of memories
with Cynthia,
we'll be absorb
the residual vibe energy
from the object
that killed her.
- Can this machine
restore my vibe powers?
- No, we're not the generators
of the vibe,
but we will be
the receptors of it.
- But I'm gonna have to see
Cynthia die, won't I?
♪ ♪
- It's the only way we have
of finding out who killed her.
My white noise machine
will stimulate
our delta-wave patterns.
Add the shell casing
as a trigger,
and that'll do it.
B.A.R.I., initiate artificial
vibrational sequence.
[machine whirring]
If we want this to work,
we have to make
physical contact.
♪ ♪
[both grunting]
[computer beeping]
- [yells]
♪ ♪
- You murdered my daughter.
- No.
No, I didn't do it.
I swear.
- [growls]
Liar!
- You have to believe me!
- Leave him alone!
- Where did you get that?
- In Cisco's workshop.
I don't know how it got there.
- I do.
He just murdered
my daughter with it.
- No. Breacher.
I don't care what
you think you saw, okay?
You know Cisco.
You know how much
he cared about Gypsy.
There's gotta be
another explanation.
- Babe, please.
- What about doppelgangers?
- She's right.
There's thousands of other
versions of me out there.
- Yeah, and they're
all pencil-pushers.
None of them are scientists
like you!
You had motive,
and just enough guts
to do this.
- Breacher, I swear.
I don't know
how this is possible.
Unless...
- Unless breach psychosis.
- Kamilla,
what time did you find me
sleepwalking the other night?
- I don't know.
Maybe 4:00 a.m.
- [grunts]
You're guilty.
But you're not
in your right mind.
I didn't just lose
a daughter today.
I lost a son.
Because...
I still respect
the man you were.
Now I'm gonna give you an hour
to get
all your affairs in order,
and then turn yourself in.
Or I will end you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
- I'm gonna blow
this blockade sky high.
- You do that,
this whole thing collapses,
we're dead.
- I do nothing,
and we're dead anyway.
- We still have time
for my team to show up.
- Enough.
Enough about your team and you.
- You know where I stand.
- How can you have such faith?
- Because someone
or something called The Monitor
says my son is destined to die
in some kind of Crisis,
and the only way
I can stomach any of that
is have faith
that his continuing life
or his death
is for the greater...
the greater...
the greater good.
- You've seen Mar Novu?
Captain.
- Hey. Hey.
I got you, big guy.
You're all right.
- [panting]
- Oh, you got my text.
- No.
I called CCPD
with a Ramsey update,
and nobody had seen you.
Ran your plates,
tracked your car
to a block from here.
Your notes
had this tunnel marked.
I'm guessing...
because of him.
- Lone Ranger.
- Hi.
♪ ♪
- I see you got my message.
Cait.
You know, it's a bit weird
seeing you like this.
- I guess both our looks
are evolving.
Yes, I did get your message.
It reminded me of when we both
used to work for your mom.
Way back when I was a resident.
- You were like the daughter
Mum never had.
Do you know
at first I was jealous?
Over time, I came to see you
less as a rival
and more like a sister.
And that's why I'm offering
you a chance to join me.
- You want to kill me, too.
- I'm offering you life, Cait.
I've learned to control it,
discovered its secret beauty.
This my final masterpiece,
Cait.
Life eternal.
- Immortality?
- You see?
I'm no monster.
I'm a miracle.
- You're talking
about reversing nature.
- Nature never meant
for us to fly,
and yet
we've touched the stars,
and not by being slaves
to the shackles
of the natural order,
but by transcending them.
Take a look
at your own life, Cait.
How many times have you had
to say good-bye to people?
How many more have you not
even had the chance to do so?
My mum should be here.
Your father should be here.
Your husband should be here.
Join me,
and this is the end
of good-byes.
No one you love
will ever die again.
- I've seen
your version of life.
It's a nightmare,
but you can still be
your mother's son.
She had so much faith in you,
and so do I.
You just need
to have faith in yourself.
[gasps]
- Your words are madness.
Next time won't be a choice.
- [panting]
♪ ♪
- Look,
we have to face the facts.
And I have to own up
to whatever it is that I did.
- You're gonna turn
yourself in?
- I have to.
I can't trust myself anymore.
- Anymore?
You stopped trusting
yourself the moment
Barry asked you to take over
as team leader.
I mean, you built
this elaborate device
just so you wouldn't have
to make
any decisions for yourself.
- That's...
- Let me make
this decision for you.
You are innocent.
- How can you be so sure?
- Because I have faith in you.
The real question is why don't
you have any faith in yourself?
- Because Barry's gonna die.
What if I can't keep people
safe the way he does?
I'm not the Flash.
- Babe.
Barry didn't choose you
to be the Flash.
He chose you to be you.
All these doubts,
they aren't you.
They're just noise
in your head.
♪ ♪
- It's been in Wi-Fi mode
this whole time.
- What is it?
- This code.
It's turned
my white noise machine
into a micro neural
impulse disruptor
that could go
all "Wreck-It-Ralph"
on my brainwaves.
It might even look
like breach psychosis.
- Who'd be smart enough
to code like that?
- Me.
- Sometimes the truth is
the hardest lie to see through.
When you can't put
your faith in the truth...
all you have left is yourself.
- You're under arrest, Ramon.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I surrender.
I'm guilty.
- Suspect is in custody.
Initiate QT-net removal
so the prisoner
can be transferred to Earth-19.
- Copy that.
- Breacher.
That holo-cube will tell you
everything you need to know
about what happened to Cynthia.
- QT-net is off.
- QT-net's down, sir.
I'll cuff him.
♪ ♪
- Sorry it had to go down
this way...
but I needed you
to lift the net.
- Re-engage the QT-net.
- That'll take four minutes.
- I don't care
if it'll take four minutes.
Just get on with it!
- [grunts]
I hate force fields.
- I know.
- Cisco.
You think I'm gonna let the man
that murdered
my daughter escape?
- No, sir.
And neither am I.
♪ ♪
I'm here.
There's no sign of him.
- His breach portal energy
puts him
at the east end
of the warehouse.
- Game over, Echo.
- Oh, no.
You found me.
How did you find me?
- I tricked the Collectors
into lifting the QT-net.
When they did,
I knew you'd jump at the chance
to get out of here
and try to open a breach.
I just had to track
the portal energy.
- Babe,
just get him back here
so the agents
can take him down.
- You have approximately
two minutes
before my ride out of here
boots up.
I go bye-bye,
and you take my place
in Earth-19 Collector jail,
but you're the one
with the gun.
So...
do you have it in you
to stop me?
- I guess we'll find out,
won't we?
- You are an anomaly.
Makes me wonder why
it was so easy to frame you.
Don't you want to know
how I did it?
You might learn something.
- No, I pretty much
figured it all out.
After you got here,
you killed the top agent
in the Collective,
but you still needed a way out.
So you used your face
to get into S.T.A.R. Labs
and plant this gun
in my workshop.
Is that right?
- So far, so good.
- But hacking
my white noise machine
to make me sleepwalk...
[screams]
That's when you tipped
your hand.
I'd recognize
that coding anywhere.
And since didn't hack it,
I knew it had to be
some other version of me.
- I'm not just
some other version of you.
I specialize in hacking
multiversal databases
to create new identities.
I could change your world...
in an instant.
You see, somewhere out there
is a Cisco Ramon
who isn't as lucky as you are,
who doesn't have the job,
the mind,
the life you have.
But if the price is right,
Echo can reverse
those fortunes.
And you might just wake up
tomorrow
living someone else's life.
- Is that why you killed her,
so you could keep peddling
these fake identities
to people?
- I didn't kill Gypsy.
You did.
[laughs]
I'll give her this.
She was a formidable fighter.
But not even the smartest guy
in the room could beat her
in hand-to-hand combat,
but it didn't matter.
Even though she'd
been chasing me for years,
she never even knew
what I looked like.
So when she caught me,
and she saw my face,
all it took was one moment,
one moment of her flinching,
and that gave me the second
I needed to use that gun,
the same gun that's
in your hands right now.
Do you need me to spell it out
for you, genius?
Gypsy is dead
because when she saw me,
she saw you.
- Stop talking.
- She didn't have to die.
She couldn't let me go.
She breached me to this Earth
and I vaporized her.
- No.
- Yes.
[both grunting]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Don't feel bad, Cisco.
You're just not wired like me.
- You're right.
I'm a hell of a lot smarter.
I programmed
that weapon to trigger
an anti-vibrational force field
around whoever fires it.
In this case...
that's you, genius.
Did you get
my holo-cube message?
Took you long enough.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Echo is in an Earth-19 cell.
Where he belongs.
I'm sorry I lost faith in you,
Cisky.
- You know what?
It's okay.
Things were looking
pretty bad there for a second.
But what I don't get,
if she was dying,
why come here?
- Because she knew
you would bring Echo
to justice.
She had to lure him here,
to this Earth.
♪ ♪
- She never lost faith
in you, Cisco.
- [snorts]
♪ ♪
- Now that this is over with,
what am I gonna do?
- Same thing I have to do.
We start healing.
- I want to invite you to...
Cynthia's remembrance ceremony
on Earth-19.
♪ ♪
You, too.
- I'd be honored.
- Cynthia would've liked you.
♪ ♪
I do, too.
- What's not to love?
♪ ♪
- Awkward.
I have to go now.
[portal whooshes]
- Well, uh, yeah.
I, um...
Well, we haven't...said it.
- Yeah, I know.
- So...yeah, I, um...
♪ ♪
- Me too.
Big-time.
- Oh, thank God.
- [laughs]
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- Please tell me
you went home at some point.
- I knew I smelled
SPF 90.
[chuckles]
How was it?
- Amazing.
15 beaches in 24 hours,
one of the many perks
of marrying a speedster.
- [chuckles]
[electronic beeping]
Yo, Chester's energy level's
already up to 87%?
- Yeah, yeah.
The, uh...
the M.A.C.'s gonna be done
cooking him up
any day now.
- So the B.A.R.I.
was a success?
- Uh, actually,
I had to get rid of it.
I did use it...
try to use it...
at first, but...
over time,
I finally realized...
And you already knew
that was gonna happen.
- It's just more
proof that you're
the right person
to lead the team.
- Hmm.
- Cisco, we got your message.
I'm...I'm really sorry
to hear about Gypsy.
- Some things
you never get over.
But her service
is next week.
- You want us
to come with you?
- Yeah.
I mean, we loved her, too.
- Thank you.
Uh, Kamilla's coming
with me, so...
I'm very lucky to have her.
♪ ♪
Is it wrong
to feel that way...
I mean, with everything
that just happened?
It's like I'm moving on,
What kind of person does that?
- Someone who is very much
in love.
♪ ♪
- It's funny.
Cynthia wasn't the person
I ended up with,
but, um,
I think she taught me how to be
the person I needed to be
for when the right person
came along,
and for that,
I will never forget her.
♪ ♪
- Your vitals are good, Joe.
- You know, in all the hubbub
of saving your keisters,
I never got to ask
what the hell
you were doing
down there.
- Hey, 1940s,
no one says "keisters."
- Nash, if you would just
tell us
what you're looking for
down there,
we might be able
to help you.
[dramatic music]
- All right, tomorrow morning,
9:00, tunnels.
Bring your whole fancy team.
- Why should we do that?
- 'Cause...
I know how to save
Barry Allen.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.