[dramatic music]
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
- Barry, please!
That's not me!
[sighs]
This can't be happening.
- Are you real?
[gasps]
No, of course you're not.
[laughs]
That's it. That's it.
I've finally lost it.
- It's okay.
I-I'm real.
- [laughs]
Oh, my...
I...
Oh, I-I...
I can't believe
I'm talking to another person.
It's been so long.
- Wait, I know you...
you and your husband,
Joseph Carver,
you founded
McCulloch Technologies.
You're Eva McCulloch.
But you're supposed
to be dead.
- No.
Not dead.
Just trapped.
♪ ♪
Now so are you.
[eerie music]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
You see, until now,
this place was a whole world
with one inhabitant...
Me.
- This must be another Earth.
- Same Earth.
Another dimension.
You see, a mirror-version
of Central City.
Same city, same buildings,
just empty.
Who are you anyway?
- I'm Iris West-Allen.
I'm a reporter
for "The CC Citizen."
- Never heard of it.
Not that it matters.
God, it feels so good
to have a conversation
that's not one-sided.
- Everything is backwards.
Eva, you said that this place
was a mirror-version
of our own.
How is that possible?
- Think of it like this:
our reality is observed
by three dimensions:
width, depth, and length.
The superstring theory posits
that there are other realities,
fractal dimensions
humans can't see.
So...
Two sides.
One, our world.
The other is just
some empty reflection.
I'm a quantum engineer.
It's...
it's my wheelhouse.
♪ ♪
[high-pitched ringing]
Yeah, that is a side-effect
of this dimension.
I...
I barely notice them anymore.
- How did you end up here, Eva?
- Six years ago,
I was developing
the technology
to open doors to other
planes of existence.
I was in my office
the night Harrison Wells'
dream went up in smoke.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[screams]
I've been here ever since.
- Dark matter must have
washed over that mirror
and created a doorway.
I was in this office
when I got pulled in too.
But that's not all.
There is someone else on
the other side of that mirror,
another me.
How is that possible, Eva?
- A fractal variable
caused by the mirror.
A duplicate of you.
- You mean the mirror left
a fake clone of me
in the real world?
We're getting out of here.
- I've tried.
For six years,
I've been in
my own personal hell.
- Eva, I have to go home.
- I'm sorry
you're stuck here, but...
♪ ♪
I thought I was gonna
die here alone.
At least now there's two of us.
♪ ♪
- Investigation into
the disappearance
of socialite Sue Dearbon.
Day 274
since her parents
first hired me to find her.
♪ ♪
Status update.
Nothing.
Sue's trail went cold
in Midway City
after Remington Meister
provided a dead end.
However, she was there.
Meister confirmed that much.
- Hey, what are you still
doing here...oh, seriously?
Ralph.
When I left last night,
you were standing here staring
at the exact same board,
same as the night before.
Honey, don't you think maybe
it's time
you got a little help?
And a shower?
- Cecile, this is my process.
I work things out with
the only person
that can keep up with
my beautiful detective mind.
Me.
- You could work with me.
We took down the FEMA guy
together, that was so great.
You're not loving that,
all right.
Um...
- Cecile, you know me.
I-I like doing things
my own way.
- Ralph...
every Holmes needs a Watson.
[electronic chime]
- Hang on.
- Mm-mm.
What is it?
- So a couple months ago,
I put up these alerts
on Sue's bank accounts,
trusts, and credit cards.
Apparently, she just made
a small deposit on..
an apartment in Central City.
[chuckles]
See? Told you.
Only partner I need is...
[clicks tongue] This guy.
- Mm-hmm.
- See you.
♪ ♪
- Oh, wow, something definitely
just died in here.
- Kara and Lex Luthor?
Man, this post-Crisis world
gets harder to understand
every day.
- Right?
- [grunts]
Man.
- What's wrong?
- I'm still sore
from our little double date
with Amunet and Goldface.
So, so weird.
- Maybe you should stay
home today.
- No, no.
Are you working on
more Black Hole stuff?
- Yeah, I think I am getting
really close to taking this
son of a bitch down.
- Yeah.
That's the mirror gun?
- Yeah,
it contains bleeding-edge
reflective micro-chip
technology.
If I can examine the gun
up close,
then maybe I can find
some kind of small clue
that connects the gun
to Black Hole
since McCulloch created it.
It's still
in the Starchives, right?
- Yeah, yeah, it is.
- Could you, um,
get it for me?
- Uh...
I-I mean,
unlocking a weapon like that
sounds like a bad idea.
- Barry, it's me.
[scoffs]
- I-I know, but I mean,
after what just happened
with you and Carver...
w-what if the gun
fell into the wrong hands?
Just like the cold gun
fell into Snart's.
- It won't, trust me.
- Iris, I...
look, you I trust,
but, um, the guy
who just tried to
to have you assassinated,
not so much.
I mean, and if Black Hole
had a weapon
as powerful
as the mirror gun,
I mean, there's no telling
what could happen.
- Yeah, you're right.
I will...um,
I'll try a different angle.
♪ ♪
- I'm just being cautious.
- Yeah, I know, I get it.
Have fun.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
- [scoffs]
Not exactly the Ritz.
[glass shatters]
[object crashes]
- Get down!
[coughing]
- What the hell, lady?
- Hey, I just saved your life.
You're welcome, by the way.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
It's you.
You're Sue Dearbon.
- In the flesh.
And you are?
- No one followed us.
We're clear.
- Sue, I...
I have been looking for you
for nine months.
- Ouch.
I hope you don't bill
by the hour.
- Where have you been?
A-and why did your apartment
explode in my face?
- Yeah, hate it
when that happens.
- Look, I'm serious.
Now who set that bomb?
Why are they trying
to kill you?
And how long has this been
going on for?
- Uh, my ex.
Because I know too much.
About nine months.
You done?
- No, I'm most certainly
not done.
Why is your ex sending you
explosive candy grams?
- Ooh, the cheap stuff.
- [sighs]
Look.
Drinks later.
Spilling your guts
to tell a tragic story?
That'd be now.
- Fine.
I fell in love with a murderer.
Happy?
[jazzy music]
♪ ♪
John Loring.
Turns out Mr. Dreamy Muscles
and charisma-for-miles
was also a major arms dealer
on the black market.
- So why does Loring
want you dead?
- Because I stumbled across
his client lists,
weapons inventory,
and everything else
that exposes him
for the bag of crap that he is.
The first time
he tried to kill me,
I was asleep.
- All right, well...
♪ ♪
- Who are you calling, Slick?
- Your parents.
To let 'em know you're safe.
[keyboard clacking]
- Hmm.
- What...
come on, I just switched plans.
- John can track your phone.
You call my parents,
they're dead.
- All right, then, uh,
we'll go to the police.
I know a Precinct Captain
who can help us.
- The last time I tried that,
they tried to kill me too.
John's got cops on the payroll
in every city he does business.
♪ ♪
- Then what's your plan
to get out of this?
Sue, you can't run forever.
- Who says I'm running?
♪ ♪
- You and Loring
are hunting each other.
That's why
you're in Central City.
- John's in town
for a massive sale.
If I can get damning evidence
on what he's doing,
he goes to jail.
And I go home.
- [exhales]
I smell a mystery.
- I smell...
[sniffs]
Expired milk.
- Look, everything
is gonna be fine.
Your parents hired me
to do whatever it takes
to bring you home safely.
And that's what I'm gonna do.
- How?
- Easy.
I'm gonna find Loring,
I'm gonna get your evidence,
then I'm gonna take it to CCPD.
And after I do that,
I'm gonna take you home.
- John's a killer.
You'd be risking your life.
For me.
If you get killed...
my parents are out good money.
I'm coming with you.
♪ ♪
- [whispering]
1,322. 1,322.
Okay.
- Eva, there has got
to be a way out of here
that we haven't thought of yet.
- There isn't.
There's only two options
in this place:
survival or madness.
1,322...
- Eva, my husband will
be looking for me, please.
- This is how it all starts!
Don't you understand?
You sit here and you think
everything's gonna work out.
You can't possibly
stay here forever,
and then 1,322.
- That's how many times I've
tried to escape this place.
That's how many times
I've failed.
1,322 reminders
that I'm never
leaving this place.
So please don't...
give me another one.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I'm having a really
bad hair day.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
I...
I've been alone
for a very long time.
- Well, you're not anymore.
We just need
one way out of here, Eva.
That's it.
♪ ♪
Sam Scudder.
- Who?
- He was one of the bad guys.
He trapped...
someone in a mirror
a few years ago.
And my friends got him out by
bringing it to absolute zero.
We...
Eva, we just need to find
some liquid nitrogen.
- Well, I-I have a lab
down the hall.
There should be some in there.
The nitrogen should slow down
the mirror's molecules
to the lowest enthalpy
state possible.
Oh, my God.
This could work.
♪ ♪
[elevator dings]
- Hey, Barr.
Morning.
- Hey.
- You got a sec?
- Yeah, what's up, Captain?
- Eh.
- Yeah, that never gets old.
- Yeah, it kinda does.
Um, listen.
There was a house fire
on Batton Street last month.
- Okay.
- The occupant died
of smoke inhalation.
I'm wondering if you could
take a second look.
- Joe, this case was already
declared an accident.
- Yeah.
I need, uh, fresh pair
of eyes on it.
- Okay, I mean,
what am I looking for?
- Whatever you find.
- Joe, I mean,
I've got a mountain of cases
I need to go through.
Ones that haven't
been solved already.
- Okay, all I can say
is that you'd be
doing me a favor.
And whatever you find, Barr,
bring it directly to me.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
- John owns that warehouse.
That's where the deal
will go down.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going with you.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Oh, look, I get it.
Chivalry's your brand.
- You're an MIT grad,
speak six languages,
and you play polo.
You belong in a country club,
not in the field.
- [scoffs]
You belong in the 19th Century
with your Victorian,
save-the-damsel-in-distress
crap.
- Loring doesn't know
that I'm coming,
so I have the element
of surprise.
You, on the other hand,
he might kinda know
that you're coming.
Translation:
stay in the car, please.
♪ ♪
[car door shuts]
[camera shutter clicking]
♪ ♪
I hope Loring looks good
in orange.
Uh, I don't suppose
you're a fellow bird watcher?
[grunts]
Huh.
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Vin Diesel!
You still want me
to wait in the car?
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- So you mind telling me
how you know martial arts?
- My parents sent me to Kyoto
for a summer.
Trained with a blind sensei.
Taught me everything I know.
- Really?
- No.
[scoffs]
I trained with a guy
named Frank at a YMCA.
Will you relax?
We're safe here.
John's not stupid.
Killing me in a public place?
Uh-uh, it's not gonna happen.
- I'm sorry, I believe
he blew up an apartment
to get to you.
- That building was scheduled
for demolition next month.
But he does know
that someone's after him now.
It'll make him
harder to get to.
Thanks to you.
♪ ♪
- Where are you going?
- Sorry, Slick.
I can't partner up with someone
who doesn't think
I can pull my own weight.
- Hang on a second, Sue.
Hang on.
Will you just
hang on one second, please?
Look, when I take a case,
I see it through to the end.
And this doesn't end
until you're safe.
- Do you trust me, Ralph?
- I just met you.
But you did save my keister.
Twice.
And that means I owe you.
And I always pay my debts.
- I'll take that as a yes.
So...
without those pictures...
- We are back to square one.
- Fortunately,
we still have John's ledger.
He keeps a detailed record
of every deal
he's ever made in it.
Years of evidence against him.
- But his office is still
on the seventh floor
of that warehouse.
- Which has probably doubled
its security by now.
- But the sewer system,
that's a good way in.
Those tunnels, they lead
directly to the center
of the building.
- And then we time our entry
for when the guards...
both: Change shifts.
- And then we mosey up the
stairs into Loring's office,
we get the prize.
- Well, you are slick.
- Oh, my God,
Ralph, you found her!
- Oh, technically,
I found him.
- Sue Dearbon.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Cecile Horton.
Meta-human attorney.
But I also have 20 years
of experience
defending non-meta-humans.
The law is my game,
Cecile is my name.
I can cover you no matter
what you've had going on
all this time.
- Just need a quick word.
- Oh, gotcha.
Just one sec.
- Listen, we're...we're...
we're kind of in the middle
of something.
Uh, Sue's been on the run
for the last year.
It turns out that
someone's after her.
- [gasps]
And you're her knight
in shining armor?
Ralph, I love it!
By the way, you two?
Hmm.
When I read the both of you
with my powers,
I could barely tell you apart.
Like, emotionally speaking,
you and Sue are definitely
surfing the same wave.
- Just trying to keep her safe.
I mean,
it's not like we're dating.
- [mouthing words]
- [mouths words]
- I can't believe I didn't
think of this before.
[grunts]
- You would have, eventually.
♪ ♪
- What's happening?
[both gasp]
- No.
- It should've worked.
[sobs]
No.
[sighs]
[shouts]
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
I really thought I was going
back to my old life.
- Eva, you will.
- [sighs]
It doesn't even matter anymore.
♪ ♪
My sweet Joseph.
We were so in love.
♪ ♪
I saw him in the mirror.
I watched him for five years
as he mourned, grieved, and...
moved on.
And I can't...
I...
I can't move on.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Gah!
- Oh, my gosh. Nash.
- I didn't think anyone else
would be down here.
[clears throat]
- I-I lost something
down here, so.
- Oh, right.
Well, that makes sense.
These Starchives
are so massive.
- Okay.
[sighs]
- I'm sorry, what were you
doing down here?
- Cisco asked me
to hold down the fort
while he, uh...
[snaps fingers]
He wanted me
to take the inventory,
so I gotta do that.
It sucks.
- That's a lie.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Uh, what are you doing here?
- I lost Nora's journal.
I haven't seen it
for a couple weeks.
And, um...
you know, it's the
only thing I have left
of my daughter, so.
- Ah, must be hard.
- You would know, wouldn't you?
- Now that I think about it,
that's probably...
I am digging up the past,
and, you know, maybe I should
start living in the present.
- So should we all.
- Mm-hmm.
- But it's difficult for you.
Isn't it, Nash?
There's so much
unfinished business.
- Look, Nash.
- Right.
- Barry doesn't know
about this.
He'll be crushed if he knew
that I lost
anything of Nora's, so.
Could you maybe not mention
me being down here?
- Maybe you should mention
why you're down here.
- It'll be our little secret.
- I always knew I liked you.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Loring's office is right up
those stairs.
Last one there
buys the Gingold.
- Hey!
Freeze!
Stop or we'll shoot!
♪ ♪
[door creaks]
- At least he's not a pack rat.
- Focus.
- Um...
♪ ♪
Not finding it.
- Search faster.
♪ ♪
- Think I've got something.
- That's not a ledger.
- No, it's a key
for a safety deposit box
at the CC Mercantile Bank.
Where I'm guessing your ex hid
the ledger for safe keeping.
- Good point.
Time to go.
♪ ♪
- Whoa!
Uh, we have a problem.
- Do you trust me?
- Define trust.
- Hang on.
- Are you crazy?
- Sometimes?
Don't let go.
[arm stretching]
- [screaming]
♪ ♪
We just...
You just...
You're the Elongated Man?
- Yeah, I'm just
full of surprises.
♪ ♪
- How...how did you become
the Elongated Man, anyway?
- I was brutally
experimented on
by a covert organization
for years.
They forced me to consume
rubber-based polymer compounds.
- Seriously?
- No.
- I rode a bus.
- So you're, like,
an honest-to-God superhero.
What's that like?
- It's like any other
job you love.
It's rewarding as hell.
But boy, the hours?
Let me tell you.
- Seriously.
You're like a...
good person.
- I helped you get a key.
It's no ledger.
- Well, Loring's ledger
will definitely be in the box
that goes with this.
- Now we know where the box
is located.
- All we have to do
is open it.
- And then you can get back
to your life.
- Listen...
I want you to know
how much I appreciate you
trusting me with your secret.
It means a lot.
- Uh...
I can call my friends at CCPD
and get a warrant
for Loring's deposit box.
Shouldn't take
more than a day.
- We don't have a day.
Loring's already spooked.
He could move that box
at any minute.
I feel like our
only chance at...
nah, it's too crazy.
- Come on.
Share your thoughts
with the class.
- [sighs]
What if...
We break into
CC Mercantile Bank now?
Just us.
And take the ledger
for ourselves.
- Believe that's
called stealing.
- Oh, come on, Slick.
You're also a P.I.
You can't tell me you've always
operated by the book.
- No, but I can't
commit a crime.
- I get it.
And I respect that.
But Ralph,
I'm not a hero.
So if this is
the only chance I have
to see my parents again,
I have to take it.
- Sue...
being a hero,
it's about helping
innocent people.
I'm not gonna let you
do this alone.
- You're not?
- No.
But we do this my way.
We get inside,
get the ledger,
and immediately bring it
to my friends at CCPD.
Deal or no deal?
- Deal.
- So?
What did you find out?
- These scorch marks.
- Mm-hmm.
- They're giant burns like
sunlight through
a magnifying glass.
- So in your expert
CSI opinion...
- The fire was started
by UV light rays.
Same way Dr. Light torched
"The Citizen."
- [sighs]
- All right, Joe.
What's going on?
- Look, this isn't
the only file I found
where it looks like something
had fallen through the cracks.
All of these cases involve
accidental deaths.
All the victims are associated
with this guy Joseph Carver.
I'm start to think that
somebody here in CCPD
is helping him cover this up.
♪ ♪
- You think
there's a mole here?
- Carver's influence
runs deep, man.
Governors, mayor, CEOs.
- Okay, all right, um,
look, this is what Iris
is already investigating.
Her lead had to do
with the mirror gun
that we stole from McCulloch
Technologies last year.
It fell through because
I wouldn't give it to her.
- Why didn't you
give it to her?
I mean, was it dangerous?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it could
put her in danger.
Yeah, I don't trust
what the world might do
if that gun got out there.
- Yeah, well,
the world is crazy,
but it's clear that Carver
is really dangerous.
Iris is your partner
and family,
and I don't think
we can trust this right now
with anybody other than family.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry you're not gonna
see your husband again,
but it's easier
if you just accept it.
- Eva, you said that you wanna
go back to your old life.
Look, maybe it's gone,
but you can start a new one.
- I'm glad it's broken.
- [sighs]
[sniffles]
I'm tired of looking at a world
that doesn't want me anyway.
I'm tired of waiting for
someone to come and rescue me.
And I'm sick and tired of
people
telling me that everything
is gonna be all right.
Because it isn't.
It's never gonna be all right!
Never!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What just happened?
- I think we just found
our way out of here.
♪ ♪
- And you're sure
this is necessary?
- A credible tip
came in to CCPD
saying this branch was
a target for robbery, so yes.
- Well, this is the only way
in or out of the vault.
The inner gate is fitted
with an anti-theft
electrical system.
Opening or closing it without
the manager's key
automatically activates
a 50,000 volt fail-safe.
- An electric fence
to keep the cattle in.
- Yeah.
- Smart.
Thanks, pal.
[Taser buzzes]
- [grunts]
- Sweet Fancy Moses.
- Mmm.
Huh, I understand why people
are grossed out when I do that.
- Your turn, Slick.
- Oh, right.
[stretching]
You know, besides a passion
for fisticuffs
you've got a real knack
for detective work.
You ever think about
getting behind a desk?
- Ugh, that sounds worse
than my boarding school.
Or the times
my parents made me take
horseback riding lessons.
Or learning French
every Saturday
at the US Embassy in Paris.
- Gee, your childhood
sounds just awful.
- I didn't say it was awful.
It just wasn't me.
The truth is,
I always hated
the whole socialite scene.
Which is why, one day,
I woke up and realized
I had no idea who I was.
Guess I still haven't figured
out exactly where I belong.
- [scoffs]
- Poor little rich girl.
How could she be so lost?
- No, I...
I get it.
I used to wear that uniform
you've got on.
I was a cop.
A damn good one.
And then that ended abruptly,
and I got lost too.
And I rode that bus,
and found where I belong.
- So you're saying
there's hope for me?
- There is from where
I'm standing.
- So, partner.
- [laughs]
- It's a big moment.
You mind if I do the honors?
- Of course.
You earned it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Found it.
- Must be a tiny ledger.
Now what do you say we get out
of here and play "Mario Kart"...
[yells]
♪ ♪
[groans]
[door clangs]
What the hell?
[door slams]
- I guess you're not the only
one that's full of surprises.
- We are this close
to taking down Loring.
[screams]
Sue, why are you doing this?
- Who cares about Loring?
I don't even know the guy.
I do, however,
know where
he keeps his valuables.
- [exhales]
[grunts]
There never was a ledger.
- Keep going.
- That's why you rented
an apartment in Central City.
You knew I was keeping
tabs on you,
so...
so you lured me in.
You rigged your own apartment
to explode for...
for what?
Just to sell the story of...
of sympathetic socialite
running for her life?
- You bought it.
But don't feel bad.
You're a good guy.
And a hero.
You probably see the best
in everyone.
Me, I see what I want
and I take it.
- You used my detective mind
to track down Loring's
deposit box.
You...you played everyone.
Your parents are desperate
to find you.
Do they even know
what you really are?
- No.
That's our little secret.
If they found out their only
daughter was a thief,
they'd be devastated.
So you keep your mouth shut
about who I am,
I keep mine shut
about who you are.
Deal, Elongated Man?
- Sue, was anything
you told me real?
- Yes.
And no.
See you around, Slick.
♪ ♪
[guns cocking]
CCPD.
You're all under arrest.
- Nice try, officer.
But I have a silent alarm
on my deposit box.
So I know you stole
that from me.
♪ ♪
- No phone.
Can't stretch through
these bars
without getting
seriously toasty.
♪ ♪
Always come prepared.
- You don't wanna do this.
- Yeah, I do.
I'm that guy.
- [struggling]
[object clinks]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
You're not getting rid of me
that easily.
- [clears throat]
- Give us a minute.
- Kill 'em both.
- [stretches]
- I'm inside you?
Do you have any idea
how disgusting this is?
- I'm saving your life.
- No, you're not.
We are not partners.
I have handled being
shot at before.
- Why does that
not surprise me?
- Let me out.
- Sure, I'll let you out.
And then I'll take you
to Iron Heights
as soon as these idiots
run out of ammo.
- Ugh, do you ever shut up?
Do something.
- I am doing something.
What's your contribution to
this quaint little scenario?
Oh, wait, nothing.
This is all your fault.
[fabric unzips]
- Always come prepared.
[men grunting]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Spanish]
- Is there anyone that
doesn't want to kill you?
- Not really.
♪ ♪
- I have really gotta
learn Spanish.
[creaking]
[yells]
[grunts]
[groans]
- You want the diamond?
Come and get it.
[both speaking Spanish]
[both grunting]
[Dead Sara's "Heaven's Got
A Back Door" playing]
- ♪ Maybe heaven's
got a back door too ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Heaven's got
a back door too ♪
♪ Out of walls I heard
the voices of the preacher ♪
♪ Telling me all the reasons
why I'd die alone ♪
♪ I've never been
your perfect song ♪
♪ Your favorite daughter ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Heaven's got
a back door too ♪
- Looks like
we've both been had.
- [screams]
- She softened him up.
Let's finish the job.
[guns cocking]
♪ ♪
- It's all yours,
Captain West.
- Thanks, Flash.
Clear this out, guys.
- Hey, bud.
- Flash.
- Yeah.
- It's him.
He's the one who robbed us.
- Excuse me?
- That's a case of mistaken
identity, sir.
I'm sure Captain West
can explain.
It's all right.
Hey man, I'm sorry
I got word late,
but I searched the whole area.
Ultraviolet's gone.
Couldn't stop her.
But don't worry, we'll get her.
I promise.
- I wasn't talking about
Ultraviolet.
- Loring's in custody,
but facial recognition
isn't picking her up anywhere
in Central City.
- Looks like Sue Dearbon
has vanished.
Again.
- That's on me.
She played me, Iris.
Like...Coltrane's soprano sax.
- Ralph, you can't beat
yourself up.
I mean, it's not like you knew
who you were dealing with.
- I'm supposed to be
a master detective!
- Ralph, we've all put
our trust in people
who have betrayed us.
God knows I have.
- I'm gonna go tear down
my crime board.
♪ ♪
- It's gonna take him a while
to get over this one.
- Hey, Joe told me that you
came by CCPD today.
I think I know why
you didn't come say hi.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- What happened to it
falling into the wrong hands?
- These are the right hands.
Joe and I found evidence
linking Carver's assassins
to more killings.
Crimes that CCPD thought
were accidents.
Black Hole is a lot more
dangerous than I even realized.
But if you can use this in your
investigation in any way
to bring down Carver
and his people faster,
then that's a good thing.
And while I don't
trust the world...
I do trust you.
With everything.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- You have a connection
to the mirror, even
when it's broken.
- Now who sounds crazy?
- I've seen a lot of strange
things in the last six years.
You being able to control that
mirror is the least of it.
Sam Scudder could even
travel through them.
- Well, I'm not a meta-criminal
who jumps through mirrors
to rob banks.
- I know.
You're much more than that.
We're the only people
in this world, Eva,
so trust me when I say that
you're stronger than you think.
You're a survivor.
Now prove it.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- You did it.
Now keep going.
- [exhales]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
1,323...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm still with you.
- How did I do that?
♪ ♪
- I don't know.
But I promise you,
we will figure it out.
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- Game on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.