BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multi-verse,
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was
only to find things
weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
IRIS: Previously on The Flash...
We have to think about
getting back to our Earth.
We've been here long enough.
A whole multi-verse of
Harrison Wells out there.
You want one? Let's go get one.
Wells with a sense of humor.
- Harrison.
- Call me H.R.
Out with the old. In with the new.
What are you doing here? "Julian Albert,
Meta-Human CSI specialist"?
I don't trust you.
And I don't like things
that I don't trust.
How have I worked with this guy
for the past year?
You say that all the time.
Do you maybe want to
grab some dinner tonight?
I got movie night with
my kids tonight, rain check?
You were the only one who wasn't affected
when I messed with the timeline.
Yo!
You know you don't need
to do this every morning, right?
Come on, it's the least I can do.
I mean, I love Joe, but at some point,
man needs his own space,
and until I find my own space,
that means your space.
So, as a token of my appreciation...
Two eggs over easy. Bacon, toast.
I can't remember,
do you like it buttered or not?
Barry, sometimes a man
just wants to butter his own bread.
Okay, sorry. I was just...
Yeah, no, you're right.
Look, don't... Don't get it twisted, okay?
I love having you here.
You're a great guest. Not sure how
I feel about our other visitor though.
- Wells?
- "Please, call me H.R."
So, you don't like him?
Well, it's not so much
that I don't like him. I just...
The way he says things,
there's something about him.
I don't know what it is.
Dude, he's only been here a few days.
Let him settle in.
I know we've had
our Wells issues in the past,
but you can't just stop trusting everybody
or giving them chances, you know?
You can't live like that.
This is true. Wise words from a wise man.
Joe knowledge.
I'm gonna take this to go.
- Okay, all right.
- Yeah, I'll see you there.
Yeah, well, I can take you.
No. No. I'm gonna drive myself today.
Yeah, cool. Cool.
- Can I help you?
- I'm here to see Dr. Tannhauser.
Do you have an appointment?
No, but I'm pretty sure she'll see me.
You can just tell her
Caitlin Snow is here.
Dr. Tannhauser is a very busy woman.
I'm sure you can understand.
I appreciate the diligence, Jackie,
but Caitlin's always welcome here.
Even if I wish she'd call first.
Nice to see you, too, Mom.
So, what brings you here?
Well, I didn't forget your birthday,
did I? I'm pretty sure I sent a card.
You did. In April.
Thank you.
Look, I read your new paper
on applications in cryo-medicine,
and I think you might be able to help.
I had no idea you kept up on
the literature over at S.T.A.R. Labs.
That's still what it's called, right?
Yes, and I have a patient
who could use your help.
Well, if you want to send over the file,
I'll be happy to take a look
when I have a chance.
But right now, I have
a shareholder meeting to prepare for...
Mom!
I'm the patient.
Cancel my appointments.
And have Nigel meet me in the biolab.
We have work to do.
Sumptuous day!
Oh, no.
On this Earth, I believe you say...
- Good morning.
- H.R.: Good morning.
And it is. Isn't it? I mean...
The music on your Earth, well,
it strikes a chord, no pun intended.
Please, help yourself.
I find a crew works best
when it's well-fed and well-rested.
Are those coffees for us, too?
Yes indeed, Miss West.
I took the liberty of
reading through your ledgers last night.
A lot of information to absorb,
but let's see how I did.
Skim milk chai latte.
Okay!
Okay! And an iced Americano
with two... No, three
shots of espresso.
That happened, Walter.
- It's Wally.
- Wally!
Now, for my fleet of foot friend...
You'd best stick to decaf.
Probably for the best, yeah.
San Francisco.
I have prepared a French roast
with a touch of creamer.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Did you know on my Earth
coffee crop was wiped out by blight?
I mean, that's one more reason to
stay on this Earth, for the coffee alone.
Yeah, well, that's if you stay.
If I stay, time is of the essence.
Here's what I propose.
A series of team-building exercises.
Now, I've hidden a series of clues
all around the facility.
What I propose is,
we break into two groups, all right?
And you can pick a partner.
You know what...
Okay. I have to stop you, H.R.
I am not feeling this.
It's the roast, isn't it?
I should have gone with a dark...
No, it's not the roast, the roast is fine.
Our trust isn't something that
you can just build with games.
- Okay?
- No.
This is something
that goes back three years.
It's something that's been forged in fire.
Sometimes literally.
So, maybe you should just
step back and observe.
See what we do here, how we operate.
Did you get that?
Excellent note. I'm gonna run with that.
Where's Caitlin, by the way?
Have you seen...
- Yes, so she was here.
- She was?
- All right, yeah, you know, we talked...
- What?
And she knocked back
a triple-shot latte,
and she left you a message.
So, I'm gonna...
Yeah, let me just play it for you.
This is not the same as my Earth's.
This is a different... There it is.
CAITLIN: Hey, it's me. I've got
some things I need to take care of.
I shouldn't be gone more than a few days.
See if you can get along without me.
Make sure Cisco
doesn't touch my pizza pockets.
Wasn't labeled.
Okay, you know what, guys?
I gotta go to work. I'm...
Ooh. Yeah. I gotta do that, too.
- Yeah, let's go.
- I gotta bail.
You know, we'll do
the team building exercises another...
I'll leave the clues
hidden in the facility.
Cool. How do you guys say
"see you later" over there?
Until next communion.
- All right, see you later.
- See you later.
So weird.
CAPTAIN: Come.
Hey! Sorry I'm late.
I had to meet somebody and...
We can add tardiness to the list, Captain.
Allen, it's been brought to my attention
that you've been
giving yourself unauthorized access
to your colleagues' case files.
- Excuse me?
- JULIAN: Along with multiple infractions.
Repeated absences,
disappearing throughout the day,
phone call interruptions,
guests in the lab.
The list is pretty extensive, Captain.
I'm sorry.
With all due respect, I do my job here.
You do good work here, Allen.
Don't put that in jeopardy
by thinking the rules don't apply to you.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
Sorry, Captain, that's it?
- Sir, I document eight different...
- Nine.
Nine different violations of regulations
and he gets a 15-second talking to?
Must be nice.
CAPTAIN: We are done here.
You can go.
Captain.
Were you really just being a tattletale?
That's bush league, man.
You know what? You're right.
It's silly of me to think the rules
actually apply to the golden boy
of C.C.P.D.'s crime lab.
Detective.
He's unbelievable.
You know what? I wish you two could
be a little less oil and water
and a little bit more oil and vinegar.
You guys have been
at each other's throats for a year now.
That's just it.
From my perspective, it's been two weeks.
So, you're saying that
before two weeks ago,
you weren't Julian's enemy?
I'm saying before two weeks ago,
Julian didn't even exist.
Because of your Flashpoint.
I know it's
because of the Flashpoint. I...
It's Cisco, hold on.
BARRY: Hey, is this important?
I don't know, does 30 hits downtown
on the meta-human app count?
What are we looking at?
Well, nothing really.
Every traffic camera in a 10-block radius
suddenly went down, so we're flying blind.
And the hits were all over the map.
All right, well, there's one way
to see what's going on. I gotta go.
CISCO: Most of the chatter is
coming from the harbor district.
All right, I'm here.
It's a bad scene, man.
CISCO: You should be
right on top of it, Barry. What is it?
It's a monster?
Guys, did you hear me?
There is a monster in Central City.
What are we talking? Yao Ming size?
Or Andre the Giant?
No, it's like an actual monster.
- What even makes that?
- I don't even know that.
S.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
show me something.
Whoa. Ever see anything like that
on Earth-19?
You want me to observe. I'll just observe.
WOMAN: We're in here!
Iris, what are you doing here?
Working on a story.
And last time I checked,
you don't need super-speed
and a red suit to help people.
All right, get out of here.
I'm gonna try to stop that thing.
Come on, come on!
- Cisco, where'd it go?
- CISCO: Can't track it if I can't see it.
You know what you could do?
You could use your ears.
- My ears?
- What's that sound?
It's a car alarm.
I could use the car alarms
to track the direction
the monster's heading in.
We got him. Head north three blocks.
I lost him.
Yeah, me, too.
I don't get it. I don't get it.
Every meta-human we've encountered
has been exactly that, meta-human.
So, where did this thing come from?
I don't know where it came from, man.
It just vanished.
That's all I know. It was gone.
Yeah, but in my experience,
things are always different.
- What?
- Than they appear.
There must be a reason the darn thing
can just disappear like that.
Maybe the darn thing's got
some kind of cloaking mechanism.
Uh, that's a good idea,
but right now I would settle for,
"How can we stop it?"
- Yes, obviously.
- How?
- I don't know.
- We don't have a magic monster lasso.
H.R.: But you know what we could...
Oh, sorry, I forgot. I'm just observing.
No, H.R., please,
we're open to any idea right now.
On my Earth, we have ropes
made out of carbon fiber.
They are ultralight,
but strong enough to pull a battleship.
We could restrain it with that.
Right? What do you think?
- Okay, I think it's...
- Okay.
I think it's worth a shot.
We can spin it down in my workshop.
Yes. Good.
Yeah, there was something else
that was weird, though.
I saw a transformer explode
as this thing passed by it.
- That is weird.
- What's weird about that?
Monster didn't even lay a finger on it.
It exploded before it got to it.
Kind of reminds me of that Hitchcock movie
where the extra covers his ears
before the gun goes off.
You have Hitchcock on this Earth?
Oh, brilliant.
Murder on the Titanic! "Who did it?"
"Who cares? We're drowning."
The beast must emit
some kind of electrical pulse.
Is there a way I could
get a look at that transformer?
No. The whole place is a crime scene now,
with Julian in charge of it.
Ah, Julian. Who's that?
That's the CSI guy you don't like, right?
I mean...
Yeah, all right.
He's great.
Sorry. Cold hands.
I didn't even notice.
- I'm Nigel, by the way.
- Nice to meet you.
We're gonna
help you figure this out, Caitlin.
Let's get you to the lab.
CAITLIN: What's this?
DR. TANNHAUSER: It's to test how your
ability affects molecular motion.
That shaft is solid tungsten,
and it's heated to
over 2,000 degrees centigrade.
I want you to cool it down.
And when we determine how you can do that,
we can figure out
the best way to help you.
Best we could do in such little time.
So, this is where
you've been for the last hour.
I had to
reschedule my day for this, Caitlin.
A lot of things around here
require my attention.
I remember.
Whenever you're ready.
Don't hold back.
Hey, Julian.
You seen this?
It's bad enough
we have the metas destroying the city.
- Now we have this thing to worry about.
- Mmm-hmm.
Is there any point in me asking
where you've been for the last hour?
Or should I just assume
the rules still don't apply to you?
I was, um...
Yes, okay.
Look. Hey, man, so I know that you and I,
we got off on the wrong foot.
We never managed to find the right one,
and I'll take that.
That's probably my fault,
but, um, I just...
I don't want things
to be like that anymore, you know?
I'd like it if things changed.
It's funny, 'cause I remember you
saying something similar to that
right before you stole
the case from underneath me.
Do you have any idea
what it's like to work side by side
with someone
with such little regard for the rules?
You may very well
be contaminating my work.
That's exactly why I wanna learn from you.
I don't follow.
You know, whenever I read your reports,
it's clear that
your evidence collection techniques are
far superior to mine.
Go on.
I don't know. I mean,
if I could just shadow you for a day,
maybe ask a few questions,
I think that you could really
help bring my skills up to snuff.
What do you say?
Sorry.
What if I gave up the lab?
There's a storeroom downstairs
that I could convert,
so if you let me
follow you on this case, lab's yours.
Lab's mine?
Okay. Deal.
You can't slow me down, though.
- I would never.
- All right. I'll call you.
How long have you had these abilities?
They started manifesting a few months ago,
but I'm assuming I got them when
the particle accelerator exploded,
just like all the other metas.
- And you haven't told anyone?
- Just you.
I told you, you never should have
taken that job at S.T.A.R. Labs.
You could've stayed here,
had access to world-class facilities.
And have all of my work
be in the shadow of your reputation.
Of course, the only time
you need your mother
is when you're in trouble.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, come on, darling.
You ran off to Central City
to play scientist
with that disgraced quack.
I was trying to make a name for myself.
For three years, barely a word,
until trouble hits,
and then here you come, walking through
the door and expecting Mommy
to drop everything in her life
to try to fix it.
You have no idea what I've been through.
Dr. Tannhauser, look at this.
She's absorbed all that energy? How?
I'm not sure yet,
but if we can figure that out,
this could
change everything we're doing here.
So then the Flash, my Flash again,
not your Flash, we hatched a plan
to gather all the remaining meta-humans
into one place for a final showdown.
They called it "World War M."
It was glorious.
Two forces on opposing sides
of the stadium. The tension built.
No. It was like that movie,
the gladiator was the lead gladiator.
What was that called?
Gladiator.
That's better. On my Earth, it was
called Sweaty Men. That didn't take.
So, the two forces charge into battle,
and when they do...
- I need to take a five.
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
- Let's take a...
- By myself.
Yeah, you go ahead.
I'll keep working on this.
So, entry triple A, colon, two.
Plan is proceeding.
Characters are in place.
Nobody seems the wiser as to why I'm here.
Hey.
I had to give
a witness report on the attack,
and I thought I would
make it a lunch date.
Yeah, cool. I'll clear a spot.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Are things any better with Julian?
Oh, my God, it's like every time
I try to get to know the guy,
he does something
that makes it really hard to.
All I know now is
that he dislikes meta-humans
about as much as he dislikes me.
Maybe you should try
and see things from his perspective.
He might have a reason
to dislike both of you
that you don't know anything about.
Did you just hit me with a Joe-ism?
Well, sometimes he's right.
- Sometimes he's not.
- Yeah.
Speaking of which,
I just saw him downstairs,
and he was talking to the DA.
He blew off a date with her.
I saw him do the same thing last week.
I don't know. Maybe he's not into her.
No, he's into her.
I mean, when I asked him about her,
he basically told me to buzz off.
You're not too good at buzzing off,
are you?
Nope. When it comes to my dad, no.
Well, look who it is.
Looks like I have an opportunity
to see things from Julian's perspective
right now.
Sorry about lunch. I gotta go.
See you later. I need that.
If you don't stop squirming,
I'll never find a vein.
What exactly are you testing for now?
Any polymorphism that could help us
understand how you're able to absorb
that much energy from molecules
to create gelid surroundings.
You realize
I've run all of these tests already?
Then, what was the point of coming here?
Seriously, Mom?
I'm terrified of what I'm becoming.
You realize you haven't
asked me once how I'm feeling?
I'm trying to keep emotion out of this.
Believe me, it's for your benefit
as much as it is mine.
Right, because that's your specialty,
isn't it?
Being cold, just like after...
After what?
After Dad died.
I did everything I could
to save your father.
Well, you lost your daughter
at the same time.
You're the one who went away, Caitlin.
Because I had to.
You realize you never acted
like my mother again after Dad got sick?
You barely even look at me.
I couldn't handle the pain.
My work got me through it.
Losing someone like that.
You have no idea what that feels like.
Actually, I do.
My husband died over a year ago.
I'm sorry.
What do you got?
I said get here quick,
but that was quicker than I expected.
No, yeah, it was a crazy Uber driver.
Well, the blast pattern
and the scoring on the insulation
suggests that
it was a power surge that blew it out.
So, it's a coincidence?
I highly doubt it. But I'll figure it out.
Someone in this city has to
do something about these metas.
What do you mean?
We have a whole police force
working to stop these metas.
No, you have the Flash.
So, it's not just bad metas
you don't like. It's all the metas.
I'm just saying that because of him,
the police department has got lethargic.
I mean, why do anything at all
if the Flash is gonna
save the day every time?
It's a bit like you with
the rule breaking. A momentary fix,
and now you're lazy, sloppy.
Cool. Thanks.
Uh, I think the Flash is actually
a source of inspiration for the city.
I think he kind of provides hope.
Yes, that's one of many things that
we'll have to disagree on, Allen.
What? Do you see something?
A pattern. The creature's movements,
they seemed random at first,
but they were contained
to a prescribed area.
You know, like the creature was
stuck in an invisible fence.
Traffic cameras were down, right?
Maybe it was being watched
or controlled by somebody that
needed to keep it
in visual range the entire time?
Constricting the creature's movements
to the line of sight.
That actually makes sense.
Maybe there is
a brain in there after all, Allen.
Dispatch, this is CSI.
I'm requesting immediate backup.
The monster has been sighted
by the harbor.
- Hey, maybe we should split up.
- No, that's a terrible idea.
Yeah, but we gotta do something, right?
Don't worry, I have
four years training in the military.
Even still, since when
does a CSI carry a gun?
Since there were monsters in our city.
All right...
Cheers.
NIGEL: You're leaving us?
Yeah, things between
my mother and me are...
- Complicated.
- We can help you.
I don't need your help with the science.
I can do that on my own.
I came here to get something
from my mother that I realize now.
I'll never get.
What are you doing?
Sorry, Frosty,
but you're not going anywhere.
Let me out of here. Open these doors.
I said no!
I am sick of working day after day,
night after night,
only to have my work benefit your mother.
With the information I can get from you,
I can finally get out of this place.
So, you're gonna stay here
until I get everything that I need.
You are not going to test me.
Yes, I am.
No, Nigel.
You are not going to test me, now or ever.
Wait, let go! Let go!
Caitlin! Don't do this!
This isn't you!
You don't know anything about me, Mother.
I know I wasn't much of a mother,
and I know I have a lot to make up for,
but I know I didn't raise a killer.
For whatever it's worth, I am so sorry.
It's worth a lot.
- Now go.
- What about...
I'll take care of him. No one will
ever know about this. I promise.
- Thank you.
- Just go.
Every time there's been
a sighting of the monster,
multiple transformers have blown.
Hmm. So, it's definitely
feeding off electricity.
And see, I mapped out all the streets
that it's been spotted around.
Never leaves a 10-block radius.
Yeah, this is exactly
what I was talking about.
Some meta's been gifted
this incredible power,
and this is the very best thing
they can do with it,
terrorize a city. It's pathetic.
But why exactly do you hate metas so much?
If you think I'm going to break down now
and tell you that one killed my parents
and that's why I have to do this job,
I'm not, okay? I don't need a deep,
personal reason to hate metas, Allen.
I just need to see
person after person transformed,
given these extraordinary abilities,
and watch them be squandered.
Robbing banks, hurting people,
spreading fear. It's just...
Well, it's not just a crime.
It's an absolute waste.
Can you imagine what it would be like
to have those powers?
I mean, I'd be helping people.
I would be improving the world.
I guess I wasn't
one of the chosen few, was I?
That's it? You're mad at them
because you weren't chosen?
Sorry, I mean, I'm just saying,
it can't be easy being a meta-human,
having your life,
their lives change in ways that,
you know, neither one of us
could possibly imagine.
It's got to take some adjusting.
Right. So, now you're defending them?
Well, no, I mean, I'm...
I don't think that...
This internship thing we're doing
is completely over.
Whatever.
- Transformers are the key...
- No, I agree.
Anytime the monster's shown up,
any nearby have exploded.
- Yeah, they blow up.
- Car alarms keep malfunctioning, too.
Car alarms, transformers.
What is the connection?
Yeah, we'll get there, fellas.
We'll get there.
We just got to keep trying.
Maybe someone's
pulling power out of the transformers
and using it to power the monster.
Power, yes, the monster. That's...
You just beat me to it, San Francisco.
- See, that can't be it, H.R.
- Can't be it.
'Cause we would've
detected a surge in the power grid.
- We did not.
- Not if it was broadcast power.
Something like a portable Tesla tower?
A portable Tesla power.
- Tower.
- Tower. That's what it is.
Nice... Mmm-mmm. Teamwork.
So, PS, where I'm from, on my Earth,
we call that a problem solved.
I'm gonna go for coffee.
On my Earth, the coffee was wiped out.
- Blight, yeah.
- By blight, can you imagine?
He didn't really do anything, did he?
Thank you. Took me a while to realize it,
but he's just resaying everything
that we're saying in a different way.
No, he did have the idea for the rope.
Reverse inception. He made you think
he had the idea for the rope,
but he didn't even tell us how to use it.
Yeah, well, we're not gonna be
caught off guard again.
We should vibe him.
It'd be my pleasure.
Hey-oh.
- Hey, baby girl.
- Hey.
You've been hanging out here a lot lately.
Yeah, well, there's a lot of scared people
with this monster running around the city.
We'll get him. We always do.
Yeah? Is that a quote
I can use for my article?
- No.
- All right. It was worth a try.
Dad, you know Wally and I
are all right, right?
What is that supposed to mean?
We just don't want you to
not do things because of us.
You know, we just want you
to find someone.
I'm not having this conversation with you.
Dad, that DA is totally into you.
You should go out with her.
Iris, I don't need you to be Cupid.
I got my job.
I got you, Barry, Wally. I'm good.
I know, Dad, and that, that's great.
I just...
Now that I'm falling in love with someone,
I just want you to have the same thing.
Joe? Alert every task force
and sniper unit. Tell 'em to load up.
- I should get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- What's up?
Albert thinks he's figured out
the creature's next target.
If there's ever an opportunity for
a 40-foot monster to wreak havoc,
it's gonna be where people like to gather.
2nd Street Promenade.
Well, let's end this.
That's what I intend to do, Detective.
- Where'd he go?
- Doesn't matter. I don't need him.
What do you mean? What are you...
Hey, dude. Come on.
You can't just go through his stuff,
that's not...
I'm not going through his stuff.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
What even is this?
Now I seem to have won most of
the team's trust, except Francisco's.
Those are my things. What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What?
Who are you really?
We know you're hiding something.
You've been burned, twice,
by a man with the same face as me.
I imagine it's hard to trust
after something like that.
- You think?
- I do think. So play the rest of it.
I've read his journals.
I've found nothing that can tell me
why Francisco feels the way he does,
but I do hope I can change
his opinion of Harrison Wells,
and the two of us
can rebuild that friendship.
What a fantastic C story
to weave within the narrative.
What?
What narrative?
Narrative.
I'm writing a novel.
The Tales of H. R. Wells. Catchy, I know.
Wait, I'm sorry,
you're a scientist and a novelist?
- Yes.
- Wow. That's perfect.
Thank you. That's exactly right.
I'm a scientist and a novelist.
I run S.T.A.R. Labs, and also
I'm an author of a science romance.
That's my niche. Write what you know.
And I thought, "Well..."
"What better opportunity than to come
to another Earth and pen yet another"
"best seller about my adventures here?"
Why didn't you just
tell us this in the first place?
I guess it didn't seem relevant, and also,
I didn't think you guys were
gonna rifle through my belongings.
That's all it is.
I'm a scientist and a novelist.
Do you think you can trust me now,
or is that not something that
you have on this Earth? Trust?
- Trust?
- Oh!
You scared the dickens out of me.
Trust who?
- It's the app.
- It's the monster. It's back.
Monster?
Yeah, you've missed a lot.
I'll explain upstairs.
Well, I'll just stay here, then.
Come on. We need you.
All right, guys. I'm here.
Tell us everything that you see right now.
Mayhem. And the monster.
- Okay, so what's the plan?
- Great question, Miss West.
So we've fashioned
just a carbon fiber rope,
but correct me if I'm wrong,
we never actually discussed
how he was gonna use that rope, did we?
Guys.
- Barry, we're gonna do Empire.
- Empire of the Sun, Barry.
- What? Empire Strikes Back.
- Empire Strikes Back, Barry.
- Just take it down like it was an AT-AT.
- Just like an AT-AT.
Bigger they are, the harder they fall.
Even I've seen Empire.
- I like that.
- I like you.
All right, here we go.
I've always wanted to be a Jedi.
Guys? Rope went right through it.
It's a hologram.
Well, that explains everything.
The 10-block radius, the transformers.
It takes that much power to render.
- Wait, C.C.P.D. sent snipers there.
- If it's not real...
Then the bullets
will pass right through it.
- BARRY: Guys, it's gone. Where is it?
- Hold on. Give me a sec, Barr.
Okay, we don't have a second!
H.R., triangulate the signal
being sent to the monster.
We have to disrupt it
before anyone gets hurt.
Okay, let's do that now.
Let's... Let's just triangulate.
The computer doesn't
triangulate the signal the way...
Not the way I'm used to.
This is a different size computer for...
- Oh, my God. I knew it.
- What?
You're a fake.
- This whole time, he's been acting
like he can help us, but he can't,
because he doesn't know how! Does he?
How? Triangulate!
- BARRY: Guys, which way?
- Get the...
All right, you take over.
CISCO: Found it.
It's at Second and Fulton.
OFFICER 1: I have a lock on the target.
OFFICER 2: Fire when ready.
Stop! Stop firing! It's a hologram!
OFFICER 2: Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
OFFICER 1: A hologram?
OFFICER 3: Where'd it go?
Detective West, where's Julian?
He was here!
Cisco, I need that location.
Hamilton Building, 25th floor.
There's more power going there
than anywhere else in
the building combined.
Line of sight to all the attacks.
That's where he is.
JULIAN: I said put your hands up!
This is C.C.P.D.! Freeze!
Stop what you're doing!
I said put your hands up!
You're just a kid.
Yeah, a kid you almost killed!
You're gonna pay for that one, buddy.
You're gonna...
Yeah, I don't think so, man.
I think you're the one
that's gonna be paying for
all the damage you did to this city.
For a very long time.
Hey, Flash.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come on.
Do you realize how many innocent people
could have been hurt, or worse?
What made you do something like this?
I just wanted
to feel powerful for a change.
And that did it? Scaring people?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, it did.
You know, the kids at my school,
they tease me every day.
I'm the weirdo there. And I'm just
sick of feeling scared all the time.
I just wanted someone else
to feel that way for a change.
Look...
I know sometimes
things are hard at your age.
But trust me, it does get better.
So, what happens now?
Well, there are severe consequences
for what you did,
and you're just gonna have to accept that.
But listen, you're young.
You can turn all of this around.
All right. Come on.
You were named
"Entrepreneur of the Decade"
- by Tech Magazine?
- That's right.
Is any of what's on here true?
- All of it.
- CISCO: How?
You can barely turn on a computer.
There are two parts to every idea.
There is the inception and the execution.
- I provide the former.
- So, you come up with the ideas?
Yeah, I don't know how to implement them.
I'm the idea man.
So you didn't actually solve
the cryptogram that we sent you?
No, that was my partner
at S.T.A.R. Labs on my Earth.
I'm the face of the company.
I'm more of the inspiration
behind the company.
Then I was exposed.
Well, people thought that I was
something that I guess I wasn't.
Anyway, it...
It kind of all fell apart for me.
But then I got your message.
My partner brought me your message.
I realized he's bringing me an opportunity
to come to this Earth to write this book.
So many planets in the multi-verse,
and we happen to pick
the one Wells who's not a scientist.
You're right.
I wasn't completely honest with you,
with all of you.
I feel badly about that. I regret that.
But let me ask you a question.
Has there been none
amongst you that has ever shaded the truth
for what you believe
to be the greater good?
- It sounds to me like you're a con man.
- Yeah.
Was I a con man when I showed
San Francisco here how to track the beast
using car alarms?
Was I a con man when I showed him how to
fashion a rope using carbon fiber?
- I came up with those ideas!
- You were prompted by my suggestions.
That is how ideas work!
People, you need a muse!
I can be your muse.
What about stopping
all the metas on your Earth?
More of an advisory role for me,
but I was there. I remembered how we...
You don't think that's something?
Let me present you with a scenario.
You're confronted with something,
a threat that you've never seen before.
You don't know how to stop it.
Who does? That's value to you.
Let me prove my worth to you.
If I fail, I will...
Right back to my Earth,
but if I succeed,
I will have succeeded not just
in redeeming myself, but also,
I will have done some good with my life.
You know, you're lucky we're pretty big on
redemption and doing good here,
so I think you can,
I don't know, stay for a few weeks,
try to prove yourself,
but if not...
Back to your Earth.
Thank you.
Hey, no more repackaging.
Word is bond.
That, just no more that.
- All right, H.R.
- Okay.
- Where you been?
- I actually went to visit my mother.
Your mother? Oh, boy. Why?
To see if we could work through
some of our issues.
And I think we might actually
be on the road to recovery.
When it comes to family,
you gotta do whatever it takes,
'cause one day,
you might not be able to do that anymore.
Glad you're back.
This is home.
JULIAN: I nearly killed a kid tonight.
The monster we were chasing,
it turns out it was just a hologram
operated by a 15-year-old boy.
Flash came to save the day.
And he saved me from doing something...
- I heard.
- You know what's sad?
That kid, he's just acting
'cause he's scared, you know?
He wants everyone to be terrified
and to run away from the monster
so he can feel powerful.
- I know what that's like.
- How do you mean?
I come from a pretty wealthy family
back in England.
It's a long line of generations of
old money, tradition, nonsense, really,
and I was the heir.
I was their firstborn son.
I was supposed to inherit the lot.
But I was the odd duck
who would rather go in the garden
and collect samples of insects
rather than learn how to tie
a Windsor knot.
Or which fork to use first at dinner.
Yeah. No, I wanted more.
You know?
I came here to do the one thing
that they couldn't stop me from doing:
becoming a scientist,
becoming a great scientist.
Then just as I got to
the top of my field, poof!
The world changes overnight.
Meta-humans. I don't know
a single thing about meta-humans.
I don't know how they talk.
I don't know how they walk.
I certainly don't know
the first thing about stopping them, so
rendered useless.
I suppose that's the monster
that I'm running from now.
Just feeling powerless.
Yeah, I feel the same way
some days, Julian.
I lost my mom when I was a kid.
Lost my dad recently.
It's a scary world. People die.
Trusts are betrayed. Things change.
Change can be a good thing, you know?
It can bring
new experiences,
new opportunities, people.
You can treat 'em like a potential enemy
or like a new friend.
Just trust that everything's
gonna be okay.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
You can stop.
You can stay.
I was really wrong about the Flash,
so I could be wrong about you, too.
Good night, mate.
Julian?
You want to get a drink?
Yeah. Yeah, I'd like that.
All right.
Let's do it.
Caitlin, I've been going over
the data we collected,
and I've found some disconcerting results.
Your body's chemistry is changing
in ways that I don't fully understand,
but one thing is clear.
These powers you have,
the more you use them,
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
I'm sorry, honey, but listen to me.
You must not use these powers
under any circumstances.