- To understand what
I'm about to tell you,
there is something
you need to remember.
In every atom,
there is a perfect balance
of protons and electrons.
But it's those
negative particles
that let an atom grow.
[whooshing]
My name is Dr. Meena Dhawan,
and for the next
three minutes and 52 seconds,
I'm the fastest woman alive.
Oh, my gosh.
Did you see that?
I just hit
300 meters per second.
- That's your best time yet.
Now see if you can keep up.
[whooshing]
- Come on!
Come on, Meena.
[thrilling music]
♪
- [screams]
- Ahh! Ah!
[whooshing]
- [chuckles]
- I'm so sorry.
What just happened?
- You created your
own lightning bolt again.
Something I couldn't do
for months
when I first got my speed.
- I--I didn't mean to do it,
I was just frustrated
I couldn't catch up,
and then it just happened.
[electricity crackling]
- I've never seen
artificial lightning interact
with organic lightning
like this before.
- Okay.
That's disturbing.
- We should--we should
go over your biometrics,
make sure everything else
is within normal parameters.
- Yeah.
[watch chiming]
I--I can't,
I have to head back to the lab.
My speed is running out.
- Okay, tomorrow.
10:00 a.m.
- Hm.
[whooshing]
♪
[heroic music]
- Hi.
I just need
to make a little deposit,
it's in here somewhere.
I have this new client
who decides to pay me in cash.
What year is it?
[gasps] Got it.
There we go, all right.
- Everybody, on the ground!
[people clamoring]
Get down!
Move!
- [grunts]
- Get down!
You--cash in the bag.
Don't even think about
hitting the alarm.
[tense music]
♪
Hey, teacup!
You trying to be a hero?
- I--
[intense music]
♪
- Are you for real?
Get down, lady!
[shimmering tone]
What part of
"Get down on the ground"
don't you understand?
Let's go!
If you don't get on the ground,
I swear to God, lady.
Three, two, one.
♪
[whooshing]
- Ah--ah--ah--
[moaning] No.
Ah! Ah!
♪
[whooshing]
- What am I doing here?
I should have been an engineer.
- I just wanna go home.
No voodoo. Please, no voodoo.
- Oh!
- CCPD!
Stay where you are!
[wondrous music]
♪
- Fiery Frances Sumner.
Still, according to Gideon,
your empathic capacity
is up 1,000 percent.
- [laughs]
- Your brain just
got supercharged.
- Usually, when I sense
a wave of fear and panic,
it just hits me like a train.
- Like when we
fought Blockbuster?
- Exactly, except this
time when my powers kicked in,
I barely broke a sweat.
- Which is all very badass,
but is anyone else
wondering how
the heck this happened?
- Well, I mean, I don't know.
My powers have changed before,
like when Jenna was born.
Maybe it's just natural.
It's possible,
but let's run some more tests
just to make sure.
[shimmering tone]
- Barry?
- Hm?
- I can feel a massive wave
of concern wash over you.
You're worried about something.
It's way more than just me.
- It's the new speedster
I'm training, Meena Dhawan.
During our last
training session,
I got struck by her
artificial lightning.
Now, it was an accident,
but when it hit me,
it collided with my lightning
and it set off
some kind of a biokinetic
chemical reaction.
- Okay, accidental attacks,
artificial speed.
Is she about
to go all Spock Flash?
- No, I don't think so.
I mean, Meena did
find a way to generate
her own speed source
artificially,
but it's not affecting her
like it did me.
I mean, her emotions seem fine.
- So it's just her powers
that are funky.
Well, maybe you should
throw 'em over
to Fast Track Labs,
take a peek at the generator?
See how her speed
machine really works.
[light music]
- Barry Allen?
- Yeah.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- No, no.
- How can I help you?
- Yeah, actually,
I am here on behalf
of a mutual friend
who likes to run fast.
- Oh.
- Yes.
Our friend was hoping
I could take a look
at your--
your special project.
He thinks it'd be a good idea
to get a second set of eyes
on this, just to make sure
everything's safe.
- I understand.
And he's right.
I could use another scientific
eye on all this right now.
- Okay.
- Follow me.
- Yeah.
There she is,
my pride and joy.
- Wow.
Is that an oscillation chamber?
- It's a biometric lightning
oscillation chamber,
technically.
We call it the B.L.O.C.
It's built with
quantum computing
to remotely harness lightning
from the Earth's upper
atmosphere
and turn it
into artificial speed.
- This equipment is decades
ahead of any other lab.
- Oh. Including yours,
I hope?
[chuckles]
I can't take full
credit for all this innovation.
Sure, I can handle the physics,
but my colleague
is more familiar
with the nuts and bolts.
Ah, there he is.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Barry Allen,
meet the man who built
this machine.
- Eobard Thawne.
Nice to meet you, Barry Allen.
♪
- Eobard Thawne.
Nice to meet you, Barry Allen.
[tense music]
♪
- Thawne.
- I'm Chief of Engineering here
at Fast Track Laboratories.
- Eobard, here,
is our only employee who knows
the truth about this project
while I'm still perfecting it.
- And Barry here
is a friend of The Flash.
- Really?
- Yeah, you know The Flash,
don't you?
[both laugh]
- No, I--
- Do you two--
Have you met before?
- [roaring]
- You go to hell!
- You're taking
both of us there!
Now who's the villain, Flash?
Now who's the villain?
No. I mean, I don't--
I don't think so.
But my memory is a little hazy.
- Yeah, um,
Eobard suffers from a rare
form of retrograde amnesia.
- You're kidding.
- I just--
I have trouble
accessing memories
connected to my personal life,
you know.
Anything over a year ago, all
I get are occasional flashes.
[phone buzzing]
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, Avery.
♪
- I'm supposed
to believe you don't remember
who you are
or where you're from?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Why'd you build this thing?
- Because Meena asked me to,
I--
Her lightning is like
nothing I've ever seen before,
I guess that's your doing,
isn't it?
- I assure you the B.L.O.C.
is perfectly safe.
- But you aren't.
What the hell
do you want from me?
- I'm sorry,
I have no idea why you're
so upset with somebody
you just met--
- Stop, stop.
I've known you all my life.
You're the Reverse-Flash.
- Look, Allen...
I have no idea what you're
talking about
or why you think
I'm a murderous speedster--
- Because you are!
- No.
I'm not.
Now, if you don't mind.
I have work to do.
♪
- Chester, has A.R.G.U.S.
posted any security alerts?
- Uh, no.
Is everything okay, boss?
- No, I just saw Thawne.
- What? How did he escape?
- I don't know. But he's using
his original face again,
the one he had before
he killed Harrison Wells.
- Okay,
how is that even possible?
And how the frack did he end
up working at Fast Track Labs?
- I don't know that either,
but I'm gonna find out.
- I can't hire you, Mr. Thawne.
This resume is a joke.
- Well, nobody's perfect.
[chuckles]
- Wow.
You really are something.
You know, after the 11 other
interviews I had today,
I'm starting to think
all this is just,
like, a huge waste of time.
I mean, seriously,
you call this a resume?
Am I boring you?
- When calculating quantum
static in genetic speed,
you have to account
for the tachyons.
♪
- [exhales]
I have been
working on this for months.
No one's even come close.
- Well, the other candidates
were idiots.
I'm not.
Which is how I can tell, you're
trying to create a speedster.
- I can help.
[whooshing]
- How are you still here?
- Well...
I wanna see how this ends.
- Don't screw with me!
How did you
get your speed back?
- I didn't?
- Stop lying!
I saw you, five minutes ago,
1,000 miles from here wearing
your original face, pretending
you didn't remember me.
So, who is he?
A version of you
from your past?
Answer me!
- I don't know.
And I don't care.
Don't you get it?
You took my speed.
There's no other versions
of me out there,
no other tricks up my sleeve.
You took everything from me.
So, why don't you
just leave me alone?
- When you were nearly
erased during Armageddon,
it erased your past didn't it?
Which means he must
be from another timeline.
Like when I created Flashpoint,
there was another Thawne.
- I need you to kill my mother.
- With pleasure.
- The only way to fix
things was to let him go.
When you fought
with the Legends,
he tried to keep himself
from getting erased,
but Black Flash
caught up to him.
- [screaming]
- I guess he didn't finish
the job. Here's a suggestion:
Why don't you go bother him?
- The other Thawne built this.
Does that mean anything to you?
- He didn't build that,
that's mine.
That's my biometric lightning
oscillation chamber
that I built
two centuries from now,
when I was a younger man
to see if I could
become a speedster like you.
- It worked.
- But not the way I intended.
Has it tapped into
the negative speed force?
- Ahh!
That's why Meena's
powers are so erratic.
They're not artificial,
they're negative.
I've seen what that
kind of force can do.
- Who's Meena?
- Dr. Meena Dhawan,
she's the one that's
using the B.L.O.C.
- Never heard of her.
And guess what?
Neither has history.
So, I guess your new
adversary made sure that
this Dr. Meena Dhawan
never sees the future.
- Because if she keeps
using that device,
the negative speed force will
start to alter her personality.
It'll destroy her.
- Not if.
When.
There's one thing you
should know about us Thawnes,
Allen, no matter when we exist,
no matter
what our memories are,
we only look out for ourselves.
So whatever this new guy's
endgame,
he'll sacrifice
every pawn on the board
to get what he wants.
- Not if I stop him
before he has a chance.
[whooshing]
- Well.
[clicks tongue]
Just when I thought
this day couldn't get
any more interesting.
Oh, John?
You can come out now.
[dramatic music]
♪
- It's been a long time.
Last time I saw you,
you were still
pretending you
needed a wheelchair.
- [laughs]
Last time I saw you,
your friend Oliver Queen
was still alive.
[electronic music]
So what do you want, John?
- For the past two years,
I've covered every corner
of this Earth...
and I still can't get this
damn thing to open up again.
♪
But I believe you can.
This cube fell out of the sky
and dropped into my lap.
Before I could see what
was inside, it shut itself.
I've had friends
examine every inch of it.
- I can't get it open.
- Ah, damn it.
Got that same line
from A.R.G.U.S.
And all they could tell me
is that it's knowledge
that's beyond any
current human understanding
and that it can
transport matter.
So, when I heard from
Lyla you were here, I--
- You thought some 23rd
century ingenuity might help.
Good call.
Why not just have
Lyla give it to me herself?
I see.
Trouble in paradise.
- Trying to open this box...
I've had to spend
a lot of time away from home,
away from my kids.
- But you just can't
leave the box behind, can you?
- Even when this thing
is away from me,
I can still feel it
in my mind...
- Worlds await.
- Pulling me closer.
- Ahh!
- Worlds await.
Worlds await.
- And the more I fight it,
the louder
I hear its call,
but I have to know what it is.
I--I have to know what
these damn voices want from me.
- Well.
You've come to the right place.
I've seen transmatter
technology like that before,
forged at the Orrery of Worlds
with the power
to travel across realities.
So, yeah. I'll help you.
On one condition.
That when you open
up that box again, John...
I get to see what's inside.
- Chester, Allegra, I'm
headed back to Central City,
I need you to find who's still
inside Fast Track Labs.
- Pretty
cleared up for the night,
just two heat
signatures inside.
- Meena and Thawne.
- What's the 4-1-1, boss?
- I think it's
the Thawne from Flashpoint,
now he's pumping Meena
with negative speed.
- If you need backup--
- No, it's too dangerous.
I don't know
why he's doing this,
but I won't
let anyone get hurt.
- Artificial speed saturation
at zero.
Ready for infusion.
- Doc.
You set the oscillation
levels at 52 million joules,
that is more speed than you
have ever absorbed before.
Are you sure The Flash
would want you to do this?
- He's why I'm doing this.
I hurt him this morning when my
speed started to run out--
I--I need to make it
last longer.
- All right.
Powering the chamber.
Activating electrostatic fins.
[machine whirring]
Ready for biometric absorption.
[whirring]
- Meena, stop!
- Flash.
What are you doing here?
- Flash, I know
what happened today,
and I know how to fix it.
- No, you don't.
I know why you attacked me.
It's because your speed
is connected
to the negative speed force.
- Wha--
- It's an extra-dimensional
power source
fueled by rage and hate.
- The B.L.O.C.
is fueled by lightning
from the upper atmosphere.
We've run
the numbers a thousand times.
- Then your math's wrong.
Or you're a damn liar.
- Eobard?
What is he talking about?
- I'm talking
about who he really is.
The Eobard Thawne that I know,
no matter what body he's in
in or what timeline
he comes from,
he's always the same person.
A psychotic murderer...
- Please don't hurt me.
- Known as the Reverse-Flash.
- [sobbing, screams]
- I didn't do
anything to you or anyone else,
why can't you understand that?
- I'm done listening to you.
Whatever you're trying
to do to her,
it ends now.
- You're making a huge mistake.
- No, I'm taking you
to Iron Heights,
which is letting you off easy.
- Leave him alone!
- Meena don't!
[electricity zapping]
- Oh, no.
Her brainwaves are altering.
It's too much power!
- [screams]
♪
[grunts]
[intense music]
♪
- Speed.
Need. More. Speed.
[tense music]
♪
[whooshing]
[tires squealing]
♪
- Time to get faster.
[electricity crackles]
- These cubes appear
to people at a crossroads,
at a turning point
in their lives,
so when the cube first opened,
what was going
through your mind?
- I just buried Oliver.
We were moving the kids
to Metropolis.
- You were starting a new life,
you were in control
of your destiny
for the first time in years,
that is why the cube chose you,
for that sense of purpose.
- Then why did it close?
- Because you weren't
ready to accept its power yet.
Really,
the only question John, is...
are you ready now?
♪
- I am.
- Good.
Then put yourself
in that headspace again.
Close your eyes.
Think of what your
future could be.
All the light you could
bring into this world.
[whirring]
All the cosmic odysseys
that await.
[dramatic music]
- No one can know my secret.
Don't come between
those folks and their gold.
Sir, we are quite sure you
will bring them
back to justice.
- Look at them all,
all those lives
you could lead.
Do it, John. Do it.
Drink of the Bleed
Mandrakk hid within the cube.
Feel its power.
Break through the source wall,
for when you
break through that wall,
all those worlds
that await will be yours.
- This universe is
far bigger than any of us.
I will dare to imagine.
[overlapping voices]
No.
I don't want this.
I don't want any of this!
Do you hear me?
The answer's no!
- No! No!
What have you done?
Do you know what you've done?
- I do.
I finally do.
I saw a thousand lives
I could lead.
But not one of them
led me back to my family.
- I was meant
to see inside that cube!
To find a way
out of this hell hole!
- I guess it's a good thing
the cube
didn't choose you, huh?
- [huffing]
You're not special.
You're not someone important.
This was your last chance
to be someone powerful.
- But I am someone special.
Now I realize.
The cube was trying to make me
someone else, something else.
And it even tricked me
into believing that
somehow I wanted it, too,
but...
I don't.
Because there is no power
in the universe
more powerful than the love
I have for my family.
[laughter]
♪
But I suppose a man like
you wouldn't understand that.
Because if it came down
to a choice between
some cosmic destiny, or...
being a father, a husband...
There's really no choice
at all.
♪
[phone dialing,
line trilling]
Hey, Lyla.
Hey, baby.
No, no, I didn't
see Barry this time,
I think he has
a lot on his plate.
Yeah, you're right,
we do have a lot to talk about.
I'm coming home.
♪
- [grunts]
[electricity zapping]
Chester.
Meena's negative
lightning pulse just cancelled
out my speed again,
just like this morning.
[crackling]
Chester?
- Meena. Where is she?
- She's gone.
- This is what you
wanted all along, isn't it?
For the negative
speed force to corrupt her?
- Why would I want that?
I didn't even know
the negative speed force
existed before today!
- She protected you from me,
why would she do that?
- Because she loves me.
You idiot!
And I love her.
More than anything.
When I lost my memories,
I had a singular focus
in my life.
Somehow, some way,
I was going to be a speedster,
and then I met Meena.
Everything changed.
I know this sounds strange,
but I think I'm supposed to
be a speedster, I--
I think that's why, despite
all the holes in my brain,
I can see the B.L.O.C.
crystal clear.
I think I'm meant to use it.
- So you--you wanna be
like Flash, be a superhero?
- I wanna be
bigger than a superhero,
I wanna--I wanna
recharge power grids,
I wanna reverse tornadoes
before they destroy
cities and towns,
I wanna end famine, end war.
I want to save the world.
But it wasn't meant to be.
I'd already fallen in love
with Meena when we discovered
her machine could
only work for one person.
- This isn't right.
- But that
wasn't the worst part.
Meena had a heart condition,
and one night,
she went into cardiac arrest.
Meena--Meena!
No!
There was only one way
to save her.
[whooshing]
[electricity zapping]
[epic music]
♪
- You gave up your dream.
Your chance to save the world.
- You are my world.
- [sobs]
- So, please.
Even if I was
this monster somehow,
or in another life,
don't hold my sins against her.
I am begging you.
Save her.
- The Thawne I know has haunted
my life since I was just a kid.
He's killed people I care for.
He deserves to rot.
He could never put someone
else's needs before his.
I'm sorry.
You're not the man
I thought you were.
You're someone better.
[electricity crackling]
My speed's back.
- Flash!
Flash, are you there?
- Yeah, I hear you.
What's happening?
- Okay, Meena's attacking power
junctions all over the city.
- Why would Meena
need electricity?
- Her speed is
supposed to be temporary.
- If Meena runs out of speed,
the negative speed force
will lose its grip on her.
It's making her
absorb electricity
to make more speed
and maintain control.
- If that's the case,
then she's gonna look
for the largest
power source possible.
The Keystone Cleveland Dam.
[dramatic music]
[whooshing]
♪
- Time to get faster.
[dramatic music]
♪
[electricity crackling]
- Speed.
Unlimited speed.
[whooshing]
[screeches]
- Meena,
I don't wanna hurt you,
but you're not in control
of yourself right now,
and if this dam breaks,
thousands of people could die.
- Then let them.
♪
[whooshing]
- Guys, she's right behind me.
Are you in position?
- Almost.
Everyone okay back there?
- I just hacked
into Meena's speed gauge.
Her saturation is already
under 40%, it's working.
- If Flash can keep her running
for another 119 seconds,
she'll burn off
the rest of her speed.
[whooshing]
♪
[explosion booming]
- [grunts]
- Ah.
Meena?
Are you okay?
[thunder booms]
[electricity zapping]
Ah!
[beeping]
- Flash.
Can you hear me, Flash?
- She just
summoned power directly
from the negative speed force.
It cancelled out
The Flash's power.
♪
- How pathetic.
Avatar of the Speed Force
dying on his back.
[brakes screeching]
- Meena! Stop!
I can't let you do this.
Please, please,
you have to stop this.
- The Meena you knew is gone.
Lost in the electrostatic
pits of your precious machine.
- I know you're still there.
I can feel you,
locked away inside, please.
Meena, come back to me.
- You're wasting your time.
[tense music]
This is who I am now.
And killing The Flash
is my purpose.
- No, no, it isn't!
- Perhaps I should
kill you first.
- Go ahead.
Because I'd rather die right
here, right now than lose you.
I know the real you!
You're the genius who stumped
every lab tech in Central City.
We have to account
for the tachyons.
The health-conscious partner
who never let me
have a cheeseburger!
Don't tell anybody.
The hero who taught me
to put others before myself.
And that Meena,
she would never be able
to do something like this.
I love you, Meena.
- The chamber's ready,
but only one of us can use it.
- I am begging you. Please.
I want to save the world.
I wanna save the world, too.
- You are my world.
No!
I can't lose you.
Please.
Come back to me.
You should go first.
- [gasping]
[hopeful music]
Eobard?
- Oh, God.
- Flash. Are you okay?
- Yeah, I will be.
So will they.
- [panting]
You saved me.
- No.
♪
[beeping]
- Okay, well.
My speed has finally worn off.
- And so are the effects
the negative speed force
had on your brain.
- [sighs]
- I know that your experiment
didn't exactly go as planned,
but this is one seriously
dope lab.
[laughter]
- How do you feel now?
- Well, I finally feel like
myself again,
and I am so sorry I didn't
listen to you, Flash.
We built the B.L.O.C.
so we could help people.
But, if we can't use it
without me turning
into a super villain--
- Then it's not worth the risk.
Especially if we don't
even know how we tapped into
the negative speed
force to begin with.
- Right.
- What if there
was a way around it?
Whenever I start to feel like
I'm in over my head,
I think about
the person I love most.
She helps guide me home,
like a lightning rod.
Just like tonight,
when the negative speed force
corrupted you--
- Eobard brought me back.
So, you think that our bond
could help me
control my powers?
It would take some
tinkering with the B.L.O.C.,
but if Eobard's
your lightning rod,
there's nothing you
can't accomplish together.
- Well, should we take a look
at the instruction manual?
- [gasps] Oh, I thought you'd
never ask.
[giggles]
- Mm, sorry
to interrupt the sniffers.
When you said that,
Flashpoint Thawne came back,
I reached out to a mutual
friend to gather some intel.
He just left a message.
[beeping]
- Chester, hey.
Sorry it took me so long to--
to get back to--
The Quincy P. Runk Institute
is having a minor infestation
of serpent creatures from
the Morlaidh dimension.
It's under control. I think.
As for your question, I was
out having retirement drinks
with Nate, and turns out
the Legends had
their own encounter
with Reverse-Flash this year.
Yeah, apparently
the Time Wraiths
saved him from Black Flash.
- My powers stripped,
I was re-educated and assigned
here to protect
this fixed point.
- As penance
for your past crimes.
- Believe it or not, Sarah,
I came to see their point.
That history cannot
and should not be changed.
- Thawne spent years
protecting the timeline.
- Thawne!
- It's yours now.
- Until he died
helping the Legends.
Pretty tragic twist, huh?
[screeching]
Whoops! [laughs]
Just another serpent loose,
so,
I just gotta grab my sword--
[screeching]
And it's over here.
- Wait, if Thawne from
Flashpoint became a hero,
but then died,
how could he be here?
- Maybe when he
sacrificed himself
the Time Wraiths saved his
life again, brought him here.
- To Meena?
- Guys,
I know it sounds crazy but,
however it happened,
I think we're lucky it did.
- So are they.
Plus, we could always use
another hero around here.
[woman screaming]
- [sobbing]
- Stop!
You think I'm playing
with you, huh?
Gimme the purse!
[grunts]
[whooshing]
What's happening to me?
[tense music]
[groaning]
Ahh! Ahh!
[electronic music]
♪
- Wh--what--
- Now that's more like it.
- [groaning]
♪
[beeping]
- Mark?
- Yes.
- Are you in my apartment?
- Yes. Where the hell are you?
- With my mom.
I needed to get out of there.
Clear my head.
- Then do that
and get your ass back here.
Okay? I was looking at
our data again last night.
It all clicked for me.
Caitlin, I know how to bring
Frost back.
- We can't. Not now. Plus,
Barry took the Mirror Gun.
I'm sorry, Mark,
but it's over.
- We don't need the gun.
Not for what we're gonna do.
[suspenseful music]
I just need you.
♪
- [echoing]
What did you do?
My speed is my life.
I wonder what face I'll
be wearing next time we meet.
Merry Christmas.
And I'm just getting started!
Everything you are is
because of me! What did you do?
- [echoing] I got faster.
Didn't you?
- Your precious Speed Force
cannot help you now,
because in this timeline,
Iris chose me.
I've won.
- There is no trace
of the negative speed force
left in your body.
- You took my life!
And left me in hell.
- We've been looking
for you, Eobard.
The man with no past.
The anomaly.
You were invisible to us
until the light from
that damn cube showed us
where to find you.
- Well. Good for me.
Now, who are you and...
What do you want?
- [chuckles]
I guess you could
say I'm an old friend,
and a new one,
all rolled up in one.
'Cause that's how I roll.
And as for why I'm here--
[intense music]
♪
It's time
to fulfil your destiny.
♪
[heroic music]
- Greg, move your head.