Last season on
The Flash...
Iris isn't Iris.
The real Iris, my wife,
she is somewhere else,
probably in danger.
Barry!
You targeted me
from the very beginning.
I saw everything.
As for the other Wellses,
they're as much a part of you
as yourself.
- You mean, I'm gonna keep hearing them?
- Yeah.
I did this.
I killed the Speed Force.
I need your help to build
an artificial Speed Force.
I need my speed back.
I'm gonna save Iris.
This whole time
when you looked at me,
you saw this other person.
For six years, I've been
in my own personal hell.
You let me rot in here,
while you took everything I created.
Stay out of my way, Flash.
I will be resuming my position
as CEO.
My husband, Joseph, he worked
tirelessly to try to find me.
Only to be murdered
moments after we were reunited.
Eva McCulloch
has never faced us head-on.
That's about to change.
We're gonna find her, beat her,
and get back everyone.
Yeah, you're right,
for now, my sister.
But what if...
What if the entire universe
is just some kind of...
cosmic neural network?
Then what you gonna say?
Oh... okay.
Okay, okay.
You know the drill, Chester P.
We've been prepping this for weeks.
Okay. Now that is...
That is not good.
Where's Eva?
Satellites have her
at 2nd and Walczak.
Make that 3rd and Certo.
You doing okay?
I know the cryo-pod keeps your
residual Speed Force in stasis,
but waking up
can be pretty disorienting.
Call Joe,
tell him I'm heading downtown.
But, Flash,
you only have 1% of your speed left.
Then I better hurry.
Eva's coordinates slowed down.
Maybe she stopped moving?
No. She's going up.
Why do you keep interrupting
my mission, Flash?
I told you, we're on the same side.
If we're on the same side,
then give me back my wife!
My fractal photons move
at the speed of light.
You never had a chance.
I don't want to hurt you.
But I'm cleansing the world
of Black Hole's influence.
So you either die,
or you stand down.
Flash, are you okay?
Flash?
Yeah, I picked up
Eva at a warehouse on 119th Street.
Suspected hideout of...
Rosa Dillon and Sam Scudder...
AKA...
- Top and Mirror Master.
- Yeah.
Sam, no!
You just killed the man I loved.
He never told you what he really was?
'Cause Sam Scudder wasn't a man.
He was my creation.
My first.
Flash, did you make it?
Did you stop Eva?
Flash?
Well, that was the best
takeout world tour yet.
Coq au vin from Paris.
Sashimi from the Arctic.
Kansas State Fair funnel cake
was Clark's recommendation.
I just wish I didn't have
to go back to work already.
Is anybody still here?
Allegra went home for the day.
And Kamilla...
She is...
missing.
I've missed you so much.
No, this isn't right.
This isn't right.
Barry?
Oh, God, I'm still here.
Eva hit nine more spots last night.
I missed her every time.
- How much speed do you have left?
- A few days.
Maybe a few hours.
Eva's targeting
Black Hole tech, right?
So, why go after Scudder and Dillon?
They were working for Black Hole.
I found this in Scudder's remains.
I'm guessing they've been
on Carver's payroll
since breaking out
of Iron Heights last year.
And when they got in Eva's way,
she moved them off the chessboard.
Well, they are not the only ones.
The whole city thinks
that Sue killed Carver.
She and Ralph are
staying way off the grid.
And Caitlin and Cisco
are still gone, too.
And Iris.
I should get back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
If we're gonna stop Eva and fix this,
I need the artificial Speed Force
up and running.
Well, we may not know where Scudder
moved the Black Hole tech,
but I bet you Dillon does.
I'm gonna go in,
see if I can get her to talk to me.
Actually, Captain, I am.
Right. When you were prosecutor,
you put Dillon in Iron Heights.
And now I am her defense attorney
that's gonna keep her out
and get her
to tell me where that tech is.
That's my girl.
Connecting Fusion Sphere.
Fusion Sphere connected.
Activate.
Uh... activated.
It's working. Now we just have
to find a fuel source to put in it.
And then we can power
the artificial Speed Force.
Exactly.
- Hang on.
- What?
One of the sphere plates
don't look fully magnetized.
You can't touch that.
If you touch the Fusion Sphere...
While it's activated,
the Fusion Sphere
thinks you're the fuel source.
Yes.
And fuse my atoms, which would lead
to a complete molecular degeneration.
Sorry. I'm just trying
to get your speed back.
But don't hurt yourself
trying to do it.
I'd never want you to do that.
- Allen.
- What?
Can you get this guy a coffee,
wake him up?
Yes. Let's...
Come on. Let's get a coffee.
Whoa. Can I use that cappuccino
maker you guys have in the lounge?
- Knock yourself out.
- Yeah, all right.
What? What?
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
So, it turns out
we cracked the fuel problem
for this ASF of yours.
Not easy, not great.
But so much fun, huh?
I love all the brainstorming.
Plus, we got all the Wellses
back together again.
So, I expect I need no introduction,
but, yes, it is I,
master of stage and screen,
Harrison Orson Wells.
Okay, you're new.
Nash, as I know you know,
when our worlds died in Crisis,
particles from our brainwaves
were drawn to you like...
Like a moth drawn to a cosmic flame.
Whatever happened
to show, don't tell? H.R...
- Nice catch.
- I love this part.
So, there are multi-versal particles
inside you right now, Nash,
made of synaptic energy.
Now, we take those particles
and we put them in the Fusion Sphere,
theoretically, they could
power the ASF...
forever.
Forever.
Not only would Allen
get his speed back,
but I'd be rid of you lot forever.
Well, you'd be gone, too,
might be because of the whole
organic receptor thingy.
Oh.
- What?
- What's he talking about?
Multi-versal particles are just...
They're very volatile.
Right? And there's no way
they'll stay
in that sphere long enough
to be charged unless...
Unless we have an organic receptor.
The organic receptor...
is me.
For the Flash to run again,
Nash Wells must die.
- No.
- What?
No way!
Nash, you're our organic receptor.
You're the only one that can
contain us inside the Fusion Sphere.
By dying? By dying, Harry?
- Yes.
- How stupid do you think I am?
- Come on.
- I have a life here now.
I have people
that I actually don't hate.
I'm not gonna give all that up
so Barry Allen can run fast.
Nash, you're the only one of us
that can help Allen.
And I will, Harry. By figuring out
another way to save Allen
that doesn't mean
I have to commit suicide!
- Nash.
- Where is he going?
Bozos!
Didn't see that coming.
And scene.
What the hell?
Maybe I can message Kamilla.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
My wife died
in the particle
accelerator explosion.
You're not even...
human.
You do not
control me anymore, Joseph.
She killed Sam right in front of me.
If you tell me where you and Scudder
were moving that tech,
I can use that information to strike
a deal for you with the State
and... catch Sam's killer.
I wish I knew,
but Sam made all the deals.
That's funny.
Your IHP file says
that you were running
a psychotropic drug ring
out of the meta wing.
You were flush with cash...
and it's just that you felt so sad
when you were remembering that time.
It's almost as...
Almost as if you were
deliberately projecting
a fake emotion at me.
But why would you do that?
Why would you do that unless you
already knew that I was an empath.
How would I know that?
I'm not psychic.
I just cause vertigo.
What else can you do
inside people's minds, Rosa?
Let me show you.
I feel so empty.
What did you do to me?
I found a little kernel
of doubt inside of you
and spun, spun, spun it
into a full-blown
crisis of confidence.
Like a top.
Scudder's ditzy girlfriend.
It was all an act.
I was always the brains.
He was just a pretty face.
Then Sam cut a deal with Black Hole.
We got rich,
but we were in over our heads.
So, when I heard
Eva McCulloch wanted him dead...
You sold him out to her.
And in return,
Eva gave me a cause to believe in.
She delegated her next mission to me.
And what I've cooked up for her
is gonna blow this city away.
If you are planning something
that will put people in danger...
Then what?
The Flash is gonna stop me?
He can barely run.
You know, when I first got my powers,
I was an empath, too.
And look what I've grown into.
Who knows what you'd have become
if only you weren't so...
afraid.
I guess we'll never know.
Thought you could use a pick-me-up.
Thank you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- What's an organic receptor?
Oh, no, that... I'm just...
This is... I'm just helping Barry...
get his speed back,
or I'm trying to anyway.
Well, it's nice to see you care about
someone other than me for a change.
Well, you're...
You're the answer.
Multi-versal particles oscillate
at certain frequencies of light.
Allegra can control
electromagnetic wavelengths.
So,
she can push the particles out of you
and into the Fusion Sphere.
Right.
Charging a fuel source for the ASF.
Then we take all that kinetic energy
and we just
transfer it
to the track ring above us...
Giving Flash his groove back.
- Ah... Just one thing.
- What?
Aren't multi-versal particles
a little too chaotic
to be contained in a Fusion Sphere?
Yes, normally they would be,
but Allegra can use her powers
to contain the particles
inside the Fusion Sphere
from a safe distance.
Thanks for looking out for me,
but if Nash says it's gonna work,
I trust him.
Okay.
All right, then. Ready?
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, the Fusion Sphere is...
...ready for particle insertion.
Okay.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Guys, something's not right.
- What's happening?
- Uh...
The charge is dropping.
I... I can't hold it much longer.
Allen.
- Barry, are you okay?
- Please be okay, please be okay.
Hello.
What you are doing?
Uh, since when do you speak French?
- Since always, no?
- Why is he talking funny?
I think when the particles
left the Fusion Sphere,
it transferred to Barry Allen.
So, all of the brainwaves
of all the Wellses
who have ever lived...
Are inside Monsieur Allen's mind.
Allow me introduce myself.
I'm Sherloque Wells,
master detective.
- At your service.
- I'm Chester. Chester P. Runk.
- Chester.
- There's a Sherlock Wells?
Sher-loque.
Yes, there is a Sherlock Wells.
- Loque.
- Sherloque.
- Lock.
- Loque.
Good, good. Not great.
We face a mystère stranger
than the King Tut Killer
of Earth-cinquante-cinq.
The many minds of Barry Allen.
- Oh, man.
- All of them ended up inside Barry?
It looks like.
But, listen, let's not panic.
Between the three of us
and a master detective,
we can figure out
how to fix Barry Allen.
You guys talking about B.A.?
- He's so fast.
- What just happened to him?
I think another set
of Wells particles
just took over his mind.
H.R. Wells.
How are you guys doing?
So, this is simple. Just get
all the Wellses out of B.A.
into the Futon Sphere.
Stop. It's a Fusion Sphere.
- Can you stop...
- Huh?
Can you stop drumming?
Can you stop... Okay.
The drumming is so annoying.
Do you hear the drums?
They are coming.
It is I, Wells the Gray.
- Wells the Gray.
- It's a wizard Wells?
This is all my fault.
Oh, my God. Do you know Gandalf?
Barry trusted me to help him,
and I screwed up.
No, it's not...
It's not your fault.
Look, here's what we'll do.
Um... Just blast him again.
We'll push the particles
back into me.
Uh-uh. No way.
I'll just make it worse.
No, you won't make it worse.
You won't make it worse.
All you need to do is figure a way
to contain the particles
once they leave Allen's body,
like a magnet...
Uh...
Guys, guys.
What are you?
Can't figure it out?
Aw.
Did you lose your dissertation?
You're a copy of me.
No, I'm no fractal anomaly.
I am a product of your broken mind.
That's impossible.
No, it's not.
You pushed your mind
to find Singh until it broke...
Forever.
- Leave me alone.
- There's no escaping this, Iris.
How long have you been
trying to get out?
Weeks? Months?
You are weak in every universe.
An insignificant speck, a victim.
Okay, okay.
Don't worry, I'm gonna use
the mobile Gideon to diagnose him.
So Gideon, what's wrong with Barry?
An abundance
of multi-versal particles
inside his mind are causing
his cerebral cortex to overload.
Yeah, all those
brainwaves at once?
It's like when Grodd
was trapped in his mind
but to an infinite degree.
Only Barry Allen's speed
healing is keeping him alive now.
Gideon, what happens
when his speed runs out?
If the particles remain
inside his brain,
Barry Allen will instantly die.
Barry is going to die
because of what I did to him.
No, no. I should have trusted my gut.
Look, I knew we needed something else
to keep the sphere intact.
Yeah, that was supposed
to be my stupid powers.
They're not stupid.
Hey, the particles always needed
something stronger, some sort of...
I don't know,
some sort of organic receptor.
That's what you were
researching in your office.
You let me think
I was the only solution
when this whole time
there was another way?
- No. It's not that simple.
- Yes, it is.
- You lied.
- Yeah!
I lied.
Because I'm the organic receptor.
I'm not ready to die yet.
Okay, Barry wouldn't let anyone
die for the artificial Speed Force.
Yeah, so why lie about it?
Because I was scared.
I get it.
I thought you had changed.
- Chuck...
- It's Chester P., actually, but...
I need a way to aim the particles
after I push them out of Barry.
Like a particle magnet.
I can build that.
Well, I mean, I can try.
Lead the way.
What the hell.
Harry...
Look at these brainwave readings.
Allen's cerebellum is burning up.
Harry, if you want the kid to
survive, then maybe you better relax.
I'm fine! I'm fine. Do not touch me.
- What happened to the JV squad?
- Ah...
Why are you moping around here
instead of helping them?
They don't want my help.
Frankly, I don't blame them.
- Garcia found out the truth?
- Yeah.
You know what Cisco said
after Crisis?
He said, "An infinite number
of Harrison Wells,
and we're stuck with the one
who killed the multi-verse."
And every day, I ask myself, "Why?
Why am I the one left standing?"
So who should have gotten the slot?
One of us "bozos"?
You're not bozos.
I only called you that
because I find
the Wells' very annoying.
Present company excluded.
But you know what you are?
You're a daily reminder
that even though we may all look
the same, we're not the same.
Because you're all good men...
and I'm...
I'm not.
So you're a selfish jerk.
- Mm.
- You think that I wasn't?
That we all weren't?
Hell, when I met this team,
I was working for Zoom.
H.R. lied.
Sherloque kept secrets.
We all came here broken men.
Thanks to Team Flash,
eventually, we learned to be better.
That's why I believe in you, Nash.
There's a good man
in there somewhere.
You just need to dig him up,
let him breathe.
They're not real. They're not real.
Boo.
- No, I'm not crazy.
- But you are.
There's only two options
in this place.
Survival...
...or madness.
No.
This is not neural dissonance.
I'm not seeing you
because I'm crazy and broken.
This is something else.
Someone else.
Keep trying to break me down...
because I am not afraid
of the woman that I am today.
But you are...
Eva.
You want me distracted.
I must be getting close
to finding my way out of here.
You can push yourself until you break
and you will never escape this world.
I'm sorry, Iris, but if you can't
accept my conditions either,
you might never see
your husband again.
Wow. You actually came back.
I'm a defense attorney, Rosa.
I can handle a few mind games.
I'm here to get you a deal.
Am I supposed to be
intimidated by you now?
The woman who's afraid
of her own powers?
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I am afraid.
When I first got these abilities,
I was so excited.
But then my powers,
they started to grow
and change, and I...
I bottled them up
because I was afraid.
I was afraid I was gonna become
someone like you.
Are you trying to rile me up?
No, Rosa,
I'm trying to remind myself
of all of that fear
that I have locked down deep inside
so that I can put it all into you.
My heart is racing...
Do you wanna go back to prison?
Or do you wanna tell me
what you're planning?
Hey, what's wrong?
There's a supersonic jet
about to leave
a secret Black Hole site
in the Badlands,
and it is loaded
with all of Carver's remaining tech.
But that's not the only thing
it's carrying.
Rosa Dillon planted a bomb onboard.
If it blows over the city,
hundreds of people will die.
And the Flash isn't fast enough
to stop it.
Okay, okay. Here, put this on.
Once Allegra pushes the particles
outside of Barry,
these ionic circuits will catch them,
put them back into you.
- Smart, Runk.
- Brilliant.
Thanks.
Listen, when this is over,
I'll find a way to make
this up to you.
This is a pretty good start.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Hey!
It's working. Keep going.
Barry?
Are you... Barry?
Yeah, it's really me.
All right, let's celebrate later.
We still have a supersonic jet
about to explode over the city.
I still can't stop it.
That plane is only three minutes out.
We need a plan.
No.
- We need the Flash.
- Nash!
- That'll kill you...
- I know.
But I'm the organic
receptor that we need.
You're getting your speed back.
- We'll find another way!
- What other way, Allen?
There's no time.
Nash, you don't have to do this
just to prove a point.
I'm not doing it to prove a point.
I'm doing it because
I won't watch you die.
I won't let any of you die.
No, no.
If you touch him,
we'll lose you, too.
Nash. Please.
I can't let anyone else die for me.
I've already lost so many people.
Do you know
what I feel right now, Allen?
Pride.
Honor.
It's been so long
since I felt those things.
And it's not just me.
The Council feels it, too,
and we've made a decision.
We're doing exactly...
Is it charging?
Uh...
Yeah, the Fusion Sphere is charging.
How can I be the Flash
without a Wells on this team?
You've always been the Flash.
You always will be.
With or without me.
Hey, B.A.
How's it going? So fast.
No, B.A., don't be upset.
This is not goodbye.
It's just until our next communion.
Not great,
hm, our current situation,
but it will be.
Allen...
When I came to your stupid Earth,
with its good burgers...
I was a broken man.
Lost, angry, blah, blah, blah,
and you showed me
how to be a better person.
And I'll always be grateful
for our friendship.
Now...
run...
Barry...
You're at 80%.
You got this.
After I'm gone,
look out for one another.
Okay.
A.R.G.U.S. was waiting
for the jet when it landed.
They seized all the Black Hole
tech onboard.
All thanks to the Flash.
So Nash died a hero,
and I never really got to know him.
Look, I know after tonight that
none of us will ever be the same.
We all heard what Nash said.
He was so happy
to have you in his life.
Thanks, Chester.
You can call me Chuck.
I need to tell the rest of the team.
I'll call Carla,
and make sure Caitlin knows.
Cisco's gonna want to come back
from his trip.
Harry was like a father to him.
They were all in my mind.
I could feel their spirits.
I could feel how much they loved me.
They gave themselves up for me.
How am I supposed to live with that?
Uh... I think that's the point.
They put themselves in the ASF
so you could live.
And thrive.
And now, whenever you run,
it'll kind of be like
they'll be running with you, right?
Nash wasn't the only one
who rose to the occasion today.
I wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for you guys.
So, what now, Flash?
We go save Iris and our friends.
We get everybody back.
I've got friends
That will run through walls
And I've got friends that don't text
They call
And when I have nowhere left to go
And I need you the most
I've got friends
That will run through walls
Eva, what was that? Are you okay?
Eva?
Help!
Someone help me!
I died.
Everything I thought was a lie.
I'm the mirror duplicate?