- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
- Previously,
on "The Flash"...
- What happened to me?
- Ralph Dibny...
- He used to be a cop.
- A dirty cop.
- I was a good detective!
- This is not my world.
- Oh, and Earth-2 is?
Did you make a bunch
of friends there
that I don't know about?
- You said you were a good cop.
Be one.
[flesh stretching]
- Let me train you.
- For what?
- To do what I do.
What made you look
into Mayor Bellows?
- Oh, it was a client.
Last name DeVoe.
[suspenseful music]
[pleasant orchestral music]
♪ ♪
- I owe you for
the java, rookie.
Can't believe I left
my wallet at home.
- Don't worry about it.
It could happen to anyone...
five times in a row.
And could you please
stop calling me rookie?
- Sorry, uh...
old habit
from when I was
your superior officer.
You know, before
you got me fired,
ruined my career...
destroyed my life.
Crushed my spirit,
left me alone
without a friend in the world.
- Don't forget how
I turned you into
an amorphous, stretchy blob.
- Actually, that's the one
good thing you've done for me.
- Yeah.
- Course, you didn't do it
on purpose, so you don't
get credit.
- Both of you,
hand over your cash, now!
- Hey.
Uh, pardon us, okay?
One second.
Okay, this is perfect.
I've been teaching you, right?
Muggers are like Superhero 101.
- Ooh, Ralphy like-y.
- All right, what's your plan?
- Okay, I was thinking
about this
in the shower this morning:
how sweet would it be
to turn into a giant slingshot?
- That's a weird plan,
but okay.
- Oh, I got
an even cooler idea.
- Hey!
I'm still robbing you guys!
- We will be right with you,
sir!
Please!
Okay, what if I did, like,
a human Slinky thing?
Maybe wrap him up,
throw in a few on-theme puns?
- Whatever, Ralph.
We just gotta
hurry up a little bit.
- Relax, rookie.
I've seen a lot of thugs.
This guy is no shooter.
[gunshot]
[skin creaks]
- [shouts]
[thwack]
- [screaming]
both: Whoa!
- My leg!
[wailing]
- Well.
Our work here is done.
- Hey, hey, what are you doing?
We can't just leave.
You just shot him.
- I didn't shoot him.
He shot him.
- Well, I...
- Do you feel like I shot you?
- [shouts]
[gunshot]
[bullet swooshes]
[wails]
- Stop shooting him!
- I am not shooting him!
- Oh, they shot my ass!
- Okay, so he's
a little banged up, but...
we caught the bad guy.
Isn't that what superheroes do?
- No, a superhero's first job
is to protect people.
- Oh, God.
What's the second job?
Long-winded lectures
before noon?
- I barely...
take this.
One day, I'm gonna throw
a lightning bolt so far up...
I'm taking him to the hospital!
- No!
- And you owe me five coffees.
- [mumbles mockingly]
- [wailing]
- It's fine.
I know.
Come on, get up.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
This way, come on.
[whooshing]
- [chuckles]
Hey!
He left his gun!
He's reformed already.
[tense music]
- We need to talk.
- The only way it can end...
with my victory.
- What?
♪ ♪
- Fine.
Let us take the long way
and continue.
- Today, for the first time,
events will align
that give Team Flash
a chance to discover
your identity.
This is earlier
than you anticipated.
- It is of no concern.
- Like hell!
You know what's at risk.
What we are doing.
If you've miscalculated
by even a decimal...
- There is not a decimal,
a fraction,
an infinitesimal variable
beyond my thought...
beyond my mind.
Even now,
of the 7,798 variations
of this argument,
I have anticipated them all
and know how it ends.
- Then how does it end?
♪ ♪
- The only way it can end.
With my victory.
♪ ♪
[computer beeping]
- Ouch.
All-nighter, huh?
- I haven't been this tired
since Killer Frost decided
to go to Burning Man.
- Yeah?
Well, how is our search
for the mysterious
DeVoe coming?
- Allen, we're searching
for an evil mastermind.
The only clue we have
to go on is his name,
of which there's
literally thousands, so how's
the search going?
It's...
[tool clatters]
Fantastic.
- [giggles]
I missed that.
- If we're gonna find DeVoe,
we need more brain power.
- Well, why didn't you say so?
One master detective,
ready to detect.
- I said "more brain power."
[computer beeps]
- Initiating emergency
oxygen purge.
[alarm blaring]
In ten...nine...
- [stammering]
Eight...seven...six...
- [sighs]
- Five...four...
- One more second.
- Two...one...
[alarm silences]
- Like I said,
we need more help.
Maybe I should call my friends.
- Your what?
- My friends.
- Is he saying "friends"?
- I think he's being sarcastic.
- No, no, no.
This is delirium.
He's cracked from
being awake all night.
Hey, Harry, all of your friends
are in this room.
- I have other friends.
You asked me
to make new friends.
I made new friends.
It was a task.
I complete tasks.
- That's so great.
I can't wait to meet them.
- Harry, you listened to me.
I'm so proud of you.
- Okay, there's no pride...
Put that down.
Look, my friends are smart.
They'll help us.
I'll call them.
- All right, well, um,
in the meantime,
we gotta find the rest
of these bus metas.
Somehow they're connected
to DeVoe's plan.
You were on the bus.
[sighs]
Can you remember
anybody else who was?
- Well, I was in between drunk
and hungover at the time.
She is cute.
What's her deal?
- She's in jail.
- When are visiting hours?
- [sighs]
What about vibing
the rest of the bus passengers?
- I mean, I-I tried,
but, you know,
the...the dark matter
we released
was such a massive
space-time event
that my energy
just reflected back
and I ended up vibing myself.
I'm pretty sure I relived
my own birth.
Or was that my death?
- You know, there are other
non-traumatizing ways
of bringing
Ralph's memory back,
like hypnosis.
- Is that really a thing?
- I mean, not the whole
cartoon, pocket watch version,
but yeah, real
hypnosis can be used
to recover memories.
- All right.
Do you know any hypnotists?
- Mm-mm.
- Not me.
- You lost me at "cartoon."
- All right.
So who's gonna hypnotize Ralph?
- I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
- Dr. Finkel, thank you so much
for squeezing us in.
Our friend Ralph here
is having trouble
remembering information...
for a detective case.
Right, Ralph?
- So...
I see you didn't go to Harvard.
- No.
Did you?
- I see what you did there.
- If you could fix
his personality too,
that'd be great.
- Give it up, rookie.
This psycho hooey's never
gonna work on me.
- Well, that was quick.
Now, remember with me, Ralph.
It's a month ago.
You're on a bus.
What do you see?
Ralph:I see someone...
crying.
Dude's really bumming me out.
- [sobbing, sniffing]
- Hey, cheer up, buddy.
You can do it.
- What else do you see?
- I see...some women.
I can't see their faces.
34-32-36,
38-34-32.
- Are those bus routes?
- I think they
are measurements.
Ew.
- I see something else.
I see a...
[ominous musical sting]
It's a bison.
- Does a bison mean
anything to either of you?
- It's hocus-pocus.
It's never gonna work
on a guy like me,
but we can try it
if you want.
[playful music]
How'd you guys get over there?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[ominous snarl]
[roaring, man shrieking]
[indistinct police
scanner chatter]
- Security guard found him
here this morning.
We haven't ID'd him yet.
His personal effects
are scattered everywhere,
so we didn't find his wallet.
But we may find it when we find
the rest of his briefcase...
and his missing hand.
- [sighs]
Well,
judging by that avulsion
and the claw marks,
I'd say a large
predatory animal did this.
But whatever it was would
have to have four-inch canines,
a bite force of 5,000 P.S.I.,
and weigh over a ton.
That animal doesn't exist.
- What the hell did this?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- You don't think...
- Do you remember
back in the day
when we wouldn't
calmly consider
a stone statue
our prime suspect?
- No, I actually don't.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
Blood.
- Hmm.
- All right, my friend,
we got meats,
we got cheeses,
we got guac,
we got beer.
And of course...
we got my favorite chips.
Let's get this confab poppin'.
Are your friends coming?
- Yeah, let me just calibrate
the multiverse holo-projector
and we'll be on our way.
- Your friends are
from different Earths?
- You know, I would've thought
"multi-verse holo-projector"
would have given you that clue,
but...apparently not.
Yes, they're from other Earths.
[computer beeps]
And we're off and...running.
Well, allow me to make
some introductions.
From Earth-12,
the holder of four PhDs
and the author of the book
"Everything is Meaningless,
So Why Did I Buy This Book?",
I give you...
Herr Harrison Wolfgang Wells.
Guten Tag, Wells.
- Guten Tag.
- Do you know that it amuses me
that you think that saving
your tiny world matters
when the entire multiverse
will inevitably be consumed
in a fiery heat dess?
- "Dess"?
- Ja, that's what I said,
dess.
- Death.
- Oh.
- Yeah, dess.
What are you, dess?
- Yeah.
- Oh, you must be
the little one
that they call Cisco.
- You're not that little.
[laughs nervously]
- I'm 5'7".
Guten Tag.
- All right, moving on.
Um, from Earth-47,
I give you
the billionaire inventor
and publishing tycoon,
general champion
of free speech,
H. Lothario Wells.
- That's right.
Now keep that coming.
Now try the other one on.
No, not the crotchless,
that...the other...
the leopard print.
[murmuring indistinctly]
- What's going on?
- He's, uh, otherwise occupied.
[clears throat]
- Oh, golly.
There you are.
My apologies.
It appears that y'all have
caught us red-handed
here at the mansion
on dress-up night.
You know what they say:
intellect is
the greatest aphrodisiac.
- Ja, so, nobody says that.
- Here's to rising IQs
and libidos.
[whistles, clicks tongue]
- [laughs] Hate to call
two a pattern here, Harry,
but aren't your friends just...
- And from the post-apocalyptic
landscape of Earth-22,
where man and machine have
become one in order to survive,
I give you Wells 2.0.
- Right-o.
Let's make this quick.
Reapers have raided
our petrol supplies
and stolen our water tanks.
I'd like to smash them to bits.
- [chuckles]
It's a party now.
- Forget not about me!
'Tis I, Wells the Grey!
[majestic music]
- Sorry.
It's a bad connection.
- Ja, that was
a terrible connection.
- Good on ya.
That dude was strange.
- Harry?
- Yeah?
- Sidebar.
- We're gonna...sidebar.
- So, remember when I said
"make friends"?
I didn't mean with yourself.
- [laughs] Yeah,
they're great, aren't they?
And some of the brightest minds
in all the multiverse...
and good company too,
I might add.
I mean,
that Harrison Wolfgang Wells?
[chuckles]
Guy's hilarious.
- Look, we're desperate.
- Sure we are.
- So I think we should give
the Council of Wells a chance.
- "Council of Wells"?
- Pretty good name, right?
- Yes, it is.
- I know, all right.
- All right!
- Fellas.
- Fellas!
- Will you...
No, do your thing.
Here's how it's
gonna go down...
- Nein. Halt.
So, you are unnecessary...
well, so, not wanted, so...
off you go.
Off you go.
He's still here.
- Even I know when
you got too many partners.
- And I may be half machine...
but you're all useless.
- I think what the fellas are
trying to say here
is that they prefer
to work alone.
- You don't say.
- I just did.
- Done just said.
- Ja, he just said.
- Fine.
You enjoy your roadkill.
I'm gonna be eating
my favorite chips.
- We had a Cisco
on my Earth once.
[tube slurping]
He was delicious.
- [laughs]
He ate the other Cisco.
[laughing pointedly]
- I'm gonna...
- Hm?
- Leave you to you.
- So this stone sample shows
absolutely no unique attributes
of any kind...
totally normal granite statue.
Except...
it's filled with traces
of the dark matter
on a molecular level, as if
it's been flooded with it.
- So, another bus meta?
- One that somehow brings
inanimate objects to life
and uses them to kill.
- Hm.
- How can this possibly be...
possible?
- My best guess?
This meta has the ability
to leave a psychic imprint
on objects...
a sort of telekinetic
puppeteering
through a subconscious link.
- That's really smart,
34-25-34.
- Did he just give my...
- No, ignore him.
- Um...well, look.
The good thing is,
our rifles have
a "blow statues to hell"
setting,
so when this meta does
show up...
we'll be ready.
- I hope we're ready now.
Our victim's name is Jim Fox.
He was an auctioneer
at Wetherby's.
He was transporting
a Native American artifact
when he was attacked.
We just don't know which one.
- Oh, wait.
Maybe we do.
A bison necklace.
Ralph, you said you saw
a bison on the bus, right?
I mean...nothing in our world
is a coincidence.
- Vindicated.
- No one said you were lying.
- I could see it in your eyes.
- According to
this auction report,
the necklace was separated
into three pieces.
The first was in the briefcase,
the third is unknown,
but the second was in the hands
of a private collector.
- "Christoph Banks."
- I'll get the CCPD.
Get his address.
He may be in danger.
- Then we better
pay him a visit.
You ready to suit up?
- Oh, yeah.
Where's my suit?
- Now, this is
just a prototype,
but she's got an adaptive
nano-weave structure
that is...wait for it...
malleable...
on a sub-molecular level.
- Don't know what that means,
don't care.
Just yank the tarp off.
I'm ready for my super-suit.
- Ralph...
this tarp is your super-suit.
[playful music]
When you stretch, it stretches.
When you squish, it squishes.
- Squishes into something
butt-ugly.
Where's the style, the flair?
Dibny needs to peacock.
- Dibny needs
to wear the prototype
Cisco so lovingly made for him.
Either that,
or you fight crime naked.
Nope!
Don't fight crime naked!
♪ ♪
- What is this,
a puppy's raincoat?
[liquid pouring]
- The collection really is
quite impressive, isn't it?
[tense music]
It's taken no small amount
of resources to acquire.
I'm just glad to share it
with someone
who appreciates it.
- That I do.
- So, this book you're writing.
It's on Sioux artifacts?
- My entire bloodline
is Sioux...Lakota, to be exact.
- Ah.
Then you're gonna love this.
This...
is a Lakota peace pipe.
Had to have it taken apart
and repaired
so it can be smoked.
♪ ♪
Wanna try it?
- That which you call
a "peace pipe"
is no such thing.
It is a sacred gift for prayer
from Ptesan-Wi, bringer of
the seven sacred rights...
the White Buffalo Calf Woman.
You'd never hang a Christian
cross upside down...
or lay an American flag
on the floor.
Yet, you destroy that
which is wakan...
what is holy...by letting it
touch your filthy flesh.
But I am here to teach you
the price for your impudence.
- Who do you think you are?
- I am the Black Bison.
[dramatic music]
- [gasps]
[choking]
♪ ♪
- Enough.
- Whoa.
Now, that is a cool suit.
Remember to take some pics
for Cisco.
♪ ♪
- Help!
Don't leave me!
[whooshing]
- You let her get away.
- I'm getting the same traces
of dark matter from this
that I was from
the tiger statue.
- Looks like our meta
isn't restricted
to animating just stone.
- No,
but she does have
some limitations.
Out of all the artifacts
in the office,
she could only control
the knight.
- So then maybe
her psychic imprint abilities
are just restricted
to effigies.
- [snorts]
- It just means "statues."
- Yeah, I don't know.
Sounds kinda dirty to me.
- So if the statues
look like people
or animals,
she can bring them to life.
- Mm.
- Good thing there's only
thousands of those in the city.
- Oh, I got a hit
on facial recognition.
- "Mina Chaytan, professor
of cultural anthropology"?
She's a teacher?
- Was.
She became an activist,
but she lost her job
six months ago
after being arrested.
- Breaking and entering,
trespassing, burglary...
quite an activist.
The charges were dropped,
but the university still
let her go.
- She was trying to reclaim
several Sioux art pieces
from the museum.
Chaytan was at this
even before she was a meta.
- Yeah, except now she's
upped her game to homicide.
She wants the third piece
of that necklace?
Let's find it before she does.
- Okay.
West and West are on the case.
- What's wrong with you?
- You let her get away.
We could've caught her.
- Yeah, I let her go,
but I also saved Banks's life.
That was the most important
thing in that situation.
- Really, Allen?
Because to me,
when I was a cop,
getting the bad guy...
that was
the most important thing.
- [sighs]
-You're the Flash.
You could've saved him
and caught her.
- All right, look, Ralph.
I'm always gonna make
the decision
to help the person
in danger first.
That's what we do here.
- [scoffs]
All right, well,
we'll file that
under "superhero lesson
of the day," you know?
- [sighs]
- You look like
a plucked chicken.
- Guys, guys!
I still think the best thing
we can do
is figure out
what is DeVoe's goal.
And then from there,
we can track all...
- [scoffs]
That's a simple plan
from a simple man.
- That's not helping.
- Why don't we use
the Bates-Novick method first?
We determine why each meta
developed their super powers...
and then we smash them to bits.
- I've seen a lot
of strange here,
but...this takes all the cakes.
Okay, Council of Wells!
How we doing?
Have we found
our mystery foe yet?
- No, we can't even agree
on what methodology to use.
- What?
- Yes.
- You've had an entire day.
- I know.
- Wait.
- What?
- Weren't there three of you?
- Whoo!
Thanks for the merry-go-round,
sweetheart.
You know what I mean.
[chuckles]
Oh, sorry.
I had to take care
of some off-camera business.
- Oh, my God!
- What? What?
- I can see
your frank and beans.
- Come on, now.
I do my best thinking
commando. Plus,
it ain't like we all haven't
seen it before.
- I haven't seen it!
- Ah, you Earth folk.
You guys are so uptight.
- I...can...
[sighs] Can we just
get back to the task at hand?
We need answers.
- The best answer is always
the simplest.
Why don't we go to
every DeVoe we can find...
and interrogate 'em?
[flame hissing]
- What, even the baby DeVoe?
- Especially the baby DeVoe.
- Baby violence solves nothing.
[doppelgangers arguing]
- Guys...guys...
All right...gentlemen!
Clearly, this isn't working.
And by the way,
it's not me.
It's you.
[computer beeps]
This...
was a bad idea.
- It's like your junk has been
burned into my brain.
- You're welcome.
- We've got the third piece
of the necklace.
My dad found out
that it was on display
at Central City Museum,
but when they figured out
that it was a target...
Barry: It's on the move.
- Yeah, it's being transferred
via armored car
to a secure storage facility
in Brookfield Heights.
I pinged the truck's GPS.
- All right.
Ralph?
Let's go.
[rousing music]
- I'll get my ugly suit.
♪ ♪
- [murmuring indistinctly]
- [chuckles]
Kittens.
[bones cracking,
guard screaming]
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
[thudding, shouting]
[whooshing]
- Hello.
Are you ready to go to jail?
- This doesn't belong
in an auction house.
It doesn't belong
in someone's collection.
It belongs
to the Sioux people...
my people.
- Mina...I know
you've been through a lot,
but this is not the way to...
- I don't need to listen
to men like you anymore, Flash.
A few weeks ago,
something inside me changed...
changed for the better...
for the more powerful.
And now there's just
the Black Bison.
- [grunts]
[panting]
[whoosh]
- Oh, no, you don't.
[engine turns over]
♪ ♪
[tires screeching]
- [grunting]
[groans]
[crowd gasps]
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
[groans]
The power lines!
Get those people clear.
- But I can catch the meta!
[crowd screaming]
- Laura!
♪ ♪
- Whoa!
[groans]
♪ ♪
[distant sirens wailing]
- Told you I'd get her.
[electricity crackling]
- Hey, the power's out.
- Help!
Laura!
- I can't keep holding it up.
- Laura!
- [grunts]
- [sobbing]
- I got her.
- EMTs are almost here.
She's still breathing.
- Come on, wake up, honey.
Honey, come on!
Wake up!
[sobbing] Oh, God, oh, God.
Wake up, honey.
Oh, God, honey.
Honey, wake up.
[sobbing]
Come on, honey.
- Okay, you just rest up,
okay?
I'm gonna come back
and check on you
in a little while.
[solemn music]
- Well, mild concussion,
a hairline fracture
in her leg.
She's young.
She'll heal fast.
- Okay.
Thank you, doctor.
- You're very welcome.
But, considering the accident,
she's very lucky to be alive.
♪ ♪
- Look, Ralph.
We need to talk.
You can't...
- Don't.
Just...just forget it, okay?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- Hey, buddy.
You planning on bringing
the band back together,
or should I clear out
the Speed Lab?
- Broom it.
We don't need
that Council of Incompetents.
- Huh! Is that what
we're calling them now?
'Cause, uh, I distinctly
remember you saying
they were "the brightest minds
in all the multiverse."
- And the most annoying.
I thought
if I surrounded myself
with people like me,
I would like them.
I don't like them.
I hate them.
I hate them all.
- Hm. [clicks tongue]
Strong words.
- You saw them, Ramon, right?
That Wolfgang Wells?
He's always correcting people...
an extremely annoying habit.
The other guy...
the "Free Willy" Wells?
He's so full of himself.
And the other,
Cyborg Wells?
You know how he lost his eye?
His daughter gouged it out
at the Solstice Combat Games.
I don't blame her.
I'd have done the same.
I'd like to gouge out
the other eye.
- Harry.
- What?
- You know you're essentially
complaining about yourself,
right?
- [sighs]
Ramon...
do your best to pay attention
to the conversation.
I'm not complaining
about myself.
I'm complaining about them.
Yes, we're doppelgangers.
We look alike.
We have completely
different personalities.
- [scoffing]
So, you don't think
you can be quick
to correct people?
You don't think you can
be full of yourself?
- Full of myself?
No, I'm amazing.
I'm fantastic.
I'm talking about them.
I don't like them.
I hate them.
I hate them all.
- You know what I think?
I think this is entirely
about yourself.
I think underneath
all your brain and bluster,
you actually don't have
a very high opinion
of yourself.
- What?
- Why do you think it's so hard
for you to make new friends?
- [laughing]
I don't have a hard time...
- Harry.
No one's gonna like you if
you don't like yourself first.
These weirdos over here,
they...
they didn't have to answer
our call for help.
But they did...'cause
you would've done the same.
And yes, there are some
really annoying, rough parts
of you, but you know what?
I've seen some
amazing parts too.
'Cause sometimes, you're
a hard-ass, you're a hero.
Sometimes...
you're a wizard, Harry.
[poignant music]
The Council of Wells...
if you wanna make that work...
you have to start treating
yourself with some compassion.
♪ ♪
All of yourselves.
- Now is the time
that Simple Harry has come
to insult us even more?
- I didn't call to insult.
I called to...
[sighs]
Apologize.
- Apologize?
Apologizing is punishable
by banishment
under Krung the Face-Crusher!
- All right, well...
that's unfortunate.
Look, I know you guys prefer
to work alone.
You don't wanna work
with other people.
You think you're so smart,
you can just push them away,
and I can say that
because I'm one of you,
but if we're going to find
our DeVoe...
then we have to work together.
We have to work as...
friends.
- Friends...
with benefits?
Yeah, no, we're not doing that,
but I'm sure we can
all find something
that we like in one another...
like you, Wells 2.0.
You're clearly very...
resourceful and strong.
And you,
you're extremely charismatic.
I'm sure you can recruit
top talent
to your research teams.
- Oh, I bring the talent.
- Yeah...and you,
Herr Wells, you're very...
blunt.
- Ja. Obviously.
- Right, but can we just...
can you...
- Yeah, sure.
And I'm sorry, man.
What I said before
about your...you know,
your theory on
the behavioral upbringings
of nano-serial killers
being un-chill...
that was uncalled for.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's a very groovy theory.
Good on you.
- Ja...uh, danke.
I suppose that when I said
that your theory on narcotics
in molecular psychiatry was
stupider than a theory
made by tiny babies, that
that was uncalled for also.
- There we go.
- Yeah, and I'm digging
the whole creepy half-man,
half-metal vibe
you got going on.
- I just wanna say...
all of you...
I really respect the fact
that each one of you...
has two eyes.
- [stammers]
Yeah...hey, well, um,
we all agree on something.
That's great.
So, on that note,
I hereby reconvene
the Council of Wells.
Now, about our DeVoe...
- Well, about DeVoe...
perhaps if we were to combine
the Bates-Novick
of our mutant friend here
with my models
of statistical elimination...
- I'll do you one more.
Maybe we enhance
your elimination models
with a psych profile
based on
DeVoe's previous action.
I could whip up
a predictive algorithm.
- Ja, ja, ja, ja.
- Run it through
my quantum cerebral chip,
we'll find him in no time.
- I'm starting to see
why you called these guys.
- Yeah.
All right, gentlemen.
Let's get to work.
[knocking]
- [sighs]
If you're here to tell me
how I royally screwed up,
letting that little girl
get hurt...
trust me...I know.
I keep feeling
all these feelings...
guilt...remorse...heartburn.
- Well, I can't help you
with that last one,
but maybe I can help
with the rest.
What are all those?
- Past cases.
Those were simpler times.
Husband stepping out on wife,
wife stepping out on husband...
husband stepping out
on wife and husband.
That one was
a little less simple.
- Ralph, it was like you were
gonna make a point?
- My point is...
when I was a P.I., I...
I didn't have to worry about
little girls in hospitals.
I just had to get the dirt.
Whatever happened after that,
I wasn't there to see it.
Now all I see
are people getting hurt
or about to get hurt.
And then for five years,
I got by without caring
about anyone.
[solemn music]
Now I have to care about
a whole city?
♪ ♪
- It's a part of the job,
Ralph.
Maybe the most important part.
- How do you do it?
How do you walk around knowing
what could happen
to all those people?
- I...don't always
handle it well.
I've made bad decisions,
and sometimes
it got more people hurt.
You just gotta do
the best you can.
And when that's not enough,
you lean on
the people around you.
- Oh...you...
you mean you.
- [laughing]
Yeah, me, Ralph.
Look, I brought you into this
because I think that
you have the makings of a hero,
but I would be lying
if I said
there won't be hard days.
And when there are,
you need someone to turn to.
I can be that person...
if you want.
- You'd do that for me?
- I will make it
my personal mission
to protect your heart.
- [chuckles]
- [laughs]
Look, Ralph, I-I actually think
it's great
you're feeling all this stuff.
But don't forget:
that little girl
is gonna be okay.
And we got the bad guy.
- Yeah.
[hopeful music]
We got the bad guy.
- [chuckles]
[both chuckling]
Cop: Don't I know you
from somewhere?
- Not likely.
- No, I do.
I arrested you after one of
those protests last year.
- Don't touch me.
- Those artifacts are headed
for the museum.
And once the warden's people
get here,
you're headed to Iron Heights.
[door closes]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Gentlemen, feast your eyes
on this wonder.
This bad boy is replete
with polymer-coated,
flame-resistant armor,
frontal impact
deflection panels,
a dual-filtered gas mask...
so you don't cry
on your own supply.
[all chuckling]
Especially with this bad boy.
Call it the Onion.
Any questions?
[ominous music]
[grunts]
[all gasping]
[dramatic music]
[all coughing]
♪ ♪
- It's time we go
collect what's ours.
- Joe just called.
Chaytan escaped from CCPD.
- Apparently,
she made a tactical dummy
go full "Terminator"
at the station.
- Well,
we know where she's going.
- The necklace.
- The two pieces she stole
have been reunited with
the third piece at the museum.
- She has killed
for these before.
She will kill anyone that gets
in her way to reclaim them.
It's up to us.
Are you ready?
- Well...I was
until you said that.
- What are you...
- Jeez Louise, man.
What kind of rousing
"Braveheart" speech was that?
- Just put your thing on.
- Wanna help me?
- No.
- It's really tight.
- Hurry up!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hello, beautiful.
[sighs]
- Put it down, Mina.
- That belongs in a museum.
- This is a museum.
- I realized that
after I said it.
- Yes.
You keep it here
as part of American history.
But we're not history.
We are still here...
still sacred,
as is this necklace.
It's going back to the Sioux.
Get out of my way.
- Not after the people
you've hurt, Mina.
And you're not gonna hurt
anyone else.
- Is that so?
[whispering indistinctly]
[skeleton huffs]
[growling]
- Don't. Move.
Their vision. Is based.
On movement.
[growling]
[roars]
That movie is filled
with lies!
♪ ♪
We have a T. rex.
- Aah!
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- What's going on in here?
- Stop!
I got you.
[growling]
- [gasps]
- Whatcha gonna do, superhero?
♪ ♪
- [grunting, yelping]
For the love
of Jeff Goldblum, stop!
[grunting]
[flesh stretching]
[gasping, shouting]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
You're really never
going to stop chasing me,
are you?
- No, I'm really not.
- Do you have any idea
how many things
I can bring to life
in this place?
The gargoyles on the roof.
The reliefs carved
into the walls
and support pillars.
I can bring
this whole place down
in a matter of seconds.
- But you won't,
because there is one thing
you care about
more than vengeance,
isn't there?
♪ ♪
I kind of can't believe
you fell for that.
Come on.
- [shouts, grunts]
[flesh stretching]
[playful music]
- You almost let her escape.
- Well...
I kept hearing
your stupid voice
telling me to protect
the innocent.
- Nice job...rookie.
- [laughs]
[pants, sighs]
♪ ♪
Good boy.
Stay.
- All right, sounds good.
I'll let everybody know.
Hey.
That was Joe.
He says that Warden Wolfe
has Chaytan locked up
at Iron Heights...far, far away
from any mannequins,
statues, or...
- Effigies.
Looked it up.
Still say it sounds
kind of dirty,
but I'm not the mayor
of the dictionary, so whatever.
- [sighs] Joe also said
that the cleanup crew
at the museum still hasn't
found the bison necklace.
- Huh.
Guess somebody might have
mailed it back
to the Sioux reservation.
- Somebody?
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- You gonna yell at me again?
- No, not for this one.
♪ ♪
- Mina's friends and family...
they've been hurt for too long.
And I'm not sure if you've
heard this saying before,
but...a superhero's first job
is to protect people.
♪ ♪
- Wise words.
You want a coffee...on me?
For real this time.
- Uh...
thanks, but...
I gotta see about a girl.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Hey, kid.
How you doing?
- Better, thanks.
- [sighs]
That...
that's awesome.
- But I'm really bored.
- Yeah...
♪ ♪
Do you like balloon animals?
[flesh stretching]
[imitates dog sniffing]
Ruff.
- [giggles]
- Ruff, ruff, ruff.
Do a giraffe next.
- Okay, but...that might
take some toes.
[flesh stretching]
- [giggles]
- [sighs]
Hey.
What's going on?
- We think we know who he is.
- According to Harry's friends,
the name we're looking for
is Clifford...
[computer beeping]
Clifford DeVoe.
- 92% match to
our psychological profile.
No other DeVoe comes close.
- Guy keeps a low profile.
No social media,
no criminal record...
- And we know
where he's hiding.
43 Hibbard Lane.
- Well, if he's as dangerous
as you said...
I can call Singh.
We can get a squad over there.
- No.
[dark music]
Let's go get him.
♪ ♪
Guys,
Thawne, Zoom, Savitar...
for once, we actually
have a chance here
to get ahead of our enemy.
♪ ♪
Let's go get DeVoe.
- We're about to have guests.
- Then let's be ready
to greet them.
[suspenseful music]
[gun clicks]
- Is this the place?
- This is the one.
Is everyone set?
- "Eye in the Sky" is a go.
- I have eyes
on the front door.
[gun charges]
- Snow and Frost standing by.
- Just give us the word
and we'll breach in.
♪ ♪
- What kind
of criminal mastermind
has a welcome mat?
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[doorbell rings]
- Hi.
Can I help you?
- Uh, yes, ma'am.
I'm Detective Joe West, CCPD.
This is Barry Allen,
my associate.
- Is everything all right?
- Uh, yes...uh,
we were just hoping
to talk with Clifford DeVoe.
Is he here?
- Yes, he is.
May I ask what
this is about, officers?
- We just need to ask him
some questions.
- Is something wrong?
Is my husband in trouble?
- Your husband?
- No, ma'am.
- Clifford.
The police are here.
They'd like a word.
- Thank you, dear.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
I'm Clifford DeVoe.
How may I be of help?
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.