- NARRATOR: Last season on The Flash...
- (GASPS)
What's happening to me?
I wasn't the only one affected, was I?
DR. WELLS: We've been searching for
other meta-humans, like yourself.
Don't be afraid, Cisco,
you were affected, too.
- Once upon a time, you agreed to marry me.
- Yes, I did.
RONNIE: What do you say we do that?
Harrison Wells is the Reverse-Flash.
You killed my mother. Why?
We're enemies, rivals, opposites,
reverses of one another.
Just tell the police what you did.
Get my dad out of prison.
You can go back and save your mother.
A Wormhole?
MARTIN: Opening the gateway
into time itself.
REVERSE-FLASH: I always win, Flash.
JOE: Eddie!
CISCO: Eddie's his ancestor.
If Eddie dies, he'll never be born and
he's being erased from existence.
MARTIN: The Singularity won't stop,
not even after the earth is gone.
- We have to disrupt the motion!
- It cannot be stopped!
BARRY: I have to try.
(GRUNTS)
- Coming back around!
- Yeah, to die.
(GRUNTING)
I swear, one of these days,
I will kill you!
(GROANS)
I was late again, wasn't I?
Right on time.
Whoo!
(SIREN BLARING)
Two down at the same time.
Superhero double play, baby.
- Didn't do it alone.
- You're never alone, Barry.
Neither are you, Mrs. Raymond.
(CAITLIN CHUCKLES)
(GROANS) Thank you for not doing that
when I was inside you.
It happened one time, let it go.
Snart and Rory. You're gonna put
a cop like me out of a job.
Just trying to help.
You do more than help, Barry.
You give the people of this city hope.
You're the hero, Barry.
Congratulations, everyone.
A spectacular victory.
A milestone, if you will.
Mr. Allen,
I believe there's nothing left
I can teach you.
I believe
you're ready to do all of this
on your own.
(BEEPING)
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
And I became the Flash.
I used my powers to find the man
responsible for my mother's death.
I thought I would finally get justice
for my family.
But I failed.
It's been six months
since the Singularity.
I'm on my own now.
Decided it's better that way.
Keeps the people I care about safe.
There's only one thing I can do now.
I run.
How's it going?
Hey. Uh, good.
- How you doing?
- Good.
So, the victim, his name's Al Rothstein.
He's a welder here at the nuclear plant.
Co-worker found him this morning.
So what do you got?
Uh...
Petechia on his face,
in the whites of his eyes
and this bruising around his neck.
- Oh, so he was strangled?
- Mmm-hmm.
- By someone very strong and very large.
- Or something.
- Well, this wasn't Grodd.
- Oh, thank God.
(GRUNTS)
Look, I'll let you know when I find more.
So, this Flash Day thing?
I'm hoping you're planning on
making an appearance.
Uh... No, I haven't decided.
Barr, I heard the mayor's
trying to give you the key to the city.
- Yeah, I don't need an award.
- You love getting awards.
Like all those science trophies
you got in high school?
Those I deserved.
I'll let you know what I find, all right?
All right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
REPORTER: (ON TV)
Flash Day is almost here,
a special downtown rally
to honor the man who saved Central City.
It's been six months
since the Flash saved Central City
from the freak black hole
that erupted in the sky.
CAPTAIN: Joe, where are we at
with the murder at the nuclear plant?
Barry's still analyzing the evidence,
but there was definitely something weird.
Yeah, which is why I let you have that
anti-meta-human task force.
Speaking of which,
where is your scientific advisor?
CISCO: Ho, ho, ho!
Fear the beard.
It's a very distinguished look, sir.
What is all this, Mr. Ramon?
Oh, this right here?
This is a little something I'm working on.
I'm cooking it up for Joe and
the task force to take down meta-humans.
I think I'm gonna call it the Boot.
Oh, here are the receipts.
(SIGHS)
- Oh, um, Captain, one more thing...
- You are not getting a badge, Mr. Ramon.
(LAUGHS)
He's really stingy with those badges,
isn't he?
Yeah, cops are funny that way.
So, you really think
you can get this to work?
Don't have me caught out on the street
with my pants down.
Yes, once I finish the Boot,
C.C.P.D. will totally have
what it needs to take down a meta-human.
Especially now that Barry's decided to go
all Lone Wolf McQuade,
- and fight crime by himself.
- I know, right? Have you spoken to him?
Not really,
haven't even heard from Caitlin
since she started work at Mercury Labs.
- Hey, Cisco. Hi, Dad.
- Hey, baby.
Hey, I was wondering if
you talked to Barry about the rally.
- We were just saying.
- (LAUGHS)
I'm sorry, but I can't believe
they're gonna give the Flash
the key to the city.
Although, technically,
as members of Team Flash,
- we should all be getting keys.
- JOE: Uh, you know Barry.
The more we try to convince him
to do something,
- the less he's gonna wanna do it.
- Yeah, but he should go.
Someone should try and get through to him.
Maybe his best friend.
Joe, believe me, I've tried.
I meant her.
Bye, babe.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(HAMMERING)
(METAL CLAN KING)
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(EXHALES)
You know, if you ever decided that
you didn't wanna be the Flash,
you have a good future
at being a contractor.
(CHUCKLES) Thanks.
Yeah, I'm just trying to put it all back
exactly how it was before the...
(SIGHS) You know.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Seems like a lot of local businesses
are being rebuilt at night.
In secret.
I was thinking about writing an article
about it for the paper.
Don't. Please.
Look, people have heard the stories,
they've read the articles,
they've maybe even seen
the red streak racing past them.
But they have never seen the Flash, Barry.
So that's why you're here?
You came to talk me into
going to the rally?
'Cause I'm not gonna go.
People just wanna thank the man
who saved Central City.
Well, they can't, 'cause that's not me.
You should know that better than anyone.
(SIGHS)
Central City believes in the Flash.
So do I.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SHRIEKING)
Brilliant! He's contained the Singularity
by adding to its angular momentum.
Barry, it's stabilizing!
Keep doing what you're doing!
I'm not sure how much longer I can.
- Cisco?
- Now what?
We have to merge
the inner and outer event horizons.
How do we do that?
By separating in the eye of it.
The amount of energy from the fissure
should do the trick.
It's our only hope, Ronald.
Ronnie, no. It's too dangerous.
What if you can't escape the inrush?
Cait, we have to try.
Ronnie.
Professor.
No!
(GROANS)
Ronald? Ronald...
I'm so sorry.
(CAITLIN SOBS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Are you expecting trouble?
Cops always expect trouble.
In this city,
I expect super-evil flying monsters.
That's a solid expectation.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I'll be... (CHUCKLES)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Good morning, Central City.
A year ago, our world changed.
Our city became ground zero
for some pretty weird stuff.
(EXHALES)
We got a new breed of criminal.
Men and women
who defied not only our laws,
but physics and reason.
But we got something else, too.
We got the Flash.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Our wounds run deep,
and I know many of you are afraid
of what threats tomorrow may bring.
But the Flash doesn't just protect us,
he restores hope where it was lost.
That's why I'm honored to present the key
to the man who saved Central City.
The Flash!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD CHANTING)
Flash! Flash! Flash! Flash! Flash!
Flash. Flash.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
The doors to Central City
will forever be open for you, Flash.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Look out!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- You all right?
- (EXHALES)
I got this, all right?
The man who saved Central City.
Hate to rain on your parade.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(GROANS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
JOE: Cisco?
Cisco! The Boot!
Right.
Locked and loaded. Go.
(WHIRRING)
Booted.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GRUNTS)
(ROARS)
Cisco, you said this thing would
take him down. He's not going down.
(THE FLASH GROANS)
He went up.
Run. Run!
- What are you doing?
- I'm throwing, you're shooting.
(JOE PANTING)
(THE FLASH GROANING)
(PANTING)
That's Al Rothstein.
The body we found at the nuclear plant.
He's alive.
According to the coroner's office,
Al Rothstein's body
was in the morgue all night,
so we can scratch off zombie attack.
- JOE: Rothstein have a twin brother?
- Nope, only child.
And get this,
the night the accelerator exploded,
Rothstein was on his honeymoon in Hawaii.
Huh.
So we're looking for a guy who's
really strong, can grow twice his size,
and just happens to look exactly like
the guy he murdered?
I would think this meta was really cool
if everything about him
didn'tjust terrify me to my core.
Is that what happened to you?
You looked really spooked there
for a minute.
Uh...
I actually see the guy
that I can ask about it, right now.
Call you back, okay? Hey.
So, the hospital
next to the Flash Day rally?
The X-ray and CT machines
all failed at once.
Was that because of you?
I did not do anything
that would cause that.
I'm 92% sure.
I'm gonna go make that 100. Excuse me.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- You okay?
We need to talk.
Okay.
Barry can't do this alone anymore.
(SIGHS)
That's his plan, and I don't know
how to talk him out of it.
At this point, I'm just trying not to
push him further away.
Well, maybe Barry has been so successful
at pushing you, me and everyone else away
because we keep letting him.
Let's not let him.
What do you suggest?
Well, if you keep getting no
for an answer, stop asking questions.
- I say that. You quoting me to me?
- What can I say, you are a very smart man.
(LAUGHS)
(TYPING)
So, this is what it looks like
inside Mercury Labs.
Security here is way better
than it was at S.T.A.R. Labs,
what, with people walking in and out
of the Cortex all the time.
Hi, Cisco.
Sweet Sarek, is that a 6K proton splicer?
Yes, it is. Dr. McGee insists on having
all the latest technology.
Wow.
You deserve it. (LAUGHS)
I spotted you at the rally today,
and I'm guessing you saw what happened.
Cisco, I can't come back.
Okay, check this out, we found this
on a victim at the nuclear power plant.
But the badge shows absolutely nothing
at all, which is so weird.
And what's also weird is that
at the same time that meta-human grew,
all the X-ray machines
within a mile radiusjust went belly up.
- Cisco...
- Just...
If you could just see if the badge
was tampered with or something?
I mean, if it's broken or whatever.
It would really help.
(MOUTHING) Yes.
MAN: Mr. Allen? Barry Allen?
- Yeah.
- I'm Greg Turk.
I'm an attorney at Weathersby and Stone.
I don't usually make house calls, but
I've been trying to get in touch with you
- for several months.
- Yes, yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I've just, um...
I've been really busy with police work.
We need to talk about S.T.A.R. Labs.
As you know, Harrison Wells
left the property to you
as part of his living trust.
Yeah, which I did not ask him to do,
but I've been keeping the place up.
Well, it's gonna take more than cleaning
the floors to retain it, I'm afraid.
The facility and the real estate
are scheduled to go into receivership
at the end of this week.
Unless
you watch this.
- What is this?
- A video message drafted by Dr. Wells.
- What's on it? Have you seen it?
- No.
He was very specific.
It was only to be watched by you.
The device will send me a notification
after you've viewed it,
and at that point,
I'll have everything ready to execute.
- I'm not gonna watch that.
- Well, that's up to you, Mr. Allen.
I'm only here to represent
Harrison Wells's final request. Good day.
(BEEPING)
- What are you guys doing here?
- LRIS: Working.
So, Caitlin was right.
Yes, all humans contain
small amounts of radiation
due to contact with cell phones,
microwaves, televisions, et cetera.
Our bodies are natural conductors.
I think our meta's been sucking up
all the radiation around him
and using it to power himself.
Which is why the X-ray machines at the
hospital failed the day of the rally.
So if we wanna find him, we got to look
for places without radiation.
All right, guys,
I don't want any of you here right now.
Tough. You need your partners.
You need your friends.
IRIS: Barry, everyone in this room
cares about you.
But we also care about this city.
We all wanna make a difference,
and that means fighting meta-humans,
and that means working with the Flash.
You can't deny us that. Not anymore.
Got him. There's a three-block dead zone
near a hazardous waste reclamation plant.
It should be blooming with rads,
and right now it's at zero.
That's where you'll find
your Atom Smasher.
Huh.
Because he absorbs atomic power and he,
well, smashes.
Come here.
(LAUGHS)
- That's a great name. Welcome to the team.
- Thank you.
Great. Guys, thank you.
You can go now, all right?
Barry, you need to let Cisco and Stein
figure out a way to stop this guy.
No, I don't.
(SIGHS)
Barry left his comm system behind.
We can't talk to him. He's on his own.
(SIGHS)
Ah!
Well, this is a curveball.
I thought I was going to have to come
looking for you.
I'm not gonna let you hurt anyone else.
- I'm only here to hurt you, buddy.
- Yeah?
Then why did you kill Albert Rothstein?
And why do you look like him?
- You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
- (LAUGHS) Try me.
I'm about to.
Is there really no way of knowing
what's going on in there?
I'm looking for the security cameras.
Booya!
(GRUNTING)
My turn.
(CHOKING)
Dad.
- Maybe I can make it there.
- No, you won't.
And what are you gonna do
when you get there?
- The Boot didn't work on him.
- Alarm.
- Believe me, we're all alarmed.
- No, the alarm system.
You've tapped into
the surveillance cameras, correct?
Correct.
Come on, feel the noise.
(GROANING)
He said you were some kind of big hero.
But you don't seem worthy of him
or this city.
(ALARM BLARING)
Professor Stein, you are a genius.
I believe
that's already been well established.
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING)
No, thank you.
Iris says mac and cheese is your favorite.
I'm not hungry.
It's been six months, Barry.
You got to eat, son.
It's a good move,
being angry all the time.
I get it.
You miss your mom and dad, and you wanna
show them that you're strong.
Being mad makes it easier.
Tougher thing to do
would be to let yourself feel.
It's okay to be sad.
You can be sad, Barry.
Your parents will understand
if you're not strong all the time.
That is why I'm here.
It's okay, son. I got you.
(BEEPING)
You're good, I got you.
Where is everyone?
I figured you wouldn't want an audience
when you came to.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, thanks.
Iris is right.
We're not gonna do this anymore.
For the last six months,
I've given you your space
to work all this out, come back to us.
But today proved that
you'd rather just get yourself killed.
(LAUGHS)
It's better than
getting my friends killed.
You want me to tell you
that it wasn't your fault?
I can't. It was. Guess what?
You weren't the only person
making decisions that day.
All of the rest of us were there, too.
Eddie and Ronnie...
They chose to help you stop Wells,
and stop that...
- Singularity.
- Singularity thing.
It's on all of us, Barry.
So stop with this
hogging all the blame and regret.
We got to live with it.
Move on.
What do I do now?
Well, I know that you've been
rebuilding Central City at night.
That's just bricks and paint.
Maybe you should start trying to rebuild
things that really matter.
What are you doing here?
Sorry, I should've called or something.
I just... I wanted to see you.
It's been a while.
Yeah, Cisco said that he saw you
at the Flash Day celebration.
I was surprised.
You better than anyone know that
I wasn't the hero that day.
- Of course you were.
- No.
(SIGHS)
Cait, Ronnie died saving me and I...
I should've saved him and I'm so sorry.
Barry, I know that you did
everything you could.
It wasn't your fault.
I don't blame you for Ronnie's death.
I blame myself.
You...
Why?
(SIGHS)
When Ronnie first became Firestorm,
he asked me to leave Central City
and go somewhere
that we could have a normal life.
And I said no.
I couldn't leave S.T.A.R. Labs,
Dr. Wells, you.
If I had gone with him,
Ronnie would still be alive.
Being at S.T.A.R. Labs
just made think of that every single day.
- Here.
- (CHUCKLES)
Oh, you carry a handkerchief now?
What are you, 80?
(CLEARS THROAT)
- What's that?
- Uh, it's uh...
Apparently, in the case of his death,
Wells had some kind of, um, living will.
- And you haven't watched it yet?
- No.
No, I've been too afraid.
What if we watched it together?
All right.
(EXHALES)
Hello, Barry. If you're watching this,
that means
something has gone horribly wrong.
I'm dead, and the last 15 years
have been for nothing.
Bummer, 15 years. (LAUGHS)
You know what I realized?
In all those years helping raise you,
we were never truly enemies, Barry.
I'm not the thing you hate.
And so I'm gonna give you the thing
that you want most.
It won't matter.
You'll never be truly happy. Barry Allen.
Trust me, I know you.
Now, erase everything
I said up to this point.
Give the following message to the police.
My name is Harrison Wells.
Being of sound mind and body,
I freely confess to the murder
of Nora Allen in her home
on the night of March 18th,
in the year 2000.
- I attacked Nora Allen...
- CAITLIN: Oh, my God.
(VIDEO CONTINUES PLAYING)
He confessed.
This is it.
(LAUGHS)
This is what I need to free my dad.
Hey, Joe. Yeah. Hey, can you have
everybody meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs?
Yeah. All right, thanks.
Yeah, all right, bye.
(EXHALES)
- I'll drive.
- Okay.
Do you think the video's enough?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, sure.
- What's she saying?
- Hold on.
Wells gave all the right details.
It's not a done deal yet,
but the D.A. says it looks good.
Yeah, I'm here.
Is it good news?
- I think so.
- Henry's coming home?
(EXCLAIMS)
Okay. Well, that still leaves
Atom Smasher to deal with.
Last time you faced him,
it did not go well.
No, it did not.
I clearly can't stop him by myself.
So how are we gonna beat him?
Well, ever since
I was shown a drained radiation tag,
which I haven't been able
to stop thinking about, thank you, Cisco.
You're welcome, Caitlin.
If this guy likes radiation so much,
I say we give it to him.
(SIGHS)
Showtime.
What's up? I see you got my message.
That light was perfect bait.
What made you think of that?
I don't know, I think I saw it
in a comic book somewhere.
You want me,
you're gonna have to catch me.
It's working, dude.
Rothstein's following you.
I must say,
he's quite agile for a man his size.
- Run, Barry, run.
- Come on.
(BEEPING)
- (CRASHING)
- (ROARING)
Didn't think I could catch you, huh?
No, I knew you could.
Now, Cisco!
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(ALARM BLARING)
The amount of radiation
about to flood that room...
Atom Smasher
won't be able to absorb it all.
(ROARING)
(ATOM SMASH ER GROAN I NG)
(BEEPING)
The radiation's been cleared.
It's safe for you to go in.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't let you hurt anyone else.
Why?
Why did you wanna kill me?
He promised he'd take me home...
If I killed you.
Who? Who promised you that?
(GASPING)
Zoom.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
(CHUCKLES)
Let's get out of here.
I'll race you.
(LAUGHS)
You will lose.
(BOTH LAUGH)
- Welcome home!
- (ALL CHEERING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Gather around, everyone, please.
(SIGHS)
Looking at all of you,
thinking how far we've all come,
and remembering those
who are no longer with us,
I'm reminded of a Hebrew word
used during times of graduation.
Kadima.
It means...
Forward.
- Forward.
- Well said.
- Thank you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- You good?
- Yeah.
That stuff goes to your head
after being away from it
- for 14 years.
- I bet. (LAUGHS)
All right, well, look.
I was thinking, what, uh,
if in the morning,
the two of us started looking
for an apartment for both of us?
And Iris actually has been doing
some research on
how to get your medical license back
so you, uh, could start
your practice up again?
Or if you wanted,
come work with us at S.T.A.R. Labs?
- I don't know. I mean...
- (CHUCKLES)
What's wrong? You okay?
Um, yeah, it's a party, come on,
we can talk about all this tomorrow.
- Talk about what?
- Barry.
Are you not planning on sticking around?
Okay.
Okay, do you think...
Can you be all that you are becoming
with me here?
(CHUCKLES)
You're the only family that I have left.
Well, that's not really true, is it?
Don't you have another family
in this room?
They need your help too, Barry.
When you need me, I will be here.
But right now, Central City
doesn't need you to be Henry Allen's son,
it needs you to be
the Flash.
My kid...
The superhero.
I have to go.
I need you to tell me that it's okay.
Yeah, all right.
- Hey.
- JOE: Hey.
- Your dad get off okay?
- Yeah, I just dropped him at the station.
You good?
I don't know.
It just feels like every time I win,
I still lose.
Well...
It's not bad.
- No, it's not bad.
- (CHUCKLES)
- This is pretty cool. (LAUGHS)
- lt's really cool! Come on.
- Hey.
CISCO: Oh!
Hey, guess what?
I added a little upgrade to your suit.
(BARRY LAUG HS)
It's just like the one from the
future newspaper Gideon showed us.
I was thinking, you know, we shouldn't
fear the future anymore, right?
No, and it'll be here
faster than we think.
I must say, I like it, the lightning
definitely pops more against the white.
And S.T.A.R. Labs is now safer than ever.
Increased security and surveillance.
Re-coded, double fire-walled
electronic locksets.
Nothing is getting through here
without us knowing.
So people can'tjust waltz
in and out of here.
- Exactly.
- (CAITLIN GASPS)
- For real?
- Stay where you are.
Who are you?
You don't know me, but I know you,
Barry Allen.
Take one more step,
it'll be the last step you take.
The man asked you a question.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Jay Garrick.
And your world is in danger.