He was the most
brilliant mind I ever met.
They all were.
Whatever the problem,
you could...
count on a Wells...
a council of them to have the answers.
Now...
they're all gone.
We gotta find the answers ourselves.
Why does it always feel like
for us to win,
some of us have to lose?
This wall is nano-engraved
with the names of everyone we've lost.
So that no matter
how the timeline changes...
they'll never be forgotten.
Those Wells...
they took some getting used to,
didn't they?
If we learned anything from them,
it was that our greatest weapon
against darkness
isn't our superpowers.
It's our humanity.
And our love for each other.
Barr?
Barr... I know what you're doing.
Don't blame yourself.
What you just said...
Ramsey infecting me,
Eva using a copy of Iris
to manipulate my emotions...
Lately, it feels like my heart
is my enemy's greatest weapon.
Have faith, son.
We will get Iris back.
I feel that in my heart.
What the...
This is supposed to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse?
Yeah. Supposed to.
I thought I could use Atlantean tech
to tackle perpetual motion,
one of science's greatest problems.
But guess what I found waiting for me?
More problems. This thing's a dud.
I don't know what to do.
I lost my friend...
my girlfriend is trapped
in another dimension...
and nothing my brain comes up with
seems to get me any closer
to saving her.
I promise you, we will get them back.
Kamilla, Iris, Singh. All of 'em.
Yeah.
Okay.
Refocusing.
So, Chester's away at Grandma Runk's,
but lucky for us,
he's been scienceing
in between bingo rounds
and he seems to think
there are two problems
we need to solve
if we wanna open our portal.
Problem number one.
You haven't found the method
to reconfigure the molecular stability
of the dimensional barrier
that damages organic matter?
Yeah, that's right.
How did you know that?
I saw you write it.
No, you didn't.
I thought I did.
I was about to.
But you guessed right.
Eva used Ramsey's blood
to tackle that problem,
and open her portal.
Unfortunately, for us,
without a replacement
for Ramsey's evil sentient goo,
we're kind of up a creek.
So that brings us to problem number two.
Quantum entanglement from reversed
Higgs boson particles
disrupts the geo-spatial algorithm,
preventing us from locating people
in the Mirrorverse.
Meaning, we have to know Kamilla, Singh,
and Iris' location
in order to pull them out.
You freaky.
I know where they'll be.
Iris sent a message to Kamilla
and Singh in the Mirrorverse,
telling them to meet
in the Speed Lab tonight.
Don't ask me how I got it
'cause I have no idea.
Iris's neural pathways have likely
achieved an equilibrium
with the harmonic frequency contained
within the fractalized
dimensional plane.
He freaky.
Our mission's going
better than expected.
Hoshi and Ultraviolet's raids
on Black Hole stash houses
have liberated crates
of your mirror-tech.
Good.
Rawlins, do you notice anything...
different about me?
Sorry?
Do you see anything out of place?
Yeah. Now, that you mention it.
You look tired.
Your desk is a mess
and you skipped your coffee today.
You got me.
But there is something...
familiar.
That look in your eyes.
It's how Carver looked
when he kept secrets from us.
I'm nothing like Joseph.
I will never lie to you.
I promise.
Good. Because we've located
our next stash house.
Want me to gather the Assassins Three?
No.
It's been a while since I've enjoyed
the pleasure of tearing down
my husband's empire, so...
I will handle this one myself.
So, he's what, a genius now?
No, I'm a genius.
My guy's on a whole other level.
His neurons are firing at super-speed,
synaptic connections are off the charts.
The quantum computers can't
even keep up processing his results!
The Artificial Speed Force.
The Artificial Frackin' Speed Force.
It didn't just give you
your old powers back,
it gave you a new one.
Enhanced cognition by way
of a Speed Force booster shot!
Huh?
Barry can think fast, now.
Cool. How fast?
Let's find out, shall we?
Lady and gentleman, this...
is a Quantum Ball. Trademark pending.
Ever heard of it? Of course you haven't.
But you will.
Mark my words, one day, Quantum Ball,
trademark pending,
will be the world's
next great sporting event.
You see, this little sphere
amplifies kinetic energy,
firing in directions that can only be
described as... unpredictable.
But not for you.
Your enhanced cognition should let you
analyze every variable,
in every scenario.
And predict the unpredictable.
Barry Allen.
Places, please.
Call it.
Eh... no cheating. Turn around.
Ready.
Wall, lamp,
pipe, conduit... Duck. Now!
I have super-speed thinking.
I know how to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse.
- Uh... what?
- Yeah, repeat that.
For Allegra.
All right. I'm sorry. I'm...
Let me show you.
Ramsey's unique cells
created a polar-covalent bond
with the molecules
in Eva's mirror portal.
That's why she needed his blood.
Right. It formed like
a bio-friendly skin
on the inter-dimensional barrier.
So, we need Ramsey's blood.
We knew that.
No, we don't need it.
His blood would have bonded
with the electro-negative particles
and become dark matter photons.
Those particles wouldn't just stay
on the mirror portal.
No, they wouldn't.
They'd attach themselves to Eva.
Those photons are still on her.
If we could collect them,
we could open our portal.
But it would take years to develop
a prototype that could do that.
Not if we integrate the neural net
in The Thinker's chair,
synched to a nanite bridge, fed into the
Tachyon Enhancer's non-reductive loop.
No. But wait, wouldn't...
Well...
Yeah... I guess that could work.
But isn't Eva still holed up
behind McCulloch Tech's force field?
We'll never get close to her.
You're gonna bring out another board.
Factoring in geographical
analytics, concealment probability,
these are the remaining
Black Hole stash houses.
There's a 97.6% chance
Eva's hitting this one next.
Right, so...
that's where we go,
and that's what we do.
Just wish I could
have seen it earlier.
This isn't on you.
We wouldn't be in this mess
if I had seen through
Iris' mirror duplicate sooner.
Eva's not the first to use my emotions
against me.
Let's make sure she's the last.
- Kamilla.
- Iris.
Thank God.
When you disappeared, I thought
that neural dissonance sickness got you.
Yeah, well,
she tried to use it against me,
but I was able to fight her off.
I think
I've been in this place for so long,
that I've gained control over it.
I think that's how I was able to send
you and Singh that message.
That's amazing.
What about Singh?
Did you find him at the hospital?
I looked everywhere, but...
Iris, what if we never find him?
What if we never escape?
What if we stay here so long,
that our minds just get
completely destroyed...
Kamilla, we've been through
our fair share of danger.
So, no matter what dimension we're in,
no matter what kind of villain we face,
there is nothing that can stop us
as long as we stick together.
- Are you with me?
- Let's do this.
Good.
Because I'm thinking
if my message got to you,
then it could have gotten to Singh, too.
So let's go find him. Come on.
That doesn't belong to you.
Then again, it never belonged
to my husband, either.
It was my reflective chip technology
that was twisted to create that weapon.
So, it's mine...
to wield or destroy. Now, step aside.
Go! Go!
You were right.
Eva's here, and she's amped.
How do you like
your phantom now, Joseph?
Not the day for us
to be short-staffed.
Actually, we're good.
I called in a little bit
of extra muscle.
S'up?
Nice outfit, by the way.
Why are you here?
You know, for funsies.
Looks like
someone's back to a 100%.
Long live the Snow Queen.
Eva's faster than me.
Frost is gonna distract her,
while I run by with the Tachyon Enhancer
and collect the particles we need.
We might only get one shot at this.
Let's make it count.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Frost!
Barry, help her!
Frost.
You let her get hit.
Whatever Eva hit Frost with,
it's light-based.
Her healing's trying to compensate,
but it's not enough.
I can't fix this without Caitlin.
- What is that?
- A cure.
Has it been tested?
I ran 2,371 tests in my head.
We're good.
Barry, that is not...
What are you doing?
What happened?
You took the brunt of
Eva's laser blast to help us.
I just returned the favor
with a cryogenically fortified
paracetamol cocktail.
That fortified my cellular walls.
Yep. That'll do it.
Of course you wouldn't have had to
take the brunt of the blast
if Barry hadn't let you get hit
in the first place.
- Cisco, let me explain.
- Barry...
What were you thinking? I saw you. I...
You had the time
to run her out of the way,
and you just stood there
like you wanted her to get hit.
There was a.0002% chance
of the Tachyon Enhancer getting damaged
in that scenario.
I couldn't risk that.
I also knew I could reverse
any ill effects
Frost received from Eva's blast.
These aren't ill effects!
This was a light wound.
Like the kind that almost killed her.
And we just got her back!
Cisco, it's okay.
I'm fine, and now,
we have a chance to save our friends.
I'd take a hit for that any day.
You got lucky with that cocktail.
Luck had nothing to do with it.
So... super-speed thinking, huh?
What's that like?
Sometimes, it's like a barrage
of images flying at me.
Others, it's like a scene
playing out in my head.
So...
what is your speed-brain say
our next move is?
You saw Iris' message. Eva's watching.
She would no doubt
see our attempt to open a portal
to the Mirrorverse and stop us.
I need to find a solution.
You should recuperate for 14.2 minutes.
Then help Cisco gather
all our McCulloch intel,
so I can cross-reference it
with our Eva data.
I need to aggregate.
Huh.
Well, Barry seems like
he has things in hand and then some.
Yep. He'll probably have this Eva sitch
wrapped up in no time.
You're thinking about Nash.
I'm sorry.
Honey, it's just my empathic abilities,
they take on
a mind of their own, sometimes.
It's okay. It's just...
My dad left me before I could walk.
And ever since then,
anyone's who's even
come close to being...
A father figure?
Yeah, I...
I cut them out of my life
before they could cut me out of theirs.
That's why I pushed Nash away.
Anyway, I should just get over it.
He's gone.
Only if you let him be.
Did you know that the law goes
way back in my family?
Yeah, my granddad was the first
Black paralegal in Oklahoma,
and my mom,
first female independent counsel
in the State of Texas.
Both of them were pioneers
for social justice, and my heroes.
- I'll say.
- Yeah.
Right now, my granddad's file cabinet
is in the corner of my office.
And I carry my mom's briefcase
into court with me every single day.
Honey, the people that we love,
they're only gone
when we stop carrying them with us.
How you choose to carry Nash
is up to you.
I figured out her secret.
This isn't her world. It never has been.
Thank you, Arielle.
I'm glad to to be here.
- I'm lucky to be anywhere.
- Indeed.
Let's jump right into it.
You came here today,
to make an announcement.
Yes.
Before I was kidnapped,
I was developing technologies
with promise to advance the world.
Fresh water. Healthier crops.
Clean renewable energy.
I am thrilled to finally return
to my life's work.
Improving our world.
Why are we watching this?
At the stash house,
Eva referred to herself as a phantom.
It reminded me of Carver's
dying words when Eva killed him,
that she wasn't his wife.
I've analyzed behavioral patterns,
body language,
even graphological handwriting.
That... is not Eva McCulloch.
What? What do you mean?
She's sitting right there,
talking to Rachel Maddow 2.0.
I slept in the same bed
with a mirror duplicate of Iris
without knowing the difference.
You did the same with Kamilla.
So, you think this is a mirror Eva?
McCulloch security database
will show us.
Yeah, good luck.
I tried hacking them a week ago.
What? How?
McCulloch's black box servers
run a hybrid theorem-proving system
with model-checking.
His mind is getting faster.
Yes, it is.
Did she just die?
- Oh, my God.
- No.
Help!
Someone help me!
Which brings us to why
you're here today.
Precisely. Allow me to present
McCulloch Technologies' future
for humanity.
Whoa, what you doing with that footage?
Exposing the truth.
Eva?
No. No, please stay with me.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
Help!
No! Stop that... Stop!
No! Stop!
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- That footage we saw,
does it show you killing
the real Eva McCulloch?
No, of course I wouldn't do that.
- I didn't do that.
- What are you?
A meta?
- A shapeshifter?
- No. I...
The world wants answers.
We deserve to know.
Rawlins!
If you're not Eva McCulloch,
who or what are you?
I'm not a monster.
I'm not a monster!
Why did you do that?
Eva would sense us opening a portal.
Now, she is too distracted to notice.
And there couldn't be
another way to distract her?
There were 141 ways.
This was the most efficient.
Uh, I'm not sure emotionally wrecking
an already whacked out villain
was "efficient."
Historically speaking,
when our enemies are upset,
which is exactly what I accomplished,
they make mistakes.
We need to prep the portal machine
while Eva's on her heels,
and then retrieve our targets.
You mean our friends.
One and the same.
- Cisco...
- I know.
Something's seriously wrong with Barry.
Greetings, Barry Allen.
Your biological signals
indicated state of distress.
- May assist you?
- I needed a second opinion, Gideon.
I just ran the necessary calculations
to operate Cisco's portal device.
The results have me concerned.
Analyzing
temporal-spatial data.
Estimated time to complete
quantum computations, 18.4 hours.
Invert the Feynman shortcut and apply it
to one-half mass times velocity squared,
compensating for tachyon decay.
Thank you
for a more efficient method.
Calculations complete.
I was correct.
We cannot save all of them.
We have to choose.
Would you like me to inform
the rest of the team?
What do you mean
we have to choose?
Simply put, the longer
the person is in the Mirrorverse,
the more dark matter photons
are required to pull them out.
Kamilla and Singh
have been trapped for less time,
therefore, they can be
retrieved together.
With Iris...
It would take everything
we have to retrieve her.
There's got to be another way.
Barry? What's your speed-brain tell you?
We have to choose.
Kamilla and Singh. Or Iris.
It is the only way.
How the hell are we supposed to do that?
- I guess... we vote.
- On this?
I don't know. Dude,
do you know another way to be fair?
This is beyond screwed up.
But if this is the only way...
who thinks we should save Iris?
And Kamilla and Singh?
Sorry, Barry.
Got to go with the numbers.
Are you all right, Barry Allen?
You appear to be distracted.
I just ran a simulation
to see how this will play out.
Would you like me to inform
the rest of the team
of this development?
No.
This is something I must do alone.
Are you sure, that's the best...
What is all this stuff?
I have no idea.
Iris, help me, please.
David.
David, can you hear me?
Is this Neural Dissonance?
No, but it's similar.
It's a side effect of being sent
to the Mirrorverse by the Mirror Gun,
instead of Eva pulling
Singh through her office mirror.
How do you know that?
I don't know, I just do.
Iris, I was shot, too, with...
Kamilla!
Hey.
Talk for a sec?
Of course.
What's with the suit?
We're about to open
a portal to the Mirrorverse.
One must be prepared.
Right. About that...
I looked over the schematics,
and I think there might be something
wrong with the Artificial Speed Force.
You remember how Thawne
used negative emotion
to stabilize his Speed Force machine?
Well, since we didn't want
to make the same mistake,
we used an inert substance,
an argon-xenon hybrid
that would generate
no emotional fallout.
But I think that was a mistake.
Yes, the ASF gave you...
increased cognitive function...
a thousand times over, but...
it's done the exact opposite
to your emotional response.
I'm better this way.
The team is safer this way.
Look, man...
I know you think your heart
has been used against you...
but it's not a weakness.
It's what makes you human.
I mean, without it...
Why's the portal target set to Iris?
What about saving the others?
We do not have enough dark matter
photons to save all three of them.
So, instead of consulting your team...
you just decided on your own.
I've already seen
the outcome of this debate.
You eventually vote to save
Kamilla and Singh...
Like hell, I would never vote
on something like that.
If you would come to me, I would have
told you we'll find another way.
That's what we always do.
Your emotions are making you irrational.
And your lack of them
are making you wrong!
You cannot predict
what I would have done
because you cannot predict emotion!
Barry... I know you.
I know your heart and I know that
you're doing this because you miss Iris.
My feelings are irrelevant.
Iris has knowledge of Eva,
which could give us
a tactical advantage.
Therefore, Iris is
the logical choice to liberate.
The fact is, Singh and Kamilla
are expendable.
Expendable?
Don't ever call her expendable.
We're gonna give you
back your heart, Barry.
And it's gonna be by choice.
Or by force.
Don't make us do this, Barry.
Iris would agree with me.
No, she wouldn't.
You've just been hit
with Velocity-Zero charge.
It temporarily dampens your speed.
You're not the only one
who could predict reactions.
Your defeat is inevitable.
Velocity X in your system
is nearly depleted.
Your time as a speedster
is coming to an end.
Maybe... but I'm not only a speedster.
The Babel Protocols aren't just
force fields and tech. It's us.
- Sorry for the tough love.
- But we need the real you back.
Don't worry.
We're going to shut off
the Artificial Speed Force
and get your head straight.
You lost this fight
before it even began.
Look out!
Hang on, guys. I'm gonna get you
to the Med Lab, and we'll get you some...
Barry.
Oh, my God.
Please tell me this isn't a trick.
Your message to Kamilla and Singh
led us here.
I'm ready to bring you home now.
Okay. Um...
I just want to get Singh
and Kamilla through first.
They're in pretty bad shape
and they're gonna need some help...
Not them, just you.
We cannot bring you all back.
You have been there longer.
You have more knowledge of Eva.
Therefore retrieving you
is the logical choice.
Did you hear what I just said?
Barry, they could die.
They need you to save them.
This is not the outcome I predicted.
What?
You need to come through. Now.
Iris... Stop.
Your resistance
is de-stabilizing the portal's energy.
That is dangerous.
Barry, this isn't you!
This isn't right!
Iris?
Hey, hey, hey, Iris.
I didn't see this.
No, no, no...
No, no, no, no.
No!
Iris.
This isn't my world.
This isn't my world...
But it can be.
Good night, Hawkshaw.
- Tell Gwen thanks for the brownies.
- I will.
You see, they're not coming to save you.
They're coming to save me.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::