My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
What's happened to me?
- Ralph Dibny.
- He used to be a cop.
- A dirty cop.
- I was a good detective.
- This is not my world.
- And Earth-2 is?
Did you make a bunch of friends there
that I don't know about?
You said you were a good cop, be one
- Let me train you.
- For what?
To do what I do.
What made you look into Mayor Bellows?
It was a client. Last name, DeVoe.
I owe ya for the java, rookie.
Can't believe I left my wallet at home.
Don't worry about it,
it could happen to anyone.
Five times in a row.
And could you stop calling me rookie?
Sorry. Old habit from when I was
your superior officer.
You know. Before you got me fired,
ruined my career, destroyed my life,
crushed my spirit. Left me alone
without a friend in the world.
Don't forget how I turned you into
an amorphous stretch-y blob.
Actually, that's the one good thing
you've done for me!
- Right.
- 'Course it wasn't on purpose,
so you don't get credit.
Both of ya, hand over your cash! Now!
Hey. Pardon us. Okay? One second.
Okay. This is perfect.
I've been teaching you, right?
Muggers are like Superhero 101.
- Ah, Ralphy likey.
- What's your plan?
Okay. I was thinking about this
in the shower this morning,
how sweet would it be
to turn into a giant slingshot?
It's a weird plan, but okay.
- I got an even cooler idea!
- Hey!
I'm still robbing you guys.
We will be right with you, sir. Please!
Okay, what if I did like
a human-slinky thing
maybe wrap him up,
throw in a few on-theme puns.
Whatever, Ralph.
We just gotta hurry up a little bit.
Relax, rookie. I've seen a lot
of thugs. This guy's no shooter.
My leg!
Well, our work here is done.
Hey, what're you doing? We can't
just leave. You just shot him.
I didn't shoot him. He shot him.
- Well...
- Do you feel like I shot you?
You. Stop shooting him!
- I am not shooting him!
- They shot my ass!
Okay. So, he's
a little banged up, but...
We caught the bad guy.
Isn't that what superheroes do?
No. A superhero's
first job is to protect people.
Oh, God! What's the second job?
Long-winded lectures before noon?
I barely... Take this. One day, gonna
throw a lightning bolt so far...
I'm taking him to the hospital.
And you owe me five coffees.
It's fine. I know. Come on, get up.
Not gonna hurt you. This way, come on.
Hey. He left his gun!
He's reformed already!
We need to talk.
The only way it can end...
With my victory.
What?
Fine. Let us take the long way
and continue.
Today, for the first time,
events will align that give Team Flash
a chance to discover your identity.
This is earlier than you anticipated.
- It is of no concern.
- Like hell! You know what's at risk.
What we're doing.
If you've miscalculated
by even a decimal...
There is not a decimal,
a fraction, an infinitesimal variable
beyond my thought!
Beyond my mind.
Even now, of the 7,798 variations
of this argument, I have anticipated
them all and know how it ends.
Then how does it end?
The only way it can end...
With my victory.
Ouch! All nighter, huh?
I haven't been this tired
since Killer Frost
decided to go to Burning Man.
Yeah? Well, how's our search
for the mysterious DeVoe coming?
Allen, we're searching
for an evil mastermind.
The only clue we have to go on
is his name,
of which there're literally thousands.
So, how's the search going? It's...
Fantastic.
- I missed that.
- If we're gonna find DeVoe,
we need more brain power.
Well, why didn't you say so?
One master detective ready to detect.
I said, "More brain power."
Initiating emergency oxygen purge...
- In ten, nine, eight, seven...
- I, I...
- I...
- ...six, five, four...
- One more second...
- ...three, two, one...
Like I said, we need more help.
Maybe I should call my friends.
- Your what?
- My friends.
- Is he saying friends?
- I think he's being sarcastic.
No, this is delirium. He's cracked
from being awake all night.
Hey, Harry. All of your friends
are in this room!
I have other friends. You asked me to
make new friends, I made new friends.
It was a task. I complete tasks.
That's so great.
I can't wait to meet them.
Harry, you listened to me!
I'm so proud of you.
Okay, there's no pride...
Put that down.
Look, my friends are smart,
they'll help us. I'll call them.
All right. In the meantime, we gotta
find the rest of these bus metas.
Somehow they're connected
to DeVoe's plan.
You were on the bus. Can you remember
anybody else who was?
Well, I was in between
drunk and hungover at the time.
She is cute. What's her deal?
- She's in jail.
- When are visiting hours?
What about vibing the rest
of the bus passengers?
I tried, but, you know, the...
The dark matter we release was such
a massive space-time event
that my energy just reflected back
and I ended up vibing myself.
I'm pretty sure
I relived my own birth...
Or was that my death?
You know, there are other
non-traumatizing ways
of bringing Ralph's memory back.
Like hypnosis.
Is that really a thing?
I mean, not the whole
cartoon pocket-watch version.
But yeah, real hypnosis can be used
to recover memories.
- All right. Do you know any hypnotists?
- Mm-hmm.
- Not me.
- You lost me at cartoon.
All right. So who's gonna
hypnotize Ralph?
I'm Doctor Sharon Finkel.
Dr. Finkel, thank you so much
for squeezing us in.
Our friend Ralph here is having
trouble remembering information,
for a detective case. Right, Ralph?
So, I see
you didn't go to Harvard.
No, did you?
I see what you did there.
If you could fix his personality, too,
that'd be great.
Give it up, rookie. This psycho-hooey
is never gonna work on me.
- Well, that was quick.
- Yeah.
Now, remember with me, Ralph.
It's a month ago.
You're on a bus. What do you see?
I see someone crying.
Dude's really bumming me out.
Hey. Cheer up, buddy!
You can do it!
What else do you see?
I see some women.
I can't see their faces.
34-32-36. 38-34-32.
Are those bus routes?
I think they are measurements.
Ew.
I see something else. I see a...
It's a bison.
Does a bison mean anything
to either of you?
This hocus-pocus is never gonna work
on a guy like me.
But we can try it if you want.
How'd you guys get over there?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Security guard found him here
this morning. Haven't ID'd him yet.
His personal effects
are scattered everywhere.
So we didn't find his wallet.
But we may find it
when we find the rest of his briefcase.
And his missing hand.
Well, judging by that avulsion
and the claw marks, I'd say
a large predatory animal did this.
But whatever it was would
have to have four-inch canines,
a bite force of 5,000 psi,
and weigh over a ton.
That animal doesn't exist.
Then what the hell did this?
You don't think...
Do you remember back in the day
when we wouldn't calmly consider
a stone statue our prime suspect?
No. I actually don't.
Blood.
All right, my friends.
We got meats.
We got cheeses, we got guac,
we got beer.
And of course, we got my favorite chips!
Let's get this confab poppin'.
Are your friends coming?
Yeah, let me just calibrate
the multi-verse holo-projector,
and we'll be on our way.
Your friends are from different Earths?
No, but I thought
multi-verse holo-projector
would've given you that clue,
but, apparently not.
Yes, they're from other Earths.
And we're off and running.
Well, allow me to make
some introductions.
From Earth-12, the holder of four
PhDs and the author of the book
So Why'd You Buy This Book?,
I give you,
Herr Harrison Wolfgang Wells.
- Guten Tag, Wells.
- Guten Tag.
Do you know
that it amuses me that you think
that saving your tiny world matters,
when the entire multi-verse
will inevitably be consumed
in a fiery heat desk?
- Desk?
- Yeah, that's what I said, desk.
Death.
Yeah, death. What are you, deaf?
- Yeah.
- You must be
the little one they call Cisco.
- Not that...
- I'm 5'7". Guten Tag.
All right. Moving on. From Earth-47.
I give you the billionaire-inventor
and publishing tycoon
General Champion of Free Speech,
H. Lothario Wells.
That's right. Keep that coming.
Now try the other one on.
No, not the Crocs.
Just the other leopard prints...
- It's really...
- What's going on?
He's otherwise occupied.
Oh, golly, there you are.
My apologies. Appears that you all
caught us red-handed here
at the mansion on dress-up night.
You know what they say,
intellect is the greatest aphrodisiac.
Yeah, so. Nobody says that.
Here's to rising IQ's and libidos.
Hate to call two a pattern here, Harry,
but aren't your friends...
And from the post-apocalyptic
landscape of Earth-22,
where man and machine
have become one in order to survive,
I give you, Wells 2.0.
Right. Let's make this quick.
Reapers have raided our petrol supplies
and stolen our water tanks.
I'd like to smash them to bits.
What? It's a party now.
Forget not about me!
'Tis I, Wells the Grey...
Sorry. It's a bad connection.
Yeah. That was a terrible connection.
Good on you.
That dude was strange.
- Harry?
- Yeah?
- Sidebar.
- We're gonna, sidebar.
So, remember when I said,
"Make friends"?
I didn't mean with yourself.
They're great, aren't they?
And some of the brightest minds
in all the multi-verse.
Good company, too, I might add.
I mean, that Harrison Wolfgang Wells.
- The guy's hilarious.
- Look, we're desperate.
- Sure we are.
- So, I think
we should give
the Council of Wells a chance.
- Council of Wells?
- Pretty good name, right?
- Yes, it is.
- I know.
- All right.
- Fellas. Will you...
- Fellas.
No, do your thing.
- Here's how it's gonna go down.
- Nein. Halt.
You're unnecessary also,
not wanted, so...
Off you go. Off you go. Off you go.
Still here. Off you go.
And even I know when
you got too many partners.
I know I may be half machine.
But you're all useless.
I think what the fellas
are trying to say here,
is that they prefer to work alone.
- You don't say.
- I just did.
- Don't just say it.
- He just said it.
Fine. You enjoy your road-kill.
You won't be eating my favorite chips.
We had a Cisco on my Earth once.
He was delicious.
He ate another Cisco.
I'm gonna leave you to you.
So this stone sample shows absolutely
no unique attributes of any kind.
Totally normal granite statue.
Except, it's filled with traces
of the dark matter
on a molecular level,
as if it's been flooded with it.
So, another bus meta...
One that somehow brings
inanimate objects to life.
And uses them to kill.
How can this possibly be, possible?
My best guess?
This meta has the ability to leave
a psychic imprint on objects
A sort of telekinetic puppeteering
through a subconscious link.
That's really smart, 34-25-34.
- Did he just give my...
- No, ignore him.
Um... Well, look,
the good thing is, our rifles have
a "blow statues to hell" setting,
so when this meta does show up,
we'll be ready.
I hope we're ready now.
Our victim's name is Jim Fox.
He was an auctioneer at Wetherby's.
He was transporting a Native American
artifact when he was attacked.
We just don't know which one.
Oh, wait. Maybe we do.
A bison necklace.
Ralph, you said you saw a bison
on the bus, right? I mean...
Nothing in our world is a coincidence.
- Vindicated.
- No one said you were lying.
I could see it in your eyes.
According
to this auction report
the necklace was separated
into three pieces.
The first was in the briefcase,
the third is unknown,
but the second was in the hands
of a private collector.
Christoph Banks.
I'll get the CCPD. Get his address.
He may be in danger.
Then we better pay him a visit.
You ready to suit up?
Oh, yeah! Where's my suit?
Now, this is just a prototype,
but she's got an adaptive,
nano-weave structure
that is, wait for it...
Malleable, on a sub-molecular level.
Don't know what that means, don't care.
Just yank the tarp off.
I'm ready for my super-suit.
Ralph,
this "tarp" is your super-suit.
When you stretch, it stretches.
When you squish, it squishes.
Squishes into something butt-ugly.
Where's the style? The flair?
Dibny needs to peacock.
Dibny needs to wear the prototype
Cisco so lovingly made for him.
Either that or you fight crime naked.
No, don't fight crime naked.
What is this? A puppy's raincoat?
The collection really is
quite impressive, isn't it?
It's taken no small amount
of resources to acquire.
I'm just glad to share it
with someone who appreciates it.
That, I do.
So this book you're writing?
It's on Sioux artifacts?
My entire bloodline is Sioux.
Lakota to be exact.
Ah...
Then you're gonna love this.
This is a Lakota peace pipe.
Had to have it taken apart
and repaired so it can be smoked.
Wanna try it?
That which you call a "peace pipe"
is no such thing.
It is a sacred gift for prayer
from Ptesan-Wi,
bringer of the Seven Sacred Rights,
the White Buffalo Calf Woman.
You'd never hang
a Christian cross upside down,
or lay an American flag on the floor,
yet you destroy that which is wakan,
what is holy, by letting it
touch your filthy flesh.
But I'm here to teach you
the price for your impudence.
Who do you think you are?
I am the Black Bison.
Enough.
Whoa! Now, that is a cool suit.
Remind me to take some pics for Cisco...
Help. Don't leave me.
You let her get away.
I'm getting the same traces
of dark matter from this
that I was from the tiger's statue.
Looks like our meta isn't restricted
to animating just stone.
No. But she does have some limitations.
Out of all the artifacts in the office,
she could only control the knight.
So, then maybe her
psychic imprint abilities
are just restricted to effigies.
- It just means statues.
- Yeah, I don't know.
Sounds kinda dirty to me.
So, if the statue looks like people or
animals, she can bring them to life.
Good thing there's only thousands
of those in the city.
I got a hit on facial recognition.
Mina Chaytan.
Professor of Cultural Anthropology.
- She's a teacher?
- Was.
She became an activist,
but she lost her job
six months ago after being arrested.
Breaking and entering,
trespassing, burglary.
Quite an activist.
The charges were dropped,
but the university still let her go.
She was trying to reclaim several
Sioux art pieces from the museum.
Chaytan was at this even before
she was a meta.
Yeah. Except now she's
upped her game to homicide.
She wants the third piece
of that necklace
- Let's find it before she does.
- Okay.
West and West are on the case.
What's wrong with you?
You let her get away.
We could've caught her.
Yeah, I let her go
but I also saved Banks' life.
That was the most important thing
in that situation.
Really, Allen? Because to me,
when I was a cop,
getting the bad guy,
that was the most important thing.
You're the Flash. You could've
saved him and caught her.
All right. Look, Ralph,
I'm always gonna make the decision
to help the person in danger first.
That's what we do here.
All right, well.
We'll file all that under "Superhero
Lesson of the Day," y'know?
- ...part chicken.
- Guys, guys.
I still think the best thing we can do
is figure out what is DeVoe's goal
and from there we can track...
Ugh, that's a simple plan
- from a simple man.
- That's not helping.
Why don't we use
the Bates-Novick Method first?
We determine why each meta
developed their super-powers,
then we smash them to bits.
I've seen a lot of strange here, but...
This takes all the cakes.
Okay, Council of Wells. How we doing?
Have we found our mystery foe yet?
No, we can't even agree
on what methodology to use.
- What?
- Yes.
- You've had an entire day.
- I know.
- Wait.
- What?
- Weren't there three of you?
- Whoo!
Thanks for the merry-go-round,
sweetheart. You know what I mean.
Sorry, I had to take care of
some off-camera business.
Oh, my God!
- What?
- I can see your frank and beans.
Come on now.
I do my best thinking commando,
plus it ain't like
we all haven't seen it before.
I haven't seen it.
You guys are so uptight.
All right. Can we just get back
to the task at hand? We need answers.
The best answer is always the simplest.
Why don't we go to every DeVoe
we can find and interrogate him?
- What, even the baby DeVoe?
- Especially the baby DeVoe.
Baby violence solves nothing.
Gentlemen, clearly, this isn't working.
And by the way, it's not me.
It's you.
This was a bad idea.
It's like your junk
has been burned into my brain.
You're welcome.
We've got the third piece
of the necklace.
My dad found out that it was
on display at Central City Museum,
but when they figured out
that it was a target...
- It's on the move.
- Yeah.
It's being transferred via armored car
to a secure storage facility
in Brookfield Heights.
I pinged the truck's GPS.
All right. Ralph, let's go.
I'll get my ugly suit.
Kittens...
Hello.
Are you ready to go to jail?
This doesn't belong in an auction house.
It doesn't belong
in someone's collection.
It belongs to the Sioux people.
My people.
Mina, I know you've been through
a lot, but this is not the way to...
I don't need to listen
to men like you anymore, Flash.
A few weeks ago,
something inside me changed.
Changed for the better.
For the more powerful.
And now there's just the Black Bison.
Oh, no, you don't.
The power lines. Get those people clear!
But I can catch the meta.
Laura!
Whoa! Whoa!
Told you I'd get her.
- Hey, the power's out.
- Help!
- I can't keep holding it up.
- Laura.
Laura.
I got her.
EMTs are almost here.
She's still breathing.
Come on, wake up, honey.
I need you to wake up.
Come on, honey.
Hey, you just rest up, okay?
I'm gonna come back and
check on you in a little while.
Well, a mild concussion,
and a hairline fracture in her leg.
She's young, so she'll heal fast.
- Okay. Thank you, Doctor.
- You're very welcome.
But considering the accident,
she's very lucky to be alive.
Look, Ralph, we need to talk.
You can't...
Don't. Just...
Just forget it, okay?
Hey, buddy. You planning on bringing
the band back together
or should I clear out the speed lab?
Broom it. We don't need
that Council of Incompetents.
Ah?
Is that what we're
calling them now, 'cause...
I distinctly remember you saying
they were the brightest minds
in all the multi-verse.
And the most annoying.
I thought if I surrounded myself
with people like me,
I would like them. I don't like them.
I hate them. I hate them all.
- Hmm... Strong words.
- You saw them, Ramon, right?
That Wolfgang Wells,
he's always correcting people,
an extremely annoying habit.
The other guy, the "Free Willy"
Wells, he is so full of himself.
And the other cyborg Wells,
you know how he lost his eye?
His daughter gouged it out at the
Solstice Combat Games.
I don't blame her.
I'd have done the same.
I'd like to gouge out the other eye.
- Harry.
- What?
You know you're essentially
complaining about yourself, right?
Ramon, do your best to pay attention
to the conversation.
I'm not complaining about myself.
I'm complaining about them.
Yes, we're doppelgangers. We look alike.
We have completely
different personalities.
So you don't think you can be
quick to correct people?
You don't think
you can be full of yourself?
Full of myself? No, I'm amazing.
I'm fantastic. I'm talking about them.
I don't like them.
I hate them. I hate them all.
You know what I think? I think
this is entirely about yourself.
I think underneath
all your brain and bluster,
you actually don't have
a very high opinion of yourself.
What?
Why do you think it's so hard
for you to make new friends?
- Well...
- Harry.
No one's gonna like you,
if you don't like yourself first.
These weirdos over here, they didn't
have to answer our call for help.
But they did.
'Cause you would've done the same.
And yes, there are some
really annoying, rough parts of you,
but you know what?
I've seen some amazing parts too.
'Cause sometimes, you're a hard-ass,
you're a hero.
Sometimes, you're a wizard, Harry.
The Council of Wells...
If you wanna make that work,
you have to start treating yourself
with some compassion.
All of yourselves.
Now is the time that simple Harry
has called to insult us even more.
I didn't call to insult, I called to...
- Apologize.
- Apologize...
Apologizing is punishable
by banishment
under Krung the Face-Crusher.
All right, well, that's unfortunate.
Look, I know you guys
prefer to work alone. You don't wanna
work with other people,
you think you're so smart,
you can just push them away,
and I can say that
because I'm one of you,
but if we're going to find our DeVoe,
then we have to work together.
We have to work as...
- Friends.
- Friends...
- With benefits.
- Yeah, no, we're not doing that.
But I'm sure we can
all find something
that we like in one another.
Like, you, Wells 2.0,
you're clearly very...
...resourceful and strong. And you,
you're extremely charismatic.
I'm sure you can recruit
top talent to your research teams.
I'll bring the talent.
Yeah. And you,
Herr Wells, you're very...
- Blunt.
- Yeah.
- Obviously.
- Right.
But, can we just... Can you...
Yeah. Sure. I'm sorry, man.
What I said before about your...
You know, your theory
on the behavioral upbringings
and nano-serial killers
being unchill, that was uncalled for.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's a very groovy theory. Good on you.
Yeah. Danke.
I suppose when I said that your theory
on narcotics in molecular psychiatry
was stupider than a theory
made by tiny babies,
that that was uncalled for also.
- There we go.
- Yeah, man.
I'm digging the whole creepy half-man,
half-metal vibe you got going on.
I just wanna say, all of you...
I really respect the fact
that each one of you,
has two eyes.
Yeah, well, we all agree
on something. That's great. So...
On that note, I hereby reconvene
the Council of Wells.
Now, about our DeVoe...
Well, about DeVoe, perhaps if we were
to combine the Bates-Novick
of our mutant friend here,
with my models
of statistical elimination...
I'll do you one more.
Maybe enhance your elimination model
with a psych profile based
on DeVoe's previous action.
I could whip up a predictive algorithm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Run it through my quantum cerebral chip.
We'll find him in no time.
I'm starting to see
why you called these guys.
Yeah.
All right, gentlemen.
Let's get to work.
If you're here to tell me
how I royally screwed up
letting that little girl get hurt...
Trust me, I know.
I keep feeling all these feelings...
Guilt. Remorse. Heartburn.
Well, I can't help you
with that last one.
But maybe I can help with the rest.
What are all those?
Past cases.
Those were simpler times.
Husband stepping out on wife.
Wife stepping out on husband.
Husband stepping out on wife
and husband.
That one was a little less simple.
Ralph, it was like
you were gonna make a point.
My point is...
When I was a PI, I...
I didn't have to worry
about little girls in hospitals.
I just had to get the dirt.
Whatever happened after that,
I wasn't there to see it.
Now, all I see are people getting hurt,
or about to get hurt.
And for five years, I've got by
without caring about anyone.
Now I have to care about a whole city?
It's a part of the job, Ralph.
Maybe the most important part.
How do you do it?
How do you walk around knowing what
could happen to all those people?
I don't always handle it well.
I've made bad decisions and sometimes
it got more people hurt.
You just gotta do the best you can.
And when that's not enough,
you lean on the people around you.
- You mean you.
- Yeah, me, Ralph.
Look, I brought you into this
because I think that you have
the makings of a hero.
But I would be lying if I said
there won't be hard days.
And when there are,
you'll need someone to turn to.
I can be that person. If you want.
You'd do that for me?
I will make it my personal mission
to protect your heart.
Look, Ralph, I actually think it's
great you're feeling all this stuff.
But don't forget,
that little girl's gonna be okay.
And we got the bad guy.
Yeah.
We got the bad guy.
Don't I know you
from somewhere?
Not likely.
No. I do. I arrested you after
one of those protests last year.
Don't touch me.
Those artifacts are headed
for the museum.
And once the warden's people get here,
you're headed to Iron Heights.
Gentlemen, feast your eyes
on this wonder.
This bad boy's replete with polymer
coated flame resistant armor,
frontal impact deflection panels,
a dual-filter gas mask.
So you don't cry on your own supply.
Especially with this bad boy.
I call it "the onion."
Any questions?
It's time we go collect what's ours.
Joe just called.
Chaytan escaped from CCPD.
Apparently she made a tactical dummy
go full Terminator at the station.
Well, we know where she's going.
The necklace.
The two pieces she stole have been
reunited with the third piece
at the museum.
She has killed for these before,
she will kill anyone that gets
in her way to reclaim them.
It's up to us. Are you ready?
- Well, I was until you said that.
- What are you...
Jeez, Louise, man. What kind of
rousing Braveheart speech was that?
Just put your thing on.
- You wanna help me?
- No.
- It's really tight.
- Hurry up.
Hello, beautiful.
Put it down, Mina.
That belongs in a museum.
- This is a museum.
- Realized that after I said it.
Yes. You keep it here
as part of "American History."
But we're not history.
We are still here.
Still sacred. As is this necklace.
It's going back to the Sioux.
Get out of my way.
Not after the people you've hurt, Mina.
And you're not gonna hurt anyone else.
Is that so?
Don't move.
Their vision is based on movement.
That movie is filled with lies.
We have a T. rex.
What's going on in here?
Stop. I got you.
What you gonna do, superhero?
For the love of Jeff Goldblum, stop!
You're really never gonna
stop chasing me, are you?
No. I'm really not.
Do you have any idea how many things
I can bring to life in this place?
The gargoyles on the roof.
The reliefs carved
into the walls and support pillars.
I can bring this whole place down
in a matter of seconds.
But you won't.
Because there is one thing
you care about more than vengeance.
Isn't there?
I kinda can't believe
you fell for that. Come on.
You almost let her escape.
Well...
I kept hearing your stupid voice
telling me to protect the innocent.
Nice job, rookie.
Good boy. Stay.
All right. Sounds good.
I'll let everybody know.
Hey. That was Joe.
He says that Warden Wolfe has Chaytan
locked up at Iron Heights.
Far, far away from any mannequins,
statues, or...
Effigies. Looked it up.
Still say it sounds kinda dirty,
but I'm not the mayor
of the dictionary, so whatever.
Joe also said that the clean-up crew
at the museum
still hasn't found the Bison necklace.
Huh?
Guess somebody might've mailed it
back to the Sioux reservation.
Somebody?
You gonna yell at me again?
No. Not for this one.
Mina's friends and family...
They've been hurt for too long.
And I'm not sure if you've
heard this saying before, but,
"A superhero's first job
is to protect people."
Wise words.
You want a coffee? On me.
For real, this time.
Thanks, but...
I gotta see about a girl.
Hey, kid. How you doing?
Better. Thanks.
That...
That's awesome.
But I'm really bored.
Yeah.
Do you like balloon animals?
Do a giraffe next.
Okay, but that might take some toes.
Hey. What's going on?
- We think we know who he is.
- According to Harry's friends,
the name we're looking for
is Clifford. Clifford DeVoe.
92% match to our psychological profile.
No other DeVoe comes close.
Guy keeps a low profile.
No social media, no criminal record.
And we know where he's hiding.
43 Hibbard Lane.
Well, if he's as dangerous as you said,
I can call Singh.
We can get a squad over there.
No.
Let's go get him.
Guys, Thawne. Zoom. Savitar.
For once, we actually have a chance
here to get ahead of our enemy.
Let's go get DeVoe.
We're about to have guests.
Then let's be ready to greet them.
- Is this the place?
- This is the one.
- Is everyone set?
- Eye in the sky is a go.
I have eyes on the front door.
Snow and Frost, standing by.
Just give us the word,
and we'll breach in.
What kind of criminal mastermind
has a welcome mat?
Hi, can I help you?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Detective Joe West, CCPD.
This is Barry Allen, my associate.
Is everything all right?
Yes. We were just hoping to talk
with Clifford DeVoe. Is he here?
Yes, he is.
May I ask what this is about, officers?
We just need to ask him some questions.
Is something wrong?
Is my husband in trouble?
- Your husband?
- No, ma'am.
Clifford. The police are here.
They'd like a word.
Thank you, dear.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
I'm Clifford DeVoe.
How may I be of help?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::