The city is in chaos
and hospitals are overwhelmed.
C.C.P.D. advises you, stay indoors
as the violent speedster war escalates.
Iris, I need to get back out there.
Dad, something's wrong.
Our family...
...the future...
It's all changed.
Flash has to do something
before it's too late.
Nora!
What's happening?
People are getting attacked
in their offices,
their cars, their own homes,
and seemingly at random.
So, Godspeeds are attacking folks
in their homes now?
You mean I could just
be hanging out at home,
listening to my Nas, Nasty Nas,
drinking coffee and a whole Godspeed
could just...
The Godspeeds are gone again.
You're hurt. What happened?
They ambushed me
while I was evacuating City Hall.
I barely made it out in one piece.
Okay, let's get you to the med lab.
- Chester, can you call Iris?
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
No. No, she's still home feeling sick.
Let her rest.
Frost is out there, helping.
Chester, how long was it
before they showed up this time?
About eight hours.
But their movements are unpredictable,
and we still have no idea
where they're going once they disappear.
Can't we figure out
when they're going to come back next?
I could start working
on a predictive algorithm.
Right, okay.
If there's a pattern to their
freaky-deaky moves, I'll find it.
Even if we figure out
when they're gonna attack next,
I mean, we still have no idea
what these new clones want.
The original six want your speed.
Just as they were gonna get it,
six more showed up and saved you.
Right, but why?
Why?
I mean, how do we stop a civil war
if we don't even understand
why both sides are fighting each other?
Hey, has anybody heard from Joe?
He left town with Kramer hours ago.
I haven't been able to get ahold of him.
I think I know why.
Okay, this Godspeed war is causing
a build-up of electricity,
shielding Central City
in what's essentially a Faraday cage.
Any electronic signal
is being totally contained inside.
So no one in the city can text or call
the outside world right now.
I'm sorry.
Cecile, if there's one thing
Joe knows how to do,
it's take care of himself.
And right now,
anywhere is safer than Central City.
Ah. You got out.
Two against one.
Not fair.
Time to go huntin'.
So that was quick.
How did you know
he had us in his sights?
That light.
I'd recognize the signature
of Adam's pulse rifle anywhere.
You okay?
I'm alive, so I'm good.
We need to get backup, though.
Damn it. I can't get a signal.
He's jamming cell service
to keep us isolated...
which means he knows
we didn't die in that blast.
We need to keep moving.
Easy. You still have six broken ribs
and some internal bleeding.
Another hour of speed healing,
I'll be fine.
Those Godspeeds will be back soon.
I need to be ready.
Look, I've patched you up enough times
to know that this isn't about
some broken bones or clones
or even Iris being under the weather.
I had a dream about Nora.
My Nora, from the future.
It was the second dream, actually.
This time she was so afraid.
She told me the future had changed
and that I needed to do something.
I know it was just a dream, but...
Caitlin, I'm really worried.
When Godspeed
was Nora's enemy from 2049,
if all these other Godspeeds
are here now,
well, what does that mean
for the future of my family?
What if it somehow means...
Your Nora doesn't exist anymore.
You could go check on her.
Run to the future.
I want to, but I'd risk causing
another Flashpoint.
Plus, more Godspeeds
could show up at any moment.
Then you wouldn't be here to fight them.
I get it. You're right.
I can't leave. Not while there's
a civil war in the city.
Maybe I can help with that.
- John?
- Digg.
Barry. Caitlin.
I brought you something.
What is it?
If we're lucky, a way to end this war
before someone gets killed.
It's called an entropy trap.
And hopefully,
it's going to save your city.
Wait, wait, wait!
So you're saying that John Diggle
is gonna help us end the Godspeed war?
Aka Spartan.
Aka Oliver Queen's right-hand man.
Aka the heart and soul of Team Arrow.
Yeah.
And this is something that
Cisco cooked up after you called him
and gave him the 411 on Central City.
Digg, when we reached out for help,
I had no idea he was going to send you.
He didn't. I volunteered, man.
You're fighting a war, Barry.
I know something about that.
And with a battle-tested soldier like
you on our side, we're gonna win.
This motion-detection plate
has a response time
of a picosecond.
And now it's live.
Hey, do you mind handing me that thing?
Oh, yeah. Absolutely, yeah.
I mean, like, absolutely, I don't mind
kind of...
I'm the new guy, by the way. Chester.
Big fan, man. Big fan.
Thanks.
All right, guys,
you might wanna stand back.
Oh, dope.
So the plasmatic wave eliminates
all entropy from any object
or person.
Yep, freezing it in time.
Guys...
If we could trap one of these Godspeeds,
find a way to communicate with it...
We can find out what they want
and why they're fighting.
And end this thing.
All right, once we've caught one,
we'll bring it back here
for questioning.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You want to invite the enemy
into your house, Barry?
Is that a good idea?
Look, these new Godspeeds
saved my life last night.
If there's any chance of finding allies
in this war, it's with them.
Right.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's go catch a speedster.
This band is made
of the same metal alloy as your mask,
so your body won't reject it.
It'll maintain the laryngeal structure,
but you're good to go.
No more updates, no more surgeries.
I'll let you two catch up.
You going somewhere?
I have work to do.
This is on some old
Black Hole security squad.
Wait. Are you serious?
You're going after the dregs
of Black freaking Hole
before your anesthesia
has even worn off?
You have a death wish?
Those who survived Carver's reign
are digging up old bank accounts,
giving money to those
same doctors who hurt me.
I get it. These are bad dudes,
like, really bad.
But they can wait
'cause you have to heal first.
I have a chance
to stop them now.
I may not get another.
What about your chance
at a new beginning?
Caitlin just saved your voice.
And probably your life.
You really want to risk it
for some Black Hole scum?
Damn it! Esperanza...
You are not strong enough to fight them.
So help me!
So you can get more blood on your hands?
No!
Fine, no killing.
But we will do this together,
as a family.
I can't.
It has to wait.
There is a war going on, prima.
A whole lot of lives are in danger.
This city needs me.
Team Flash needs me.
I need you.
Those doctors will torture others
if I do nothing.
Just wait.
As soon as this is over,
I promise, I will help you.
The clones are back.
It seems like they came back
awfully fast this time.
Flash, we got company.
I'm ready, Chester. Do it.
Signal activated.
Hey, Flash's suit is emitting a signal
identical to the original Godspeeds.
So the new Godspeeds
will think that he's their rival...
When he's really bait.
We got one.
What happened?
Did it work?
It worked, all right.
That's something
you don't see every day.
Okay, so... why isn't he talking?
He's a soldier.
He'll talk when he's ready,
and not a moment sooner.
So, word at A.R.G.U.S.
is you are leveling up, Cecile.
Hmm. Didn't know you guys
kept tabs on us ordinary people.
I guess that means
you're far from ordinary.
Speaking of, can you sense
what's going on inside his mind?
No. Barry already had me try,
and the only thing that I could feel
was hatred and determination.
Why isn't he trying to make contact
with the rest of his team?
Oh, he's trying, but I'm sending out
serious interference.
He can't get through.
She's our own personal signal jammer.
Well, that'll come in handy
in the field.
This whole team is leveling up.
Guys, it might not understand me.
I think it might be a drone.
Maybe.
Cue up your translator.
A translation
will not be necessary.
So you can speak.
Yes.
And we have much to discuss,
Barry Allen.
Now, where, oh, where could she be? Hmm?
You want to tell me
why he's trying to kill us?
No idea.
But killing is what
the Army taught him to do, so...
- We need to move.
- Hey.
If we head north, we can hit
the main road in about an hour.
I'm not letting him go.
I'm not going into a suicide mission.
Look, you do what you have to do.
The 12 soldiers Adam killed
were my family.
I promised I would do whatever it takes
to get them justice.
Justice is that way.
So while I'm gonna do
whatever it takes to finish this,
I won't ask you to do the same.
Hey, I'm not gonna let you
go after him alone.
I got your back. But Kramer...
if he did everything he could do
to make sure you weren't a part
of Operation Griffin,
why would he try to kill you now?
He doesn't know who he's hunting.
If he doesn't know
who he's trying to kill,
I know how we can catch him.
And I know what we're gonna need.
Let's go.
You've been listening this whole time.
- Why talk now?
- I needed to be sure.
In this war,
we fight versions of ourselves.
But when two sides are evenly matched,
there is no winning,
only endless suffering.
I know now you are strong.
You are the advantage we need
to achieve our goal.
- Which is?
- To live!
We did not ask to be born,
but we do ask not to die.
The others, they want your speed
to give to their master, August Heart.
But upon completion of their mission,
they will bow down to his final edict.
Total submission.
And once they do, they'll die?
We do not want that fate.
I understand the need
to defend yourselves.
But if you're from the future,
why bring your war here?
We had no choice.
The prime August Heart is here,
in this time.
That's what they're all doing.
That's what they're doing.
They're searching for August Heart.
And whoever finds him first...
Wins the whole damn war.
We are on
the same side, you and I.
We have the same goal.
Stop one man from gaining a power
so great it would destroy us all.
So join us, Flash.
And by doing so, you can end this war.
Save your city.
Save your family.
If I do help...
what happens to August Heart
once we find him?
We kill him.
Until he is dead,
our freedom will be compromised.
I won't kill.
Not even an enemy.
Then know this.
Anyone who stands in our way
will die with him.
Uh... Godspeed's biometrics show
he just tapped into his speed.
Barry, turn on the trap.
If you are not an ally,
you are an enemy.
Let him go.
- Is everyone okay?
- How did he get out?
I don't know. The meta cell
should have kept him powerless, but...
Oh, man. Godspeeds
are fueled by a velocity formula.
A chemical Speed Force substitute.
Which means he's an artificial meta,
so dampeners wouldn't do anything.
So why didn't he just peace out
as soon as we un-froze him?
We thought we were interrogating him.
He was interrogating us.
Chester, you have to fix this.
Uh... I'm sorry, but Cisco built this
core with original Time Trapper tech.
That kind of tech's one of a kind.
I can't...
You have to.
It's the only way to stop one of them.
Barry, this isn't junk.
Okay, without access to bleeding-edge
temporal components, there's just...
Then find another way!
Chester, Allegra,
give me a second with Barry.
So you want to tell me
what's really got you so upset
that you're talking
to your teammates like that?
And don't tell me
it's about some broken tech, Barry.
It's my daughter...
Nora.
Before she came to join us,
she lived in the future.
2049.
The exact time Godspeed's from.
Okay. And with everything
that's going on,
you think it affects the future somehow?
Digg, if August Heart is here, what...
What does that mean for Nora
and the future of our family?
Is she okay?
Will Iris and I still have a family?
Is Nora even alive
in the future anymore?
Now, all I want to do is run to 2049
and make sure Nora's okay.
See with my own eyes
that my daughter's safe.
But I can't do that.
Why not?
Digg, you know better than anyone
what could happen if I did.
Besides, man, with this civil war
destroying the city,
staying here to fight
is the right thing to do.
No, it's not.
Barry, I lived a long life
here on this Earth.
I've been a spy, a vigilante, a soldier.
Hell, I've even been the Green Arrow.
The most important job
I've ever had is as a dad.
And there's not a bullet
I wouldn't take,
there's not a timeline
that I wouldn't risk changing
if it meant protecting my family.
I know that now.
Lyla...
my kids, they're my heart, man.
My soul, my entire world.
How far would I go for them?
As far as it takes.
Everything else be damned.
Don't be afraid to do the same.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Godspeeds are gone again.
How are you holdin' up?
Cecile, as long as these Godspeeds
are here,
I can't shake the feeling
that my family's future is in trouble.
That's why I need to go
and make sure my daughter's okay.
Nora? How?
I'm gonna run to 2049.
It's... I know, it's dangerous,
but I'd risk anything
to keep this family safe.
Yeah, well, you and me both.
Which is why I've been reading this.
- Nora's journal?
- Yeah.
Iris gave it to me.
Apparently,
she has been looking for
anything about the original
August Heart.
Yeah, I know.
Even when she's under the weather,
your girl is thinking
of ways to help us.
Now, turns out Nora mentioned a few
places that seemed personal to Heart.
So if he really is here in 2021,
Iris thinks he's hiding at one of those.
But without the entropy trap,
finding Heart first is our best chance
at ending this war.
Exactly. And with Iris
out of commission,
I'm about to go follow up for her.
Cecile, I mean, going after Heart
by yourself is dangerous.
Okay. Then I'll take John
and Allegra with me.
- Thanks for coming.
- Happy to help.
Where's Allegra?
We could've used the extra firepower.
I know. I called, I texted.
Still nothing.
Do you hear that? Do you hear that?
No. John?
John, hey, are you all right?
It's just headaches.
But this one's a lot worse
than the others.
Okay.
Are you sure that that's all it is?
Oh!
It's too much.
It's like... fighting a hurricane.
Okay.
John, buddy, I don't know what that was,
but that was a hell of a lot more
than a headache.
I... I felt something.
I don't know what it was,
but it felt huge.
No. More like... infinite.
John.
- Maybe you should stay here.
- No.
No, I'm fine. I promise.
If there is something really wrong,
the doctors in Gotham would've found it.
I don't think...
Really, whatever it is,
I can handle it when we're done here.
Let's just find Heart
while we still have the chance.
Comms aren't working
in the Speed Force for some reason,
but you'll have mobile Gideon with you.
Okay.
Chester...
about earlier, I was out of line.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for saying that.
And look, I totally get it.
I was just trying to keep the city safe.
Good luck.
Now passing 2022, 2023.
Warning, Barry Allen.
Temporal passage blocked
by invasive forces.
Warning.
Deon?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Good... because we got
a lot to talk about.
Deon, what's happening?
I mean, a second ago,
I was in the Speed Force.
Those clones, they attacked me.
Yeah, I know.
It's kind of crazy stuff, right?
What were they doing
in there in the first place?
Feeding on pure Speed Force energy.
It's pretty tasty
to their artificial cells,
only they can't hold onto it for long.
That's why they keep
coming back for more.
Does the Speed Force know?
Hell, yeah.
Man, those wannabes in white
infesting the Speed Force
like damn roaches.
Now, big sis has got her hands full
trying to exterminate their sorry asses.
That's why I stepped in.
Wait, Deon, you can control time.
You can take me to 2049.
No, man, not till she's done.
Look, until then,
it's solo trips only.
All right,
it's too dangerous for anyone else.
Besides...
I kind of don't have the strength.
Pretty busy right now.
Doing what?
Keeping me safe.
Iris?
What are you doing here?
Turns out I have more
than just a bad cold.
What's wrong?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Thanks to Deon.
Barry, something is causing me
to move in and out of our timeline.
How is this possible?
We don't know.
But Mom's been phasing
through temporal planes, man.
Look, I don't know why,
but once I sensed it,
I knew I had to step in and help.
Look, I've been using all my stillness
just to stabilize her.
Otherwise she'd fracture
through time itself.
I can keep her alive...
as long as she stays here with me.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I know I should have just told you
what I was gonna do,
- there just wasn't time.
- No, it's all right.
Thanks for looking out for us.
How long do you have to stay here?
I don't know, but I trust Deon.
Thanks, but...
Look, I'm using all my energy just
trying to keep you here this long.
I got to put you back inside
a pure temporal stream, right now.
- I'm coming with her.
- Man, you can't.
Moving back and forth
through that kind of power
ain't recommended, even for a speedster.
Besides, man, you've got a war to fight.
- Iris, we can't just...
- Barry, we have to.
It's my only chance.
We got to go.
Deon, you have to find a cure
for whatever this is,
- whatever's happening.
- I will.
Iris, I love...
Yo, Casper,
I got something for you.
Nanites, courtesy Ray Palmer.
Hey. You're gonna be okay now.
Go. Get to safety, go.
- Worlds await.
Worlds await.
Spartan, look out!
You all right?
Yeah, I am, since you had my back.
It happened again.
I gotta get you out of here.
Caitlin needs to examine you.
No.
Not while Heart is still out there.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
Uh...
Isn't he supposed to come back
at the exact same time?
Yeah.
And if he hasn't,
it's because something's gone wrong.
- Barry. Is Nora...
- Not Nora, Iris.
Esperanza.
I'm sorry.
I never should have let you go.
I should have chosen you,
my real family, the second you asked.
But you did not.
I fought alone.
Now I die alone.
But I'm not afraid.
No. No, don't leave me.
No.
Better make it quick.
You sure this is the right place?
Yeah. Iris's notes say that August Heart
works at this address in 2049.
But in our time,
Dayton Labs hasn't been built yet.
This was the last place on your list?
Yeah.
Did you see that?
Wait.
He's scared, I can feel it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
We're not gonna hurt you.
We're not gonna hurt you. Hi.
My name is Cecile Horton.
Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- What's your name?
I don't know.
Okay.
Okay. Well, look, we got to get you
out of here. It's not safe.
No, no, no. I can't leave.
There...
This place is... It's important.
It's important.
I can feel it.
Do you know why
it's so important to you?
No! No.
Do you?
Well, that was fun.
What?
Nothing?
Still looking for a way out of this?
There isn't one.
Oh, you can try.
You could shoot me.
Light me on fire.
I know it's a trap,
but I've died before.
Seventeen times, actually.
So why don't you give me your best shot?
'Cause I can't be killed. Hmm?
Is that why you killed
12 innocent soldiers from Fort Dakota?
Because you knew they'd die
and you wouldn't?
Kristen.
You were like a brother to me, Adam.
How could you do it?
I'll tell you. Right after you tell me
who the hell you are.
'Cause Kristen Kramer
died in that explosion.
And that means you're dead.
What's he on about, Kramer?
I don't know... and I don't care.
All I care about
is why you killed our unit.
Was it money?
If you were in trouble,
I would have helped.
Trouble?
Listen, I'm immortal.
And once I discovered that,
I realized the world was meant for me,
because I deserved it.
What you deserve is life in prison.
Really? I gave my life to the Army,
and where did it get me, huh?
Nightmares and a kick in the teeth.
That's when I realized
I'd go down broke or live it up rich.
'Cause there's plenty of folks out there
willing to pay for my new talents.
Look at him,
trying to figure out what I am.
I already have. You're the kind of meta
that gives the others a bad name.
You killed innocent people.
I finished a job.
You're a mercenary.
Did I ever know you at all?
You're the only one who knows me, Kris.
Sure, I'll kill anyone
if the price is right.
But I take half the money I make
and I give it back to the res
to build something good.
Something we never got.
Doing something good
doesn't erase something evil.
Oh, yeah? You tell that to the kids
that look like you and me.
They got futures now.
Everything I did, I'd do it again.
- You're not even sorry.
- Kramer.
Stand down.
Kristen... It's not worth it.
Come on.
Hmm. Uh...
If this is the real August Heart,
shouldn't he be in, like,
I don't know, triple lockup
- at A.R.G.U.S. or something?
- Right now, it's just a feeling.
Yeah, we need to find a way
to prove it, one way or the other.
It's what Iris would want.
Based on everything you told us,
being with Deon
is the safest place
for Iris to be right now.
Yeah, I mean, we've all seen
what the Still Force can do.
If anyone can keep her safe, Deon can.
All right, right now, let's stay focused
on keeping the city safe.
Right. Right. Okay.
I just finished running the algorithm
on the Godspeed disappearances.
Turns out these clones are coming back
exponentially faster each time.
- How long do we have?
- At first it was eight hours, then four.
And now?
If we're lucky, 90 minutes.
This war is about to go turbo.
Cecile, can you sense
anything from this guy?
Yeah, I tried. The only thing
I'm picking up is the same fear
that anyone suffering
from memory loss would have.
Whoever this person is,
he seems like somebody who needs help.
I ran complete diagnostics on him.
There's no sign of speed powers,
organic or artificial.
But take a look at this.
His neurological scans
show severe memory degradation,
but his somatic memory cells
are still intact.
- They're just inactive.
- Can we access them?
I could give him a nano dose
of neurogenic dark matter.
It might reactivate the cells,
but it's risky
and the effects would only be temporary.
I think if there's a chance
that what's inside his head
could save lives, it's worth trying.
As long as he agrees.
Let's get the shot ready.
I'll ask if he's willing to help.
Tell Cisco that I have scanned
every element, and I am on the case.
If there's any way to duplicate
this Time Trapper tech, we'll find it.
I know you will.
You got skills, man.
This team's lucky to have you.
Thanks, man. So, see you soon?
For sure. Take care of yourself.
Are you leaving?
There's something I've been
putting off for far too long,
and today it nearly got me killed.
And now I have to deal with it.
I get it. It's just this war.
We need all the help we can get.
Barry, you think I don't know that?
As much as everything inside of me
wants to stay and help you fight,
in my heart and soul, man...
I know I can't put this off any longer.
All right, well,
whatever's going on,
let us know if you need anything.
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
And Barry...
- Good luck with everything.
- Thanks.
- Will this hurt?
- No.
- Are you sure you want to do this?
- I need to know who I am.
And if you think
this could really help...
then do it.
Can you tell me your name?
My name is...
It's okay. Take your time.
August.
It's him.
August Heart, the real Godspeed.
Only, that's all we could
get out of him.
His memory loss is too severe.
So even though we found him,
we're back to square one.
Damn it.
Barry, you never said what happened
when you went to 2049.
I never made it.
Those clones were blocking my path.
I couldn't get past them.
Now I can't check on Nora,
plus, I can't help Iris.
This war keeps getting worse.
Cecile, even with all my speed,
I've never felt so helpless.
Barry,
it's okay to be scared... and angry.
But I just need you to save
a little bit of room for hope,
'cause no matter how bad
things might seem right now,
we will get through this.
All right. I am gonna
check in with Chester.
- He's trying to help me reach Joe.
- All right.
Okay.
- Hey, Dad.
- Nora!
And yes, before you say anything,
I know I'm not supposed to be here.
- But it's really important, I promise.
- Thank God you're okay.
Well, yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
Because I...
Well, I couldn't get to the future.
And then with Iris gone...
Wait. But if you're here, that means...
Oh, right. Don't worry.
Mom's gonna be okay.
I'm proof that everything
works out all right.
We both are.
You...
You and Iris?
Not exactly. Um...
But, uh... Hey, I mean,
if you're happy to see me,
you're gonna be twice as happy
in just a second.
Whoo!
What did I miss?
Dad, meet your son, Bart.
Hey, Dad. What's good?
Or Pops. Can I call you "Pops" yet?
You like it when I call you
"Pops" later.
I can't remember when that is, though.
Yo, this place is crash!