My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
That day is today.
What?
No Big Belly Burger?
It's one of the few perks
of living in this time.
We're out of cows where I come from. You
don't care about that. You have questions.
I'm not sure where to start.
Thawne.
That is your real name?
- Eobard Thawne?
- Since the day I was born.
- When was that?
- One hundred and thirty-six years from now.
This is not what you wanna know.
Go ahead, Barry.
Ask it.
Why did you kill my mother?
Because I hate you.
Not you now.
You years from now.
- In the future.
- In a future, yes.
We're enemies, rivals, opposites.
Reverses of one another.
Why? Why were enemies?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is neither of us
was strong enough to defeat the other.
Until I learned your secret.
I learned your name.
Barry Allen.
And finally, I knew how to defeat you
once and for all.
Travel back in time, kill you as a child...
wipe you from the face of the earth.
But then you, future you, that is,
followed me back and we fought.
We both landed some pretty solid shots.
And then you, future you,
got your younger self out of there.
I was so mad.
But then I thought...
what if you were to suffer a tragedy?
What if you were to suffer something
so horrible, so traumatic...
that your child self could never recover?
Then you would not become the Flash.
So I stabbed your mother in the heart.
And I was free.
Finally able to return to a future
without the Flash.
Only to realize that in traveling back,
I lost my way home.
Lost my ability to harness the Speed Force.
And without it,
I was stuck here, stranded in this time...
unable to return to my home,
and the only one way back was the Flash.
But the Flash was gone,
and so I created him.
Why train me?
Why help me save so many people?
Because I needed you to get fast.
Fast enough to rupture the space-time
barrier and create a stable wormhole...
through which I could return home.
Why would I ever do that?
Because, Barry Allen...
if you give me what I want...
I'm gonna give you what you want.
You can go back and save your mother.
You can prevent your father
from going to prison.
You can reunite the Allen family.
No.
No, I don't believe you.
I wanna kill you right now.
I know that rage.
I used to feel that rage
every time I looked upon you.
And now somehow...
I know what Joe and Henry feel...
when they look on you with pride.
With love.
No. No, don't you ever say that to me.
I know you're upset,
but I'm giving you a chance.
I'm giving you a chance
to undo all the evil I've done.
Don't you want that chance?
A rare opportunity to go back in time
and right a wrong...
and save your mother's life.
Quite the paradox
Harrison has presented you with, Mr. Allen.
The chance to be with someone you love?
Seems pretty cut-and-dry to me.
At first blush, Dr. Snow, it would appear
so, but this gift has unparalleled risk.
Barry, the night your mother died...
the night you saved yourself
from being killed...
that event altered the timeline you were
already on, and changed the course of history.
So, what you're saying is
we're living in a parallel universe?
- Just like when I time-traveled before.
- But he only changed one day that time.
Exactly. Now imagine 15 years
of compounded experiences.
One different decision, no matter how big
or small, impacts everything that follows.
Moments upon moments,
choices upon choices, new relationships.
Nothing would be as it is today,
and you'd never know the difference...
because you'd never remember any of it.
So if I go back and save my mom,
my dad doesn't go to prison.
I never live with Joe and Iris.
You might never meet me
or Caitlin or Ronnie.
Truth is...
there's no real way of knowing
what your life will be.
There's no choice here, Barry.
You have to do this.
You gotta change the past.
Joe.
So, what, that's it?
You think I should just do it?
Yeah, I do.
Which means
I will never come to live with you...
and you're okay with that?
Barry, you get the chance to grow up
with both parents.
- You don't have to grow up without a mother.
- What about growing up without a father?
You will have a father. Your real father.
Wells has messed with our lives
long enough.
This is why you became the Flash, Barry.
To put things right.
You saved a lot of people's lives
this past year.
Now it's time to save yours.
Dad, look, I know this sounds crazy.
I think we're way past crazy, slugger.
Look, you're fast, I get it,
but turning back time...
I wouldn't be turning time back.
I would be going back.
To that night, to save her.
What does Joe think about all this?
He thinks I should do it.
No.
You can't.
Dad...
I can make it so
that night will never have happened.
- We'll be a family again.
- We are a family.
Not like this, not without Mom.
Barry, there's a natural order to things.
Okay, things happen the way they do.
We may not know why at the time,
but there must always be a reason.
Now, I believe that.
I've had to believe it.
I... I can save Mom.
At what cost?
You said time would change.
What if it changes you?
- Well, I don't care.
- I do.
I am in awe...
of the remarkable man
that you are becoming.
All the things you've achieved,
and not just as the Flash...
but you, Barry...
your honesty, your heart.
You were always a hero.
And your mom would be just as proud.
And if she had a say in this,
if she thought for one second...
you going back to save her would mean
you losing what makes you so special...
She would never want that.
Barry, what I hope for you...
maybe the greatest thing
that a father can hope for his son...
is that one day
you will become a father yourself.
And then you will know...
how much I truly love you.
Ninety-eight-point-six.
Normal.
- Don't know what that word means anymore.
- Me neither.
I know Barry really appreciates you
coming back to help him stop Wells.
That's not the only reason I'm back, Cait.
I'm here now, for good.
- But I thought...
- I thought too.
Okay, I thought too much about what might
happen if the government tracked us down.
If we couldn't control our powers
and we hurt someone, if we hurt you.
But I realized that, although
sometimes, I'm more than one man...
I'm not whole unless I'm with you.
I love you, Cait.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
Once upon a time...
and a particle accelerator or so ago...
you agreed to marry me.
- Yes, I did.
- What do you say we do that?
Thought I might find you here.
I needed to get out of the lab.
I thought this would be
a good place to think.
Oh, it is, trust me.
I've done a lot of thinking up here.
When I wasn't having clandestine meetings
with the mysterious Streak.
Yeah, not mad we lost that name.
Hey, I thought that had pizzazz.
No.
So are you gonna do it?
It's just so huge.
It's the biggest decision of my life,
and if I'm wrong, I can't undo it.
Why would you want to? I mean...
you'd get to see your mom again...
your dad.
Have a great career.
Even get married.
Iris West-Allen, huh?
I never really thought of myself
as a hyphenator.
Must be a 2024 thing.
We don't know that
that's gonna happen. I mean...
Do you think that
because you didn't live with us...
that's why things are different there?
Growing up together
and knowing so much about each other...
it made it hard for me
to admit how I felt about you.
And I waited too long,
and you fell in love with Eddie.
But...
But living with you and Joe...
I've had a great life, Iris.
Come here, Barry.
What do you think I should do?
I need someone to tell me.
I think...
that for once in
your life, Barry Allen...
you should stop thinking
about other people.
I think you should do what's in your heart.
Do what you need to do for yourself.
Ah.
Well, if it makes you feel any better...
it took you a whole hour longer
to decide than I thought it would.
So how does this work?
- Your grand plan.
- Well, it's really not that grand at all, Barry.
In fact, it's rather simple.
- We use the particle accelerator.
- The particle acce...
The last time that happened, you caused
an explosion that hurt a lot of people.
This time, the accelerator will operate
exactly the way it was designed to.
Except instead of two particles
moving in opposite directions...
colliding at the speed of light
in the inner ring...
we're only gonna inject one particle
into the accelerator.
And I'm what it collides with.
And if you can go fast enough, Barry...
if you can hit that particle
with enough speed...
you will punch a hole
right through the fabric of reality.
And you will create a portal...
connecting this
time... to infinite times.
A wormhole.
Through which one might travel
back to the past...
say, to the night your mother died,
or forward to the future to, say, my time.
You said if I run fast enough.
What happens if I don't?
If you don't achieve
the desired velocity, Barry...
you'll die.
According to Wells' calculations...
Barry super-speeds
inside the accelerator ring.
Once Barry reaches optimum speed...
we then launch a hydrogen proton
into the accelerator.
Once the collision happens,
a wormhole forms...
opening a gateway into time itself.
At that moment, I plan on shouting
something along the lines of:
"Eureka," or possibly, "Excelsior."
I'm uncommitted.
What do you think?
I mean, on the one hand,
it does make a kind of sense.
On the other hand...
why?
Why?
- Why would you ever consider doing this?
- You know why.
So for this to work,
how fast would Barry have to go?
By my estimates, Mach 2 at a minimum.
You've never gone that fast.
So, what happens
if Barry doesn't reach that speed?
I mean, I'm imagining a bug
hitting a windshield. How far off am I?
Not very far, I'm afraid.
Let me worry about how fast I have to go.
- We're gonna need something else too.
- Really?
And what's that?
Because I don't know about you guys...
but I'm not at all interested in
helping you get yourself killed.
I need you to build a time machine.
Go on.
So if Wells is as fast as you,
what's he need a time machine for?
Apparently, he lost his speed
when he killed my mom.
He gets it back sometimes, but
only in spurts. He can't fully control it.
I was right. He was using
the wheelchair to charge himself.
So after I open the wormhole, he's gonna
need the ship to travel back to the future.
- He's been squirreling away the parts.
- Now we just need to put it together.
Ronnie, I love you,
but this is a time machine...
not a bookcase from Ikea.
We got a problem.
These tiles, they're made of tungsten.
Tungsten has the highest
melting point of any other element.
Yeah, uh, but the dust it generates
is flammable.
- The pressure exerted from the wormhole...
- Yeah, yeah.
It could cause a hole
to be melted into the exterior.
It could explode.
Any ideas?
Let me ask Dr. Evil.
Heh. Which used to be a name
that made me smile.
- Something on your mind, Cisco?
- No.
Yes. How did you fit your
Reverse-Flash suit into that little ring?
Is it some sort of compressed microtech?
Or... Actually, forget it. I don't care.
Maybe a little.
Ronnie's right. I should've accounted
for temporal shearing.
Glad we're still good for something.
I've never underestimated
your contribution, Cisco.
Or Ronnie. As a matter of fact,
do you know how many times...
I wished you were with me
as I rebuilt the accelerator?
- Would've been a lot more fun.
- Yeah?
Well, it doesn't change the fact
that your nifty little Time Sphere...
- Oh, is that what you're calling it?
- Whatever. It's gonna blow.
Not if you cement the tiles
with a cobalt resin.
That'll prevent degradation
in conditions of extreme heat.
Okay. Fine, we'll try that.
That's it? That's all?
Well, what do you want me to say?
I don't know. I thought of anyone, you'd be
more understanding of my predicament.
I don't belong here.
These barbaric times.
- It's like living among the dead.
- Is that what you told yourself...
when you killed me?
What?
What did you say?
It was an alternate timeline,
one that Barry reset.
But I never forgot it.
It just kept coming back to me.
And I can still picture
the way you looked at me...
when you called me a son.
And you crushed my heart...
with your fist.
Cisco...
I'm sorry.
- Yeah, it sucked.
- Not for killing you. I'm sure I had a reason.
I'm sorry for the fact that you're able
to retain traces of another timeline.
You're able to see through
the vibrations of the universe. It means...
- I wasn't sure until just now.
- Sure of what?
The night the particle
accelerator exploded...
you were affected too.
What are you talking about?
No.
I wasn't.
Don't be afraid, Cisco.
A great and honorable destiny
awaits you now.
I only hope that
as you're living your great adventure...
that you remember
who gave you that life.
And that it was given out of love.
I'm sorry, but I'm told this is the only station
with enough power to run these calculations.
If we make a slight error
creating the wormhole...
Say no more. Joe told me
to stick around in case I was needed...
- but it seems I'm only in the way.
- Well, everyone has a contribution to make.
Perhaps you just haven't
discovered yours yet.
No, Dr. Wells made it pretty clear when he
told me about the future, I don't matter.
As far as history's concerned,
I don't save the day, or get the girl.
And you believed him?
He had a newspaper from the year 2024.
And I have a mug that says
"World's Best Boss."
I doubt my teaching assistant
would testify to its authenticity.
We're dealing with a lot
of big scientific ideas today.
But you, Mr. Thawne, might be...
the most interesting thing here
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Me?
What are the odds that
Dr. Wells would travel back in time...
and get stuck in the exact same city
as his great-great-great-great-grandfather?
Working in the same profession,
the same building.
And that part of his plan to get home
would mean...
that he'd have to preserve
and protect your life.
That makes you this rare thing
that no scientist can plan for.
- Which is?
- Coincidence.
There is no science to coincidence.
You, sir, are an anomaly.
A wildcard, as it were.
You are the only person in this whole story
who gets to choose his own future.
At least that's my opinion.
Wait, that can't be right. Oh, dear.
We have a problem.
- What?
- The calculations.
There is a danger.
- I know. I'm ready to take the risk.
- No, not just to you, but to everyone.
Wells didn't tell us everything.
Barry, even if you do
reach the right speed...
colliding with the hydrogen particle...
there is a chance that explosion
could create a singularity.
- What's a singularity?
- It's a black hole.
- We could destroy Central City.
- For starters.
If we create a singularity here
and then cannot control it...
we could be looking at
a global catastrophe.
So long, and thanks for all the fish.
Sure, there's a bit of a risk.
I would hardly refer to possibly causing an
extinction-level event as "a bit of a risk."
And your accelerator's been about as reliable
as the beater I drove in high school.
Ha, ha. Let me ask you a question.
How many metahumans,
how many dangers...
have we faced this year together?
Or did you forget that was me fighting
alongside each and every one of you?
I have been planning this
for almost two decades. It will work.
How do we make sure we don't open
a black hole in the middle of Central City?
So once the wormhole stabilizes...
Barry will have
one minute and 52 seconds...
lo alter the past
and return to this time.
If and when he does that,
you can close the wormhole...
and we can all live happily ever after.
Almost two minutes.
More than enough time to save Nora.
But not time enough to stop you
from going home?
Everything's a choice.
- And what if I'm late?
- You won't be.
I believe in you, Barry. Always have.
So I guess the question is, do your friends
and family believe in you as much as I do?
So if I don't run fast enough to
collide with the particle, then I'm dust.
If I run fast enough
but I'm not back here in time...
a black hole will form, swallow
up the city, and possibly the world.
Sure you still wanna look me in the eyes
and tell me that this is for the best?
I'd be lying if I told you I did.
Truth is I don't... I don't
know what to think.
I thought you were the sure one. I...
I was kind of banking on that
when I made my decision the first time.
I was faking it.
- Yeah.
- Sometimes parents do that.
Most of the time, parents do that.
Look, of course I'm scared.
But I didn't want you to not help your
mother because you were worried about me.
Well, I'll always worry about you, Joe,
just like you'll always worry about me.
Sorry, but you can't stop that.
Do you think I can do this?
Do you think I can save my mom?
I mean, do you think I'm fast enough?
Yes.
I know you are.
You know, I've dreamed my whole life...
about saving her, freeing my dad, and...
I never thought I'd have to lose
another parent to do that.
- Barry...
- Joe, it's true. It's...
It's true.
I've always been so focused
on everything that I lost that night.
But I gained so much too. I...
I was born with one father,
and that tragedy gave me...
another.
And I don't think I can lose you.
You will never lose me.
Ever. You hear me?
Ever.
Wow, slow news day?
If they only knew, right?
I thought you would be at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I was.
But I got hungry, so I went to Mama Chow's.
For dim sum? Your favorite?
- And to remind myself of something.
- What?
A coincidence.
A pretty big coincidence, actually.
About a year and a half ago,
I had a date with this girl.
Katie Rogers.
She was a dancer.
We had plans to meet at Mama Chow's...
but she texted me,
she pulled a hamstring and had to cancel.
Oh, those fragile dancers.
I was bummed
because I was looking forward to it.
So I had dinner by myself,
and I was walking home...
when I saw a mugger
running with a stolen backpack.
Your backpack.
And I arrested him.
That's how you and I met.
I remember.
Someone just told me
how powerful a coincidence could be.
And it made me realize...
how many coincidences had to happen
for you and I to get together.
In this time.
We've all been so focused on Barry's
destiny, I forgot that I have one too.
And it's you...
Iris West.
Every moment of my life led to meeting you.
Screw the future.
Is this actually binding?
My father made me become a rabbi
before he would send me to MIT.
This will be legit, as the kids say.
No kids say that.
- Let's not fight on our wedding day.
- Okay.
If it's all right with everyone,
I'd like to skip all the Hebrew.
I've learned a lot about merging one's life
with another this past year.
And yet for all the incredible advancements
in science we've all been party to...
the mystery that brings two people
together through love...
is still the province of magic.
Mr. Ramon, the rings, please.
- I owe you a real ring.
- I don't need one.
I have everything and everyone
that I could ever need right here.
And if all the events of the past year
have led us to this moment...
it was worth it.
I love you, Ronnie.
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Stop telling me what to do.
Okay, there are gonna be
three yous back there.
You from the future, who saved
younger you from the Reverse-Flash...
and now "you" you.
Remember, wait until future you
gets younger you out of there...
- and then you can go and save your mom.
- Piece of cake.
May the Speed Force be with you.
Goodbye, Dad.
Goodbye, son.
- Iris...
- You don't have to say anything.
I already know.
I hope whatever life you get,
it's enough for you...
that it makes you happy.
You too.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Remember, Mr. Allen...
assuming you achieve the proper velocity
and open the wormhole...
you will only have one minute and 52
seconds to save your mother and return.
- Or else...
- I know.
Well...
you hold both our futures
in your hands now, Mr. Allen.
And I know you can do it.
Now...
run, Barry.
Run.
The accelerator's structural integrity
is holding.
What was that?
- Is Barry okay?
- Yeah.
He just passed Mach 2.
I was waiting for you to bring Barry home.
Well, it looks like he's gonna
be staying with us a while.
Barry, what you're seeing
is the Speed Force.
Your past, your present, your future,
all at once.
So you need to focus
on where you want to go.
So think about that night.
Think about your mother.
It's time for bed. Good night, slugger.
Mom.
- Mom!
- Barry, no!
- It's working.
It's working.
Inject the hydrogen particle now.
- What's that? What happened?
- Barry, he's gone.
- Look.
- The wormhole.
And it's stable. Start the clock.
Mom!
- Mom!
- Barry! Barry!
Mom!
Barry, get back! No!
Nora, hold on!
Run!
Barry!
No!
No! No!
Hey.
- It's okay, it's okay. You're okay.
- Please.
My husband, my son, are they...?
They're okay.
They're both safe. I promise.
Who are you?
I'm...
I'm the Flash.
I don't understand.
You look just like my father.
This won't make any sense...
but it's me, Mom.
What?
It's Barry.
- Barry?
- Your Barry.
My beautiful boy.
I got a second chance...
to come back here and...
To tell you that I'm okay.
Dad and I are both okay.
And we love you, Mom.
I love you.
Oh, my sweet boy.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Barry.
Mom.
I believe it's time to say goodbye
to Harrison Wells.
It's beautiful.
Rip Hunter would be impressed.
He built the first one of these.
Interesting man.
Now what the hell is that?
That's my cue to leave.
Thank you, Cisco.
Don't ever come back.
Thirty seconds.
Home.
- Oh, my God.
- Barry.
We have to shut down the wormhole.
Quickly!
Caitlin.
You didn't save her?
Why?
Why? You could have had
the life you wanted.
You could have had everything
you ever wanted!
I already do.
Not for long.
Cut the internal generators.
Ten seconds. Hurry.
Three, two, one.
Ronnie, are you okay?
- Did you do it?
- Yes, I turned them all off.
They did it. They cut the generator.
Just so we're clear...
after I kill you,
I'm going to kill them.
And then I'm going to kill your father.
I always win, Flash.
Aah! Eddie! Oh, my...!
Eddie!
What did you do?
What did you do? What did you do?
No such thing as a coincidence.
- What's happening?
- Cisco, help me.
Eddie's his ancestor.
If Eddie dies, he'll never be born, and...
He's being erased from existence.
No!
No! Eddie.
Eddie? No, don't.
Ed, stay with me, okay? Stay...
He was wrong. Turns
out I'm a hero after all.
You are, Eddie. You are my hero.
That's all I ever wanted to be.
Your hero.
I've controlled your
life for so long, Barry.
How will you get along without me?
Guys, that's not good.
Professor, I shut down the wormhole.
What's happening?
I don't know. You did close it,
but it seems to be reopening.
- We gotta go.
- You okay?
- Iris, we have to go.
- I'm not leaving him.
- We have to go now, honey, I'm sorry.
- Come on.
So that's what we didn't want to happen.
- What's it doing?
- Feeding.
The singularity won't stop,
not even after the Earth is gone.
I'm afraid the accretion disc
has already assembled.
- What?
- Diffused material...
that's in orbital motion
around the singularity.
- What does that mean?
- We have to disrupt the motion.
Basically, it's just like the tornado,
only upside down and bigger.
- And scarier.
- Barry...
that event has an energy level
of at least 6.7 teraelectron-volts.
It cannot be stopped.
I have to try.
Oh, God. Barry.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::