Last season on The Flash...
- I'd finally come to grips with her death.
- No!
Finally at the place I can move on...
My father's taken from me.
I need to find some peace.
Whatever you need to do, do it.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
- No.
You're safe.
There's only one thing
I know about life.
I know some things happen by chance.
Today's the day.
Today's the day. I'm gonna talk to her.
Where is she? Okay.
And some things happen
because we make them happen.
Okay. It's not a big deal.
I'm gonna do it.
- I've talked to her a million times.
- Say something clever.
Channel 52, breaking news.
The latest from Central City
where the mysterious meta-human criminal
known only as "The Rival,"
is once again terrorizing the populace
with his incredible speed.
Need our help, Flash?
No. When I'm done
with this fool, he might.
What have you got against my city?
The city's just fine.
It's the people in it
who need to be educated
that I have no rival!
Especially not you.
You okay, man?
Yeah, thanks.
Guy is really becoming a pain in my ass.
Don't worry about it.
You'll get him next time, Flash.
Excuse me. Hi. Sorry, is this yours?
I think maybe you dropped...
It was just right...
I don't know what happened, but...
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, I didn't even realize I dropped it.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah? Yeah, it's okay.
Wait, I've seen you before, haven't I?
Uh...
We actually went to
elementary school together.
You don't remember me? PS 23?
- Oh, my gosh! Right.
- Yeah!
- Yes, I remember! Gary, right?
- Yeah.
Uh, Barry.
- Barry. Right.
- Barry Allen.
- It's fine. No, it's fine.
- Sorry. Sorry.
Yeah, yeah. No, we had Mister...
- Mr. Hinkley! Yeah, for Math.
- Yes!
Yeah, he used to always
hit the chalkboard with his...
His fists!
And all the dust would come flying off.
- He looked just like Pigpen from Peanuts!
- Pigpen from Peanuts. Yeah, that's...
Yes. How are you?
I'm really good.
Yeah, I'm, uh, CSI.
I work over at, uh, CCPD.
Yeah. My dad works there, too.
He's a detective.
Yeah, I see him sometimes.
I don't really know him,
but I, you know, see him in passing.
Cool. Yeah.
Um, well, thanks again.
I guess you're my hero today.
Glad I could be there for you.
You know what?
Would you wanna get a coffee?
I mean,
I know you're having a coffee right now.
I meant like, you know,
at a different time. With me.
Or it doesn't even have to be a coffee,
it could be any kind of beverage,
like a wine or beer...
Not that I wanna get you drunk.
We could get iced tea.
Do you like iced tea?
Would you wanna get an iced tea with me?
Um...
- Yes. Yes.
- Yeah?
Yes, I would like to get an iced tea
with you.
Okay.
Barry Allen, you're very cute,
you know that?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, but you should
try talking just a little bit slower.
Speed has always been my problem.
I'll see you later.
- What's up, Barry?
- Hey.
You look a little less glum
this day's afternoon.
Captain Mendez,
I asked out a girl and she said "yes."
- Ah, there's no better feeling, is there?
- No better feeling.
Till the day she says, "I do."
Yeah, we got a ways to go
before that, I think.
Oh, great. Well, that'll give you
a lot of time
to catch me up
on where we are with The Rival.
Nothing substantive.
He hasn't left any hair or skin samples
at any of his attacks on the CCPD.
So, you're telling me
there's no way to ID this guy?
We'll figure out who he is
when The Flash stops him.
Well, The Flash better hurry up.
Pun intended.
Okay. All right.
Has anybody seen Detective West?
You know, uh,
I think he had to stop by evidence.
Uh-huh.
I don't know where he is, actually. Sorry.
Oh, Captain, is it okay
if I leave a little early today?
For your hot date?
No, I'm, uh, just meeting
a friend for dinner.
Barry! No!
You're not gonna kill her this time.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You're safe now, okay?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Dinner.
There better be curly fries in there.
You know, human beings can go
almost three weeks without food,
so I'd sound a little bit more grateful
if I were you.
You wouldn't do that to me, Barry.
After all, you're the hero.
Or did you forget that?
Too busy leading your reverse
It's a Wonderful Life?
Reverse, huh? That's irony for you.
So...
What should we call
this, uh, brave new world
that you've whipped up for us?
I was thinking "Flashpoint."
So, you don't want this?
You may have figured out a way
to dampen my speed with this glass cage,
but I will get out of here
and I will destroy your life, Flash.
One way or the other.
No. You won't.
You're never getting out of here.
And you're never gonna
hurt anybody ever again.
I have everything back
that you took from me.
I have everything Zoom took.
I'm finally free. I'm home.
This isn't your home, Barry.
This is a mirage,
a fiction that will end us both
unless you let me
the hell out of this thing!
Wow.
You're not listening, Thawne.
Why would I wanna get out of here?
I'm whole here.
There's even a "Flash,"
so I don't have to be.
Yeah, and who is
this dashing young speedster, huh?
Do you know? You even care?
While you sit around and hide
like a lost, lonely little boy,
letting someone else risk their life
to protect this city,
our common enemy is coming for us both.
What common enemy is that?
Time.
It's already screwing with you
and everyone you love,
and pretty soon, it's gonna
take me right down along with you.
Wow.
You know, you've got some nerve.
I'll give you that.
Warning me
about messing with other people's lives.
You know the whole reason I did this
is because of what you did to my life.
To my family. To my mother.
Yeah, and one day soon, Barry,
you'll be begging me to kill her again.
It would be really nice
to take a little trip there.
Can you hold this for me?
All right, yeah.
Oh, I wanted to tell you,
the car's making this noise,
kind of a clanking noise.
I think we probably should...
- Do you wanna drive?
- Whatever you want.
- Hey, slugger.
- There's my beautiful boy.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, everything's great.
Morning!
- Morning, Barry.
- Morning.
Ah...
- Looks good. Hey.
- Hey.
- What is up with you?
- What do you mean?
Well, lately you hug me every morning
as if it's the first time
you've seen me in months.
Well, I mean, I'll stop
if you really want me to.
Never. I love it.
Oh, Barry, I wanted to tell you,
I sold a house to a nice, older couple
a few weeks ago.
- The basement apartment.
- Mmm-hmm.
They emailed me this morning to tell me
they wanted to rent it.
- Cool.
- Very reasonably.
You want me to move out?
No, no. Son, come on.
It's just, you know,
if you ever thought about dating...
Oh, I forgot to tell you guys!
The girl that I've seen at Jitters...
This the girl you've been stalking
for the last three months?
Okay, I have not been stalking her.
I've been working up the courage
to ask her out.
- And?
- And I did.
And she said yes.
- All right! Good job!
- Oh!
This girl just got the best guy, huh?
- Mmm...
- Oh, honey.
- All right.
- Hey, Barr.
- Yeah?
- Have you seen Detective West?
- He's...
- I told him that if he was late again,
he'd be facing a 10-day rip.
Uh... Yeah, no, he mentioned something
yesterday, actually,
about running another canvas
on that Jefferson case.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
Then I can see why
he hasn't answered me for the past hour!
Uh...
Maybe he's in a weird zone or something.
Are we...
Cell zone.
Detective West?
Detective?
Oh, no.
Joe. Hey, Joe, you got to get...
on...
I'm sorry about this, Joe.
What the...
Afternoon, Detective.
Oh. Hey, Allen.
Hey. So, I told Captain Mendez you were
canvasing for the Jefferson case again.
Breath mint?
What... Why are you talking to Captain
about me?
Oh, well, you're just a little late again.
That's my business, not yours.
I was just trying to help you out.
Am I wearing a sign that says "help me"?
You might as well be.
Look, like they say in the movies,
we're not partners and we're not friends.
You don't know me, you don't know my life.
So, why the sudden interest
in me keeping my lousy job?
And what the hell
makes me so interesting to you, Mr. Allen?
- Tell me, I'd really like to know.
- I...
And remember, I have a hangover and a gun.
I...
- Oh, I get it.
- What?
No. I do not approve.
- Hi, Barry.
- Hey.
- Dad.
- Iris.
You think it's a good idea
dating somebody I work with?
It's just a lunch.
And, truthfully,
I wasn't even sure you still worked here.
- You ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
Okay.
- This way?
- Yeah, I just got to grab my jacket.
I'm sorry about that mini-scene
- with my dad earlier.
- Oh, yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I just feel bad for him and you.
You barely even know us.
Feels like I do.
Is that weird?
Is that a weird thing to say?
No. No, I mean, strangely,
I know what you mean.
I never say yes to guys
asking me out like that,
yet I said yes to you.
Why did I do that?
I don't know.
Some people are just
meant to be in your life, I guess.
So, tell me about you.
- Yeah.
- Mom and Dad?
Uh, alive and well.
- That's nice. Are you guys close?
- Mmm-hmm.
We are, yeah, very.
I couldn't imagine life without them.
They're, like, stupid in love.
I hope I have what they have some day.
You just haven't met the right girl yet,
is that it?
That's the thing about the right girl.
She's out there, waiting.
Just have to be lucky enough to find her.
Where'd you come from, Barry Allen?
I've always been here, Iris.
Are you okay?
Uh, sorry, yeah. That... I was just
thinking of something, and I lost it.
What's going on?
The Flash and The Rival are going at it
in the Werther building.
Everyone needs to evacuate this area.
I am so sorry, I have to go.
- Really? What...
- Yeah.
Yeah, there's something that I have to do.
This was... Rain check, okay?
Anytime.
Okay, come on.
Yeah, Cap. Come on, I got you.
No, no. Hey, hey, hey. No, no!
I thought I had him.
Wally?
Who the hell are you?
So, this is your base of operations, huh?
Yeah. What were you expecting, a fortress?
Uh, no. You know...
Just something a little more secure.
I mean, you never know who's gonna
come walking through that door.
Yeah, I was just about to say
the same thing.
- Iris! Hi.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm not, I'm...
He showed up
when I was fighting The Rival,
and he already knew who I was.
Is that why you asked me out?
Because my brother is The Flash?
No, no, this is a complete coincidence.
Okay, how'd you know
who I was under the mask?
Uh, I'm CSI, you know?
So, I just put it together.
So, what I don't know is
how you got your speed.
Oh, okay, so before I went on
the straight and narrow,
- I used to drive illegal cars.
- Uh-huh.
I was messing around with a new nitro
formula to get my engine revving faster.
Then, one night,
I'm racing in a thunderstorm,
my car gets struck by lightning!
And, then, it must have mixed
with the formula, because, boom!
I was in a coma for nine months.
Then when I woke up,
I was the fastest man alive.
The Flash.
More like Kid Flash.
- Don't call me that.
- I call you that.
Okay, how about no one calls me that?
- Hmm.
- So, how did you get involved?
- I'm a reporter for CCPN.
- Uh-huh.
Instead of just reporting on crimes
that are happening in the city,
I decided to do something about it.
Brother-sister crime-fighting unit.
So, does your dad know about you two?
You work with the guy, what do you think?
I think that we need to stop The Rival.
- Yeah.
- Well, we're open to suggestions.
I've been trying to
run him down for months.
No luck. He's fast. Maybe faster than me.
Well, if you're willing,
I think maybe I could help.
There's only one man who can help us now.
Cisco Ramon.
Didn't this used to be S.T.A.R. Labs?
Where have you been the past few years?
Running around.
Cisco Ramon made billions
with his tech apps. Bought the building.
- Billions?
- Yeah.
Cisco Ramon is the richest man in America.
Oh!
Is there a better way to get to work
than by helicopter?
Let me answer that.
Capital "N," little "O."
Quite right, Mr. Ramon.
As for LogicFrame,
it's a relatively small start-up.
The IP's expected to be in the low teens.
Offer them 20 mil.
Huh!
Babe.
I, um, have some business to attend to,
so we'll get on that other matter later?
Not if I get on it first, huh?
Independent woman. I like it. I like it!
Huh. Well.
I told you never to come back here.
I make you a friction-proof suit
so your clothes don't explode at Mach 2,
and you leave me out of your
brother-sister war on crime.
- That was the deal.
- Okay, listen to me.
Mr. Ramon, we need your help!
I'm sure you've seen The Rival on TV.
He is terrorizing the city
to prove that he's the fastest.
I mean, God only knows
what he's gonna do next.
- We have to stop him.
- Okay, so stop him.
Please, go with God, have fun.
But you know what?
You know what happens
when you mess with a speedster?
That! That's what happens.
You get a vibrating hand
going right through your rib cage.
No, thanks. My money needs me.
Wait, Cisco, you're not gonna help us?
Oh. That reminds me. Who the hell is this?
Huh?
You brought some stranger into my lab
and told him I helped The Flash?
- Cisco.
- Uh-uh.
I don't know you, string bean.
String... Mr. Ramon.
Oh. Yes?
I do know what kind of person you are.
Deep down you care
about helping other people.
Please, tell me more.
I heard a story about
how when you were 15,
your brother, Dante, owed a bookie
and he couldn't pay back what he owed,
so you gave him all the money
you earned that summer delivering pizzas
to help him.
How do you know about that?
I have a feeling that we would work
really well together as partners.
Taking down meta-humans together,
I mean, it's what we're supposed to do.
We're a team.
We're friends.
Hey-
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm okay, I was just...
What was I... What was I just saying?
What is going on with you?
I'm not sure.
And here I was starting to think
you'd forgotten all about me.
But I am forgetting.
What's happening to me?
I was wondering when you'd notice.
It's like I'll be thinking of a
moment from my past and then it vanishes.
I can't get it back. Why?
Flashpoint, it's a side effect.
See, I told you before
you don't know what you're doing.
This new reality you've created
is starting to overwrite the reality
that you and I know.
So your original life,
your friends, your family...
Pretty soon,
all of that will just fade away.
- Why isn't it happening to you?
- Not sure.
Unless...
What?
What the hell is so funny?
Your speed!
What?
The more you use it,
the faster you'll lose your memories.
No. No, you're lying.
You just want me to let you out of here.
That's never gonna happen.
The you I know from the future,
he's not this stupid.
Pretty soon, you won't even remember
that you're The Flash,
and when that happens,
this world will become permanent.
Time will set like concrete
and nothing will be able
to change it back to the way it was.
That's fine by me.
You know what you have to do.
You have to take me back to that night
and let me finish what I started.
You go to hell!
You're taking both of us there!
Now who's the villain, Flash?
Now who's the villain?
Unbelievable.
It's like I'm really there.
Don't do that,
I told you it freaks me out.
It wasn't me.
Who are you?
The man who's gonna help you
stop The Rival.
Barry?
Okay, so, I can tell from the
"I don't believe you" looks on your faces
that you don't believe me.
We believe you're a speedster
but you're gonna have to
explain that part about Flashpoint again.
All right, look.
This is as simple as I can put it.
I'm gonna use this glass, Mr. Ramon, okay?
What?
Imagine that this line is time, okay?
I went back in time, stopped the
Reverse Flash from killing my mom.
In doing so,
I created an alternate timeline,
a whole new existence
where you're Kid Flash...
- "The" Flash.
- Kid Flash.
And Cisco's a billionaire.
So you're saying there's a timeline
out there where I'm not rich?
Boy, that's a glitch in the universe.
No, not buying it. Um, my life is my life.
Didn't just start three months ago, okay?
I've always been me.
Yeah, I don't know what to tell you,
Wally, it's complicated.
Okay, look. Even if we did believe you,
why are you telling us this now?
Because I've been hiding here
for too long.
The Rival needs to be stopped.
I stop the bad guys,
and we can all take him down together.
I can get him myself.
Then why haven't you?
Well, I'm not interested.
I don't know how many times
I gotta tell you freaks,
I already did my bit
for queen and country.
Wait, we're missing something.
Excuse me.
What're you doing? Hey, don't touch that.
Got it...
Oh!
What just happened?
Stop bringing strangers into my lab!
Who is this?
This is Dr. Caitlin Snow.
In my timeline, she's a part of our team.
Did you... You just kidnapped this woman.
No, I didn't... Well, yeah, I guess, I...
She's a scientist, we need her.
I'm not a scientist.
- You're not a scientist?
- I'm an ophthalmologist.
- An eye doctor?
- A pediatric eye doctor.
And we're done.
Okay. Um...
Can I talk to you in private?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Excuse me?
- Hmm.
Have I been kidnapped?
Unclear.
Look, I'm sorry,
I know that this is hard to believe.
No, that's just it, Barry,
I do believe you.
You do? You believe me?
I have a good life.
I have a good job, I love my brother.
But something has been off,
something has been missing.
And that feeling that
something is not right with my life,
that went away the moment that I met you.
We're something else to each other
where you come from, aren't we?
Yes.
What?
It's... It's escaped definition.
But it's love?
Because this is what love feels like.
Since the day that I met you.
Hey... We got something.
Turns out kiddie eye doc here
actually had a good idea.
I have always wondered why no one
turned the speed cameras in the city
to register near-sonic velocities.
Seems like a
ready-built early warning system.
So I reprogrammed the cameras.
Babadook, there's your rival.
The old sawmill out by Williamson.
All right. Follow my lead?
The Flash doesn't follow anyone.
Listen to him, Wally. He's The Flash.
You know, you would be
an excellent candidate for Lasik.
You know how to flank?
People always say that in the movies.
Is that like a thing, "flanking"?
What're you talking about, flanking...
Yes, flanking's a thing.
All right, look. I'm gonna go at him
head on. You attack at a 90-degree angle.
When he turns to fight you,
leaves himself vulnerable to me.
- When he turns to fight me...
- I get him.
Exactly how it should be.
How'd you find this place, Flash?
I'm so gonna kick your ass.
There's two of you now?
Okay, is that supposed to scare me?
Little quaking in your boots
wouldn't be inappropriate.
Well, here's how scared I am of you.
My name is Edward Clariss.
Rivals should know each other's names.
I mean, you might as well tell me
since neither of you
are leaving this place alive.
Who are you?
Me? I'm The Flash.
That's all you need to know.
Well, after I rip that cowl
off your corpse, I'll know who you are.
Just another pretender
who thought they could take me on.
So who wants to meet the Speedforce first?
Hey, stay in position.
I can take him. I got this.
The Flash is taking on The Rival
at Prescott Sawmill.
Get down there, make sure the action
doesn't spill out into the neighborhood.
We can't leave The Flash out there alone.
Whoo!
Wally!
Telemetry from the suit
says he's still alive.
Barely.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're gonna be okay, all right?
You're gonna be okay,
I'm gonna get you out of here.
That one was never my rival.
You could be, though.
You wanna find out?
Defeat me, and I'll let you
take your little friend for help.
No, you're the one who's gonna need help.
Goodbye, Flash.
Oh, my God. It's like Twister in there.
The movie, not the game.
Satellite's picking up
two distinct funnel patterns.
Tornados measuring F3
on the Fujita scale.
This guy's like a weather wizard
or something.
Guys, I can't stop him!
Listen to me, Barry.
You said we love each other
in that other life.
If I were your Iris from over there,
I am sure I would know exactly what to say
but I don't.
All I can say is I believe in you,
and you can stop this guy.
Be The Flash, Barry,
because that's who you are.
You're The Flash.
I'm The Flash.
That's impossible.
You really are the fastest man alive.
It's over.
Joe, it's Wally, he needs help.
Wally? Wally! Son!
Son, can you hear me?
Wally's vitals are low,
and he's lost a lot of blood.
He should be rapidly healing.
It's one of the gifts
of being a speedster.
He's not. I'm sorry.
- Am I free to go?
- Mmm-hmm.
This is why I didn't wanna get involved.
Crime-fighting sucks.
I thought I could just make things better,
but everybody's been
paying for my happiness.
Will you help me?
Do what?
Make things right.
Ah...
Oh, I need that.
You don't need that.
- Yes, and this.
- You do not need that.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Hey, slugger.
Who's this?
This is Iris.
- It's nice to meet you, Iris.
- Hi.
Can I get you something to drink?
Oh, no, I'm okay. Thanks, Mrs. Allen.
Are you okay, Barry?
Yeah, I just wanted to see you both
one more time.
What does that mean?
Nothing. Nothing. I, uh...
These last three months
have been the best.
Just getting to spend time with you.
I just wanted you to know how grateful
I am, to both of you, to be your son.
Barry, you're scaring me.
No. There's nothing to be afraid of.
Promise.
I just love you both.
Phew.
Hey, Barry! Are you okay?
It's getting worse.
We have to hurry before it's too late.
- Okay.
Hey!
Having a bad day, Barr?
Well, if it isn't the future Mrs. Allen.
Barry told me
not to listen to anything you say.
That's just bad advice.
'Cause I'm the answer man.
I am the answer to all your prayers.
All you need to do is ask me, Barry.
We need to go back in time, to that night.
To do what?
You know what I need you to do.
Yeah.
But I wanna hear you say it.
I need you to kill my mother.
With pleasure.
I hate you.
And I hate you. And I sometimes wonder
which of us is right.
It seems weird to wish you good luck.
I'm so sorry about all this.
Will I know when things change back?
Will I feel it?
It'll be like it never happened.
I'll see you soon.
- Barry!
- Get back!
God, I wish I could kill you.
But today, I get to be the hero.
No!
You're not gonna kill her this time.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you. Okay?
You're safe. You're safe now.
Actually, she's not.
Please don't hurt me.
No. No!
No!
There we go.
Things are back to how they should be.
Well, for me, anyway. For you...
Well, I guess
you'll just have to wait and find out.
What? What does that mean?
See you sometime soon, Flash.
What's this for?
Just glad you're here.
Are you okay?
Whoa...
Yeah, I am now. Yeah.
You just lost your father, Barry,
you don't have to be okay.
Actually, I feel closer to my parents
than I ever have.
Well, good, son.
- To your pops.
- To Henry.
To my dad.
Where's Iris?
That ain't funny.
I'm gonna chalk that up to grief.
I'll see you both in the morning.
What was that about?
Are you kidding me?
You know Iris isn't here.
What?
They don't talk, Barry. You know that.
Oh, God, What did I do?
Clariss. Clariss!
Who's there?
It's time to wake up.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::