My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Not a ghost.
I'm Leo Snart from Earth-X.
- I didn't do anything!
- I understand.
But your radioactivity is dangerous.
You are part of this team.
And I'm the only one with a body
that DeVoe is trying to snatch.
Now, you will die for me.
Melt.
- Killer Frost...
- Is gone.
My new host body holds
an ancillary benefit.
Dark matter siphoned from the room
where Dr. Wells was charging
his counterfeit cap.
Maximum capacity, now!
Again.
Dr. Wells, the odds of a different
conclusion are extremely low.
- Run it again.
- Yes, Dr. Wells.
Same results, Dr. Wells.
The excessive infusion of dark matter
into your neural system,
has disrupted the area of the brain
where general intelligence
and executive function occur.
My ability to integrate information
is declining.
I'm losing my intelligence.
At some point soon,
you'll need to re-learn
everything you've ever known.
Is there a way to use the
thinking cap to reverse this process?
Unlikely, Dr. Wells.
Your thinking cap and the dark matter
is what caused this.
- I tried to caution restraint...
- I know!
Gideon, how long
before everything I know
is gone?
You know, it's only been
a couple of days since he died,
but it still doesn't feel real.
How close were you with Ralph?
We were becoming close.
Yeah, it took me a while
to see past the things
that I didn't like when we first met,
but after a while,
I started to see what a good guy
he was.
Started to see the hero
that he became.
You consider him a hero?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
What about you, Barry?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. I mean, you know,
I'm working through it.
So, you weren't
as close to him as Iris was?
No. I mean, we were about the same,
I'd say.
They used to work together.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
And you're fine already
with his death?
I've dealt with a lot of death
in my life.
Yes, you have.
Your mother, father, Eddie,
Ronnie, H.R.
Has Ralph's death had any impact
on you at all?
I think I just know
how to deal with death now,
so, it doesn't affect me
as much as it once did.
All right,
I guess we'll pick this up later.
Yeah.
- Same time next week?
- Or before, if you need.
Barry, grief is a complex emotion,
that as you know
deals on its own terms.
There is no practice makes perfect.
Thirsty, my love?
You're happy?
More than I've been in a long time,
my love.
To your return.
- I never left you, Marlize.
- It felt like you had.
Those days are past us now.
All our sacrifice, our commitment,
our planning,
everything is as it was and more.
There's been no decline
in your metabolic processes
since your last transference.
My mind, my abilities,
these elasticized cells,
can hold another bus full
of meta-humans powers,
and I still wouldn't be affected.
It gives me peace, Clifford.
I need your mind focused
for what happens next.
- We start today?
- Yes.
But we have time, my love.
Could we not spend time together
as husband and wife?
- I think...
- Hmm! That is your first mistake.
Leave the thinking to me.
Whoa! Stop! Don't bother.
- It doesn't work.
- I don't know about that.
Yeah, well, I know about it. I'm the
guy who wore it on his head.
It helped you gain ground
on DeVoe, didn't it?
Mapping the pocket dimensions,
building the Scepter.
We stopped you from using it,
right when we needed it most,
when Ralph got...
We thought you were addicted.
We shouldn't have stopped you.
We were wrong.
That's not... You know,
you weren't wrong.
No, I was addicted.
Yeah. It was stupid
when you think about it.
Because I'm a pretty smart guy.
How much smarter is
this intelligence booster making me?
10%? I think we both agree that
DeVoe is at least
twice as smart as that.
Then maybe
I should get to wear it, too.
Okay, no. No.
This thing would never work on you
because I specifically designed
this to stimulate my brain waves.
My brain waves, not yours, okay?
- My cerebral firings, okay?
- Harry! Harry!
I'm saying we should build
a second thinking cap.
- Intelligence booster.
- For me.
- For, for you?
- Yes, for me.
Think about it.
Two heads are better than one.
Your ideas, my ideas,
put 'em together, we combine them,
we build upon each others ideas.
Harry, with two caps...
With two caps, we can get DeVoe.
Okay. Get on it.
Melt.
Anything new?
No sign of DeVoe.
I meant with you.
No. No cold signatures
anywhere in the city.
Killer Frost is nowhere to be found.
That doesn't make sense. DeVoe
created every bus meta for a reason.
I mean, he had no
interest in Barry's powers,
or Cisco's,
or any of the metas at Iron Heights,
so, I don't know
why he would suddenly want yours.
We all saw what happened. When DeVoe
touched me, my powers disappeared.
Had to be him.
DeVoe?
Satellite's picking up three
different pocket dimensions
opening in Keystone. That's each...
All right, you and me, all right.
Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait.
They all just closed.
- What?
- Hmm.
Wrong coordinates.
Maybe, he made a mistake.
He doesn't make mistakes.
He must want something in Keystone.
- Tracy Brand's lab.
- He's going after Fallout.
All right, call Tracy, tell her
we're coming for Borman, okay?
Wait, and gonna do what?
Just to take him somewhere else.
We can't take him here.
We can't even contain his fallout.
Tracy's barely been able to contain
his powers as is.
Yeah, the guy is a nuclear explosion
waiting to go off,
and I don't know about you,
but I have had
my fill of nuclear bombs this year.
But if we can cool him down,
we can get him somewhere safe.
What about Snart's cold gun?
I mean, I have a prototype,
but to modify it to our needs,
- that would take at least a day.
- We don't have that kinda time.
DeVoe is coming for him.
DeVoe has known our every move.
I mean, we've gotta do something
that he hasn't accounted for.
How are we supposed to find
a way to cool down Borman,
and take him somewhere
DeVoe won't know about,
with a plan he won't see coming?
Call Lyla. See if A.R.G.U.S.
has anything off the grid.
Okay, but even if they do,
I mean, what are we gonna do
about the other two problems?
War's over. Bad guys and girls lost.
Nazi regime's been dismantled.
And the rebellion's in charge now.
Why don't you turn yourself in?
Save us the Tom and Jerry.
Find some other misguided cause
to get all agro about.
Not this night.
I will fight until
every last one of you
finds the same fate
as my brothers and sisters.
Your timing is impeccable.
We need your help on our Earth.
Right now, I'm kinda busy.
Doing what? Dying?
Touché.
So, you're trying to stop a guy who
thinks he's smarter than everyone,
and his true believer lover,
who are hell-bent in achieving
their evil machinations at any cost?
Well, it's right up my alley.
Except DeVoe actually is
smarter than everyone, Leo.
He created 12 meta-humans
just so he could steal their powers.
And he left everybody dead
in the process.
Including Ralph Dibny,
who was a team member of ours.
I'm sorry. That's rough.
All these deaths have been rough.
We can't dwell on them right now.
We have to focus, so that
DeVoe doesn't know what we're doing,
and we have a shot at saving Borman.
Which is why we came to you.
I see.
I'm just outside the box enough,
to catch DeVoe off-guard.
That, and we need your cold gun.
Oh? For what?
We've been working on modifying
a radiation hazmat suit
to regulate his internal temperature
to keep his core from raising to the
point of detonation during transport.
Your cold gun would be our backup.
It must be happy hour.
And I'm the two-for-one.
What about your chilly friend?
She doesn't want in on the fun?
- She's gone.
- That's too bad.
All right. You get me for 24 hours,
not a minute more.
Wait, why not?
Because I thought I'd make
Ray an honest man tomorrow.
You're getting married?
That's so exciting.
I figured if you two could make it,
so could we.
- What?
- No, we...
I tease.
So, where are we moving this guy to?
A.R.G.U.S. has a facility
in New Brighton,
high tech, high security.
He should be safe there.
And how long till you're
done with the suit?
Few more tweaks.
Okay, I'm gonna call my dad
and let him know the plan.
- Hey.
- Is that it? Are you done?
- Yeah.
Well, the truth is,
the first one was the hard part.
This one is simply, basically,
following the plan...
Precisely. Let's take this
for a spin, shall we?
All right. Okay.
Here. Have a seat.
Okay. All right then, I guess...
Hey, I trust you.
Yeah, well, I know that.
Okay, here we go.
Connection established.
- It tingles.
- Yeah.
Kinda feels like my conditioner. Ooh!
That's your
synaptic activity enhancing.
Whoa!
Boy, is it ever.
It's like a party in my brain.
I can see why you like this thing
so much.
I can feel my neurons firing. Okay.
Whoo-hoo!
Pikachu! Whoo!
- Harry! Harry!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hoo!
Yeah, I think what happened was
probably a hyper limiter valve that...
- Promethium ion diodes.
- Ion diodes.
You overloaded the cap?
We overloaded it. Real bummer.
Oh, well, we tried.
How the hell did you get
promethium ion diodes?
I got 'em. I... In my lab.
On my Earth, I had them there,
but I'm all out unfortunately.
We don't have any here. It would
take us weeks to get some.
Oh, well, well, you know what,
we'll put in a back order,
and we'll see if I can come up
with something else.
Right.
I see our scare tactics worked.
They are going to move the asset
as you anticipated.
Yes, but unfortunately,
not to the location I predicted.
What is this?
Your favorite dress.
And you chose to wear that now?
To please you, my love.
Now, what would please me
is your understanding
of the gravity of our undertaking.
To right the misguided course
of all humanity.
I just thought...
You see, again you thought,
which led you to this trivial notion.
And now, go and change into something
a bit more appropriate.
Your role from now,
until the enlightenment has occurred,
is as my technician.
Now leave me be, so that I can figure
out a way to motivate Team Flash
to deliver our quarry to where
initially intended.
All right, look,
I think we take Highway 14.
It's as rural as we're gonna get. And
it's a straight shot to New Brighton.
Best chance to get Fallout to safety.
Sounds like a plan, Barry.
You know how I feel about plans.
Yeah.
This was your team member, right?
Ralph Dibny.
Yeah. Elongated Man.
Elongated Man.
I don't remember someone with that
name being part of the fight
- against the Nazis.
- No, no. He wasn't ready yet.
A rookie hero.
- So, you trained him?
- As much as I could. Yeah.
Even harder death to take,
someone you've mentored.
And yet, somehow, you seem okay.
Considering this happened, what,
just a few days ago.
I am okay. I'm just trying
to do what I have to do.
- I'm trying to stay on task.
- Oh, is that what you're doing?
You know how may rebels
we lost over the years, Barry,
trying to defeat those Nazi bastards?
- Countless, I'm sure.
- Not countless.
Counted. 18,322,
3,679 were under my watch.
And I felt the weight of each
of their deaths, I still do,
so many years after they died.
Leo, look...
The thing I realized is that
to continue to lead,
to be clear-headed, I had to
grieve those men and women I lost.
So, I did. Each and every one.
Look, Barry, you want me to help
you move a meta-human nuclear bomb
that some genius with nearly every
meta power on this board is after,
I will do what I can.
As long as your head is on straight,
because if I die before Ray and I
get married, Ray will kill me.
Suit's ready.
And Fallout is ready at Tracy's lab.
So, let's get to Keystone. You good?
- I'm good.
- Then let's go get our guy.
Meta-human nuclear bomb.
And Fallout is ready at Tracy's lab.
Let's get to Keystone.
Then let's go get our guy.
Yes, let's.
After all,
a nuke is a terrible thing to waste.
You're telling me I have to wear
this thing the whole time?
Yeah. Look,
that suit protects us from you,
so that
we can protect you from the guy
that's trying to hunt you down.
But why is he after me?
Honestly, Neil, we don't know. But
we wanna find out as much as you do.
And we will, trust me.
You saved me once, Flash,
I trust you to do it again.
What's that?
I whipped up this cocktail of
atomized DTPI and potassium iodide.
It should flood our thyroids
with enough non-radioactive iodine,
so that
if our containment suit doesn't work,
it should offer some protection
from radiation.
Some protection?
How vaguely reassuring.
- How long will this last?
- Two, three hours max.
Then you better get going.
All right, let's just go over
the plan one more time, okay.
I'm gonna be running ahead
of the truck, scouting the route
- for any signs of trouble.
- Right.
I will be at S.T.A.R. Labs, tracking
any pocket dimension en route.
And I will be in the truck with Neil,
monitoring his vitals and rads.
With me at the ready in case our
meta of mass destruction here
goes all mushroom cloud. No offense.
And I'll be driving
and reciting every prayer
that Cecile's ever taught me.
I might join you.
Look, guys, I know
DeVoe has hit us pretty hard,
but right now, let's just try to
forget what he's taken from us
and stay focused on
taking something from him,
by getting Neil safely to A.R.G.U.S.
We do that, whatever DeVoe
has planned falls apart.
Winning this battle
may just win us the war.
Hear, hear. Let's all make sure
we keep our heads in the game.
So, we can stay safe out there.
- I know what that was about.
- It was a good speech, Barry.
Just making sure you heard it,
didn't just give it.
What is that supposed to mean?
If you don't confront your feelings,
they will confront you.
All clear on my end.
There's no pocket dimension
activity in the area.
Roads are looking good, too. Joe?
Yeah, the rig is secure.
- Caitlin?
- Rads are good. Heartbeat regular.
On Earth-X, we have a saying,
"If you laugh out loud,
"you gotta share the joke."
By-product of living on an Earth
where joy is a scarce commodity.
It's a Post-it note
from Killer Frost.
It's how we talk or talked.
"Broke the thermostat again.
I think it hates me."
Aw! That's cute. Do you miss her?
It's not that. It's just that
we were starting
to become close lately.
And I know how crazy that sounds,
considering, we're talking
about someone
who actually lived inside of me.
I'm on an alt-Earth,
transporting a human bomb.
With an escort that can literally
run back to the future.
Your story is the least crazy thing
I've heard all day.
One thing's for sure.
I will miss those little notes.
Alter-ego or not,
it's okay to miss someone we've lost.
How's he doing?
Good. His rads are low,
vitals seem stable.
I gave him a sedative,
and it seems to be working.
Okay, good. We're almost there.
Guys, there's
pocket dimension activity.
Dad?
We're trapped in here.
The doors are unlocked,
but it's just like it weighs a ton.
- Iris?
- Dad?
- The comms are out. It's DeVoe.
He's here?
Mr. Allen,
as usual, you're a step behind me.
Yay, puns. You Earth-1 villains
sure are a hoot.
You have no idea, Mr. Snart.
You're not taking Fallout.
I can, and I will.
If not here and now, then after your
top secret transfer to A.R.G.U.S.
Yes, I know.
Remember?
Good. I won't have to feel guilty
about doing this.
Well, that deescalated quickly.
The minuscule soundwaves produced
by that toy trinket of yours
are far too weak
for this new body of mine.
What a gift Mr. Dibny provided.
Well, it was a gift in
a manner of speaking. Right, rookie?
Barry.
Why such turmoil in your mind,
Mr. Allen?
Allow me to ease your pain.
That's it. I'm leaving.
No, I need you to stay here,
and calm down!
Neil, wait!
I want you all to listen to me
very carefully,
and hopefully,
I won't have to raise my voice.
This truck is now mine.
We really have no way of finding
Joe and Caitlin,
not even by tracking Fallout.
That hazmat suit is hiding
his radiation signature.
So, the satellite can't even
find him, unless he heats up.
Okay, what do you know
about Laurel Lance's doppelganger?
Why was she hunting you?
That was Siren-X.
All that's left of the Reichsman.
An elite assassin gone mad,
and she is relentless.
Carried the torch for Dark Arrow.
Unrequited.
So, she is none too pleased
with those responsible for his death,
present company included.
So, she has the same powers
as Black Siren?
The Laurel Lance of Earth-2.
- And Earth-1's Laurel Lance?
- She died.
She was the second Black Canary
after her sister.
Who also died and came back,
but as White Canary 'cause...
- Cisco.
- It's complicated.
Right. Doppelganger confusion aside,
Siren-X has my cold gun and a nuke.
And her thirst for vengeance won't
prevent her from using either one
on me, or all of you now.
- Hey. Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm just a little worried.
It seemed like
she got the jump on you out there.
She didn't.
She just caught me off-guard.
But why does it matter right now?
We don't even know
where Joe and Caitlin are?
Hey, Cisco, will you just see
if Harry has any ideas?
- I'm on it.
- Just watch the satellites,
like a hawk.
Leo, what exactly happened out there?
Well, just your typical deadly combat
between two metas
from multiple Earths.
Leonard.
- I'll go talk to him.
- Thank you.
Where is it?
Hey, Ramon, what are you doing?
A Nazi Laurel Lance
just kidnapped Caitlin and Joe.
We're gonna make this thing work,
and we're gonna make it work now.
Well, we can't.
We can't. I still haven't found
a replacement for that...
- Where did you get that?
- I found this
in one of the cubes Gypsy sent me.
How clever of you. You know what,
Ramon, it's still not gonna work.
- It's not gonna work.
- Why?
Because it's not gonna work, okay?
Because it's a waste of time.
Because I said so, that's why!
- Well, in that case...
- Listen, Ramon.
- Our friends' lives are at stake.
- You don't...
Look, I don't know
what's going on with you,
but if you're not gonna help me
with this thing, I...
What...
Why would you do that?
To protect you.
The cap did this?
And dark matter.
You used dark matter.
I used dark matter.
Look, Ramon, it was the only way.
The only way to do what,
fry your synapses?
Harry, you promised me.
I know I promised you.
I promised you.
Oh, my God.
Harry, how could you be so stupid?
'Cause I felt so stupid.
We all feel stupid right now!
Yes! But you're Vibe,
Allen's the Flash, who am I?
My only job is to be smarter
than all the villains
who wanna hurt this team,
and without that, I'm nothing.
I'm about to lose the only part of me
that is any value to this team,
the only part of me that matters,
and so, yeah, I destroyed the cap.
So that you wouldn't make the same
mistake I did.
- This should not be happening.
- Perhaps, you miscalculated.
I calculated everything.
The Flash's involvement
with the bus-meta.
The little recruitment
of Snart's doppelganger.
Even the arrival
of the Earth-X banshee.
Every event occurred exactly
as I predicted,
except the outcome!
You were supposed to defeat Siren-X?
No.
The Flash was, but
Barry Allen just stood there, frozen.
And now,
I've lost my only nuclear meta.
Because the Flash failed!
Why? Why did he fail?
Perhaps, there were variables
that we just did not consider.
As I already explained,
there is no variable
beyond my examination.
Even less apparent.
The last time Barry Allen saw you,
you took the life
of his close friend.
And now, he sees you and he pauses.
You really don't see it.
You can calculate near infinite
outcomes across multiple Earths,
but you cannot account
for how someone is feeling.
What did you see out there, Barry?
- When you froze up?
- Nothing.
You just got
two of your teammates captured,
and almost got me killed,
so, either you explain what happened,
or I leave.
- I saw Ralph.
- I warned you.
He's messing with your head.
No, it's not like that.
Do I miss him? Yes.
Do I regret what happened? Of course.
But I don't need lessons in loss.
What I need to do right now,
is lead my team.
You're gonna lead them to their
deaths if you don't deal with this.
- Back off, Leo.
- You need to grieve him, Barry.
Grief is a luxury
I don't have time for.
- Make time!
- I can't!
Not Ralph. Not right now.
Ah.
So, we've finally reached the core.
You don't want to grieve this one.
So, Ralph's death must be different
from all the other losses
you've experienced, but why?
Why?
Barry, trust me,
there is no outrunning grief.
That was a pun, I'm sorry.
Run! Run!
CCPD.
Home of the brave, land of the dead.
Killing all these people
won't bring back your regime.
No, it won't. But decimating
your so-called officers,
will make it
a hell of a lot more even.
I'll make sure of it.
- Remove your helmet.
- What?
Take it off!
CCPD. Why would she take him there?
We destroyed her Earth's protectors,
maybe she wants
to do the same thing to us.
- Harry, we need eyes.
- You know what?
Why don't you let me
take care of it, all right?
You keep an eye on the rads.
Leo, we're on.
Barry, I'm always on.
- But wait, I need a...
- Got you.
- Thank you, Iris.
- Mmm-hmm.
How much time do we have left
on the injection?
Not enough.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- Barry!
- This is for destroying my world!
- 7,000 rads.
- And climbing.
Guys, you gotta cool him down.
8,000 rads and climbing.
Flash! Get up! Get up!
Flash.
People are going to die, Flash!
- I'm not ready to die.
- Rise up.
- Let me train you.
- Train me?
Fight it, all right. Fight it!
I'll save you!
Flash.
Flash, you have to deal
with the pain.
No!
You can't get away from
what's inside you, so, stop trying!
Flash!
9,000 rads.
The whole place is gonna blow.
Flash! It wasn't your fault!
Ralph!
I'll save you.
You already did, Barry.
He's burning up.
Time to get cold-blooded.
8,000 rads.
7,000 rads.
Keep icing him, it's working.
And dropping.
- He's contained.
- They did it.
Where's the Flash?
Barr. What's going on, Barr?
He trusted me, Joe.
And I let him down.
Ralph, I'm the reason he's dead.
- No.
- I failed him.
He was my responsibility.
Now, he's gone.
It's all right.
So, we're sure
that Fallout is secure?
Well, Lyla said she had some people
who would be very interested
in helping Borman control his power.
She took him
to a different A.R.G.U.S.
- black-op site way off the grid.
- How far off the grid?
Like, it would take Jack Ryan
two Tom Clancy novels to find him.
I gotta say, on any Earth,
Snarts have style. Perfect fit.
I thought
you could do something with it.
- You wear it well.
- Thank you.
You sure
you can't come to the wedding?
I could put all of you
at a table with Ray's uncle, Skip,
he murders the Macarena.
- Yeah, DeVoe is still out there.
- Suit yourselves.
But if you are looking
for a place to honeymoon,
our Earth
has some pretty spectacular spots.
What is this?
That is an interdimensional
extrapolator.
It makes small-scale breaches.
In case, Ray's uncle, Skip, wants
to see how the other half lives.
Look at that. "Something old,
something new, something borrowed."
Something navy.
We're gonna miss you, Leo.
I'm gonna miss you too, Caitlin.
You're quite the badass, you know.
- Enough to make your alter ego proud.
- Thank you.
Detective West,
I know my Earth-1 counterpart
gave you a lot of headaches.
Hopefully, I've begun
to make up for that.
Man, you prevented a nuke
from leveling the city.
We're good.
Cisco, I think
I'm gonna miss that hair.
Okay.
Iris West-Allen,
thank you for helping me take down
Nazi scum again.
You're welcome again.
And then there was one.
I could see why the other Snart
turned over a new leaf
and joined the good guys.
You treat everyone around you
with kindness and respect.
Just remember to do the same
for yourself, every once in a while.
- Thanks for helping me push through.
- Anytime, Barry.
Don't be a stranger.
Oh, you never know.
How you doing?
I know last night was pretty rough.
I'll tell you about it
when we see Dr. Finkel.
We're seeing, Dr. Finkel?
Yeah, I gave her a call.
How's it going?
I don't know.
Hauling a nuclear meta
across the state,
getting kidnapped
by a screeching psychopath,
and helping save this city,
I'd say that's pretty impressive
for someone without a meta other half
to lean on.
Thanks. You know,
the thing I realized yesterday is,
even though
I can live without Killer Frost,
I don't think I want to.
Run some more tests,
find out for sure.
I already did.
- And?
- I'm too afraid to find out.
Let's find out together.
What does it say?
It says the reason dark matter
isn't registering in my body,
is because there is none.
So, she's gone?
It says there's still another
cryogenic anomaly in my DNA.
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
I just have to figure out
how to get her to appear.
You going somewhere?
Yeah. As a matter of fact, I'm gonna
visit my daughter while I'm still...
Of sound mind. It's not like I can
help you guys around here, anyway.
'Cause that is the only part
of you that matters,
- that mind of yours.
- Exactly.
Is that why
Jesse turned out so great?
Yeah. No. I don't know.
What's your point?
- Jesse Quick, superhero, scientist.
- Yeah, I know who she is.
All-around wonderful person.
She turned out that way because...
- I don't know.
- I think you do.
You told me you were about to lose
the only part of you that has value.
Yeah. Yeah.
Raising Jesse?
Raising a kid
that turns out like that.
That takes a lot more
than intelligence.
If you asked her, I'm pretty
sure she'd tell you, learning
quadratic equations at age five
from her math-obsessed father
wasn't nearly as important to her
as having a dad,
who was there for her,
and who gave a damn.
- So, my point is...
- Well taken.
So, now what?
Slow down, wait till I regress
to a simpleton?
Now, we figure out a way to fix you.
Just like you did
when Barry lost his speed,
we find a way to
jump-start your brain.
But this is the hard part 'cause
it's gonna take all of us to do it.
Which means
you have to tell the team.
I gotta tell the team.
Yeah. I know you're right,
but maybe not today.
When you're ready.
- Ramon.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
I knew Ralph since
I was a rookie on the force.
And all that time,
I thought I knew exactly
what kind of person he was.
Why is that?
We just never saw things
the same way.
You know, I was raised
to believe that people are good.
And Ralph?
He always saw the worst in people.
And he knew
how to take advantage of it.
But, um, he changed.
Yeah, he did. He changed,
and I couldn't see that
for a long time.
And now, that I can, I...
I think that's what's so hard, is...
You know, of course I miss Ralph,
but it just took me so long to see
what he had become.
I just,
I never had a chance to tell him
just how proud I am
to be his friend.
And I always will be.
- I'm sure he knew that, Barry.
- Yeah.
What else would you tell him
if you could right now?
That I feel responsible.
I feel responsible for what happened.
And he taught me more than
I could have ever taught him.
And for that,
I'll always be grateful.
Allowing events to unfold naturally
turned out in our favor.
Just as you said it would.
And success came our way
without the hindrance of that most
aberrant of human follies,
- emotion.
- It did, indeed.
To think for a moment there
I experienced doubt.
So, perhaps now, you can accept
that the primitive, cognitive
entanglements that
derailed Mr. Allen today,
can only serve to hold us back
from completing our work.
Yes.
I see that, now.
More clear than ever before.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::