Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- When I threw the Philosopher's
Stone into the Speed Force,
I accidentally ran
into the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
- How are you gonna tell Dad?
- I'm not.
- If you guys got
something going on,
I hope you know you
can talk to me.
- Every night when I go to bed,
I'm afraid that I'm gonna
wake up and be her.
I didn't ask for these powers,
just like you didn't ask
to be used by Savitar.
- So you're telling me that
every time I'm blacking out...
- You've become Alchemy.
- Alchemy can restore the powers
that people had in Flashpoint.
- What Alchemy did
was not your fault.
- I'm saying that at this point
in his training,
you're faster than Barry!
- What?
It's crazy how fast I've gotten
in such a short time.
- And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
I'm not gonna save Iris
from Savitar.
You are.
- So this is it, huh?
- Yeah.
This is the starting line
to our race.
Cisco set up sensors
all along the course,
and he'll be tracking your speed
all the way to the finish line
on the other side of town.
- No, I meant this is it...
the day the greatest upset
in speedster history goes down.
- Wally, man, this isn't
about winning or losing.
Okay?
This is about training
so you can get faster
and beat Savitar and save Iris.
- Yeah, which I'm gonna do.
- Okay.
- But first I'm gonna make you
eat my dust.
I'm sorry.
- Okay, you know there
is a reason they call me
the fastest man alive.
Cisco, you good?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
the Central City Speedster 500
is about to begin.
But first,
I've got five-to-one odds
Barry takes down Wally.
Any takers?
- Yep.
Game of speculation?
Are we...we're betting?
Yeah, no, I'm in.
On my Earth, financial wagering
was banned
after an unfortunate incident
with Vice President Al Capone.
- Well, lucky for you,
you live here now.
- Yes.
- Put me down for 20 for Barry.
- Joe, got to be in it...come on.
- No, not me.
That's a Sophie's Choice
I'm not gonna make.
- $80 on Barry.
Mama needs a new
confocal microscope.
- All right, H.R.,
you put your life in my hands,
so I know for a fact
you like high stakes.
How much you in for?
- Wallace's recent speed tests
ensure that he is a lock.
Put me down for
an Abe Lincoln.
- Hm?
- Uh, 100.
Whatever 100 is on this Earth,
put me down for that.
- Guys, we're ready.
- All right, all right.
All bets are in, and may
the odds be ever in your favor.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
- Ready?
- Get set.
- Go.
[thrilling music]
♪ ♪
- At the first marker,
1/3 of the way in,
Flash is in the lead...
or is that Kid Flash?
- Kid Flash!
Come on, little Joseph, go.
Come on, mama needs
a new pair of shoes.
Come on, Wallace, down the lane!
- I think he's done this before.
♪ ♪
- Ooh, second marker.
Wally's in the lead.
- Yeah, Wallace!
That's my boy!
- You mean that's my boy.
- That's your boy.
I want to double down.
I want to double down
on that right now.
- Oh, H.R., big spender.
You serious?
- Serious?
Serious as a heart attack, Rich.
- Guys, they're neck and neck.
- And almost at the finish line.
♪ ♪
- Oh!
- Oh, yes!
Pay up.
- Hmm?
- Now?
Do you guys take IOUs?
- Come on, man,
that didn't count.
You know I can't phase yet.
- Man, you just
saw me do it, right?
And you have to be ready
to face any obstacle
that's put in your path.
- Yeah, well,
don't worry, Barry.
I'ma get faster.
Pretty soon I'm gonna
be faster than you.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, until then,
what's my name?
[laughing]
[police siren wailing]
- Joe, hey, this one, is, uh...
- Pretty ghastly, Detective,
I warn you.
- That's the body?
- Yeah, why?
- Because he died
less than eight hours ago.
- Eight hours?
- He was a chef here...
Stuart Holzman...
and the owner confirmed
that he was working last night.
- Huh.
- That's a lot of damage
in a short amount of time.
- We thinking he's a meta?
- Possibly, although
certain chemicals
can cause a similar reaction.
- Yeah, any acid
with a pH below two.
- Precisely.
We could be looking
for an aggressive variant
of a necrotized fasciitis.
- A flesh-eating disease.
- In a restaurant?
I'm never eating out again.
- Okay, so an autopsy
might help us hone in
on what really did this.
- Yes, I agree.
Unfortunately, County
denied my request
for a 3D image medical scanner,
which would make short work
of the process.
- Okay, well, we have one
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Allen, this is
an active investigation.
There is protocol to follow...
surely?
- Not if we're gonna
figure this out.
- Okay, I'll bag the body myself
and meet you there.
- Great.
Iris, hey.
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm just, uh,
running up against
a deadline, so...
- Since I have you both,
I wanted to ask,
um, Cecile's daughter, Joanie,
is in town, and I was thinking
that maybe we could
all get together.
If you don't think
it's too soon.
I mean, I haven't exactly been
dating Cecile for that long.
- It's not too early, Joe.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- And Jitters...
is that cool?
Or is that too casual?
- Dad, don't worry, okay?
It's great.
Joanie's gonna love you.
- I love my kids.
I'm gonna set it up.
Thank you.
- All right.
It's nice to see him so happy.
- Yeah, it is.
- You okay?
- Hey, I need to show you
something at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Okay.
- Look.
That's the name of the
restaurant where we just were.
- Yeah.
- I spoke to the owner,
and he said he doesn't think
that the restaurant can survive
an attack like this...
that they'd most likely
have to reopen under a new name.
It's all coming true, Barry.
- No.
- I thought things
were changing.
- Things are changing, okay?
They are.
I was supposed to stop
Plunder, right?
And instead Wally did.
And we're gonna...
[sighs]
Stop Savitar too.
I'm making sure of it.
- What if we can't stop
all of this?
I'm scared, Barry.
- Okay, uh...
- [sighs nervously]
- Maybe we should tell Joe.
- No, no.
No, we agreed
that we wouldn't.
Besides, you saw him earlier.
He's...he's planning
for a future with Cecile.
If we tell him about Savitar,
it's all he's gonna think about.
I-I can't do that to him.
I won't.
- Okay.
Whatever you want.
Now listen to me.
I promise you I'm doing
everything in my power
to make sure that
that future never happens.
- Okay.
- You think this is what it's
like to be a character on "CSI"?
- What do they hope to gain
from that examination?
- They're trying to find
the exact cause of death.
Once we know that,
we'll have a better idea
of what we're dealing with.
But until then,
we need to train.
I'm gonna teach you
everything I know,
starting with phasing.
- Yes! Finally.
- You know what we should do?
We should concoct
some simulations
to help Wallace learn
this new skill.
What do you say, Francisco?
- I got one word for you:
quebracho.
- Let's go.
- Quebracho!
- What's his name?
- Doesn't really matter
much now, does it?
- Of course, we should call him
by his name.
After everything
he's been through,
he deserves that much respect.
- He is a corpse,
thus impervious to such
bedside manners.
- Well, thank goodness,
'cause I'd hate to have
to subject him to yours.
- [sighs] Victim is male,
between 30 and 40,
with a highly necrotized
epidermis.
We plan to do a full-body scan
and a chest wall retraction.
- Julian, look.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- The decay continues even
after the tissue's dead.
This is...this is not a bacteria.
- Or any other disease
known to medical science.
- That was one crazy set, man.
I'm telling you, Rob, you keep
wailing on that saxophone,
you're gonna running up
to Lee Jay Thompson in no time.
All right, have a good one.
Catch you laters.
[chuckling]
[whispering] All right.
[sniffing]
- [slow clapping]
Whoo!
[laughs]
- Do I know you?
- Unlikely.
But I know you,
Julio Mendez.
Man, that was some set.
Your cover of "Dock of the Bay"
took me to a different time
and place.
- Well, I'm glad
you dug the set, man.
- Hey, before you go, uh,
I'd just really like
to shake your hand.
- Yeah, anything for a fan.
[crackling]
[gasps]
What'd you do to me?
- What you deserve for all
the pain you caused me.
♪ ♪
- Oh!
Oh, no!
Ouch!
- [moans]
That hurt like a...
- Like you ran into
a giant wooden wall?
'Cause you did.
- And it's not just any
big wooden wall.
That's double-reinforced
quebracho.
That's like the strongest stuff
on the planet, right there.
- Well, fantastic choice, Cisco.
- Well, it shouldn't matter
if it's wood or steel or stone.
If you're moving fast enough,
you can phase through anything.
- Even molten lava...you know, if
you ever ended up in a volcano.
- You know, I...
I still don't get it.
How do you do this?
- All right.
Here.
Watch.
When you vibrate at the
natural frequency of air,
your body, your cells,
will be in an excited state
that'll allow you...
to phase.
- Yeah, it's not...
it's not really helping.
What exactly do I do?
- Connect with your body, right?
Connect with the air.
Be pure electricity.
You have to feel everything
that's around you.
All right?
- So go fast and feel things.
Yeah, no worries.
- [laughing]
You can do this, Wallace.
[clapping]
- Okay.
All right, all right.
You can do this.
[thud]
Oh!
[groans]
- All right, again.
Yeah?
- You got this.
[whooshes]
[whistles]
- This isn't working.
- It's not working.
- You've been training him.
What's worked?
- You know what works
with that guy?
Vocal encouragement.
You got this, Wallace!
- I don't know why
you even ask him.
- What did Wells do with me?
- His plan was, uh, more
methodically constructed
than John Doe's in "Seven."
And he had a bit more time
to work it out
by, give or take, 15 years.
- Well, we don't have 15 years.
[phone buzzes]
I have a crime scene.
I got to go.
I'll be back.
Just make sure he
keeps practicing.
- Go, Wallace!
- Body was found
by that bicyclist.
Same M.O. as the first one.
This victim was performing here
last night.
He's a lounge singer
named Julio Mendez.
- Julio Mendez?
- Has anybody seen
Detective West?
- In Flashpoint,
he was Captain Mendez.
- Sorry. In Flashpoint, this...
this alternate universe
that you lived in,
he worked at the CCPD?
- Yeah.
Wait a second, the other...
the other vic, Stuart Holzman...
do we have a photo of him?
- Yeah.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah, hold on.
That's him.
What is it?
- He was a cop there, too.
- So this is the second
dead cop from Flashpoint?
- Yeah.
We got to figure out
who this guy is.
- Well, if we hurry,
there's still a chance
we can get some
of the attacker's
residual DNA before
this corpse disintegrates,
but we've got to move quick.
- Barry, you can help with that.
- All right, come on.
[whooshes]
Did anybody see me?
- Damn, I barely saw you.
Look, we got to get going.
- Hey, Joe, hold on.
Um, look, I-I know
how excited you are
for this coffee thing
with Joanie and Cecile,
but I think we
should hold off.
I don't think it's
a good idea right now.
- Bar, these two attacks
don't establish a pattern.
- Well...
- And besides, I'm a cop.
If I canceled my plans
every time I was in danger,
I'd never leave the house.
- I-I hear you.
I would just feel
a lot better
knowing you were someplace safe.
- Name a place safer
than a coffee shop
with my two speedster sons.
Meeting Joanie is important
to Cecile,
therefore it's important to me.
Some things are worth
taking risks for.
- All right, let's
get out of here.
- Julien:Anything?
- Aside from this body
disintegrating before our eyes?
Nothing unusual.
- There must be a heightened
point of necrosis somewhere.
Look!
We have less than 50 minutes
before this corpse disintegrates
into ash like the last one.
We need to find it now.
- I'm aware.
- This might be a faster process
if I did it alone.
- You know, I've done
autopsies before, Julian.
- I'm sure you have.
This might just be
a quicker process
if I did it alone.
What are you doing?
- The gradation is darker
on the palm of his hand
from the point of contact.
- I see, I see.
- You know, I used to think
Barry was overreacting
when he complained about
sharing a lab with you.
But now I understand
his frustration.
- Believe me, no one is
more frustrated than I.
- You do realize that it's
possible not to be a jerk
all the time, right?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
[device beeps]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Two strains of DNA.
- One of them must be
from our killer.
- But, you know,
there's something else here.
One of the DNA strains
has an element in it.
Have you ever seen anything
like that before?
- I have...
in all the meta husks
created by Alchemy.
♪ ♪
Which means the meta that killed
our two innocent people...
was created by me.
♪ ♪
- French roast for Cecile.
- Thank you.
- Non-dairy green tea latte
for Joanie.
You not much
of a coffee drinker, Joanie?
- Well, I used to be,
but then I learned
hot roasted coffee beans contain
cancer-causing levels
of acrylamide.
- Well, damn.
- Uh, Joanie, Cecile says
you're at Coast U?
What are you studying?
- I'm undecided.
- Are you leaning
towards anything?
- Not really.
- Uh, Coast U's
pretty far, right?
Do you ever miss Central City?
- Actually, I like it
better there.
Well, there is one thing I miss
about Central City.
- What's that?
- You're gonna regret
that you asked.
- Kid Flash.
- She's a little...
little obsessed.
- Kid Flash is the one thing
you miss about Central City?
- Whoa, Barry, slow down.
You don't have to be
so skeptical about it.
Kid Flash is cool.
What do you like best
about him, specifically?
- Well, he's fearless.
And he's brave.
- Yeah.
- He's a hero, and he's probably
pretty cute under that mask.
- Yeah, I think so, too.
- Come on, Joanie, honey,
Kid Flash?
He's a showboat...
he's snapping selfies,
he's leaving graffiti bolts
on buildings.
- Okay, that's his
signature move.
- That's kind of his signature.
- Yeah, well,
from what I hear,
The Flash is the one
who's actually saving people.
- Sounds like Cecile's
Team Flash.
- Uh, Joanie,
my dad would never
brag about this,
but he knows Kid Flash.
- You do?
Is my mom right?
Who's the real hero...
Flash or Kid Flash?
- Mmm...
they both are.
Uh, they both do great things
for Central City.
- Okay, but if you
had to choose?
- I-I don't...
I don't think I could choose.
- Yeah, but if you,
like, had to.
- Um, would you go get me
some cream, Wally, please?
[cell phone buzzing]
- Yes.
- Ah, this is work.
I'll be right back, sorry.
Hey, what's up?
- Barry, we got some DNA
off Mendez's corpse.
We were about to match it
with CCPD records.
- The meta's name
is Clive Yorkin.
We're sending you
his info now.
♪ ♪
- Detective Joe West!
Long time, no see.
♪ ♪
- Do I know you?
- You don't remember me?
You and your cronies had
a very fun time ruining my life.
Not gonna let you do that
this time around.
- I think you have
the wrong guy.
- No, no.
You're the Joe West
I remember.
Look a lot more full
of life now, though.
But don't worry...
I can change that.
[crumbling]
- Everybody get back.
- Joanie, go.
- Everybody get out of here.
Everybody go! Go!
[crowd clamoring]
- Yes, everybody run.
I only want him.
You can't hide up there,
Detective.
No one can hide
from me anymore.
- Joe...
- One more step, and I'll shoot.
- Didn't work then.
Won't work now, either.
[dramatic music]
Told ya.
- Stop!
- Ah, ah, ah.
Can't touch me, speedster.
[chuckling]
[air whooshing]
♪ ♪
- I knew it.
Kid Flash is the hero.
- Well, thank God
for Kid Flash, huh?
- He's gone.
[sighs heavily]
- This guy's got
the touch of death.
- Yeah, he does,
and it's not just people.
Anything he touched
turned to ash.
Joe, I...I really think
you should just stay here
until we find Yorkin.
- No, I'm gonna go check
on Cecile and Joanie.
They were pretty shook up.
- Dad, are you crazy?
This guy wants to kill you.
If it wasn't for Wally
and Barry, he could've.
He could've killed
any one of us.
- [stammers]
Come on, we have been through
much worse metas than Yorkin.
What?
- [exhales]
- Iris, I'm fine.
We're all fine.
We're not losing
anybody today.
- Maybe not today, but soon.
- Soon?
W-what are you saying?
- Iris...
- Wally, he needs to know.
- Needs to know what?
[somber music]
- When Barry threw
the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force,
there was an explosion,
and he was propelled
to the future.
- The future?
- It was a few months from now.
- What he saw was himself
standing before Savitar...
and me.
Right before Savitar killed me.
♪ ♪
- So you're saying
that in a few months...
you die?
♪ ♪
- Unless we can change
the future, Dad.
- Which we're gonna do,
Joe, okay?
I'm not...we're not
gonna let this happen.
- How long have you
known about this?
♪ ♪
[shouting]
How long?
- A couple weeks now, Joe.
- And you're just
telling me now?
That's my daughter!
- Dad, I didn't want them
to say anything
because I knew how
you would react.
- This is not something you
keep from your father, Iris!
You should've known that.
And you should've too.
- I know, Joe.
- Look, I can understand why
they didn't want to tell me
because they didn't grow up
under the same roof
that you did.
They don't know...they don't know
what my baby girl means to me,
Barry, but you do.
- I know.
Joe...
- [stammers]
♪ ♪
- I'll talk to him.
- I'm...I'm gonna go to CCPD,
see if I can find anything
that might lead us to Yorkin.
- Well, that went swimmingly.
- Joe's right. We should've
told him before now.
- What you should have told him
is that I'm the one responsible,
that the meta trying to kill him
is one that I created.
- Julian, you can't change
what happened to you.
It's not your fault.
- You keep saying that,
but it is my fault.
People are responsible
for their own actions.
To say otherwise is just...
it's just a way to make yourself
feel better.
- Is that what you think
I'm doing?
Making excuses for things
I've done in the past?
♪ ♪
[scoffs] You know, I'm really
starting to regret
bringing you in here.
♪ ♪
[relaxing ambient music]
- Come on, Dad.
Ah, hey, Dad, it's me...
calling, again.
Look, I know you're upset,
but, um, give me
a call back, okay?
I love you.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[loud clang]
[ominous music]
Honey?
♪ ♪
[phone beeping]
- Good evening, Iris West.
[alarm blaring]
- It's Iris's panic alarm.
- She's at the apartment.
I'll call Barry.
- No, no, no.
I-I got this.
Uh, he's at CCPD,
and I'm closer.
- Okay, go!
[whooshes]
- You know, initially,
I wanted your dad dead.
But then I thought, "If I really
want to make him suffer,
I should kill his
daughter instead."
- This is not how
I'm supposed to die.
[grunts]
- Oh, I'm pretty sure it is.
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
- No, stop!
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- Too late, Kid Flash.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- Me or her?
♪ ♪
- I've got you, baby girl.
I'm not going anywhere.
- Elevated heart rate.
Temperature's 104.
- The decay is reaching
her subcutaneous tissue.
- I'm here, all right?
What happened?
- Yorkin went after her.
- Why didn't you call me?
- Because I was here.
- You call me!
All right?
We have to give her something.
There has to be something
we can give her.
- It's not bacteria.
Antibiotics won't work.
- We have to do something.
Nothing's not an option.
- Okay, what do you do
when a banana ripens
too quickly?
Put it in the freezer.
- That's brilliant.
Caitlin, you can freeze
her arm.
It'll stop the spread of decay
and give us some time
to find a cure.
- I trust you.
- I can't, even if I wanted to.
We're not talking about
a cold blast.
This is a specific
and continuous cold stream.
- Too high a temperature
and the decay spreads,
too low and the frostbite
will destroy your nerve endings.
- And that long
using my powers,
I could lose control.
- Caitlin, you are strong, okay?
Stronger than you know.
You are not going
to lose control.
- Caitlin, try, please.
- [gasping]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- It worked.
- Oh, thank God.
- You okay?
- So far, so good.
- Wally, where are you going?
- Out of the way
where I can't screw up again.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Hey, look,
what I said back there...
- No, you were right.
We should've called you.
I just thought...
I thought I could do it.
I thought I was ready.
Obviously, I'm not.
- It's not on you.
- I wasn't fast enough, Barry.
That...that is totally on me.
- No, not really.
It's not, all right?
Look, when I got these powers,
I-I...
I was really lucky,
in a weird way.
You know, I had a lot of people
helping me through all of this.
I had Wells...both of 'em...
and Jay and Zolomon.
I mean, two of them turned out
to be bad guys,
but even they were
good teachers
who really taught me
how to use my powers.
I just don't think that I've
been that for you yet.
- You're telling me everything
that I need to learn.
I'm just not getting it.
I...
- No, that's not it.
It's...I've been...
I've been letting you coast by
on your raw talent,
which you have a lot of,
but teaching...it's a lot more
than just doing something
and expecting you to follow.
It's about inspiring
and empowering you
to use your gifts
to succeed on your own.
That's what I need to do.
That's what I'm gonna do
from now on.
So the next time you're
out there and you're alone,
you will win.
Deal?
- Deal.
♪ ♪
- H.R. and I just
came up with a way
to track down Yorkin,
and it's...
crazy.
Like, defies time
and space crazy.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Okay, here's what we know.
We know Yorkin's going after
cops in Flashpoint, right?
What we don't know is
who he's going after.
- But if we find out
who they are,
then we can be ready for him.
- Right, so how do we do that?
both: We vibe Flashpoint.
- Flashpoint doesn't
exist anymore.
- Stop you right there, BA.
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore
in this universe.
- But in quantum mechanics,
the daughter
universe theory
tell us...
- Universe theory.
- For every decision you make,
a universe exists
where you don't.
Yeah, I actually went
to that class.
- You better be going
to all your classes.
- So if there is a universe
where you stay in Flashpoint,
Francisco here could vibe it.
- And you're sure
you can do that?
- No, no.
Not at all.
But Gypsy did say I could do
some pretty incredible things
with my powers...
- Yeah, she did.
- Things I'm not even
aware of yet, so...
things I haven't even imagined.
- Well, let's get to imagining.
- All right.
- What do you need me to do?
- Oh!
- All I need you to do
is to stand there,
focus on Flashpoint, okay?
Focus on CCPD, Joe, Mendez,
that part of it,
and I'll take care of the rest.
[suspenseful music]
[cacophony of sound]
It worked!
I'm here.
Huh, for some reason
I thought Flashpoint
would look a lot different.
Okay, all right,
if I were Joe West,
where would I be?
- He was at the same desk.
- Got ya.
- If it wasn't
for this takedown,
we'd be having a different
conversation right now, Joe.
- Understood, Captain.
- Ooh, Joe's in trouble.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
for today's perp walk,
we have a literal degenerate:
the one and only Clive Yorkin.
- Here we go.
[applause]
- Captain Mendez,
Detective West,
thanks for the assist.
Couldn't have bagged this goon
without you.
- Get him to Iron Heights.
♪ ♪
- Stone...
[cacophony of sound]
- Who's Stone?
- Stone...that was the other cop.
And let me tell you,
she loves her perp walks.
- Laura Stone.
She's a PI.
- Yeah, that's her.
It was you, Mendez,
Holzman, and her.
You guys took down Yorkin
in Flashpoint.
- Well, then, that means
she's the only one
that Yorkin hasn't
gone after yet.
Classic example
of saving the best for last.
- I'm on it.
You guys stay here
and try to figure out
how to catch somebody
we can't touch.
♪ ♪
[indistinct P.A. announcements]
- Joe West.
Long time, no see.
- Hey.
I wish it were under
better circumstances.
Listen, you're being
targeted by a meta.
- Sweetheart, take
a look over there.
I'm the only one doing
the targeting here.
That chick's husband
is paying me
twice my going rate,
so scram.
- Look at this.
The guy that's coming
after you
can do that with one touch.
- Attention, all passengers.
The S.T.A.R. City Express
is now boarding all platforms.
- How about we multitask?
- All aboard, please.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Julian.
You have anything?
- Look, it's early days, but...
first tests show that her blood
is attacking the cells
in her body.
- Wait, that's the opposite
of how my blood
causes cells to regenerate.
- Precisely.
- Can we use my blood
to save her?
- Listen, I don't think
that your blood
is the key to saving Iris.
But I do think it might be
exactly what we need
to take down Yorkin.
All is not lost, mate.
[electronic beeping]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- The decay is spreading.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- [strained grunting]
- Caitlin?
♪ ♪
- Hey.
Caitlin?
- I'm losing control.
- Okay, all right,
it's spreading.
We need you.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
- Just a little bit longer,
and she's dead.
[distorted voice] How's that
for changing the future?
- I know who you are, Caitlin.
You do not want to do this.
- This who I am.
You said it.
It's time for me to take
responsibility for my actions.
Time for me to own
who I really am.
- Who you are
is Caitlin Snow.
I know firsthand the battle
going on inside of you.
I know what it feels like.
When it happened to me,
I lost.
All right?
I was weak, and I let it win.
And I did...
I did horrible things
to a lot of good people.
And you don't
have to do that.
You're not gonna do that.
You're stronger than I am,
Caitlin.
You're far stronger
than I am.
You're one of the strongest
people I've ever known.
You can win this fight.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Iris needs your help now.
- It's all right.
It's gonna be all right.
♪ ♪
[train whistle blows]
- And how do you know this guy's
coming after me, Joe?
- We have pretty reliable intel.
Look, Laura, this is not someone
you should be ignoring.
He's dangerous.
He's already killed two cops.
He tried to kill me
and my daughter.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[crumbling, cracking]
- Well, I've certainly pissed
off a lot of people in my day.
But the only thing I fear now is
forgetting to clear my browser.
Consider me warned.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
[electronic beeping]
[alarm blaring]
- What is that?
- It's Joe's panic alarm.
- He must be on that train.
- There's no way that train
can stop...
[whooshes]
♪ ♪
[train whistle blows]
- It's not gonna stop in time.
We have to get everyone
out of there.
- We don't have enough time.
- Oh, no!
- What is it?
- Everybody brace yourselves!
- What's happening?
- We're gonna move the train.
- How are we gonna do that?
- I'll vibrate it.
I'll vibrate it fast enough
that it can phase through this.
- You can do that?
- I don't know.
I've never tried before.
♪ ♪
Everybody hold on!
- Is that even possible?
- We're about to find out.
[train whistle blows]
[rapid warbling tone]
♪ ♪
- Holy Kardashians.
[warbling tone fades]
- [panting]
[applause]
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- All right!
- Barry.
Barry!
- We're good, man.
Took a lot out of me,
but it worked.
- Yeah, maybe,
but we got another problem.
Yorkin's back.
♪ ♪
- You know what they say,
Kid Flash.
If at first you don't succeed,
try, try again.
- You have to stop him.
I don't have it
in me right now.
I need you to get
your blood into him.
It'll counteract his cells
and negate his powers.
- How am I supposed to do that
when I can't even touch him?
- You're gonna phase it
into him.
- You know I've never
done that before.
- And you just watched me
do something I'd never done,
but I did it because I had to.
All right?
♪ ♪
I know you can do it, okay?
I need you to believe it, too.
♪ ♪
Now run, Wally.
Run.
♪ ♪
- It worked!
I did it!
- You sure did.
Good-bye, Kid Flash.
♪ ♪
- Oh, wha...look at that.
Your powers are neutralized,
Yorkin.
- What did you do?
- I won.
- Iris.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- [chuckles softly]
- [whispering] Dad?
- The last time I was this happy
looking in your eyes,
you'd just been born.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
It's okay.
You're okay.
Yorkin's done.
- What happened?
- I'll tell you what happened.
Wallace was a total badass.
That's what happened.
Translate.
- Yeah, he phased
his speedster blood
into Yorkin and neutralized
his powers.
- That's the science behind it.
- I had a great teacher.
- And me?
- Once Yorkin's blood
was stabilized,
we actually managed to get
an antidote that cured you.
- You'll have to wear
the bandage for a few days,
but other than that,
you're absolutely recovered.
- Thank you.
I know what you risked for me.
- I had some help.
- Couldn't have done it alone.
It was all of us
working together.
- Yup, really proud
of everybody.
Great job.
Big ideas today.
- My point is, if we're
gonna save Iris from Savitar,
we're gonna have to up our game.
No more lies...
even well-intentioned ones.
We have to be completely real
with each other.
- I agree.
- I agree with Joe, too.
- From here on out,
complete honesty.
♪ ♪
both: Honesty.
- All right, Get some
rest, all right?
I'll check on you in a bit.
♪ ♪
- Bar?
- Yeah?
- Savitar's prophecy
of someone dying...
was it Iris?
- Yeah.
But it's not gonna happen.
- Look, I'm glad she comes first
in your life now.
If you're gonna date
my daughter,
that's the way it should be.
- You're still a close second.
- [laughs]
- It's just heartwarming.
It's just truly heartwarming.
- You're already crafting
a version of this
for your book, aren't you?
- "Peace finally descends
upon the family West."
The West family,
or family West?
- Right, it's time
I get to work.
- At this hour?
- Yes, there's still one
husk meta out there,
and I intend to find him.
Good night.
- Hey, Julian?
- Hi.
♪ ♪
- I don't think you're weak
because of what happened
to you with Savitar.
The strength that I found
to stay in control...
that came from you.
So thank you.
♪ ♪
- Well, I wasn't gonna let Iris
die at the hands
of Killer Frost, was I?
- I knew there was a good guy
inside of you somewhere...
one that the rest of us would
like to see a little more often.
♪ ♪
- Good night.
[soft dramatic music]
- Do you want to get a drink?
- Uh...what?
As in now?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'd love that.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
What brings you to my neck
of the bullpen?
- Oh, Joanie's headed back
for midterms.
We just thought we'd come
and say good-bye.
- Aw.
I was hoping a redo
on the coffee,
seeing as how the last one
went off the rails.
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding me?
I got to see Kid Flash
in action, right up close.
- Well, we got a lot
of stories about Kid Flash
I can guarantee
you've never heard.
Maybe we can tell you them
over dinner
next time you come to town.
- I have a long weekend
next month.
- You sure you're ready
to commit to something
that far in the future?
- I am absolutely sure.
- Hmm?
Good.
We should go.
- Good luck at school.
- Thank you. See ya.
- Bye, babe.
- Bye.
[uplifting pop music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, good as new.
Actually, it's better than new
with the three extra locks
that I added.
- Which you didn't have to do.
- Well, Cisco did offer
to build us
a custom security door,
but we've both seen how well
those things keep people
out of S.T.A.R. Labs.
So...
- I like deadbolts.
Deadbolts work.
- Yeah.
It's just with...
what happened here,
I want to make sure
you feel safe.
- I do.
- About everything?
- You know, you've been
saying for weeks
that you were gonna save me
from Savitar.
- Mm-hmm.
- And while I trust you
with my life, it was
hard not to feel scared.
♪ ♪
You know, sometimes it feels
like The Flash is this guy
my boyfriend becomes when he
runs off to save other people.
Like I'm the only one
who doesn't get The Flash.
He felt separate from you.
But yesterday when you saved me,
I remembered that I have
no reason to be scared.
- Mm-mm.
- The man I love
is a superhero.
♪ ♪
I love and trust you,
Barry Allen...
The Flash.
♪ ♪
I love all of you,
and I always will.
♪ ♪
- I love you.
That was so nice.
♪ ♪
- [breathing deeply]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
Jesse!
- No, no, no, no.
- What's wrong?
- Grodd.
He's got my dad.
And he has him
in Gorilla City.
- Greg, move your head.