My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Iris' mom is alive.
And you thought you could pay me
to walk away from
my own daughter?
Last time, you walked
away for free.
When you created the Singularity
you also created a breach...
a portal connecting
our two earths.
You really think he's just
bringing these guys
here to kill me?
Zoom is obsessed
with destroying me.
Now he wants to destroy you.
I'm starting to perceive things...
horrible things.
We have to merge the inner
and outer event horizons
by separating the eye of it.
No!
Ronnie died saving me,
and I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, get Come here.
Professor Stein,
can you hear me?
2 YEARS AGO
Everyone secretly thinks
they've figured out what
their life is gonna be like,
but what no one ever
considers is that life has
its own plans for you, whether
you like them or not.
And so you're left
with a choice.
You can either embrace the
change and move forward,
or fight it, and be left behind.
Dude! I knew you could do it.
That was some touchdown, man.
You won us the game!
Hey, no, man. We
won us the game.
Hey, that's not what the
cheerleaders were saying.
Oh, yeah? For real? A'ight.
Jefferson, great game.
Hey, thanks, coach.
I'm not the only
one that noticed.
Lot of scouts in the
stands tonight,
and after that touchdown,
they all pulled out
their cell phones.
You're gonna get your
pick of colleges, son.
You really think so?
I know so.
You get home and
celebrate with your mom.
Everybody, run!
Hey, hey, come on,
man, I got you!
We gotta get inside the tunnel!
Hold him steady!
He's dropping out.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- PRESENT DAY
- Cisco, we're losing him!
Got it!
Thank God.
He's getting worse.
Look, I did what I
could to re-engineer
Doctor Wells's
original stabilizer
to quell the reaction,
but I don't know
what he used as a power source.
Best I could find was the
one from his wheelchair.
And how long will that last?
Well, that's the problem,
is we had already used up
most of its energy trying
to dampen the metas' powers
during our little rogue air trip
with Weather Wizard and company.
I think we got a few days tops.
And he's stuck in bed?
Yeah, when he wakes up,
I'm gonna transfer the
stabilizer to this,
give him a power cane,
get him moving.
We gotta figure out
a way to save him.
I think I might know
how to do that.
When the Particle
Accelerator exploded,
the dark matter that collided
with Professor Stein
fused with the Firestorm
matrix and altered
the normal molecular processes
that occurs within his body.
Those highly reactive
molecules needed
something to bond with
in order to stabilize.
And that's where Ronnie came in.
Yes, and now that
Ronnie is no longer
a part of Professor Stein...
Those molecules don't
have anything to bond to.
And the longer he
goes without merging,
the more unstable he becomes.
All right, so, what do we do?
We find another... participant.
Okay, cool, so, how
do we do that?
Are we just gonna
make a Tinder app
for potential meta-humans?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
merging with Stein
and randomly
bursting into flames
sounds like the biggest
"swipe left" of all time.
I mean, even if we could
find someone willing,
Stein can't just merge
with whoever he wants.
No he can't, but I have
done some research,
and found two
potential candidates
that might be
compatible with him.
They both were affected
by the dark matter,
and they were both
admitted to the hospital
showing symptoms of gene
rearrangement mutation.
And they both share
the same blood type
as Professor Stein and Ronnie.
All right.
I mean, this is more
than organ donation.
We'll need more
than tissue typing
to see if their bodies
are compatible.
If I can isolate
the genetic locus
of the two candidates
and cross-reference it
with the mutations
in Professor Stein,
I might be able to find a
match and save his life.
What do you need to do that?
All right, blood samples from
both potential candidates.
Damn, that was
fast even for you.
I may have skipped the
asking for permission part.
Let's see if we
can't find a match.
You were two in that picture.
You'd just got some shots. You
were so mad at the nurse.
You kept saying,
"She pinched me."
So we took you to the park
afterwards to cheer you up,
gave you your first
ice cream cone,
which was a mistake, because all
we heard the next month was,
"Mint-choplat chip,
mint-choplat chip."
That's where the
obsession started.
Babe, you don't have to do this.
If you don't want to meet your
mother tomorrow, I get it.
No, it's okay. I
want to meet her.
I need to meet her.
It's gonna be fine.
My brave baby girl.
Take after you.
Love you.
Love you more.
Barry?
Hey, I was just looking for you.
I would've called, but I don't
have your number yet, so.
Oh, yeah...
No, no, no, I just
wanted to show you this.
These were just found
in an alley off of
Eastwood Avenue.
What are these, teeth?
Shark teeth.
And I have an
eyewitness that says
he saw a shark walking on land...
a man-shark.
- Man-shark?
- Yeah.
Sounds like a bad sci-fi movie.
Or awesome sci-fi movie.
Totally.
Are you for real? You
think there's actually,
like, a shark...
Yeah, I mean, I know it
sounds really wacko...
But, I mean,
nothing seems
impossible now that
we have meta-humans, right?
And I thought it would
be fun, you know,
for us to work together
again on a case.
Yeah, I mean, I really...
I'd love to work on
anything with you.
Um, it's just, you know,
meta-humans aren't
really my thing.
Oh, okay, yeah, that's fine.
I can handle it.
No, you... look, how
about I just...
I'll run a test, see where
the teeth came from.
That would be amazing.
- All right, cool.
- Thanks.
Yeah, sure.
Detective Spivot.
Detective.
How's your man-shark
case coming?
It's good. I was just gonna go
and canvas the area, see
what else I can dig up,
and Barry here agreed to
run some tests for me.
Really?
So, progress. Thanks again.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were flirting
with my partner.
What, Patty? No, I'm...
What are you talking about?
I'm not...
What is it with you and
Iris and my partners?
Hey, how is Iris, by the way?
Eh, she's pretty nervous
about seeing her mother
after all these years.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what, I gotta go.
It's Cisco. It's about
Professor Stein.
Okay, go. I'll cover
you with Singh.
All right, thanks.
Well, I must admit,
I never imagined
the Sphinx's riddle about a
man requiring three legs
would ever apply to me,
but if this device
keeps me mobile,
then I will gratefully oblige.
Hopefully, you won't
need it for much longer.
There was no agglutination
in the blood samples,
and cross-matching was
negative for both,
and it appears that
the dark matter
from the Particle
Accelerator explosion
mutated their genes
in a very similar way
it did to yours.
I think they're both
potential matches.
So who do we go with?
Well, my first choice
is Henry Hewitt.
He graduated summa cum laude
from Hudson University
with a double major
in Applied Physics
and Bioengineering.
A Hudson boy, I
like him already.
Now, what about this other
guy Jefferson Jackson?
High school quarterback,
4.0 student.
He's got the
physical attributes.
And it looks like more of his
alleles match than Hewitt's.
Doesn't that mean that
he's more compatible?
On paper, perhaps, but
Hewitt is a scientist.
Clearly, he's trying to
make something of his life.
I think he'd be open to
something like this.
I think we should meet
with both of them
before we make a decision.
That's an excellent idea.
I'll see if I can
get Hewitt here.
All right, in the meantime,
we'll go meet with
Jefferson Jackson.
And I will try to
find something else
to help keep you stable.
Are you sure this
is the right place?
Yeah. Jefferson's a mechanic.
Could indicate a strong
technical aptitude.
That's a positive.
Oh, prone to allergies.
That's definitely a negative,
not to mention his
taste in music.
Would you prefer
Celine Dion instead?
I got the "Titanic"
soundtrack in the back there.
No, thank you.
Jefferson Jackson, right?
People call me Jax.
Catchy.
My name's Barry Allen, and
this is Martin Stein.
We're with the
Department of Safety.
It's a small, newly
formed agency.
Very new, we probably don't
even have a website yet, do we?
You need to see our licenses?
I mean, we're all
up to code here.
No, no, nothing like that.
We are compiling data on
people who were affected
by the Particle Accelerator
explosion two years ago.
Look, man, I lost
enough time in my life
'cause of that stupid
thing going wrong.
Now, you don't got a car I
can fix, I can't help you.
If you would consider coming
back to S.T.A.R. Labs with us,
I believe we can help you.
Help me how?
Well, we know what the
Particle Accelerator did...
Look, I already told you, I
don't talk about that night.
Why is that?
Because that's when
everything changed.
I got hit hard.
When I woke up, I was
in the hospital.
Busted up leg, torn ACL.
The look on my mom's face,
I knew any dreams I had
of playing pro ball were over.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, well...
look, I gotta get back to work.
Yeah...
Here, it's just...
it's our number.
Just think about it, okay?
Thank you for putting
this together, Joseph.
Iris's idea, not mine.
Hey, baby.
Hi, Dad.
Iris... this is Francine.
Hello.
Hi. Hello, Iris.
Can I get you a
coffee or something?
Um, no, thanks.
Let's just sit.
I can't get over what a
beautiful young woman
you've become.
And a journalist? I'm
so proud of you.
Why are you here?
Why now, after two decades?
I want to make this
right with you.
How about you start
by apologizing
for walking out on us?
I am sorry, so very, very sorry.
There's so much you don't know.
I'm sure that you've been
through a great deal,
and I can appreciate you
feeling like this is
suddenly the right time for
you to want me in your life,
but that doesn't mean that
it's the right time for me.
Iris...
No, Dad, it's okay.
I've thought about this a lot,
and it wasn't fair for me
to make you the bad guy.
So I want you to
hear this from me.
I don't hate you, Francine.
I do wish you well,
but we have lived separate
lives for over 20 years.
Let's keep it that way.
I've always thought
my destiny was for
greater things.
And people, of course.
Well, when it's all
said and done,
flying will be the
least impressive
of your new abilities.
Man finally achieves the
promise of the Atomic Age.
Caitlin, what's going on?
Hi, I'm glad you're back. This is Dr.
Henry Hewitt.
This is Barry Allen and
Professor Martin Stein.
How do you do?
The illustrious Martin Stein.
I've read all your
papers back at Hudson,
especially on transmutation.
Fascinating.
- You're a legend.
- Oh, please.
I think you're overestimating
my contribution to the field.
- I... I appreciate your enthusiasm.
- Isn't he great?
He's got an ego the
size of Texas,
but, yeah, he's all right.
So, where's Jefferson Jackson?
We just need more time.
We don't have more time.
I couldn't find
another power source
for the cane and that
thing's running out.
Okay, then let's do the merge.
Hewitt's in.
What do you mean? You
told him the details
of the Firestorm Matrix?
Absolutely, becoming Firestorm
is a huge life change.
He needs to know what he's
getting himself into.
If I remember correctly, vector,
variance, hypotenuse...
- Protonneutron, go H.U.!
- Yes!
Look at that, that's so cute.
We'll have two Professor
Steins if this works.
It's gonna work.
Yeah.
Okay.
When I put this
splicer on your chest
you're gonna feel a rush.
That's a molecular primer being
released into your body.
Then you can make
physical contact
with Professor Stein, and...
Firestorm Matrix will take over.
Easy enough.
Ready?
No time like the present.
Thank you, my dear.
Okay.
Try again.
This is unexpected.
Something's supposed to
be happening, right?
Why isn't it working?
I don't know.
Well,
looks like you two aren't
compatible after all.
I'm just gonna...
So all this was for nothing?
Believe me, no one is more
disappointed than I am.
Yeah, don't be so
sure about that.
Next time, try to get
your act together
before you get
someone's hopes up.
Move the show-and-tell
to next Tuesday,
remind me to call
Richard tomorrow
about the shareholders
meeting, and where are we
with the replacement
for Doctor Snow?
Applied sciences.
Stop!
Don't move!
Harrison?
Detective West, Thank
you for coming.
Doctor McGee, this
is my new partner,
Detective Spivot.
It's nice to meet you.
I was saddened by Detective
Thawne's passing.
Please extend my condolences
to your daughter.
Thank you. On the phone
you mentioned this was
a sensitive matter.
It is, and I called you directly
because I've always appreciated
your discretion in the past.
Of course, can you tell
me what was stolen?
It's not so much what was
stolen, but who stole it.
The person who broke into
my facility last night
was Harrison Wells.
Harrison Wells is dead.
I seem to recall
the circumstances
around his passing were
a bit inconclusive.
Is there any possibility
he could be alive?
Zero possibility.
I knew the man for
over 20 years.
I know who I saw.
The only thing distinctively
different was...
he's walking again.
Like I said, I trust
your discretion.
You have full access
to the facility.
Thank you again, Detective.
First a shark-man, now
a dead man walking.
We need to call Barry,
get him in here first.
Barry can't hear
about any of this.
What... why?
Because he's got a
lot on his plate.
He's got a friend who's
sick who he needs his help,
and Harrison Wells is the man
who murdered his mother.
Once he hears that...
Is he okay?
He's fine, but...
not a word to him
or anyone, okay?
Okay.
Yeah, it's just, I'm not
really good at lying.
Well, you better learn, quick.
Yeah, definitely.
CENTRAL CITY POLICE
Spivot, go on ahead.
Sure.
This is the last time
you ever show up here.
Do you understand?
I needed to talk to you again.
How much clearer
do we need to be?
Iris and I do not want
you in our lives.
Leave, please.
Go home, live your life.
Joe, there's something else.
I wanted to tell you when
I first saw you, but...
What is it?
Few months ago, I
started getting weak.
The doctors ran a
bunch of tests,
they couldn't figure it out.
But finally, they did.
Said I have something
called MacGregor's.
Supposedly it's pretty
common among ex-addicts.
Told me I had till the end
of the year if I'm lucky.
Is... is that why you came back?
I just want my
daughter to know me...
this me.
I'm really glad you
decided to come.
I thought S.T.A.R.
Labs had to shut down.
It's under new management.
What kind of treadmill is that?
Cosmic.
Cool.
So, let's get started.
You got some kind of "Billion
Dollar Man" technology
that gonna fix my knee?
Actually, Jax, this isn't
about fixing your knee.
What are you talking about?
When the Particle
Accelerator exploded,
the energy wave that
collided with you
is known as "dark matter."
And it didn't just
hurt your knee.
It... it changed the molecular
structure of your body.
Hold on, Grey.
So you're saying I'm like
one of those meta-humans
I keep hearing
about on the news?
Yes, I am. Please,
call me Professor.
We think you have
potential capabilities.
What kind of capabilities?
The same as Professor Stein:
the ability for your body to
process fission and fusion.
And you can harness
excess energy
and turn it into these
massive nuclear blasts.
And you can fly.
There's also that.
So you're saying you
can do all this?
Only during times of convergence
with a willing partner.
Convergence? You and me?
Yes.
No, this is crazy.
No, Jax, this is your chance
to right the wrong
that was done to you.
Yeah, sorry, you
got the wrong guy.
I don't want nothing
to do with this.
Wait a second, we are
giving you the chance
to be a superhero,
and you're gonna say
no that quickly?
Yeah, not my kind of thing.
If the man isn't willing
to participate...
Look, I saw your
test scores, Jax.
Your grades were good
enough to get into college,
but you didn't go. Why?
Is this the type of guy you are?
One setback and you fold?
Well, then maybe
you're not the guy
for us anyway.
Well, maybe I'm not.
Jack...
Maybe this just
wasn't meant to be.
Cait, come on, I mean,
Jax could be our last chance
at saving Professor Stein.
He said no to being a superhero.
Who does that?
I mean, you didn't say no
when you had the chance.
Cisco, would you?
Chance to have superpowers?
Sign me up.
Look, we're asking Jax to
change his entire life,
to sacrifice what he does have.
I mean, that's not a decision
that can be made lightly.
It took me a long time
to figure out this
whole hero thing.
Exactly, which is why we need
someone who wants to do this.
Where are you going?
To get Hewitt back.
We have to try again.
Human DNA?
Yup, definitely not a man-shark.
Not even a land shark, Ma'am.
Well, thanks for
testing it for me.
Yeah. What are you gonna do now?
I don't know, probably file it
under "never gonna happen."
I have another case anyway.
Oh, anything I can
help you with?
No, no, no, no, Detective
said definitely n-not.
Is everything all good?
Sure, why?
I don't know,
you're just acting
kind of different.
No! No.
I'm the same old P.
Spivot, you know?
What... actually, I have to
go, but thank you so much
for testing this,
and I'll see you.
Okay, I...
Yo, Joe.
Hey.
You good? Everything all right?
Yeah. No, I'm...
just had hell of a day.
Yeah?
Iris's mother,
she told me she was dying.
Yeah, and I know Francine.
She's telling the
truth about this.
Okay.
Does Iris know?
Not yet.
Did... did you need something?
No, no. I just...
Patty said you that you
don't want me on some case
that she's on with you.
No.
I was checking out a lead.
I'll let you know.
All right, cool.
What is up with you and
my partner, anyway?
Come on, I...
Bar, you can't take your
eyes off that girl.
I don't know what you
want me to tell you.
I mean, she's great, you know.
She's adorable and funny
and we have a lot
in common, but...
"But, um."
I don't know. She's
not Iris, I guess.
Right.
You've known Iris
since you were ten.
You've been in love
with her since forever.
I mean, you two are friends now,
but she was your first love.
You're never gonna feel the
same about anybody else,
but you can't let that stop you
from exploring something new.
Yeah.
And in happier news,
remember Flash Day,
the downtown
celebration to honor
Central City's one
and only superhero?
Well, just weeks...
Hewitt, you have those
nucleosome results?
Tomorrow.
I told you I needed
them tonight.
And I'm telling you you'll
have them tomorrow.
You know, I know you think
you're smarter than
everyone here, Hewitt,
but I'm sick of your
not doing your job,
your not showing up.
If I have any more trouble
from you, you're done here.
What, you're gonna
take the test away
and give it to another
lab rat of yours?
You're gonna report
me to the board?
Or maybe you're
thinking of firing me?
I'd like to see you try!
Now get the hell out of my lab!
What's being described as
a "spontaneous
energy malfunction"
erupted last night at
Eikmeier Technologies.
Wanted for questioning is
scientist Henry Hewitt.
Hewitt's dormant abilities
must have been triggered
when we attempted the merger.
This could be catastrophic.
If his powers are
anything like mine
he requires a grounding
mechanism to
stabilize his volatility.
Otherwise...
Yeah, he's gonna pop his top,
and he's got a long
history of violence,
according to his police record.
Police record?
I didn't find a police record.
Yeah, of course
not, it was sealed,
but guess what, ya
boy hacked in and...
hold on, wait for it.
One count battery, two
counts aggravated assault,
court-ordered anger
management therapy.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
He even knew your
Hudson nerd song.
You okay?
It appears Mr.
Hewitt's stability
isn't the only one in question.
I think I need to lie down.
Yeah, I'll come with you.
Thank you.
Professor Stein
is getting worse.
And Hewitt's like
this because of me.
And now Jefferson Jackson
will never come back
because of what I said.
I just didn't believe that
he has what it takes.
This isn't because you
didn't believe in him.
Sometimes, great possibilities
are right in front of us,
and we don't see them,
because we choose not to.
I think that we need to be open
to exploring something new.
She's dying?
A few months left.
I just don't think I
can see her, Dad.
And that's fine.
But you and me need to be
crystal clear about this, Iris.
If you want to have a
relationship with Francine,
it's okay with me. You
don't have to protect me.
I'm a grown man and I've
dealt with these feelings
a long time ago.
So you... you just believe her?
She's done some bad
things in her life,
but she wouldn't lie about this.
Dad, she shows up
out of nowhere,
and only says that she's dying
after I told her to stay away.
Look, she didn't come to
Central City to see me.
She came because of you.
I just wanted you
to know everything
so you can make the best
decision for yourself.
I mean, she is
still your mother.
Either way, whatever you decide,
just know, I got your back.
I know.
Let me guess,
you don't got car troubles.
I came to apologize. I'm
sorry for what I said.
It's fine. Apology accepted.
Look, we could
really use your help
to save Professor Stein.
That desperate?
Yes.
My husband, Ronnie,
he used to be Professor
Stein's other half.
He actually helped build
the Particle Accelerator,
and when it exploded, he
was affected by it too.
Ironically, that's how
he got the chance
to show the world what
he was truly capable of.
And he died saving this city.
Wait, he was the guy that
flew into the black hole?
That was him?
He was a hero.
You can be one too.
I never wanted to be a hero.
What I wanted was
to go to college,
but we couldn't afford it.
Football was my way in, until
that got taken from me.
I know. Look, I know
the Particle Accelerator
took something from you.
but it also gave you
something in return,
something even more spectacular,
the opportunity to be
part of something bigger,
to be part of a team that's
working to protect people
from losing what you lost.
I believe you were
meant to be a hero.
Hold on.
I've been looking for you, Dr.
Snow.
Hey, look, man, we're...
You did this to me!
But it's not what you
promised, is it?
Is it?
Come on!
Where to?
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Caitlin.
- What's wrong?
- Come here.
Oh, good, you're here.
This thing, it ran out,
like, 30 minutes ago.
His temperature is 142
degrees and rising fast.
He's going into rapid oxidation.
We need to find a coolant.
I think it's too late for that.
I'll do it.
I'll merge with him.
You said this is a
chance for me to be
a part of something
bigger than myself,
to help people.
That's what I want.
You're sure?
Once you merge, there's
no going back on this.
And you said I could fly, right?
- Damn right.
- Okay.
So what do I do?
Okay, well, here's the
abridged version.
Professor Stein?
- Professor Stein?
- Clarissa, five more minutes.
No, Professor, you
have to get up.
Jax is here.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Jax is here.
- Here, grab onto me.
- Jax?
Yeah.
This is it.
You came back,
Jefferson, thank you.
Well, like my coach always said,
"Out of yourself and
into the team."
So, how's this work?
Okay, all you're gonna
do is touch him.
And then what happens?
You become Firestorm.
Okay.
Jax?
Is Professor Stein...
How will I know?
Hello, Jefferson.
Now you know.
Oh, so I get Grey as my copilot.
Did no one ever inform you
of that fringe benefit?
So when do we get to take
this for a test spin?
How about now?
It looks like
Hewitt's re-charging
at Central City High
School's football stadium.
Wait, that was where I got hurt.
Cisco, cut the
power to the field
so he can't draw anymore energy.
I'm on it. Stand by.
Hewitt! You need to stop!
This is not who you are!
Stein? You chose him over me?
That's who I'm supposed to be!
I deserve the Firestorm Matrix!
Move, now!
Calm down, Jefferson, focus.
Use your natural athleticism
to gain control.
Hey, you okay?
I was a quarterback. I
know how to take a hit.
Hey, guys, cutting the
power didn't work.
It's like the more we anger
him, the stronger he gets.
That's it, it's like
one of those...
controlled fusion devices.
Tokamak?
Yes, exactly,
and the more powerful
they become,
the more unstable they become.
Barry, make him angry,
and he'll blow his fuse.
You up for a little game
of "catch me if you can?"
Let's go for it.
Okay.
Hey, Hewitt, over here!
Paging Dr. Hewitt.
Man, you are not good at this.
Do you need a hug, Doctor?
Come on, Hewitt, give
me your best shot!
Now.
Is that all you got, Hewitt?
Man, no wonder you
didn't make the cut
if that's how you fight.
Not bad for your
first go at this.
Well, I had a great coach
to help me through it.
Isn't that right, Grey?
Despite my initial reservations,
we make a pretty fantastic team.
Welcome aboard, Firestorm.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
You have no idea what
this means to me.
My dad told me you were sick.
You know, I wasn't sure
that I could believe you,
so I did some checking.
Turns out you're
telling the truth.
I would never lie to you
about something so big.
Really?
'Cause I was actually thinking
that I could give you
another chance after
hearing that news.
But you're still lying,
still keeping secrets.
I'm an investigative
reporter, Francine.
I uncover things that
people want to keep hidden,
like having a son.
Iris...
He was born eight months
after you left Central City.
Let me explain.
Who's the father, Francine?
Is it my dad?
Do I have a brother?
Wait, you know, I don't even want...
I don't want to know.
I mean, I wouldn't
be able to tell
if you were telling the
truth or if it was
another one of
your lies, anyway.
I want you to leave.
You stay away from me, and you
stay away from my father.
If he finds out that he might
have a son that grew up
without even knowing
him, it would crush him.
Just...
Leave us alone.
Iris, I was...
And how is Mr. Hewitt?
Seems like that last burst
of energy has burnt him out.
Our Tokamak's gone dark.
Yeah, we're just
gonna keep him...
safe and sound in the pipeline
till he decides to keep
quiet about all this.
So you're gonna meet
up with Clarissa?
We're meeting in
Pittsburgh in three days.
Why Pittsburgh?
A colleague of mine
was monumental
in helping train Ronald and me.
She's graciously offered to
help the two of us as well.
How's she gonna help us?
Well, there were many
aspects of our abilities
that we never quite achieved.
Hopefully now, we can fully
realize that potential.
Oh, my dearest Dr. Snow.
Ronald may be lost to us, but
he will never be forgotten.
Speaking of...
this was Ronnie's.
He always used it to
find his way back home.
I want you to have it.
Thank you.
You know, this whole
thing is strange,
being 50% of someone.
Yeah, but you're 100% a hero.
I went ahead and
recalibrated the splicer
so the merging should
be even smoother now.
Thank you.
If I may offer a bit
of parting advice.
Cisco, I know you're scared,
but this ability you have
is a gift, not a curse.
It's natural to be apprehensive
about the unknown,
but look at Jefferson.
He took a leap, and it changed
his life for the better.
The very thing that
makes you different
is what makes you special.
Tell your friends.
And now I believe it's time to
take this show on the road...
or to the sky, if I
am to be literal.
Are you ready, Jefferson?
All right.
- See you later.
- Yeah.
That was one hell
of a leap of faith
that kid took, merging
with Professor Stein.
Yeah, it was.
There's a lesson in there
somewhere for you.
Things aren't always
what they seem.
Our fears can play tricks on us,
making us afraid
to change course,
afraid to move on,
but usually, hidden
behind our fears
are second chances
waiting to be seized...
PROJECT: FIRESTORM
Second chances at life...
At glory...
At family...
At love.
And these opportunities don't
come around every day,
so when they do, we
have to be brave,
take a chance, and grab
them while we can.
Zoom wants you dead.
Oh, my God, it's real.
Hey! Put him down!
Put your hands...
your fins in the air!
Who the hell are you?