Freedom comes at a price.
- So I'm down a point.
- [Ashley] Nine and a half.
- [Stormfront] Bad day?
- Goddamn it.
Hey, I'm with you.
But there's a way to handle it.
I owe you.
Thanks to the Church of the Collective,
I now know the kind of man I want to be.
Hashtag "Brave-Maeve!"
[Maeve] This is Homelander.
He's fucking with me.
I can't protect you if you leave.
What are we gonna do?
You think by saving Kimiko
you can make amends
for those children
that Lamplighter burned.
Fuck you.
- You can't go through this on your own.
- We're all alone.
How do you think the world will feel
when I tell them
that you used to be Liberty?
Wow.
[French hip-hop playing over speakers]
[Jay & Cherie laughing]
Why are you laughing?
- You're ridiculous.
- Oh, no. I am not ridiculous.
Okay, then you are high.
Well, beside the point.
- Point is,
- Mm-hm.
I learned everything I know
from those girls.
The Golden Girls.
I was alone in New York, you know?
Turning tricks, begging for the scraps.
Who do you think kept me company?
The Golden Girls. 3 a.m. to 5 a.m.
They lit up that shelter's shitty TV.
And you're not talking about porn?
The Golden Shower Girls?
That's disrespectful.
Aw, he's so sensitive.
No. Those saucy ladies,
they made their own family.
So I did what they did.
You are my Blanche.
- Blanche?
- And Jay.
You are...
my Dorothy.
I guess you're a little gay. Yeah.
So you're Betty White?
Oh, what a fucking question.
Of course I'm Betty White.
Now...
[keypad beeping]
Who wants to rob a bank?
Fuck yeah.
Will it get through my skin?
If it can't, nothing can.
Okay, I feel like I need to say something.
I don't think this is a good idea.
Stormfront knows I leaked the V.
Yeah, but she hasn't come after you.
But that makes it so much worse.
That means that she has
some fucked-up plan for me.
I need this chip out now.
I understand, Petit Hughie.
And though you've been covered
with entrails of many a person,
even a sea mammal, it's always harder
when it's someone you love.
- What?
- L'amour.
No, no. No, I don't.
I mean, I do, of course.
It's just... It's a platon...
We're just friends.
Okay. Can we just do this already
before I change my mind? Please?
Okay, this is happening.
- Okay.
- Mm-hm.
- This might sting a little.
- Okay.
[saw whirring]
- [Annie shouts]
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Okay.
Okay.
[Annie groaning]
Bonjour, my little spy.
[sirens wailing in distance]
Howdy ho, buckaroo.
[bones crack, then man shouts]
Shit! I think you broke my hand.
What do you want to do with him?
Hand him over
to the police, of course.
Well, of course. We are heroes.
That's what heroes do.
Absolutely.
But he'll probably just be released
tomorrow.
- Please, just take me to the hospital.
- Yeah.
- Please.
- That's a really good point.
You know, sometimes it feels like...
Like the justice system
just doesn't work anymore.
Everyone always recording
on their phone all the time.
Mm-hm.
It's like you can't even
do your job anymore.
Please just take me in.
Just take me in, please.
["Happy Together" playing]
It really speaks to the deterioration
of good God-fearing American values.
- [bones cracking]
- Help me!
Oh, what's this world coming to?
Fuck.
♪ Imagine how the world could be
So very fine ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ - I can't see me loving nobody but you ♪
- [both moaning]
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ When you're with me, baby ♪
♪ The skies will be blue for all my life ♪
- [Homelander] Don't be shy, embrace it.
- [Stormfront] I'm saying thank you.
Okay. Let's be honest for a moment here,
who is the biggest prankster on set?
Oh, I just, I don't think
we should get into that.
I don't know. No comment.
I mean, he is right.
But you know, Black Noir
has definitely got just the biggest ego.
[Homelander] Such a diva...
- They're fucking.
- [Stormfront] under that helmet.
[footsteps approaching]
- Did you get her chip out?
- This is where you're living?
Yeah, you know, it has its charms.
The rats are, like, Pokémon.
- With Hep-C.
- Oh, God.
Oh, so you're back?
Tired of killing people for money?
Uh...
Hi.
Remember me?
Well, well, well.
What have we here?
I know what you're gonna say, but we
took out her chip. Everything's fine.
Starlight,
don't you just light up a room, eh?
You're looking well.
Yeah, no thanks to the 50-calibre round
that you pumped into my chest.
Well, what don't kill you
makes you stronger.
Hmm.
What's she doing here?
Uh, she has a lead on Stormfront.
I broke into her laptop,
and I got a look at the inbox.
Dozens of e-mails from Stan Edgar.
Stan Edgar?
And what does Vought's Big Slapper
have to say?
How they're close to a breakthrough
at the Sage Grove Centre.
It's a psychiatric hospital
in Pennsylvania.
- [Hughie] Wait, what kind of breakthrough?
- She came in before I could see any more.
Well, we better have us a little dekko
at this looney bin, eh, lads?
Starlight, would you be amenable
to joining us on this little caper?
You want her to come?
Oh, most definitely.
If shit goes sideways,
who do you think Vought's gonna go after?
Us or their
billion-dollar-baby-turned-traitor
who just ripped out her own fucking chip?
Never go into shark-infested waters
without chum.
♪ Give a little bit of love... ♪
[Maeve] This is who I am. Who are you?
Brave Maeve Pride Bars.
Because you can't be proud
on an empty stomach.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
You fucking idiot.
You were supposed to call first.
- Did anyone see you?
- I'm allowed to visit my friends.
- Did you find it?
- No, sorry. No black box.
But I told a couple of my contacts
to keep an eye
on the North Atlantic Current.
So this school of Halibut,
these are rowdy motherfuckers.
- Deep.
- [clearing throat]
Anyway, they found some of the wreckage
that drifted up near Iceland.
And they found this.
I mean, I'm not sure
it still even works, but...
You want back in The Seven?
Not a fucking word of this to anyone.
♪ Here Comes the A-Train
Mr. Fleet feet ♪
♪ Saving lives, takin' names
Nice and easy ♪
♪ There ain't no day
Like a race day, what ♪
♪ Ain't no love like a raceway, what ♪
♪ I'm the best to ever do it, y'all crazy
Make way or you're pushin' up daisies ♪
♪ Bring the heat
Now they're begging for some a.c. ♪
Isn't it lit? Your very own anthem?
Yeah, it's dope.
Well, this is just the demo, of course.
We're going out to Lil Nas X
for the official version.
Maybe you could bust out
Prince's guitar for the video?
I had to sell Prince's guitar.
- I'm going 10-1.
- Okay.
- Ashley.
- What?
- I can't find her.
- Where the fuck is Starlight?
[director] Back to one, everyone.
We're going again.
Yo! Here comes the A-Train!
What, what?
I'm right here, buddy. Over here.
- Yeah.
- What's up, buddy?
Good to see you.
- What are you doing here, man?
- Oh, not much. Just here to see, uh...
No reason, really.
But, hey, bro, I've been thinking
about you lately.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I see what they're trying to do to you.
Yeah. Talk about getting ass-fucked
with a soup can. Am I right?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, come on.
If anyone knows
what it's like to get bounced, it's me.
Yeah. Did some shit I'm not too proud of.
Some weird shit.
I'm good, man.
Nike and Under Armour
are already talking to my people,
so, you know, this is actually gonna
work out to be really fantastic for me.
- Oh, that's great. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Well, then I guess
you don't need his help.
Or... Never mind.
Forget I even said anything.
But hey, it's great
to see you, man. Always.
All right.
Whose?
Whose help?
Would you like a Fresca?
[Milk] Sage Grove, a proud
subsidiary of Global Wellness Services,
- which is a subsidiary of...
- I can guess.
Thanks.
This is what you bought
with your blood money?
No one will believe
you're an orderly with that, you know.
[Annie] I should go in with them.
They can manage
without one bony blond Supe.
You just get them in
and get the fuck back, yeah?
Okay, just...
If anybody recognizes your face
in there, I mean...
Hey, Frenchie.
Don't get caught.
I never do.
[alarm buzzes, then door opens]
[Grace] Weaponized Xanax.
The grenades you used on Behemoth
during the bank heist.
You got a Supe activated by rage,
so you simply take away his rage,
turn him into a cupcake.
Clever.
I don't know what you are talking about.
And Cold Snap two months ago?
Malchemical a month before that?
You don't know about those, either?
What is this about?
Armed robbery, breaking and entering,
aggravated assault on a Supe.
You're looking at 20 to 25, minimum.
Or you can come work for me.
I could use someone with your imagination.
Madame... fuck you.
That's a pity, for you...
but even more so for Cherie and Jay,
I believe?
ADX Florence is a supermax in Colorado.
They've got the Unabomber,
head of the Aryan Brotherhood,
all the greats.
And your friends too. Maybe.
Or they go free.
But that depends on you.
Right now.
You can't do that.
- [door opens]
- Wait.
What kind of work do you do?
Hey.
Um...
Come into my trailer for a second.
I have a surprise for you.
I have to stop by Vought Tower,
see my social guys.
No. Come on, blow them off. Come.
I will be back in 20 minutes.
[whispering] And then...
[in normal voice] I'll let you surprise me
wherever you want.
Ooh.
Yeah, okay.
Oh.
Hmm.
- You see them?
- Yeah. I see them.
[gun clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
Get in.
Here.
Seriously?
What is your problem with me?
I ain't got no problem with you.
Really? That's why
you won't even touch my hand?
Guys, come on. Not the time.
You know what? No.
I think it's exactly the right time.
I think the time is long overdue.
You know that I hate Vought
as much as you do.
You know that.
But it doesn't even matter to you
because what you can't stand
is in my blood.
I'm sub-human to you.
Only good Supe is a dead Supe, right?
Your words, not mine.
- [Hughie] That's enough.
- You know what?
Underneath all that swagger,
you're just a bigot and a bully.
I know another guy just like that.
He's got a flag for a cape.
Annie, stop.
[ominous music playing]
[whooshing sound]
Oh, fuck me.
Hughie, call them. Now.
[keypad beeps, then line ringing]
[knocking on door]
Open the door. We need help.
I have a patient that needs help.
Hurry up. Please!
- What's wrong with him?
- Just open the door.
He's swallowing his fucking tongue!
[door unlocking]
- What's wrong with him?
- Easy.
Holy fuck.
What the fuck is all of this?
Vought is making more Supe Terrorists?
Who the fuck knows.
Goddamn. Brother's got a love sausage.
Stormfront is here?
How you doing today?
[Tim] Good.
[Stormfront] Do you want to show us
a little of what you've been working on?
Hey. Hey.
You're okay.
You're all right.
It's okay.
That is very impressive, Tim.
That orderly Stormfront's with,
he look familiar to you?
[speaking in French]
- What about headaches? Nausea?
- No.
Well, that's promising.
I think we are getting close.
Ma'am.
Can I go home now?
I want to see my family.
[Stormfront] Tim, you were admitted
to Sage Grove because you're suicidal.
You could be a danger to yourself.
I'm not doing any more
of these pet tricks
until I talk to my sister.
Okay. Okay. We'll work something out.
[Tim screaming]
Lamplighter. That's fucking Lamplighter!
I didn't recognise him
without the mask and hood.
Fucking Lamplighter.
We have to kill him for...
- No, no. No, we can't.
- For Madame Mallory.
- For her grandchildren.
- No, not right now.
First we got to find out
what the fuck all this shit is.
- Oh, come on.
- Listen, listen.
Stick to the plan, Frenchie.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Hughie.
- [Hughie] You guys okay?
- Stormfront's in there.
- That ain't all who's here.
Okay, okay. She just left.
Get the hell out. Now.
All right, let's get out of here.
[dramatic music playing]
[alarm wailing]
Hey, Cindy.
Let's be cool. Okay?
You remember that extra helping
of Kraft Shells & Cheese
that I snuck you?
I like you. You know that, right?
Who are your friends?
We ain't his friends.
Go ahead, fuck his ass up.
[Cindy] You're dressed like his friends.
I don't like liars.
Oh, shit.
[dramatic music playing]
Let's get out of here!
[inmates shouting]
[keypad beeping]
Hey, let go!
Stay the fuck back,
or I will burn your skin off, asshole!
Oh, you won't get the chance.
Someone help me!
[shouts]
All right, listen up, man.
You can burn us, but she's a Supe.
All you're gonna do is piss her off.
So why don't we all calm down
and live through this motherfucker?
[man shouting]
What's going on here?
It's a lockdown.
No one's getting out of here.
- [Milk] Gotta be an access code.
- [Lamplighter] At the front door.
And there is no fucking way
I am telling you or taking you with me.
You realise an army of Supes
on the other side of that door
want to tear you apart, right?
She can help.
I'm gonna take my chances.
[door opens]
[shouting]
[screaming, then gurgling]
Okay, you guys can come.
What the fuck?
- Come on, M.M., pick up, damn you.
- [line ringing]
[voicemail] Your call has been forwarded
to an automated voice messaging system.
- [Milk] Marvin.
- Oh, hello.
Easy does it, lad.
No trouble from us.
You just stroll on by, yeah?
I don't want them to hurt me again.
Oh, no. No, no.
No one's gonna hurt you, son.
We're all friends here, aren't we?
[gunshots]
Hughie.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Fine.
- Oh, shit.
- Hughie. Hughie.
Hughie! No, no, no. No.
- Can you cauterize it?
- Uh...
Oh, fuck.
The kid must've fried everything.
I need power.
Well, you got a pretty shite
superpower then, don't you?
- We got to get him to a doctor.
- Okay. How?
I'm not gonna just sit here
and watch him bleed out. All right?
- Okay! Okay, okay. Come on.
- Come on.
- What about the others?
- They're on their own.
[clock ticking]
[sirens wailing]
Ashley? Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Don't you dare tell me
you haven't found Starlight yet.
[coughing]
[whooshing sound]
I've been searching everywhere for you.
What happened to your trailer?
Electrical fire.
How was your meeting?
Sorry, it ran long.
No need to apologise.
All right, well,
I gotta go run lines with Noir.
Scene 48 tonight. Real megillah.
- Something wrong?
- No. Nothing.
You sure?
Why would anything be wrong?
By the way, I went to the Tower,
and you weren't there.
No one had seen you.
So you're checking on me?
Wanted to see how your meeting went.
- Hold on. Let me...
- Explain?
Come on, now.
Why would you need to explain
anything to me?
[ominous music playing]
["Orinoco Flow" playing]
Deep, your numbers among women
have been ticking up quite nicely.
Did you catch Malala Yousafzai's tweet?
Called you a sweetheart.
Well, she's the sweetheart.
So what's on your mind, A-Train?
Hmm. Um...
Deep invited me here, so you know.
Yeah, I don't know.
Just having a really nice lunch,
I guess, here.
And, Deep, what's on your mind?
Well, I think A-Train sabotaged me
my entire career.
- What?
- Well, you do think you're better than me.
And I fantasise about drowning you,
over and over again.
But, man, I don't want to feel that way
anymore. I want to be clean.
Oh, boy.
Looks like we got ourselves
a good old Truth Exchange.
Oh, hell, no.
- Please sit down.
- [A-Train] No. Look, man.
I've seen that documentary about you guys.
It's not my type of shit.
For a man in seven-figure debt,
a heart condition and in heavy withdrawal,
do you really think you have the luxury
to get up and leave?
Who told you that, huh?
Did he fucking tell you that shit?
No. The Church knows all kinds of things.
But don't worry, we also know
how to be discreet,
especially for our members.
They're gonna give Shockwave
your uniform, you know that?
- Call him the next A-Train.
- No, they can't do that.
Why not? A-Train is a trademark.
You are just another nobody
from the south side of Chicago.
- Man, fuck you, man.
- [Alastair] I can help.
I can get you back in.
But first...
sit down.
Let Deep tell you his truths.
[alarm wailing]
Come on, in here.
[keypad beeping]
[woman screaming in distance]
It's beautiful.
Hey. What the hell is going on here, huh?
You'll are juicing people
with motherfucking Compound V,
only to burn them alive? Why?
Maybe I just like watching people burn.
[alarm stops]
I remember you, you know.
You were tailing me the night
that I torched those kids.
So why didn't you stop me?
Maybe you like watching people burn too.
- [speaking in French]
- No, no, no!
- Come on! Come on!
- Easy, easy. Breathe.
[shouting]
Easy. Come on, man.
[speaking in French]
And I don't want to hear
I'mma get tired of the pussy.
I love this girl.
Like, this is the one.
All right, brother. All right.
Congratulations, Marvin.
Thank you, colonel. Check it out.
It's beautiful.
Oh, the bachelor party I will throw you.
What's your thoughts about
transgender strippers?
Strippers ain't really
my kind of Hershey's,
with or without nuts.
But you golf?
Thinking about doing a golf trip.
[door opens]
Oi.
[dramatic music playing]
What?
What the fuck are you laughing at?
Sorry, mate.
You just look like one of them
poncy baton twirlers.
- A majorette.
- That's right, a fucking majorette.
[tablet beeps]
You look good in these.
So here's what happens now.
You're gonna tell us every single thing
you see and hear at the Tower.
Especially when it comes to Homelander.
Please don't pretend
like you have a choice.
I look forward to your call.
Easy peasy.
[Grace] I don't like it.
You don't back an animal like that
into a corner.
Fuck him.
We own the cunt.
Frenchie.
Don't let him out of your sight.
[speaks French]
Hey, what's the trouble, miss?
Sir, I need you to get out of your car.
What are you talking about?
FBI. I need to commandeer your vehicle.
Bit of an emergency.
- Jesus, what happened to him?
- Long story, that.
Can I see some ID?
Left it in my other pants,
too busy saving this one,
but you can call my boss.
Yeah, okay.
Look, I'll... I can get you guys
to the hospital,
but we're in the middle of nowhere here.
I'm not gonna give you my car.
Have it your way.
Butcher.
Don't.
[gun cocks]
- Stay back.
- Whoa, okay.
- [man] Stay back!
- That's not necessary. Let's talk.
FBI? Get real.
You're not even American.
What, is he even hurt?
What is this, some kind of a scam?
If I wanted to boost some wheels,
it wouldn't be a fucking Hyundai,
you daft cunt.
This is a "stand your ground" state.
You stay back.
Oh, you can stand
wherever the fuck you want.
I'm taking your keys.
Butcher, stop.
Buddy, just put the gun down.
- I said, stay back.
- I said, put it down!
[engine sputters]
You couldn't just listen to me
and stay back?
Come on. Cauterize him.
[engine starting]
[Hughie groaning]
All right. It won't hold long. Come on.
Is this the right time to go shopping?
One, why not?
And deux... this is good news.
What do you mean by that?
Some aerated propofol,
some other odds and ends,
I'll make a knockout bomb.
Even for Supes.
[Milk] Okay.
Why are we still alive?
- Dumb luck.
- [Frenchie] Non. I mean, that night.
We went underground for months...
but you never came for us.
Not you, not Homelander.
- Why?
- You're disappointed we didn't kill you?
I thought The Seven always retaliates, no?
You're nobody.
Not worth it.
You didn't told them, did you?
Why wouldn't you told them?
Who says I didn't?
I figured
you'd boast about it to Homelander.
Must've been thrilling for you.
I'm not a fucking animal.
[Frenchie] Only a fucking animal
would do what you did.
Drop it.
- You murdered innocent children.
- Shut the fuck up.
You watched them burn alive,
crying for their mama.
If that's not an animal,
then what is, huh?
I didn't know!
I didn't know they were gonna be
in that bed.
It was supposed to be your boss.
Then they started screaming.
But it was too late.
So, what, are we supposed
to feel bad for you now?
Fuck you.
[Lamplighter]
I don't want anything from you.
But you...
I saw you following me that night.
And then you disappeared.
I keep asking myself, why...
Why didn't you stop me?
Why didn't you?
Good question.
[cameras clicking and crowd clamouring]
All right, all right.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Cherie, this is not...
- [Cherie] He's dying.
- Quoi?
- Jay, he's OD'ing.
I don't... I don't know what he took.
- Take him to the hospital.
- Please come now! Come.
Serge, you fucking come right now.
Cher...
[line disconnects]
Fuck.
Come on.
Come on, mon ami.
- Okay. Look at me.
- [gasping]
You went out. Okay. Can you sit?
Come on. Come on, mon ami.
Come on.
- Oh, my God.
- He's okay.
Okay. You stay with him.
- You keep him talking. Okay?
- What?
- Where are you going?
- Don't let him fall asleep.
- What?
- I told you, I have something.
Something more important than this?
More important than us?
- Cherie, I cannot do this right now. Okay?
- Okay, fine.
Please, stay with him.
[sobbing] Fine, you want to go. Go.
We don't give a shit.
Serge?
I'll be back.
[speaking in French]
- He's burning up.
- I'm going as fast as I can.
- I appreciate what you done back there.
- Oh, thanks.
Your approval means everything to me.
And some sarcasm to stick the landing.
Nice one.
You didn't have a choice.
You know what I was thinking
when I was looking at him?
"Why did you pull the gun,
you stupid fuck?"
That's all.
Maybe once
I would've cried over him, but...
now he was just another person in our way.
- No.
- No what?
No to that fucking look of quiet respect
or approval or whatever that is.
I don't want it.
We're nothing alike. Nothing.
You really think that's gonna work?
I think so.
You know, they're not trying
to make Supes here.
These people are test subjects.
They're trying to stabilise the V.
- Explain.
- Infants handle it best.
But adults? I mean, you saw what happens.
Sometimes you get powers,
sometimes you get a freak,
sometimes you just explode.
Vought is trying to stabilise it,
so that you put the V
in any adult arm, anywhere, anytime,
you get a solid Supe, solid powers.
[speaking in French]
Okay, so...
a thousand more Supes?
Hundred thousand? Why?
Why would Vought do that?
It's gonna fuck up their movies,
their merchandising...
Look, they don't tell me.
They just make me burn the evidence.
Okay?
My, uh...
My best friend OD'd...
and I left to save him that night.
Why I didn't stop you.
You were at the party.
I was away for 30 minutes.
Came back, you were gone.
Did he live?
Your friend?
[speaking in French]
But I never saw him again, and...
Then he died a few months later.
Another overdose.
Are you serious? Frenchie, wh...?
Why didn't you ever tell us?
What difference would it make?
After all these years, man?
We would've let you off the hook.
What makes you think
I want to be let off the hook, huh?
[thud]
[dramatic music playing]
Get it off me!
Get this thing off of me!
[punching sound, then man groans]
[door opens]
Was that...?
It's okay.
That's his fucking dick.
Don't be so closed-minded.
[dramatic music playing]
- I thought you said that's gonna work.
- I said I thought it would.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
[screaming]
Lamplighter?
Lamplighter!
I'm here.
I just killed six subjects out there,
like a fucking Teddy Bear picnic.
What the hell happened?
Dr. Carlton got the propofol dose
wrong again.
So Cindy got loose,
freed some of the others.
I'm sure some of them got out
before lockdown.
Where is Dr. Carlton?
Uh, he was in the cafeteria,
and the hallway, and...
some of the walls.
Clean up this mess. I'm gonna go see
if anyone else got loose.
Yes, ma'am.
We need help!
[monitor beeping]
What'd they say?
Just needs a couple of days
for the cefazolin to kick in,
but he should be all right.
- We don't have a couple of days.
- Well, we're gonna have to risk it.
Jesus.
- What?
- Just... It's the kids' shampoo he uses.
I can smell it.
L'Oreal for Kids "Strawberry Smoothie."
I've seen the bottle.
Hateful shit.
And his Axe body spray? Oh.
I mean, that's how Vin Diesel must smell.
You know, every morning, he slathers
his bum with Creamy Desitin.
- No.
- I fucking swear to God.
He's got rashes down there.
I don't want to know that!
Fucking mental, that's all I'm saying.
But he really just
never gives up on you, does he?
Aye.
And he follows you around
like a right little pup.
He's too good for either of us.
Hmm.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna Postmate Sugarfish.
- [Maeve] What?
I'm gonna Postmate Sugarfish.
Where's your phone?
- I can't hear you.
- Where is...
[shower running]
Homelander and Queen Maeve.
Oh, my God, they're leaving us.
- [woman] What's gonna happen?
- [man 1] It's okay, everybody.
Hey, did you say Sugarfish?
[woman] Please save us!
- Take these two. Just these two, please!
- No, no. No!
What, so they can tell the world
we left the rest of them to fucking die?
- No, Maeve.
- Elena.
[woman] Take my daughters!
- [man 2] Help us! You got to help us!
- [woman] Don't leave us!
I love you.
Tell the boys I love them.
I'm gonna show that to Homelander.
And he's either gonna leave us alone,
or I'm gonna put it on CNN.
Elena.
Elena. This is our out.
I was scared. I...
I know I should've stood up to him.
I know that.
Elena, I watched a plane
full of people die.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Yeah. Right.
Yo. Close stitch, but Hughie's okay.
Oh, bien.
Hey, tell Butcher
about that thick penis around your neck.
[whispering] Fuck you.
[in normal voice]
It's just Frenchie being Frenchie.
I am sorry.
For a long time,
I was trying to save you.
I thought if I did,
somehow that would make up
for the things I've done.
You never asked to be saved.
You cannot absolve my sins, no one can.
I know this now.
So...
I leave you alone.
[car approaching]
Got to go.
[car door opens, then closes]
- Colonel.
- Marvin.
- Where is he?
- This way.
Madame Mallory.
I know I wasn't welcome at the funeral,
so all these years,
I couldn't offer my condolences...
Where is he?
Why isn't this man restrained?
No need. I wanted to come.
I don't want to hear a single
goddamn word from you.
I thought this was behind me,
but it's not.
It never is.
Then let's both be done with it.
I know what you have to do.
Do it.
You'd be doing me a favour. Do it.
Madame, please, if I may?
Besides you, no one wanted him dead
more than me,
but I am begging you for his life.
[sobbing] I have no choice.
It won't help you.
All you'd be doing is ending his torment.
You cannot punish him
as much as he punishes himself.
Trust me.
So...
what exactly are you proposing
we do with him?
Hey.
I'm so glad you're here.
I want to apologise.
Please, just let me explain.
Flap, flap, flap
goes that little mouth of yours.
You remember you told me
that you don't break easily?
Well, I've been thinking about that.
A lot.
I will never lie to you again.
I will tell you everything.
Starting with this.
Your grandmother?
My daughter.
Chloe. She died of Alzheimer's
a few years ago.
How old are you?
I was born in 1919.
In Berlin.
- Is that you with...?
- Heinrich Himmler.
He was a lovely dancer.
And that's Goebbels.
And the most important man in the room...
Frederick Vought.
He gave me the first successful
V injection.
He taught me everything.
And then we fell in love,
and he gave me a daughter.
He made me, and his genius made you.
Frederick didn't care about
all the fans or stardom
or any of that shallow bullshit.
We are in a war for the culture.
The other races are grinding us down
and taking what is rightfully ours,
but we can fight back.
With an army of supermen, millions strong.
Because that is Vought's true destiny.
And you will be the man who will lead us.
You are everything that we dreamed of.
So I love you with all of my heart.
How could I not?
Everyone I have ever loved
is in the ground.
And then I found you.
We found each other...
and now neither of us
has to be alone ever again.
And that is the truth.
["Thank You For Being a Friend" playing]
♪ Thank you for being a friend ♪
♪ Travelled down a road and back again ♪
♪ Your heart is true ♪
♪ You're a pal and a confidant ♪
♪ And if you threw a party ♪
♪ Invited everyone you knew ♪
♪ You would see
The biggest gift would be from me ♪
♪ And the card attached would say: ♪
♪ "Thank you for being a friend" ♪
[hip-hop music playing]
♪ Word. And ready, set, go ♪
♪ Here Comes the A-Train
Mr. Fleet feet ♪
♪ Saving lives, takin' names
Nice and easy ♪
♪ There ain't no day like a race day, what
Ain't no love like a raceway, what ♪
♪ I'm the best to ever do it, y'all crazy
Make way or you're pushin' up daisies ♪
♪ Bring the heat
Now they're begging for some a.c. ♪
♪ Only place I will lose in your daydream
Ain't no after, you can get that action ♪
♪ Taking back my title like the Alamo ♪
♪ They be trying to play me
Like a saxophone ♪
♪ But I'm about to knock 'em down
Like I'm playing Whack-A-Mole ♪
♪ Y'all won't ever touch me
Like an isotope ♪
♪ Presto, yeah he's gone in a flash
Skrrt off, zoom ♪
♪ Y'all getting passed
Leave 'em in the dust when I dash ♪
♪ Can't be caught too fast
Gingerbread man ♪
♪ Yeah, A-Train, second to none ♪
♪ You're looking for the best
I'm the definition ♪
♪ If anyone playin'
Leave 'em under the dust ♪
♪ I'm in love with the crown
We gonna never split up ♪
♪ I'mma do it all my way ♪
♪ Picking up the pace
Y'all will never stop me ♪
♪ Putting in the work
Fly away ♪
♪ Slipstream, we're taking off, fly away ♪
♪ - When I'm... ♪
♪ - Faster than the speed of light ♪
♪ Watching as your dreams take flight ♪
♪ - Dreams take flight ♪
♪ - I think I should stand and fight ♪
♪ Then disappear into the night ♪
♪ Faster than the speed of light ♪
♪ Watching as your dreams take flight ♪
♪ I think I should stand and fight ♪
♪ - Think I, think I ♪
♪ - Then disappear into the night ♪