[Annatar] The Greatest of Elven-smiths
is consumed by his work.
He asks that I handle all matters
of administration in his stead.
I'm just fatigued.
You are the Lord of Eregion.
You have responsibilities.
Until the Nine are complete,
nothing else matters.
[Annatar] Without mithril, the remaining
Rings of Power may never be complete.
We need more.
The answer is no.
Tell Narvi we're expanding the dig.
Have you gone mad?
Take off the Ring.
I have nothing to prove to you, boy.
-[grunts]
-[Prince Durin IV groans]
We'll lay our bodies in front of that mine
ourselves if we have to.
[Narvi] Disa?
[Elrond] The Orcs are not in Mordor.
A legion of them are headed for Eregion.
Galadriel was right.
You must send aid!
Our armies cannot defeat both Adar
and Sauron. Not alone.
[Orcs laughing]
[Adar, in Sindarin] I brought you here.
For we share a common enemy.
[Galadriel, in English] Elrond hastens
from Lindon with an army of Elves.
And Nenya, my Ring.
[Adar] Sauron believes he is still
beyond my grasp.
But I know he hides in Eregion.
How fares your progress?
[Celebrimbor] I cannot forge
more Rings without mithril.
[Annatar] I have been to Khazad-dûm.
One-ninth portion.
It should be enough.
[Galadriel] Sauron has no army of his own,
so he's lured yours here instead.
He wants you to attack Eregion.
[Adar] Eregion will fall.
And Sauron with it.
Bind her.
No!
This is what Sauron wants!
[bellows]
[Orc shouts]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
Nine...
...for mortal Men.
[sighs]
[skittering, chittering]
[chittering]
Hello, Mr. Mouse.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Have you fallen?
Come. The floor is hardly the place
for the Greatest of Elven-smiths.
No, I... I, uh...
[stammers]
Fëanor's hammer is, is missing a--
Missing a, a...
You know how forgetful you can be.
No, no.
No, this was different.
I trust you are not feeling
overwhelmed again?
No.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
These past weeks,
I have felt such clarity,
a focus that I have not known in years.
And I have you to thank for that.
Please.
When the world is still,
then the ideas can flow freely.
My work is but to let them share
the secrets of their song.
How fares your progress?
[sighs]
The Rings of Power are nearly complete.
How long?
[scoffs]
What is another few days
to perfect something
that shall last forever?
[chuckles]
It will be a sad occasion.
I have so enjoyed our time together.
Well, all things must end.
A pity. Is it not?
[door opens]
[door closes]
[dramatic music playing]
[Orcs shouting]
[in Black Speech] It is time.
[Elves clamoring]
[in English] My lord.
What orders from Lord Celebrimbor?
Lord Celebrimbor refuses
to permit a counter-attack.
He says the river will protect us.
Every moment we remain idle,
more Elves die.
We must do something.
And that is why
we're not going to obey him.
[rumbling, explosions continue]
Gather your finest troops.
I am taking command of our defenses.
-Valar bless you, my lord.
-[soldier] This way. Go!
What is it? What are you not telling them?
Celebrimbor's mind is gone.
We are alone.
[soldier] Quickly.
Not alone.
You have proven your quality, Mirdania.
When the time comes,
I will see to it that you are...
[rumbling, explosions stop]
...duly rewarded.
What is it?
The siege engines. They've gone silent.
[woman] Get to safety!
[Orcs grunting]
[Zhor] Push it!
I said, push, you maggots.
[Orcs grunting]
Push, come on, you maggots!
Come on, you filth.
Put your stinkin' backs into it!
He's turning them away from the city.
Celebrimbor was more mistaken
than we knew.
Prepare for ground assault.
Ground assault? From across the river?
[grunts]
[distant explosions]
[Zhor] Again!
They're damming the river.
Prepare for ground assault!
[soldier] To your positions!
-[chittering]
-[gasps]
[Narvi] Eregion is under siege.
The guards received that entreaty
from an Elf at the West-gate.
Then they are more desperate
than we thought.
I need the mine taken back, now.
But, sire, your son is still down there.
And so is Princess--
Every hour that we delay
costs us unthinkable wealth.
We must dig.
Go!
Here they come.
Slow to learn, are you?
Easy, lads. Just turn around.
[Narvi] No.
We stand with you.
Down your axes.
That Ring has taken the King's heart.
I will not let it take this mountain.
We have to get it off him.
Ours is not the only kingdom in peril.
There's an Elf outside, wants your ear.
Let him in.
Well, we'll have to do it quietly.
This particular Elf has been banished
from all Dwarven lands.
Elrond.
My heart sings to see you, old friend.
You tidal-haired,
flowery-tongued flagpole.
-"Tidal-haired"?
-Mm-hm!
You've got some sand comin' here.
Have you any idea what I've gone through
since you left?
It can hardly be more eventful
than what's transpired with me.
I'm about to overthrow my father.
What've you got?
Defeat.
Without your aid.
Thousands of lives are at hazard, Durin.
Celebrimbor is among them.
I know I ask too much of you, Durin,
but I need your axe, old friend.
I need it now.
[shouting, snarling]
[Orcs shouting]
Move it!
[shouting]
[arrows whooshing]
[in Sindarin] Loose arrows!
[groans]
[grunting]
[shouting]
[in Sindarin] Hold fast!
[in English] Captain, they have a Ravager.
[Commander Malendol, in Sindarin]
Prepare to fire!
We must stop that machine!
[shouting]
[groans]
[grunting]
The Rings. Are they finished?
[shushing]
Wait for it.
Wait for what?
[chittering]
Captivating.
It is a pattern.
Do you not see? A cycle.
Repeating itself at intervals
throughout the day.
And there is more.
Here.
Look. The embers--
Celebrimbor, whatever so
inspired this epiphany,
I assure you, we have not the time for it.
On the contrary,
we would appear
to have all the time that we need.
The candles...
have not burned an inch all day.
You sought peace.
I gave it to you.
No.
Whatever... Whatever this is,
this is hardly a gift.
What have you done to me?
Done to you?
You welcomed my instruction.
You practically begged for it.
Now, a... a mouse scurries by,
and you fly to pieces.
Listen to yourself.
[shouts] Oh, what have you done to me?
No Emissary of the Valar would do this.
[softly] Who are you... truly?
I am the one keeping the storm at bay.
Balancing the very sun above your head.
All to give you this one chance
to prove your worth!
Now, I want the Nine!
No!
[shattering]
[explosions in distance]
-[explosions]
-[Elves screaming]
[melancholic music playing]
[sobbing]
[gasping]
What...
[wailing]
[clatters]
What... The mithril.
[gasps]
What... What is... What is this?
I have learned so much from you,
since I came to Eregion.
But no lesson more lasting than this.
True creation...
requires sacrifice.
You are He.
Are you not?
-You are--
-I have many names.
[Elves shouting]
[groans]
-[tinnitus ringing]
-[grunts]
[all shouting]
Mirdania!
[panting] Thank the Valar you're alive.
We have been deceived. All of us.
He planned all of this,
to force me to forge the Rings.
He put me in some kind of a prison.
A prison of the mind. But I am out.
I am out.
He must've been distracted by the siege,
so he forgot the ruby.
And the mouse. The same mouse--
And...
You must... You must believe me.
[gasping]
You have to believe me!
[Orcs grunting]
This is the thinnest part of the wall.
[Orc] Come on!
[grunting]
We have to brace the foundations!
Quickly, now!
Seize him.
He is Sauron.
Seize him!
He has been lying to you all along.
No. He has been protecting us.
While you've been in your tower,
giving orders that might have been
the end of us all.
No. No, that was him.
He is Sauron!
If you do not believe me, cut him open.
Look at his hand, look at his blood.
Black as pitch.
[gasping]
Come, my lord.
Let's get you back where you belong.
Get your hands off me!
-[screaming]
-No!
[gasping]
[grunts]
[shudders]
All this can end.
Finish the Nine,
and I will spare your city.
What will you do with them?
Create a perfect and lasting peace.
[horn bellows]
[all shouting]
-[horn bellows]
-[horse neighing]
[horses neighing]
[shouting]
Come on!
[Orcs shouting]
[in Sindarin] Death to our foes!
[all shouting]
[grunting]
Halt!
[in English] Welcome, Commander Elrond.
The Ring you carry.
Show it to me.
A foolish act if I had brought it here.
You are a courtier.
More suited to wielding a scroll
than a sword.
You've never seen me wield either.
You should've just kept charging, Elrond.
If she speaks again, cut out her tongue.
[Orcs growl]
Sauron is my enemy as much as yours.
Give me what I need to defeat him
and let us all be rid of him.
Is it not you that has done his bidding
by laying siege to Eregion?
Eregion has fallen into shadow.
It belongs to the Deceiver now,
as does every Elf within its walls.
Not Lord Celebrimbor.
It was Celebrimbor himself
who welcomed Sauron in.
You cannot save him.
You can save Galadriel.
It is an earnest offer.
I suggest you take it.
And leave Sauron to me.
You have the beauty of your foremother,
Melian of the Valar.
If even a fragment of her wisdom
is in your veins,
you must know you cannot
defeat me in battle.
I will outmaneuver you,
my forces outfight yours,
and you will fall.
Not before you have painted
the sands of the Glanduin black
with the blood of your kin.
[growls]
My children have endured cruelties
your bravest couldn't bear
to hear spoken aloud.
Are you prepared
to spend their lives so freely, Adar?
Are they?
The Ring for Galadriel's life.
What is it to be?
Ask me on the field,
when the neck
with a blade against it is yours.
[Orcs seethe, snarl]
Very well.
I will meet you there...
with her head on a pike.
If that is to be the way of things,
I should like to bid her farewell.
He's unarmed.
[whispers in Sindarin] Forgive me.
Win.
Vorohil.
[Orcs snarling]
[in English] The enemy outnumber us
ten to one. So why the confidence?
[in Sindarin] Because I know something
the Father of the Orcs does not.
[in English] And what is that?
[in Sindarin] Even now Prince Durin is
rallying a legion of Dwarves to our aid.
And at the first rays of sunlight...
...you will guide them
straight into Adar's flank.
Outstanding.
[in English] Ride to them now.
Meantime, I will ensure
that Eregion's walls
hold for one more night.
Warriors of Khazad-dûm.
At this moment,
the great tale of our Age
is being written.
And it falls to us
to decide whether it will end
in tragedy... or triumph.
Sauron the Stoneheart,
who stole the seven smithing secrets
from our forebearers, has returned.
Forging Rings to enslave us
and all of Middle-earth.
The Elves cannot defeat him.
Not without us.
And Sauron knows this.
He thinks, by stoking our greed,
he can turn our hearts to ash
and sweep us from the field
without a fight.
But we are stronger than he knows.
[all] Aye!
For there is something all Dwarves prize,
far more than riches.
More even than this mountain we hold dear.
Fight with me, so all the world can see,
that Dwarven loyalty
is a force stronger than any sorcery!
[all] Aye!
More powerful than any army!
Deeper than the bones of the earth!
[all] Aye!
Will you fight with our friends?
Will you fight for Khazad-dûm?
[all] Baruk Khazâd! Baruk Khazâd!
Baruk Khazâd! Baruk Khazâd!
[all cheering]
Khazad...
[all] Dûm!
We march for Eregion!
[all cheering]
[in Sindarin] Defend the city!
-[horse neighing]
-[groans]
[all shouting]
To the wall!
-[grunting]
-[groans]
[growls]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[Zhor, in English]
Gonna spill your guts, Elf.
[gasps, coughing]
[in Sindarin] Die.
[coughing, exclaims]
[in English] No! No! No, no! No!
[screaming]
[arrows whooshing]
[grunting]
[hammering]
[grunts]
That's enough!
[grunting]
[Orc laughs]
[Orc captain] Again! Reset the Ravager!
Move!
[Glüg] Lord-father.
The wall is stronger than we thought.
We may not breach it before morning.
The Elf is faring better
than you expected.
His troops have already destroyed five
of our trebuchets.
Many Uruk are dying.
What are your orders, Lord-father?
-Shall we sound the retreat?
-No.
Sauron must not escape.
Bring down that wall. At any cost.
Adar!
[in Black Speech]
You told us... you loved us.
[in English]
With all that is left of my heart.
Too much,
to let you become Sauron's slaves.
[in Black Speech] Hurry!
[in English] She's still in the camp.
Find her!
[grunts]
[snarling]
[Orc] He's dead.
He's gone.
Eh. You there! Come here and help.
He's dead.
[Orcs grunting]
[growling]
[in Black Speech]
In flames they return to darkness.
[growling]
[in English] Look at that pretty hair.
-[arrows whoosh]
-[groans]
[Galadriel sighs]
Whatever force it was
that brought you here, soldier,
I am grateful for it.
Come, I know a hidden way into the city.
We must find Sauron.
I'm here for him.
Try to move against him now,
the cost will be your life.
He can have it.
He has taken everything else from me.
Arondir.
There is a dearth of Elven heroes
this night.
It would be a pity to lose another.
And the true fight with Adar
will come later.
[Prince Durin IV sighs]
The army has assembled at the West-gate,
Prince Durin.
Good.
[Narvi shouts] Durin!
Prince Durin!
Wait!
Your father, he turned his axe on my men.
He cut through them like stalks of wheat.
[chuckling]
But he's gonna dig.
He's gonna loose that beast!
-Disa, is she--
-I don't know.
But she sent me to find you.
She says you have to recall the army.
And what about Elrond?
You take that army to Eregion now,
and Khazad-dûm
might not be here when you return.
Be not afraid. This too shall pass.
I promise you,
when Middle-earth is healed,
and its people see
what you and I did here...
all our sufferings will be worth it.
"Our sufferings"?
You must know it pains me,
treating you like--
Like you've treated countless others?
Like Morgoth treated me.
Do you know what it is to be tortured
at the hands of a god?
I cannot imagine.
I see the end, Celebrimbor.
So clearly.
I have seen it from the moment I awoke.
But his end, it was different from mine.
For what he wished to destroy,
I wished... to perfect.
Sometimes, the pain
almost became a reward.
Became a game.
A contest,
to see whose will was the mightier.
And after all that, you would still choose
to inflict the same pain upon me?
No.
You chose it.
Not I.
What?
All depends... on the Rings.
And since you forced me
to torment you to bring them into being,
I am but a victim of your obstinance.
And you, the true author
of your own torment.
[scoffs]
You truly are the Great Deceiver.
You can deceive even yourself.
Finish them.
[disembodied voices whispering]
[groans]
Release!
[grunting]
[Elrond] Hurry!
[gasps]
[soldier] Fire!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[grunting]
[panting]
[shuddering]
Whose will is the mightier?
[flesh squelches]
[shuddering]
-[explosions]
-[shouting in distance]
[shuddering]
[indistinct shouting]
[heart beating faintly]
[soldier 1]
Look what he's done to himself.
[soldier 2] The old fool
really has gone mad.
You are to remain in the tower,
so as not to be a danger to yourself.
By order of Annatar. Lord of Eregion.
[groaning]
[Galadriel] Release him.
[Commander Malendol] My lady?
That is Lord Celebrimbor.
Greatest of Elven-smiths.
-Release him.
-But the Lord of Eregion ordered--
This is the Lord of Eregion.
Celebrimbor, it's me.
Celebrimbor.
When I saw you,
for a moment, I was certain
that you were but another illusion,
another cruelty devised to torment me
with false hope.
Sauron?
More Rings?
Nine.
Nine Rings to enslave the world of Men.
As he... enslaved me.
I-- It was my fault.
No!
From the beginning, a part of me... knew.
A part of me saw. But I--
I wanted what he offered.
So, I, I blinded myself to,
to what he was.
So did I.
[Sauron screams]
-It is him.
-Hurry.
The old Dwarven tunnel.
I used it to enter the city undetected.
It will bear you and the Rings
far from here.
No. No.
Go! Now!
I cannot. It must be you.
He will realize what has happened.
He will come for the Rings.
I will ensure it is some time
before that comes to pass.
Take the Rings,
save anyone in the city you can. Hurry!
No.
I won't let you face him alone!
I... I built this city.
My place is here.
[Commander Malendol]
And he will not be alone.
I'm sorry. I brought him here.
I'm sorry I wasn't stronger.
Neither of us was strong enough.
There might not be anyone
in Middle-earth who is.
But perhaps, the Elves need only remember
that it is not strength
that overcomes darkness,
but light.
Armies may rise,
hearts may fail,
yet still, light endures,
and is mightier than strength.
[growls]
For in its presence,
all darkness must flee.
[sniffling]
[in Quenya] Namarië.
[in English]
Again! We're almost there! [grunts]
[growls]
They'll breach the wall soon, Commander.
Won't they?
No, Rían! Our enemy will not
breach that wall!
A single arrow from you
may yet turn the tide.
-How many torch arrows do you have left?
-Enough to do my part.
All I need is a clear line of sight.
Follow me.
[in Sindarin] Go!
[grunting]
Take the shot!
[screams]
No.
[gasping]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[explosions]
Dagranno!
[Elves shouting]
[grunting]
[in English] Destroy it!
Send him in.
Lord-father, he will kill our own kind.
[grunting]
[groans]
The Orcs, they're fleeing!
No. They're clearing a path.
-[rustling]
-[growling]
[shatters]
You shall not find them here.
They will be far from your reach by now.
Then you are going to bring them to me
and place them in my hand.
Your hand will never touch
another Ring again.
[speaks Sindarin]
[in English] By order
of the true Lord of Eregion,
you, Sauron, are hereby--
-[disembodied voices whispering]
-[choking]
You think it was only you,
who put yourself in my power?
You will give me the Nine.
[all shouting, grunting]
-[grunts]
-[Orc screams]
It must not reach the wall!
[grunts]
[roaring]
[screaming]
[groaning]
[growls]
Watch out!
[grunting]
[Orc groans]
Commander, look out!
[growling]
[grunting]
[in Sindarin] Kill it now!
-[roars]
-[groans]
[roars]
[gasping, wheezing]
[panting]
[roaring]
[laughing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[laughing]
[groans]
[horse neighs]
[growls]
[groans]
[groaning]
[in English]
Go back to your hill and be buried.
[grunts, groans]
[grunting]
[groaning]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
Commander!
[grunting]
[laughing]
[grunts]
[screams]
[groans, coughs]
[growls]
[chuckling]
[chokes]
[laughing]
[groans]
[sighing]
Commander.
[Elrond] High King.
You should not be here.
A king's place
is wherever the need is greatest.
[horn bellows]
-[drums banging]
-[Orcs chanting]
[in Black Speech]
My children! March with me!
[Orcs shouting]
[menacing music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[birds chirping]
[in English]
The Dwarves! The Dwarves are coming!
Look to the north!
[horse neighs]
Vorohil.
[groaning]
[groans]
[panting] Durin recalled their army.
The gate of Khazad-dûm is shut.
-No, there... must be some mistake.
-[groaning]
Durin will come!
[Orcs shouting]
[in Sindarin] Form ranks!
[metal clinking]
[in English] Durin will come.
[in Black Speech] Kill them all!
[Orcs shouting]
[in Sindarin] Attack!
[all shouting]
[in English] Durin will come.
Durin will come.
[all shouting, grunting]
[groaning]
[groans]
[shuddering]
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[Orcs shouting]
-[muffled shouting]
-[melancholic music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[in Sindarin]
Have you forgotten your Rúmil?
"Never make war in anger."
[groans]
[thunder breaking]
[closing theme music playing]