- Previously on
"The Flash."
- You're no longer you.
You're a part of
a negative force.
- Thawne's Speed Force
is fueled by negative emotions.
- What do you do?
- Trust me,
you wouldn't believe
me if I told you.
- You're not super satisfied
with your secret identity.
- Are you saying
I don't want to be Vibe?
- Barry: There won't be any
future for any metas
if we don't get rid
of that dagger.
- If anything's gonna
destroy that dagger,
it's this Mirror Gun.
- It works.
- Follow my instructions
and we'll defeat Cicada,
destroy her dagger,
and save your father.
- Thawne is manipulating her.
- Iris:He's on death row,
how is he manipulating her?
- Something doesn't add up.
- The dagger
is Thawne's plan.
Don't shoot it!
- Nora:I always wanted
to be a hero,
to use my extraordinary
abilities to help people.
That's why I came here.
To meet my family,
to stop Cicada,
help fix
the Flash's legacy,
and save him from
disappearing in the future.
I believed I could
do the impossible,
but I never imagined
it would turn out like this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- No, no!
What's he doing?
[music intensifies]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[thud]
- Cicada...Thawne,
dagger.
♪ ♪
- Barry:How's Ralph?
- I've never seen
anything like it.
I can't quite figure it out.
His cells are
kinetically inverted.
It's like they're
the reverse of themselves.
- Should've spent more time
trying to figure out
how this thing works.
- I just don't understand
why he would jump
in front of that blast.
I mean, why would
he do that?
- That's the question,
isn't it?
That's the question.
- In other news,
Cicada deuce is still MIA.
- All right,
we should get to CCPD,
see if we can find anything
that could help us track her.
[cell phone buzzing]
[groans]
- What?
- I'm supposed to meet up
with Kamilla later.
- I thought things were going
really well for you two.
- They are.
I just haven't told her about
my vibratory alter ego yet.
- Cisco, if you're serious
about being with her,
you have to tell
her the truth.
- I know.
[siren wails]
- All the metas that we
couldn't cure,
we got safely evacuated
and they're waiting
at a protected
holding facility.
- Nice work, both of you.
- Well the work's not done yet.
I mean, the metas
are safe for now,
but Cicada's still out there,
so the people
are still in danger.
- Fill me in
on the details.
- I'm ready for
this nightmare to end.
- It should've been
over already.
- Nora, look,
I'm sure Ralph
had a good reason.
Until we figure out
what it is, we just gotta
concentrate on this,
all right?
Wait a second.
- What is that?
- Looks like wood.
- From what?
I mean the floor is marble,
furniture's untouched,
and the skylight's made
of glass and metal.
- Well if it didn't come
from Cicada's point of entry...
- She must've brought
it from somewhere else.
- Grace:What do we do now?
- Orlin:You know what to do.
Hit them when they
least expect it.
- When they least
expect it.
[dramatic music]
The Time Sphere.
If I repair it,
I can bring the
last of the virus back
to the night
of the Particle Accelerator.
- When meta-humans first
appeared in Central City...
- And the Flash becomes
a hero to stop me.
- Destroy the meta-humans
before they destroy the world.
- They'll be born
only to die.
- Definitely some
kind of wood fragment.
- And you think those will lead
us to where Cicada's hiding?
- We can find out.
We can cross-reference this,
see what kind of wood it is,
then see where we end up.
- Is there any
progress on Ralph?
- No, he's still unconscious,
and I can't figure out
a way to reverse his cells.
- So I guess that means we
still don't know why
he jumped in front
of that Mirror Gun, do we?
- We do.
We do...
because Dibny solved
the greatest mystery of all.
The Flash legacy,
how to stop Cicada,
repentance for his past sins...
all the reasons
Eobard Thawne was helping you.
- And stopping Dad from
disappearing in the future.
- Disappearing in the future
is part of it, hmm?
But this has nothing
to do with your father.
The real reason that Thawne
wishes to defeat Cicada
and destroy Cicada's dagger
is because this dagger
is the only thing keeping
the Reverse-Flash in prison.
[building violin music]
[dramatic percussion]
♪ ♪
- Guess this is it.
- Looks like it,
doesn't it?
- Mm.
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
I almost forgot. [chuckles]
I contacted the Flash Museum,
had them send
something over for today.
I thought it should
be buried for good...
along with you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Consider it
a parting gift.
[music intensifies]
- Destroying Cicada's
dagger in the past
will save Thawne
from dying in the future?
- That's right.
Cicada's dagger
has been dampening
Thawne's powers
all this time.
- So if we get rid
of the dagger now,
it disappears
in the future?
- And Thawne gets out
of Iron Heights.
- A reverse time hack.
- Everything you said
about Thawne is true.
The only person
he ever helps is himself.
- Nora, this
is not your fault.
- Yes, it is.
- Now the question
we have to ask...
do we stop Cicada
or do we stop Thawne?
- No, we're not gonna let
thousands of meta-humans die,
now or in the future.
We find Cicada.
We destroy the dagger
once and for all.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- You gotta get
out of here.
- No, we gotta wait
for the results...
- We can handle
it until you get back.
Go see Kamilla.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- How do you choose?
- That's more of a question
for Iris than for me.
Hey.
- Hey.
- [laughs]
She seems to be happy
with my photos.
I was kinda hoping
she'd send me over to CCPD
to take photos of
the meta-humans
when they were
getting that cure.
Can you imagine being there
when that Cicada guy attacked?
- Cicada woman, actually.
- A woman?
- Her name's
Grace Gibbons.
Her uncle was
the first Cicada.
She killed him after he took
the meta-human cure.
The cure that I made.
- The cure you made?
[laughs]
You're serious.
That's the scientific project
you've been working on?
- At S.T.A.R. Labs.
- You never told me your lab
was S.T.A.R. Labs.
- There's a lot
I haven't told you.
- What is that
supposed to mean?
- [sighs]
- You're Vibe.
- Look, Kamilla,
I've seen firsthand
how hard it is
to have two lives
like this.
And I tried to separate
you from that,
but I don't want to keep
this from you anymore.
I can't keep lying
to you like this.
I'm sorry.
- Cisco, wait.
I totally get it.
I've read a lot
of comic books.
I know all the tropes
that go with
revealing secret
identities.
But in real life,
I would never expect you
to tell me something
like this right away.
- You're amazing,
you know that?
- Cisco, this isn't
about me.
It's about you.
If being Vibe is a part
of the life you want,
I would never get
in the way of that.
- You know you really
are a lot like me.
Trusting.
And you always blame yourself
when things go wrong.
- How do I fix this?
- I don't know
if you can, Nora.
You made a mistake,
you know?
A big mistake.
Sometimes in life,
all we can do is just
live with the consequences.
So what you have to ask
yourself is
what kind of hero
are you gonna be?
One who takes a do-over
after every mistake,
or one who lives with it
and moves forward?
♪ ♪
- Nothing?
- Nope, I still cannot
figure out how to reset
his cells back
to normal.
- He's till Humpty Dumpty'd,
huh?
- Yep.
- He hasn't been
this much of a mess
since he first got his powers.
- Since...
And what did you do
to help him then?
- We introduced a stabilizing
enzyme that reset
his body back to its original
form using vulcanization...
and muscle memory.
- Muscle memory.
Well then it appears
all that we need to do
is wake him up.
- How would you
suggest we do that?
- Simple.
We blast him.
- We blast him?
- If you blast him,
the vibrational jolt,
it will be more than enough to
kick-start his consciousness.
I'm sure of it.
- Can't we just play some Gaga
and hope he wakes up?
- Gaga is not the solution
to everything.
You have to blast him.
Allez, young
Ralph Macchio, please.
Be careful.
This could get a little ugly.
- Okay.
Sorry, deuce.
- [warbling]
WrestleMania!
- Voilà!
Good as new.
- Blasted why
you happen what?
- Hmm?
- B-b-blasted why
you happen what?
- Except for
the language skills.
Those will return,
probably.
[alarm beeping]
- Everybody going,
where is?
Everybody going
where...every...
- What is it?
- It's the wood particles
you guys found.
"Swiss ash."
- Part of the flowering ash
trees indigenous to Europe,
but also make up
our biggest wood space
not 12 miles
from Central City.
- Kolins Woods.
- That's where Cicada
almost killed me.
- That's also one of the
largest wooded parks
in the country.
- We need a better plan.
- I've got one...
that can stop
Cicada and Thawne.
- Out to sniff?
So really we're
using her Cecile?
- Well, she is a highly
sensitive empath
and Cicada emanates hate.
DA Cecile Horton will serve
as our early warning
detection system.
- If we're lucky,
Cicada won't see what's coming.
- Nora:Then once we find
Cicada II to entrap her,
we give Young Grace
the choice to take the cure.
And hopefully, when
she's no longer a meta...
- That bitch will
cease to exist.
- That way we can stop her
without destroying
the dagger and Thawne
never goes free.
- Now all you have
to do is help Grace
make the right choice.
- What do I say?
- Whatever's in your heart.
She'll listen.
- What a bunch
of sentimental crap.
You two sound like
a friggin' Hallmark movie.
- I hear ya, sister.
- I think we're close.
You good?
- [gasps]
Oh, yeah, jeez, sorry.
Uh, this way.
- Here we go.
- The Sphere is ready.
We can leave.
[crackling]
- Guys, we found her.
Get ready.
- I'm actually glad
you found me before we left.
Now I can end your lives
twice today.
- Not on my watch.
- [grunts]
- We got her.
- Nora, you're up.
If you can connect
to Grace as an adult,
you can connect
with her as a child.
You just have to tap
into her anger.
You can do this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You shouldn't
have come back here, Nora.
- I had to, Grace,
because a lot of people are
gonna die unless you help me.
- If I can help it,
you'll be the first to die.
- [grunting]
- Uh, the force field's
integrity
just went down to 86%.
- Grace, I know you think your
uncle wanted all metas dead,
but he was a meta.
That's why he took the cure
and why he wants you
to have it too.
You're a meta,
just like your uncle.
- No I'm not!
Take it back.
- [grunts, growls]
- 70%... 52...
- Don't listen to her,
Gracie.
- This hate.
It's consuming you,
turning you
into a monster.
And what's worse,
you're all alone.
- Uncle Orlin
wouldn't leave me.
- He had no choice.
Take the cure
just like your uncle did.
- No.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- 40%.
- Nora's gotta
convince Grace now.
- Metas killed your parents,
Gracie.
They all deserve to die.
- Don't believe him, Grace.
This is just
in your mind.
- She's right, Gracie.
- It's why you
created him.
He's the man
who took care of you.
[electronic pulsating]
- 19%.
- I know a part of you knows
that this is wrong.
But the other dark
part of you is out there
in the real world
killing innocent people.
You can make a choice
to stop it.
- How?
- Wake up
and take the cure.
- Shut up.
- You can do this, Gracie.
- Get ready.
[electronic pulsating]
- Grace.
- Gracie.
- Grace. Grace
- Grace. Grace.
- Grace!
- [groans]
- Okay, I don't
want people to die.
I'll take the cure.
- [gasps]
Thank you.
- Here she comes.
- Okay.
- Iris:Did it work?
Guys, what's happening?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Joe, no!
[screaming]
- Now I'll finish
what I started.
- It didn't work.
- That shard in her head.
It's still part
of the dagger.
Its dark energy is enough
to counteract the cure.
If we want to cure Grace,
we must destroy that dagger.
[music intensifies]
- [screaming]
[groans]
- You took my family
away from me, Flash.
Now watch me take yours.
- No!
- Cisco:Barry!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[groaning bestially]
[screams]
♪ ♪
- Just in time.
- Gentlemen.
I hate to inform you, but...
You're all dead.
- Thawne...
I...I can help you.
- Isn't this ironic?
Time to repent.
- [screaming]
- Consider this
a parting gift.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Just...in...
Well, well.
It appears as if someone
has figured out
how to reverse time.
Clever girl.
- We figured
out everything.
- Oh, really?
What have you figured out?
- We figured out why
you sent Nora back,
why you had her punch
DeVoe's satellite...
to create a Cicada
we could stop.
Right?
A dagger
we could destroy.
It was the dagger
that was keeping you
in prison all
along, wasn't it?
- That's right.
15 years.
The second time I've
been stuck somewhere
against my will
for 15 years.
Boring.
Except for your visits,
of course.
You're leaving out
the most delightful part:
how you both
helped me escape.
- We helped you?
- That's right.
When you traveled
to the Time Vault,
remember that?
Oh, we need help
trying to figure out
how to drain dark energy
from the
"one who got away."
- Cicada!
- Remember that?
When you blurted that out
in the middle of the Time
Vault, so that years later,
when I ended up with
Cicada's dagger strapped
to my chest, I knew
exactly what I had to do:
get Nora Allen
to trust me.
Easy.
Just like when I got
you to trust me,
and then everything starts
falling into place.
Why?
Because I am
the only speedster
that knows how
to manipulate the timeline
to get what
I want,
orchestrate the changes
that I need,
some of which...
are happening right now,
to ensure one thing:
that I go free.
- We don't need
a dagger to stop you.
- Well then,
let's just see how much
your father taught you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [shouts]
- [groans]
- I guess you're not
as good a teacher as I am.
You can't save him, Nora.
No matter what you do,
no matter what you try,
the Flash will always vanish.
That is his legacy.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Isn't this nice?
Team Flash,
back together again...
with a new guy.
Ralph Dibny.
Welcome.
You should be dead.
- Yeah, I guess
we have that in common.
- [chuckles]
We'll take care of that
in a moment.
Iris.
Always a pleasure.
Frost.
Cisco.
It warms my heart
to see you again.
I want to apologize for...
[grunts]
But had I not done that,
you never would've had the
means to become extraordinary.
- I don't need
powers for that.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Now!
- [coughs]
- [grunts]
It's not my father's legacy
that's gonna disappear, Thawne.
It's yours.
- Nora!
- Hey!
- So close,
Little Runner.
It was never going
to work anyway.
- [grunts]
[gasps]
Mom? Dad?
- No, no, no, no.
- Mom, what's happening?
- A new timeline
is setting in.
- What?
- A new timeline
that you created
when you destroyed
the dagger!
I'm sorry,
Little Runner,
for trading you
in like this.
But I had to be sure
that I could go free.
- [yells]
- You can still
save her, Barry.
- [breathing heavily]
- There's still time.
You can still save her.
- How?
- The Negative Speed Force.
She has to go there.
It's the only place immune
to timeline changes.
But you have to go now.
You have to go, Barry!
Or we lose her forever.
That's right.
I've grown fond of her too.
In many ways.
She's shown me what it's like
to have a daughter.
See you in our next crisis.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I can't do this.
- Yes you can, yes you can.
You have to, all right?
Just hold on
a little longer.
- No, Dad, I can't.
- Nora!
- [breathing heavily]
I can't.
- Nora, what are we doing?
- It's too late.
- No, it's not.
We gotta go back.
- Dad, no.
- Barry, you have
to take her back.
- I know, I know.
- Mom, Mom.
- Nora, you have
to go back now.
- No!
[all gasping]
- If I go back in,
the Negative Speed Force
will be a part
of me forever.
- No, we'll get
it out of you, Nora.
We can get it out.
we can save you.
Please, I promise.
- Mom, you can't.
Mom, you can't.
None of you can.
It's making me
like Thawne.
Full of anger
and hate.
I...I don't want that
to be my legacy.
This is all on me.
- No.
All of it.
My mistake.
And I'm not gonna
make another one.
Sometimes all you can do
is live with the consequences.
- [crying]
Oh my god.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- [sobbing]
- It's okay.
- We love you.
- [sobbing]
- Thank you
for everything.
[both gasping]
- [sobbing]
[solemn music]
- We're so sorry.
♪ ♪
- We have to believe
that we'll see her again.
- We will.
- Nora...
made sure that we didn't
lose everything tonight.
- She saved every meta
in the city.
- And she gave Grace
a new future.
- Gave all of us, right?
Especially me.
Without Nora,
I never would've met
the love of my life, Renee.
- And you wouldn't
have stopped your 38th Cicada.
Or your 39th.
- Right.
It's been quite
a journey.
Pleasure.
An honor, Flash.
- We never could've solved
this mystery without you.
- Well, don't be too sure.
You already have a master
detective in your midst.
Congratulations, Adult Giraffe.
- Well done,
Sherloque.
- Sherlock.
Well, all right then.
Without further ado.
Mes amis.
Good luck, Team Flash.
[cell phone buzzing]
- It's Singh.
- Yeah, he, uh...he wants us
to meet him in CCPD
and bring Barry.
- Yeah, go.
I kinda want
to be alone anyway.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[sobs]
- Is everything okay?
- What Thawne said...
I don't want that.
I don't want
the extraordinary thing
about my life
to be my powers.
- No one feels that way.
- Here's the thing.
I do.
All these years
I thought that Vibe
was the person
I was supposed to be.
I think it's time Cisco
finally got his turn.
- So what does
that mean?
- It means I want
to take the cure.
- If you do this...
- There's no going back.
I know.
- [exhales]
Killer Frost and I
are really gonna miss Vibe.
- Me too.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[rasps]
- How do you feel?
- Scared.
But I'm hopeful.
Before I forget,
I left you something
in the workshop.
Just, you know,
my way of saying thank you.
- For what?
- Being a great friend.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- Well, Grace Gibbons
is currently scheduled
to meet with our
county counselor.
And as soon as possible,
we'll get her in with
a good foster family.
Look, I won't
keep you long,
but I just want
to thank you
for being at
the forefront with Cicada.
- Just doing
our job, sir.
- Well, you went way beyond
just doing your job.
And I know you did it
because of how much
you care for
the people of this city,
which is how I know I can leave
it in your capable hands.
- What do you mean,
leave it?
- The mayor's
offered me the job
as the new
chief of police.
- What?
- Dave.
- David.
- Congratulations.
- That's great.
- Thank you, thanks.
Of course that leaves me
responsible for finding
my own replacement.
And, uh...
I would like that
to be you, Joe.
- Re...replace you?
As...as captain?
- Captain Joe West.
Oh, I like
the sound of that.
- And don't worry.
If things get dicey,
as they tend to around here,
you'll have
plenty of help.
Isn't that right, Flash?
- [stammering]
- Oh come on, Barry.
I'm a detective too.
- Sir.
[chuckles]
- [laughs]
- Congratulations.
- I'll do my best.
[beeping]
[time vault opens]
- Hey.
[sighs]
- Now I know what my dad
meant when he said
being a parent is like
wearing your heart
on the outside
of your body.
- Yeah.
Thawne got away.
Again.
Nora's gone.
Should feel
like a loss but,
I also feel...
- Pride?
- Pride, yeah.
- She did good.
- [sniffles]
Yeah.
- She was the best
of both of us.
- She was my legacy
all along.
And us, together,
as a family,
that's how I want
to be remembered.
As a good man,
a loving husband...
A supportive father.
- You're already
all of those things.
Nora felt that way too.
- [sighs]
Time language.
- Mm-hmm.
- No matter what changes
with the timeline,
that'll never change.
- We'll always have this
to remember her.
- Hi, Mom and Dad.
If you're watching this,
it means that
something went wrong.
But I don't want you
guys to be sad.
I'm not.
I always wanted
to be a hero,
to use my extraordinary
abilities to help people.
That's why I came here:
to meet my family,
stop Cicada,
help fix
the Flash's legacy,
and save him from
disappearing in the future.
I believed I could
do the impossible,
but I never imagined
it would turn out like this.
I'm glad it did.
I wouldn't
change anything
about my time with you,
my sweet parents,
the most important people
to me in the world.
I wish I could be there to
celebrate every new chapter,
to witness every success.
Just know...
that no matter where
I go in my life,
you'll always
be my side.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
Because of you,
I know I will never,
ever, truly be alone,
and I will feel your love
and support like a warm hug
comforting me,
wishing me to be the best
person I can be.
Thank you
for everything...
For making me a hero
and for loving me
even if I wasn't perfect.
Please remember
that I love you both
and I always will,
no matter what
the future brings.
♪ ♪
- Gideon:Incoming time flux.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.