My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Is that what you think I am?
Some sort of evil secretary?
- You tell me.
- I am now,
and forever will be,
my husband's partner.
Pleased to meet you, Dominic Lanse.
Hello, Mr. Allen.
Devoe, if you hurt my family...
I have no interest in your family.
Besides, you're gonna need someone
to miss you when you're gone.
- What did you do?
- I left something for you.
I don't have need for it anymore.
Barry Allen, you're under arrest
for the murder of Clifford Devoe.
My name is Barry Allen.
And I'm an innocent man.
I know that you'll find my fingerprints
all over his body.
And I know that you'll
find his DNA on mine.
But I don't know who stabbed him...
Or how he ended up in my loft.
All I can tell you is I'm being framed...
For something I didn't do.
I didn't kill Clifford Devoe.
All right, Allen,
let's run it back from the beginning.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This is exactly what Devoe wanted.
I mean, we all played right
into his plan, especially me.
Why would Devoe want to
orchestrate all of this?
I don't know, but we
know that this started
when I was still in the Speed Force.
But why target Dominic?
Dominic's power must have allowed Devoe
to inhabit his body.
We should've been on
top of this earlier.
What about the other metas on the bus?
Why create them?
Part of a larger plan?
How are you even here right now, Allen?
Aren't you on house arrest?
- Yeah, well...
- He's at Joe's, actually.
Either that or the courthouse.
I managed to hack into
the ankle monitor GPS.
That's not the only thing Cisco hacked.
When you came out of the Speed Force,
you were talking gibberish at CCPD.
You said something about
not wanting to kill anyone.
I digitally scrubbed a video.
Last thing we want is
somebody hearing something
we don't want them to hear.
- Your Honor, I'm innocent.
- I didn't do this.
I didn't kill anyone.
Yeah, I mean, I don't
remember saying any of that.
- You don't?
- No.
We should look at
everything else he said
when he first came
out of the Speed Force.
- Might give us a clue.
- That's a good idea.
Okay, guys, but remember,
I mean, considering all the
evidence they have against me,
this trial is not even
gonna last very long.
Okay, but with Cecile
taking a leave of absence
to represent you, you got
the best lawyer in town.
- Yeah,
- I mean, even if they did
find you guilty, it's not
like any prison can hold you.
Well, I'm not gonna run.
I won't be a fugitive.
If I'm convicted, I
have to go to prison.
We're not gonna let that happen.
- Right.
- Let's get to work.
We should get to the courthouse.
Yeah.
- How you doing?
- They say the first year
of marriage is always the hardest,
but I never thought my husband
being on trial for murder
would be one of the challenges.
We have been through so much.
We'll get through this too.
Will we, Barry?
I know the Speed Force gave you
a new outlook on life, but...
I don't know if being
positive is enough right now.
I'm just trying to be strong
for the team and for you.
Remember, we're The Flash.
We're The Flash.
Ralph, hold up.
Listen, I'm not gonna
let Barry go to prison.
I failed his dad, I'm
not gonna fail him.
I need your help.
My help, huh? As in the stretchy kind?
As in the underhanded
private investigator kind.
- Oh, ha, no offense taken.
- Come on.
Science has long pondered
what would be required
to successfully transfer consciousness
from one living being to another.
But we've accomplished far beyond
a simple transfer of consciousness.
We've extracted that
which elevates our humanity
and added upon it.
I am both who I was before...
And who I desire to become.
Yes, you are, my love.
My hand still feels
foreign upon your flesh.
And you don't care for it.
No, I do.
As I said, I inherited my host's ability
to read thoughts.
We have never lied to each other before.
Let's not begin now.
Okay.
Marlize, my love...
See past this body.
See past these eyes.
See me, Clifford.
I am nothing without you.
Your Honor, ladies and
gentleman of the jury,
If you don't understand what it
is I'm about to tell you today,
you need to do something.
I need you to believe in the impossible.
As children, we're taught that
the police are there
to protect us, to serve.
We're told that our tax
dollars go toward training them
to be the champions of the city.
But for some of us, it
still seems impossible
that a police investigator,
one of Central City's finest,
could betray that trust.
And even worse, under the
guise of upholding the law
to commit the most heinous act
that one person can
carry out against another.
But that is exactly
what Barry Allen did.
Now, the prosecution will
prove beyond any doubt
that he stood among us a
wolf in sheep's clothing.
But here's the thing.
Barry Allen wears a mask,
used his connection to the law,
his experience as a police investigator,
especially as a crime scene technician,
to stalk a beloved professor and husband
and murder Clifford Devoe in cold blood.
All right, Mr. Borwin,
just sign on the dotted line
and your savings account is all set up.
Appreciate your helping me
out, I want to get this right.
It's my first savings account.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Just a little lightheaded
before lunch, I guess.
Have a great day.
Ladies and gentleman,
the document in my hand,
it's a court-issued restraining order.
It's issued to Marlize
Devoe, the wife of the victim,
on behalf of her husband
against a Mr. Bartholomew Henry Allen.
Now if you'd like a better
look, I have a bigger copy.
And if you'll allow me to call out
what's written underneath
"reason for order issue,"
harassment.
The defendant was
seen just days earlier,
illegally breaking and entering
into the victim's house,
searching through the victim's effects.
A man obsessed.
Barry Allen's skin cells were found
under the nails of the victim.
Now imagine that, if you can,
Mr. Devoe, a man in a wheelchair,
desperately trying to defend himself
as Mr. Allen sought to overpower him.
And finally, this is the knife
that was used to kill Clifford Devoe.
If it looks new, that's because it is.
It was a wedding gift to Mr. Allen.
Now let's just let that
sink in for a moment.
This was supposed to commemorate
the most joyous moment
in a couple's lives.
But instead Mr. Allen used it
to forever separate a
couple from one another.
He used a wedding gift
as a murder weapon.
That is a special kind of evil.
Defendant showed
- an absolute disregard...
- Cisco,
there's a meta attack downtown.
- We got to go.
- Brazen callousness...
I'll stay here with Barry.
When you're done,
could I get some coverage
of the work stations?
Detective, would you
get a statement please?
- Mr. Ramon.
- Captain.
- What happened here?
- Well, vintage Central City.
Aning another weird one.
No data breach, nothing
stolen. Everyone just collapsed.
I have officers at the hospital
interviewing people now,
but so far, no one knows anything.
- Hmm.
- Whoa.
Dark matter city.
Yeah, we're definitely
dealing with a meta here.
You want to see what kind of
perimeter we're dealing with?
You read my mind.
Hey, Joe, you sure you're
okay to run this case?
Because I totally understand
if you need a little more time, uh...
Uh, I'm fine, really.
I may have to go over
to the courthouse later.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
I'm actually heading over there myself.
The prosecution called me to testify.
I'm sorry, Joe.
You know how much I care about Barry,
but I have to tell them what I know.
I get it, you got to
do what you got to do.
Yeah.
Do I need to repeat the question?
No, I heard it.
The person standing over
Clifford Devoe's body was Barry Allen.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Captain Singh, you stated
that you interviewed
Barry Allen five years
ago for the job of CSI.
I wonder, what was your
first impression of him?
He was young.
Had half the experience of
everyone else I interviewed.
Hmm. Why'd you hire him?
It was really something
he said in the interview.
Everyone always talks about
going after the criminal, the guilty.
But Allen said he wanted
to help the victims.
The innocents.
I thought Central City
deserved someone like that.
Allen is one of the good ones.
One of the good ones.
No further questions, Your Honor.
I'd like to redirect, Your Honor.
Proceed.
Would you cover for
Mr. Allen if you had to?
- No, of course not.
- No.
It says here in his personnel file
that he took a six-month sabbatical
to the Czech Republic.
Did he get approval from you first?
Not exactly.
He said it was for something personal,
I'm sure he had a good reason to go.
Is saving the world a good reason?
It also says in here that he was late
72 times in the past two years.
Did you ever ask him why?
No, because regardless
of what time he got in,
he always did his job.
I was just curious to
imagine what he does
with his time instead of being at work.
It's almost like he
has this secret life.
So in spite of all these infractions,
you never thought to discipline him?
What are you suggesting?
That whether you realized it or not,
you've been covering the ugly truth
about Mr. Allen for years now.
- That is not true.
- Is it true that he was
targeting and harassing Mr. Devoe?
Yes or no?
Yes, which is why
I granted Devoe the restraining order
and told Allen to stay away.
But that didn't stop him, did it?
He kept going after him
right up until the night
- that Mr. Devoe was killed.
- Objection! Conjecture.
Withdrawn.
Captain, now, you said that Mr. Allen
wants to help the
victims, or the innocents.
But disappearing for months at a time
and being late 72 times
doesn't sound like he wants to help
or care for anybody but himself.
Now, do you still think that
he's one of the good ones?
Hope you're right about this.
Oh, trust me,
I'm very good at reading body language.
Right now, you're tense.
Huh, now you're annoyed.
Ooh, here we go.
- Yahtzee.
- Did you get that?
Oh, Ralphie got it.
I smell an acquittal.
As we thought might
happen, we are in trouble.
David's testimony hurt us, but
we still have a few options.
What are they?
I can go to Slater, I
can ask for a plea deal,
maybe get you a shorter sentence.
Or we could use an insanity defense.
No, both those options
are admitting I'm guilty, and I'm not.
Fine, then the only
other way out of this
is for you to testify.
Cecile, I'm sorry, I won't do it.
All of the evidence, every
bit of it, it points to you.
If you're not willing to take
that stand and defend yourself,
then this is an impossible case.
I'm not taking a stand.
Barry, even if that means
turning this case around
and not going to jail?
Iris, if I testify, I have to lie.
I commit perjury, I become
exactly who they think I am.
Then don't lie.
- What?
- Tell the truth.
Tell everyone you're The Flash.
Barry, if the court
knows you're The Flash,
then you can explain everything
and they'll believe you.
Prosecution's gonna wrap up soon.
I need your answer today.
This is the only way, Barry.
Tell the city you're The Flash.
This is all we got?
- This isn't a lot to go on.
- I know, okay?
We're lucky we even got this footage.
- Why?
- For some reason,
all the security cameras were fried.
Hey, guys, I was just at the hospital
going over the medical records
of everyone who was at the bank.
I know why they passed out.
Why did they pass out?
Well, they all suffered from fatigue,
vomiting, abdominal pain, skin rashes.
So everyone ate a bad burrito?
No, radiation poisoning.
That's why the security
cameras are fried.
- Mm-hmm.
- We got to find this guy
before he poisons the whole city.
- Yeah, or worse.
- Hmm?
Guys, if this meta can cause
these levels of radiation
in these patients, that means this meta
has a similar makeup to a nuclear bomb.
So, like, enough to blow us all up?
What are we talking here?
The fallout from a nuclear explosion
could be catastrophic.
- Exactly.
- Fallout.
- Great name.
- Terrible power.
Okay, I'll see if the satellite
can track his radiation signature.
Mrs. Devoe, when did
you first meet Mr. Allen?
Um...
Mr. Allen showed up at my
house almost two months ago
claiming to be investigating
one of Clifford's former colleagues.
We reassured him that we didn't
have information to help him.
But Mr. Allen persisted and
continued to harass my husband.
And what prompted the restraining order?
My husband has...
had advancing ALS.
I was alone with Kevin most of the time.
But something about Mr.
Allen's aggressive manner
just made me feel unsafe, so
we went to the authorities.
And we thought the complaint
would dissuade Mr. Allen.
But it didn't.
Psst.
Could you please describe for the court
the last time that you saw your husband?
It was Christmas.
And Clifford wanted
to confront Mr. Allen.
He had hoped that in the holiday spirit,
he could convince him to let us be.
And I...
I begged Clifford not to go.
But even with his disability,
Clifford insisted that it was his job
as my husband to protect
us, to protect me.
He didn't want to live in fear, so...
He left...
And I wish... I wish
I could have stopped him
and stepped in and
told him not to do this.
But I let him go.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Your Honor, I would like to enter
Exhibit F into evidence.
Objection, Your Honor.
Why wasn't this entered into discovery?
Oh, I've only recently
received this new evidence.
May we approach?
Your Honor, there are protocols
that need to be observed.
This is my courtroom, Mr. Slater.
I'll run it any way I see fit.
I'll allow it.
These photographs were
taken earlier today.
Mrs. Devoe.
Could you tell me please
who is the man that you're
kissing in that photograph?
It is most certainly not
your husband, correct?
His name is Dominic Lanse.
And how long have you known Mr. Lanse?
A few months.
So it appears to me that
perhaps your marriage
was not quite as perfect
as you've portrayed.
Maybe you were ready for a
life without your husband.
So you ran into the arms of another man,
another man you convinced
to kill your husband.
Clifford and I met Dominic Lanse
at an ALS charity gala months ago.
He was there to honor his father,
who had recently passed
away with the disease.
Clifford noticed the bond
that Dominic and I shared,
long before I did.
My husband was happy that
I found someone to talk to,
and he urged me to turn to Dominic
for the needs and comforts
he could no longer fulfill.
My husband wanted me to be happy.
Clifford didn't see my
relationship with Dominic
as a tool to pull us apart
but to bring us together.
And it did.
My heart will always belong to Clifford.
No further questions, Your Honor.
You're excused.
- Okay, that did not go well.
- What's your decision, Barry?
I'm not gonna do it.
Marlize.
Mrs. West-Allen, I don't
think it's appropriate
for the two of us to be seen talking.
Oh, please. No one is watching,
so you can drop that
ridiculous act already.
Hmm.
If you insist.
- Why are you doing this?
- Hmm.
What is wrong with you?
It's not about what's wrong with me.
It's what's wrong with the world.
There are problems
bigger than your husband.
Such as?
Whatever it is that you are up to,
it will come to an end.
Such passion. I had that too
when Clifford and I first got married.
But passion fades, and what remains,
if you are fortunate
enough like Clifford and I,
is something deeper than
ardor that cannot be destroyed.
Then why are you so hell-bent
on destroying our lives?
I am doing what I have to do
for my husband, Mrs. West-Allen.
The question you should truly be asking
is, what are you
willing to do for yours?
Hope you enjoy the rest of the show.
Still no word from the courthouse.
- That's good news, right?
- No news is good news?
No, good news is good news.
No news is miscommunication.
The satellite was able to
track a spike in radiation
downtown on Main Street. We found him.
Fallout's on the move.
We got to get down there now.
I'll monitor him from here.
- Harry, time to book it.
- Yep.
- I got two rads.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, hey, stop!
- Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
What's going on out there?
Nuclear waste tanker.
Sorry!
- Idiots.
- Okay.
Move along.
Mr. Slater, call your next witness.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Your Honor.
There's something you
need to know right now
that will alter the
outcome of this case.
Mrs. West-Allen, I have no idea
what you think you're doing.
Explaining what my husband won't.
Barry Allen is...
The Fla...
What's happening?
We're moving so quickly
that everyone else is still.
How are you able to do this with me?
I actually don't know.
Iris, hey.
I already decided not to
tell anyone else who I am.
Barry, if the jury knew
that you were The Flash,
there is no way that
they would convict you.
I'm trying to protect you, okay?
If everyone knew my secret,
we would never stop running.
I would rather run forever with you
than stand alone without you.
It wouldn't just be us running.
Everyone that has stood
by us the last four years
would have a target on their back.
If criminals knew my name,
they'd know my weakness.
I'm trying to be strong, Barry.
I know.
I can't anymore.
How can you?
My dad. He went through this too.
The trial is not over, Barry.
Yeah, it is.
All the evidence points towards me.
Can't tell them, okay?
Okay.
Yes, Mrs. West-Allen?
Um...
Your Honor...
Barry Allen...
is innocent.
And I just thought you
all should know that.
Thank you for your time. Okay.
If there was an award
for best crocodile tears
by the most emotionally
manipulative widow,
Marlize, definitely in the top three.
Let's snap something more
damning than a lip lock.
We're not here for that.
Can you do your gross stretchy thing
and slip inside and open the door?
Those are carpet fibers.
Those are from Allen's
loft, aren't they?
You're gonna plant
evidence to frame Marlize.
She was the only one
that could have planted Devoe's body.
Fibers on the treads of her shoes
places her at the crime scene.
This is the right thing to do, Ralph.
Just open the door. I'll do the rest.
Okay.
It's a solid plan, Joe.
Subtle, but it's crafty
with a touch of pathos.
After this, you're gonna sit
back and kick up your feet
and sleep as sound as a
millennial after Burning Man
because you did the right thing.
You took down a bad, bad chick.
Ralph, could you hurry up?
And you're gonna ride that feeling
like it's Space Mountain.
And then when they catch you
and they take your badge and your gun,
that self-righteous indignation
is gonna keep your chest
puffed and your chin up
because you did the right thing.
Sure, you're gonna be
mad for a few years,
but that fades.
It evolves,
turns into self-pity.
A few more years, and...
your life is gonna be a
shell of its former self.
And then, one night,
it's gonna dawn on you that
you did the wrong thing.
It's gonna ruin everything.
Your colleagues won't talk to you,
your friends hav hvanished.
And your family?
It'll be like...
Like you were never born.
Because you turned into the very thing
that you swore to protect them from.
Anywho...
Good luck with that.
Mr. Slater?
The prosecution rests, Your Honor.
Ms. Horton, are you ready
to present your case?
The defense rests, Your Honor.
Should've gone with the insanity plea.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
What is going on?
There's a massive spike
in radiation downtown,
at Prentice and Rawlins.
The driver of the nuclear waste truck.
Radiation signature's already
at 3000 rads and climbing.
We need to stop this guy
before it hits 10,000.
What happens at 10,000 rads?
Hiroshima.
Barry Allen has dedicated his life
in service of Central City.
He's helped us solve countless crimes.
His testimony has led to the conviction
of dozens of criminals.
Barry Allen is a good man.
He's an innocent man.
And frankly, Central
City is lucky to have him.
Dare I say...
Few men in this city are as honest,
upstanding, and dependable.
Mr. Allen?
Your Honor, I...
I have to go.
Barry, what are you doing?
I have to.
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
this is an emergency.
Someone needs me.
And I need you to respect my courtroom.
I will not stand for
theatrical disruptions.
Your Honor, uh, my client
is still free on bail.
And there are no laws that require him
to be present during closing statements.
Be advised, Mr. Allen.
You are required by law
to be here for sentencing.
Yes, Your Honor.
Stay where you are!
What is happening to me?
Hold it, right there!
I didn't do anything!
- You need to stop.
- I don't want to hurt anybody.
I understand, but your
radioactivity is dangerous.
- Guys?
- 7,500 rads!
Barry, don't get too
close to him, all right?
The radiation he's emitting
is too hot to allow you to self-heal.
Yeah, thanks for the heads-up.
What am I supposed to
do? How do I stop him?
I can't stop this!
- Oh, damn.
- We need to cool him down.
Killer Frost.
- Great.
- Well, go, turn!
Well, that's not how it works.
I can't just snap my
fingers and make her appear.
It only happens when
I'm scared or angry.
Oh, good Lord, Caitlin.
The city's about to explode!
Everyone, everything you know and love,
the birds, the trees, the fish,
the puppies!
The puppies are going down
because you didn't want to...
Show up for work!
Thanks.
- That was pretty good, yeah?
- That was pretty good.
- Now go already!
- Okay!
Okay, there you go.
What's going on?
Is this business or a social call?
Business, I see.
- She okay?
- She's gonna be okay, yeah.
Do you have any more ideas?
Where do I breach him?
Ramon, no, you...
You drop him a breach, he could explode.
And Fallout's fallout would kill us all.
Do you think?
Wait, what if I create
a vacuum around him?
That way, even if he does explode,
at least we contain the blast.
Yeah, yes, Allen, yes.
That... that could work,
that could contain it.
Whatever you're gonna
do, though, do it fast.
Fallout just went above 8,000 rads.
The vacuum's containing his energy.
Good.
But he's still getting stronger.
Allen, I don't know long
you can take this much radiation.
I don't have a choice.
We have to contain his energy.
Allen, 9,000 rads.
10,000 rads, critical mass.
Ramon, you need to send
that energy somewhere.
What? To where?
Earth-15, Earth-15 is a dead Earth.
Breach it there now!
- You did it.
- Oh, man, you did it.
You saved the day.
Ladies and gentleman of the jury,
you've reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
All rise.
For Docket Number 5567-B,
in the matter of The People
vs. Bartholomew Henry Allen,
we, the jury, find the defendant
guilty of murder in the first degree.
Thanks to your meta metabolism,
your radiation burns should disappear
in the next few minutes.
- What about Fallout?
- He's unstable,
but we sent him to Tracy's lab.
She's gonna analyze his DNA,
see if it's the same
as the other best metas
and then we'll be
able to neutralize him.
Superior Court, where minutes ago,
the jury found Bartholomew Henry Allen
guilty in the murder of
Professor Clifford Devoe.
Mr. Allen has been a CSI
with the Central City Police Department
for the last five years.
In just a few short hours,
the judge is expected to announce
Mr. Allen's sentence.
Prosecutor Anton Slater made a statement.
He hoped Mr. Allen would
receive a life sentence,
given the brutal nature of the cri...
I wanted to be the one to tell you.
I can't believe this is happening.
Come on, guys, we just
saved the city today.
We knew this wasn't
gonna go my way in court.
That doesn't mean that Devoe beat us.
Whatever happens, we're
gonna keep fighting.
I know.
We need to get you back.
You need to be there for sentencing.
Yeah.
I'll see you guys later, all right?
I'm gonna be okay, all right?
Come on.
You know you got your strength
from watching your dad be your rock?
I got mine because...
you're mine.
I'll be strong for you.
I love you.
Come on.
- Allen...
- Step back.
Yeah, I need a minute, all right?
Mrs. Allen, did you expect this?
Mr. Allen.
Devoe.
Did you know there was a 12% chance
that you were gonna tell
the world you're The Flash?
I'd recheck your math.
There's no need.
Because no matter what path you chose,
all avenues led to my triumph.
Why do you want us distracted?
Why do you want me out of the picture?
What are you planning?
At you think that you could understand
the breadth of what I'm about
to do is almost humorous.
Yes, I think you will miss Iris.
That's right, Mr. Allen.
I didn't just take Dominic's body.
I took his ability.
I know what you're thinking right now.
Well, I want you to hear me say it.
I'm gonna figure a way out of this.
And when I do,
I don't care who's face you're wearing.
I'm coming for you.
You haven't beaten us yet.
Haven't I?
Have a nice life, Mr. Allen.
Your Honor, I'm innocent.
I didn't do this, I didn't kill anyone.
And I know that one day,
the truth will come out.
Thank you.
Rise for sentencing.
In my 30 years behind this bench,
I have seen my share of criminals.
But I confess this
defendant stands apart.
Thank you all for coming
on such short notice.
A few hours ago, the
very existence of our city
came under the threat
of nuclear destruction.
But one man rose to meet that challenge.
The defendant was in a
position of authority.
Our city trusted him to
bring the guilty to justice.
He ran into danger,
knowing he would suffer
burns all over his body.
He used that trust to take an
innocent and vulnerable life.
This man was not thinking about himself.
He was thinking about you.
The first responders on the front lines.
Never have I seen a
defendant more unmoved.
man with more bravery.
Never have I seen such inhumanity.
Such heroism.
Such a lack of regard for human life.
It is my great honor to present
Central City Police Department's
Award of Valor
to this city's finest hero.
The fastest man alive, The Flash!
The court hereby orders
that Bartholomew Henry Allen
should be incarcerated
for the rest of his natural life,
without the possibility of parole
and that Mr. Allen be
immediately remanded
to Iron Heights Penitentiary.
And may God have mercy on your soul.
Be seeing you around, B!
Get comfortable.
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --