Howdy, boys.
Oh, sorry. sorry, sorry, sorry.
How are you guys doing? Good?
Why don't you go have a smoke
or something, okay?
I got this.
Oh, and you guys...
you are the real heroes.
Gentlemen.
All clear, boys. Mission accomplished.
God bless America.
Captain.
I found this.
The Islamic State is not exactly
a hotbed of scientific expertise.
But they've counterfeited
this Compound V shit of yours?
It seems that way, Mr Secretary.
How did they get the formula?
Honestly, we have no idea.
Well, you must have some idea.
Some tourist shoplift it from your lab?
Or maybe an inside job?
Sir, we would like to get to the bottom of this
as much as you would.
Ms Stillwell, if I had my way,
the Justice Department
would haul your smug, tennis-toned ass
into Congress and make you testify
to corporate fraud.
What is Lockheed Martin's number one product?
Sorry?
Its top seller.
You should know this,
you served on their board of directors.
- The Patriot missile.
- Correct.
Northrop?
B-2 Stealth.
General Dynamics?
Tomahawk and the M1 Abrams.
Billions of dollars of bleeding-edge hardware.
Do you know what all of that is as of today?
A worthless pile of shit.
Because Naqib and other super terrorists like him
can flick away that junk like flicking a flea.
So it doesn't matter
where heroes really come from.
Frankly, it doesn't even matter
how the enemy got the Compound V.
What matters is they've got it.
It is a whole new world now.
And there is only one company
that has the product to fight back.
My company.
My product.
What can I say? The Pentagon's agreed
to keep Compound V classified.
Classified?
What the fuck are you on about?
Because of the Naqib asshole that is out there,
we have to keep Vought happy now.
Vought are the ones that fucking created the cunt.
- We have no solid proof on that.
- No hard proof?
I fucking well rescued
the proof from a basement.
She's sitting on a bloody bog as we speak.
Listen. Listen.
Vought's manufacturing super villains.
It's the story of the century.
Don't you want a fucking Pulitzer?
Well, fuck you, too, then.
Susan, come on.
There must be something we can do here, yeah?
Look, the military deal is signed and sealed.
Do you think one mute girl
is going to derail that?
Especially coming from the fugitives
- that killed Translucent?
- Fugitives?
Vought insisted and... And the DOJ agreed.
You're wanted men now.
Hello?
This isn't a day spa.
Other people got to use the facilities.
Look, I gave you the V.
I gave you everything you asked for and more.
I trusted you, and this is
the fucking thanks I get.
Butcher, I will still protect your families.
Yeah, and keep your bleeding career even safer.
Well, what about me and the Boys, then, eh?
You cut bait and run for your lives.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Right.
All right, then, love.
Well, that's all under control, isn't it?
We need to split up.
Oi, what the fuck are you doing?
We ain't done yet.
The hell we ain't. We got Vought, the Supes,
and the feds on our asses.
I'm going to Montreal.
How you gonna get
your crazy-ass girlfriend over the border?
She has a name.
It's Kimiko. Okay?
- Kimiko.
- Oi, listen.
Shut your fucking traps.
We're on the verge of nailing these cunts.
And you want to cut bait and run
before we've played our final card.
Okay, what is it, man?
Give us a couple hours. Yeah?
Hughie, you're with me.
Come on, son.
Chop-chop.
Annie.
You scared me.
You didn't say you were coming.
I hid this under my floorboards
right after Daddy left.
I thought that maybe he would come back
for it, but...
- Still smells like him.
- It was a bad habit.
His father smoked a pipe,
so, you know...
What's Compound V?
Compound V?
I don't know, sweetheart. Should I?
How old was I?
How old was I when you let
Vought pump me full of drugs?
- Annie, honestly, I don't know what...
- How old
when you let them turn me into a freak?
You're not a freak.
Never say that.
So it's true.
Annie...
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Did Vought tell you all this?
- No. No. A friend told me.
How much did they pay you?
- It wasn't about money.
- How much?
There was no money.
They just paid for the medical bills, that's it.
I did it because they, they promised
that you'd have a chance at an extraordinary life.
To be strong and successful and special.
I mean, who wouldn't want that for their...?
You made me think that I was chosen by God.
You were!
God brought Vought into our lives.
He made this possible.
Bullshit!
You did!
And then you controlled every single minute of it.
You woke me up at 5 a.m.
to train for those stupid pageants,
and the tap dancing and the tae kwon do.
I gave up every moment of my life.
And I was happy to do it.
- This was our dream.
- This was your dream!
I never got a chance
to choose my own dreams.
No wonder I don't know who
the fuck I'm supposed to be!
Annie.
Was it really bad investments?
- What?
- You told me that Daddy left
because he lost all of our savings.
He agreed to all of it.
And then, one day, he didn't,
so he walked out on us.
Maybe he didn't want to lie to me.
So I'm the monster?
You have a good life.
People would give anything to be what you are.
I thought I did what was right.
Annie, Annie.
Annie! Annie!
It's time to knock back some
of this per diem, buddy.
Oh, it's a pretty fancy bottle.
What are we celebrating?
What are you talking about?
The Seven getting called up.
Yeah.
You know the whole reason the Navy discontinued
their sea mammal mine clearance programme?
It's because it cost way too much
to train the fucking dolphins.
Yeah.
But with me onboard,
it's like a pick-up game of basketball.
I've always wanted to lead my own unit, Jeff.
It's like a dream come true for me.
Smells like a comeback.
Anyways...
Cheers, buddy.
So, when?
When, what?
When do I ship out?
Gosh.
You know that water park's
opening up a new splash zone,
and they are real excited
to have you cut that ribbon.
You know, I'm seriously leaving, Jeff.
Fuck Ohio.
Here's the sitch.
I talked to New York.
And... you're not.
So much.
Leaving.
What?
They didn't share details.
But hey, look...
the boys in Marketing have
created a primo tag for you:
The Saviour of Sandusky!
That has a nice ring, doesn't it?
William.
What are you looking at out there?
Eastern meadowlarks.
It was either bird-watching or alcoholism, so...
birds.
I thought we agreed that you
were never going to come out here.
Yeah, well, you taught me a thing or two
about broken promises.
Didn't you?
This is Hugh Campbell.
We're working with M.M. and Frenchie.
I got the Boys back together.
Grace Mallory.
I'm the founder of your little club.
- You're...
- So, let me hear it.
I need your help.
Sorry, I can't.
I'm hoping to photograph
a snowy owl in the dunes.
Look...
I didn't want to come here,
but I need your help.
And you're going to fucking help.
Why's that?
Because you owe me.
You fucking owe me, goddamn it.
Look at you, mon coeur.
Run! Run!
Who's got eyes on her?
Over here!
Good job.
We won't let her get away.
This is Alpha Team. Suspect is in custody.
There's simply nothing else to say.
I can't help you.
You're gonna have to do better than that.
- Do I? Why?
- Because you made me a promise.
But then my grandchildren got incinerated.
Tends to change one's perspective.
There weren't even teeth left,
Lamplighter had burnt them alive so thoroughly.
Well,
I think I've had enough sun for one day.
Pleasure meeting you, Hugh.
Butcher.
Well, what about what you've done?
What I've done?
To who?
To me, goddamn it. To me.
You trained me up, manipulated me,
aimed me at Homelander like a fucking howitzer.
And then when it didn't suit you anymore,
you just threw me away.
And not a day goes by I don't regret it.
Day late, dollar short, love.
Now, I'm going to finish what you started,
and I need your help.
Please.
You can leave with something,
if you never come back
and you keep your goddamn promise this time.
Madelyn Stillwell.
Vought's VP?
- Homelander's her main account.
- Yeah, that ain't news.
No, but this is:
They have a... What shall we say?
A very special relationship.
Complicated, intimate, hard to quantify.
And you know this how?
Still have a few fingers in a few pies.
I don't know if Homelander has a weakness,
but if he does, she'll know it.
Goodbye, Grace.
You want to kill yourself, that's your right...
I won't stop you, but, Billy, not the others.
Vengeance isn't a path to glory, Hugh.
It's a one-way ticket to a dead end,
looking at fucking birds.
No, go ahead. Sure.
- Dude. Dude, it's A-Train.
- Really?
It's fucking A-Train.
- Can I help you?
- I'm just keeping an eye out.
That's funny, it really looks like
you're only keeping an eye on me.
You know I'm A-Train, right?
Yeah, and I'm Homelander.
Dude, whip back to A-Train.
Listen, I'm sorry about that.
We're good.
Wait, so now that you...?
Now you know I'm A-Train, now we're good?
Listen, man, I'm sorry. It was my mistake.
Yeah, you're damn right it's your mistake.
I'm A-Train.
I'm the fastest fucking man alive!
What are you all fucking looking at?
- You missed it.
- Eyes front.
Eyes fucking front, Hughie.
- Boys are gone.
- What?
Someone's grabbed them.
Oh, yeah? How do you know that?
The window's new, the path is scrubbed,
and there's a black van with "Flowers" on it,
probably full of cunts waiting to jump us.
- Vought?
- Nah, someone else doing
their dirty work for them,
probably some fed black ops unit.
Okay. Okay, what are we...?
What are we gonna do?
How are we gonna get the guys back?
We're on our own. We've got to get to Stillwell
- before the walls close in.
- Who gives a fuck?
- We have to go back.
- You don't get it.
We got about a couple hours before they find us,
and that's if we're lucky.
We got to hit back and hit back now.
You're abandoning them.
I mean, they all... They risked their...
Mother's Milk has a daughter.
- They'd want us to finish the job.
- Your job.
Your job, not theirs.
It's all about Homelander, isn't it?
And A-Train. This is your
fucking shit, too, Hughie.
I promised you payback, didn't I?
Mallory give you the same speech
back in the day?
Yeah. Yeah, she did.
But she broke her promise.
I'm keeping mine.
I'm so fucking stupid.
You never cared about me.
Or Robin, did you?
I was just useful to you.
Fuck, Hughie. Of course you're useful.
I mean, that's why you're here, isn't it?
Now we just got to take one more step.
Yeah?
Come on.
No.
We have to save them.
For fuck's sakes, Hughie, we don't have time
for this shit right now, okay?
We get Stillwell. Now, get in the fucking car.
Then what?
Becca comes back from the dead?
Robin, too?
This is never gonna stop,
it's just gonna be more blood
and... awfulness.
That's the fucking game.
If you don't like to play,
why did you join the fucking team?
Mallory's right, you're just
gonna drag us all down with you.
Not me.
Not anymore.
You're a fucking pathetic cunt
and an insult to Robin's memory.
I think I'm doing this for her.
Goodbye, Hughie.
Fucking idiot.
Stupid fucker.
Fuck.
Idiot.
Stupid fucking idiot.
I remember you telling me
you like to come here to listen
to the choir rehearse,
so I figured I'd take a shot.
You've got a lot of balls.
Just two.
I mean, you must want me to arrest you.
Actually...
Annie... I need your help.
- Please just listen to me.
- Why?
More awful secrets you want to tell me,
more drugs that I was dosed
with as a kid, maybe?
That just came out. I'm sorry.
I thought you wanted to know the truth.
Oh, okay, so you're all about the truth.
Vought is giving Compound V
to some bad fucking people, like really bad.
Like, that Supe terrorist.
That's insane.
No, it's true.
Look, my friends want to stop it,
but they got caught
on Vought's orders, and I figured,
because you had security clearance,
maybe you could help find them.
Hughie, I was almost arrested
just for knowing you.
I had to convince them that I was an idiot
that you threw out
and you used, and now you want me
to help your psycho killer friends?
When you put it like that...
You have 30 seconds to get the hell out of here.
Okay.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I mean, why the hell would I ever help you?
Because Vought's up to some evil shit?
Because it's your job.
Because you're a superhero.
Really?
I can't remember the last time I saved anyone.
You saved me.
When did I ever save you?
Bowling alley.
What are you talking about?
I was angry after Robin.
I was headed for this cliff,
and then you and me went bowling.
Bowling?
Yeah.
Bowling.
That's it.
That's not saving you, that's just being there.
The thing is...
I don't care.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Doc said six weeks minimum
after a fracture like that.
I'm all good, man.
Look, I'm back to training.
I feel fucking great.
- You're healed?
- I'm healed.
How the fuck are you...?
You back on that Compound V.
You promised me that you would stay clean.
No. I am clean.
A-1, all-natural A-Train, baby.
Your fucking bones fused back
together overnight?
- That sound natural to you?
- Maybe I'm just strong.
- Oh, yeah.
- I am the world's fastest man.
Bet you can't outrun this.
Hey. Wait, hey, where you going?
I'm not gonna sit here and
watch you kill yourself.
You know what? I don't need this shit.
You've always just been jealous of me,
so go ahead, slow-ass fucking loser.
I'm just, yeah, I'm just gonna...
- There he is!
- Our hero.
Stop it.
Stop, please.
Amazing. Great job, everybody.
- You're gonna make me blush here.
- Madelyn?
- Stop, please.
- Mr Edgar.
I didn't know you were gonna come.
Let me borrow you for a moment.
The Pentagon's shelling out
north of $40 billion per year.
You should enjoy a bonus that reflects that.
I don't know what to say.
Well, say thank you.
Thank you.
Don't get too excited.
It comes with strings.
You're gonna need to move
your office down to 82.
- That's your floor.
- And...
I'm gonna want you to start
riding shotgun on my meetings.
Hey, don't go planning my retirement yet.
I'm just saying, someone needs to run
this shit show when I move to Belize.
Enjoy yourself, Madelyn.
Start thinking about the view from 82.
Thank you.
Electricity goes in, blast comes out.
That's a hell of a party trick.
Do you ever use it for fun?
Can I tell you a secret?
Sometimes, my eyes light up when I...
you know.
Will you excuse me?
Just a second.
You want me to hold your hair back?
Don't touch.
Leave me alone, I'm not in the mood.
Not in the mood for what?
Your bottomless casual cruelty.
So just make whatever shitty comment
you're gonna make and then go.
Look.
What am I supposed to be looking at?
No... my radius never healed straight.
I really did break every bone in my right arm.
- What?
- Stopping the bus from falling.
You said the Marketing guys made it up.
It was me.
Twenty-three-year-old, bright-eyed,
ass you could bounce a quarter off of...
me.
I really did want to make a difference.
I really did care.
I was just like you.
And then...
I started giving pieces of myself away...
and I guess I gave away everything.
So you know what? Be...
Just be original.
For fuck's sake.
My position is already taken.
Be the annoying goody two-shoes
asshole that you are.
One of us has to be.
You've been avoiding me.
- No, I haven't.
- Really?
Seems that way.
You do know that I went to see Vogelbaum,
though...
right?
And you do know what he told me?
I never meant for you to find out that way.
Let me guess.
You wanted to protect me.
Well, we all did.
Of course.
You think I'm fragile?
No, I do not.
You try doing any of this...
I mean fucking any of it.
...without me.
I couldn't.
Madelyn.
Did it ever occur to you...
that a Supe terrorist showing up
exactly when we needed him to was...
a pretty fucking incredible coincidence?
It's almost like...
someone planned it.
Me.
I made him.
What do you mean you "made him"?
Well, I borrowed some Compound V,
had A-Train run it all over the globe,
and I supercharged some jihadis.
Not to oversimplify it.
I mean, it was actually very difficult
and very messy, using adult subjects.
There's a good reason that Vought doesn't do it.
But... well, enough survived
to call the operation a huge success.
Huge.
And now...
we have villains all over the globe...
that only we can fight.
In sequel after sequel...
after sequel.
Well?
Say something.
No.
Take off your pants.
Sit down.
- Gentle.
- I'm...
No.
Oh, my sweet boy.
My special, special, sweet boy.
I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- No, you did good.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, my boy.
I'm proud of you.
That was so lovely.
Well, you know, in mediaeval times,
they locked prisoners inside a pillory barrel.
Then they'd kneel in their own excrement
till they got sepsis and died, so...
Thank you, Frenchie,
for that disgusting
yet fascinating piece of trivia.
I'm just saying it could be worse, huh?
Right.
Why didn't you tell us?
Tell you what?
That you had a daughter.
I don't know.
I mean...
I guess she's...
the only good thing I ever did, man.
I just wanted just to leave her
clean out of it, you know?
But I fucked that up to high heaven.
Probably never see her again.
I understand.
She made you a better person.
Hey, man.
Kimiko's gonna be okay.
So you do know her name.
Do you like that?
No.
Mr Edgar came to the party tonight
and he practically offered me his job.
Well, not right away. But he...
wants me to move to the 82nd floor
so that I can be closer to him.
Really?
Okay, but you'll still be my day-to-day, right?
Yeah. Yeah, of course. Of course.
I will be there for you always.
Okay, good.
Good.
Madelyn.
From now on, no more secrets.
- Promise me.
- I promise.
No more secrets.
Okay.
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you about your baby.
It's just that...
you carry so much...
and the pain of losing a child to...
miscarriage is...
I just wanted to spare you that burden.
Do you understand?
Yes.
What the fuck?
Hey, easy with him, man.
Fuck wrong with you? Shit.
- Bitch ass.
- You okay? You break any bones?
- No, no. No.
- No?
Did they get Butcher, too?
- No.
- They got you separated?
When? When?
Well...
he went after Homelander.
But I...
I came to save you.
So, you came here?
You meant to come here?
- Without Butcher.
- Yeah.
Never has a man thrown his life away
so completely
like you've thrown yours away today.
No...
no, what I mean is, you rescuing us
is the most useless,
futile gesture I can think of.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Unbelievable.
- All right, so what's the plan?
- Okay.
All right, so they searched me.
Very, very thoroughly.
But I managed to Poligrip
in my 12th grade retainer.
- Let me see.
- It looks like a permanent bridge,
- and it totally worked.
- Shit.
Frenchie, you can pick a lock
with anything, right?
There's premium metal wire
in this thing.
- Come on, take it out.
- Okay, one second.
Come on, man. Spit that bitch out.
It's stuck.
- Okay, okay, stand still.
- Wait, what?
- Stand still. Open.
- What...?
Open the mouth.
Come on, get up in there, Frenchie.
Just go deeper. Just a little deeper.
All right, all right, all right, hold...
What the fuck, man?
Let me get this. Let me get this.
Relax, okay?
- Look. Look, focus. Focus.
- Okay, okay. What?
- I'm gonna knock that bitch out your mouth. Okay?
- We're not at that step yet.
- We don't have to do that.
- It's just gonna sting a little bit. All right?
- Sting?
- On three.
- One to three.
- Okay, if you count down...
You all right?
You okay, buddy?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Good job, Hughie.
Good night, Ms Stillwell.
Good night, Miles.
Maria.
Maria, I'm home.
Maria?
Your kid's a sound sleeper.
Don't worry.
He's all right.
So is the nanny.
She's out the back sleeping off
a little bit of propofol.
Put your phone on the table.
William Butcher.
CIA showed me your file.
- What do you want?
- You know what I want.
I don't know how breaking into my home
and threatening my child
is gonna get you Homelander.
All these years...
I've been searching
for that cunt's weakness.
He doesn't have any weakness.
- No?
- There isn't a weapon on Earth
that they haven't thrown at him.
They've all failed.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking... about you.
Me?
Yeah, you're the only thing
he gives two shits about.
You're his weakness.
It's a fucking maze.
Where is she?
Ready... go on.
Mon coeur.
Frenchie, what the fuck?
Fuck! Move. Move.
Fuck.
- No! God.
- Just stay down.
Oh, fuck.
She better be fucking worth it.
Wait, what?
- You cover him. Cover him!
- Wait, what?
No, I don't... I can't do this.
- You just pull the fucking trigger right now!
- Okay!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Shit, it's out, it's out. What do I do?
Take this. Take it.
- Reload.
- What the fuck do I know about reloading?
- Reload the magazine.
- How do I do that? Okay.
- Let's go.
- Good? It's good.
M.M.! M.M.!
M.M.!
Go!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm out.
- Oh, shit.
- Drop your weapon!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- On your knees.
- Don't shoot.
- On your fucking knees!
Face the wall!
Hands on your heads!
You came.
Like you said...
I'm a fucking superhero.
Come on.
Hughie, check the doors.
Is it working?
- No, no, no.
- Fuck.
Try this.
Yes.
- Son of a...
- Go, go, go.
- Go. Go, go, go.
- Holy shit.
Oh, shit. Go.
- Hughie, let's go.
- Go! I'll be okay. Go.
Homelander was right.
You are a fucking rat.
Oh, and you're the jailbreaker?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Turn around and walk away, A-Train.
- I got this. Go.
- No. I'm the one he wants.
I'm not leaving you.
Please, just go.
Hughie!
You killed the only person I've ever loved.
I didn't kill her.
I know.
I did.
But it was your fault.
Holy shit.
What? What?
I think he's having a heart attack.
Oh, fuck.
All right.
One, two, three.
Call an ambulance.
One...
He'll never stop coming for you.
I know.
This is Starlight.
I have a code 78-65. A-Train is down.
I think he's had a heart attack.
You have to go. I'll take over.
Hughie, go!
Or else you'll get caught.
Well, well, well.
About fucking time.
I know you can see through the ceiling.
You try to kill me...
and my trigger finger goes soft.
Now... why don't you stop playing rapey Santa...
and come down and join us?
Take it easy.
We don't want to upset Teddy, right?
What are you doing?
Hey, look. Mommy.
- You all right? Madelyn...
- No.
- Take him upstairs.
- All good. I got it.
I got it.
Billy Butcher.
You don't mind if I call you Billy, right?
You are pretty darn impressive.
I mean, especially for, you know, one of you.
See, even now, most people
standing where you are
would be pissing their pants terrified, but you...
Sure, your heart's pounding,
but you're not afraid.
It's anger.
That's a new one for me.
Homelander, will you please
take the baby upstairs?
All because of your lovely wife Becca.
Right?
Okay. Let's cut the bullshit, huh?
You know that we...
Bro, not my fault, okay?
- She came on to me. It happens.
- Will you stop?
You know, it's the fame. They get crushes.
There's nothing I can do about it.
But what I will tell you is,
she was a hell of a lay.
She came three times, eh?
Three times.
All right, little man, have a little lie-down.
Good boy.
I want you to take him out of here.
There you go.
But that's not really it.
No, no, no.
No, it's more than just that.
You think I'm responsible
for her death, don't you?
So now you have a hostage
that I care about, right?
Someone I love.
So, what's your plan... from here?
What do you want?
Do you want a confession, or...?
What's your endgame?
I'm just gonna hurt you.
I mean really fucking hurt you,
and that will be good enough for me.
So, you don't really want anything, per se?
You just... You want to blow her
up in front of me.
Right?
Wow, fuck.
You are dark, and I kind of like it.
Will you please take Teddy upstairs?
It's okay.
Just answer one question for me.
Just one.
How do you know?
I mean, you must have
some rock-solid proof, right?
That it was actually me who killed your wife.
You must have that, right? So what is it?
Share. We're all very interested.
Now's not the time to be strong and silent.
Go for it.
Are you telling me that this whole thing
is based on fucking feelings?
- On a hunch?
- Will you please
- take him upstairs?
- A little bit... Hold on.
- Take him upstairs!
- Shut the fuck up!
Excuse me.
You promised me no more lies.
You fucking promised me.
You and Vogelbaum should have
got your stories straight.
They were so close.
So fucking close, but there was a few
little details that were different.
So I went back to Vogelbaum,
and I managed to squeeze the truth out of him.
The real truth.
Yes, that's it.
I'm so sorry.
I should never have lied to you.
I know now that you don't need
to be protected.
I'm so sorry.
Will you please take Teddy upstairs?
Did you ever really care about me?
You mean everything to me.
No.
No, no.
I mean everything to your job.
You care more about that fucking baby
- than you do about me.
- No.
I love you.
I love you. I love you. I swear I love you.
But?
Tell me the truth, or I walk out right now.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of you.
What?
I said I'm scared.
- Of?
- Of you.
I'm scared of you.
Thank you.
Thank you for finally being honest.
Now...
what was that plan again?
Oh, well...
Wakey, wakey.
Hey, buddy.
You were out for quite a while.
You can thank me
for saving you sometime later,
but, for now,
time to get up.
Come on. You're gonna love this.
Come on.
Mom!
Wow, look at this handsome devil.
Hey, pal.
You know who I am?
Homelander.
Yeah, that's right...
but you know who else?
No.
Becca?
What?
Mommy didn't tell you.
Well...
I'm your father,
and we are a family.