You little brats, beat it!
Hey!
It should have been me!
I should be the one
going to that Jap's house.
You'll miss the train.
Hurry.
PART ONE
Kouzuki Noriaki
Go back to sleep.
We're still far from the house.
Pleased to meet you. I am Okju.
This property has three buildings.
A Western-style wing by
an English architect
and a Japanese wing form the main house.
Not even in Japan is there
a building combining two styles.
It reflects Master's
admiration for Japan and England.
Next is the annex
which Master had furnished as a library.
Last, the servants' quarters.
As the Lady's handmaiden,
you won't sleep there.
You may eat her leftover food,
but tea leaves go to the kitchen girls.
Used soap is for the steward.
Anyone caught pilfering
is expelled that day.
I'm sure you wouldn't dare, Tamako.
Huh.
"Tamako" is you.
Your name Okju in Japanese.
We live in the Japanese style here.
Speak Japanese to the Master and Lady.
- Call me Sasaki.
- Yes, ma'am.
I don't trust new servants.
Even if they make a good impression,
if the house burns down, they'll
run away with a manuscript.
The Lady's routine is simple.
Taking a walk, or reading for Master.
Among the richest men,
Master is the greatest book lover.
And among book lovers, he is the richest.
His ties to the colonial government
even let us use electricity.
In such a home,
you know what's expected
of a maid like you?
Don't be alarmed at the blackouts.
I sleep in here?
Miss Hideko wakes easily
on account of her nerves.
She's behind this door?
Shh!
Mother!
Ah!
Miss!
Miss, are you all right?
Junko! Is that you?
Junko was kicked out, Miss.
I'm the new girl.
Seems you had a bad dream.
You see that big cherry tree?
My aunt went mad and hanged herself there.
Sometimes on moonless nights,
my aunt's ghost
dangles from that branch.
Here, drink up.
When babies cry, my auntie
feeds them a spoonful of sake.
Sweet bird, sweet bird
My sweet bluebird
What scent is this that fills my nose?
- What?
- Coming back from the toilet,
I saw a light going down the hallway.
That's it! They're meeting in her room.
Or else it's the ghost
of the cherry tree?
Those fuckers.
This is Tamako.
I am at your service. Miss...
A reference letter
from Lady Minami, my last mistress.
So is this place to your liking?
The sun scarcely ever shines here.
Uncle won't permit it.
Sunlight causes books to fade.
One could never grow fond
of such a dreary place.
Not a good liar, are you?
We look a bit alike.
Are you also an orphan?
- Uh...
- I'll take my leave.
Whereas in my case,
my aunt and Mrs. Sasaki
showed me how the love
of a mother...
isn't worth a thing.
My head aches
before every reading practice.
Would you read it to me?
Pardon?
Oh, how kind of her.
Lady Minami said such
nice things about me!
Is that so?
You're a Japanese lady,
why don't you speak Japanese?
I'm sick of it.
The books he makes me read
are all Japanese.
So read that for me.
"Dear Miss lzumi Hideko,
"Count Fujiwara said
you're looking for a maid.
"Maids are like
"a spoon..." No...
"Are like chopsticks..."
Is it a spoon?
I don't know how to read, Miss.
Not at all? What about Korean?
This is your name.
Can't you read it?
Reading can be learned,
and I don't care if you curse or steal.
But don't ever lie to me. Understood?
Yes, Miss.
My mom.
She's beautiful, quite the charmer!
And me? Am I "quite the charmer"?
Everyone says I can't compare to my mother.
Count Fujiwara said...
So you've met the Count?
Pardon?
No, I never met him...
My aunt! I heard it from my aunt.
She was his nanny.
What did the Count say about me?
He said your face...
Every night in bed he
thinks of your assets...
Your face.
Why in bed, I wonder?
What's with your foot?
I've nowhere to go.
I've just stayed in this house
since coming to Korea at age five.
But in new shoes,
even well-trodden paths feel fresh.
The ones from here
up to here should fit you.
Why not the prettiest ones?
Like these?
Time for reading practice.
I'll go alone.
Miss? But rain is falling.
At noon, come knock on the door.
Promise?
See you at...
What's this?
My new handmaiden.
The snake, the snake!
You mustn't pass that point.
Be warned!
The snake marks the bounds of knowledge.
He has the habit of licking his plume
when he thinks,
otherwise he's someone clean.
What kind of servant would
hog the umbrella like you?
Pardon?
Miss!
These books make me sink.
They bore me to death.
Do you read so many books?
You'll become a professor
in no time then.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Pardon.
The Count?
Today?
That's why you insisted on a bath.
My aunt, when she heard
a guest was coming,
dropped everything
and bathed her baby, Miss.
Nothing made her happier than
when guests praised her baby's scent.
You are my baby, Miss.
Auntie gave the babies candy during baths.
To teach them that bath time is sweet.
What's wrong?
One of my teeth is sharp.
It keeps cutting me.
So this was the scent.
All smooth.
Welcome, sir!
You are too kind to greet me
this way upon my arrival,
when the journey has left me so unkempt.
Now your tedium is over.
I'll ensure your painting lessons
are stimulating.
This must be Okju.
At your service, milord.
You know if you fail,
it'll put me in an awkward position?
A decent bone structure for a Korean...
So, are you carrying out
your duties faithfully?
Thank you for your recommendation.
You chose a perfect servant for me.
You wouldn't want one who's too stupid.
I did my best.
Take good care of our dear Lady.
Take this.
Count Fujiwara asks Miss Hideko
to kindly allow her maid Tamako
to be sent to his Lordship
for a brief errand.
- Did you call for me, milord?
- You may enter.
Do you think you can fool me with this?
Who do you take me for?
You think I'm Tamako,
a poor Korean handmaiden.
But my real name's Nam Sookee.
Raised by Miss Boksun,
top purveyor of stolen goods.
I was able at age five
to tell a real coin from a fake.
Then learned to forge stamps from Gugai,
and studied pickpocketing from Kutan,
but these babies will never
learn such useful skills.
Abandoned as newborns,
we'll wash and feed them,
then sell them to Japan.
Such meaningful work.
Instead of starving, they grow up
gentlemen and ladies.
Kutan only breastfeeds her own kid.
I wouldn't be so miserly.
I wish my breasts gave milk.
I'd breastfeed all of them.
Milord!
I'll tell you the story of an interpreter,
who bribed his way into
translating for high officials.
After helping Japan annex Korea,
he got rights to a gold mine.
Now he wants to turn fully Japanese.
So he gets naturalized,
marries the daughter
of a fallen Japanese noble,
and adopts his wife's family name Kouzuki.
Ba... Bas...
Bastard builds a mansion,
fills it with books and antiques.
He invites Japanese
collectors to his library,
holds readings of rare books,
and auctions the books off.
He loves books and paintings
like his own flesh,
but he can't help parting with a few.
What to do, when he must sell,
but can't bear to?
He sells a fake.
He seeks out a specialist
to create intricate forgeries.
Unlike him, this specialist
is a real Japanese, of noble birth!
Count Fujiwara from Nagoya.
So, who is this?
It's the wife. His Japanese wife.
- You'll seduce her...
- Is she pretty?
The Jap wife died ages
ago with no children.
But the dead wife's
dead sister's living daughter
performs those book readings.
But is she pretty?
An orphan. Her father was rich.
Soon she'll fall in love with me,
and we'll elope to Japan.
After marrying her there,
and inheriting her fortune,
I'll declare her insane
and lock her up in a madhouse.
Right!
Sookee will be my mouse,
work as her maid, eavesdrop on her,
stay by her side and gently
persuade her to fall in love.
Love?
What does a crook know about love?
What of her fortune? She's rich?
Each night in bed
I think of her assets.
1.5 million in cash. 300,000 in bonds.
The uncle is just a guardian.
It's Hideko's fortune.
That's why Kouzuki
schemes to marry the girl.
To his wife's niece?
What a sick...
Right, a sick fuck.
So what's our share?
I'll share 50,000.
Sookee gets the dresses and jewelry.
I'll do it! Take me!
My Japanese is better,
and I worked as a maid!
On top of the fifty,
I get dresses, jewelry and my own 100,000.
B- b-beautiful!
I'm flummoxed in your presence!
If you stutter like that
and make your face go red,
those uppity bitches will feel superior,
and then they'll open up to you, all right?
Watch how to make your face blush:
Breathe in deep and
squeeze your stomach tight,
lower your chin
and contract your asshole,
don't breath, and swallow
your saliva ten times.
Got it?
Go ahead.
The blue kimono
with the white peonies,
or the black one with
the drawings of cranes?
The shit-colored one with caterpillars,
or the caterpillar-colored one
with drawings of shit?
Don't ask her opinion!
Questions make her think.
You're the one who should be
thinking for her!
That's how you dominate your mistress,
got it?
Yes.
This is the letter. Listen closely.
"Dear Miss lzumi Hideko,
"Count Fujiwara said
you're looking for a maid.
"Maids are like chopsticks."
"You hardly notice them, but their
absence plunges you into disarray."
Did my morn cry before they hanged her?
Women who steal once
and are hanged always cry.
They even cry a lot.
Your mother stole a thousand times,
was caught just once, and died once.
Did she cry?
She laughed.
Said she was lucky to
have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Imagine what a good
thief you'll become!
It should have been me!
I should be the one
going to that Jap's house.
What a pity...
Everyone's talking about you in Eunpo.
How you'll be an even
greater thief than your mom. Hmm?
Who believes the talk of a swindler?
When I give the signal,
"fully ripe",
arrange for her and I to be alone.
Then I'll gobble her up to the pit.
She's so naive,
even if a man pulls on her nipples
she won't know what he wants.
So it's your job to tell her
that everything is because of me.
"Oh my, since the Count arrived,
your toenails are growing much faster!"
That sort of thing, all right?
Here, a gift.
Oh, he's so thoughtful!
That'll be mine when
she goes to the madhouse.
It pains my heart to see this poor girl.
Have you ever seen sapphires so blue?
Let's take a look...
This isn't a sapphire, it's blue spinel.
It's all right, Miss.
Spinels are expensive, too.
How do you know...
Oh, my Auntie...
I mean, Lady Minami taught me.
But it's fine!
No need to be ashamed at all.
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart.
Is that so?
Of all the things
I've washed and dressed,
has anything been this pretty?
I'd like to show her to the people at home.
What would they say?
Probably this?
Mesmerizing!
Spellbindingly beautiful!
He's shameless.
The Count kept pushing wine on me.
Does it feel okay?
It's suffocating.
How do ladies wear such things?
You think this is suffocating?
Miss, you're killing me!
Dressed up,
you look like a lady, too.
I think I know
what the Count meant.
Your face...
Each night in bed,
I think of your face.
Don't be silly, Miss.
Ladies truly are the dolls of maids.
All these buttons are for my amusement.
If I undo the buttons
and pull out the cords,
then, the sweet things within,
those sweet and soft things...
if I were still a pickpocket,
I'd slip my hand inside...
Miss, are you truly
going to marry your uncle?
That's what he raised me for,
knowing he'd need my fortune.
There's a famous collector in France.
He'll be putting his entire library
up for auction.
The gold mine's proceeds
won't cover the cost.
If it were me, I'd sell books
to buy gold, not the opposite.
Did you ever think of
marrying someone else?
- Count Fujiwara for example...
- You!
You're quite curious for a servant.
For now,
the Lady needn't go read to the sick fuck
who wants to marry his wife's niece.
Instead the fake Count goes
to the library to make fake books.
The Lady waits for her 2:00 art class,
and waits...
Poor girl,
losing her heart to a fake.
Please, Count!
Sorry to be late.
It's no matter.
Maybe I need more practice
to give it dimensionality?
Dimensionality, perhaps.
Nonetheless, you have a vision
that transcends mere skill.
As if you see directly
into an object's essence.
For example, the fact that this
peach contains a lot of water.
I hesitate to stand before you,
for fear that you might read my thoughts.
That's enough for today.
Almost fully ripe.
Already?
Damn...
Do you know what?
Since the Count arrived,
your cheeks have grown ﬂushed.
Have they?
How did your mom die?
When I was a baby,
at a big house, she was hanged...
- I mean, she hanged...
- Hanged herself? Like my aunt.
Well, pretty much.
Still, while alive she hugged you a lot?
My mother died giving birth to me.
So it's as if I strangled her myself.
I wish I'd never been born.
No baby is ever guilty of being born.
If your mother thought
you could understand,
this is what she'd have said.
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Wait here a moment, Miss.
I'll go pick mushrooms.
We'll have mushroom stew tonight,
you like that.
I'll go with you.
I'll be quick.
Before it rains.
Good girl...
What a coincidence.
Indeed.
May I sit by you?
The lady sits, shy and trembling.
The gentleman is persistent.
The perceptive maid
has stepped out for a moment.
All is well, Sookee.
Everyone's performing
their roles so damned well.
Fucking hell.
You know servants can't use this entrance!
Hey!
I wish I'd never come here.
It was wrong to come.
Tamako,
you brought watercolors, right?
Of course, milord!
Watercolor paints and brushes...
Go and get the oils.
A day like this demands oils, yes!
Shit!
Lady.
Milord.
A blackout! Bring a lantern.
I need to think.
I need to become rich,
sail off to a distant harbor,
eat food I scarcely recognize,
buy my fill of glittering baubles,
and not think of Hideko.
Never think of Hideko...
I returned
and you didn't even come to me?
It was late, I must have slept.
My apologies.
You know how hard it is
to do those readings?
Must I remove makeup
and change clothes all by myself?
I feel a nightmare coming. Sleep here.
He proposed to me.
Next full moon,
when my uncle visits his mine,
he wants to elope to Japan.
What did you say?
I said I wasn't sure.
Why?
I'm scared.
Of your uncle's anger?
Of the Count.
What's to be scared of? He's so kind.
I don't know, I just feel it.
Like the reflex of pulling
your hand from a flame.
Tell me...
What is it that men want?
Pardon?
I mean, after getting married,
at night...
How would I know?
I'm practically a child.
With no mother. No one here to...
First,
I guess they'd kiss?
And then?
They hug each other.
Standing up?
When there's no bed or
they have to be quick.
Normally one does it on a bed.
Let yourself go without thinking.
It'll work itself out.
Without thinking?
Are there girls who feel nothing
like how blind people don't see?
What the hell.
I'll show her one thing,
then put her to bed.
Poor thing,
alone in a strange country,
reading those useless books,
without learning a single useful skill.
Why does the candy taste different?
The bitter turned sour,
the sour turned sweet,
the sweet turned savory...
How do you know all this?
You must have experience?
My friend Kutan taught me.
Taught you? In words?
Yes, only in words.
So this is how it feels.
That's what you will feel for the Count.
Really?
The Count, truly...
He won't think he's
making love to a corpse?
You know about my cold hands and feet.
Really?
Here.
Feels just fine.
You like it?
Do it to me. I want to know how it feels.
I'm sure he'll want to do this too.
And then...
It's so cute.
If the Count sees this...
Will he really be so tender as this?
Of course.
And he'll touch you like this.
And like this...
Keep doing it like the Count would.
And this is what he'll say.
It's so soft, warm,
wet, and
spellbindingly beautiful!
Okju.
Hideko.
Mommy.
Daddy.
Now, the model must stay still.
Okju.
- Hideko...
- Wait.
Stop!
Leave Hideko alone.
Stop it!
I can't do this.
Come here, Tamako.
Find some other job to do.
You catch my meaning?
I've no other job to do.
My job is to look after the Lady.
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's fully ripe! Fully ripe!
If I miss this fortnight, I'm finished!
Can you feel it? How much I want it?
After fighting so hard to escape
my garbage heap of a life,
you think I'll let you
fuck it up, you bitch?
Shall I tell the Lady
you're nothing but a lowly pickpocket?
Fine, I'll have something to tell her too.
That you're nothing but the son
of a lowly Korean farmhand and shaman...
Sookee.
Think of your family at home.
Boksun raising babies with her bad back,
and those two halfwits.
How will they feel
if you go home empty-handed?
Want to shit on your mother's legend?
You should go home in glory.
So don't push Hideko too hard.
She's got no one on this earth.
If you frighten her,
she'll close up hard as a clam.
And please...
Don't ever again put my hand
on your tiny joke of a cock.
Oh, my.
Your toenails have grown faster
since the Count arrived.
How curious.
Miss, doesn't it bother you not to know?
How many ships sail on the wide sea...
People leaving, people returning,
those saying "Farewell" or "Welcome back."
What's the farthest you've traveled?
The hill beyond the manor?
My uncle would follow me
to the ends of the Earth.
I've always lived like this.
I could be content here,
if you were with me.
We go for walks
wearing new shoes,
you tell me stories,
and you massage my feet like that.
You're fortunate, Miss.
The man who loves you
has the power to protect you.
That's rare.
But I'm not sure if I love him.
You do love him.
How do you know?
You stare out the window all day.
Turn in your sleep and sigh.
And your toenails.
Even if I say I don't love him,
if I say that I love someone else...
Me, who has no one on this earth...
Do you still want me to marry him?
You will love him.
Miss!
In the end,
Hideko accepted the proposal,
provided that I come to Japan, too.
The Count, after feigning
annoyance for a bit,
nodded his head.
On the day her uncle
left to visit his mine,
the Count pretended to go back
to Japan and hid nearby.
You'll have a week of freedom,
but always remember the basement.
Miss!
Thank you for traveling on our ferry today.
We will arrive at Shimonoseki at 7:30 p.m.
Finally we're going home.
It's been three years...
To not steal...
To not commit adultery...
To not lie...
Spider web around in my waist
Strumming makes a zither sing
Thousand woes
Under the blue sky
Only the crows cry
How sorrowful my zither
My beloved zither
Did you sleep well?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
The Count paid the innkeeper to spy on us,
afraid we might run off.
Why get dressed?
I've nothing to do anyway.
Things are moving too slowly.
I fear Hideko might truly go mad.
Shall we play maid, like before?
From morning to night
we see no sign of the Count.
Certifying the marriage
and converting the inheritance to cash
require much work, he says.
How cruel can you be?
You plucked the ﬂower, now re-plant it.
What do you want?
Hurry up and throw her into the madhouse!
A week here...
Then finally...
This way.
There are the doctors,
you know what to say!
Who is that person?
The Countess Lady Fujiwara.
Her maiden name was lzumi Hideko.
And who might you be?
I am the Lady's handmaiden.
- Your name?
- My name is Tamako.
Then, what kind of treatment
do you believe your Lady requires?
She should be confined in a place
where no one can harm her,
and where she can do no harm.
Just a few tests, then let's have
lamb chops at the Peace Hotel.
Almost there. Good work.
Don't be frightened.
Good day, Countess.
Do you remember me?
Countess?
What is this?
We mean you no harm, Countess.
We're going to look after you.
You've got the wrong person.
She is the Countess.
Tell them, Your Lordship!
She still believes
she's a Korean handmaiden.
It's because her nanny was Korean.
You scoundrel!
Let go of me, you filthy bitches!
We do not use such language here,
your Ladyship.
Miss!
My poor Lady, she's gone nutty.
If it's any help,
this is from her mother,
and she used to cherish it
before going mad.
Such a considerate maid.
You thought Hideko a lamb.
Lamb, my arse.
I tell you, right from the start,
Miss lzumi Hideko
had always been...
Miss!
...a rotten bitch.
PART TWO
PART TWO I'm not a rotten bitch!
No! No!
I'm not a rotten bitch!
Put it in your mouth, Hideko.
Hold out your hand.
Next time you feel like talking back,
remember the taste of this metal bead.
You'll sleep alone from tonight.
All right?
Please give me a light.
We've been ordered to save oil.
You little brat.
Speak Japanese!
In there is a man the size of an ogre
who can't stand the sound
of girls screaming.
If he hears you, he'll burst in
through that door after you.
And then?
He'll smother you with his giant body.
So you can't make a sound.
Aunt.
My, my...
Scaring a little girl like that.
And me?
Am I pretty too?
Look closely.
Everyone says I can't compare
to my big sister.
Day.
Night.
Man.
Woman.
Eye.
Nose.
Mouth.
Ear.
Shoulder.
Nipple.
Navel.
Eye.
Nose.
Mouth.
Ear.
Shoulder.
Nipple.
Navel.
Penis.
Vagina.
You think if you speak Korean,
I won't understand?
I was going a bit crazy,
so I made them crazy too.
When Mrs. Sasaki looked as crazy as me,
life was more bearable.
I know you are a bit insane.
It runs in your mother's family.
That's why I'm training you.
To set your mind right.
If I fail, there's a place called
a "mental hospital" in Japan.
Um...
Established by the rational Germans,
it's very effective in treating lunacy.
They dig holes in the dirt,
put a patient in each one,
and put lids on top.
If patients improve, they get a leash,
so they can crawl around like dogs.
The cherry tree that came with me
on the ship from Japan
bloomed twice.
"When Jinlian finally took off her clothes,
"Ximen Qing examined her Jade Gate
"to find it hairless white as snow
and smooth as jade..."
You must pause between words.
Don't read like a dog lapping at his plate!
Listen to your aunt read.
"When Jinlian finally took off her clothes,
"Ximen Qing examined her Jade Gate..."
Discovering the Secret Well
"...to find it hairless, white as snow,
"and smooth as jade.
"Tight as a drum,
"and soft as silk.
"Once he drew apart the curtains of flesh,
"the scent of well-aged wine
emanated from within,
"and on fold upon fold
of the red velvet interior,
"beads of dew were forming.
"Its center was dark and void,
"yet as if it had its own life,
"it twitched and twitched."
Everyone wanted to cut it down,
but my uncle refused.
He said this tree from Mt. Fuji
had absorbed my aunt's soul.
The servants whispered it was
due to the tree's high cost,
but I think my uncle was right.
You can tell from the cherry blossoms,
which turned brighter and bloomed longer.
"'Tell me, Juliette.
"'Do you wish this impetuous
young knight to save you?'
"The duchess shook her head resolutely,
"to my great disappointment.
“Now,
"'my brave knight."'
Oh, it's a new customer!
"Now,
"my brave knight."
When you see these old scars
and the fresh pink wounds,
what do you feel?
I pity the poor woman.
I wish to lick her and lick her,
caress her and caress her.
If you pity her so,
why not take her place
and let her whip you?
"The duchess raised the whip
high in the air, and then..."
"And again..."
"My cock became painfully erect."
If she could be yours for 10 minutes,
what would you give in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires.
Anything in this whole wide world.
"Once the duke untied me,
"I sat on the chair, pulled her to me,
"and slid my cock into her cunt."
"'Oh, Juliette, Juliette...'
"As I felt the duke approach from behind,
"a rope slithered around my neck.
"The duke slowly tightened the rope.
"Like a drowning man grasping at straws,
"I pulled the swirling
currents of her hair.
"Then the duke spoke.
"'The 10 minutes are almost up.'
"'Slowly, my dear, ' said the Duchess.
"'I haven't yet fully savored his pain.'
"'No, ' the knight cried, 'don't stop!
"'Please let me die
"'in the midst of this pain.
"'In this suffocating pain."'
Is it Sade?
It's Sade-esque.
Believed to be the same Japanese
man who wrote The Lizard Skin.
Acquired from a Japanese sailor
on a ship from Hamburg.
Poorly printed, on low-quality paper...
used and torn,
stained from food
and human secretions...
I have a predilection
for this kind of little cherub.
Can you imagine my joy when,
after such a journey,
it sat on my shelf with its brothers?
An untouched 1st edition of Milton
wouldn't satisfy me more.
Yes.
These are the babes
to whom I feel the most affection.
It used to contain an elaborate
monochrome woodcut illustration,
but as you can see...
So unfortunate.
If that were intact,
you could've named your price.
The author felt words alone could
not fully describe the positions,
and so included an illustration.
In that regard, before
we start the bidding...
Hideko!
Can you perform this scene?
Pain is a Garment
Beautiful!
See you again.
Yes, thank you.
Today's reading was outstanding.
Especially the puppet!
You are of noble birth,
yet you engage in the lowly work
of copying paintings.
There was a time when
I dissipated my wit and skills on gambling.
Imagine the torment
of having so many women
make advances on me,
when I couldn't afford to
buy them a glass of Burgundy.
Do the women here advance on you?
I look at women's eyes.
Only the eyes.
They turn their gaze away,
but then they always look back.
It's a kind of silent dialogue.
If I were to slide under
someone's covers tonight,
only one woman here would refuse me.
Does that include Mrs. Sasaki?
Mrs. Sasaki...
Is she not your former wife?
You left her to marry a Japanese woman.
But the servants tell me
you still share a bed with her.
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
You went so far as to abandon your wife,
why this urge to become Japanese?
Because Korea is ugly,
and Japan is beautiful.
Some Japanese say Japan is ugly
and Korea is beautiful.
Beauty is cruel by nature.
Korea is soft, slow, dull,
and therefore hopeless.
Tell me about this woman
who would resist you.
Does it include Mrs. Sasaki?
Mrs. Sasaki...
If I gave her the right signal,
she'd knock on my door
without her underwear.
My thoughts exactly.
Then who is it?
The one who would deny you?
I heard you own the highest quality
antique bookmaking tools of East and West,
but I don't see them here.
I'll show them to you later.
This woman...
who is she then?
I met Hideko's eyes by chance,
but she didn't look away.
Indeed it was I who shifted my gaze.
Will she make an appearance
in your lewd dreams tonight?
Even if honored with such a visit,
I don't think I could consummate.
I would regret it as soon as I began.
Because her body
would be as cold as waterfowl.
The result of long training.
I heard you are engaged to her.
If I'm not mistaken,
you are yet to have intercourse?
Her eyes have no desire.
It means her soul is dead inside.
You should go easy on her training,
unless you enjoy making love to a corpse.
Would you like a cigarette?
How could a man with such refined tastes
indulge in a pleasure
as vulgar as a cigarette?
My particular way of possessing beauty.
Hideko, too, must have
received painting lessons?
In fact, I was too occupied teaching
her to read with correct diction.
Dear me!
In England, where I studied,
all ladies were expected to produce
vibrant color and graceful lines,
even in the less noble families.
A phone call, sir.
At this hour?
It's the lwamura Bookstore.
Is that so?
Excuse me a moment.
You are mesmerizing.
Men use the word "mesmerizing"
when they wish to touch a lady's breasts.
I'm familiar with
Western conversational etiquette.
I do a bit of reading, you know.
There was no calculation in what I said.
It was a reflex, like pulling
one's hand from a ﬂame.
I'm no flame.
I'm cold as waterfowl, your Lordship.
He will return soon.
Mr. lwamura only called
with a frivolous inquiry,
at my request.
There's an issue regarding your future
you should know.
I'll wait by the stone lamp at midnight.
That lwamura is a real fool.
Good night, Miss.
My maid is asleep in the room next door.
I don't fancy being
in scandalous rumors with you.
I saw Junko go to the servants' quarters
with her pillow.
Consider your reputation as a nobleman.
I'm no nobleman.
I'm not even Japanese.
Think it was easy for a Korean
farmhand's son to reach here?
Fifteen hard years in Japan
before hearing about you.
Another three years to prepare.
I studied bookmaking
and learned to paint forgeries.
All so that I could meet you.
To seduce and marry you,
to possess your father's inheritance,
and then probably to get rid of you.
But I knew as soon as I met you.
For a man to seduce you would be...
Impossible.
So in place of seduction,
I decided to propose a deal.
Most marriages are prison,
but this one will free you.
I'll rescue you from here,
take you far away,
and give you freedom.
Of course, we'll split the money.
Nonsense.
Marrying an old man with a black tongue
at your tender age makes sense?
I won't marry anyone.
What have you in mind?
Mmm.
That's not proper.
There's no beauty in that.
If you kill yourself, what of your fortune?
That will be the sum of your efforts?
Your fortune going to a pervert?
So he can buy 10 little girls
and teach them to read books?
My uncle will find us somehow.
Then he'll take us to the basement.
Uncle.
The basement?
It says here when people are hanged,
their tongues stick out
and feces is expelled.
But that day, Aunt's mouth was shut,
and her bottom was clean.
Want to go somewhere nice?
I'll tell you in detail
what I did to your aunt
after I caught her running away.
So don't you ever think of running,
understood?
That day I just watched and listened.
But if I ever end up there again...
Highly concentrated opium.
Three drops will make you sleep all day.
Five drops will knock down a horse.
If you crave death within five minutes,
drink it all.
If you carry this, he can never
take you to the basement.
At least not alive.
It'll be my wedding gift to you.
It's more expensive than jewels.
Bring a girl to be my maid.
One who could disappear and not be missed.
If a bit dense, all the better.
We'll send her to a madhouse
under my name.
They say that the sick are
buried alive in pits.
I want my name to be buried there.
I can find you a new maid,
but what do we do about Junko?
You really think
I'm prettier than Miss Hideko?
Sure, Hideko's pretty,
and you're pretty.
What? You speak Korean?
You know...
I learned it.
To speak more easily with you.
I really wanted to say this to you.
You are just mesmerizing.
Oh, my gosh!
You little tart!
I can't!
If they catch me with a guest,
I'll be thrown out!
Forget this wretched place.
Come live with me!
Oh, fucking hell!
Fucking hell?
Fucking hell...
The Count sent exactly what I ordered.
Naive and a bit foolish.
We look a bit alike.
Are you also an orphan?
Mother!
Show Sookee your old clothes
or jewelry at every opportunity.
The material greed she got from her
mother will make her more gullible.
P.S. Don't worry if she reads this
letter, she's totally illiterate.
Would you read it to me?
Pardon?
"...said you're looking for a maid.
"Maids are like
"a spoon..." No...
"Are like chopsticks..."
Is it a spoon?
Countess Fujiwara Hideko
This is your name.
Can't you read it?
What's with your foot?
Who did it?
Who took Tamako's shoe?
Apologize before all the servants!
If she ever runs away
because of one of you,
I'll strip you all naked
and throw you out!
Fucking hell.
All smooth.
You like the scent?
Want to come in?
Pardon?
This must be Okju.
At your service, milord.
You know if you fail,
it'll put me in an awkward position?
A decent bone structure for a Korean...
So, are you carrying out
your duties faithfully?
Thank you for your recommendation.
You chose the perfect servant for me.
You wouldn't want one who's too stupid.
I did my best.
Take good care of our dear Lady.
Take this.
There's no shame
in being rewarded
for being a good companion
to the Lady.
Isn't that right Ms. Hideko?
No need to be ashamed at all.
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart.
Is that so?
Returning the earrings you loaned me.
A woman might wager her fate
on such an exquisite pair.
I'm sure that Sookee will try her very best
in order to see herself
wearing these in the mirror.
I'll tell you how to keep her
from getting suspicious.
Keep her busy until the
day of the wedding.
Make her spend all her energy
on making you fall in love with me.
In other words,
don't fall in love with me so easily.
Mesmerizing!
Me?
Dressed up, you look like a lady, too.
Almost fully ripe.
How did your mom die?
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Is this the companionship
they write about in books?
I'll go pick mushrooms.
We'll have mushroom stew tonight,
you like that.
I'll go with you.
I'll be quick.
What's wrong with her?
Is it her period?
Men are disgusting.
How can they be so single-minded?
What's on my mind?
You don't really believe
that I crave your body?
You do!
You read too many of those books.
If there's one thing I'm after, Miss...
It's not your eyes, your hands or ass,
it's your money, only that.
Of all that you have, money is the best.
Feels great being so rude to a noble lady.
What's with her?
Why does she stomp her feet,
expressing her anger,
sit up in the middle of the night
and sigh?
Every time she sees the Count,
her eyes seem to say...
I despise you.
Try to bear it. Only if she sees this
will she believe the proposal.
Think of me as that puppet,
and I'll imagine another woman.
What woman?
The duchess Juliette.
Lady!
Milord!
Lady“.
"The lady's emotions lay deep inside.
"Jinlian could not fathom their depths.
"Knowing this, Lady Sun
"gave Jinlian four small silver balls.
"'These are minling, or bells of passion.
"'Place two in the lady's Jade Gate,
"'and the other two in yours.
"'Spread your legs apart
"'and like two scissors
'"trying to cut each
other, put them together.
"'When the lips below
rub against each other,
"'you'll hear a clear ringing sound."'
A blackout! Bring a lantern!
Yes, sir!
The Sound of Bells on a Windless Night
"'When do I put this in?' Asked Jinlian.
"'Does the lady breathe deeply
and swallow hard?
"'Does she whisper sweetly in your ear,
"and kiss you?
"'Does she embrace you tightly
"'and caress your nipples?
"'Does her secret part become slippery
"'as she gently bites your shoulder?
Does she press her legs between yours?
And curl her toes?
"'Then, put in the bells."'
- Amazing!
- Indeed!
It's so cute.
If the Count sees this...
Will he really be so tender as this?
Of course.
And he'll touch you like this...
And like this...
Tamako, keep doing it.
Like the Count would.
The Count...
He'll go crazy over this.
And this is what he'll say.
It's so soft, warm, wet, and
spellbindingly beautiful!
Shall I teach you more, Miss?
Yes...
Teach me everything.
I wish that I had breast milk
so I could feed you.
Do you like it when I do this?
Do you like me?
Can you promise that you won't betray me?
I'll never,
never,
ever...
Miss, how could such an innocent...
You must be a natural.
Stop!
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's got no one on this earth.
If you frighten her,
she'll close up hard as a clam.
And please...
Don't ever again put my hand
on your tiny joke of a cock.
You see?
If you don't give the impression
you want this marriage,
she may throw another fit
and refuse to go forward.
Be more convincing
when you pretend to love me.
I can't do it.
What?
I want to quit.
What's with you all today?
Why then?
I hate all of you. My mother, my aunt,
my uncle, you, and...
And?
I can't stand Sookee anymore either.
You feel sorry for her?
What is it with women?
You know what that poor
Sookee said about your Ladyship?
That you're too dense to get it
if someone pulls on your nipples.
That she was nice out of pity,
but you ate it up.
That you were so gullible!
That naive servant's face...
Yes, you will love him.
If I say that I love someone else...
Me, who has no one on this earth...
Do you still want me to marry him?
Yes.
Miss!
I wish I'd never been born.
Let go.
Miss, I'm sorry!
Let go!
I'm sorry, Miss!
Don't die.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
I tried to trick you
into marrying that bastard.
I was going to put you
in a madhouse and run off.
Don't die. Don't get married, Miss!
Sookee, are you worried about me?
I'm worried about you.
How do you know my name?
You think you're tricking me?
You're the one being tricked.
You're the one bound for the madhouse.
I was going to lock you up
in there under my name,
then I'd become you
and run far away, with him.
I won't say sorry,
since you tried to trick me, too.
That fucking son of a bitch!
Oh, sorry, Miss!
"I hope this letter finds you well.
This is Sookee.
"I'm writing to inform you
of a change in plans.
"I decided to team up with the Lady Hideko.
"As such, I'm now in need of all your help.
"I'm enclosing an item as advance payment."
Always remember the basement.
You want to go somewhere nice?
You didn't teach me to read Japanese.
Did that bastard draw this?
Is this what you've been reading
to that dirty old man
and those gentlemen?
Ah!
The daughter of a legendary thief,
who sewed winter coats
out of stolen purses.
Herself a thief, pickpocket, swindler.
The savior who came to tear my life apart.
My Tamako.
My Sookee.
How cruel can you be?
You plucked the ﬂower, now re-plant it.
What do you want?
Hurry up and throw her into the madhouse!
You scoundrel!
Let go of me, you filthy bitches!
Miss!
Let go!
I'm hungry-
The first month, I ordered
a slim herringbone suit.
The next month, I wore it to
dine at the Imperial Hotel.
PART THREE The next month, I wore
it to dine at the Imperial Hotel.
PART THREE
Me, a colonial boy working
as a tout at a brothel.
Some Englishmen who frequented
the brothel recognized me.
I thought they'd call
the maitre d' and kick me out,
but what do you know?
They were amused I'd
spend a month's pay
on one dignified meal.
They started calling me Count
and taught me manners
to go with the name.
Frankly, I'm not that interested
in money itself.
What I desire is, how shall I put it...
The manner of ordering wine
without looking at the price?
Something like that.
Fourteen hours by train from Vladivostok
is the summer home of
a genuine Russian noble family.
The villa is entirely furnished.
The carpets are very soft.
Shall we marry there?
In a few days I'll hear from the hospital.
That my wife Fujiwara Hideko has died.
You didn't just ask them to keep her?
I doubt Sookee would want
to live there very long.
Fuck!
Motherfucker.
I never pretended to be
anything but a crook, my dear!
You will soon become
the Korean servant Nam Sookee.
I'm a talented counterfeiter.
I arranged it
with a photography studio.
From tomorrow, we'll
give Sookee a new life.
I'm glad.
Marry me once again.
This time as Nam Sookee.
You want another wedding night?
I think I like you, slightly.
Poor Sookee, in a place like that
all by herself...
Did such a thought ever cross your mind?
Not at all. Why should I pity her?
Where I come from,
it's illegal to be naive.
Where you come from, it's not naive
to fall in love with a business partner?
Of course. It's illegal.
So even if my love for
you leads me to ruin,
don't pity me.
Love?
What does a crook know about love?
What's that?
Fire!
Come this way!
This way!
Because you desired me
and overcame all obstacles to reach me,
I have been born anew, it's true.
I'm grateful for that.
I'll allow a kiss.
No.
Why not?
I don't like kisses with conditions.
I never learned how to stop halfway.
After this I'll thrust
in deep, to your navel.
Please do that.
Those aren't the eyes of one who wants it.
You know you can't
deceive me in such matters.
If I could be yours
for ten minutes,
what would you give in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires.
Anything in this whole wide world.
There's much
I want to teach you.
You'll become a completely new woman.
It won't hurt.
You know from those books?
In truth, women feel the
greatest pleasure
when taken by force.
Now I'm going to rip your underwear.
Would you fetch those for me?
OK, look here.
One, two, three!
Respected Uncle,
it always pained me to see you straining
to speak flawless Japanese
before the Count from Nagoya,
and even to quiver your voice
like a nobleman.
So I'm happy to inform you
that you no longer need do so.
That man is the son of a Korean farmhand.
Oh, did my gift arrive safely?
Please tell this to my gift, in Korean.
I'm afraid that in real life,
no woman feels pleasure
at being taken by force.
But, for sending me Sookee
out of all the girls in the world,
I feel "slightly" grateful.
You wished to see my bookmaking tools?
Don't just look,
experience them for yourself.
I'll choose five books that I cherish...
That I used to cherish more than anything.
Let's see...
First...
First of all.
The Lizard Skin.
Decadent Girls Who Sell Lingerie.
May I please
smoke a cigarette, sir?
Sir.
Bells and Balls.
The Mortician's Bedroom.
How could you
let a little girl fool you?
But don't worry.
I'll catch them for you soon.
I'll bind two books with the skin
of these bitches.
And you, you'll be the third volume.
I arranged so that no two girls
traveling together can leave Kobe.
Please change the destination
to Shanghai.
Changing two tickets,
from Vladivostok to Shanghai.
Yes, that's correct.
Show me your passports.
Miss Nam Sookee?
Mr. Go Pan-dol?
You need to pay an additional three yen.
All right.
Hideko was
like a peach that I looked at
on its branch.
I was content just
imagining its flavor.
Should I have bitten into it?
No, no.
I'm just an old man
who likes dirty stories.
Even listening to the same story,
people imagine different things.
Peering into each of those fantasies
was this old man's humble recreation.
What to do, now that it's all over?
You should at least tell me your story.
How did that bitch Hideko taste?
Was she fully ripe? Tell me.
A cigarette might help my memory.
Right, right...
You have that silly
penchant for cigarettes?
So how was Hideko?
You have no windows here?
Sookee could be listening in.
Let's do our best.
That's it, good.
Why aren't you talking?
You can't stop there,
dear fellow.
So, where did you touch first?
Her face?
Her breasts?
Or straight for her cunt?
Was it soft?
Did it tighten up?
Did it have many wrinkles?
Was it sufficiently wet?
The viscosity and transparency
of her vaginal secretion?
Please, one more cigarette, sir.
Spider thread pulled into strings...
I dare say
no book has ever described
such a ferocious wedding night.
I thought I heard a nightingale sing.
And the clear,
bright crimson blood!
Thus the Lady became my wife.
Coy one moment, bold the next...
But how was she coy,
how was she bold, tell it to me in detail!
A story is all about the journey.
You should know.
Did she resist?
So did you pinch her ass as punishment?
Or did she spit at you in contempt?
Or else...
Did she beg you to do it?
Like the lady in
The Widow's Lapdog?
How dare you!
Hideko is my wife.
What kind of scoundrel rattles on
about his wedding night!
It's odd...
Your smoke.
It's cold, blue,
and strangely beautiful.
You too have become soft,
slow and dull.
Mercury is most deadly
in its gaseous state.
One cigarette would have sufficed.
At least I will die with my cock intact.
I hear a sound in the distance
that sounds like the steps of my love
An echo that makes my heart
Skip a beat
But I wait all through the night
And my love never comes to me
There is no end to the heartache
That grips me in this hour
Waiting for the footsteps of
My dear love
But then in my waiting heart
Suddenly happiness overflows
There you are in the distance
Coming to me
Filled with dreams of a new life
Filled with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
Flowers start to bloom
Come my lover, come to me
I missed you so
Let's dream of happy times
Like long ago
Filled with dreams of a new life
Filled with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
Flowers start to bloom
Waiting for the footsteps of
My dear love