[dramatic music]
- So we built a machine
powerful enough
to big-bang a new Speed Force
into existence
based solely on the teachings
of history's
most evil Speedster.
Are we sure
we wanna hit this switch?
♪ ♪
- Do it.
[computer chimes]
[machine buzzing]
- Cisco: Uh, what's happening?
[machine stops buzzing]
- It didn't work.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[knocking]
- Guys, you in there?
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt...oh.
How'd the machine test go?
- Well, it didn't.
That's the problem.
- How did Thawne
manage to build
a Speed Force machine
on his own
without a journal to guide him,
but all the brainpower
in S.T.A.R. labs
can't even get
this thing to work.
It's like we built
a 12-ton paper weight.
- Okay, okay, but hey!
Maybe getting out of here
for a minute
might clear your heads.
I, myself, was on my way over
to "The Citizen' right now.
Does anybody...Barry...
wanna come with me?
- No.
Look.
Every day that
the machine is off
is another day
I can't protect this city.
I have to keep working.
- [sighs]
Barry, wait.
Are you sure you
don't wanna see Iris?
[soft dramatic music]
Can I tell her
anything for you?
- Tell her I miss her.
- His speed has been
draining non-stop.
Your plan was a success.
- You've done an amazing job.
Is everything okay?
You seem...distant.
- Sorry, um...
I'd just like to know
if you want us to proceed
with the next phase.
- Yes.
Go join your brother
and prepare.
Because tonight...
I will finally have
my liberation.
both: Success is assured.
[knocking on door]
[mirror shimmering tones]
- Come in.
- Hey.
You busy?
What's up?
- I just wanted to...
- You're here
about me and Barry?
- Yeah.
He's in a really bad place,
Iris.
His heart is breaking.
He won't talk
to anybody about it.
- He promised me after
he took Nora to the future
that would be the last time
that he made a decision
about our family without me.
But then he took my dad into
Witsec and didn't even tell me.
I had to find out from Singh.
How do you get over that,
Cecile?
- Well, it...
I don't really know, Iris.
But I would think
the first step is wanting to.
What do you want?
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- I...I don't know.
Can you feel what I want?
Can you tell me?
[psychic humming]
- You feel...
sad.
Sad and concerned.
- I think what Iris
needs right now is space
to focus on what's
really important.
- Right.
Um...
It's important for me
to take care of myself
right now, Cecile.
- Okay, yeah, um...
Your husband wanted me
to tell you that he misses you.
♪ ♪
Uh...
[knocks]
Bar?
- Hey.
- There's something
blocking the door.
- Yeah, um...
- I thought you were still
at the Speed Lab.
- Uh...
- Hey, Barry.
- Hold on.
- Why can't I get
inside my own house?
- Sorry.
Hold on.
One second.
- Geez!
- [clears throat]
Cecile, I can explain.
- What the hell is this?
- Iris isn't Iris.
[dramatic music]
- So then I thought
well obviously, this can't be
an Iris doppelganger
from another Earth
because doppelgangers
don't exist anymore.
Because the Multiverse
doesn't exist anymore.
Because Crisis
blew it all up, right?
- Uh-huh.
- Exactly.
So if that's true,
who else do we know
that could be
pretending to be Iris?
- I...what...
- Shapeshifters.
All right, so Everyman
was my first suspect.
And Cisco's report show that
he is alive post-Crisis.
Then I remembered something
that Breacher said
about Plastoids.
Which made me realize,
there could be shapeshifting
Martians on this Earth now.
This...this fake Iris
doesn't even have
to be from our planet.
But then, it hit me that
J'onn J'onzz would sense
if there was a Martian
hidden among us,
so that was a dead end,
but it led me
to my biggest
breakthrough yet.
Okay, Cecile, the night
that this all started,
Iris left
to investigate a story.
I analyzed her phone's GPS
and it shows that
she went to McCulloch Tech.
Cecile, I think that something
happened to Iris that night.
- Barry...
All of this...is this
the reason you've been
avoiding Iris?
- That's not Iris!
Okay, look...I didn't want to
tell anyone else about this
until I gathered more evidence,
but now you know, so I...
what do you think?
- Uh...
What do I think?
I think...I think that this...
this sounds...
- I know how it sounds,
but look.
We've seen crazier.
And look at all the clues.
Okay, I mean, she speaks
Italian all of a sudden.
She smashed a bottle
over some guy's head.
She made incredible pancakes.
Cecile, trust me.
Iris can't make pancakes.
All right?
But the biggest clue was...
Her throwing me out.
The real Iris would never
stop fighting for us.
- Okay, okay, um.
Sweetie.
Do you think that maybe...
just maybe...
you're feeling a little scared,
you know.
Because your marriage
is going through
a rough patch, and maybe,
what you need to do
is just go see Iris.
- That's not Ir...
Cecile, look.
Do you know why my Speed Gauge
is still glowing red?
It is because the moment
that I stepped out of the loft,
I realized
Iris, the real Iris, my wife,
she is somewhere else.
Probably in danger.
And if that's true,
I need my speed back.
My...my lightning, all my powers
if I'm gonna save her.
[sighs]
It's all I've thought
about ever since.
No matter how insane
this all sounds,
I know in my heart
that the real Iris
is out there somewhere.
Waiting for me to find her.
I won't let her down.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Polar bear's a little
on the nose, don't you think?
- Well, it's not like
the stores have a
"Get well soon from dual
light-assassin attacks" card.
[knocks]
What'd you bring?
- Oh, I got a mobile bio-lab
so she can catch up on her work
while she recovers in bed.
Don't be a jealous.
It's a scientist thing.
Come on, snow-poke.
It's us.
[knocks]
[door handle sizzling]
- It's ice cold.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Caitlin.
- Help me.
- Since when is Caitlin
the frosty one?
[thermometer beeps]
- She's not.
Hang on, Caitlin.
We're on the case.
- I think I've come up
with a new idea
to get us out of this place.
- [gasps]
Stop!
What are you doing?
- Eva, think about it.
This is the only mirror
that you can control.
So there's gotta be
something different about it.
And until we can
figure out what that is,
we're just working blind.
Move.
- So to examine it,
you want to smash it?
- Yeah, I mean, we both know
that you can put it
back together,
so let's just take
this thing down,
dissect it piece by piece,
and learn what its secrets are.
- Fine.
You do what you wanna do.
- [scoffs]
- Gonna go to my lab,
and work on a plan
that would actually help us.
- [scoffs]
[button beeps]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
- Can you, uh, maybe hurry up?
You know, when Iris
gave me a spare key,
it was to water her plants.
It wasn't to hack her computer.
- It's not hacking
Iris' computer
if it's not really Iris.
- What are you even
looking for anyway?
- Anything that might be
suspicious
from the past few weeks.
Bingo.
- What'd you find?
- This photo.
It was deleted
from Kamilla's camera,
but not before it was uploaded
to "The Citizen"'s
cloud server.
Do you see this text?
- Prismatic Filter.
What is that?
- It's the science
that we're gonna use
to test our
imposter's identity.
Expose her for good.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- That's better.
Much more homey.
- "Closer" is how
I'd describe it.
Closer to our Mother.
It's time for our next move.
You ready?
- Yes.
Are you?
All that matters is Eva's will.
We follows orders
and assure her success.
That's all I want.
- We need to focus.
There's still one item
Mother needs to obtain
for her liberation.
[dramatic music]
And it's the
most dangerous yet.
♪ ♪
- Iris: Hey, I saw your text.
I got here as fast as I could.
What's the emergency?
- You are.
Apparently.
- What's going on?
- You're not Iris.
That's what.
And you're not leaving here
until you tell us
who or what you are.
[dramatic music]
- [scoffs]
What the hell
are you talking about?
And why are you pointing
that gauntlet at me?
- This photo was taken
on Kamilla's camera.
You see the prismatic
fragmentation?
Only your image is affected.
I think that
the camera's filter
is revealing
a dimensional shift.
Showing us things
in the picture
from another dimension.
Things that don't
belong in ours.
- Cecile, you actually
believe this?
- You seemed off
in your office earlier,
and...and that photo.
- That could've been anything.
A glitch in the camera tech.
Guys, this is insane.
- This prismatic scanner is
just a more powerful version
of the camera's filter.
If I'm wrong, and you are
from this dimension,
then when
the prismatic wave hits you,
you'll look completely normal.
But if I'm right,
you're gonna look
just like that photo.
And you're gonna tell us
where the real Iris is.
- Barry, how could you do this?
For God's sake, I'm your wife.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Okay.
You wanna see who I really am?
Fine.
I'll show you.
[machine beeps]
[mirrors glitching, buzzing]
[screeching]
[metallic shimmering tones]
- [screaming]
[yelps]
No, no...I have to know.
I have to know.
man:Someone else must
have heard the good news too
because they sent you a gift.
I had it delivered.
[high-pitched tones]
[mirror shimmering tones]
[echoing]
- Hello, Joseph.
This is your last chance.
Joseph.
- Threats are
for real people, Eva.
Not phantoms.
Because that's what you are.
[echoing]
[mirror shatters]
- And no one saw you.
[echoing]
And no one saw you.
- Thank God, you're safe.
- I'm not.
Neither are you.
Black Hole
isn't what we think.
Mirror!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [whimpering]
[yelps]
[groaning]
- [gasps]
- Shh.
- I know.
- [breathing harshly]
[echoing]
- The truth hurts.
- Barry.
I just want you to know
that if anything happens, I...
I forgive you.
[machine humming]
- What's happening?
- Nothing.
- Okay...okay, that's...
that's enough.
- No, something's...
something's wrong, all right?
Just give it a minute.
- [sighs]
[machine powers down]
Look, I...
I don't know how she did this,
but...but you have to see
that this isn't my wife.
- No, you're not my husband,
Barry.
You wanna know
what the real test is?
The real Barry
would've fought harder.
He would've fought
to come back home.
A whole week went by
and you never even tried.
[soft dramatic music]
You used to say that
I was your lightning rod.
Now let's see
if you're still mine.
[machine humming]
[metallic shimmering tones]
♪ ♪
[machine powers down]
- Guys.
I'm me.
I'm the real Barry.
[gauntlet charges]
I'm...hey!
- Wait!
Nash, no!
Back up.
- Cecile?
You believe me?
- Yes.
I do.
[mechanical clicking]
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Barry.
I'm sorry.
- Nash!
Cecile!
Don't listen to her.
That's not Iris.
- You know, you can stop
playing this game,
or rot in there.
I don't care.
Either way, I'm gonna
find my husband.
- Ah, I should've
noticed something.
I should've figured
something out...
- No, no.
No one's to blame.
He or it was pretty convincing.
- If that's not Barry,
then what is he?
He's like some
mirror version of himself.
[dramatic sting]
Guys, Joseph Carver.
- Wait...you think that
this is related to Black Hole
and their reflective
chip technology?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
That seems almost...
- No, that's possible.
I've seen that McCulloch tech
up close and it...
reflective chip technology,
it's...
it's far-reaching
to say the least.
- Okay, well, um, then
this might be our best lead.
Why don't you see
what you can find, Nash?
I will regroup with Kamilla,
and do some digging of our own.
[psychic humming]
Are you okay, Cecile?
- [inhales sharply]
Uh, yeah.
No, um...
Something just
doesn't feel right.
- Yeah, no, I understand.
But we're gonna get
to the bottom of this
and get the real Barry back.
I promise.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Caitlin's body essentially
self-induced an "ice coma"
to force her to hibernate.
She's like a cold battery.
We just need to wake her up.
That's where you come in.
Since we don't have any
ionized conductive wiring,
you'll have to be
the jumper cables.
- Got it.
- Okay.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
- [yelling]
[sputtering]
[groaning]
[body thuds]
[gasps]
- Ralph!
Are you all right?
- Is she good?
Cisco, is she okay?
Did it work?
♪ ♪
- [breathes deeply]
- [exhales]
Oh, thank Elsa.
- Welcome back.
- Thanks.
- You scared us
for a minute there.
- Yeah.
- Can you tell us
what happened?
- I was home alone,
and the wound from the light
bullet was getting worse.
- Sure your run-in
with Sunshine didn't help.
- Yeah, so I tried
to ice heal it,
and that's when
the wound ruptured.
It must have been my immune
system's way of protecting me.
Guys, I need help.
- You just tell us
what you need.
I mean, who do we know
that can help with a...
light-ice wound?
- There's only one person
we can call.
My mother.
[helicopter whirring]
- Here she comes.
- Everything went
according to plan?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we're fine.
Everything went as planned.
You guys go to the rendezvous.
I'll handle this,
and I'll meet you there.
[mirror shimmering tones]
- I've been watching
Barry Allen.
He's planning on exposing you.
- Tell me what to do.
- Go.
Meet him.
Leave the rest to me.
- You're not Iris.
And you're not leaving here
until you tell us
who or what you are.
[mirror shimmering tones]
- Now let's get
what we came for.
- One of the benefits
of being chief of police
is I can request
prisoner interviews...
even for press.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[security gate chiming]
[security system beeps]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Well...
if it isn't Kamilla Hwang,
Chief Singh...
and Iris West-Allen.
To what do I owe the honor?
- If you help us,
we can get you out of there.
- And why would I trust
the wife of the Flash?
- Because I'm not
Iris West-Allen.
I'm a reflection of her.
We're all reflections.
Faster, stronger
than our human counterparts
whose faces we share.
And our only will
is to serve our Mother.
- The real Iris would never
offer to release me.
Tell me more about your Mother.
- Eva McCulloch.
She was the sc...
- I am a scientist.
I know who Eva McCulloch is.
But she disappeared years ago.
- She's been trapped
in another dimension.
A mirror one.
And she needs
something from you.
- You need my blood.
How grand.
Even in here, fate continues
to cast me
in the role of savior.
- We just need one drop.
- But you need to decide now.
- I accept.
Release me and you shall
indeed have my life blood.
However, this is no
crude metacell in Iron Heights.
How do you propose to disrupt
a bio-degenerative
containment matrix
with triplicate
backup protocols?
- Mother has a theory.
I am the answer.
- Wait!
You'll die.
- Then it is Eva's will.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[forcefield sizzling]
[alarms blaring]
- Code zero!
Facility-wide power failure!
All levels.
Check the cells.
- We have 60 seconds
until the guards...
[both choking]
- [grunts]
- [screaming]
[squelching and retreating]
- Ah.
- [panting]
- You're almost human.
Maybe something more.
You follow
your master Eva's will,
but I see hesitation
in your eyes.
You have a modicum of will.
Are you planning to trick me?
- [labored breathing]
- Tell me now!
What do you want?
- Only Eva's will.
- Lies!
Last chance.
What doyou want?
- [choking]
To be alive.
[coughing]
- And you are worthy of it.
- [coughing]
[alarm blaring]
[forcefield hums back to life]
- Power restored.
Cell containment
reinitialized.
- What are you doing?
We had a plan.
Don't you want to escape?
- There are walls
beyond these walls.
I was never gonna
just walk out of here.
But there's more than one way
for me to be free.
Let's just call this
"the long game."
[blood squelching]
- Now go.
I'll stay here
and cover our tracks.
Now!
- Run, Iris.
Run!
[dramatic music]
- [sighing]
[computer beeping]
[door opens]
Cecile?
- I don't have all the facts.
And the ones I do have tell me
that you're not
who you say you are.
You are Barry.
I know it in my heart.
And I'm willing
to bet my life on it.
Now go get Iris back.
[dramatic music]
- Good work.
You'll apply Ramsey's blood
on your side of the mirror.
Once it is fully absorbed,
I will activate
the R-CEM on my side.
Together, they
will reconfigure
the molecular stability
of the dimensional barrier
that burns organic matter.
Creating a safe passageway
between the two worlds.
Next time I speak to you,
I will be standing
right next to you.
Liberated.
- Success is assured.
[mirror shimmering tones]
[electricity crackles]
- I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
[dramatic music]
Where's my wife?
♪ ♪
- I'll ask you one more time.
Where is my wife?
What are you doing?
[dramatic music]
- [yells]
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- I saw everything.
You targeted me
from the very beginning.
- You suffered a fraction
of my pain.
But in just a few,
I will be liberated.
- Barry is gonna stop you.
We both will.
- I used to think my love
gives me strength too.
The mirror showed me the truth.
Let me do the same for you.
[mirror shimmering tones]
- [grunting]
[grunting]
- [yelps]
[electricity crackles]
[both grunting]
- She says you're always
gonna be in her way.
And now you're
too slow to stop me.
- Whose way?
Who's making you do this?
- [grunting]
[both grunting]
- Ah!
[both panting]
[both grunting]
- You should really
mind your surroundings.
[dramatic music]
[glass shatters]
♪ ♪
[blades slicing]
- [yelps]
[yelps]
- [grunts]
- [yelling]
[moans]
[groans]
Where is my wife?
- She's all you can
think about, huh?
- [groans]
- What do you think
about me, Barry?
All those days...
Weeks.
It wasn't her.
It was me.
Enjoying meals together.
♪ ♪
Talking about our day.
Sharing your bed.
- Oh, shut up.
- Mm.
[laughs]
- [grunts]
I am going to kill you.
- Unlikely.
I have been working
on this plan
for half a decade.
This is my creation.
She is me, and I am her.
What she feels, I feel.
And we cannot lose.
- Do they feel
what you feel for Carver?
- What?
- Do they still love him?
- I don't love my husband.
I want to end him.
- Then why do you still
call him your husband?
You are just as blinded
as you were before.
And he is going to trick you
in the exact same way.
- Stop talking.
- Because you still love him.
- No!
I don't!
[high-pitched ringing]
- [grunts]
[groaning]
- Your brilliant mind
couldn't figure out
that he didn't care about you.
- Shut up!
- [groaning]
- How long did you
sit here, Eva,
pining for rescue
before you realized
that you had been abandoned?
- I hate him!
I want him to suffer!
Suffer, suffer!
- Suffer!
Suffer!
- Iris?
- Suffer and suffer and suffer!
- Suffer!
Suffer!
[groaning]
- Iris.
Iris.
I won't fight you.
I won't fight you anymore.
- [breathing heavily]
- You were made from Iris.
A part of her heart
is inside you.
I've seen you be kind.
I've seen you laugh.
I know that wasn't all a lie.
- [groaning]
- You can be more than this.
Not Iris, but...
yourself.
- You have to want it.
- No.
- You have to choose it.
- [crying]
I...I choose me.
- [sniffles, exhales]
- Go find Iris.
Go find her, Barry.
Go save Iris.
Go.
[light crackling]
[groans]
[groaning]
[laughs]
Barry.
I feel alive.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I feel alive.
[glass shattering]
- [breathing heavily]
[machine beeps, hums]
[squelching]
♪ ♪
- Look what you made me do.
[glass shimmering tones]
- [grunts, groans]
- No, I'm sorry!
[grunts]
This didn't have
to be like this, Flash.
You don't know
what it's like in there.
I had to get out.
- Iris...
Where...where is she?
- She's still in the world
I left behind.
Along with the rest
of my insurance policy.
Chief Singh,
and your friend, Kamilla.
They're safe.
How long is up to you.
- So...what?
Now you're gonna kill me?
- There's no need for that.
You're wounded.
You lost your speed.
And your healing
is not what is used to be.
You're not much of a threat,
are you?
You just stay out
of my way, Flash.
And I'll stay out of yours.
- [groans]
- I have unfinished business
to attend to.
[mirror shimmering tones]
And a whole world
to liberate.
[mirror shimmering tones]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[exhales]
[groans]
Oh, thank God.
Oh, thank...
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[Freya Ridings'
"Still Have You"]
♪ ♪
Iris, I...
I don't know if it's crazy
to think that you can hear me.
- ♪ Say, "It's mad,"
you always do ♪
- I guess right now
I just need to believe it.
- ♪ Tell me how
it's not true ♪
♪ These wings
could lift us both ♪
- I miss you.
- ♪ But you don't think so ♪
- So much.
- ♪ You are all I wanted, so ♪
♪ If I threw it all away ♪
♪ Would I still have you? ♪
♪ If I tried
to hit the brakes ♪
♪ Would you see
right through? ♪
♪ This ain't
the fair-weather love ♪
♪ Like I'm used to,
no ♪
♪ If I threw it all away ♪
- I know you probably can't
hear me, Barry, but...
- ♪ Would I still have you? ♪
- Being away from you hurts
more and more every day.
♪ ♪
But I still have hope
because I know
that you are out there fighting
to get me back home.
- ♪ Hold me down ♪
- If you can hear me...
- ♪ Say we'll never die ♪
- I guess I just need you
to know that...
- ♪ But you don't think so ♪
- I love you.
- ♪ This is all I wanted ♪
- And that love is constant.
- Across dimensions.
- ♪ If I threw it all away ♪
- Across time.
- ♪ If I try to hit
the breaks ♪
- Through the end
of the world and back.
- ♪ Would you see
right through? ♪
♪ This ain't the fair... ♪
- And if I know you...
- ♪ Like I'm used to ♪
- I know you aren't just
fighting to find your way home.
- ♪ If I threw it all away ♪
- And I'm gonna find Kamilla.
And I'm gonna find Singh.
♪ ♪
But most of all...
- I'm gonna get you back.
- I'm gonna find
my way back to you.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Would I still have you? ♪
- Greg, move your head.