- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
Caitlin:Meet Joss Jackam.
She's a delinquent teen
turned amateur storm chaser.
That weathervane,
doesn't it look a lot like...
Barry:The staff
she was carrying, yeah.
- It's infected
with a satellite shard.
- Our satellite didn't
just create new metas.
It created meta-tech.
- [screams]
- Every time you vibe
or breach,
the dark matter
is going to affect
your central nervous system,
causing you
more and more pain.
- We need to talk.
- Yes, Nora.
Yes, we do.
[ominous music]
You've been gone
a long time, Nora.
- You're lucky
I came back at all.
- Really?
♪ ♪
I can tell you have questions.
Ask them.
- You killed my grandmother?
- I did.
- In front of my father?
- He was a boy.
- Nora...
- He was just a kid!
- You're right,
and I think of
that moment every day,
how it changed
the course of destiny
for him,
for you,
for me.
- I never knew he had that kind
of hatred inside of him,
but he does because of you.
- And I have that same hatred
inside of me for him!
♪ ♪
Or at least I did.
I was inspired by him,
as you are.
I wanted to know him,
as you do.
I wanted to be him.
I wanted to be the Flash.
- You will never be the Flash.
- Exactly!
And that realization
is what broke me.
[pounds on glass]
That's the realization
that led me to do
the things that I did.
The terrible, horrible,
evil things I did.
- I've been coming here
for so long.
Why didn't you tell me
what you did?
- I thought you must know.
Your mother would've told you.
I was wrong. I see that.
I'm sorry, Nora.
- I don't trust you anymore.
- Have I not
given you everything?
The chance to go back and know
a father you never knew?
To learn from him?
To run with him?
To run with the Flash.
I showed you how
to time travel because...
I want to help you.
- No, the only person that you
ever help is yourself.
- Who told you that?
Your father?
♪ ♪
For as long as I can remember,
all I ever thought about
was myself,
and that will not
be my legacy.
That will not the legacy
of Eobard Thawne!
Let me help you!
- I don't want your help.
Not anymore.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- So we've got some good news
and some bad news.
The good news is that CCPD
is still stationed outside
of Grace's room and will remain
so until Dwyer's been caught.
- But the bad news is,
that means Dwyer won't
be visiting her again
anytime soon.
- And then the worse news is,
we have no idea where Cicada
could be hiding.
- Can't we just track him by
the dark energy in his dagger?
- Well, we can but only
when he uses it, which,
thank God,
hasn't been recently.
- And he's not showing up
on facial recognition?
- Unless he decides to make
an appearance, we've got zilch.
- Which reminds me, where
the rest of Team Flash is?
Where's baby giraffe
and young Nora?
- Ralph's visiting his mom.
He said to call if we need him.
And Nora is...
- Right here.
I just stopped by the loft
to pick up your blue suit.
I figured you'd had enough
of green.
- Hey, I made that green suit
work, though.
- [chuckles]
- What is, uh,
that for again?
- Mama Cecile's first day
back to the courtroom
and Dad's testimony
against Weather Witch.
- Joss Jackam's trial
is later today.
It starts in 30 minutes.
- Well, since my dad is with
Jenna visiting Wally,
why don't I come with you guys
and help support Cecile?
- Yeah. When are they
coming back, by the way?
They've been gone forever.
- Uh, he's not sure.
After having a psychopath
break into his home,
I don't think he's in any rush
to bring a newborn back
to Central City.
Besides, Cecile has a lot
on her plate
with this being
her first day back at work.
- I can't wait to see
Weather Witch
get what she deserves.
♪ ♪
- Hey, you ready to get those
shards out of your hands?
- Hell yes!
I haven't been able to play
PS4 properly for weeks.
- See you in there.
- [exhales heavily]
Hey, you feel that?
- Feel what?
- That's the feeling
of free time.
AKA unbillable hours,
so we better not be seeing
any invoices from you
in the near future.
- Oh, that's all right.
This is one mystery
I will solve for free.
♪ ♪
[computer beeping]
- The state versus
Joslyn Jackam,
Criminal Court of Central City,
meta-crime number 99512.
Welcome back to my courtroom,
Miss Horton.
I trust your maternity leave
was enjoyable?
- Thank you, Your Honor.
I am very happy
to be back at work.
Yeah, there never really is
enough time
with a newborn, is there?
- There is not.
You may proceed.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
The prosecution
intends to prove
that between November 20th
and 27th,
Joslyn Jackam
used this device,
a so-called piece of meta-tech,
to unlawfully and intentionally
harm the citizens
of Central City.
Her meta-crimes include
massive property damage
at Iron Heights,
the grounding
of 21 separate flights
at Sheldon County Airport,
and the attempted murder
of her own father,
Mark Mardon.
Now, this attack
on her father was...
[eerie pulsation]
Uh...
Uh, the...
the attack on her father
was premeditated.
Um, and...
the prosecution
is seeking the...
[eerie pulsation]
[gasps]
- Are you okay?
- Uh...
yeah, it's just a...
feeling.
I'll be fine.
[exhales heavily]
The prosecution is seeking the
maximum sentence, Your Honor.
♪ ♪
- Gotcha.
All right, almost done.
Micro-scale surgery
is not the easiest.
- Is that why you missed these
the first time?
- Hey, now!
- [grunting]
- All right, there you go.
Your hands are officially
dagger shard free.
- Hallelu.
- One more thing.
[shimmering]
- Mm, meta-sutures
for meta-wounds,
that's clever.
Ah! Note to self,
ice healing actually hurts.
- Don't be a wuss.
- Wuss.
You're the wuss.
Looks like you've got
this whole
Caitlyn/Killer Frost thing
down pat.
- Eh, not totally.
- I got it.
- But it is getting easier
to switch to Killer Frost
when I need to.
So those sutures should stay
frozen while the wound heals.
Once they melt, you can
take the bandages off.
You'll be good to go.
- I have to confess.
I've actually really enjoyed
not having my powers lately.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I got used to being Cisco again
sans Vibe-age, you know?
And not having villains
breathing down my neck
once a week, I have to say,
is pretty schway.
- Well, if we're gonna
defeat Cicada,
we need
a fully functioning Vibe.
So hopefully
this does the trick.
Here, souvenirs.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
♪ ♪
- Opening statements
are underway
in the trial of Joss Jackam,
otherwise known
as Weather Witch.
♪ ♪
- Just saying,
nothing wrong
with three or four
martinis at lunch.
- It is when you get in
your Lamborghini and drive.
Sir, sir, focus here.
- [exhaling]
- Touch your nose.
[pulsating]
[engine turning over]
- Hey! That's my car!
[tires squealing]
- And then what happened,
Miss Pellett?
- She created some kind
of lightning tornado.
I wasn't sure if any of us
were gonna make it.
[cell phone buzzing]
- I got to go.
- [clears throat]
One moment, please.
- I got to go.
There's been a car theft.
- What are you talking about?
You're my lead CSI witness.
You're on the stand
in 30 minutes.
- I'm sorry.
It's a Lamborghini, all right?
The cops aren't gonna be able
to keep up with this thing.
It'll be quick.
- 30 minutes.
- All right.
- Miss Horton?
[suspenseful music]
- [clears throat]
Hmm, where were we?
[engine revving]
[sirens wailing]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[tires screeching]
[truck horn blaring]
♪ ♪
- Guys, the car just turned
north on 8th,
headed towards Wakefield.
- Got it.
Get ready to take
control of the wheel.
- What are you gonna do?
- Get the driver.
- Here we go.
[engine revving]
♪ ♪
[pulsating]
[sonic boom]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Dad!
- [groaning]
- What's happening?
- I can't stop vibrating.
- Guys! We need your help!
- Guys!
- With what?
- With...[groaning]
- With that?
- I can't stop phasing.
- And I can't
counter-phase him forever.
- Okay, that's not good.
If you keep going
but you don't,
then you could...
fall to your death.
- Yeah!
- What are we gonna do?
both: Let him.
- Uh...
both: What?
- Yes, if you phase
through the floor,
you're actually gonna fall
into the pipeline cell
directly below us.
- And the dampening unit
will negate your powers.
- Unless we don't
time it right.
In which case, your torso would
be severed from your legs
as you enter the cell.
- Not helping.
- Stop, stop.
Okay, stop.
I tr...I trust you Cisco.
- Move to the right.
No, my right.
- Cisco! Come on!
- Okay, stop right there!
One step back.
- Cisco!
- Actually, never mind,
one step forward.
Okay, ready?
Three, two, one, go!
- [screams]
[screams]
[computer beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What's going on with me?
- So...
the car you touched
was saturated with
unstable dark matter.
- And because you were phasing
at the time,
it caused your body
to destabilize
on a cellular level.
- When I got close
to the driver,
I saw dark matter veins
flare up,
just like on the back
of Spencer Young's phone.
- So the car is a piece
of meta-tech?
- That or whatever was
controlling it.
- How long is he gonna
have to stay in there for?
- Without the help
of the power dampeners,
it could take up to a day?
- No, no, no, no! I-I have to
present evidence on the stand
in, like, ten minutes.
Cecile's gonna kill me.
- That's not good.
- Um...
I could do it.
♪ ♪
Cecille:You can't be serious.
- Well, when Dad
made me official,
he submitted my paperwork
to the court,
so I'm qualified to present
forensic evidence.
I can do this.
- [scoffs]
I cannot believe this is
happening on my first day back.
It's my first day back.
Okay.
Go to the court reporter.
Check in.
Tell her that Barry
was in a traffic accident.
- Yes.
- And, Nora, when you're
up there on the stand,
you just follow my lead.
Got it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Don't worry.
Nora can handle this.
- It's not that.
I've decided I'm gonna pursue
a lighter sentence.
- Why the change of heart?
- Because I keep feeling these
waves of remorse
coming off of Joss.
I think she just wants
to start over
so she doesn't turn out
like her father.
So, Miss West,
can you explain what effect
these conditions had on
the Sheldon County Airport?
- The facility was hit by winds
ranging from
150 to 250 miles per hour.
- Wow, that's...
that is pretty dangerous.
And yet not a single person
was injured.
- Well, no,
but that was because...
- What about these
lightning marks on the tarmac?
Would you say that
that is common,
given the nature of the weather
during the incident
in question?
- Yes, but luckily,
in this case,
the lightning only hit
the runway
and not
the surrounding structures.
- The structures where all
of the passengers were.
I would say
that is pretty lucky indeed.
Your Honor,
the prosecution rests.
- So that's it? You're not
gonna ask me anything else?
♪ ♪
- Well, it would appear so.
Mr. Lee, I think you're up.
♪ ♪
- Miss West,
is my client a meta-human?
- No, but she used meta-tech.
Specifically a weather staff
that was corrupted
by dark matter.
- So one could say it was
the staff, not my client,
that attacked the Sheldon
County Airport that night?
- No, one couldn't.
She used that staff.
- But isn't this just
an ordinary weather staff
corrupted by dark matter?
These are your words.
- Yes, but...
- And since dark matter
was able to corrupt a tool
and turn it into a weapon
of destruction,
isn't it also possible it could
corrupt the defendant?
- No. Dark matter doesn't
make you do things.
She pointed lightning at a
hangar full of scared families.
Your Honor, there were
little kids in that hangar.
Did you know that...that
lightning is five times hotter
than the surface
of the sun?
That is the kind of power
that the defendant unleashed
upon those people.
[scoffs]
She did this.
This was her choice,
and she can't be trusted.
- No, Miss West,
you must sit down.
- I know, but, Your Honor...
[gavel banging]
- Sit down!
- No! She's right.
I'm guilty,
and I should pay
for what I did.
♪ ♪
- What you doing?
- Get a load of this.
You know those shards
you removed?
I ran a biochemical analysis
on them
and the tissue
from my hands.
- You know how to do that?
- I picked up a thing or two
from Caitlin Snow MD
over the years,
and I found this.
[computer beeping]
That's my tissue
right after I got sliced.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's from today.
- Almost all the dark matter
is gone.
- The shards weren't dampening
my powers.
They were removing them.
- So the dagger has
anti-dark matter properties.
- Yes!
- Cisco, if we can synthesize
that into a serum,
we could get rid
of Cicada's powers entirely.
- And not just his powers,
everyone's.
- Everyone's?
- Caitlyn,
we could make
a meta-human cure.
- You think we need
a meta-human cure?
- Don't you?
- Um...
- Okay, maybe not.
But I seem to remember
a time when you did?
- Sure, when I first discovered
Killer Frost,
I wanted to get rid of her.
But when she was gone, it felt
like a piece of me was missing.
Besides, we have seen
meta-human powers
do really good things.
- Okay, yeah! If you can
build an ice bridge
to avoid rush hour traffic,
but what if my existence
gives everyone around me
radiation poisoning
like "Fallout"?
Those metas, we created them
against their will.
- No, Thawne created
the particle accelerator
and he sabotaged it.
- And who shattered the
satellite full of dark matter
and created God knows
how many metas?
We did that.
This cure could give
meta-humans a second chance
at having a normal life.
- Maybe not everyone wants
a normal life, Cisco.
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
[engine revving]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
- Watch out!
[tires screeching]
[brakes squealing]
♪ ♪
- Who does this lady
think she is?
♪ ♪
[device beeping]
[pulsating]
[locks clicking]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- Who are you?
- Your ride.
Let's go.
- So Joss Jackam never made it
to Iron Heights.
- Nope, and
the transport driver said
that the woman who took her
used something
that completely
shut down his truck.
- Pause.
That. Look familiar?
- Ugh, another piece
of satellite shard.
- So the fob is the meta-tech?
- Yeah, probably sends out
some kind of dark matter pulse
that overrides any
guidance system in seconds.
- So as long as
she has an engine,
she can control it
and we still
don't even know
who we're looking for.
- Maybe we do.
Hey, can you fast-forward?
Stop.
Yeah, look, that salute.
She's definitely military.
- Okay, let's run that face
through the DOD database.
[computer beeping]
- Raya Van Zandt.
Former air force,
ace pilot, mechanic,
and expert
in vehicle operations.
She was
dishonorably discharged.
- Call sign was Silver Ghost.
Huh?
- The rest of her
military record was sealed.
- Okay, well, I'm gonna see
if my dad can call in a favor
and maybe we can get a copy.
- Yeah, and in the meantime,
it looks like we have
two bad girls to track down.
- I'm not so sure, Nora.
I mean, Cecile said that
she could feel Joss' remorse.
- Come on, Mom.
That was a show.
I mean, do you think
this escape was a coincidence?
- Uh, well,
we don't know yet, Nora.
- Yes, we do.
Raya got that fob to break Joss
out of the prison transport.
I guarantee you Joss
is a part of this.
- How do you know that?
- Because bad people
don't change.
[computer beeps]
- Hey, guys, any way
you could send down
some food?
- Welcome to home base.
- Home base of what?
- The Young Rogues.
There's been enough
old men running this town.
Our turn.
I have my eyes
on a few candidates,
but for this job, plan on it
just being you and me.
- Um,
I'm not planning anything!
I don't even know who you are!
Just take me back!
- You ever heard of A.R.G.U.S.?
It's an off-the-grid facility
primed with bleeding-edge tech,
and it's protected by one
of the most advanced
security systems on Earth.
The only thing that can
short it out is
a billion joules
of electricity.
- So a few bolts of lightning.
- You're the
Weather Witch, right?
Beneath this wall is
the facility's power junction.
You hit that and we have
a four-minute window
to get something that
will make us unstoppable.
- No, look,
even if I was gonna help you,
and I'm not,
I need my weather staff
to control any of that,
and right now,
that is in police holdup.
So if you could
just take me back.
- Okay.
[clears throat]
To do what?
- Turn myself in.
- I see.
You don't want to be
like your dad.
I get that,
but it's too late.
You're a criminal.
So am I.
And those people out there,
trust me, all they think is,
"Like father, like daughter."
But I guess you need to find
that out for yourself,
don't you?
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
- Find me when you do.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- Well...right.
- Yeah.
- [clears throat]
That will hold you
until you get out...oh!
[slurping]
Uh, can I ask you a question?
Uh, do you have a minute?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
Yes, you're not
going anywhere.
So, um, last year, you came
out of the Speed Force
and you were writing
a kind of a symbol language.
Do you remember that?
- Yeah, I remember.
- And apparently,
Cisco could only translate
one of these phrases.
Right?
- So far, yeah. I mean,
Gideon couldn't even do it.
- Gideon.
Right, Gideon.
So what do you think
that language was?
- I don't know. It was some
kind of, uh, chronolinguistics.
- Chronolinguistics
that you got from your time
in the Speed Force, which
is all time at once, right?
Past, present, future.
What do you think this
language was? Future, maybe?
- Why? Is this about Cicada?
- Cicada? No, no.
No, It's just, um...
le mystère, huh?
I'm a detective.
I see mystery everywhere, so...
- Uh-huh.
- Uh, all right. Thank you.
See you next time.
Okay...oh!
Ah, before I forget,
the Legends, uh,
dropped off some, um, books
to help you pass the time.
- Huh.
- "Uncaged Desire."
Your kind of caged desire.
Hope you enjoy it.
- Huh.
- See you next time.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, probably not very good.
See you!
[siren blaring]
- What is it?
- According to Doppler, it's
a hurricane in Central City.
- No, it's not a hurricane.
It's Joss.
I'm on it.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- What, no Flash today?
- Figured he wasn't needed
to stop a fake hurricane.
Guess we can add
damaging private property
to your résumé.
- Look, I just need your help.
- Oh, stop with the sorry act.
That ended when your friend
helped you escape.
- She is not my buddy,
and I did not escape.
Look,
I want to turn myself back in.
- Oh, you really expect me
to believe that?
- My dad
is the career criminal,
not me.
I just...
I want to show everybody
that I'm not the person
that they think I am.
- Then what do you need me for?
- You're a hero.
If you vouch for me,
people will know
that I'm telling the truth.
Look, I will tell you
everything.
I'll even show you
where that woman took me.
Just give me a chance.
♪ ♪
- If anyone asks,
you never saw this.
- Thank you, Major Morgan.
Please tell
the lieutenant general
that my dad and I owe him one.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Special delivery.
One Weather Witch.
- What? I thought you were
gonna help me.
I'm trying to turn myself in.
No, I-I didn't escape.
I-I was kidnapped.
Will you please tell them?
- Sorry,
I don't trust criminals.
She's all yours.
- No! No, no!
This is a misunderstanding!
This is unfair!
If I could just talk to her,
please!
[whooshing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales heavily]
- Your father does
the exact same thing.
When something's on his mind,
he runs.
- Nothing's on my mind, Mom.
- I got to take a look at
Raya Van Zandt's DOD file.
- Oh, yeah,
did you find the connection
between her and Joss?
- Well, there doesn't seem
to be one.
- Really?
- Yeah, she left the air force
after a failed mission overseas,
and then she spent
two months on desk duty,
and then she was
dishonorably discharged.
- [scoffs]
But it seems like she has
a pretty good service record.
- Exactly, so clearly
the DOD had egg on its face
and Raya became its scapegoat.
I'm just saying, Nora,
not everyone is
as bad as they seem.
Raya, Joss. I think everyone
deserves a second chance.
If you don't believe me,
ask your father.
He gives more second chances
than anyone I've ever met.
♪ ♪
[machine buzzing]
- Come on. Come on.
Yes. Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
[keyboard keys clacking]
[computer beeping]
Yes!
♪ ♪
What the hell are you doing?
- What the hell
areyou doing?
- Well, I was distilling
dark matter ore
from Cicada's dagger shards.
But I can't really
do that anymore, can I?
- Whoops.
- Why did you do that?
- You're smart.
You can figure it out.
- When are you
gonna figure out that
a meta-cure could
actually help people?
- Listen, I heard all about it,
short stuff.
But you know what?
Caity and I,
we're doing just fine,
and so were you until Cicada
got all up in your head.
- Don't do that.
This isn't just about me.
- Oh, the hell it isn't!
And...and you know what?
I get it.
He tried to kill you.
You're trying to create
something that'll save us all.
- Yeah, I am!
All of us!
Barry, Iris, Nora,
they have a family.
Even you and Caitlyn have
your weird little family.
But what about my family?
I want a wife
to grow old with.
I want a kid.
And I don't want them
to wonder all the time
if their dad is in trouble,
if he's even gonna
make it home tonight.
- Cisco, you don't have
to choose between having powers
and having a family.
- Yeah?
Well, some of us do.
I'm not the Flash.
I don't want to be the Flash.
I want to be me.
A cure is the only way.
Or it was.
♪ ♪
- What?
Oh, come on, girl.
- [sighs]
You're reading Mick's book?
- This is...
surprisingly well-written.
♪ ♪
What's going on?
- [sighs]
Just having
a hard time believing
some people can change.
♪ ♪
- How come?
- 'Cause after everything
that you've seen,
don't you think that
bad people stay bad?
- Not always.
When I first met Leonard Snart,
he was a criminal.
Probably the worst criminal
in the city.
But I...
you know, I knew
that there was a good person
in there somewhere,
and look at him.
Turned out to be a Legend.
Died a hero.
If he can change,
anyone can.
- You really believe that?
- Yeah. I do.
- What about Eobard Thawne?
♪ ♪
- I think...
part of being a hero
is being able to see
the good in people.
So yeah,
maybe someday in the future...
even Thawne could change.
Besides,
if we don't believe in people,
who will?
♪ ♪
[siren wailing]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[sirens wailing]
- Very funny!
I got 595s!
[sirens wailing in distance]
- We got a lot of vehicles!
Let's go.
- Copy that. Suit up!
- We've got multiple 595s
in our own parking lot!
- Get out there quick!
- Requesting more backup!
We've got a lot!
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- Doing what no one else
is gonna do for you...
♪ ♪
Offer you a second chance...
Weather Witch.
♪ ♪
- That's it.
That's where
the power junction is.
Give it everything you got.
[dramatic music]
[thunder booming]
♪ ♪
[lightning crackling]
- What the hell was that?
- I don't know, sir.
But it knocked out
security grids 41 through 60.
♪ ♪
[siren blaring]
- Ten years
and $24 million later,
the stealth automobile,
AKA the SAM, was born.
Rumor has it that everything
under its hood
comes directly from WayneTech.
♪ ♪
- This is a $24-million
prototype?
What can it do?
- Let's find out.
[device beeps]
[pulsating]
[exciting music]
[giggles]
- [laughs]
[engine revving]
♪ ♪
- Is it Joss or Raya?
- I'm guessing both
because someone just stole
a very expensive vehicle
from A.R.G.U.S.
after a very precise
lightning strike.
- It's a next-gen prototype
with all the bells
and whistles.
If bells and whistles could
explode and murder people.
- And supposedly
it's untrackable.
So how do we find it?
- We don't search for the car.
- We search for them.
- If Joss made lightning
strike again,
it means she has her staff.
- Oh, so we can track
the dark matter in it. Nice!
- I got the location.
♪ ♪
- Okay, remember, Nora,
whatever you do,
don't touch the car
while using your powers.
- Hey, Caitlin, can I steal you
for a second?
[engine revving]
[women cheering]
- [laughs]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
[tires screeching]
- Joyride's over,
Silver Ghost.
Joss,
I need to talk to you.
- Hard pass.
[tablet beeping]
[grille clicking]
[missile beeping]
- [grunting]
- Got to love
remote detonation.
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
- Icy roads ahead.
- Oh, my God. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Raya!
Raya!
[tablet beeping]
[tires squealing]
[gasping]
♪ ♪
[tires squealing]
- [sighs]
- [laughs]
- Holy Buckaroo Banzai.
- It phases?
- Whatever phase-trick
they just used,
it jammed our tracking.
We can't get a lock on them
if she doesn't use
that weather staff.
- XS is gonna come after us.
- Let her try.
[tablet beeping]
♪ ♪
Hear no evil, see no evil.
We're invisible.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Cisco?
Can you connect me
to the car's comm system?
- No, but best I can do is
have you send out radio waves,
and if the car's nearby,
it'll pick them up.
- Do it.
[computer beeping]
Joss? Joss, it's XS.
I hope you can hear me.
You tried to tell me
something earlier.
that you wanted to pay
for the crimes
that you committed.
You said you weren't
a criminal like your father.
You asked me to give you
a second chance,
but I didn't listen.
Now I'm asking you
for a second chance.
Joss,
this isn't who you are.
[engine revving]
♪ ♪
- Nora, the car's headed
straight for you.
- I don't see anything.
[ice crackling]
♪ ♪
- Nora, look out!
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
- How the hell
did I lose control?
[pulsating]
- Hey, hold on to me.
This is gonna feel weird.
[tablet beeping]
- Well, at least
we got their wheels.
What's left of them.
- Thanks for
the last-minute rescue.
- For the what?
- Icing up the road.
- I didn't ice the road.
- What? Who...
♪ ♪
- And...
time! 24 hours are up.
- Okay, I double-checked
with Caitlin,
and there doesn't seem to be
any unstable dark matter
in your biometric scans.
- Okay.
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
- [chuckles]
- Man, it feels good
to be out of there.
- We definitely missed you, Dad.
- Sorry I haven't been able
to help with everything.
Do we know where
Joss and Raya are now?
- No, we got nothing yet.
- But you were right
about Joss.
She saved my life.
If she hadn't iced over
the road...
- But she did because
you connected with her.
- It's like Dad said,
she just needed someone
to believe in her.
- Sounds like you found
your own Leonard Snart.
- Well, time might prove me
wrong, but I think so.
I hope so.
I'm sorry I messed up
your first day back.
- It's all right, Nora.
There's always day two.
I'm happy you're back.
- Thanks.
- Hey do you wanna
help me find Cisco?
I gotta get this extrapolator
thing recalibrated.
I went to go see Joe in Tibet,
and I ended up in Fiji.
- [chuckling]
- Being a parent
sure is hard sometimes.
- Yeah, it is.
But there's nothing like it.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[footsteps tapping]
♪ ♪
Okay, well, we can't both
be the basket case.
- "We're all pretty bizarre.
Some of us are just better
at hiding it."
Come on, "Breakfast Club"?
It's one of the only movies
Killer Frost and I
actually agree on.
- Let me guess,
she's into Bender?
- Totally. She loves him.
- Yeah, makes sense.
I'd ship that.
- Put that on.
It's cold where we're going.
♪ ♪
- Your dad's old lab.
- Mm-hmm.
- Cool.
Caitlin,
why did you bring me here?
- Because despite our
last encounter with him,
he did create a meta-gene.
So I was thinking that you
could use his research
to do the reverse.
- Um, okay,
don't look now, but if I
didn't know any better,
I'd say this feels a lot
like you helping me
make a meta-human cure.
- I couldn't stop
thinking about
what you said
about how a cure
would give you a second chance
at a normal life.
No friend would stand
in the way of that.
- But there is a difference
between you standing in my way
and you actively helping me.
- I still think this is
dangerous, but...
maybe if I'm involved,
we can have some ground rules.
Like the first
and most important,
we will never,
ever force a cure on anyone.
- Okay.
Rule number one.
We're not just here
to make a cure.
We're here to make a choice.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Nora.
You either trust me,
or you don't.
There's no in-between.
- Fine.
I don't trust you.
- [scoffs]
- But I'm willing to give you
the chance to change my mind.
- Well,
that might take some time.
And time,
as you may recall,
is not on my side.
Minutes are minutes,
seconds are seconds,
and there's very few
of them left.
[timer beeping]
♪ ♪
- I want to believe that
there is good inside
of you somewhere, Thawne.
♪ ♪
- Let me prove there is.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
What's next?
[pulsating]
♪ ♪
[lights clunking]
[device whirs, beeps]
- Hello, Dr. Wells.
- Hello, Gideon.
I have access to all the files?
Right?
- Of course.
Which files would you
like me to locate?
- I would like you
to locate the files
from Nora West-Allen.
- I'm sorry, Dr. Wells,
but all entries have been
permanently deleted
by Nora West-Allen.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.