(intro to "Jingle Bell Rock"
begins)
♪ Jingle bell, jingle bell,
jingle bell rock ♪
♪ Jingle bells swing
and jingle bells ring ♪
♪ Snowing and blowing... ♪
TRANSLUCENT:
Ho, ho, ho! Merry Christmas!
Who's been naughty?
- It is dead center on your brand.
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's get a picture.
- I love pictures.
Hey.
♪ In jingle bell time ♪
- PHOTOGRAPHER: Smile.
- ♪ Dancing and prancing in Jingle Bell Square... ♪
Another one.
♪ In the frosty air ♪
♪ What a bright time,
it's the right time ♪
♪ To rock the night away ♪
♪ Jingle bell time
is a swell time ♪
♪ To go gliding
in a one-horse sleigh... ♪
BUTCHER:
Oi, gorgeous.
- Vodka soda, hold the soda.
- Thank you.
Drinks are free,
but the food's bloody awful.
Ahi tartare, for fuck's sakes.
Okay. Just let me shake
a few more hands,
and then we'll be
out of here... whoa.
Easy, tiger.
I want you on your "A" game.
- "A" game?
- Mm-hmm.
You know,
I like the sound of that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
HOMELANDER:
Merry Christmas.
Becca.
New senior director,
digital marketing.
- Uh, yeah. How did you know?
- I have my sources.
And your nametag.
- (chuckles)
- Yes, that, too. (laughs)
- Uh, this is my husband, Billy.
- Great to meet you.
Billy Butcher.
Becca, you handled
my takeover, right?
Y-Yes, I-I did.
- You saw it?
- I loved it.
- U-Uh, wow. Thank you. (laughs)
- No, thank you.
- What'd you take over?
- BECCA: Vought's Twitter account.
- Yeah.
- Your brilliant wife here
did all the work.
She posted my photos,
she wrote my messages.
It was exceptional.
All right, so they thought
it was you up there,
but it was really Becca.
- (chuckles)
- Bit deceptive, isn't it?
Uh, no, Billy, that's what we do
'cause Homelander's busy
saving lives.
It's okay, it's okay.
I-It... you're right.
It's a little dishonest,
but I'm all thumbs when
it comes to that kind of stuff,
so leave it to the experts.
Listen, I would
love to talk to you
about maybe quarterbacking
the rest of my social media.
- Seriously?
- Absolutely.
My dad, he always said,
"Surround yourself with people
smarter than you."
Oh, my, uh, better half is, uh,
wanting my attention, but maybe
we could chat tomorrow.
That sounds wonderful.
Thank you.
Greet to meet you, pal.
Good to meet you.
Love that accent.
Hello, beautiful.
How the fuck does he walk around
in that sweaty fucking wetsuit
all day long,
- balls mashed up against his leg like pancakes?
- Oh, shh.
- What?
- You promised to behave.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
(siren wailing in distance)
HUGHIE:
Hi.
♪ ♪
(both moaning)
(gasps)
- Huh.
- Hmm.
I didn't realize you were
such a cigar aficionado.
(laughs)
I really, I just...
Mm. I can't get enough
of huge gross logs
- of filterless tobacco.
- (chuckles)
(laughs softly)
- This is all really nice.
- Mm-hmm.
But...
There is a "but" coming.
Okay.
But why did you bring me
to a hotel?
Hmm? And not your place?
Well, you know.
I mean, yeah, sure, my Dad
(laughs): could make you
some post-coital pizza rolls.
I just figured this would be
slightly less humiliating.
Yeah, all right.
Yeah.
Yeah, very convincing.
You okay? What's going on?
It's just...
I've never seen your place,
or your job.
You're kind of a mystery to me.
T-That's hot, right?
Look, you got to understand
that my dad
was nothing but corny jokes
and expensive gifts,
until he was gone, and all
the money along with him.
I know that
that's not you, but...
I need to know that the hotel
is a nice thing
and not a red flag thing.
I quit my job.
Um, I'm sorry, I-I...
I really should've told you.
After Robin, programming
other people's remotes,
it felt kind of pointless.
And yeah, I mean,
you can-you can meet my dad,
but you're gonna
regret asking that.
So everything's okay?
It's great.
No red flags.
Hmm.
♪ ♪
(birds singing)
Now, I know this is not
as swanky as New York City,
but to have a hero like you in
a place like Sandusky, I mean,
everyone down at the local
branch is just tickled pink.
- Yeah.
- Now, we got Cedar Point,
biggest roller-coaster park
in the whole U.S. of A.
We're just a couple short hours
from Cleveland or Toledo.
And Lake Erie? Right here,
- if you want to swim.
- Oh, yeah.
Ooh. Uh...
There it is.
- What's this?
- That's your per diem.
You get $75 a day.
Grocery store,
right down the street.
To make my own food?
There's a Dairy Queen, too.
Like Blizzards and stuff?
You betcha.
Well...
(sighs)
I mean, what about
my crime itinerary?
I think the best thing's just
to, you know, get out there
and put some points
on the board.
Not much crime in Sandusky.
I mean, we're not a shithole
like Akron.
(laughs)
But if something comes up,
we'll call.
You'll call?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
♪ I'm all out of love ♪
♪ What am I without you? ♪
♪ I I can't be too late ♪
♪ To say that I was so wrong ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ What are you thinking of? ♪
(vomits)
- Oh, this is killing me.
- Come on.
(groaning)
Damn.
Oh, no fucking way.
You need 3,000 calories an hour,
or you're gonna pass out.
I can't do this shit, man.
Tough shit.
You heard the doc.
Your heart is getting bigger,
balls are getting smaller,
your bone density's for shit.
That Compound V shit
is killing you.
Hey. Don't even say it out loud,
all right?
You don't know shit about it,
you understand?
I don't want to know.
And you're done, okay?
No more fucking around.
Did you see my last time
out there?
Sioux City's got a fucking
faster runner than me.
Then no more club openings
and commercial shoots.
Okay? None of that shit.
We train.
Back to the basics.
Nobody gets it back at my age.
I'm gonna be a freak show
like Ben Johnson,
racing against horses.
At least you'll still
be breathing.
(phone chimes)
(sighs):
Shit.
- I got to go.
- Where?
(sighs)
- What's going on?
- I missed you guys.
Just wanted to see
your smiling faces.
- (claps shoulder)
- Take a seat, buddy.
And, truth be known,
I felt like we were overdue
a little heart-to-heart.
A rap session,
maybe a little tough love.
(scoffs)
What's that supposed to mean?
(Homelander sighs)
It means that lately,
some of you
have been, eh,
a little out of sorts.
Erratic.
Unreliable.
Downright sloppy.
Not you, Noir.
You've been great.
But the rest of you...
(clicking tongue)
It is fair to say
that I am disappointed.
Got to keep your eye
on the ball, guys.
The enemies
are storming the gates.
I mean, we're not even The Seven
anymore, we're down to five.
We're dropping
like fucking flies,
but at least now I know why.
Uh...
Why...
Is this a joke?
Why is Hughie up there?
I don't understand.
Who is this guy?
This guy is Hugh Campbell.
He and Starlight
are going steady.
He's also one of the guys
who killed Translucent.
Wait, what?
HOMELANDER:
As well as blackmailing
Mesmer, Ezekiel, Popclaw
- and God knows who else.
- Popclaw?
No. No, no, no.
You... That-that is insane.
Starlight, sticks and stones
won't break my bones,
- but words...
- No, sir.
I'm sorry. I wasn't...
It's just, he's not...
I mean, why would he do that?
Good question.
A-Train, over to you.
- What?
- HOMELANDER: Oh, boy.
That little egg of yours
is still scrambled, huh?
How about now?
Oh, shit.
I know this guy.
HOMELANDER: You did smash
through his girlfriend,
so I should hope so.
Robin s-something or other.
I-I remember now, I-I've seen
him outside of Popclaw's place.
He was all in my face.
- You're fucking this guy?
- S... Okay, slow down.
I don't know what's going on,
but Hughie is not capable
of anything close to this.
Well, that is true, actually.
That's very true.
He is just a man, and,
(laughs): by the looks of it,
not much of one.
But... but hear me out.
W-What if he was helped? Hmm?
Say someone,
I don't know,
got him in to see Ezekiel
and got rid of the Deep.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on.
Keep those hands down
by your sides, missy.
Sit down.
Now... I know
that you want to make
this whole Deep thing
an "All the single ladies"
moment.
Power, right?
But really, what you've done
is pulled off
every criminal's wet dream.
I mean, The Seven
is down by two.
I just can't help noticing
that it all started
when you came along,
which makes me wonder,
which one of us is next, hmm?
You bitch.
- I didn't do anything.
- HOMELANDER: Enough!
We're a different fucking breed.
We shine with the golden light
of providence, but you,
you've been helping these
fucking mud people
- to go against us.
- No.
Shut your fucking mouth,
young lady.
If you were in my position...
...what would you do to you?
(crying)
Homelander, that's enough.
You got something to add, Maeve?
She didn't know.
Well, she stinks of adrenaline
and her heart's beating
like a little rabbit.
The only thing she's guilty of
is being fucking stupid.
She obviously fell
for this Hugh Campbell guy
and he's pumping her
for information,
so back off, leave her alone.
Wow.
Starlight,
you must be something special.
Hmm?
I can't remember the last time
Maeve gave a shit ab...
Well, gave a shit about anyone,
really.
And if I say no?
Come on.
(whispering):
I got this.
It's you and me,
remember?
(whispering): Don't say
I never do anything for you.
All right.
You want her, you got her.
She's your responsibility now.
I just hope
you're right about her,
for both your sakes.
Class dismissed.
Look at this.
Oh, no. You don't stir,
you fold. Like this.
Now that's what
makes them spongy.
Here you go.
(door opens)
She wants to know
where you were.
That's a compelling
fucking question.
Hey, can we talk?
That's what we're doing,
innit?
No, I mean...
There ain't no secrets here,
son. Spit it out.
Stop being an asshole,
just talk to the guy.
Hughie doesn't mind.
Do you, Hughie?
Okay, fine. I don't think
I can do this anymore.
- Do what?
- This.
I mean, Vought,
whatever with Kimiko,
it's-it's awful,
and you got to stop it,
- but I can't.
- Right.
You just want to kick back,
drink a few Mai Tais,
and let us do all the work,
is that it?
You know, I managed to go
my whole life
without seeing someone
die horribly,
and now I'm up to about
a half dozen,
- so I think I'm good.
- Please.
You're a fucking killer, Hughie,
just like the rest of us.
Now, why don't you
stop pissing around
and tell everybody what this
is really all about?
- Yeah?
- Fine.
Annie.
- Fuck.
- HUGHIE: Okay?
It's about Annie.
Fucking finally.
He's been sneaking off to
give her one at Lincoln Grand.
- You've been following me?
- Like you gave me a choice.
She doesn't know anything, okay?
I'm not gonna tell her anything.
- All right? We'll just...
- Just what?
Fuck off to Epcot? The Hamptons?
Maybe pump out a few
flying babies?
No. I... I don't know.
No, you don't know
'cause you ain't thinking,
- except with your dick.
- You're wrong about her.
That bitch is fucking
playing you,
and you're too fucking blind
to see it.
Right, so better to be loyal
to a dead woman
who doesn't know
and doesn't care?
How's that working out for you?
(cell phone ringing)
- HUGHIE: Hey, Dad.
- MAN (on phone): Hey, Hughie.
Long time no talk.
You know, I've been thinking
about you a lot lately.
Who's this?
I thought you would
recognize my voice.
You spend so much time obsessing
about me, am I right?
- Say hi to your baby boy, Dad.
- Oh. H-Hey, hey, hey, Hughie.
Why is he here? He says you're
in some kind of trouble.
Dad, are you okay?
Oh, o-okay.
He's fine.
Remington Steele's almost on.
A-Train, listen to me.
Oh, shit, if he's burned,
then I'm fucked.
HUGHIE:
He's on fucking Medicaid.
He's harmless. Let him go.
My place is burned.
They've got me.
Oh, my God.
Get your ass over here
in 20 minutes,
or I'm gonna burst through him
like a fucking piñata,
do you understand me?
Just like I did your girlfriend.
- Yeah. Got it.
- And, Hughie,
alone. If I catch a whiff,
a whiff of one of your
- little asshole friends...
- I got it.
All my bank accounts are frozen
and flagged. Monique,
listen, when you get this,
leave the house immediately.
Lay low and call me.
- Well, I hope she was fucking worth it.
- It's not Annie.
- She doesn't know.
- It doesn't matter.
- I'm gonna fucking do her in.
- The hell you will!
Hey, hold on a second.
She doesn't know. It wasn't her.
She's never seen me before.
Not once, not ever.
So how did I get burned?
Mesmer. You fucking idiots
had to go to Mesmer.
Fuck me.
Thank you.
That was not smart,
to sleep with her.
- Hughie.
- Dad.
(whispering):
He's acting strange.
You know, real jumpy.
- Where is he?
- I don't know, he...
Right here, sport. (laughs)
Look what I got.
Special 2016 Comic-Con edition?
What, did they make, like,
a few hundred of these?
- Watch out, A-Train's coming.
- (laughing)
You were a fan!
You were a fan, and not,
like, a dabbler, no,
you were super fan 99.
Excuse me, sir.
- W-What is this about?
- Shut the fuck up.
Dad, it's gonna be okay. Hey.
I came alone.
You let him go.
Alone, huh?
- Wow.
- Ah!
You really did come alone.
Next time... there's not gonna be
a next time, but next time...
have at least
a few cards up your sleeve.
Okay. You mean, um,
you mean, like this?
- Jonesing for a little jet fuel?
- W-What is that?
I don't know what that shit is.
Oh, you don't?
So you don't mind if I do this.
- No, fuck!
- What?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I have a bigger dose.
I have a real dose
hidden somewhere outside.
Let him go, I hand it over,
then you can do whatever
you want with me.
Now tell me what's better,
the rush or knowing that,
as long as you take it,
you'll be the fastest?
If you try anything,
I can catch up to dear old daddy
in a millisecond.
- Dad, time to go.
- Not without you.
I'll be right behind you.
I am not leaving you
with him, all right.
You're just a kid.
You're my kid.
Dad.
I'll be all right.
I got this.
Go.
(door opens, closes)
All right, where is it?
You know, this shit
must be pretty good
if it's worth running through
a human being for.
Oh, my God, man,
that was an accident.
- Where the fuck is the V?
- That accident had a name.
And what about Popclaw?
She had a name, too.
Charlotte!
The only good thing
in my life is gone now.
What is this, man? I kill your
girlfriend and you kill mine?
I didn't kill your girlfriend.
You used her.
You put her in danger,
and then you threw her out
like she was fucking garbage.
How does this not all start
with you, Hughie?
The only difference
between you and me
is that I made a mistake.
The shit that you did
was on purpose.
So who's worse?
(screaming)
You bitch!
You know, you're right.
It would've been stupid
to come alone.
(grunting)
(groaning)
MOTHER'S MILK: Monique,
it's not safe here anymore.
We got to go.
You swore to me
and to Jesus Christ
that you were done
with Billy Butcher.
I know, I get it.
Everything Butcher touches
- turns to flaming hot shit.
- No, I ain't blaming him.
Last I checked,
you're a grown-ass man.
It's my fault, okay?
But we can't do this right now.
- You put us in danger without thinking twice, Marvin.
- Monique, just...
Daddy!
Hey, baby, come here.
Give me a hug. Oh.
- What have you been up to?
- I was drawing you a picture.
You were? Can I see?
Oh, my goodness,
this is beautiful.
Thank you, baby.
Janine, honey, Daddy's gonna
take us on a sleepover.
Can you help Mommy
pack your toys?
- Good girl.
- Baby, we're running late.
We don't have time to pack toys.
We got to go.
I knew you'd vote
your conscience, Senator.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
(sighs) Three votes to go.
(laughs)
And the B.A. guys
said that the Pentagon
is shelling out
$35 billion on the low end.
- That puts us ahead of Lockheed.
- Amazing.
That's incredible.
Edgar must be thrilled.
Ugh, fuck Edgar.
We did this, you and me.
This is about us.
Hey, do you remember
that marketing girl?
Ashley?
Um, I'm sorry,
I-I had to fire her, she...
No. No, no, no.
Seven, eight years ago.
Becca.
Becca?
- Yes.
- Becca Butcher.
That's it.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, her.
What about her?
Well, she's missing.
What do you mean, missing?
I mean missing, as in missing,
presumed dead.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I looked at her file, and
the cops think it was suicide.
Mm.
Yeah, it seems her husband...
Well, he got pretty riled up.
William Butcher.
Am I supposed to know his name?
No. Not specifically, but...
I was just wondering if you knew
what happened to her.
No, I just assumed
that she quit.
Quit?
Is there any particular reason
why you are asking
all of these questions?
No, no. I'm just... curious.
It's interesting, right?
I mean, it's...
Yeah. Yeah, it's definitely sad.
Yeah. Yes, very.
You know, I was, I was
thinking that maybe, um,
I could get Maria to stay late
with the baby and...
...maybe we could
order in and...
catch up. (giggles)
Just me and you.
You know what?
That sounds amazing.
But you go be a mommy.
(pats leg)
I'm telling you,
you're gonna love it here.
You like roller coasters?
I'm more of a water park guy.
Well, Cedar Point's got both.
Mm-hmm.
You first.
(panting):
Huh...?
Oh. Well, most girls
like the suit.
Well, I'm not most girls.
Mm. Is it true what they say?
Come on, baby.
I got you here in the flesh.
I gotta see it.
Please?
I don't, I don't look
like everyone else.
That's what I'm counting on.
All right.
(belt thuds)
(chuckles):
Oh, look at those gills.
(gasps)
Oh, my God, that's so fucked up.
Hey, can-can...
Can we just, uh...
Ah... be gentle, be gentle.
Ow, it's tender. Oh, God.
Okay. That hurts.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
- Stop, stop. Stop, stop, stop.
- Come on, it's just my pinkie.
No, I said it hurt.
All right, look,
I think maybe you should go.
(scoffs)
I'm not going anywhere,
you little fucking freak.
- Lay back.
- (scoffs)
I said, lay back.
Ah. God. Ow!
- Oh, my God. Oh, God.
- (moaning)
- Oh, yeah. You like that?
- Ow.
Oh, you little fucking freak.
Oh, you like getting
your fucking gills fingered?
(grunts)
Ow. Oh, God.
Ow, ow. Oh, God.
(indistinct P.A. announcement)
(screams)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
Having a good growler, are we?
How did you...?
I stuck a little bug on you
back at that shithole of yours.
'Cause, you know, fuck you.
No...
What did you expect me to do?
It was Homelander.
(echoes):
You got to talk to me.
(panting):
Wait, wait. No. I can help you.
Becca?
(whimpers)
Your wife.
'Cause she's missing?
I can help you find her.
(panting)
Please, I have a daughter!
No!
(panting)
(doorbell rings)
Don't want none, fuck off.
I'm here about your wife.
I believe this was a few days
after you met Homelander
at that Christmas party?
She was alone with him
for three hours.
Not long after that,
Rebecca went missing
and has remained so ever since.
One way or another, Mr. Butcher,
I believe Homelander
was involved.
Homelander?
But he's a fucking superhero.
You wouldn't believe
what they get up to.
Who the fuck are you?
My name is Mallory.
I'm the person
who can get you payback.
(ringing)
Who's calling?
(sniffles)
Nobody.
(sighs)
Listen, if you...
if you want to talk,
I suppose we...
No.
But would it kill you
to make me one of those?
(chuckles)
You know, I had someone once.
We were gonna get away,
start a family.
So what happened?
(chuckles)
Well...
Everyone always asks,
what's our special weakness?
Gamma rays?
Iron daggers?
Some ridiculous, stupid thing?
The truth is,
our weakness
is the same as anyone's.
It's people.
The people we care about.
So I say, cut them loose.
For your good and for theirs.
That way
you're really bulletproof.
What's up, man?
How'd you end up here?
Oh, tell me about it.
(sighs)
Me, too.
What's that?
Oh.
Wait, you can't get
in your head about that.
It's really not
that big of a deal.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Just hang tight.
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, hey. Can I take one of these
lobsters back with me?
- You got it.
- Thanks.
Oh, wait, no, no, no, no.
Not that one.
This one.
Yeah, that's my guy.
(chuckles)
Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
FRENCHIE:
Larry, please.
I just need a secure place
for a few nights.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Putain!
(sighs)
STARLIGHT:
Hi, you've reached Annie.
- I can't come to the phone...
- Oh, damn it.
(cartoon playing on computer)
That's Hughie, baby.
- She looks like you.
- Nah.
She's good-looking, man.
Right, baby? (chuckles)
Mr. Campbell.
Ooh, yeah.
Pleasure to meet you.
Billy Butcher.
Oh, Hugh Campbell.
- You got a hell of a lad there.
- Well, yeah.
He's all mine.
Hello, hello, hello.
What have we got here, then, eh?
What's your name, sweetheart?
You can call me Uncle Billy.
He ain't your uncle, honey.
- He ain't nothing to you.
- Monique.
Good to see you.
Hi, you've reached Annie.
I can't come
to the phone right now...
(clears throat)
(whispers):
What's she doing?
Uh, okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Does the Oriental girl not talk?
Uh, Asian.
- Yeah.
- You're right. Asian.
And no, I don't think she does.
Dad, I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
No, no, no. Don't say sorry. No.
Look at you,
standing up for yourself.
Jings.
(both chuckle)
(pats knee)
Cold feet, huh?
What?
You said Raynor got cold feet.
Yeah, that's what I said.
You know what I think it is?
I think
Raynor's plenty interested,
only she didn't bring you
Homelander's head on a plate,
and you blew
the whole fucking thing up.
How am I doing so far?
No, mate. Way off.
Bullshit, Butcher.
You're so hot for Homelander
right now, Butcher,
you're not gonna let anything
get in your way,
even if it's
your own fucking friends, man.
You promised me
things would be different.
Matter of fact, you swore it.
But this is worse, man.
This is gonna be
Mallory's family all over again,
only this time
it's gonna be my family.
And if something happens
to them, Butcher...
I don't know what happened
with you and Raynor
or how that situation
got fucked up,
but just please call her.
Please.
(dogs barking)
(dog whines)
Yeah.
- (whooshing, thud)
- There you go.
Dr. Vogelbaum.
Surprise.
Thought I'd drop in on you.
You look well.
How long's it been, John?
(chuckles) Long enough that
no one calls me John anymore.
Mm.
So, what are these? Uh... pets?
No, just breeding them.
German retrievers.
I try not to get
too attached to my subjects.
Hmm. Well, that's true.
Seems retirement suits you.
Between this
and 80-hour weeks at the lab,
I'll take the lab. No contest.
So, you ever, uh...
catch up with any
of the old gang from Vought?
(chuckles)
Look, do you mind
if we don't do this?
- Do what?
- This cat and mouse bullshit.
You want to know
about Rebecca Butcher.
You went to Stillwell
about it because you knew
that'd tip over
the first domino.
Well, it led to me.
So just ask.
I'll be honest.
Well, that would be a first.
Eight years ago...
Stillwell called me with quite
an interesting challenge.
Rebecca Butcher
had come to her with a...
completely unprecedented
medical condition.
What condition?
VOGELBAUM:
She was pregnant.
With your child.
Pregnant?
Wh...
(stammering):
But I thought I couldn't.
So did I.
Apparently, nature is tenacious.
The fetus was developing
unnaturally fast.
We told her we'd deliver
the baby safely
at a secure location,
but she had to sign an NDA.
Couldn't tell anyone.
Not even her husband.
You can imagine the size
of the potential scandal.
(nurses' voices echoing)
BECCA:
No!
No! Pull it out...
Oh, my...
(screaming)
(wailing)
The birth was difficult.
The baby clawed its way
out of her.
The blood loss...
no one could have survived.
She died on the table.
A-And the baby?
Lived all of ten seconds.
Drowned in its mother's blood.
Was it a boy?
Does it matter?
Why didn't you tell me?
To protect you.
That's always job one
at Vought, isn't it?
Protect our
most profitable asset?
So why are you telling me now?
You don't understand.
The thing about
cross-breeding dogs,
you get the right genes,
you can get a perfect creation.
But it doesn't matter
how perfect they are.
It's not enough.
When I raise subjects
without their mothers,
they become violent.
Aggressive.
Downright hateful.
You should have been raised
in a home with a family
who loved you.
Not in a cold lab with doctors.
And yet, I turned out great.
(scoffs) When I think
what it's done to you,
and what you can now do
to everyone else...
(exhales)
I'm sorry.
I don't want
your fucking apology.
All this is my fault.
What do you want?
What?
What do you want... forgiveness?
Now?
After you raised me
like a fucking lab rat?
No.
Too little, too late.
I don't want anything
from you, John.
I'm just an old man,
thinking about his mistakes.
(sighs)
I'm the world's greatest
superhero.
You're my greatest failure.
(line ringing)
STARLIGHT:
Hi. You've reached Annie.
I can't come
to the phone right now, but...
(vehicle approaching)
(tires squealing)
- (tires squealing)
- Merde!
Butcher.
- Yeah, yeah, here's a gun.
- Fucking hell.
Calm down.
- Okay, come on.
- (gun chamber clicking)
All right, easy, lads. Easy.
(radio crackles)
M.M.
Deputy Director.
Your family's gonna be okay,
you have my word.
Thank you.
You called?
You are a human after all.
Well, let's not get
too carried away.
Thanks, man.
AGENT:
Come right this way, ma'am.
Monique, I'm sorry.
I never want to see you again,
Marvin.
Come here, baby.
Mmm.
Daddy loves you, okay?
You're gonna be safe with Mommy.
All right? All right.
(sighs)
Take care of yourself.
All right. All right.
- No Homelander.
We had a deal.
Everyone else is fair game.
Do you want this or not?
(phone buzzing)
Annie, are you okay?
(sniffles)
I have to see you.
I, uh...
I don't know. I don't think
that's such a good idea.
You have to explain, Hughie.
You have
to make this make sense.
Just you and me.
You owe me that much.
MADELYN:
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I'm not following.
You and your corporation
are fucked.
Unequivocally,
unilaterally fucked.
How was that?
Is that clearer for you?
For the last half century,
you have been feeding
the American people the line
that your superheroes
are chosen by God.
I mean, I get it.
Jamming illegal drugs
into babies' arms...
I mean, that doesn't quite
have the same ring,
and that's not even the worst.
What did you do
to this one, and why?
I've never seen her
in my entire life.
Uh-huh.
- What do you want?
- For starters,
there are no superheroes
in the U.S. Armed Forces.
The bill's already gone down
to the floor.
They're gonna vote on it
any day now.
And you're pulling it.
Retooling the concept
for internal development.
I don't give a shit,
but the deal is dead.
And we're gonna go
back to status quo,
where we're the government
and the military,
and you're just assholes
running around in your capes.
- And if we refuse?
- Everything goes public.
Corruption story of the century.
Vought shares go to zero.
The civil suits,
criminal prosecution,
and you go bankrupt,
and your cute
little suit goes to a lovely
shade of orange for 15 to 30.
- (door opens)
- WOMAN: Ms. Raynor?
Thank you, Michaela.
We're done here.
Everything okay, I hope?
(door closes)
Someone tell me
what the hell is going on.
About 12 minutes ago,
Navy SEALs took out Abu Ressam
about 15 miles
outside of Damascus.
Right, as planned.
So what's the problem?
Watch.
- (gunfire, woman screams)
- (indistinct shouting)
- MAN: We got two.
- (man yells)
- MAN 2: Nice eye.
- MAN 3: Stop.
That's our guy. Light him up.
Great.
The prick behind Flight 37
is dead. What am I missing?
- Just wait.
- (beeps)
- Step inside.
- Watch this.
(woman whimpering,
glass clinking)
(debris clinking)
- We got movement!
- Hey! Hey! Get down!
- Hey!
- Get down!
- Get down, motherfucker!
- Don't fucking move!
I said get down!
What the fuck does that say?
"Naqib."
MAN:
Hey!
Freeze, motherfucker!
- Kill him!
- (rapid gunfire)
That's not all.
How is that son of a bitch
still alive?
"Naqib" means "Captain."
We believe it's his...
Supe name.
Are you telling me
they have a Supe terrorist?
Look, Annie, I-I...
Did you kill Translucent?
It's-it's...
it's not that simple.
And you haven't been using me
to get back at A-Train?
(Annie sighs)
Y...
You're a murderer.
We didn't have a choice.
- There is always a choice.
- Wait.
Aah. What-what are you doing?
- I'm taking you in.
- What... No. Annie, hold on.
To the cops! At least
they'll treat you better
- than The Seven would.
- Just listen to me.
Listen to me, okay?
I know this is so fucked.
You were the only thing, Hughie.
You were the only thing
that I could count on.
I'm still me, Annie.
Please. You know me.
I don't know you.
- Never did.
- If you bring me in,
- I'm dead before sunrise.
- No.
Vought will want to string
you up for a long trial.
Lots of press.
The guy who killed Translucent.
This isn't about Translucent.
Okay? This is about Compound V.
(both panting)
Compound V?
It's this drug.
It, um...
It gives the Supes their powers.
Vought will do anything
to cover it up.
N... No. What? Wha...?
What are you talking about?
We're born like this.
I'm so sorry.
Annie. Annie.
- Annie, watch out!
- (screams)
- (people shrieking)
- Fucking run, Hughie.
(groaning)
- (screams)
- (panting)
- I'm so sorry.
Get the fuck away from her!
What the fuck were you thinking,
coming here?
I didn't ask for your help.
Yeah. Looked like
you had it all under control.
- (grunting)
- (sirens blaring)
(groaning)
(gasping)