Oh, wow!
You really did it this time, Barry.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, seriously.
You come to Star City,
you ask for my help,
and then, inevitably, immediately,
we end up up the creek.
- Yeah, okay, that's fair.
- Thank you.
- They're moving in.
- On three, Team Leader.
- What's that?
- That would be heat vision.
- Three.
- Okay.
Kid gets faster every time we test him.
- Mach two.
- Already?
He just got his speed a few days ago.
How are his vitals?
His running economy, lactate threshold
are all way above expected levels.
Think we might have
a little prodigy on our hands.
Like, a Wizard of Whiz...
Guys, I don't want Wally
thinking that he's Barry,
rushing off half-cocked,
trying to take down Alchemy or Savitar
- the next time one of them shows up.
- Okay, but, guys,
Wally's not like me,
he doesn't want his powers gone.
We're gonna have a hard time
convincing him not to use them.
Yeah, well, we have to until he's ready.
- How?
- By convincing him that he isn't.
That means no encouraging him,
no training him,
and, you,
no talking to him about his suit.
Please, it's for his own good.
Why the hell not, it's just another lie
between friends, right?
Cisco...
What? Still not good?
Um, I think, maybe
we should try again tomorrow.
I can run a few more tests.
That was amazing.
Dinner's on me, whatever you want.
H.R.: Test, test.
Fellow S.T.A.R. Labs employees,
your presence in the cortex
would be greatly appreciated.
That's tonight? His presentation?
Great.
What do you think if after,
maybe we get a drink? You, me, Barry?
Barry?
We're just gonna get drinks,
pretend like we're friends?
Nice try. Ain't gonna happen.
BARRY: You wanna open S.T.A.R. Labs
to the public?
- In two weeks?
- Soft open,
not a hard open. But you know,
I'll use your input, all right?
Right now, it's very important
'cause the clock is ticking.
My vision is set to include, but
not limited to, bam,
a personal transportation
tour of the facility.
Or, for the faint of heart, we have, pow,
a Virtual Reality alternative.
Both set to include "Particle Vision!"
"Particle Vision?"
"Particle Vision,"
which is a moment-to-moment
reenactment of
the Particle Accelerator explosion,
but seen from the point of...
- Particle...
- H.R.: the particle!
Listen, H.R., I know that you're trying
to figure out how you add value
- to the team, I get it, but this...
- Let me stop you right there, B.A.
- Okay, don't call me "B.A."
- I can make S.T.A.R. Labs
the powerhouse in the scientific community
that it once was,
and moreover, earn back
the people's trust. Look at you guys.
You just, you're faces are so darn gloomy.
Here's what we'll do,
I'm gonna make you guys a...
Was that, was that the satellite?
I hope that wasn't the satellite.
- Is that a meteor?
- Why, yes, that is a meteor,
and, yes, it is heading for downtown.
I gotta go.
- Guys.
- CISCO: What is it?
- Barry, what do you see?
- This isn't a meteor.
Barry? Barry, come in. Can you hear me?
Guys.
Oh, come on.
Aliens!
Government officials are reporting,
the mysterious object that crashed
in downtown, Central City,
was simply a DOD aircraft
on a routine training operation.
Thank you,
but we'll brief the White House.
You're not listening to me about this.
The intelligence we've gathered
- at A.R.G.U.S...
- Is not accurate.
We got this covered, Director Michaels.
Go back to Star City,
let the big guns take over.
Lyla, what is this?
- I saw the weird ship that crashed...
- You saw a ship?
- What else did you see?
- Enough to give Ridley Scott nightmares.
Meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I'll tell you everything I know.
Aliens.
The Alien aliens or little green men?
Both. Sort of.
Since we learned of them,
we've been calling them the Dominators.
WALLY: Okay, that is not the name of
a species that comes in peace.
No, no, it, it's very aggressive.
So, how long have you guys known
about these "Dominators?"
- Since the '50s.
- That was them.
Redmond, Oregon,
the government tried to cover it up.
What? I watch SyFy channel.
In 1951, they appeared
under the same sort of circumstances.
A ship crash landed,
little to no communication.
We learned they were abducting humans
to gather intel about us.
They attacked, and hundreds of soldiers
lost their lives.
Then for some inexplicable reason,
they left.
All contact had been lost,
until three months ago
when the DOD received this.
ALIEN:
We pose no threat,
human inhabitants.
Understanding is our purpose.
Any action against us,
as shown to us in the past,
will prompt swift retaliation.
So, when we discovered four ships
heading towards Earth,
we were concerned
that it was happening all over again.
One of them, obviously, landed here.
Right. 'Cause we ain't got enough crazy
going on here in Central City.
- Do you know what they want?
- They've ignored all attempts
to communicate,
but we do know, just like before,
that the dropships
contained reconnaissance teams
sent here to gather more intel about us.
Looking for our weaknesses?
- We need to do something.
- LYLA: We are.
Nearly every member state in the UN
is in talks to coordinate a response.
- Action is being taken.
- So, wait,
you want us to just sit this one out?
These things are like World War Z zombies,
if they decide to attack,
no military can stop them.
Neither could you.
Not by yourself, anyway.
Just let us handle this for now.
I'll be in touch.
So, the plan isn't to just
- stay still and do nothing, right?
- No.
Barry, you heard Lyla,
you can't do this alone.
I don't plan to.
GREEN ARROW: Anything?
- Zilch.
- He's gotta be here somewhere.
FELICITY: What are the chances
this guy just decided
that he'd had enough of this life?
You know, no health insurance?
He's sick of the crazy hours.
I mean, bullets aren't actually that cheap
and he loses them...
- I'm sorry, man, I...
- It's okay.
Yeah...
- Hey.
- Hi, Barry.
- So, who was that guy?
- That
was Vigilante, and we nearly had him.
You nearly had him?
Ollie, it looked like
he was about to Scarface you guys just...
Barry, is there something
that I can do for you,
another evil speedster to help you with?
Uh, maybe, actually...
That's not why I'm here.
What was so urgent
you had to rush to Star City?
- Aliens.
- Aliens?
Aliens.
I swear to God, Barry,
my life was somewhat normal
before I met you.
Hey, I know, I mean, I'm sorry.
Look, okay, they're real,
and they're already here,
and from what Lyla told us,
it does not appear to be for peace.
- Oh, no.
- Lyla knows about this?
Lyla, yeah, she came to. Where you...
- I called Thea.
- Yeah, I, uh...
I came to have you sign this
before City Council went into mutiny,
but that can totally wait.
Count me in.
For what, I thought you retired?
Yeah, but it's...
It's aliens.
Oh, that is so cute.
You guys are just gonna
get together and go fight some aliens?
Have you lost your minds? They're aliens,
and there's only four of you.
Not if we get Stein and,
- you know, all the others.
- They're calling themselves "The Legends."
Egotistical, but catchy.
Do you know where they are?
I know where they were.
What is this place?
It's this old hall,
hangar thing that S.T.A.R. Labs owns,
or I guess, I own it.
Well, you should do something with it.
All right, so let me get this right.
Our, time-traveling buddies
in a flying time ship
are supposed to just pop up
right here, right?
Yeah, this is the time and place
I gave them,
so if they got my message,
they should be here...
Right now!
You know why I've never done drugs?
It's 'cause I was always afraid
I'd see weird stuff.
Okay, take everybody inside, all right?
And tell Oliver I'll be right back.
- Where you going?
- Well, since we're fighting aliens,
I figured we should get
one of our own, right?
- You found the right Earth?
- Tachyon device
tracked you on Earth-38 when you met her.
- So you should find her there.
- All right.
Just so you know, I'm only doing this
because we're on a mission.
I'm not gonna let my issues with you
get in the way of them.
This might take a few tries.
This better be the right place.
'Cause if this isn't the right place,
someone's about to be real confused.
- Barry!
- Hey.
I knew it. I knew that was you.
I knew it was you in that weird space.
Sorry, it took a couple of tries
to get here.
- This is my friend, Cisco.
- Well, friend is a loose term,
we work together. Hi. Cisco.
I have to say it, this
- is a nice universe you got here.
- Thank you.
Do you... Okay, do you remember last year,
when I helped you out and you
promised to do the same for me?
What are we up against?
Team Arrow is here.
Team Legends is here. Is that everyone?
I think so?
Nate and Amaya are back
watching The Waverider.
The newbies.
- That was cool.
- BARRY: Guys!
- Thanks for coming.
- Barry, I thought
- you were bringing an alien?
- And, yeah...
We did. Everybody, this is
my friend, Kara Danvers,
or as she's known on her Earth, Supergirl.
- What makes her so super?
- Well...
I'm convinced.
Best team-up ever!
Okay, I think I have this.
- Oliver?
- Green Arrow.
- Digg.
- Spartan.
- Thea.
- Speedy.
Okay. And, Sara?
- White Canary.
- Jax and Professor Stein?
Firestorm.
- Ray?
- Palmer, The Atom.
And, Mick.
Mmm?
Oh, Heat Wave.
Uh, and...
Iris, Caitlin, and Felicity.
Whoo! Yes!
And, you, you have cold powers
but you can't use them?
- You have powers?
- It's a long story.
Uh, Barry, so,
- Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God, he just got so much hotter.
- Oh, my God.
Okay, Cisco, we should probably
get started?
Okay.
These are the Dominators,
- we don't know much about them...
- Except, they're really strong.
I heard a lot of stories about them
when I was a kid, they came to my planet
before I was born, they did experiments
on a lot of people, killed a lot more.
Well, they're not the only ones
with super-human strength, I hear.
Barry says that you're more powerful
than a locomotive?
We should use Kara
as a stand-in for training.
Since when was Robin Hood
calling the shots?
What, I think, Mick is trying to say is,
it would be nice if we knew
who was in charge around here.
Maybe we should take a vote,
choose a leader. Someone we can all trust.
Well, I trust Oliver.
He's got my vote.
Appreciate that, Cisco, but Barry
put us all together, it should be him.
Fair enough.
Okay, um...
Cool, all right, well, I guess as
team leader, first thing to do
is start out by, um...
- Doing a test run.
- Let's do a test run, yeah.
Let's do a test run.
- Against Supergirl.
- Against Supergirl. All right?
- Test run against Supergirl.
- Are we just supposed to
- pretend like we don't hear him?
- So, just suit up.
Okay? Look alive, we're training
to fight aliens,
by fighting an alien, so...
- Do it. Just suit up.
- Stop.
What? Oliver, hey, Kara,
um, really quick. I was excited about
the two of you guys meeting each other.
Yeah, Oliver was the first person
to train me.
- Really? Well...
- Yeah.
- You did a really good job.
- It's 'cause I didn't hold back,
I shot him.
You can't hold back either.
He did shoot me.
Ouch, ah...
Okay. Um, are you sure about that?
I just met these people.
These people need to understand
this isn't gonna be easy.
Don't hold back, especially against me.
Yes, sir.
- Did he not like me?
- No, he's
like that with everyone, it's...
He'll warm up to you.
Old West dwarf star plus replicator
equals new suit.
You know what, Ray?
Maybe it's just me, but,
I think this thing's due for an update.
Ha! Yes, but after we
dominate the Dominators.
Oh! I see what you did there.
Hey-
Uh, listen, I gotta get to work,
Felicity is waiting for me,
but we'll talk about this later.
Hey, Barry.
Uh, where's Snart?
Oh, man, I'm sorry, Barry,
I forgot that we never told you.
What happened?
He sacrificed himself,
saved us all.
- He died a hero.
- A "Legend."
IRIS: Wally, what are you doing here?
You can't just show up and think
you're gonna train with everyone else.
- Why not?
- Because we need to test you more.
H.R. said that my results were great,
he said I'm good to go.
I don't care what H.R. said,
you are not ready.
- I am ready.
- Wally,
everyone here has been doing this
for a long time.
And this is gonna be
the hardest challenge they've faced.
Fighting Alchemy or Savitar, or aliens
isn't something you just show up and try.
If you screw up, you could die.
Do you get that?
Great.
Satellite's not picking up
anything abnormal.
No.
I don't know if we're gonna find
any Dominators this way.
Hey I, um...
Just... I couldn't help but notice
things are a little bit tense?
You don't need to be able
to "vibe" to figure that out.
Okay, so, apparently, it's, like, illegal
to be mad at Barry, but guess what,
he screws up just like the rest of us.
Yeah, and when he does,
he feels bad like the rest of us, too.
Felicity, he took it upon himself
to change the timeline.
And because of it, my brother
was killed.
So, there's no amount of feeling bad
that could ever make up for that.
Barry, before we start training
there's something you need to hear.
A message, that would be better
if we could share with you in private.
- All right, I'll step away.
- No, no, it's fine, you can stay.
All right. But no one else.
All right.
Let's make it quick.
OLD BARRY:
A war is coming, Captain Hunter,
and at some point, you're gonna be
called back to Central City to fight it.
So you need to know
that while you and your team
have been in the temporal zone,
I made a choice
that affected the timeline.
As you know, whenever you alter the past,
those changes affect the present
and get compounded in the future.
When you return, you will be
in the new timeline I created,
where everyone's past and everyone's
future has been affected,
including yours. When you come back,
don't trust anything or anyone,
not even me.
Where did you get that from?
We found it in a secret room
inside The Waverider.
It was sent by you, 40 years from now.
Forty years from now? Barry,
what the hell does this mean?
It means I screwed things up
when I changed the past.
- What did you do?
- I went back in time and
I saved my mom.
I created a timeline where she's alive.
It's called "Flashpoint,"
and I lived in it for a few months,
until I realized
that I made a big mistake,
and I tried to reset the timeline
to put things back
to how they were supposed to be but...
But it didn't Work?
No.
Wow, Barry, that's...
So, what's changed since you did this?
Cisco's brother is dead,
Caitlin has powers,
Diggle has a son now
instead of a daughter.
What? John had a daughter?
I didn't just screw up my life, man,
I screwed up everybody's lives,
and apparently
everybody's lives in the future.
I felt like, when these aliens got here,
that finally something had happened
I didn't cause, and maybe I could make up
for everything
I had done to everybody, but I...
I think we should be on the up and up
with everybody.
We gotta tell 'em.
We're going up against a bunch of aliens,
and you wanna tell people
that their lives might have been affected
by time travel?
One sci-fi problem at a time.
You made a mistake, Barry,
it's part of the job.
We can't deal with it today.
Professor Stein, are you okay?
MARTIN: I'm not sure.
Ms. Snow, would you mind
accompanying me to my home?
There's something I need to do.
Sure.
She really is a badass.
Yeah, it's kinda hot.
Let's go again.
So this is what,
your way of advising me to do nothing?
The Dominators have yet to engage
in an act of aggression, sir.
What does A.R.G.U.S. think?
I think us being passive is exactly
what they want, Mr. President.
Well, finally, someone here with balls.
Ike ignored all the signs
and waited until it was too late,
I'm not gonna make that same mistake.
You saw what happened
the last time we engaged them.
That's a lot of casualties
to be remembered for.
Four dropships landed on this planet,
all of them sent to gather intel.
If we do nothing and they attack,
that's what I'll be remembered for.
Proceed as instructed.
You know, Director Michaels,
the reason that Amanda Waller
lasted as long as she did
is because she learned
how to follow my lead.
I suggest that you acquire that trait.
Soon.
He's gone.
Traveler has been taken. I repeat,
Traveler has been taken.
The Dominators have the President.
- Hey, son.
- I don't understand, Dad.
No one in this family
wants me to have powers.
You don't, Barry doesn't, even Iris.
According to this,
everything is fine with me,
in fact everything is better than fine.
What, did you run back
to make sure I didn't see these?
I'm faster than you now, remember?
Whether you, or Barry,
or anyone likes it or not.
Wally, look, I know
you're upset with me, I was,
I was just trying to protect you.
Come on,
I know you don't want me training,
I just don't get why.
Because I'm better than Barry was
when he first got his speed.
You know, in Flashpoint,
you and I were a brother-sister
crime fighting unit.
So, it sucks you don't have
the same faith in me here
as you did there.
Brother and sister crime fighting unit.
Hi, there, Wallace.
Uh, I came back to get some... Lip balm.
It's okay, you seem to be the only one
that'll tell me the truth around here.
- Me?
- We're kinda treated the same way, right?
No one shows us any respect.
I'm... Respect, I'm just trying
to earn that, Wallace.
Well, maybe we should
stop listening to them.
Yeah. What, what does that mean?
It means I want you to train me.
Me?
I would be gone faster than humor
in a Liam Neeson movie,
- do you know what I mean?
- No.
- Yeah.
- Not if they don't find out.
- Wallace.
- Come on, no one's gonna do this for me.
I wanna make a difference, H.R.,
I'm never gonna be able to,
if I don't know how to use my powers.
Please, I wanna help people
same as you do.
So, show me how.
Nah.
Thank you for joining me, my dear.
Of course, I wasn't being
much help back there, anyway.
You know, having powers
isn't exactly a death sentence,
no matter who your doppelganger is.
I attacked my friends, my best friends.
And said horrible,
horrible things to them.
But, that wasn't you.
And, and believe me, as a person who
sometimes shares a body
with another human being,
I know the difference
and so do your friends.
I'm just so scared.
What if she comes back
and I can't keep her out. Then what?
We'll all be there for you.
Are you okay?
You're back!
I'm sorry, I was looking for my wife.
Very funny, she's not here.
It's so good to see you,
I missed you so much.
- Did you?
- Of course.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too.
But I'm sorry, we have to...
We have to go.
Please tell your mother,
I'll see her soon.
- Professor Stein?
- We have to leave, now.
Where are you?
OLD BARRY:
A war is coming, Captain Hunter...
Are you sure you want me to keep going?
Yeah. Yes.
Just give us five minutes, please.
- Hey.
You know what this is?
This is really you.
Like, future you.
Come on, look.
You told them, right?
I'm gonna tell them, yeah,
when this is finished.
When this is finished.
Even though you're about to lead them
through an alien war?
Even after Flashpoint?
After everything you've messed up,
all the lives you've changed,
you still don't think
you should tell them?
Tell us what?
Uh, Jax and Professor Stein
found a message from me in the future
saying that, right now,
I can't be trusted.
And why would future you say that?
I think because I went back in time
and changed the timeline,
and now
things here are different
than before I left,
including some of your lives.
Some of our lives? Like who?
Cisco, Caitlin, Wally.
Digg.
Me? Why, what happened?
Hey.
Apparently, you had a daughter.
I had a daughter, Barry?
Baby John was Baby Sara.
So, what you...
Let me get this straight, you just, uh...
You just erased a daughter from my life?
- Yeah.
- Look, you can't go back
and just change things
- like that, Barry.
- I know.
Do you know how hard
it is for me to not alter events
to bring my sister back?
But I don't, because I know
the implications.
RAY: And all those aberrations
we've spent the last eight months
traveling through time trying to correct,
you just decided that it was okay
for you to create your own?
We should've told 'em before.
Guys.
Guys, it's Lyla, the President's
been abducted by the Dominators.
She needs us now.
Okay, you guys go, all right?
I'm gonna sit this one out, obviously.
You have Supergirl,
she's just as fast as I am.
Get the President,
we can talk about this later.
You still trust me, right?
I'll always trust you but...
It might take more to convince them.
- If you need me, I'll be there.
- Guys, this is... Hey!
This is crazy!
Everyone is going, including Barry.
I... I'm not going without him.
Then you'll be here, Oliver.
Okay, you know what, Oliver, it's okay.
I will go with them,
we'll get the President,
and, you stay here with Barry.
Sure we're in the right place?
Oh, this is the last place
the President's tracer gave a signal.
Must be nearby.
Yep,
- he's in there.
- How do you know that?
I can see him.
Oh, I have X-ray vision.
Oh, you can see everyone's bits
with those little peepers, huh?
- No. No, I...
- Ignore him.
How did you get the name Heat Wave?
I burned my family alive,
and I like to light things on fire.
Oh, well, that's a colorful backstory.
Well, my shrink thinks so.
By the way, I'm not gonna
call you Supergirl.
- It's stupid.
- You could call me Kara.
That won't work either.
Well, what are you gonna shout
if you need my help?
- Skirt.
- Seriously?
Seriously.
And I'm not gonna need your help.
SPARTAN: Look, the President!
Get me out of here.
- This doesn't feel right.
- MARTIN: I agree, Jefferson.
Something's coming.
Release the President.
We knew you would come.
Did you guys hear that?
'Cause I heard it in my head.
Yeah, we heard it.
Well, if nobody else is freaked out by it,
far be it for me to panic.
You don't need to harm him
to get whatever it is you want from us.
Release him,
and nothing will happen to you.
He is not who we want.
It's a trap!
Supergirl, do something.
I didn't think about it, Oliver.
I didn't think about the future.
I was so focused on the past
that I didn't think about it until now.
I changed so much.
What is this?
This is an article from the future.
It's a story about me vanishing.
Used to be written by Iris West-Allen,
but now, I don't know,
something's changed with Iris.
Something's changed with our future.
- God, what did I do?
- Barry,
this is a weird-looking newspaper article.
It doesn't mean anything.
You need to stop
beating yourself up over this.
I'm sorry, but how can you say that?
I'm responsible for all of this.
Well, maybe, maybe not.
Barry, you made a choice.
You wanted to see
your parents alive again.
Do you honestly know anyone,
that if they were in your shoes,
wouldn't do the exact same thing?
I would do the exact same thing.
Barry, after the Gambit went down,
it was me, my father
and a crew member on a life raft,
lost at sea.
Enough food and water
for one person, maybe.
My father took a gun,
shot the crew member,
told me to survive,
and then turned the gun on himself.
He shot himself in the head,
he sacrificed himself
so that I could live.
Nothing I could do, no choice.
Slade Wilson drove a sword
right through my mother's heart
in front of my sister,
and I was there.
I was helpless on the ground,
I was powerless to stop it.
No choice. Do you not think
that I wouldn't give anything to go back
and to make things different?
You never told me that.
Barry, the world isn't different
because you changed the timeline.
Change happens,
tragedy happens.
People make choices,
and those choices affect everyone else.
You're not a God, Barry.
CISCO: Hey, guys, wherever you are
right now, we need you.
Oh, things just got so much worse.
Guys.
Can we talk about this?
Guess not.
- What's wrong with them?
- I don't know. We need to find out.
Okay.
You really did it this time.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, seriously.
- What's that?
- That would be heat vision. Okay.
What is going on?
Barry and Oliver stayed behind while
everyone went to go save the President,
but now everyone's crazy and
going all Kill Bill on the both of them.
The Dominators have them
under some sort of mind control.
They can't hold them off forever.
- I gotta get out there.
- The hell you do.
They can't beat them by themselves,
especially not
with Supergirl against them.
Wally?
Kid Flash.
Wally, talk to me.
Hey, come on.
Guys, Wally's hurt bad but he's alive.
Get an ETA on overriding the mind control?
- Bingo!
- Yahtzee!
You go first, you go first,
it's your office.
There's a weird signal
coming from the salt mines.
For the record,
that is what I was gonna say.
Well, can you jam it?
Um, no.
- How many of those you have left?
- Probably not enough.
Okay, this hallway leads
to a bunker under the building,
- just hold them off as long as you can.
- Where're you going?
If they can't shut it down, maybe she can.
Okay.
Hey, Supergirl,
let's finally see who's faster.
Too slow.
- What is he doing?
- He's making her angry.
But he knows Supergirl is invincible.
I think maybe that's the point.
Barry?
Guys,
they're back.
What happened?
You didn't kill me,
so my day is looking up.
I'm so sorry, I...
You're not the first superhero
to be mind-controlled.
Okay, I know what you're gonna say,
but I had to do something.
- I'm...
- I'm glad you're okay.
- Don't ever do that again.
- Ah!
Sorry, not sorry.
Come on, let's get you checked out.
And then we can talk about
how dumb that was.
Okay.
H.R.: Okay.
"Okay," what?
They don't see your potential, I do.
One of my many gifts.
You wanna train?
I'll train you.
So what's it like,
being all mind-controlled and stuff?
I didn't realize
he had a mind to be controlled.
RAY: Barry, about before,
message or no message,
- we're with you.
- Thank you.
- So where's Supergirl?
- Scanning the city to make sure
there aren't any more of the orbs
that whammied all of you.
Okay. So now what?
We call Lyla, tell her these Dominators
aren't here peacefully.
Sara!
Everybody inside, go!