- Previously,
on "The Flash"...
- Vibe must live again.
- I am no longer Nash.
I am Pariah.
I freed The Anti-Monitor.
Now I am forced
to bear witness
as he destroys
world after world.
- Oliver scarified himself
to create this new world.
- Our Earths must have merged
when we helped Oliver
reboot the Universe.
We all live
on the same Earth now.
- This is the same guy
that kidnapped
your cousin Esperanza
and turned her
into a meta-assassin.
- The guy you questioned
was killed in the same lot
you questioned him,
on the same day.
- There's major UV energy
coming off this thing.
- Looks like Team Citizen
has a new mission.
[pop music plays]
- Come on in, folks.
After five months
of Vibaccinos to-go,
welcome to the new Jitters.
Here you go.
And remember, folks,
CC Jitters is here to stay,
rain or...
- Hands in the air,
you foam-loving fascists!
- Are you kidding me?
We're already being robbed?
- Jitters just reopened
and was immediately attacked
by terrorists.
Why am I not surprised?
- I'll go bail out
those latte-sippers.
- Guys, I got this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
-  You.
Open the register.
Give me everything inside.
- Dude, we just reopened.
There's barely anything
in there.
♪ ♪
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
♪ ♪
Well, I'm gonna start
blowing stuff up then.
♪ ♪
[groans]
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- Oh, crap.
- Sorry I'm late.
I love what you've done
with the place.
[applause]
[all chanting]
Flash! Flash!
- Oh, stop.
Stop it, guys.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
Crisis is over,
we beat the bad guy,
and you're still worried
because...
- Because...
an infinite number of Earths
experienced a cosmic heat death
from which only one Earth
was rebuilt.
- Mm-hmm.
- So now not only
do Superman, Supergirl,
and Black Lightning live here,
but now our entire timeline
has been rewritten
so that they've always
lived here,
and I don't remember
owning this shirt.
- Great shirt.
Besides, isn't that
a good thing?
We're all one big,
happy family now?
- No. No!
No, it is not.
Not when these guys
are crashing the reunion.
Not a single one
of our doppelgangers
survived to make it
to Earth Prime,
as far as I can tell,
but we did manage to pick up
a butt-ton of bad guys
and aliens and more metas,
and you know the best part?
[laughs]
The best part
is a bunch of our old villains
are back,
with fresh paint jobs!
- When did you have time
to do all this?
- Edencorp, The Top,
Rainbow Raider.
Our Earth has more threats
than ever,
and we don't even know
where they're coming from.
[knocking]
- What the hell was that?
- Pipes...bad pipes.
The heating.
Don't worry about it.
[banging]
- Let me out.
- Are you sure?
Cause it looks like
you locked Nash in the closet.
- No.
[banging]
- Let me out.
- Okay, one of the auxiliary
pipes was leaking,
so he's patching it up
in exchange
for a Crypto-circuit.
- Fine, don't let me out.
I'll let myself out, actually,
thank you very much.
I'm gonna put an Atlantean
shoulder check
into this door
and bust right through.
In three, in two...
- Okay.
- In one!
[grunts]
- Sup?
- [panting]
Killer Frost.
- It's just Frost now.
- Give me my Crypto-circuit
or I'm gonna punch you
in the throat.
- I have your Crypto-circuit,
and I could give it to you,
but, you know,
I'm not really sure
what you'd need it for,
because you're an adventurer,
so shouldn't you be off
somewhere, adventuring?
Preferably not here.
- Yeah, I mean, Gorilla City's
part of Earth Prime now.
Don't you wanna go mythbust it?
- No.
Gorillas are atheists.
[laughs]
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm gonna run tests
on my dig site
to insure that nobody ever
accidentally reopens
the anti-matter universe.
- Run your tests,
but I've already run tests,
and that cave is staying shut,
so you're not really
needed here.
- Oh, you ran the tests?
Then I'm really needed.
- What happened to Magenta?
I liked her.
- Isn't it great?
It's still our
number one story.
[soft music]
Thanks again, friend.
- Iris. Hey.
- Hi.
- I was running back
from a car fire on Route 119,
and look who I found
on the way back.
- Hey.
- Dig, hey.
[laughs]
How's the fam?
- Oh, everyone is very busy.
Lila just accepted
a new posting,
so next week we'll be taking
the kids to Metropolis.
- I heard.
So shouldn't you be at home,
helping to pack boxes
right now?
- Right.
But...
[groans]
Oliver's last will
and testament
was read yesterday,
and, um,
he left something for you,
Barry.
♪ ♪
- Oliver's mask.
- It's the original.
♪ ♪
This is the one I made him.
- Yeah, it's interesting,
because Oliver was never
a man given to sentiment.
- Hey, do you see this?
Right above the left eye.
Oliver hasn't worn this
in years.
Why is there a mark on it?
- I don't know.
Felicity skimped
on the dry-cleaning?
- Or he left it on purpose.
I mean, you just said it.
Oliver wasn't sappy.
What if the mask is a clue
to some new threat out there,
something too dangerous
to put in writing?
- Barry, you got all that
from a smudge mark?
I don't, uh...
- I...
- Iris, what do you think?
- Um, that you two
will have to figure this out
on your own.
I'm so sorry, babe, I gotta go
meet with this source,
like, right now.
- Yeah, no, that's fine.
Do your thing.
Break your story,
and Dig and I can work on this.
- We...we can?
- Can we?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- Were you followed?
- No.
- You sure?
- Yes.
- Uh, no...no...no recordings.
The people you're after,
they know my voice.
- These people...
you say you've learned
quite a bit about them, so you
should recognize this, right?
- [gasps]
I spent 20 years working
for McCulloch Technologies.
R&amp;D department,
classified division.
And then this guy showed up,
said his name was
Malcolm Strombard.
He'd been promoted
into our group,
but he had no technical
know-how.
But last fall, I...
I came in late one night,
and I...I found him
with the infrared photon rifle
we'd been developing
for years.
The next day,
he and the prototype
were gone.
So I started looking into it,
and this man,
Malcolm Strombard,
he doesn't officially exist.
Of course, no one
at McCulloch believed me,
so they fired me.
- The group that sent him
to steal that rifle,
they found out I was after him.
♪ ♪
- Oh, they killed
their own man.
- They have destroyed
way too many innocent lives,
and they will not stop
unless someone helps us
bring them to light.
Someone like you, Mr. Huskk.
- And I can stay anonymous?
- No one will ever know
your identity.
I will do whatever it takes
to keep you safe, I swear.
- These people...they will not
be brought
out of the shadows easily.
They live in the darkness.
In the absence of light.
♪ ♪
- I didn't talk.
I didn't talk, I swear!
- They call themselves...
- [screaming]
- Black Hole.
♪ ♪
[both speaking Japanese]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You're telling me
that a secret organization
has been operating
in Central City
for seven years now?
- Yes, and according
to my source,
they have a name.
Black Hole.
- We've been building
a timeline.
It looks like Black Hole's
activity started
just after the Particle
Accelerator exploded.
- They've been abducting
and training meta-humans,
like my cousin Esperanza
and potentially others.
- And Black Hole's reach
goes far beyond
theft and training
meta-human assassins.
They are also involved
in international arms deals.
- And they kill anyone they
believe has been compromised,
including our mystery man,
who's now crispier than
the chicken strips
Allegra insists
on ordering for dinner.
- Better than
your vegan donuts.
- [scoffs] Iris,
have you told Joe about this?
- Yeah, I have,
but Dad would have to launch
a RICO investigation to pursue
a conspiracy like this.
This is reporter territory now.
- Okay, okay, look.
Guys, I get it.
There's nothing stronger
than a reporter's drive.
I...I literally can feel it
coming from all three of you.
But as your legal advisor,
I gotta tell you...
I think that running
this story is a mistake.
Iris, if McCulloch
doesn't like what they read,
they can sue you
for defamation.
- I know. My dad was worried
about the same thing,
but that's a risk
that I'm willing to take,
Cecille.
- Guys, we don't even know
who's running Black Hole.
- We're gonna find out.
- Yeah, she's right.
Reporters don't walk away
from the truth.
Now, I have a meeting
with the CEO
of McCulloch Technologies,
Joseph Carver, in an hour.
So let's see if he's
willing to comment
on what's been happening.
But either way,
be prepared to go to print.
We are running this story
with or without his comment.
♪ ♪
- I know it's sort of like
asking the ocean
to be less wet,
but Barry, do you think
you could, um, slow down?
- Dig, you wouldn't let me
speed you to the crime lab,
so I had to speed
the crime lab here.
- [scoffs]
Look, man, if Oliver
really wanted you
to look into something,
don't you think he would've
left you a note
instead of some secret code?
- Oh, because Oliver never
kept a secret from you before?
[machine chimes]
There's sediment traces
on the mask
usually found on islands
in the North China Sea.
Like Lian Yu.
- Like Lian Yu...
Barry, there's more than one
island in the North China Sea.
- Yeah, but only one
with Mirakuru.
- Does that mask really
have Mirakuru on it?
- Anton Ivo's
super soldier serum.
You really think there's any of
this stuff left on the island?
- Yeah, well, Oliver
always thought that
some samples could have
survived on Ivo's freighter.
- And we don't even know
what the state of Lian Yu is
post-Crisis; I mean,
if somebody got their hands
on Mirakuru, they could become
a living weapon.
Or replicate it and build
an entire army.
I mean, Dig, this...this is...
this has got to be
why Oliver left me the mask.
He wants me to find
the last stash of Mirakuru
on Lian Yu
before it threatens the world.
♪ ♪
Look, I know you don't want me
to run you there,
but it's a 20-hour plane ride.
[pills clattering]
That's too much.
- What you got?
- My wife and I
started this company
with three employees.
Now we have almost 3,000,
but I still know
each one of their names.
It's what Eva would've wanted.
- That's very thoughtful,
Mr. Carver.
- Joseph, please.
I'm a huge fan
of "The Citizen."
How can I help?
- Well, I have a source
who can prove that
one of your classified
Photon Rifles
was stolen last fall
and it's now in the hands
of a secret organization
linked to terrorism,
kidnapping, illegal arms deals,
and murder.
Would you care to comment?
- Maurice, tell the board I'm
running a little bit behind.
Ms. West-Allen and I
need to speak
someplace a little more private
- Great.
[tense music]
[beeping]
♪ ♪
-  Your source...
it's Gene Huskk, isn't it?
I completely respect your need
to protect your sources,
but there's something
that you should see,
off the record,
for Huskk's sake.
Just a sec, please.
♪ ♪
Someone did infiltrate
the R&amp;D division
here at McCulloch, but it
wasn't a secret organization.
It was Obsidian Tech trying
to steal one of our prototypes,
but Huskk couldn't accept that.
He became convinced
there was some
larger conspiracy,
and the paranoia consumed him.
He became troubled,
started scaring
other employees.
I had no choice
but to let him go.
- Mm.
- But, uh, I can assure you
that we have dealt
with this problem internally.
We just completed
our investigation,
and we're getting
a whole new security system
starting tomorrow:
new badges, new cameras.
The works.
There's no story here.
- Well, with all due respect,
Mr. Carver,
I think that there is.
♪ ♪
Maybe it's just one
that you won't like.
♪ ♪
- Mm.
Ms. West-Allen,
everything that I do,
I do in my wife's honor,
to protect her legacy.
♪ ♪
A story like this
could really damage
our company's reputation.
Not to mention,
scare our investors.
I'm asking you,
please, don't run this story.
♪ ♪
- I understand.
You have an obligation
to your shareholders.
- Thank you.
- But I have an obligation
to the truth.
You were robbed, Mr. Carver,
and I get that
that's embarrassing,
but the public deserves
to know what happened
before anyone else gets hurt,
so if you wish
to withhold comment,
that's fine...
But I'm running this story
either way.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
-  100,000 views in one hour.
That's gotta be a record.
- Citizen just fired
its first shots at Black Hole.
- This is a cause
for celebration.
- Ooh.
- Are you even 21?
- I'd hold off
on the balloons and bubbly.
McCulloch Tech
just sent a memo.
They are suing "The Citizen"
for defamation.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[whirring]
- This is ridiculous.
- Iris.
- Fabricated statements,
deliberate omission
of exonerating evidence...
- Iris, something's not right.
♪ ♪
- Carver is just trying
to bury us in legal fees.
He's just trying to scare us.
- Everybody down!
♪ ♪
- Why is someone
shooting at us?
- It's them. It's Black Hole.
- Okay, we...we gotta go.
- So they can kill us outside?
- Okay, look,
it's me that they're after,
okay, so you guys get
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I will make my way out
through Nash's tunnels.
- No way.
We're not leaving you.
- Look, I have to make sure
that my source is safe, okay?
Once I do, I will
meet you there, I promise.
Now we need to go.
On my count, okay?
One, two, three.
Go!
[gun fires, glass shatters]
[dramatic music]
[shutter snapping]
Go. Go, go, go, go, go.
♪ ♪
[gun fires, glass shatters]
-  You're okay. Oh.
What happened?
- Black Hole tried
to assassinate Iris.
She went to go find her source.
Cecille went to Joe's.
- Where's Barry?
- He's in Lian Yu.
I've been trying to radio him,
but that place
is a total dead zone.
- What about those
clicky things you guys use?
- The extrapolators don't work.
Now that the multi-verse
is gone,
the physics behind breaching
has changed entirely.
But don't worry, Frost is out
there looking for the shooter.
- She should be careful.
Do you see these burn marks?
Whoever tried to kill us
was using high-intensity light.
- Holy crap.
[scoffs]
I'm glad you two
made it out alive.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You're fine.
[sighs]
Good.
Yeah, why didn't you tell me
that they were in danger?
Okay, I could've...I could've
gotten them out of there.
- Don't come at me, Nash.
I'm not here
to keep you in the loop.
You're not even
a part of this team.
- Oh, that's so hurtful.
How's your little team doing
in the standings?
Your little team...
- Okay, you don't see
this is exactly what I'm
talking about.
No, you don't care
about the team.
You only work with us when
you want something from us.
- Yo, keep me out of this.
- So what is it this time?
You...you got a couple glyphs
you need Allegra
to x-ray for you?
Oh, or maybe you
just want to open up
another Pandora's box
of Hell.
- Are you kidding me?
I was the one to...
I was the only one
trying to stop Crisis.
- A Crisis you started!
Billions of worlds,
trillions of people gone,
like they were never even born.
- And I paid for it!
As Pariah I paid for it
and still managed
to help defeat
the Anti-Monitor.
- Which did nothing
for the people who died.
♪ ♪
Oliver.
Harry.
Jesse.
An infinite number
of Harrison Wells's.
And we're stuck with the one
who killed the multi-verse.
♪ ♪
- Babe, what the frak was that?
- Just making sure we learn
from our mistakes.
Iris is still out there, guys,
and we need to figure out
who this assassin is
before they get to her first.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Thank God you're safe.
- I'm not.
Neither are you.
Black Hole isn't what we think.
[gun fires]
- Oh, my God.
- [groans]
Mirror.
[groans]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whirring]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
- Iris.
- Boss, you're okay.
- Yeah, no, I'm fine,
but my source isn't.
The person that tried
to kill me got to him first.
Hey, Cisco,
where's that binder?
- Right here.
- Thanks.
Where is it?
Where is she?
Her.
Dr. Kimiyo Hoshi.
- Hoshi...
She went missing
four years ago.
She's an astronomer
out of Tokyo
with the power
to fuel starlight,
but her meta-powers
aren't precise enough
to do the kind of damage
you showed me in those photos.
- What if she used
the Photon Rifle to focus them?
- Good thinking,
maybe the reflector chip
could condense
her UV photon emissions.
- The rifle is the weapon.
- No, she's the ammunition.
- So Black Hole turned her
into some kind
of evil light doctor.
- So we've got a brand new,
more powerful,
murder-happy Dr. Light
on our hands.
Another new meta-surprise
courtesy
of Earth-frakking-Prime.
- Actually, you know what?
Hoshi killed my source,
but I managed to save some
evidence that he gave me.
Ow.
[groans]
Damn it.
- Hey, you should sit down.
- I'm fine.
- Did you get hurt out there?
- I said I'm fi...
- Whoa, whoa.
Call Frost, now.
- That was on the freighter?
- Yeah.
If there's anything left,
it's in here.
- Open it up, man,
let's see what's in it.
- All right.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- This can't be right.
No, this can't be right.
I...I...I searched
the whole island a dozen times.
- [laughs]
Take the win, man.
There's no more
Mirakuru left, Barry.
- No, I mean, Oliver's mask,
it's a warning.
- Or...
Maybe this is exactly
what it was intended
to be in the first place:
a gift.
- No, man, no, it can't...
it can't just be a gift.
I mean, there's got to be
something we're missing.
What if somebody
got to the Mirakuru first?
- Really, and left
the box behind?
- [sighs]
I don't...
Okay, I need to run more tests.
Or why don't we
bring in the DEO?
Or call Felicity or Thea,
I mean, we...we can't just
let somebody create
another Deathstroke.
We have to stop
this threat, man.
I mean, I have to finish
what Oliver started.
- Barry!
Are you all right, man?
- Yeah, I'm...that's never...
I...I...I'm just frustrated,
I guess.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Look, I think I know
exactly what went on here.
Oliver and Thea came to this
island a couple of years ago,
and they faced off with the man
who used to live in this cell.
Deathstroke himself,
Slade Wilson.
Oliver brought his uniform
with him.
- Which is how he could have
soil and Mirakuru on his mask.
It wasn't a warning at all.
- You're searching
for a mission
that doesn't exist, Barry.
But no amount of searching
is gonna bring Oliver back.
[sighs]
That man sprinted
from crusade to crusade.
But, Barry, life is more
than just the mission,
and unfortunately Oliver
learned that too late.
And he wouldn't want you
going down that same path.
- Oliver died so this Earth
could live, Dig.
I have to do everything
I possibly can to protect it.
- Oliver died for more
than this Earth's survival.
Oliver laid down his life
so the people he loved
could live theirs.
That includes you.
Life's a marathon,
not a sprint, Barry.
Slow down and enjoy it.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- So Kamilla asked me
to check on you.
What are you watching?
- So my latest experiment
jumpstarts my neurons...
- Harry.
- They're currently firing
at 120 times per second.
And I think
we can get to 200.
Yeah, so this is, you know,
progress.
It's real progress.
I'll let you know.
Anyway, miss you.
- He was regaining
his intelligence.
All of Earth-2.
Wiped out.
And he doesn't even know it.
- But that wasn't your fault.
- Wasn't it?
When the Monitor gave me
my powers back,
for Crisis,
I remembered how powerful
I used to be.
I can't help thinking that
if I hadn't stopped being Vibe,
maybe I could have sensed
that first anti-matter wave.
Maybe I could have saved them.
- And that's why
you've become so obsessed
with all the new threats.
You want to protect everyone
who did survive on Earth Prime.
Cisco, do you regret
taking the meta-human cure?
- No.
- Do you miss being Vibe?
- Caitlin,
it's not that simple.
♪ ♪
I don't know.
- You know...
I think you might be
onto something over here.
[sighs]
With all these new threats,
changes to our reality,
we need someone whose job
it is to compile all of them.
Somebody who remembers
the difference
between the way it was
and the way it is.
- Yeah, but...
what you're talking about,
that can't just be done
in a day.
And it certainly can't be done
in some room in the middle
of Central City.
- I know.
But I still think
you're the man for the job.
Besides, maybe some time
away from Central City
will allow you to figure out
who you want to be
in this post-Crisis world.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
Maybe.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- So you gonna tell me?
Your thinking.
Running this story.
- I knew what I was doing, Dad.
- Really, Iris?
Frost told me.
You have fifth-degree burns.
My forensics guys
have been in your office
for hours,
and they found nothing.
There's no bullet holes,
there's no casings.
If that assassin would have...
murdered you today,
I would have no evidence
to bring her in.
- Black Hole
attacked my office.
Dad, they nearly killed
my friends.
They murdered my source
right in front of me.
He's dead because I asked him
to speak up.
And I have to honor that
by exposing each and every
person
behind this organization,
so I'm sorry, Dad,
if you want me to give up...
- I...you know
I wouldn't say that.
But this organization has been
in operation for years,
and their roots run deeper
than you have dug, Iris.
You can't win this war
in a day.
Look, when you and Barry
told me that Crisis was coming,
I was determined to solve
as many cases as I could
because God knows
how many days I have left
to make a difference.
But then Crisis came.
Barry survived.
So now I have to remind myself
every single day
that we don't live
in Crisis mode anymore.
We have time now.
- So what am I
supposed to do, Dad?
How am I supposed
to fight these people?
- Well, first thing's first.
Don't go charging
to the front line
like you have nothing to lose.
Now...okay, your source.
Are you sure he hasn't told
anyone else about Black Hole?
- No, no.
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Actually,
someone else did know.
♪ ♪
[foreboding music]
- [speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
- Can I get you
something to eat?
- No, I'm good, Dad.
Thanks.
- How about a glass of water?
- Yeah, okay.
Sounds good, thanks.
♪ ♪
[whirring]
[gun fires]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
Gotcha.
- Lower your weapon, now.
We've got you surrounded.
Put it on the floor.
♪ ♪
- Pretty good Iris, huh?
- Uncanny, babe.
♪ ♪
Now it's up to the real one.
- Mr. Carver, hello.
- Ms. West-Allen,
what a surprise.
- I know.
Reports of my death
were greatly exaggerated.
Oh, careful,
there's a scrum of reporters
20 yards down the hall.
Might not be the most
convenient time
to call up your meta-assassin.
- That's quite the allegation
to make without any evidence.
- Oh, no, there's evidence.
You gave it to me.
Your McCulloch ID.
It uses a microchip that
reflects ultraviolet radiation.
And as your former employee
tried to tell me,
it's the same microchip inside
your company's reflector gun
and inside Black Hole's
badges.
Black Hole has been using your
optics technology for years,
all while abducting metas
like Esperanza Garcia
who have light-based powers,
your area of expertise.
You placed Malcolm Strombard
in Gene Huskk's division
so that he could obtain
the rifle
before it went to market.
and then place said rifle
in the hands
of the one person
who could power it:
Kimiyo Hoshi,
your personal assassin.
You weren't robbed
by Black Hole.
You are Black Hole,
and you've been using
McCulloch's resources
to power a global conspiracy
in meta-human trafficking,
weapons sales,
and murder-for-hire.
♪ ♪
Now would you care to comment?
- I would.
But I don't think you have
the whole story yet,
because if you did, why would
you be here trying to scare me
while your family
risks their lives for you?
♪ ♪
- Weapon down, now!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whirring]
[gun fires]
- [chuckles]
- You're right.
I can't stop
Black Hole tonight.
But I can't let you
hurt anyone else.
Which is why I've set up
a dead man's switch.
If I, my employees,
any of my sources,
my loved ones die?
All the information I have
tying you to Black Hole
will be immediately released.
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
Come on.
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
- Screw you.
- So tell your friend
to stand down.
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
[speaking Japanese]
- That's it?
You're just leaving?
- I follow orders.
- Mr. Carver.
[overlapping chatter]
- Hi, thank you all so much
for coming.
Here...
[clears throat]
Given new information
that has come to light,
I have decided that
McCulloch Technologies
will be dropping its lawsuit
against Central City
Citizen Media.
[overlapping chatter]
Any questions?
- Thanks for coming.
- Hmm.
- I'm going away for a bit.
I might not have
my Vibe powers anymore,
but at least I can still do
some good, old-fashioned
foot work,
so I'm gonna go suss out
whatever brave new threats
we might have
to our brave new world.
And I was thinking,
in the meantime,
maybe you could hold down
the fort here at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Ahh.
Oh, wait, you...
you got cameras here?
- There's no cameras.
- This is...
this is some kind of trick.
Right?
- No.
It's not a trick.
It's more of an olive branch.
- Oh.
- I'm sorry
I said those things.
I should have
held myself accountable
for what happened in Crisis,
but instead I chose
to take it out on you.
- [sighs]
Anyway, so...
Hitting the road?
- Yeah.
So while I'm gone,
do your best
not to break anything,
will you, Nashville?
- Break everything
while you're gone, got it.
- It's like you're
literally not listening
to what I'm saying.
- What's that?
- Nash?
- Hmm?
- I hope you find
what you're looking for.
- How was Lian Yu with Dig?
- I thought Oliver
left the mask as...
a reminder to keep fighting.
But with all the danger
we've been through,
I guess I kind of
forgot why I made it for him
in the first place.
It was so Oliver
would always remember
to protect the people he loved.
That's why he left it to me.
He wanted me
to take my own advice.
- I've been in overdrive
ever since
we learned that you were
gonna die in Crisis.
I've spent the last month
trying to live every day
like it was my last,
hell-bent on...
Trying to make the most
of the limited time
I thought we had left together,
but Crisis is over now,
and you didn't die.
And I think I just...
I forgot to...
- To slow down.
- So are you also thinking
that tonight maybe
we just take it easy?
- Great minds.
- Beautiful minds.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
[gunshot]
- Oh, my God.
- Mirror.
♪ ♪
- Eva.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whirring, beeping]
[latch unlocks]
♪ ♪
[camera shutter clicking]
[computer beeping]
- What were you up to,
Eva McCulloch?
[electronic chime]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.