My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multi-verse,
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was
only to find things
weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
This has already been
a really amazing date, Flash.
Cecile. Thanks for stopping by.
Hey, anything for my favorite detective.
Then you restored the timeline
and things were different?
Exactly.
Jesse. You're a speedster.
When I came back, things weren't the same.
You mean people?
Yeah.
How do I look?
Better. How much?
Do we really need to ask that question?
Our take wasn't that big.
Big enough.
But the only question you should be asking
is what size rock you want
dangling from this beautiful neck.
Kiss from you makes my world spin.
You're so full of it, you know that?
I gotta be honest.
I never understood this.
Well, like my sister says,
anyone can stoop over and pick up nothing.
What do you want, Snart?
I told you two to sit on your cut
for a while. Till things cool down.
Some of us like to actually
spend the cash we get from these jobs.
Not when it's from the ones with me.
You didn't pull 'em off yourself.
Without us, you'd still be
kicking down liquor stores.
I think you spend too much time
staring at yourself in the mirror,
because your perception of reality
is a bit warped.
You know the rules.
I don't give a damn about your rules.
Or laying low.
There's no one in this city
who can stop us.
Including you, Snart.
Sounds to me like
you're saying you want out.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Guess so.
Well, if you're out,
you're out.
No!
You lost, Scudder.
Sam!
Go. Go!
Sam?
Give me a hand here.
Demo starts in a month.
Get everything outta here.
The hell?
Where's Snart? Where's Snart?
This is from a security camera
inside Iron Heights.
Forensic analysis indicates that
the footage is genuine,
no evidence of tampering.
We're pretty sure this is
Doctor Alchemy that did this?
Last thing Clariss said before he died.
Unless someone else killed him.
Like a meta with telekinesis,
or cloaking abilities.
We've got both on Earth.
So what do we do now?
Our meta-human specialist at C.C.P.D.,
Julian Albert, he prefers to work alone.
But I got feelers out on
his investigation.
I'm gonna go there now
and see if he dug up anything.
All right.
Okay.
Well, until then, you guys want to train?
Well, no. We have to think about
getting back to our Earth.
We've been here long enough.
I've still got a lot to learn.
I mean, your words, not mine.
Fine.
Well, if you want to train,
let's train. Speedster style.
Damn. Jesse's almost as fast as Barry.
Velocity's just under Mach three.
Heartrate, a 100 BPM's.
Her vitals are normal.
Yeah, no. We already know all that.
Cisco, we need to test her reflexes.
Can we test her reflexes?
Patience, Harry. Patience.
If anyone's gonna teach Jesse
- the ways of the speed force...
- It's Barry.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, that wasn't very heroic.
Nope, uh, but there is
a lesson in there, somewhere.
What's that?
The difference between
having powers and having precision.
What do you mean?
I mean, it's gonna take more than speed
to take down some of these metas.
You gotta think. Anticipate.
When you enter a new environment,
you gotta case every inch of it.
You never run in blind.
Oh, my God. I've become Oliver.
Maybe we should stay a little bit longer.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's gonna take some time
to master your powers, Jesse.
You'll get the hang of it.
Yeah. I know. Thanks.
Well, since I will be here for a while
do you wanna get out of here?
Where to?
Does it matter?
No touching.
Not what I meant
by staying longer!
- I should probably get to CCPN.
- Okay.
I'll see you tonight?
- Can't wait.
- Okay.
- Hey, Harry.
- Yeah?
Are you really sure you have to leave?
Just a lot that I still have to
fix on my Earth.
Yeah. But you know it's more fun
when you're here
helping us fix stuff on our Earth.
He is right.
Hasn't been the same without you.
Team doesn't feel complete
without Harrison Wells.
Then change that.
There's a whole multi-verse of
Harrison Wells out there
at your fingertips.
You want one? Let's go get one.
Yeah, now I remembered it.
Thank you, Officer.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
So sorry. I got held up at the courthouse.
No problem.
You're the one doing me the favor.
Yeah, I wouldn't thank me just yet.
Oh, you couldn't find anything.
Nope. No one at the DA's office knows
anything about anybody named Alchemy.
Oh, damn.
This is, um,
meta-human related, I assume?
It appears to be.
- Yikes.
- I know.
Okay, you let me know if there's anything
I can do for you, yeah?
Yeah.
Thanks for bringing it yourself, Cecile.
It's my pleasure.
This is really nice.
Staying in is so much better
than going out.
- When you have jobs like ours? Yes.
- Yes.
What?
You're just really handsome.
You are not so bad yourself.
Hey, um, hi. I thought...
I didn't think you were gonna
be home for a while. Right?
My plans changed. I... Unfortunately...
I'm just gonna go upstairs.
You can have a beer. Sit with us.
Have a good night.
I know.
- I'm sorry.
- Should we rain check or...
Barry, I am not upset because
our date got interrupted.
That I understand.
- What do you mean?
- You, speeding away when my dad walks in.
- Yeah.
- Because, what, we're kissing?
Yeah, Iris. Exactly.
What, you don't want to kiss me?
Of course I want to kiss you,
but not in front of him.
Why does that matter?
He's your...
Our Joe. I don't know.
Barry, we are adults.
- I know.
- We are dating. We should be able to kiss.
I agree.
Okay. Yep. Yep. You should talk to him.
Mmm, about...
For real?
Yeah. Go talk to him.
Yeah, sure. I'll talk to him.
- Okay.
- About us kissing.
- Yeah.
- It's not gonna be awkward at all.
Let me know how it goes.
It's gonna be awkward, so...
Where's Snart?
Who said that? Where are you?
Boo.
Scudder?
Where's Snart?
I don't know, man.
Then I guess I'll just have to
find someone who does.
And I know just the girl.
Yeah, Sam Scudder.
He threw me into a mirror,
I fell out of a second story window.
So Scudder's going after everyone
in Snart's old crew to track him down.
Yeah, but the only problem is Scudder's
not gonna find him. Snart's gone.
What do you mean, "He's gone?"
He's gone. I thought I...
Oliver told me that Snart left
with some friends of ours on a trip.
I don't even want to know.
One of Snart's old crew
is at Iron Heights.
I'll go see if I can talk to her.
Okay. I'll see if I can locate
any others at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Hey actually, I'm sorry. I just need to
talk to you about something really quick.
Um...
Okay. So, I know it's probably awkward,
seeing me and Iris kiss.
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah. So, I was just thinking.
- Maybe if...
- Did it have to be awkward?
Uh, do you mean like this conversation?
Like this conversation. I don't know.
It's just cause the next time you see us.
- We may kiss again in front of you. So...
- Okay.
I just want to make sure that,
that is okay.
- Look, Barr...
- Uh-huh.
- You're an adult.
- Yes.
Do what you got to do. I love you.
- I love you, too.
- I love her.
I don't love watching you two make out.
Urn, okay. Just so you know, I am gonna
tell Iris that we talked about this.
Yeah. Like I said, do what you got to do.
Okay.
WOW.
How sure are you that this will work?
Pretty sure.
Okay, but how's this going to help us
find another Harrison Wells?
- You ever go fishing, Snow?
- No.
No, all right. When you go fishing,
you use lures. Lures attract fish.
Fish end up on your fishing pole.
This satellite is our fishing pole
through which we're gonna cast
our very tempting bait
out into the world's largest ocean.
Okay. How?
How. Cisco will open a breach and
this satellite will shoot a message
embedded with a tachyon-enhanced laser
out into the multi-verse
and any Earth that is technologically
advanced enough
should be able to receive it.
Okay. Let's say this somehow works.
Just 'cause they can solve a riddle,
doesn't mean they're
a right fit for the team.
- A riddle. Did you say riddle?
- Yeah.
How dare you, sir? This is not a riddle.
This is a complex algorithmic cryptogram
designed to test deductive reasoning, IQ,
problem solving skills,
anything that our team will need to combat
threats, meta-human or otherwise.
Okay. So you're just sending out
an intergalactic IQ test
to all of your doppelgangers
in the multi-verse.
Not just a test.
Think of it as an invitation,
think of it as an elaborate help
wanted ad.
Will it test their attitudes too?
I'm not sure I can stomach another Wells
with your bedside manner.
I care for you too, you jack wagon.
System is calibrated.
What are you waiting for?
And...
- That's it.
- That's it?
- Yeah. That's it.
- So, now what?
Now? We go get a Big Belly Burger.
That's insane. What a rush.
I know. I mean, it took me a while
to get used to it.
I can't believe you're not sick at all.
I must have an iron stomach.
Okay, so you're telling me that Barry
has never taken you on a run?
No.
Well, then, I guess it's
a good thing you've got me.
Guess so.
Whoa, um, hold up.
Oh, uh...
I'm sorry. Am I reading this,
like, completely wrong or something?
No, no. I like you, Jesse. It's just...
It's just what?
Well, you're going home soon.
To another Earth.
Ah, right.
Yeah, yeah. No. It's cool. Yeah.
Jesse, I...
No, no, no. It's totally cool. I get it.
So, uh, still friends, then?
Yeah. Friends.
Well, as friends, I mean,
we can still run around the city, right?
For sure.
Good looking guy. For a criminal.
Well, he's more than just a criminal now.
Apparently he's a meta
who can travel through mirrors.
Oh, oh, I got this one. He's a...
- Mirror Master.
- What the...
- Boom.
- That's good.
Thank you. We had a Mirror Master
on our Earth. Evan McCulloch.
He wasn't a meta, though. He had
some kind of Mirror Gun that he used.
How'd it work?
Must've had dimensional warping tech that
changed everything into two-dimensions.
Well, Scudder is hell-bent
on finding Snart
and he's going after anybody that
worked with him in the past.
Joe's interviewing one of them right now.
Well, all of Snart's known associates
are either presumed dead
or have gone AWOL except for one.
That's her.
Rosalind Dillon.
Says she has the ability
to induce crippling vertigo.
A top. Like a top. She's a top.
That's her name. Top. Amazing.
What? You wanna go?
Okay. Do we think that
she can lead us to Scudder?
Love to see if Joe gets
any answers out of her.
Heard your ex is back in town.
You know anything about that?
He pay you a visit, Miss Dillon?
They don't let people like me
have visitors here, Detective.
All day, all night,
in my boring little cell.
Makes a girl go crazy.
Scudder tried to kill one of your
old crewmates last night. Leon Williams.
Tried? Too bad he failed.
He's gonna try to kill more. Any idea who?
Give us a name, I'll see what we can do
about your current situation.
Okay. Let us know if you change your mind.
Sorry, Joe.
It's all right. I appreciate
you setting up the interview, though.
Looks like I owe you another one.
You know, these IOU's are
starting to pile up.
- I have an idea about that.
- Do you?
Scudder?
You want me, come and get me.
So you saw Sam Scudder and Rosalind Dillon
escape through a glass window?
Like I said, he grabbed her hand.
They walked to the window and poof.
They were gone.
So, mirrors, windows, it sounds like
he can travel through anything
that has a reflective surface.
How exactly does he do that?
He must be able to link
Einstein-Rosen bridges to anything
with high solar reflectance, right?
So he creates wormholes
through reflections. That's a new one.
Look, I can't pretend to understand
or care about the science of it all,
but we need to find Dillon and Scudder
before something really bad happens.
So, I'm gonna go old-school
at the precinct.
I'll see you later.
Oh, my God. Pings. We got pings.
Looks like some of your
doppelgangers out there
actually cracked your code, Harry.
That was fast.
Let's go take a look.
Guys...
Um, Dad seems fine.
Um, yeah. No, he's still a little weird
about it.
You talked to him though, right?
Um, yeah. I did. Yeah. It'll be good.
- Okay, great.
- Yeah.
- Then I'll see you tonight.
You'll pick a good movie?
- I'll try.
- Okay.
Also gonna try to find the meta-humans
that apparently
no one else cares about right now.
Where the hell did you go?
How many times
do I have to tell you, Rosa?
I was stuck in there.
Whatever it was that hit me,
gave me this crazy ability.
And to me, all of this
just happened last night.
It's been three years, Sam.
So many things are different now.
You were hit, too, weren't you?
- You can do things like me?
- Yeah.
Show me.
You might want to hold onto something.
Oh...
See, Sammy?
Too much has changed.
Then let's change it back.
Huh?
I can stop Snart, Rosa.
We can stop Snart.
Snart?
He's gone. Long gone.
Then let's take this city.
We can be who we wanted, now.
We can be in control.
There's no one in this city
who can stop us now.
There's one person who can.
Who?
The Flash.
Well, hey now.
I solved the riddle,
that you done beamed up.
My name is Wells. Harrison Wells.
They call me Hell's Wells.
They call me that 'cause of my past.
I gonna get into it with you now,
right and proper.
I like to hitch wagons and
I had a bad dinner...
- Pass.
- All right. This is Earth-17.
I'll be in touch.
Salutations to all
of you out there in the multi-verse.
I have of late, wherefore I know not,
received a communique
from the citizens of Terra-Prime.
Terra-Prime?
Nerd. Pass.
- You can't trust a mime.
- Can't argue with that.
- Pass.
- Okay, guys!
We're oh-for-three now.
This is our last one.
He's coming from Earth-19.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello out there in the multi-verse.
Whoever you may be.
Um...
I really enjoyed cracking
the cryptogram you broadcast.
I like the cute trick.
Embedding the secondary measures
in the primary data string. It's clever.
Most people wouldn't have caught it,
I caught it. But that's the point.
You need a genius, I guess.
To help you in your fight against
these awful meta-hominids.
Well, I gotta tell you, I gotta tell you,
to me that sounds like fun.
So, I've enclosed my Curriculum Vitae.
You already know we speak
the same language, take a look,
tell me what you think.
Until our next communion.
Oh, where are my manners? Thank you.
- Not bad.
- Not bad at all.
- Harry?
- Pass.
- What?
Wait, what... Wait a minute.
That guy cracked the code
and he wants to do it.
And he's nice and he's not evil.
And that's a combination of Wells
we haven't had thus far.
All my life, everyone I've ever hired,
to work for me, I have trusted my gut.
My gut tells me that's not the guy.
Keep looking.
It's all right. He's my friend.
Oh, I'm just gonna get...
Oh, for God's sake. Okay. You know what?
I can't take this anymore.
What?
I thought you guys were supposed
to talk about us.
- We did.
- Then why are you being so weird?
- I'm not...
Dad?
Iris, I already told him.
If you two wanna cuddle, make out,
do whatever.
Go for it. I don't care.
- Barry?
- Hey.
- Should we give you guys a minute?
- No, no. It's fine.
Look, Barry. This isn't about
my dad anymore. He's fine with it.
- I'm not totally fine with it.
- So, why do you have a problem with this?
Thank God.
There's a robbery at First National.
Suspects match Scudder and Dillon's
description.
Scudder and Dillon. Yeah.
Sorry, I gotta go.
- Okay.
- Hey, uh, let me help.
We've been training for a reason, right?
You gotta try.
Yep. All right, cool.
Just, follow my lead.
We keep this up,
baby, we'll be set for life.
Then what are you waiting for?
Let's do it again.
Anything for you, baby.
Yeah, so, uh, we're not gonna
let you leave here with that.
Hey, Flash. Heard a lot about you.
That's great.
- Can't say the same for you, though.
- The name's Jesse Quick.
So, I'm sorry, Scudder.
But your little crime spree,
it's gonna have to end here.
Oh, I don't think you have
much of a say in it.
I'm gonna take whatever I want.
I thought you were
looking for Leonard Snart.
Why bother? His reign is over.
There's a new king in town.
And I'm the queen.
Yeah, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Oh, I would, little girl.
- Where'd they go?
- There.
Stay here. I'm not kidding.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- Nice skirt, Top.
- Top.
I like it. Because they spin, spin, spin.
What's this? What's happening?
- I can't get my balance.
- I know. It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
But you won't.
Good luck getting him out.
Barry!
What happened?
I don't know. I don't know, okay?
I looked at Dillon and I lost my balance.
She's a meta-human who induces vertigo.
She just whammied you.
Yeah, I guess so.
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Because now Barry's trapped in there
and it's because of me.
- Well, you know, I...
- I'll go talk to her.
- What is he saying?
- Is that some sort of mirror language?
Mirrors show objects in reverse.
Maybe that's what we're hearing here.
Only one way to find out.
What are you looking for, Cisco?
You ever seen Twin Peaks?
'Course not. Why do I ask?
This is an old back-masking trick they
used for The Man from Another Place,
where they record his audio backwards
and then play it forwards.
Like those Ozzy Osbourne records.
Sure, let's go with that.
Okay, Barry. Say something.
Say it again.
- Um, get me out of here.
- Now, we can understand you.
- How do we get him out of there?
- Barry, have you tried to phase out yet?
- Yes, it's not working.
- If Scudder's used this mirror
as a wormhole, then these molecules
are in a hyper state of flux. So all...
We need is something
really cold to slow them down.
I can help with that. Let's go.
Keep him company.
Aren't you gonna need that?
What's the point? I mean, I thought
I was ready but clearly, I'm not.
Jesse, you can't blame yourself for this.
What happened to Barry...
Was totally my fault.
I mean, he told me to stay back,
but I didn't listen.
I just ran in blind
and now he's stuck. So...
Look, you made a mistake. So what?
I mean, I'm sure Barry made
a lot of mistakes at first too.
Yeah.
Don't let this destroy your confidence.
You're meant to do this, Jesse.
You're meant to be a speedster.
That's why you have these powers
and I don't.
You're just trying to cheer me up.
I know you said
you don't want to hang, so...
You know, I said I didn't want to hang out
because I was scared.
Because you live on another Earth.
But I realized I don't want to be scared
of that anymore.
I don't think it's gonna work.
What do you mean
you don't think it's gonna work?
- I built this to go to absolute zero.
- I realize that. But we need the mirror
to maintain zero point energy long enough
for Barry's molecules to pass through it.
Absolute zero's more than
cold enough to do that.
Normally, but we have to account
for internal energy
of the mirror's molecules as well.
So absolute cold might be
lowest possible temperature...
It's not the lowest enthalpy state
possible.
Exactly right.
- So what are we gonna do?
- I don't know yet.
Okay. Go with me here.
What if we send this to the other Wells
- and see if he can figure something out?
- Yeah.
What? No. What?
Everybody's replaceable now?
Is that right? Is that what this is?
What? What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
It's what you said.
- That's not what I said.
- It's exactly what you said.
I'm saying we need
to find a solution to this problem...
Yeah, that's not gonna help.
You're not contributing to the problem.
You're making things worse.
- You know what I think?
- What do you think?
I think you don't like the idea
of someone taking your place.
This is why you don't
like the other Wells.
What are you talking about?
It was my idea.
But that doesn't mean you have to like it.
It's got nothing to do with liking it.
You know what it has to do with?
- A Molecular decelerator.
- Molecular decelerator.
If we augment a molecular decelerator on
the cryogenic generator, the cold gun...
The cold gun. I can build that.
I can build that.
Great.
What are you doing?
- Do these pants make my butt look big?
- I'm, literally, stuck in a mirror.
Sorry. Yeah.
- Mmm.
- What's it like in there?
Um...
Dark.
Look, Iris.
I'm sorry that I'm stuck right now.
Oh, honey. I know that you're stuck.
It's okay.
- We're gonna get you out of there.
- No...
No. That was misleading.
Not the mirror, I mean with us.
This thing with Joe...
And you were right. It's not Joe, it's me.
It's my problem.
I've just been feeling nervous
about this new dynamic
between the three of us.
I don't know. I have everything
that I've ever wanted right now.
And I've never had that in my life
and a lot of ways
it's scarier than having nothing
because it's easier to fail than succeed.
And I really want to succeed.
What could you possibly be
laughing about right now?
I am so sorry, Barry.
You are really sweet,
but it is weird talking to you through
a mirror and a speaker
and I really want to kiss you right now.
But, can we please talk about this later?
Yeah, we can talk about it later.
Guess it is pretty weird.
It's like I'm here but I'm not.
What?
I just thought of a way to stop Scudder.
- What is that?
- This is how we get him out of there.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Try it now.
It's only negative 280 degrees Fahrenheit.
We got to get it colder somehow.
Thought you guys said this thing
could get him out of there.
Okay. "This thing," is a highly advanced
molecular decelerator
that's being powered by a cryo-engine.
We just kind of improvised it
in the last 30 minutes,
so let's just, just cut us
some slack, please.
Just keep trying, Barry.
- Meta-human alert.
- Oh, for God's sake.
- If it's not one thing...
- It's the other.
Hold on, Barr.
Guys?
Hello?
Central City Municipal Bank
just got robbed.
Let me guess by who.
Guys?
- Barry.
- Hey.
How?
I say, let's figure it out later.
Right now we need to stop
Scudder and Dillon.
- Okay, so what do we do?
- We're gonna use mirrors.
An old trick and an old friend.
Yeah?
It's Snart.
I heard you were back in town.
- Snart?
- Scudder. Rosa. Long time.
Not long enough.
Hang back. This guy owes me.
So you called us. The hell you want?
Same thing. You two. Gone.
Things have changed. This is our town now.
- Is that right?
- Yeah it is.
And that little cold gun of yours
isn't going to save you from me.
We'll see about that now, won't we?
Bang!
Funny thing about holograms.
They're just pale reflections
of the real deal.
Hello, again.
Jesse Quick. Quick to run,
quick to fall.
Quick to learn.
Uh-oh.
Well played, Flash.
Oh.
- What?
- I know, right?
This is the, uh, Droste effect.
I'm sure you've heard of it, right?
It's infinite reflective loop that
even you can't escape.
Good luck getting out.
So you're sure he can't Mirror Master
his way out of this cell?
It's impossible.
Every inch has been modified
with an anti-reflective material.
Even Scudder's gonna forget
what he looks like after a while.
Well, I should go.
Hey. So, thank you for everything.
Oh, no. Thank you. We got another bad meta
right where he belongs.
- Yep. All right.
- Hey, Joe.
We have an awful lot of IOU's.
Do you maybe want to
grab some dinner tonight?
- Dinner?
- Yeah.
Yeah. I...
Well, I got movie night with
my kids tonight, rain check?
Yeah. Of course. Another time then.
Yo. What was that about?
Why didn't you just say yes?
I don't know. You're not the only one
that gets nervous around here.
Guys, I've never vibed across
18 dimensions before.
Just a little bit longer.
Greetings, Earthlings.
I'm just kidding.
I don't really talk like that.
Just always wanted to say that.
"Earthlings."
Wells with a sense of humor. That's new.
Hey. Sharp shooter.
You, you're handsome.
- I know.
Likewise.
- Yeah.
- I'm sure. Harrison.
Harrison. Call me H.R.
H.R. It is.
This is the team, then.
This is Cisco Ramon, he can do anything.
Mmm. Okay.
This is, uh, Doctor Caitlin Snow.
- Hi.
- She is brilliant.
- Single.
- Don't.
All right. That's my daughter,
you don't have to shake her hand,
uh, that gentleman there is Wally West,
this is Barry Allen.
Or as we call him on this Earth,
the Flash.
Welcome to Earth-1.
Thanks. Earth-1. That's weird.
Okay.
Well, we don't have to stand on ceremony.
We don't have to go through all
the tears again, do we gang? Right?
- Well, did I... Did I cry last time?
- I'm talking about myself.
Oh, that's right.
Hey, listen. Don't worry about him, okay?
There's only one Harry.
I wanted to tell you.
The molecular decelerator,
it wasn't working.
What does that mean?
It means that we did not get Barry
out of the mirror. It wasn't us.
Then who did it?
You tell me.
See you later.
Earth-2's gonna have
one hell of a speedster protecting it.
Well, I did learn from the best.
If you ever need any help,
you know how to get back.
Yeah. Yeah. Definitely, I'll be back.
All right.
Okay. You guys. Ready?
Uh, yeah.
Okay, Cisco. Out with the old.
In with the new.
Oh...
You'll never be old to us, Harry.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Okay.
Okay. Let's do this.
Oh, one more thing. While I'm gone,
never, ever, no matter what...
Oh, oh.
What was he gonna say?
We're all, like, "What was he gonna say?"
That's cool, though. I'm starving.
You guys have Big Belly Burger?
Some things never change.
Famished.
Barry say anything about this
embarrassing moment with Cecile?
- Hey.
Hey.
How did your first meeting go
with the new Wells?
Uh, good.
Yeah, I think he'll work out fine.
- Good. I look forward to meeting him.
- Mmm. Whoa.
- What?
- I'm just kidding.
I gotta be honest. It's gonna take
a bit for me to get used to that.
Um...
I actually have something to run by you
guys that I think might help with that.
- Really? What up?
- Yeah.
Uh, well, I've just been thinking
that maybe for all of us
that I should probably,
um, get my own place?
- Really?
- Yeah. What do you think?
I say yes.
- I thought you'd never leave.
- Seriously?
- Dad!
- Yep. Look, Barr, come on.
I'm gonna miss you, but damn!
You're grown. About time.
I can't tell if I'm leaving or
if I'm getting kicked out.
You feel like you feel.
- I mean...
- Feel like I'm getting kicked out.
Yeah.
I feel like you're getting kicked out too.
Like, it's pretty obvious
you're getting kicked out. Dad!
Well. Cool.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::