Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him
murder the woman I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm going to do
everything in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough
to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- When I threw the
Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force,
I accidentally
ran into the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
I wasn't fast enough
to save you.
- We can't do this alone,
Barry.
- Why don't you come
work with us?
You can help Team Flash
fight meta-humans.
- Welcome to the team.
- Yeah.
- If his powers
are linked to the energy
that ties together
the multiverse...
- He can open a breach
to any Earth he wants.
[warbling tone]
[dramatic music]
[electronic beeping]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- The thing they never tell you
about fighting villains
is that nothing
ever stays the same.
The harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
the more they up their game.
- Gentlemen,
welcome to the future of crime.
Not even the military
has these yet.
- Looks like Christmas
came early.
- You know what
the only problem is?
You're on Santa's
naughty list.
[rousing dramatic music]
Christmas is canceled.
[gun zapping]
- Fortunately, our team
has a secret weapon of its own:
a man of science,
a man of action,
and that man's name
is H.R. Wells.
Look who has a vortex cannon.
Ho, ho, ho.
[gun powers up]
[laughs]
[laughing]
- H.R.?
H.R.?
- With a blast from
my trusty vortex cannon,
I dispatch the miscreant...
- H.R.
- Hey, yep, here we are.
- Barry needs help.
- Yeah, Barry needs help.
- Where's Kid Flash?
- He's on his way.
Are you on your way?
They need you
at Keystone Bridge.
- Surely all your adventures
are not this disorganized?
- There's a method
to the madness, mate.
Watch and learn.
- The Electric Gang
is headed north.
- You gotta cut 'em off
before they reach the freeway.
[tires squealing,
engine revving]
[glass shatters]
[gunfire]
- Oh, hey.
- How you wanna play this?
- I have an idea.
[whooshing]
[engine revving,
tires squealing]
- Eyes up!
[whoosh]
- Here he comes.
Just the red one.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
[tires screeching]
[sirens wailing distantly]
[soft triumphant music]
- Nice work.
They're out cold.
Okay, boys.
- They saved us.
- They saved us!
Who are you?
- Um...
I'm Kid Flash.
- Oh, my gosh.
Can we get your picture?
- Yes.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
Whoo.
[laughs]
Okay. Bye.
[cheerleaders cheering]
- Go Kid Flash!
♪ ♪
[heroic orchestration]
- Nice save!
Could not have scripted it
better myself.
- Thanks.
Barry did most
of the heavy lifting.
- B.A.
- Yes, bravo, boys.
Although I did find
at least six ways
you could have done it
more efficiently,
just...just saying.
- I mean, the busload
of hot cheerleaders
seemed like the way
that we did things.
- Oh, that's going in the book.
You know what?
I'm running low;
let me buy you a cup of coffee
over at CC Jitters.
Bond, are you coming?
- No, thank you.
- So exactly how many
hot cheerleaders?
- I was a good boy.
You know, he's just been
looking forward to this
for a long time;
he's enjoying the moment.
- Well, I'm glad
you have his back.
- We have each other's back.
It's actually been really nice
having him out there.
- Hey, I meant to ask you.
When you found
the Electric Gang,
did you see them meeting
with anyone else?
- Like who?
- Well, word on the street is,
there is a new
arms dealer in town
with access to
sophisticated weaponry
like the gun
that Plunder used.
- Don't you think
that's something
for the police to handle?
- I'm still a journalist,
Barry.
I can't hide from the world
because of what you saw.
See you at home.
[pensive orchestration]
- [exhales]
♪ ♪
Can't lose her, Cisco.
Please tell me you found
a way to change the future.
- We found a way
to change the future.
- Did you really?
- No, but Caitlin and I
did find a way to map it.
You're gonna love this.
Follow me.
♪ ♪
Julian suggested we make
a 3-D reconstruction
of the scene from the future
exactly as we saw it.
- With toys.
- The medium's not important.
- Thank you.
Eye on the ball, Barry.
- Is this me?
Why is he an astronaut?
- Eye on the ball,
Barry, okay?
Now, this diorama tells us
you need to cover
this distance
in less than 0.21 seconds
if you want to save Iris
from Savitar.
- What do you guys think?
- Think what you're proposing
is impossible.
Therefore, you will fail.
- Why?
- Multi-universe is
maybe a new concept to me,
but mathematics is not.
Pay attention, Allen.
[thoughtful music]
This is your speed timeline.
♪ ♪
This is your maximum velocity
when you first
acquired your powers.
This is your current top speed,
and this is
where you need to be
in May to cover that distance
in 0.21 seconds.
At your current rate
of improvement,
impossible.
- Wow.
Thank you for that
rousing pep talk, coach.
Okay, why don't you take a knee?
I think we got it covered here.
- It looks like it.
I actually have to be
back at CCPD.
As do you.
Cheerio.
[metal dings]
- He really does
want to help
in his own snobbish,
thoughtless way.
- He is right.
I mean, he's kind of
a dick about it,
but you can't argue
with his math.
- Okay, well, then,
we'll find another way
to make this work.
- We need to.
Iris isn't gonna die.
[sonic blast]
[brooding dramatic music]
[zap, glass shattering]
[glass crunching]
♪ ♪
[coin clinks]
[warbling tone]
- [echoing]
Thank you very much.
[warbling tone]
♪ ♪
- Gotcha.
- Freeze!
[coin clinks]
How'd you get in here?
- You know what they say.
Every time a door closes...
[zap, officer grunts]
[glass shattering]
A window opens.
[warbling tone]
♪ ♪
- Barry.
- Hey.
- Nothing's missing.
- Nope.
- Cash is still in the register.
Safe's not touched.
I mean, it seems like
a lot to go through
to just get a late night
cup of coffee, right?
- Yeah, it's
definitely a meta.
I'll have Julian look into
his meta database,
but I think this
is someone new.
New and dangerous.
- Well, it's nothing
that The Flash
and Kid Flash can't handle.
My two superhero boys.
- He is doing great.
- Speaking of my kids,
Iris, she tell you
about this
arms dealer story
she's following?
- Yeah, she's mentioned it.
- Well, now that you're
her live-in boyfriend,
could you look out for her
and maybe get her
to back off a bit?
Because this isn't something
she should be doing on her own.
- I agree.
I'm trying.
- She seem...okay to you,
otherwise?
- Yeah, why?
Do you not think so?
- If you guys got
something going on,
I hope you know
you can talk to me.
- Yeah, I know, Joe.
Thank you...I...we're...
both doing great.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Talk to you later.
- Yeah.
[brooding orchestration]
♪ ♪
- So this is
the footage from Jitters
that should help us
ID our new meta.
- Brunette?
That really narrows it down.
- Mm, I'll clean that up.
- Oh, look how clear
the picture is on that screen.
- That's 'cause that's
not from Jitters.
That's our security footage.
- H.R. Wells.
I know you're in there.
Come quietly
if you don't want trouble.
- H.R.,
how does she know you?
- Talk.
Who is this...gorgeous intruder?
- Her name is Gypsy,
and she's what's known
on my Earth as a collector.
- What is she collecting?
- She's come to collect,
you know, me.
[warbling tone]
Oh!
[dramatic music]
[electronic whirring, zap]
[yelps]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[sonic blast]
♪ ♪
- Where does it hurt?
- [groaning] Oh, everywhere.
- You can vibe?
Oh, I like it.
- Slow down there.
Let's just talk about this,
like two adults,
over coffee, or maybe dinner,
if you prefer that.
There's a great Thai place
up the road, if you like Thai.
I'm Cisco, by the way.
You must be Gypsy.
It's nice to meet you.
- Are you asking her
on a date?
- Are you kidding me?
- I am negotiating.
- Well, you showed me yours.
Only fair I show you mine.
[warbling tone]
[zapping]
- [grunting]
- Cisco!
- [panting]
- Ma'am, I'm gonna have to
ask you to leave the building.
- Speedster.
That's fun.
I like to have fun too.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I see you've got a lot
to learn about your power.
- Yeah. Like that.
How do you do that?
That's cool.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[groans]
- You're harboring
a fugitive from justice.
Our world has a strict ban
on inter-dimensional travel.
He knew that when he came here.
- So you tracked him here?
- Honestly, it wasn't that hard.
Not when he's beaming
"H.R. Wells'
Adventures in the Multiverse"
back chapter by chapter.
- You know what?
Whatever H.R. did,
you can't just come here
and take him by force.
Not without going through us.
- If I really wanted
togo through you,
you would all be dead.
I've got a lock on you now.
There is no getting away.
You've got an hour
to get your affairs in order,
and then you are
coming back with me.
[dark pensive music]
Adios, Cisco.
♪ ♪
[warbling tone]
- What an exit.
"As Francisco threw back
his lustrous locks
"and laughed,
I outlined my plan
for neutralizing
the rampaging creature."
It goes on like this for pages.
He's been broadcasting this
without our knowledge
or permission,
all the while making himself
the hero.
- Yeah, every book
needs a central protagonist
that the audience can invest in.
- I would have gone with Barry.
- Barry?
- Cisco, what was that
back there?
First Golden Glider
and now her?
- [scoffs] I can't help
who I'm attracted to,
even if it is the...
sexy, intense, deadly ones.
So she takes you back
to Earth-19,
and, what, you pay a fine?
- The punishment for
an unauthorized breach travel
on my Earth...
it's death.
- Death?
- About 24, 25 years ago,
a neighboring Earth
invaded our planet
through a breach
and almost destroyed the place.
So to prevent it
from happening again,
they banned all
inter-dimensional travel.
And then they put
the collectors in place
to punish those of us
who violated the ban.
I just didn't think
that she'd track me down.
- So why would you risk
your life by coming here?
- I...I'm gonna get packing.
It's time for H.R.
to face the music.
Mm-hmm.
[foreboding music]
- Guys, I know H.R.
can be annoying,
but he doesn't
deserve to die.
- Different Earth,
different morality.
- But he doesn't go back.
I saw him.
In the future, with me and
Iris and Savitar, he was there.
I mean, that must mean
we don't let her take him back.
- Maybe we do.
Maybe by letting him
go back to his Earth,
it changes your future
and prevents Iris' death.
- I gotta go see her.
♪ ♪
- Are you just gonna let
this woman take H.R.?
- I don't know.
No.
I just...
I wish I knew if it would
make a difference.
You know, I mean, what if
he goes and nothing changes?
How do we ever know if our
actions now impact the future?
- Yeah.
You know, sometimes I wish
we had normal-people problems.
- Yeah, that would be nice.
Hey, you didn't tell Joe
about the future,
did you?
- No, of course not.
The last thing I need
is for him to worry about
something four months away
that might not happen.
- Thatwon't happen.
- That won't happen.
- Maybe in the meantime,
you could let this
arms dealer thing go?
- Oh, God, did my dad
put you up to this too?
- No, he didn't have to.
- Barry, look, this...
- No, look, I'm sorry.
I'm not trying to keep you
from doing your job, okay?
But when we're all focused
on this H.R. thing
and trying to prevent
the future.
I mean, do we really need to go
looking for more trouble?
Please?
- Okay, I'll drop it.
- Really?
Just like that?
- Um, yes.
Sometimes I do listen to you,
you know?
- That hasn't been
my experience.
- Shut up.
- All right.
I'll see you later.
- 'Kay, bye.
- Thank you.
[light orchestration]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Don't you get tired
of running?
[door whirring open]
[chuckles]
[whoosh]
- That's the thing,
running just
sort of keeps my mind
off of things, I guess.
- Must be an amazing feeling.
- It is.
- You know, cracking a big story
gives me an amazing feeling.
And...I think I'm onto one.
- Oh, that, uh,
arms dealer thing?
- How do you know about that?
- Because both Dad and Barry
want you to lay off of it.
The phrase "death wish"
got tossed around a lot
by them.
- Okay, I do not have
a death wish.
I just want
to see justice done
like everyone else
in this building.
- I get that, but it is
dangerous, Iris.
- Wally, how dangerous
could it be?
I don't die till May.
Barry said that
in Flashpoint, you and I
were a brother-sister
crime-fighting team.
I say we make that
a reality again.
- Shouldn't we
ask Barry first?
- No, this is
just between us, Wally.
We can do this together.
[upbeat tone]
- Do you know what I'm really
gonna miss about this Earth?
- I don't know. Uh...
- Soap operas.
I mean, a long, winding story
served up daily
in hour-long chapters?
- You never answered
Caitlin's question.
- Oh, about why I put
mustard on my fries?
- Why you risked your life
to come here.
- That.
I looked in a mirror.
- I don't follow.
- Look, on my Earth,
I had fame. I had power.
I had respect.
I was "H.R. Wells."
[imitates fans cheering]
But when I looked in the mirror,
I knew the truth.
And the truth was...
I didn't matter.
[pensive music]
I was a fraud.
That is why
I came to this Earth,
so I could rewrite my story,
both literally and figuratively.
- There's gotta be something
you can do, H.R.
- [laughs]
There's not.
- You can't hire a lawyer?
Appeal the case?
- There's nothing I can do,
B.A.!
I don't mean to snap at you.
It just...I don't have
any options here, all right?
Unless, of course,
I appeal for
trial by combat.
♪ ♪
[intercom warbles]
- Guys, Gypsy's here.
- Always so punctual.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I'm impressed!
Thought you'd
try and flee again.
Time to go.
- [clears throat]
All right.
Gypsy,
take me home.
- Wait.
You're not taking him anywhere.
- What?
- Why not?
- Because I challenge you
to trial by combat.
- What are you doing?
- I'm challenging her
to trial by combat.
- No, no, he isn't.
Okay, I am.
I'm gonna fight you.
- Well, that one spoke first.
- What?
That's like a real rule?
- By the laws of Earth-19,
I hereby challenge you
for possession of H.R. Wells.
If you want, we can
solve this another way.
There's a great spot
for drinks...
- You realize trial by combat
is to the death?
- Yeah.
For the loser.
- [chuckles]
- Listen, you want him?
You're gonna have
to come and claim him.
- Hmm.
- That's Arwen.
That's...Arwen.
- I take it you also want the
customary 24 hours to prepare?
- [scoffs]
Do I want the customary...
- Yes, you do.
- I would love
to take advantage
of the customary 24 hours,
if you don't mind.
- Very well.
One day.
- One day.
- See you then.
[warbling tone]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
She's gonna kill me,
isn't she?
[sonic blasting]
- [exhales]
She's good.
- She's great.
I mean, Gypsy is a legend
on my Earth.
- So why, exactly,
did you agree to fight her?
- I don't know.
- You did what
any of us would have done.
- I might not have done it,
just being honest.
- Okay, all right.
Lay it out for me.
What are my chances here,
scale of one to ten?
- She's gonna kill you.
- It's a pretty solid
"one," mate.
- You have the same powers
Gypsy does, right?
I mean, she's not doing
anything you can't do.
- Much better...look, I mean,
she's doing it just much better.
- You can do this, okay?
You just need a little practice
and a little confidence.
And we're all gonna
help you with that, right?
- Yes.
- Uh, sure, sure, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
I believe in you, all right?
You can beat her.
[soft orchestration]
- Listen,
I have some ideas
for a training regimen
I can set up in here.
Caitlin, why don't you get
the medical bay prepared
in the meantime?
- What?
Well, why does...why does she
need to set up the...
the medical bay?
- For when you...
beat her,
when you beat her,
she's gonna...she's gonna
need medical attention.
'Cause you will beat her,
I have every faith
that you're going to beat her.
- We need to work on
your interpersonal skills.
- I wasn't really trying.
- Has anyone ever beat her?
- Yeah.
No.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I've officially reached
a nice, comfortable level
of just straight-up panic.
- I mean,
you don't even like me.
Why would you
risk your life for me?
- Well, you heard Barry.
It's what we do around here.
- Come on. Why?
- You're not like
the other Wellses.
- Yeah, so you keep
reminding me.
- No, I mean, those two,
they were geniuses.
We depended on them.
But with you,
the roles are reversed.
You depend on us.
Harrison Wells
was always there for me,
so I guess in some weird way,
I just...
I want to be there
for Harrison Wells.
[pensive music]
Anyway...
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- So what are we doing here?
I thought you didn't
want Dad to know
we're going after
this arms dealer.
- Oh, yeah, no, I don't.
But, um, actually,
I need you to swipe
his file on the case
and photograph the pages
and then put them back.
Thanks.
- What?
Iris.
Have you lost your mind?
Dad will kill us.
- No, no, Wally, he won't.
He won't even know
that Kid Flash was there.
- First, you
have to tell me why.
- Okay, look.
I know everyone
is working really hard
to prevent Savitar from...
- Yeah.
- But, honestly, these could be
my last few months on Earth.
- Can you not talk like that?
- I'm just being
realistic, Wally.
I get to do that.
Look, I want my life
to mean something,
more than just a daughter
or as a sister
or as a girlfriend,
but as a reporter.
This story can do that.
It can say that I,
Iris West, mattered.
- You know, my life
was a lot easier
before I had a sister.
- But it's a lot better
now, isn't it?
Come on.
- Okay.
- I can get you
the no-knock warrant,
but, Joe, this guy
is armed to the teeth
with God only knows what.
You're gonna have to move
in there fast and hard.
- [laughing]
- [laughs]
"Fast and hard," okay,
I kind of walked into that...
- Hey. Sorry.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hi.
- [kisses]
- Hi, Iris.
- Hi.
Good to see you, Cecile.
Um, Dad, can I borrow you
for a second
for a little
father-daughter talk?
- Uh...
- I need to go
catch up with Captain Singh,
so I will be back
in a little while, yeah?
It's good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
- So...what's up?
How can I help you?
- Can I talk to you
for a second over here?
Um...
[clears throat]
Uhh, yeah, so, um,
I wanted to...
to speak to you about
me and Barry.
- You and Barry?
- Yes.
- Okay?
- So there comes a time
in every couple's relationship
when you realize
that there is
too much love
for two people.
And...
[whoosh]
Uh, when that happens,
you know in your heart
that the only solution is
to make your family
a little...bigger.
- Okay, I'm gonna need a second.
- Oh!
Dad, hey, hey,
listen to me very closely.
This is so important to me.
- Oh, God.
- Um...
Um...
[whoosh]
Is Barry a dog or a cat person?
- What?
- Yeah, what kind of animal
does he like?
Because I was thinking
about getting him a pet
and I don't really remember
him having a preference.
- Oh, man, you had me
going there for a second.
- What, what did you
think I was talking about?
- Nothing, nothing, I...
you can get him any kind
of animal you want
as long as it has four legs.
- Good, great advice,
four legs, copy that.
Thanks for the chat.
Okay, bye.
- [exhales]
Damn.
[sonic whoosh]
- Oh, yeah.
Facing the wrong way again.
How many is that?
- Three.
- Nine.
- You'll get there.
- Yes.
Hopefully in the next
21 hours and 46 minutes.
- All right, look,
whenever I'm out there,
I'm in a tough fight,
I think maybe I don't have it,
I just take a deep breath...
- [breathes deeply]
- Trust my instincts.
- Trust my instincts,
that's good.
That helps.
[exhales]
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know.
[sonic whoosh]
- Guys?
Up here.
- Let...let's go talk.
- All right.
- We can't let
Francisco fight Gypsy,
because if he does,
he is a dead man.
- You don't know that.
- Oh, I know that.
You know that.
He knows that.
- Okay, I get it.
- She knows that.
We know that; everybody knows...
- So what are we supposed to do?
- We're supposed to stop her
before she fights him.
- That would be great
if we knew where she was.
Yes?
- I know where she is.
- How?
- I tagged her with a tracer
last time she was here.
A magician friend
told me you kind of
distract 'em and tag...
- H.R.
- I needed to know
where she was
so I could stay
one step ahead of her.
She is...
[tablet beeping]
both: At the waterfront.
- What do you say?
For Francisco?
- [sighs]
All right.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- This world may be
a primitive,
uncultured backwater,
but they do make
an excellent cup of coffee.
- That they do.
You know what you gotta try?
You gotta try the
Brazilian roast, it's new.
It is so good.
- Maybe I'll take
a few bags back with me.
- Yeah, think that's wise.
- Will you be
going back in a bag?
- Look, that kid,
Francisco,
he's just trying to protect me.
- Then he's as foolish
as he is cute.
- Okay, Gypsy.
Let's go home.
[dramatic music]
[The Flash grunts]
- B.A.!
- [grunts]
- Nice try!
You think I didn't
see that coming?
- Stop, stop!
- Stop what?
- Stop...
- Stop trying
to enforce the law?
You are a criminal.
Now, it's great that
you made friends here,
but that doesn't change
the fact that you lied.
You broke
our most sacred laws,
and now it is time
for you to face justice.
- Wait!
You still need to face Cisco.
- No, I think this
little stunt forfeits his claim.
And his time.
- You just said you believe
in the law, right?
We made a mistake.
Cisco will hold up
his end of the deal.
- He will.
- You have really pulled
a number on these people
if they would die for you.
Tell Cisco there is
no backing out now.
I'll keep this one
as insurance until then.
- B.A...
[grunts]
- [exhales]
That's not good.
[dramatic music]
[soft orchestration]
- She took H.R.?
- Mm-hmm.
- Can she do that?
I mean, I though this whole
trial by combat thing had rules.
- Which apparently we broke
when we tried
to get the drop on her.
- Well, that wasn't
very clever, was it?
A deal's a deal.
It should be honored.
- You know what?
You're right, Julian.
A deal is a deal.
And our deal was that
I would train
so that I could fight Gypsy,
but I guess you two
wanted to go behind my back
and try to sub in?
- We didn't go...we just thought
maybe you could use some help.
- Yeah? What happened to,
"Cisco, you can beat her"?
- You can.
- "I believe in you."
- I do.
- "Trust your instincts."
♪ ♪
- [grunts and sighs]
- Well, right now,
my instincts are telling me
I should be writing
my last will and testament,
so please excuse me.
- Cisco, come...
- Should I go talk to him?
- No, I...
I got it.
♪ ♪
- Looks like
I'm not the only one
who has to work on
their interpersonal skills.
♪ ♪
- Oh, hey.
I'd be careful
if I were you.
Last thing we want is
for me to touch a button
and blow your head off, right?
[mock laugh]
'Cause I don't know
what I'm doing, right?
- You know I don't think that.
- Yeah, well,
you have a very,
very strange way
of showing it.
[gentle music]
- You're right, man.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I just...
guess this whole
"not getting faster" thing,
it just has me rattled.
I was always able
to do it before, you know?
I mean, against Reverse Flash
and then against Zoom, but...
Savitar's on
a whole other level.
And knowing what he'll do
to Iris if I fail?
- I'm afraid just...
thinking what's gonna happen
to H.R. if I don't beat Gypsy.
But you, you're the hero.
I mean,
how do you handle
all this pressure all the time?
- By just leaning
on all of you guys.
You know, I mean,
you're always in my corner,
helping me face my fears.
And it is okay to be afraid.
Trust me.
And when you are,
I'll be there
in your corner.
- Yes, lovely
little speech, Allen.
But what Mr. Ramon
needs to defeat
his inter-dimensional adversary
is a practical stratagem.
Lucky for you,
I found one.
[keys clacking]
This is Gypsy's signature move.
I call it her
"breach and blast."
- Oh, yeah.
That move.
- You see just before she comes
in and out of a breach,
her feet come off the ground.
- So for that split second
she's off the ground,
she'll be off-balance.
- Yes, and vulnerable.
It might behoove you
to use this during the battle.
- This is great, Julian.
- Hmm, just glad
I could be helpful.
- This is...more than helpful.
I gotta work on this.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
- Thanks.
[rousing music]
[ominous music]
- You sure this
is the place?
- Positive.
- All right.
You ready to bust
an arms dealer?
Get me a front-page headline?
- Wally, wait.
CCPD's been looking
for this guy for months.
He might have some sort
of secret tunnel network
that helps him
slip out and get away.
- I should do a quick recon.
- Yeah. Thorough.
We don't want
to miss anything, okay?
- Be back in a you-know-what.
[whoosh]
[brooding string music]
♪ ♪
[eerie music]
[camera shutter clicks]
- Hope you like what you see,
'cause this sneak preview
is gonna cost you your life.
- Yeah, I don't think so.
[dramatic music]
- [chuckles]
Are you crazy?
This'll rip a hole
right through you.
- Everyone's gotta go
sometime, right?
And I am pretty sure
today just...
isn't my day.
[suspenseful music]
[whooshing]
- [grunts]
- What the hell, sis?
Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
- God, okay, look,
we gotta get you out of here
before CCPD sees you.
[sirens wailing]
- Don't worry.
Dad's, like, my biggest fan now.
He's totally cool
with me doing stuff like this.
♪ ♪
- Hell no,
I ain't cool with this.
You two almost compromised
a major CCPD sting operation
that took the DA's office
months to assemble.
- You still got the guy,
right?
- That is not the point,
Iris.
The point is, you had
you and your brother out there
in danger, and for what?
A story?
And where the hell were you?
- Dad, this is more
than just a story for me.
- Yeah, which you almost
got shot for.
[tense ominous music]
- Oh, God.
♪ ♪
- What?
- [exhales]
- Iris.
What is going on with you?
♪ ♪
- Joe, I'm sorry...
can I talk to you for a second?
We'll be right back.
[somber orchestration]
♪ ♪
Joe already suspects
something's up.
You going out there like that,
it just hangs a bell on it.
- This story is going
to change lives, Barry.
Why do you think that
you're the only one
allowed to risk your life
to do good?
- I don't.
♪ ♪
It's okay
to be afraid of the future.
But I won't let you die.
- I am not afraid to die,
Barry, I'm not.
- Then what?
- I'm afraid...
[gentle piano music]
What if I end up
just like my mom?
Just gone without
making a mark,
without leaving
anything behind.
- Iris, your mom,
she left something behind.
She left a brave, wonderful son
and the woman that I love.
All right?
I don't know what the future
holds, none of us do.
♪ ♪
I know that we will
face it together.
- Gypsy just vibed me
her location.
Let's do this.
- I don't think the
literary critics on our Earth
would know a real
sci-fi romance best seller
unless it bit them in the...
- Time's up, Wells.
Looks like your so-called
friend is a coward after all.
- He's not a coward.
He's one of the finest
men I've ever known.
- Oh, you're right
about that!
I'm fine as hell.
- [chuckles]
There he is.
- Didn't think you'd show.
- Oh, I wouldn't miss
an evening with you,
even if it is for a showdown.
- I will kill you, Cisco.
- We'll see who dies tonight.
[soft suspenseful music]
- To the victor
goes H.R. Wells.
- May the best vibe win.
[dramatic music]
- Part of me was hoping
you wouldn't show tonight.
- How do you want to do this?
"Westworld"-style, back to back,
ten paces, turn and shoot?
- No.
- [grunts]
[dark dramatic music]
- This does not bode well.
- Cisco can hold his own.
- Hmm. Barely.
- Barry, we can't let
this happen.
What if he can't defeat her?
- I can't interfere again.
If I do, then we forfeit.
H.R.'s a dead man.
- At this rate, Cisco's
gonna be the dead man.
- Oh.
Ooh, girl!
You done did it now!
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[both panting]
- [exhales]
- [panting]
Stronger than I thought.
- I'm just getting warmed up.
- Yeah, maybe not do that.
- Time to turn things up
to 11.
- "Spinal Tap."
That's, like,
one of my favorite movies...
[grunts]
[dramatic musical flourish]
[electronic beep]
- Where did they go?
- I...they could be
anywhere by now.
- In any universe.
- [grunts]
- [panting]
- This is Earth-2.
[blows land]
- You're cute,
but you talk too much.
- Oh, you want
to play dirty, huh?
Let's play dirty.
[sonic blast]
[dramatic music]
[warbling tone]
- [gasps]
[table crashes]
- [grunting]
- Oh!
That hurts.
[blow lands]
That too.
[sonic blast]
♪ ♪
- Is it me,
or is this city getting weirder?
♪ ♪
[Cisco grunts]
- [panting]
[warbling tone]
- Well, this is hot.
- I think you're flirting
with me to distract me
'cause you're afraid.
- [laughs]
My collection record
is flawless.
In these trials,
I am undefeated.
- [laughs]
Oh, please.
Everybody's got a weakness.
Even you.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
- Says the man afraid
of showing everyone
how powerful he can be.
You and I resonate
on a similar frequency.
I can feel it.
Yet you allow your fear
and insecurity to hold you back.
That's why you're gonna lose.
[warbling tone]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[blast lands]
- Does this look like
holding back to you?
I could do this all night.
- How did you...
- You might want to work on
your balance next time, girl.
[soft orchestration]
♪ ♪
Admit it,
I won.
- Yes!
- He won.
- Yeah, he did.
both: Yes!
[clapping]
- She must have been having
an off day.
♪ ♪
What?
- Wow.
♪ ♪
- By the laws of Earth-19,
the prisoner is yours
for the taking,
as is my life.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
We don't roll like that
around here.
Come on.
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
In all the multiverse,
I have...
never...
met anyone like you, Cisco.
- Please, call me Vibe.
Or...or you can call me Cisco.
That's also allowed.
I'm just a regular guy.
Just a regular...
single guy.
[triumphant orchestration]
- It says you're totally fine.
- So what happens now?
Go back to your Earth?
Tell all your superiors
that you were bested in battle,
all the charges
against H.R. are dropped.
- No.
I tell them I killed him.
- Wait, what?
- If I return empty-handed,
they'll know I failed.
And I never fail.
Until today.
- Okay, but if you
tell them that
you killed me, then I...
- You will never go back
to Earth-19,
ever.
Do we have a deal?
- Yeah.
I guess we have a deal.
I don't really have
anything to go home for.
- You'll always have
a home here, H.R.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- Listen, I know there's
no coffee on your Earth
'cause of the whole
Blight thing or whatever,
but this...this is
just an absurd
amount of coffee you're
bringing back to your Earth.
That can't be legal.
- I mean, I won't tell
if you won't.
- You know, for someone so
fixated on enforcing the law,
you sure seem oddly at ease
about breaking it.
- Well, I guess some laws
are worth breaking
for the right person.
- Mm.
- Hmm.
♪ ♪
- So this good-bye then?
- For now.
[gentle music]
[warbling tone]
- [exhales]
Wow.
What an exit.
♪ ♪
- Okay, you know,
for the fastest man alive,
you are theslowest reader.
- Hey, this is your big article.
I'm not gonna rush through it.
- [sighs]
- I'm just kidding.
I read it five times already.
You sure sold the hell
out of Kid Flash
as Central City's
next super savior.
I'm sure Wally's loving that.
- Well, I did promise him
the front page.
But what do you think?
Do you think it'll
make any difference?
- Kid Flash already
changed one thing
that we saw in the future.
[soft orchestration]
- No, I meant the article.
- What?
- The article?
- I think you should be
really proud.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's the beginning of...
an amazing journalistic legacy.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- How amazing?
Like Pulitzer amazing?
- Time will tell.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I...
Do you know what I realized?
- Hmm?
- Savitar, he said that
I trapped him
wherever he is;
you know what that means?
Means I beat him.
And I'm gonna do it again,
I promise.
So don't worry.
The Flash is gonna save you.
- My hero.
♪ ♪
- The thing they never tell you
is that nothing
ever stays the same.
So the harder you work
to take down the bad guys,
the more they up their game.
- Hey.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
- No.
- Just had to grab
some stuff for...
- Yeah.
- I thought you were finished
working with that stuff?
- Oh, no, it's just, uh,
this is just for me.
No, the...the book, it...
you know,
my own personal sense
of accomplishment.
- [scoffs]
Well,
you've accomplished
plenty.
- Ha! Ha!
What have I accomplished,
Francisco?
- Well, for one,
you got me to risk
my life to save yours.
And trust me, my friend,
that is a huge accomplishment.
[soft orchestration]
- Yeah, about that...
I just want to say that
I appreciate
what you did for me.
- Yeah, it's what we do
for our friends, right?
Besides, it was a way
for me to balance the scales.
- Balance the scales, right.
What does that mean?
- I just mean...
I can't tell you
the amount of times
that I've been in your shoes
and a man with your face
has made me feel better.
- Yeah, about that,
I would...
[exhales]
I would love if you could share
some of my doppelganger's
knowledge.
I would love to know what
the smarter versions
of me think.
- Okay.
Um...
- [clears throat]
- The first Wells told me
my time would come
to be a hero,
that it was my job
to show up,
to be ready
for when it did.
You know why
I love working here?
- Why?
- We're all making investments
in each other.
I made an investment in you,
and one day, that
investment's gonna pay off
when you use that...
crazy way of thinking you have
to help me out.
I guess if he were here,
he would say,
"Show up."
- Yeah.
- Be ready.
- 'Cause...
one day, you might need
to save my ass.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
[bright orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- [pants]
- [chuckles]
Keep it up at this rate,
you're gonna reach Mach 3 soon.
- I know, it's...it's crazy
how fast I've gotten
in such a short time, right?
- Yeah.
And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
- Why's that?
- Because I've done the math
over and over and I finally
realized that I've been looking
at things the wrong way.
I'm not gonna save
Iris from Savitar.
You are.
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.