Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- The Philosopher's Stone
has been the key to everything.
- So we destroy the Stone,
and Savitar is gone for good.
- There's only one thing
we can do with it.
Throw it into the Speed Force.
- I have to do
what I can to help.
I'm the guy who avoided
his dying mother for weeks.
I have a whole lot
to make up for.
- I like you, Julian,
but I'm also afraid
of my powers
and what they could do
to anyone who gets close
to me.
I didn't ask for these powers,
just like you didn't ask
to be used by Savitar.
- I think we should
be terrified together.
- Sure.
Together it is.
- It's crazy how fast I've
gotten in such a short time.
- And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
I'm not gonna save Iris
from Savitar; you are.
- [growling]
- Iris West,
will you marry me?
- [gasps]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- And Wally just beat
his personal best.
Oh, Barry's putting him
through the wringer today.
- Excuse...Barry?
Excuse me?
Uh, yeah, I suppose
it could be Barry,
or it could be his genius coach,
whose sole purpose
on this Earth
is milking epic greatness
from those around him.
Thank you very much.
- It could also be Jesse.
- What?
- Come on, Wally doesn't want
to get beat by his girlfriend.
- Also, please, just refrain
from using "milk" as a verb
from now on, please.
[exciting music]
- I'm getting kind of dizzy.
- You're supposed
to get dizzy, Wallace!
You're supposed to get exhausted
on this route.
It's supposed to simulate
the stress
that you're gonna feel
when you finally confront
Savitar,
so my suggestion to you is,
suck it up, buttercup!
Milking epic greatness.
- Yeah, no kidding.
Why don't you take it down
a little, Tiger Mom?
- Barry and Jesse
are at the final mark.
- You ready?
-Wally's at the home stretch.
♪ ♪
- Come on...
[stopwatch beeps]
[dramatic music]
- Guys?
- 0.21 seconds.
♪ ♪
- 0.21.
Just fast enough
to save Iris from Savitar.
You did it.
- [laughs]
- You did it.
- We did it.
- You did it!
- You did it.
[suspenseful music]
- You okay?
- [stammers]
Uh, yeah, yeah.
I'm just...happy.
- We all are, Wally.
We all are.
♪ ♪
- Julian. Hi.
How are you?
- Ah, Caitlin, how are you?
- It...
You've come straight
from the airport?
- Uh...
Yes, yes, uh...
Barry said he had
something to tell me.
Is he here?
- He'll be here any minute,
I'm sure.
- Shall we? Yeah?
- Yes, we shall.
- [chuckles] We shall.
[indistinct conversation]
- Look who I found.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh!
- How are we doing?
- Julian.
- It's good to see you.
Good to see you all.
Jesse, I thought you were
heading back to Earth-2.
- I actually decided to stick
around for a little while.
- Hey, does anybody know
what's going on?
I mean, I got a mountain
of paperwork back at the office.
- No, not the foggiest.
I was gonna ask you.
- Ah.
Welcome home, James.
Can I brew you
a proper cup of tea?
And a robust pick-me-up
for you, mate.
- No need. We hit Jitters
on the way.
Got everybody something.
- You guys are...
- I thought
you were on deadline.
- I am.
- You ready?
- For you.
- Here.
- Okay. What is going on
with you two?
- Uh, do you want to?
- Mm-mm.
This is all you.
- Okay, here goes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...
[clears throat]
[sighs]
- [gasps]
- No!
- Congratulations!
That's so exciting!
- Thank you.
Thanks.
Hey, thanks, man.
- Wow.
You did it. This is...
This is fantastic.
Well done, Joe.
Congratulations.
- Dad, say something,
please.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- My baby girl.
You have grown
into a beautiful woman.
You're marrying
the best man I know.
- Thanks.
- You two bring me
nothing but joy.
I'm so happy for you.
- Okay.
This cuteness right here,
I cannot...
Congrats.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- And speaking of, um,
best man...
- I'll do it.
Of course.
When Barry and I first met...
- H.R.
- You mean him.
Okay, good.
- I...
I'd be honored.
Really.
I mean, as long as I can
get that plus-one.
'Cause, you know,
me and Gypsy,
we about to tear up
the dance floor for you guys.
[laughter]
- Barry.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yeah, yeah.
[laughter]
- Now, I wanted to be sure that
you heard what I said in there.
I couldn't be happier.
- Okay, right.
- So...
Why didn't you
ask my permission?
I mean,
I told you the story
of me asking
Francine's dad's permission,
like, a hundred times.
- At least, yeah.
And that's a great story.
- Eh, but you missed the point?
- I...
Yeah, I...
I don't...
It was spontaneous.
I knew you'd say yes,
and I wanted to surprise you.
- Yo. There's a three-alarm fire
in the Raab building.
Fire department
is evacuating it now.
- Jesse is a little preoccupied
with the ring,
so it's just you and me.
- Okay.
- What you two waiting for? Go.
- Yeah.
[exciting music]
[sirens wailing]
♪ ♪
- Wallace...
Wallace West.
[dramatic music]
- [grunts]
- Wally...
♪ ♪
- What the hell?
- [growling]
- Wally.
Hey.
What's happening?
What's wrong?
- Where'd he go?
[gasps]
- Who?
- Where is he?
- Who? Where is who?
- Savitar.
♪ ♪
- I feel fine.
- So now Savitar's
mind-punking you...
[chuckles] Oh, boy.
This never stops
never stopping.
- How long has this
been going on, Wally?
- Like a week.
- [scoffs] A week.
- Wally, why didn't you say
anything before?
- Because I didn't know
what this was.
I thought that this
was just maybe in my head.
You know, I wasn't looking at it
like I was keeping it to myself.
- That's exactly what you did,
though, Wally.
You did keep it to yourself,
and with Savitar,
that's not something we can do.
This is Iris' life
we're talking about.
- Yes, I know that.
- Do you, though, Wally?
- Yes.
- Uh, okay.
- [clears throat]
- Until now, it was...
you only saw him, right?
- Yeah, this was the first time
it was physical.
- What...he wasn't there!
Okay?
You weren't fighting him.
He was messing with
your head.
It was all in your mind.
- I've been there.
Done that.
It's miserable.
- Okay, why don't I run
a brain scan on Wally,
see if he was
similarly affected
to when Julian was possessed?
- Yeah, that's fine.
Why don't we do that?
- Wally shouldn't
be in here anyway.
- What?
- Barry, he knows he messed up.
- That's not what this is about,
okay? Look, it's...
If Savitar's using Wally
the same way he used Julian,
how do we know he's not spying
on us through Wally right now?
Wally, we don't know
how this works.
How do we know he can't see
and hear everything we're doing?
Look, you're out.
- I'm out?
- I'm sorry, Wally.
- Yeah, you don't sound
real sorry.
- All right, fellows,
let's take a quick ten.
We're all still
the "Four Amigos" here, right?
- What?
- You don't have that movie
on this Earth?
- I'll go talk to him.
- Yeah, talk some sense
into him.
- All right.
- So what now?
- Well, we know
from the future
that Savitar gets out
of wherever he is,
but for now,
he's still trapped, so...
[sighs] I need
to talk to him again.
- No, I knew you were
thinking this.
All right?
And I won't do it.
I'm not gonna be your personal
walkie-talkie to him.
- Guys, we can't.
We don't have the Stone.
- Actually, we can.
We still have Savitar's
spatial frequency
from when we plugged in
Linda Blair here,
so I think we could work
without the Stone.
- Julian, I'm sorry, man.
We don't really have a choice.
- Oh, we do have a choice.
I have a choice.
And I choose to decline.
I'm sorry.
- We're starting to fray.
- Well, we can't. All right?
Everybody just needs
to trust me.
I know what I'm doing.
[door opens and closes]
- [sighs] Come to talk me
into it, then?
- No.
- Barry's lost his bloody mind
if he thinks
I'm gonna volunteer to be...
abused again.
- He's just trying
to protect Iris.
- We all are.
But...not like that.
- Is the reason you don't want
to do this because...
you don't want me to see it?
- [sighs]
I just think...
Hearing his voice
coming out of me, I...
It just makes it impossible
for you to see me as a normal...
- Hey.
I've had somebody else's voice
coming out of my mouth,
and you were still able
to see the real me.
How about trusting
that I can do the same thing?
- Sorry.
I just wanted to do that,
in case you
changed your mind later.
- Quite all right.
- Julian,
you're gonna be okay.
You know the drill.
Just let your mind go blank.
We'll take care of the rest.
Okay?
- Just let Savitar back in
the driver's seat once more.
Brilliant.
- Thank you.
- Let's just get this
over with, yeah?
[electricity whirring]
[breathing deeply]
[gasps]
[distorted]
Bow before my greatness.
Be in awe, as you are
in the presence of the Almighty.
- Enough with the...
religious nonsense.
You were just a man.
Like me.
- I'm nothing like you,
Barry.
You're cruel, you're selfish.
From my perspective,
you're the big bad.
- [scoffs] Stupid.
- Still here, pretender?
Still trying to find your place?
- I found my place.
It's standing here
with these people,
against you.
- You know, the sad thing
is that you live.
You survived my wrath.
The coward. Irony.
- Where are you?
You said that I trapped you
in the future, where?
- The only place
that you could think of.
The only place
that could hold me.
- How long have you
been imprisoned?
- Long enough to lose my mind
several times over.
It's only my will that keeps me
on this side of sanity.
- You know, it's funny,
when I think of sanity,
I don't necessarily
think of Savitar.
- Well, that's because
you're small, Cisco.
You've always been small.
Reverb told you that
you could have been a god.
But instead, you'd rather
work as...tech support.
- You want to tell me
why we're enemies?
- Because we had to be.
Only one of us could live.
You thought that Thawne and Zoom
were your biggest foes,
but...
But it's me.
It's always been me, Barry.
- Man, what did we ever
do to you?
- You took everything from me!
I never asked
for any of this, Joe.
I am only this way
because of you.
All of you!
- When do we meet?
- Not long now.
You're there
when I become who I am.
- You're saying I caused you
to get your speed?
I created you?
- Oh, no.
I created myself, Barry.
Only I can bring out
my greatness.
- Your greatness?
Well, you're still trapped,
wherever you are,
and I don't know how
you're gonna escape.
I mean, we got rid
of the Philosopher's Stone.
- Did we?
I am closer to my freedom
than I have ever been.
Every step, every move
that you make,
it only brings me
nearer to it.
I only need one more thing.
- Man, do you love
to hear yourself talk.
- Iris, trying to show
that you're not afraid?
But I know you are.
I'm sorry that
you have to die.
But it's you or me.
And despite your feeble efforts
to change the future,
you can't,
because I am
the future, Flash.
Barry, you've had to suffer
worse than anyone.
You've endured pain
your whole life.
Your mother,
your father...
Trust me,
you'll never get over this.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Well...
Well?
Good chat, was it?
[melancholic music]
- I-I don't know
if I can take another
one of those séances.
Anyone else with me?
I almost filled my drawers.
- Okay, so other than
Savitar taking
scaring-the-bejeezus-out-of-us
to a whole new level,
did we actually learn anything?
- Please say yes.
- Maybe.
When I mentioned the Stone,
he questioned whether or not
we'd really gotten rid of it.
- We did. We threw it
into the Speed Force.
That's like throwing it
into outer space.
- Uh, maybe we didn't.
I mean, maybe
there's more to it.
- A second Stone?
- Or maybe the Stone
that we had was part
of a larger piece.
- How about the Acolytes?
Maybe they know something
we don't.
- Hey, what about that one guy?
- Craig?
- Yes, the Acolyte
that you dropped in on
when you went all cold?
His car's GPS has him located
somewhere near...
Mount Buccelato.
- Buccelato, that's miles away.
What...what would he
be doing over there?
- There's one way to find out.
[exciting music]
-Talk to us.
What do you see?
- Some serious
"Temple of Doom" stuff.
They have a box.
- God of Speed,
soon your enemies will fall
and you will rise once more
on Earth.
- It looks just like the
last one that held the Stone.
- You were right, Barr.
- Iris:What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna go see
what's in it.
♪ ♪
What exactly were you guys
doing up here?
- Worshipping His Greatness.
- Let's see how far he gets
without this.
- [chuckles]
He's ten steps ahead of you.
There's no stopping Savitar.
If I were you...
[breathing heavily]
I'd move up the wedding.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- So far...not so good.
Can't get any readings
off of it.
- It's the same
as the last time.
- Are we sure
this isn't the same box?
- Well, it can't be.
I mean, I threw the other one
into the Speed Force.
- Yeah, but you said
the explosion
sent you to the future.
What if it did something
to the box too, you know?
- [sighs] I hate to say it,
Barry, but,
after all my years of research,
I've never heard or come across
another box or Stone;
I think this is it.
- If that's true, we need
to consider the possibility
that Savitar has that Stone.
- I'm gonna check
for radioactive isotopes
or gravimetric force residue,
'cause if it's the same
as the last time...
- We're in big trouble.
[sighs]
- You can go faster than that,
Wally. Run!
And...
Time!
Yeah. Yeah.
That was, uh...
Good.
We need to go again.
- But I don't understand.
I was fast enough this morning.
Now all of a sudden,
I'm too slow?
- You're in your head. You gotta
get out of your head, man.
You gotta just run,
you gotta push
everything else to the side.
- Yeah, I'm trying, H.R.
I can't do it!
- Okay.
- All right?
All right.
Why not?
- I don't know.
- I do.
You're afraid.
Which is...
I totally understand.
I mean, if I were in your shoes,
I'd be terrified.
But you can't run from
a place of fear, all right?
Nobody can do
anything effectively
coming from a place of fear.
Trust me, I know.
- Savitar can get
inside my head.
What am I supposed to do
if he does that
at the wrong time?
- [sighs]
- It sure would be
a lot easier if I just
knew exactly
how that night went.
- [chuckles]
Would it ever.
Are you picking up
what I'm putting down?
- Uh-huh.
- Let's go.
- No way.
I'm not gonna vibe you there
for you to watch
your sister die.
- Okay.
Cesco-Cesco-Cesco...
Th-this is to help Wallace.
To help him see what happens
so he knows what to do
in the moment.
- Come on, Cisco, please.
If Savitar is coming back
and I'm the only one
that can save Iris,
I have to do
everything I can
to make sure that happens.
- And you're sure
you want to do that?
Because this is not something
you can unsee, Wally.
- If this is gonna help me
save my sister, yeah.
I have to see it.
Please.
- Okay, if you
have to see it...
Come on down.
Be my guest.
H.R., you know
how to work this, right?
- I know how
to work this, yeah.
- Anything goes wrong,
you get Caitlin down here stat.
- I know what I'm doing.
I was here the last time.
I saw what you did.
All I got to do is do this.
- The other one.
- It's the other button.
[electricity whirs]
Bit of a lighter touch
next time, please, H.R.!
- Copy. Lighter touch.
- This way.
- Don't!
- This is it.
- Okay.
- So that's the distance
I need to cover.
- Don't do this!
- Now, finally,
I am free of you!
- [sobbing] Barry, I love you.
- No, don't say that, all right?
You're gonna be all right.
Hey, I'm begging you,
I'm begging you!
I'm beg...[sobs]
- Barry?
- You lose, Barry.
- No!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Iris?
Iris, Iris.
Look.
- Come on.
- What...what'd you see?
[stammering]
Was it good?
Did that...did that help?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- It helped a lot.
- Wally...
♪ ♪
- Why does nobody
ever listen to me?
- You're so full of it.
- What?
- Railing at me
for not telling everyone
about Savitar?
What about what you're not
telling everyone, Barry?
- What are you...
- Cisco vibed me
into the future.
I saw what happened.
Tell my sister why
you asked her to marry you.
Go on, tell her
the real reason, Barry.
- What is he talking about?
Barry.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- The night that
Savitar kills you,
you didn't have a ring
on your finger.
- We weren't engaged yet.
So you thought
that if we were...
- That it might
change the future.
Iris...
Iris, wait.
Iris, hey. Come on.
Hey, I love you, okay.
I love you more than anything.
That part has never changed.
It never will.
- Barry, we moved in together
after some rash decision
that you made at Christmas,
and then a couple weeks later,
you proposed.
You didn't even ask
for my dad's permission.
- I know. I don't know...
I guess I got caught...
I got caught up in the moment.
I...
- That is exactly
what I am afraid of.
- Iris, please, come on...
- Barry, I just...
I need time to think.
- Hey.
You okay?
- I'm worried.
- Yeah, I understand.
I keep coming back
to the thought that...
I could be the cause
of all this.
- What do you mean?
- Savitar's prophecy.
"One will betray you."
You may well have invited
Judas into the group, Caitlin.
- It's not you.
- It's impossible to tell.
Savitar could be controlling me,
and none of us
would know about it.
None of us, not even me.
- But this time,
we know who it is.
- How?
[dramatic music]
- Because...
I'm the one
who betrayed everyone.
♪ ♪
- How long have you had this?
- Ever since you threw
the box into the Speed Force.
It's such a small piece.
I didn't think
it would really matter.
- Why would you even risk it?
- Because...
I thought I could use it
to get rid of my powers.
- And...can you?
- I don't know.
I haven't been able
to figure out
how to use it yet.
- Okay, well, look, gang,
I think we can all agree
that this is a simple case
of the other side...
Killer Frost side of Caitlin
clouding
her better judgment, so...
- No, H.R.
This wasn't her.
It was me.
I'm really sorry, guys.
- Right now, we just need
to figure out where Savitar is.
- Yes, I think
that's a fantastic plan.
How are we gonna do that?
- Uh...
- No.
- One more time.
- No, no.
You want to
summon Savitar again?
- I am not a human
Ouija board, Barry.
You can't just keep...
- It's the last time, all right?
And only long enough to see
if maybe
we can track his location.
Is that possible?
- No. No.
- Julian, we gotta end this,
for everybody's sake.
[sighs]
I'll see you downstairs.
- Oh...
Okay, well, you guys
can count me out, all right?
'Cause I didn't bring
an endless supply of boxers
to this planet.
- Julian, please.
I should have told you.
- I can't believe that you
would keep part of that Stone.
Do you not remember what
Savitar had me do with that?
- Yes, I do.
- But you're not concerned,
are you?
You just want your own personal
meta-human specialist
to try and find you a cure.
- Julian, I don't want
these powers.
I can't spend the rest
of my life wondering
if or when I'm gonna
lose this battle
and become Killer Frost.
I thought you more than anyone
would understand that.
- You know...
you know what I understand?
I understand the real reason
that you invited me
on this team.
- That's not the only reason.
- Yeah, I wish
I could believe that.
♪ ♪
[banging on door]
- Dad.
- I heard what happened.
Thought you might need
a pick-me-up.
Worked like a charm
when you were a kid.
- Smaller problems.
- Yeah.
So...
You wanna talk about it?
- I don't know
what I want, Dad.
- Iris...
Whatever you may be feeling
right now about Barry,
that man does love you.
That...that kind of love
is rare.
- Dad, I wish
it were that simple.
- [chuckles] Simple.
Look, only you know
what's good for you.
But with the kind of lives
that you two have,
that love between
the two of you,
that is the one thing
that should stay simple.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[sighs] Baby girl.
Caitlin:We'll be here
if you need anything.
- Okay.
[electronic beeps]
[breathing heavily]
[distorted]
Back to worship me once again?
- We just wanted to let you know
that we're gonna defeat you.
- Unlikely.
- You told us
that you're trapped,
imprisoned for all eternity.
You're never getting out
of wherever my future self
locked you up.
You'll never know
freedom again.
- All will be
revealed soon, Flash.
You will face my wrath.
You will beg for mercy,
and you will get none.
[electricity whirs]
- Did it work?
- Yeah. We got a hit.
It's just that that hit
is all of Central City.
- That's not a hit.
The whole city?
- Yeah.
- God. Well...
Can we get
a little more specific?
Pinpoint a location at least...
uh, something?
- I think maybe we can get
a little bit more precise,
but I'm gonna have to give it
the old meta-human try.
- Okay.
It's Iris. All right.
I'll be right back, but...
Just let me know
if you get anything, all right?
- Okay.
- Hey.
You going somewhere?
- Yeah, I just wanna get back
to S.T.A.R. Labs and train.
- Seeing as how you exploded
on Barry in front of everyone,
might want to wait on it.
- Well, the truth
had to come out, so...
- Yeah, it did.
Just maybe not that way.
I mean, we all
have to help each other,
not point fingers.
- You're right.
I...
I'll make it up to them.
It's just,
this whole thing
is messing with my head.
- Don't let it.
- You don't get it, Jesse.
When you got your powers,
you were walking
down the street.
Me? I touched
the Philosopher's Stone,
I got trapped
in some cocoon, and...
[sighs] I just feel,
because of all of that, I...
There's something
wrong with me.
I feel like Savitar has
some kind of...hold on me.
- Look, I know.
Okay?
But you're strong, Wally.
You can fight this.
- You know, all I ever wanted
was to have powers.
To do some good.
But now, now I'm...
I'm the one responsible
for saving Iris' life.
I don't know if I'm gonna be
fast enough to save her, so...
- Okay, Wally.
You're not alone.
- Okay.
- She's right, Wally.
♪ ♪
You're not alone.
[dramatic music]
- Mom.
- You're never alone, Wally.
I've missed you so much.
- I missed you too.
- Wally?
- [sobbing]
- I'm so proud of you.
Of what you're trying
to become.
- That's all I want.
I just want you
to be proud of me.
- Wally, you're really
freaking me out.
- I am, son.
I'm so very, very proud.
But you have to stop.
- What? Why?
- You're working so hard.
You don't see
how dangerous it is.
Son, you're not fast enough.
You never will be.
♪ ♪
- But I can't...I can't stop.
I have to save Iris.
I have to.
- Wally.
- You're in my head again.
- You were always so smart.
[distorted]
Weren't you, Wallace?
But not smart enough.
I have what I need
to escape my hell, Wallace.
- No, not everything.
We still have
a piece of that Stone.
- Not for long.
And once I have it,
you and everyone you love
will perish.
- Wally?
- I have to go.
I can't let him get out.
- What are you talking about?
- Savitar.
- Look, you need
to tell Barry, okay?
- No.
I can do this by myself.
Jesse, please,
just wait here.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[doors opens, shuts]
- Hey.
- I got your message.
- Yeah.
Come, sit down.
- Iris, uh...
I know you're mad, but...
- No, Barry, that's not it.
I just want you
to listen. Okay?
I need you to let me say
what I need to say.
- Okay.
- I'm not angry...
at you.
I understand that you...
You want to keep me safe,
and us getting engaged
could change the future.
I...I get all of that.
Barry, when you
proposed to me...
I said yes because...
I love you
more than anything.
And I want to be your wife.
But I thought that you were
asking me purely out of love,
not fear.
And, Barry, whether
you realize it or not,
now there's always gonna be
a part of us that's tainted.
- Iris, I'm trying
to save your life.
- I know,
and that's the problem.
I want to be your wife, Barry.
I don't want to be...
someone that
you're trying to save
for the rest of eternity.
- Eternity.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I can't see anything.
- Give me those.
Are those things even working?
Yep.
- [stammers] Stop it!
- I just wanna see
if they're working.
- What are you doing?
- What do you see?
- I'm seeing these white...
flashes, it's like...
- Flashes?
- Yeah, it's like Savitar
speeding through, like, a storm.
- No, it's not a storm.
It's the Speed Force.
[dramatic music]
- He's in the Speed Force.
That's why only speedsters
were able to see him.
- Why is Savitar
hiding in the Speed Force?
- He's not hiding.
- Mm.
That's where the future you
trapped him.
- That's right.
- And that's why
Savitar only appears
for a few moments at a time,
because the Speed Force
just sucks him back in.
That makes sense.
- But we threw
the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force.
- And we gave him the very thing
he needed to escape.
- Except, he said
he still needed one thing.
I don't think he can come out
because he doesn't have
the whole Stone.
- [sighs]
- Guys...
Wally went after Savitar.
both: What?
- He started hallucinating.
He thought he was talking
to his mom.
- No, that's...that's not her.
That's Savitar.
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know.
Okay. He was freaking out.
He said that
he needed to stop Savitar
from getting out,
and he sped off.
- The Stone.
- It's gone?
- It's gone.
- Barry, we gotta find Wally.
- Yeah. If Savitar
gets ahold of the Stone, then...
- He'll escape for sure.
- I can't find him. He turned
off the suit's telemetry.
♪ ♪
- Oh, come on!
- Poor Wallace.
Can't even open a portal.
You can't get rid
of that Stone, Wallace.
Like you can't get rid of me.
- Oh, shut up, shut up.
- You know it's true.
You're not fast enough to
throw it into the Speed Force
by yourself.
- Shut up!
- I'm going to get out
of here, Wallace.
And then I'm gonna
come for you...
and Barry and your sister,
and I'll kill
everyone you love.
- No, you're not real!
You're just in my head,
just...
- Oh, I'm real,
and I know
the limits of your speed.
After all, I'm the one
who gave it to you.
- And that...
giving me speed...
that was your biggest mistake.
[beeping]
- There's a massive power surge.
- Where?
- The old Kob Factory.
♪ ♪
Pulling up security footage.
- Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- Wally.
- No!
[gasping]
Aah!
No!
No! Help me, Barry!
Aah!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[portal zapping
and whooshing]
♪ ♪
- [growls]
I am free!
- Ground. Air...
I can feel again.
I can breathe again.
I've beaten you, finally.
- Where's Wally?
What just happened to him?
- Like the Greek myth
of Atlas,
who could not put down the sky
until someone took his place,
Wally has taken my place
in the Speed Force.
You know me.
I love a good myth.
- He took your place.
What...
- When you created Flashpoint,
you unwittingly provided me
with the means for my return.
- Wally...
- You gave me the idea
to turn Wally into Kid Flash,
to make him fast enough
to replace me
in your prison.
His youth and ego
were my allies.
So taken with his fame
and speed,
he never saw he was running
right into my trap.
- How do I get him out?
- Wally's gone.
- Suffering in an endless void
for all eternity.
Another victim Barry Allen
failed to save.
- No!
♪ ♪
I'm gonna kill you!
- If you had the strength
to end my life,
you would have done it
in the future.
But Barry Allen doesn't kill.
He's the good guy.
The boy Joe raised.
The man Iris loves.
You have everything.
And deserve none of it.
I'm going to destroy this city
like I did in the future,
so you can see the truth,
Barry.
And then, you'll treat me
like a god.
- You're not a god!
[exciting music]
[winces and coughs]
Who are you?
- I am the future, Flash.
♪ ♪
- Show your face.
[groans]
- I want so badly
to kill you,
and I will.
But you have to live
a little while longer.
Long enough to see Iris die.
- [roars]
- [winces]
- The blade didn't hit
your organs,
but it did shatter
your clavicle.
- Hang in there, man,
hang in there.
- We have to take it out.
- Do it!
- Any medicine I give you
your metabolism
will burn through.
- All right.
Just do it, okay?
Just do it.
- Hold him down.
Okay.
- Gonna be okay, mate.
You're gonna be okay.
- Bite down on this.
- I'm so sorry.
Three, two, one.
- [screaming]
How long was I out?
- Not long.
Are you in much pain?
- I might be able
to do something with this.
[dramatic music]
- Joe.
[whispering] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Not your fault.
Where is he?
I mean, is he in pain?
Is he...
- One will suffer a fate
worse than death.
- [sobbing]
- Jesse, I...
I'm not like your dad.
I don't really...
know what
the right words are...
[melancholic music]
♪ ♪
- What are we gonna do?
We have to bring him back.
We have to save him...
I can't lose Wally, Barry.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm gonna work on this.
- Yeah.
I'll see you soon.
- I'm sorry.
I should have never...
I was afraid.
- I know.
Believe me, I know.
Fear makes us do a lot of things
that we shouldn't.
My fear's the reason
for all of this.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.