Of course I'm really here. Barr.
You're sounding kinda strange.
Are you okay?
[whooshing]
I am now. Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
You wanna tell me
what's really going on?'
You don't remember either.
Thawne.
He...
He changed things.
Made me think I was crazy.
He took away my life.
Piece by piece, until I lost everything.
Thawne started his own
Reverse-Flashpoint.
Joe, you died.
Uh...
Well,
I'm so sorry...
you went through that.
Hey. Listen to me.
I'm here now
and I'm not going anywhere.
I know it's...
Seeing you again,
after everything that's happened.
[chuckles]
It's just like
I can finally breathe again.
[Damien] Nothing like
a second shot at life.
Barry, why is there a super villain
standing in my living room?
Thank you.
But I'm not here to cause trouble.
Damien, how are you still here?
[Damien] I don't know. My theory,
I was connected
to the Time Stone you were wearing.
When you created a portal,
it drew me to 2021 also.
Although I haven't faded yet.
I'm sure, I soon will.
- Once you do?
- I die.
But my daughter Nora lives.
Only that hasn't happened yet
and I don't know why.
Maybe if I had the Time Stone.
That was handy.
- Damien, what you're doing now...
- I'm no hero, Barry.
I'm just a dad.
Freeze!
You are under arrest!
For what, officers?
I haven't even done anything.
Yet.
Do you want to know why?
Because I'm not ready to die yet!
I can't believe everything
that you went through.
I mean, these last few days
have been so...
normal.
Boring even.
I mean, I'm glad nobody remembers.
And Frost and Chillblaine were married?
- Apparently.
- That's insane.
What about Chuck and me?
What were we doing?
I mean same as now, I guess.
I don't know.
I mean, we weren't really teammates
in that other timeline.
I do know Chester helped build
the energy absorption tech
that saved the world. Hold on.
[whooshing]
Here you go.
Holy Ron Mallets!
Circuitry is next level.
Okay, nice work, future me.
But is it okay that I have this?
I don't want to start like,
a Chester-P-point.
I mean, maybe just don't
talk about it on your podcast.
Got you.
Well, Barr, you risked everything
to prevent Armageddon
and gave all of us a second chance.
And we're really damn grateful.
Especially me.
Ditto.
You really are a true hero, Barry.
[phone chimes]
It's Taylor with a news alert.
Thawne is at C.C.P.D.
Ah-ah.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, why did I do that?
Well, I did it to draw out your hero.
What is taking him... so long?
[Mia] You want a hero?
You?
You know, normally...
I'd be intrigued
to meet the great Green Arrow,
but unfortunately, today...
I don't have the time.
Where's William?
- Who is William?
- Wrong answer.
Oopsie.
That's a temporal fade, pal.
Looks like you're not too much longer
for this timeline.
Too bad.
Now.
Where the hell's my brother?
Enough with the questions.
Sorry, kid.
I don't have time for family drama.
Stay down, Thawne.
Flash.
I didn't come here to fight.
I came here to make a scene publicly!
So that there would be witnesses
for what I have to ask you.
What is it?
I need you to save me.
So Thawne messed with the timeline?
No wonder
I picked up on his temporal energy.
He must be loaded with it.
Is that why you're here in 2021?
No. I tracked Thawne's scent by mistake.
I was looking for something else.
Maybe we can help?
I'm Chester P, by the way.
New guy. [chuckles]
And it is so cool to meet
the future Green Arrow.
Mia Queen!
Progeny of Felicity Smoak
and Oliver Queen.
I know all the stories.
Not all the stories.
Look, what did Thawne mean
when he said, "Save me"?
Save him from what?
You see how he's... fading in and out.
Same thing happened to me
in his Reverse-Flashpoint.
He's being erased.
Once the process is complete, he'll die.
So when you removed Thawne's changes,
the timeline decided to remove him, too.
Yeah.
Okay, but when Thawne died,
he came back somehow after Eddie.
I mean, could that happen again?
No, this is different.
When I reset the timeline,
I used Damien's Time Stone.
It eliminated
all possible time variables,
restoring a single,
permanent timeline again.
- This one.
- So if he dies this time...
It's game over for good.
Okay. I need to call Frost.
If we're going to decide
what to do about Thawne,
we need the whole team here.
Wait a minute. You're not actually
considering saving him, are you?
Mia, we know that Thawne is bad,
but we still need to talk this through
before we make any decisions.
Fine.
If that's how you guys do things.
But you're making a big mistake.
I will go talk to her.
You see if you can find out
how much time Thawne has left.
You want something?
Mia.
You never said why you came to 2021.
But I'm guessing it's important.
So...
what is going on?
I'm here to find my brother.
William's missing.
I just hit another dead end.
What happened?
[sighs]
It was the night
I decided to put on the suit.
William and I went to see Dad's statue.
But...
we were attacked.
I haven't seen my brother since.
I've been looking for him for two years.
I'm so sorry.
Found a temporal energy signature
at the crime scene which led me here
but, every trail goes cold.
Now this is all I have left of him.
William gave it to me the night
he was taken.
Sometimes I wonder if it's connected
to why he's still gone.
Have you asked Felicity for help?
She wouldn't understand
what I've had to do to get this far.
What is that supposed to mean?
Mia, have you...
Killed anyone?
I will if I have to.
For William's sake.
Sometimes blood for blood
is the answer.
You know, your dad thought
the same thing once.
That in order to protect his city,
he had to take lives.
But all he ended up doing
was ruining his own.
I think you know that.
Or else you wouldn't be
so afraid to go see your mom.
You're the one who's afraid.
Thawne killed your dad,
and then tricked you
into almost marrying him.
All the while making you believe
you had a choice in it all.
You.
Iris West-Frakkin' Allen.
And now you're too afraid
to give him what he deserves.
You think my life will be ruined
if I kill?
What about yours if you don't?
Because it sounds like you'd be
a lot better off if he was gone.
How much longer do I have?
Best I can tell...
Two hours.
And then you'll fade away.
Two hours until you save me. Right?
Caitlin, because you...
Barry and Team Flash,
you are the good guys.
You'll do the right thing.
Some of us might surprise you.
But not you, you're a doctor.
You won't kill me.
No, I won't.
But I can accept it when someone dies.
Is that right?
Maybe you forget?
I know the real Caitlin Snow.
You're right where you were,
eight years ago. Remember?
Living your safe...
orderly life.
Preparing for a perfect future.
With your idiot fiancé.
And then...
[exclaims]
It all came crashing down.
What is wrong with you?
Ronnie was my whole future
and he is never coming back.
He's never coming back.
That's what happens. What about you?
You could have moved on.
I mean, you should have moved on.
But instead, you're stuck here
where you were eight years ago
helping Team Flash and Barry Allen
instead of getting on with your life.
Fine.
You want honesty?
When I was a resident,
fresh out of med school,
one of the first things
they taught me...
is that sometimes you lose a patient.
That death is a part of life.
So guess what?
It's your turn.
Because all the speed in the world
can't help you out run
what's coming for you.
You'll save me, you'll save me, Snow.
You don't have a choice.
And another thing.
I stayed here because Barry
and the rest of the team,
they're not just friends,
they're family.
And just so we're clear...
What I've been doing
for the last eight years...
is hating you.
So if you're looking for someone
to save you,
look somewhere else.
You okay?
What happened?
We need to let Thawne die.
Caitlin told me about your talk.
Something I want to know.
Why did you create a Reverse-Flashpoint
to steal my life?
Why?
That was the best way to hurt you.
Don't you have anything better to do
than trying to destroy my life?
Destroying you is my life.
[groans]
That still doesn't explain why.
Why what?
What did I ever do to you?
Almost two centuries...
from right now,
we meet
for the very first time.
For my part,
I finally discovered ways
to possess speeds,
speeds faster than anyone alive.
And, just as I was about
to present myself to the world...
you showed up.
In pursuit of some stupid case
and dazzled the crowd.
You were dazzling. And then...
and then you saved the crowd.
A crowd that I was meant to save,
a crowd that was meant to thank me,
you stole... my greatest moment.
I admired you.
And you humiliated me.
And it was in that moment,
I knew I had to get faster than you.
Only a sociopath...
would react to something so small
with that kind of rage.
What you call rage...
I call commitment.
So if you won't stop hating me,
what happens once I save you?
I'll just go on with my life's work.
Finding new ways to kill you.
[Human Despero] You know
what to do, Flash.
What are you doing here?
I went to the future to see
for myself.
Whether or not Armageddon
had been prevented.
Then you know that it was.
Yes, but I also witnessed
the return of your rival.
You must know
as long as Eobard Thawne lives,
he can still bring about
another Armageddon.
So what do you want me to do?
Listen to your friend.
Let him die.
If you want him dead so much,
why don't you just kill him yourself?
I would, but he could come back,
as he did before.
This is the only way
to assure his absolute death.
You know it's the right thing to do,
Flash.
[Chester] You can't be serious.
You can't just let Thawne die.
I gave him a chance
to prove he can change.
He can't.
So, what? We just kill him?
Thawne messed with the timeline
and now the timeline is fighting back.
I say we let it.
Me, too.
Look, Thawne did this to himself.
And it's not like we can save him so...
it's time to let him go.
Look, I know that we're the new kids
and we don't have the same history
with Thawne. But that's a good thing
because I don't care who Thawne is,
I care who you guys are.
And you save people.
I know because you saved me.
And me. Literally.
You're right. You are the new kids.
And so when it comes to Thawne,
I'm sorry, but you don't get a say.
Iris.
Maybe we should think about this.
We already have.
You guys don't understand
what Thawne is capable of.
It's time to keep everyone safe
by finally letting Thawne die.
Barry. Iris.
We need to talk.
Now.
Yeah.
What the hell is wrong with you two?
Since when do we let people die?
Dad, you know who Thawne is.
Yeah, I do.
And that man came to you for help
which means you're obligated to try
and save him.
Joe, he killed you.
No. I know you don't remember, but I do.
If we don't let this happen now,
our family will never be safe.
You don't think I want
to see him dead either?
Because I do.
If I learned one thing, being a cop
is that you can't just protect
the people you think are good.
You have to protect everyone.
That's what heroes do.
- I know that.
- Do you?
A hero is not just in the name,
Barry, or in a red suit.
It's a choice that we make to decide
who and what we become.
You know that.
Dad, we don't have a choice.
Thawne isn't giving us one.
You always have a choice!
[sighs]
Now have either one of you
even tried, to think
of a way to save him?
You already found one.
Yeah.
We could save him
if we take his speed away.
Permanently.
Just like Jefferson Pierce did to you.
[thudding]
- Listen, Joe, wait.
- Hey.
Uh-uh.
This decision is for the two of you.
But I can tell you one thing.
If you let Thawne die,
you don't have to worry
about him destroying our family.
We have to talk to Caitlin.
Yeah.
[Alien Despero] The heroes
of this world have failed.
But if they won't end
Thawne's existence,
then I, Despero,
will take matters into my own hands.
Mia Queen.
Mia Queen...
And you're gonna help me.
Barry, are you sure?
Yeah. Look, if we're really heroes,
we can't turn our back on anyone,
including Thawne.
So you want to take away his speed
to save his life?
All right. What if it doesn't work?
It will. Before the timeline reset,
Jefferson hit me
with enough continuous voltage
to nearly sever my connection
to the Speed Force.
Like blowing a fuse.
And you want to do
the same thing to Thawne.
And once his speed is gone,
A.R.G.U.S. will take him into custody.
We've already called Cisco.
Jail time won't make up
for all the lives he destroyed.
Look, you're right. But we can't
let Thawne change who we are.
[whooshing]
You're a fool.
Thawne must be erased from time itself.
Why can't you see that?
Despero, without his speed,
Thawne won't be a threat
to anyone ever again.
Thawne recovered his powers before.
This is your final warning, Flash.
Stand down and let Thawne die
or suffer the consequences.
No.
Barry!
[Alien Despero]
It's not too late, Flash!
Let Thawne die, so Armageddon can end.
Light up, Allegra,
we're going after Flash.
[Iris West]
No, Barry can handle Despero.
You two protect Thawne.
No matter what.
- You sure, boss?
- [Iris West] Yeah.
If Despero attacks us, too,
we need to be ready.
[sighs]
What if Despero kills Barry?
I mean, they've fought before
and it wasn't exactly close.
Let's hope it goes better this time.
[screeching loudly]
[both groan]
[Alien Despero] I was right about you
all along, Flash.
You are humanity's enemy.
I'm choosing to save a life, Despero,
not end one.
That's what heroes do.
But you've never been a hero, have you?
[Alien Despero] What are you implying?
What you told me about your home-world.
That was all a lie, wasn't it?
You weren't the heroic rebel leader.
You were the despot.
The one who inflicted
pain and suffering,
who killed to get what he wanted.
[Alien Despero]
I did what was necessary.
No, you're wrong.
You've been wrong this whole time
about everything.
You're no hero, Despero.
You're just like Thawne.
[Alien Despero]
Only in your eyes, Flash.
Because I know what must be done.
The greater good that must be embraced
in order for this world to survive.
All that remains is for me to show you.
Chester, secure S.T.A.R. Labs.
Frak, we just lost power.
What about Thawne?
That's what's so weird.
Backup system just kicked in,
but only for the force field trap.
What? No, no,
that doesn't make any sense unless...
It's Despero.
We're under attack.
[groans]
Mia! What the hell, girl?
[Alien Despero] Iris West-Allen.
You and Flash made this decision.
And now you'll die for making
the wrong one.
Mia, listen to me.
This isn't you.
Mia.
Mia, she's right.
Take my power.
Take my strength. Fight him.
Empath!
You think I'd release
this perfect vessel?
Mia, stop.
I know you can fight this.
The child is gone, human.
[Iris West] No, she's not.
Mia, I know you can fight this
because you already have.
Look around.
You could have killed us but you didn't.
Mia, she's right.
Fight him.
Impossible!
Mia, think about William.
Is this the path
that he would want you to choose?
[high-pitched noise ringing]
[groaning]
Iris.
Allegra and Frost, in the hallway.
I'll go check on them.
I'm so sorry.
My pawn failed.
Your friend survived.
Mia?
What did you do?
Nothing compared
to what I'm going to do now.
I told you Thawne must die and he will.
That's why I'm taking matters
into my own hands.
I'm going to be the hero
that this world needs, Flash.
Not you!
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
What's going on?
I've got the secondary power circuits
up and running,
but I'm picking up insane
energy readings out there.
I'm talking like
atomic bomb level readings.
It's Despero.
He must be willing to wipe out
the whole city to get what he wants.
He's going to kill us all.
Just so Thawne will die.
How's Mia?
She's resting.
Frost is keeping an eye on her.
Thank goodness Iris got through
to her before she...
Right. But what in the world
are we supposed to do now?
We beat Despero to the punch.
We whammy Thawne's speed right now,
make him a permanent jaywalker
before Despero whammies us.
It's okay, Cecile.
We all decided it together.
Chester, where are we with...
Project Whammy? I still have to finish
calibrating your suit.
Well, how much time do we have
before the timeline resets?
A few minutes, maybe less.
And only if Despero
doesn't wipe us out first.
Look, we're not losing today.
Not our city. Not a single life.
I don't know how,
but there's got to be a way
to stop Despero long enough
for Chuck to do his thing.
So come on, we're team Flash.
What can we do?
The energy Despero's harnessing
is from his home world, Kalanor.
But, I mean, even if
the energy is alien,
the Flame of Py'tar is still a flame.
You can harness it with a vacuum.
And then disperse it.
But I'd still need a way to direct
all that energy into the atmosphere.
Wait. If a delivery system
is what you need,
then I got the ticket.
Okay, so you know how
the P.E.D. redirects energy?
Turns out the materials in that puppy
are damn versatile.
So I took the liberty of using them
to make these.
[gasps] No way. Chuck, you're amazing.
Yeah, I can work with these.
They're a perfect fit, Chester.
[Chester] Thanks. Now run, boss. Run.
Now, Flash, your city dies
so that this planet's future
may survive.
[screams] No!
It's gone,
my connection to the flame.
Damn you, Flash.
It's over, Despero.
Flash, you've no idea what you've done.
I swear by the moons of Kalanor,
you'll pay for this.
This whole planet will.
[screams]
[Chester] Flash, we've got
less than 30 seconds to save Thawne
before the timeline resets.
All right. Get ready, Chester,
I'm on my way.
My speed.
I need more time.
We're out of time, Thawne.
Calibration complete.
Go for it.
On my mark, lower the shield.
Now.
[screams]
There is no trace of the Negative
Speed Force left in your body.
Barry, you did it.
[pants]
What exactly do you think you've done?
We just saved your life, Thawne.
Don't make us regret it.
You think you saved my life?
You took my speed.
My speed is my life.
You took my life!
And left me in hell.
Now this is epic. Epic.
Wow!
I don't know what's more impressive,
this place or us.
Us. Definitely.
I haven't been to a place this swank
since my debutante days.
Well, we've got the place
to ourselves tonight.
And since Thawne's at A.R.G.U.S.
and Despero is finally gone...
For good, it seems like.
I figured we deserved a night off.
Look, about me going evil
and trying to kill you all, I...
Already forgiven.
We're just glad to have
the real Mia back.
And that, beautiful people,
is it for shop talk.
Yes, absolutely.
I think we've had enough of aliens
and evil speedsters.
Does that go for evil magicians,
too?
I know what you did
to Laurel Lance, Damien Darhk.
How about I return the favor?
By all means, go for it.
I thought I'd be
a dead man by now, anyway.
I need a drink.
A real one.
Damien. I'm sorry.
Me, too.
And now the timeline's reset,
I should be gone.
Damien, I don't know what to say.
You just did.
That aroma seems familiar.
Sebastian James?
My favorite Scotch.
Did you guys always party this hard
after a successful mission?
[all laughing]
[chuckles]
I wish.
By the way, I...
I came across something
that might help you find William.
The symbol on the Hozen?
It matches a symbol from some
heavily redacted documents from Berlin.
Only my source couldn't find out more,
thanks to some very intense firewalls.
You know, I think I know a hacker
who might be able to help me.
You're going to see Felicity?
You were right, Iris.
I can be the person
she always wanted me to be.
Thank you for helping me
find myself again.
You made the choice to be a hero.
Your dad would be proud.
And hey, you know, don't be a stranger
while you're here in our time.
Bart and Nora, they drop in on us a lot.
And I think you guys
would get along really well.
Anyways, cheers.
Cheers.
I know that look.
Someone's got a crush.
No. No, me and Allegra are just...
we're just friends.
- Sure? Sure.
- Yeah. Yeah.
But you could be a lot more if you
decided to stop sipping root beer,
and go put a move on her.
I'm a lot more intuitive
than people give me credit for.
Come on, go for it.
- Okay.
- You look great.
Move. Moves, moves.
Put the moves, moves, moves.
- Hey, Allegra.
- Hi.
You look... wow...
[chuckles]
Thanks, Chuck.
Not bad yourself.
Thank you.
Hey, I don't know what's up
with you two...
- What? We're just standing here.
- What are you...
Like normal people.
- Normal.
- Both of us, man.
I just mean how you called me out
about Thawne earlier.
Oh! That.
I don't know what got into me.
No, I mean, you guys were right.
That's what I needed to hear.
So I just wanted to say thanks.
- Cool. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Thanks. I mean, you're welcome.
- [Chester] Yeah.
[clears throat]
Have a good night.
- Anyway, cheers.
- Cheers.
Damien Darhk?
You're here to arrest me?
I'm not a cop anymore.
I came to say thank you.
You helping Barry restore the timeline,
that's pretty damn selfless.
Well, what can I say?
Being a parent kinda...
changes you.
Mm-hmm.
For the better.
Agreed.
Yeah, I wish I knew why
I was still here.
I should be gone by now, Joe.
Nora should be in my place.
Well, maybe,
you've still got a little work to do.
Are you trying to cast a spell?
More like a prayer.
Maybe this is my unfinished business.
What is it?
It's a gift.
Father to father.
I think you're
going to need that someday.
What...
West?
Huh...
[Nora Darhk] Dad?
Nora.
It's really you.
Where are we?
It doesn't matter.
I'm just glad I got to see you
before I go.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
You're leaving?
I thought you were...
Dead?
I will be.
I guess I just needed
a little more time.
Wait.
Dad, please.
I don't know what's happening,
but you can't leave now.
I just got you back.
I love you, Nora-doll.
When was the last time
we had a night out again?
I don't know. It's been too long.
Is that Nora Darhk?
Barry Allen?
Iris?
What am I doing here?
What just happened?
Where is my dad?
Barry.
Please, someone tell me
what is going on?
[Joe] You're okay.
Thanks to your dad.
He's gone, isn't he?
Why is this happening again?
Because Damien Darhk promised
that he would do whatever it takes
to save his daughter.
And he did.
Come on.
There's a story I need you to hear.
[glass clinking]
Sorry, I've never done that.
So, a lot has happened
these past few days.
The world almost didn't make it,
but it did.
Thanks to all of you
and a dedicated father.
We all survived because
when faced with the very worst,
it's our choices that define us.
And the choices that we made
are why we're all heroes.
So, to making our own destiny,
and protecting it,
together.
Together.
- [all] Cheers!
- Cheers to that.
Thank God.
Now everything can go back to normal.