("A Lo Caliche"
by Sr Ortegón playing)
Hey, baby.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
Where have you been?
It's been days.
Yeah. I've been
handling business.
It's okay now, it's okay.
You said I had to hide, you said
we were in trouble and...
You know, I think, I think
I got it worked out.
I think I have
some-some good news.
Good news?
Stillwell. She's open
to us going public.
Don't you lie to me.
Hand on a Bible.
Yeah. But, listen,
for us to go public,
you have to come clean with me.
Like, I have to know
who you told about Compound V.
Hey, come on.
This is, this is you and me.
I mean, we're Bonnie and Clyde.
Ride or die, right?
I...
Oh, shit.
I told these guys,
you were running the V
down near the Noodle Palace.
I'm so sorry, baby.
I had to. I...
Why?
What do they have on you?
I don't know their names,
but there was this British guy,
dark hair, real smug asshole.
Buzz cut French guy,
big black guy with a goatee,
and a skinny white kid.
I think they were all
working together. Mm-hmm.
- I'm so sorry, baby.
- Nah.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- I fucked up so bad.
- It's all right.
You know what I was
thinking about
on my run over here?
Our first date.
Most first dates
order, like, a scallop
and a bottle of water.
But you...
(chuckles)
...got a dark beer,
a New York strip,
- and chocolate chip cheesecake.
- (laughs)
I remember thinking,
"Here's someone
who isn't afraid to be happy."
And I fell for you,
right then and there.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Why?
(gasping)
Well?
Heroin overdose.
(Homelander sighs)
I'm sorry to hear that.
And the V?
- She told some guys about it.
- No, no.
I mean you.
(scoffs) Come on, A-Train.
You've been shooting it up
for weeks.
You really think
I wouldn't notice?
I'm done, man.
Nah, I'm fucking,
I'm fucking done.
- Cold turkey.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Good.
Yeah.
You know,
you really screwed up, kiddo.
But you did the right thing
coming to me,
and I'm proud of you.
Thanks, Homelander,
for giving me the chance.
I appreciate it.
Hey. Come on.
I love you.
We're family.
I'll always be
watching over you.
Always.
Attaboy.
Oh, and the misplaced
Asian girl?
I'll find her.
(quietly):
Fuck.
♪ ♪
(humming)
Le poulet.
Massage the bird
with olive oil,
then a sprinkle
of salt and pepper,
then I bake. (sniffs)
Basting every 20 minutes
to keep it from drying out
is very important.
Till it's crisp,
but not too crunchy.
And voilà.
I think you understand me.
It's in your eyes.
Can you speak?
Tell me what you know,
mon coeur.
So we can find these fuckers
who did this to you,
so I can get you back home.
♪ Hear them now ♪
♪ Stamping feet and hearts ♪
♪ Are proud ♪
♪ Building like ♪
♪ A thundercloud ♪
♪ Till heaven
is within our touch ♪
♪ So take it now ♪
♪ And raise it up ♪
♪ You've won
and it's the sweetest ♪
♪ Cup ♪
♪ All that you've
been fighting for... ♪
(cheering)
I like this outfit.
You know, the other one had...
- Oh, my God.
- (laughs)
The other one had kind of
like a, you know,
a Nikki Minaj thing going on.
Oh, yeah, the other one sucks.
They're only letting me
wear this one
because, apparently,
it's family friendly.
- Hmm.
You know,
I'm surprised you came.
I seem to remember
you inviting me?
No, I mean,
I'm-I'm glad you came.
You just... I don't know,
you don't really strike me
as the religious type.
Well, yeah, lapsed, but I served
my time in Sunday school.
- Hmm.
- MAN: Hey, Starlight.
Hi.
Okay, so, do you know
everybody here,
or just, like, 99.9%?
No. My mom and I, um,
we would drive coast to coast
in her brown Honda Civic,
just doing the whole
Christian Circuit thing.
You know, Power Fest,
Capes for Christ,
Believe Expo.
(chuckles)
(sighs) We wore
the tires off of that car.
These people are like
family to me.
After everything
that's happened,
it's actually...
it's really nice
to see them again.
- Sweetheart.
- (gasps) Mom! Hi.
Mm.
- How was your flight?
- Oh, it was a nightmare.
I think we sat on the runway
for 45 minutes,
and then there was all the,
you know, Flight 37 stuff.
But a Xanax and a couple
of Pinot Grigio later,
- here I am.
- (chuckles)
Oh, hello. Uh, do you want
a autograph?
H-Honey, give him an autograph.
Oh, no, no. We...
I mean, I know her.
- I mean, I don't...
- Yeah.
- We know each other. Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Oh. Do you work at Vought?
No. No, no, no.
Mom, this is, this is Hughie.
He's... uh, he's a friend.
- Hi.
- Uh, how nice.
Starlight. You hydrating?
Hey, Donna.
- How was your flight?
- Oh, it-it was perfect in every w...
You have that "Teen Roundtable"
in about 15, are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, she was born ready.
I should know, I was there.
Great. (laughs)
Um, do you want to come?
Uh... You know what?
I'll let you go ahead.
Go, uh, go roundtable
those teens.
- Mm.
- We'll catch up later?
Yeah, sure.
EZEKIEL:
So, Jesus...
Jesus said, "Hey, bro.
"Hey, bro, bring it in.
"You shouldn't need proof.
"You should just
"believe because I say so,
"because you have
- faith."
- (cheering, applause)
"People who have faith,
those are my peeps, y'all."
That's what Jesus said.
But I am gonna ask you
one question...
Two twats at every entrance,
armed to holy hell. In church.
Well, that's America for you,
isn't it?
And God's watching
from up above.
Right there.
Over there.
BUTCHER:
Yeah.
Security's tighter
than a choir boy's asshole.
So let me ask you something:
Why could Jesus walk on water?
Why does Homelander fly?
(cheering, applause)
How about A-Train, why does he
get to run the way he runs?
(crowd gasping)
Or how do I get to hold
the whole world
in my loving embrace?
Why were we chosen?
Because of the Lord.
Because we were born
with his power.
Because we believe!
(cheering)
- We believe.
- $15,000
for an exclusive
VIP experience with Ezekiel.
Seriously?
There's not an easier,
cheaper way
for us to get to him?
We ain't getting to Ezekiel.
You are.
- I am?
- Whoa, whoa, wait. What?
- Well, Starlight's one of the headliners, right?
- Wait.
- She'll get you in.
- Whoa.
Look, we've only been on, like,
a date and a half, okay?
I can't just ask her
for a Diamond Club Pass.
What's the matter? You worried
your fake Supe girlfriend's
gonna think you're using her?
Okay, then what?
I just go up to Ezekiel,
"Hey, man. What's up with you
smuggling blue dope
into Chinatown basements?"
Yeah, pretty much.
Once you show him this.
Jesus.
This is from that club
you took me to?
You remembered our first
night together. I'm touched.
Okay, why is this the first time
I'm hearing about this plan?
This kid needs
to be trained up, Butcher.
Yeah. Yeah, what he said.
I-I don't know how
to blackmail anybody.
Hughie, you've done a murder.
Comparatively speaking,
this will be a piece of cake.
I know. I know.
HOMELANDER:
We're here today
to remember the victims
of Trans-Oceanic Flight 37.
123 brave souls lost
in an instant,
in a senseless act of violence.
Carolyn Kozinsky,
a preschool teacher from Skokie.
Dr. Julien Barro,
an esteemed French neurosurgeon.
♪ ♪
(muffled screaming)
Susan Lopez from Evanston
and her daughter Maya.
♪ ♪
Samuel Brown,
a teacher of physics
from Los Angeles.
(cameras clicking)
We are all truly sorry
for your loss.
Where'd you go?
The only thing I hate more
than blubbering people
- are boring speeches.
- Right.
You remember that nutjob
in Albany last year?
Killed his wife,
and he-he came out of the house
with a gun at his
daughter's head.
Remember that?
Cops pissing their pants,
didn't know what to do.
And then you, you...
you step up, very calmly,
ask for the sergeant's Bic pen
and fling it
26 yards,
right into
the asshole's eyeball.
(clears throat)
- Dead shot, dead shooter.
- What's your point?
My point is that
you took action.
That's what I love
about you, Maeve.
Look, Maeve, nobody wanted
that airplane to go down
the way it did, of course not.
And now...
we got to make the best of it.
Otherwise...
Well, otherwise,
it was all for nothing.
What did I tell you
about boring speeches?
Mom, when did that happen?
What are you talking about?
That's always been there.
PASTOR JOHN: I know what
you're all thinking,
"Holy mackerel, Starlight?
From The Seven? Here with us?"
Well, I knew her
when she was still
in pigtails and braces
and she'd sit right
where you're sitting.
- (laughs)
- So don't be shy.
You ask what's on your mind.
Starlight is here for you.
Yeah?
I have this friend
from my soccer team, Sunji,
she's Hindu.
I know it's kind of
my responsibility, I guess,
to get her to accept Jesus,
but it feels weird to me.
Well, Jesus also says
to love your neighbor.
But if you love your neighbor,
don't you want to save them
from damnation?
You have to look at it
as good news.
You have a chance
to help your friend
find eternal life, right?
Oh, yes.
Have you ever had a boyfriend?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, I was with Drummer Boy
for a while,
for almost a year.
Yeah?
Um... (clears throat)
Did you have...
- sex with him?
- (giggling)
Well, I...
...you know, I think,
I think everyone hopes
that their first is the one.
And... it's private, but...
I'm a virgin.
Yeah, I'm...
saving myself for my
future husband.
See? Hebrews 13:4.
"Let the bed be undefiled,
for God will judge
the sexually immoral."
Okay.
I think we have time
for a few more.
I'm-I'm not really sure what
you're saying, son.
I'm saying if there is some
geezer up there
with a big white beard,
he's a world heavyweight cunt.
- What?
- I-I'm sorry, did you
just call God a C-word?
Yeah. He's got a hard-on
for mass murder
and giving kids cancer,
and his big old answer
to the existential clusterfuck
that is humanity
is to nail his own
bleeding son to a plank.
That is a cunt move.
Come on, even you got to agree
with me there.
- Hey, hey, hey, please...
- We should lob
a fucking nuke at him,
get it over and done with.
- You know what I'm saying?
- We're sorry, sir. We apologize. My man...
All right.
Good talk. Think about it.
- I'm here all day, all right?
- You mind
piping it down
just a little bit? Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to offend
your inner black Baptist mum
shouting "Praise the Lord."
Fuck you, I'm Episcopalian.
And there's nothing wrong
with having a little church
up in you, you know?
Said the bishop to the nun.
What about you, Hughie?
You believe in God?
I mean, I don't know.
- What? Come off it.
- Yeah, I don't know.
I don't think it's Morgan
Freeman up there or anything,
but it can't all be
random chaos.
So you think that
what happened to Robert
was some kind of
divine intervention?
- Is that what you're saying?
- Come on, Butcher.
(phone rings)
Hang about. Hello?
DONNA: So what were
you supposed to say?
"Yes, I've had premarital sex,
go nuts."
Well, I'm pretty sure I wasn't
supposed to lie to them, Mom.
Aw, baby.
You're Starlight of The Seven.
Millions of kids are looking up
to you now.
You're a shining light to them.
How am I supposed
to live up to that?
Because that's the way
God made you.
You're a miracle.
You're my miracle.
Hey... hey, you two.
How's it going?
You know what?
I'll, I'll catch up.
- DONNA: You sure?
- Don't worry, I'll be right there.
DONNA:
Mm-hmm.
Keep an eye on the lad,
all right?
Where the fuck are you going?
Just do it.
STARLIGHT:
Yeah.
- You okay?
- Fine.
It's just... this place isn't
what I remember.
Hey...
Hughie?
Hey, can I ask you something?
Anything.
Is there any way you could
hook me up with one of those
Diamond Club Passes?
You know, to-to see Ezekiel?
I mean, I couldn't get one
unless I robbed a bank.
But... you know.
Ezekiel?
Yeah. Yeah. Um, okay.
Confession time. My dad is,
like, Ezekiel's number one fan.
Hmm.
So what do you think?
Pull a few strings, you know?
Hook me up with some tickets?
Yeah, yeah.
Sure, of course.
- It's the least I can do.
- Thank you.
- (cheering, applause)
- Good to see you!
Thanks, guys. Oh!
How are you, girls?
Hey, pal, how are you?
How are you?
Great, thanks for coming along.
- God bless you guys!
- Thanks!
God bless you one and all!
Take care now.
Keep believing, ha-ha.
Grab Madelyn.
I need to talk to her about
these fucking talking points.
Um... uh...
(chuckles nervously)
Ms. Stillwell isn't here today.
I thought that you knew that.
But I'm here to help you
with anything,
I'll go through the talk...
Ashley?
Where is she?
(whooshing)
What are you doing here?
Skipping work now?
I am taking Teddy
to the pediatrician.
Maybe reschedule it.
I've already rescheduled
three times.
What is the emergency?
My speech.
- Your speech?
- Yes. My speech.
It reads like corporate
fucking mayonnaise.
We're talking Believe here.
These are my people.
But you're not just
talking to them.
Every dove and Democrat
in Congress
is going to be
watching you on CNN.
- You need to appear moderate...
- No.
- Humble.
- No!
You... There is
an opportunity here.
People are scared.
They don't trust Washington
or the coastal elite,
and they hate foreigners.
What they want is a little
John Wayne frontier justice.
And that is what I do.
Don't forget... it was me that
saved that Flight 37 thing.
I turned that into a win.
For us.
You're really gonna talk to me
about "saving" Flight 37? Ha-ha.
Well, why wouldn't I?
Look, can I please just
talk to you later?
The speech is perfect.
- Trust me.
- Trust you.
Okay.
That's what you always say.
- Come here.
- You're not even fucking listening to me.
You're so full of shit!
You say you want my input,
but you don't.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
- And you never did.
- I do. Can we please just talk later?
Why? You gonna run off
and play "strong single mom"?
Please...
That baby is an accessory.
We need boundaries.
(car alarm chirps)
(Teddy crying)
(laughing)
(knocking on door)
Hey, Billy.
Rachel.
(Rachel sighs)
Just took a lovely little stroll
around St. John's.
And you'll never guess
what I happened across.
Who told you?
Well, I'll tell you who didn't
fucking tell me.
Me own fucking sister-in-law.
Would you like some tea?
I got the English stuff.
When'd you do it?
Last Sunday.
We used your last name.
We said "beloved wife."
You buried an empty
fucking coffin?
We didn't bury anything.
Just, um, a headstone.
Well, that's a sick fucking joke
then, isn't it?
And you're wondering why we
didn't tell you. (chuckles)
Look...
my mom's getting old.
She just wants a place to talk
to her daughter.
Yeah, well, she's talking
to dirt, isn't she?
- It's something.
- No.
It's fucking nothing.
It's nothing, 'cause there's
nothing fucking down there.
And for all you know, Rebecca's
still out there somewhere,
and you put up
a fucking headstone.
Stop!
You need to stop.
It has been eight years since
she's been missing.
The cops never found anything.
You never found anything.
She's not alive.
She got killed
or she killed herself.
You watch your fucking mouth.
You're not the only one
whose life was ruined.
She is my sister,
and I love her.
But she's gone.
We need this to be over.
(Rachel sighs)
♪ ♪
(panting)
Ah!
Oh, Popclaw.
You got the right
to remain silent, bitch.
I did not kill your partner.
And I did not kill
Dr. Robinson.
I wouldn't lie to you.
I love you, baby.
Love is just another lie,
Donovan.
- You must think I'm stupid.
- No.
POPCLAW:
But as you can see,
I'm pretty sharp.
DONOVAN:
Y-Yeah, you've got talent.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
(both panting)
- (static)
- POPCLAW: Oh! Yeah, say it.
You're a filthy pig
who likes to eat ass.
- I'm a filthy pig...
- (moaning)
BUTCHER:
Hold up. Easy.
Easy does it.
We ain't here to hurt you.
POPCLAW:
Who are you?
This guy's got 34 addresses
and at least a dozen aliases.
So, who the hell is he?
Something we're running down
on our own.
Uh, since when do you guys
run down stuff alone?
- Trevor...
- Yeah?
Shut up.
(indistinct chatter)
- Excuse me.
- Hughie.
Right?
You're Starlight's friend.
She got you in here.
- Yeah.
- (chuckling): There you go.
(chuckling)
Good to meet you, pal.
- Good to meet you.
- (chuckles)
How do you know Starlight?
Uh, you know, we met, um,
like, a few weeks ago, actually.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- And she got you in here?
- Yeah, I guess she did.
Oh, this is a
pricey ticket, Hughie.
You must be a special guy.
I... no. No, I'm not...
I just feel lucky
to be here. Really.
EZEKIEL:
Um, ladies and gentlemen,
uh, I would like to welcome you
one and all.
And I would very much like to
welcome... Homelander,
our special guest.
(applause)
So, without further ado,
if you would follow me.
Gather round, everybody.
Now, as many of you
may already know,
Homelander is an ordained
minister in Samaritan's Embrace.
Together, we will be rebaptizing
you, my most loyal followers.
Do you accept the Lord,
our Father, as your Savior,
- and Jesus Christ his son?
- Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
Then I baptize you
in the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
- Oh!
- Your sins have been purged.
Christ be with you.
On this blessed day,
you will be reborn a Christian.
You will be washed clean
of all your sins.
Something wrong, Hughie?
No. No, I'm-I'm
totally comfortable.
Why-why would you ask that?
Well, your blood pressure's
150/90. It's a bit high.
Yeah, sorry. Just, um...
I'm afraid of water.
(chuckles)
Don't panic.
I got you.
Do you accept the Lord,
our Father, as your Savior,
and Jesus...
as his son?
Yes.
Hmm. Then I baptize you
in the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
(coughing)
God bless.
Thank you all once again
for allowing me to be a part
of this beautiful occasion.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Good night.
See you, friend.
Thank you. Thank you for coming.
May the light of God
shine in your lives.
Excuse me, sir.
Uh, may I speak with you
just for a moment?
- Sorry, son, I got a packed schedule.
- All right, I understand, sir,
but it's just,
I need your guidance.
I need Christ's guidance.
What is it?
Just hold on... one second.
Let me just show you something.
(chuckles)
What's wrong?
Uh...
You fucked me.
What?
Yeah, in a private Supe club.
You know the one on East 29th?
Secret Lair,
- I think it's called?
- Don't know it. Nope.
- There were three of us?
- You've got nothing...
- Oiled up, and you...
- This...
...wrapped your stretchy arms
around me, and it was, it was
so fucking hot, and...
your dick was so... perfect.
And long and... stretchy.
And you... you played
my butt like jazz.
With poise and skill and...
willingness to improvise.
(choking)
You come in here.
You try to talk to me?
- (choking)
- Like this?
You are a filthy, filthy liar.
- You are unclean.
- I have a video.
- What?
I have a video
of the three of us...
sucking and fucking.
And if you don't let me go,
my friend puts the video online.
Like that.
(grunting)
(gasps, coughs)
What do you want?
You want a little bit of money?
Are you here for money?
You ship boxes labeled
as polio vaccine
but they're not really
polio vaccine, are they?
(panting)
They're Compound V.
- Who the hell are you?
- I want to know everything about 'em.
Okay? You tell me, you tell me
where they're going.
And you tell me
how many boxes you ship.
No.
No, they will destroy me.
Who's "they"? Vought?
Here's how this is gonna go.
You're gonna tell me,
or that video...
trends, number one on Twitter.
Tonight.
And you're also gonna stop
the fucking
"pray the gay away" shit.
Anyway, it's your choice.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Hey, um, so that wasn't
a piece of cake.
Hughie, that you?
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah, it's me, sorry.
I had to, had to borrow a phone.
Thanks again.
I got baptized.
Yeah. It's a long story.
Blackmailing somebody
is not cake, okay?
It is weird, it's scary,
you wind up
- just saying shit.
- Okay, but did you
get him to talk?
What'd he say?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, you-you know
that charity of his?
Samaritan's Embrace?
- Right.
- All right.
So what they do is they take
boxes full of that stuff
and they ship it to hospitals
all across the country.
And apparently the latest one
is going to the NICU
at Mercer Hospital.
It's, uh,
i-it's midtown, I think.
You are a natural, kid.
You're like the fucking...
Rain Man of fucking people over.
(chuckles) Not a compliment.
(grunting)
(grunts)
(panting)
- Hey!
- Cool your jets, guv.
- It's not a hate crime.
- (phone ringing)
M.M.? All right.
(laughs) Fucking brilliant.
I'll meet you at the hospital
in half an hour.
HOMELANDER:
Let's hear it for Jesus.
- (cheering)
- Yes!
One more for the guy upstairs!
(Homelander laughs)
Oh, I love you guys.
Let me tell you something.
I am so thrilled to be here.
Truthfully. Are you?
- (cheering)
- Yeah?
A terrible tragedy
befell our nation this week.
Terrible.
And let's not mince words
about this.
We... were... attacked.
(cheering)
America was attacked.
Some people...
...they want me
to come out here
and speak empty platitudes
to you all.
A little bit of corporate talk.
But I don't want to do that.
I can't do that.
You want to know why?
CROWD:
Why?
Because I believe
that what God wants me to do
is get on over there,
find the filthy bastards
that masterminded this...
whatever cave they're in...
and introduce them to a little
thing called God's judgment!
- (cheering)
- That's what I think!
Sounds like
the American thing to do!
the right thing to do.
But no. No, no, no, no, no.
Apparently, I got to wait
for Congress to say it's okay.
(crowd booing)
HOMELANDER:
Right?
I say I answer to a higher law.
- (cheering)
- Wasn't I chosen to save you?
- Is it not my God-given purpose
to protect the United States
of America?
(cheering)
CROWD (chanting):
Homelander! Homelander!
- Homelander! Homelander!
- Psalm!
58:10!
"The righteous shall rejoice
"when he sees the vengeance
"and he will bathe his feet
in the blood of the wicked."
(cheering continues)
MAN:
Homelander!
CROWD (chanting):
Homelander! Homelander!
(chanting continues)
Motherfucker.
(exhales deeply)
(sighs)
(knock on door)
Hey.
Maeve, what, uh...
- Sorry, what are you...?
- I was, um, stopping a mugging
nearby and I...
It's good to see you.
Can I come in?
Uh... okay. (scoffs)
Where's Freckles?
Freckles died two years ago.
Look, uh, I'm kind of busy,
so, um, maybe give me a call,
call first, next time?
Elena, you don't
have to be like this.
Well, you show up out of nowhere
asking about
the goddamn cat, so...
You've been drinking.
- No.
- (Elena scoffs)
You're not going
to meetings anymore.
Uh, listen...
(chuckles, sniffles)
Water under the bridge.
I miss you.
You don't get to say that to me.
Leave, please.
Elena, I haven't seen you
in years.
I mean...
- wouldn't it be nice...
- I see you every day.
Every time I walk through
Times Square
or turn on the fucking TV.
I'm out of your life.
You never left mine.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm really sorry.
- I didn't mean...
- I don't want your apology, okay?
I want you to get out.
Okay? I want you to go back
to your ivory penthouse
where you can drink
and fuck whoever you want.
Go back to Homelander.
(laughs softly)
I can't go back.
Oh... (sniffles)
- Oh...
- Maeve?
It's too hard.
- What happened?
- It's just too hard.
Tell me what happened.
(sniffles)
I keep thinking about all...
- all those people.
- It's okay. You'll figure it out.
Okay? You'll figure it out.
- You always know what to do.
- (sobbing)
You always know
what to do, okay?
- I don't know. They don't...
- So just tell me what happened.
(sniffles)
Tell me what happened.
Uh...
I don't know, Maeve,
if this is...
- Come on.
- No. No, this is...
You're obviously...
No, I said stop it.
(exhales)
All right, just...
- just talk to me.
- (sniffles)
Okay? Just tell me
what happened.
Yeah, this, um...
this was a mistake.
No, just talk to me.
Just tell me what...
If you... (groans)
(phone vibrating)
- Allo?
- CHERIE: They're coming.
They're on to you, babe.
Black Noir was outside
my apartment.
What location?
Which addresses do they have?
If they got to my place,
all of them.
So, you want to pay me
the professional courtesy
and tell me
where the hell
you disappeared to before?
I just had to pop down
to the shop.
I was running a bit low on
mind your own fucking business.
(phone ringing)
This better be good.
I'm burned.
What? Fucking hell,
Frenchie. How?
I don't know.
What about the rest of us?
Your concern for me
is very sweet.
Maybe, maybe not.
So far, they only seem to be
hitting my places.
I'm taking off.
- What about the girl?
- Fucking leave her.
God knows
what they'll do to her.
Supe-on-Supe violence
ain't our concern, mate.
Butcher.
I said fucking leave her.
Merde.
Burnt.
It was the Heartland Beauties
"Luck of the Irish" pageant.
The lights went out on stage
and this one lit up the room
with the glow from her hands.
The show must go on. Hmm?
That's so sweet.
- 15 minutes, Starlight.
- I'm sorry, could you, could you
just give us one minute, please?
MAN (over P.A.):
Starlight will begin shortly.
Please go to the main stage.
Mom, I can't do this.
A-Are you sick?
What's wrong?
No, it just doesn't feel right.
- What does that mean?
- Honestly...
I really thought that being here
would feel like it used to,
but it doesn't.
It's changed,
or maybe I've changed.
But...
Mom, these past few months...
Mm-mm.
No, tell them I'm not going on.
Honey.
I've waited 23 years for this.
This isn't...
this isn't about you.
Isn't it?
I mean, I-I kept your secret,
scrimped by selling houses,
took you to all the Supe events.
Please.
All my friends
are gonna be watching on TV.
Please?
They're coming for me,
mon coeur.
(zipper closes)
The Supes.
I've been ordered to leave you
here for them to find.
And Monsieur Charcuter,
you know,
he knows I'll comply,
that's how he sees me.
Like this mad bastard,
only good for hurting
or killing, you know?
Like a gun, he takes me,
points me in a direction
and fires.
It's not who I am.
(chains rattle)
It's not who you are, either.
We're the same, you and I.
Like eggs.
Hard outside, soft inside...
or pineapples, perhaps.
Whatever those bastards
got planned for you,
you don't deserve it, mon coeur.
(chuckles softly)
NEWSWOMAN:
The Deep finds himself
in hot water following
a harebrained attempt
to free a dolphin
from Oceanland.
Insiders say when police
tried to intercept
the hijacked van,
Deep lost control
of the vehicle and crashed,
catapulting the dolphin
through the front windshield
onto the road,
where it was run over
- by an 18...
- Hello there, Believe Expo!
(crowd cheering)
I am so honored
to be here tonight.
Did you know
that my first public appearance
was right here
on this very stage
with Ezekiel
and the rest of the family?
(cheering)
Today, I wanted
to share with you
how I accepted Christ...
as my personal savior.
(cheering)
How His way is the only way...
(applause, cheering)
Uh... (exhales)
Just...
just please stop the music.
- Please stop.
- (music stops)
(mouthing)
You want me to just suck it up
and do this for you?
Hmm?
You have no idea
what you're really asking.
what I've been through.
(groans softly)
Every single word that I say up
here, I'm reading from a script.
I didn't write
any of these words.
I don't even know
if I believe in them.
I mean, I believe in God,
I love God so much, but...
(chuckles)
Honestly, it's...
it's just how goddamn certain
everyone is around here.
I mean, tickets start at,
what, 170 bucks,
so that these people can tell
you how to get to heaven?
How do they know?
How does anybody know?
When the Bible was written, life
expectancy was 30 years old.
I mean, I'm not so sure you're
supposed to take it literally.
It also says
that it's a sin to eat shrimp.
What, if you're gay
or if you're Gandhi,
you're going to hell? I mean...
And if you have sex
before marriage,
that's, that's not immoral.
That's human.
What's immoral
is the guy who shoved
his dick in my face.
(crowd gasping)
- Shit.
(exhales)
Here's the truth.
Anyone who tells you they know
the answers is lying.
And I know, I know,
I'm supposed to be
this hero-idol-symbol-whatever,
but I don't know
what the hell I'm doing.
I'm just as scared and confused
as the rest of you.
I'm done pretending,
and I'm done
taking any more shit.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Jackpot.
Compound V?
Oh, yeah, and lots of it.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
That's a fucking baby Supe.
Chosen by God, my ass.
These cunts are made
in a fucking lab.
Hey.
Hey, easy.
That-that was a great speech.
I mean, come on... I mean,
know your audience,
but that was, like,
that was Joel at the Garden.
That was...
I am so glad you enjoyed it.
I'm so glad. How was your
quality time with Ezekiel? Huh?
Any more VIP tickets
I can get for you?
Because I'm so here for you.
- It's not like that.
- You sure?
'Cause I can get you
a commemorative cup.
Or I can get you
an Ezekiel figurine,
- or a goodie bag.
- My girlfriend died.
What?
Happened not too long ago,
and I came here
looking for a way
to get out of the shit
that I'm in right now.
And that wasn't fair to you,
and I'm so sorry.
I really don't think
there's anything
that can help it anymore
or fix it...
or make it better.
And everything I heard here?
Well, that helped
a total of jack shit.
(chuckles, sniffles)
Except for what you said.
I mean, you're right,
there's... nobody knows.
And that's the only fucking
thing I've heard all day
that's made any sense at all,
and that is
the God's honest truth.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
MOTHER'S MILK: Okay, easy with that.
You get some air in there,
you could kill the kid.
Well, wouldn't that
be a crying shame?
All right.
Let's bugger off.
Hey!
Hey, keep them busy.
Watch and learn, son.
BUTCHER:
Hey.
(laughs)
Holy fuck.
That was diabolical.
(laughs)
You little fucking beauty.
(panting)
You done good, lad.
- Come on, Butcher, it's time to go.
- Yeah.
Now, you keep
your nose clean, sunshine,
or I'll come back and stomp you.
Holy smokes, Starlight shocking
the Christian community
during her address
at Believe Expo,
when she questioned
her faith in...
I see you.
I know you're watching me.
You've been out there
quite a lot lately.
Always watching.
So why don't you
just come on inside?
You afraid of me?
(scoffs)
(door opens)
Come in.
(door closes)
Have I not been paying
enough attention to you?
Are you lonely?
It must be hard,
feeling so alone.
I'm sorry...
...but you cannot
give a speech like that.
You cannot be bad.
(clears throat softly)
Come here.
You have to be good.
And you have to listen to me.
And then we both
can get what we want.
(exhales)
That's good.
You're my good boy.
(panting)
(breathing deeply)
(grunting)
(panting)
(panting weakly)
(exhales)
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ It's not warm
when she's away ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ And she's always
gone too long ♪
♪ Any time she goes away... ♪
FRENCHIE:
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
(gasps)
♪ Wonder this time
where's she's gone ♪
♪ Wonder if she's gone to stay ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ And this house
just ain't no home ♪
♪ Any time she goes away ♪
♪ And I know, I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know,
I know, I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know, I know... ♪
A miracle.
♪ I know, I know,
I know, I know, I know... ♪
You are a miracle.
♪ Hey, I ought to leave
the young thing alone ♪
♪ But ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ Only darkness every day ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ And this house
just ain't no home ♪
♪ Any time she goes away ♪
♪ And I know,
I know, I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know, I know,
I know ♪
♪ I know, I know,
I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know,
I know, I know ♪
♪ I know, I know, I know,
I know ♪
♪ Hey, I ought to leave
the young thing alone ♪
♪ But ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ Only darkness every day ♪
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ And this house
just ain't no home ♪
♪ Any time she goes away. ♪