Previously on The Flash...
It's the city. They're responding
to my article.
This guy says that he saw DeVoe
at Fifth and Long two days ago.
Yeah.
This means DeVoe can't
hide from us anymore.
The injection of dark matter
from the thinking cap
which overwhelmed my synapses.
The more I try to use my brain,
the sooner I'm gonna lose it.
DeVoe plans to position each
of his five satellites around the globe.
And when the satellites link up...
He'll use that network to emit
a series of dark matter bursts.
That will reboot the prefrontal cortex
of every man, woman and child
on this Earth.
We know we need a tech-free projectile
to stop DeVoe's satellites.
We've been looking for an object
when what we really need is a person.
Amunet.
It will deliver
one savage concussive blow.
But you only get one shot.
Initially, we set out
to enlighten the world.
Now, you want to rule it.
I am leaving you, Clifford.
Agent Diggle, good to see you, sir.
- We have the specimen ready...
- The specimen?
That's a man in there
who we are supposed to protect.
Of course, sir.
Our most powerful meta-dampener
is set on the building,
I assure you.
- Elvis Banana.
- Hendrix Spaghetti.
- Eye scan?
- DNA sample, sir.
Central City branch had some trouble
with the transmogrifier
this time last year.
- You're good to go, sir.
- Good.
Now drop the dampener.
Got caught in a blast.
Slugger's microchipped now.
Dampener scrambles the frequency.
Technical, this is Castellan.
Lower the draw-bridge.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Modern music.
So lacking in the harmonic resources
necessary for expressiveness
or profundity.
The timpani in Handel's orchestra
weighed 140 pounds.
The exact gravitational force
that I'm now exerting
on your lungs.
Music Appreciation 101.
This evening's recital will be
conducted by your beloved professor.
Who's there?
My wife
cared very little for violence.
Stay where you are!
Me...
- Not so much.
- Light him up!
Get him!
Get out of my mind!
Move, move, move.
Man down!
Hey!
Come on. Come on.
"DeVoe coming for Borman."
And God said,
"Let there be light."
Okay, we got eyes on Cape Canaveral,
SpaceX and the Xichang Space Center.
And Blackhawk Island.
That's every launchpad
south of the 39th parallel.
Good man.
Okay, are we sure that DeVoe
is gonna launch
the machine from an airfield?
If he's shooting five satellites
into synchronous orbit,
that's the latitude he needs.
And whether or not he's still
moping around
about his wife ditching him,
he's gonna resurface.
He's gonna do it soon.
When he does,
I whoosh, you whoosh, she bangs.
If I can get there in time.
I mean, I'm still not fast enough
to make it through
DeVoe's pocket dimension.
That's why we split up.
Yeah, each one of us stakes out
a different launchpad.
You're serious?
I mean, you've seen DeVoe in action.
Yeah. The guy's a one-man
Legion of Doom,
so send the Super Friends.
Okay, but we're not at full
super-strength right now.
I mean, Joe's got the baby on the way,
and Caitlin's looking for Killer Frost,
and Harry's...
This chair came out of nowhere.
So, hey, Allen. West-Allen.
- Ramon.
- Cisco.
Cisco Ramon, guys.
Check this out, okay?
Somebody has been blogging
about The Thinker.
About DeVoe and the bus metas,
all of it, okay?
And if we find this blogger,
we can stop The Thinker.
- Hey, buddy.
That's... That's my blog.
Look at the byline.
It's not written by
Iris West-Allen, okay?
It's written by Anonymous
Central City Citizen. Boom.
- Mic drop.
- Hold on to that mic.
It's imaginary.
I asked you to proofread this
for me, remember?
You asked me to proofread this when?
This morning. That's when.
When you said, "Harry.
"Can you proofread?
Will you proofread? Will you read..."
It's...
Let's start by finding him a room
with less chairs.
Okay. Good.
- Powder on the floor?
- It happens.
You have 400,000 new views?
That's amazing.
I know, right?
I mean, people have been
writing in from all over,
sharing their theories
and reporting DeVoe sightings. It's...
- And Marlize sightings?
- Yeah.
I've been trying to track her down
for days.
I know Harry thinks that they split up,
but she's still
just as dangerous as DeVoe.
Right. So what?
Why would we send citizens after her?
I'm all for telling people
the truth, but...
Yeah, I mean, after I convinced you.
Yeah, I don't know if it's the best idea
to send people out there
to do our jobs for us.
No, we're inspiring them, Barry.
I mean, we could be the ones
to show them
how to do the right thing.
- I just got a new lead.
- Hmm.
Fallout.
So you think your psychosis
made a friend of yours disappear?
Yeah, I mean, she's a really
good friend of mine,
almost like a part of me.
So your friend,
is she with us here right now?
Oh, no, I'm not schizophrenic.
Um, she's more like another personality.
Dissociative identity disorder.
That is usually caused by trauma,
and from your history,
you've had quite a bit.
Yeah, I did see my fiancé die, twice.
And then my next boyfriend turned evil.
I actually meant childhood trauma.
Tell me about your father.
My dad? He was the best.
Loving, supportive,
always pushed me to get smarter.
And how did you feel when he passed?
He had ALS.
He was always hiding
his symptoms from us.
He never wanted us to see him suffer.
Sometimes when we're young,
we repress things that scare us.
Oh, I'm not repressing anything
from my childhood.
My missing friend just appeared
a couple of years ago.
It's my adult life
that's got me like this.
I'm so sorry. I have to go. Um...
Do you charge by the hour?
For you and your friends,
the quarter-hour.
I got a tip about Fallout, but it's
been scrambled by Kilg%re's code.
Hmm. Not anymore.
Consider it unscrambled.
Devoe. Where's A.R.G.U.S.
keeping Borman? Do we know?
I can't ping Lyla, but I can try Digg.
I'll just go get him.
- Uh...
- Trash can.
- How about the recycling?
- No.
- No, I got it. I got it.
- Really?
It seemed like a good idea at the time.
I'm sorry, man.
- I'm sorry.
- Mmm-hmm.
Can we just... I'm sorry.
I hate you. What is this about?
Neil Borman, the man we left
with you, with A.R.G.U.S.,
where are you keeping him?
Barry, that's classified information.
I'm not the director of A.R.G.U.S...
Digg, we don't have time, please.
He's at a place called the Castle.
It's 1,000 miles away from anything.
Please, can you check it?
Okay, looks like everything's fine
in A.R.G.U.S. except for me.
Um...
It says I checked in six hours ago.
DeVoe can shape-shift.
With Melting Point's powers,
he can trick a DNA scanner
and take over the building.
Hey, Diggle. Diggle, Diggle.
Ten thousand rads and climbing.
Borman's body's gone critical already.
We can't save him.
If that chamber hits 100K,
it'll start generating nuclear fusion,
like core-of-the-sun fusion.
Infinite fuel.
He's using Borman's body as a battery.
That's the last piece of the machine.
Wait, a battery? Borman's containment
cell is 10 feet tall.
And DeVoe has the power
to shrink it down.
It'll charge the satellites.
All he'll have to do is launch them.
How long do we have?
At this rate of fusion, we have...
12 hours until the Enlightenment begins.
Okay, Digg's back in Star City.
Now, I'm going after DeVoe.
Don't go storming the Castle just yet.
You're looking at motion-activated
electroshock plates
that A.R.G.U.S. installed
in the facility.
Seventy thousand volts.
You hit one of those,
you'll be knocked out for sure.
So I'll avoid them when I go in.
Okay, genius idea,
if their placement didn't randomize
every couple of hours.
So DeVoe is basically charging
his battery for 12 hours,
completely protected
by A.R.G.U.S. defenses.
And then he'll probably just jump
into a pocket dimension,
and he's out of there.
What if I don't avoid the plates?
What if I hit them? All of them?
I'm serious.
I mean, if I go into Flashtime,
I could you use each plate's
electric current as a fuel source.
Then I'd be fast enough to follow
DeVoe into his pocket dimension.
You would get a serious boost.
Again, another genius idea
if hitting the plates didn't cause
an electrical explosion.
Yeah, but I'd be through the pocket
dimension before the blast wave.
Ready to blow up the satellite
on the other side.
The satellite results came in.
Okay. Oh...
What? What is it?
We got six plates and six heat
signatures above them.
There are A.R.G.U.S. agents
still alive in there.
He has hostages.
You can outrun an electrical explosion.
They can't.
How's he keeping them suspended
like that?
I think I know how.
Do you know what
my favorite thing about teaching is?
Having a captive audience.
I haven't moved from this spot
in three days.
Baby, you're gonna have to carry me
into the hospital.
Okay, so I got snacks.
I got clothes for you.
I got clothes for the baby...
Damn, I forgot something.
Joe, we are not gonna need a katana
at the hospital.
Okay, so you're in my head again,
and it's entirely possible
that we get attacked
by a samurai at the hospital.
You have already repacked that bag
five times.
You've read 10 different books
on birthing methods.
By the way, I love the one about Lamaze.
Yeah...
Damn, where is this boy?
You have already left Wally
a dozen voicemails.
He's literally on a time machine.
So he has no excuse
not to show up on time
to meet his new baby sister.
I'm sorry. It's just nerves.
We have both done this before.
There's not gonna be
any surprises, okay?
- This is gonna be...
- Totally sick.
Sick? Are you feeling sick?
No, brah. No.
This delivery is gonna be sick.
Having this baby
is gonna be like one epic wave.
Are you okay? You're scaring me.
Far out! That's the 'za I ordered.
'Chovies and pineapple. Tubular.
Tubular! Brah!
There's your 'za.
That'll totally be $8.50.
Thanks, brah.
Hey, this house is...
- Bitchin'. Yeah, everybody says that.
- No.
Hard to find.
Those are some gnarly bushes outside.
Let's crush some 'za, brah.
Dude... Dude?
Where is she?
Where is...
Uh... Where is she? I don't see her.
No, Harry, I'm talking about
tracking down Marlize.
If DeVoe has popped back up,
then she might too.
And we need to put her in the pipeline
before she causes any trouble.
How are you tracking her?
Well, my readers have sent in
hundreds of tips.
Plus, there's facial recognition
and credit card checks.
- Facts.
- Right.
- Wrong.
- What?
You're looking at facts.
You should be focusing on feelings.
You remember the Council of Harrisons?
- I do.
- Handsome, but annoying.
Well, they kind of taught me
that you if you wanna...
If you wanna follow DeVoe's actions,
you gotta focus on DeVoe's motives,
which is basically DeVoe's feelings.
And so feelings,
if you're Marlize DeVoe,
where are you gonna feel safe?
So if I dig into her past,
maybe I can figure out where she is now.
Harry, that's really helpful. Thank you.
Thank you, Iris West-Allen,
for saying that.
I don't feel helpful that much anymore.
So thanks.
Hey... Um...
Are you busy, Harry?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
Um... Would you maybe wanna
help me investigate?
Yes.
- Okay, cool.
- When?
- We're gonna... Right now.
Hey, did you guys send an alert?
We did. We think we figured out
how to stop DeVoe
and save the hostages.
What is it?
Us.
You bring us into Flashtime with you.
Look, guys, it's great, you know,
you wanna help,
but we can't split up in A.R.G.U.S.
if I'm holding onto you the whole time.
Well, survey says,
you don't have to.
You guys been researching me?
At first, we thought you were
vibrating your molecules
when we were in Flashtime, but that
didn't explain why we were conscious.
Which gave us this brain blast.
When you run, you don't just
tap into the Speed Force.
You generate Speed Force around you.
It's like you're creating lightning
to protect you from the friction,
like an aura.
So when I bring you into Flashtime,
I'm actually extending my
Speed Force aura to you?
And what if physical touch
just focuses those powers?
I could let go,
share my speed.
We'd only be able to last
a few moments before we burned out,
like 55 milliseconds of real time.
And thanks to relativity, that gives us
just enough time to rescue the hostages
while you chase DeVoe
down the rabbit hole.
Okay, guys, I mean, you know,
everything looks normal to me
when I'm in Flashtime,
but it took me months to learn
how to operate like that.
Exactly.
That's what makes you the perfect
candidate for training.
Train us.
I know it's a leap, Barry,
but we're running out of time,
and I just think it might work.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Okay.
Ready?
One second on the clock.
Go.
Oh, Flashtime, how I've missed thee.
Here we go.
Mmm, is that lightning about to hit me?
You wanted to do this.
It's working.
Thank you, Speed Force.
Okay, here we go.
Just remember, when you're moving
this fast, it's not about
running with your legs,
it's about staying calm,
focused, centered.
Otherwise, you're gonna fall
on your ass at Mach 3.
Yeah, okay, sensei.
I'm just opening a breach.
- You good?
- It's a little harder than I thought.
- Yeah.
- Maybe if I shift my weight...
Hey, you're burning up already.
You okay?
- I can't move my leg.
- What?
- My leg's not working.
- All right, stay calm.
Remember, concentrate.
You're slowing down.
Okay, I can't really concentrate.
I gotta keep it loose.
I gotta keep moving
if I'm gonna breach, I mean...
- You gotta stay calm.
- Okay.
I gotta get the leg to move.
- Now both of my legs are stuck.
- What?
My legs are stuck.
I'm working with two frozen
drumsticks here.
- Okay, just relax.
- What? Okay.
Now, I'm falling.
You okay?
Yep, yep, my legs are just asleep,
but I'm gonna get this.
- I'm telling you.
- Okay.
It's Joe and Cecile.
Do you think I can spare a minute?
I just gotta walk it off. Ah.
We could use a break.
Good news is, you're totally healthy.
- Thank God.
- Oh, no, Caitlin.
Please don't think, "Relax."
If you were nine months pregnant
and you suddenly started craving
Master Kush and Surf,
I don't think that you would relax.
Actually, I was thinking relaxin,
the hormone.
As we get closer to your due date,
your body releases relaxin
to loosen the ligaments
to make it easier to deliver the baby.
It's like you're literally stretching.
So you think this hormone
is stretching her meta-powers?
Yes, I think instead of just reading
people's minds,
she's now inhabiting them.
Great. That's great.
I mean, that's just one more thing
for me to talk about at therapy.
I mean, can you believe
what Dr. Finkel said this morning?
Babe, we didn't see her this morning.
Uh, I did.
She thinks that
I'm repressing something.
I mean, repressing something?
How crazy is that?
Oh, my God, this Erlenmeyer flask
is covered in water spots.
Yeah, she's definitely me.
Uh, here, why don't I give you this?
It'll help you
take some deep breaths and focus.
I'm familiar with an albuterol inhaler.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, oh.
- I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
- Don't worry about it.
You're just going off my instincts.
How do we stop this
from happening again?
I don't think we can
until you give birth,
so I think the best thing to do
is actually keep you isolated
and use this.
Come on, we can handle that.
Okay, I'm gonna get back to training.
Thank you, Caitlin.
Uh, hey, Caitlin.
For what it's worth,
when I was you back there
for, like, 20 seconds,
it seemed like you were trying
to ignore something,
something really big.
And if there's anything that I learned
from having these powers,
it's that you cannot hide
from anything forever.
You just be careful, okay?
Marlize Milan, born in Cape Town.
Cape Town.
Summers by the sea.
Picking grapes in a vineyard.
Got a PhD in Inflationary Theory
and Engineering.
Cute, little button nose
always buried in her book.
So nice.
Tenured as a professor
of engineering at Oxford,
where she met Clifford DeVoe.
Where she met her husband-to-be.
Isn't that romantic?
A continent apart, and they find
each other. So romantic.
I mean, it's beautiful
when you think about it.
It's... What?
Beautiful? What is that?
What are you doing?
I'm empathetic. I'm being...
Council says, "Be empathetic."
I'm empathetic.
You know, I'm putting myself
in Marlize's shoes.
I should see if she's got a pair
of shoes, put myself in them.
No, Harry, this,
this is not a love story, okay?
She married a psychopath.
A psychopath now. Not then.
Back then he had feelings.
They loved each other.
He had feelings. She had feelings.
Then he lost the feelings,
and that's why she got out.
That's why she left.
She left.
West-Allen.
We should turn Marlize.
Harry, no, I don't think you
even know what you're saying.
I know what I'm saying.
I know. I have bad days.
Dumb Harry. But I'm not dumb today.
Today's a good day.
We should turn Marlize.
Marlize can help us.
And why would she wanna do that?
To stop the psychopath.
Right? And to protect the man
trapped inside the monster.
Marlize can save everybody.
Marlize is the key.
Harry, we've tried that already.
With Savitar, remember? It didn't work.
You can't save monsters.
Marlize isn't a monster.
And besides,
the clock's ticking.
I mean, 10 hours
before the Enlightenment.
What do we have to lose?
She stabbed me with a katana, Harry.
Our lives are what we have to lose.
We can't save anyone
if we're all dead.
Right.
We are gonna bring her in,
and we're gonna stop her
so she doesn't hurt anyone ever again.
Okay.
I left some of my files at home.
I'll finish my investigation there.
- I'm gonna come with you.
- No, I'm fine, Harry.
- You stay here, okay?
- I'll come with.
- Harry!
- I'll just stay here.
I'll just stay right here.
All right, just remember
to stay calm this time.
- Why are you looking at me?
- I wasn't...
Both of you.
All right. Take two.
- Yes!
- Nice!
A baby breach.
That's right, Barry. A baby breach.
And in time, she'll blossom
into maturity,
but for now in Flashtime,
she's my little breachling.
Okay.
Cait.
Cold gun is still not working,
just like Killer Frost.
We gotta find a way to offset
the friction.
Damn it!
- My leg's stuck.
- All right, just stay calm.
Hey, watch out.
Dad, my leg's stuck.
Caitlin, watch out!
- Caitlin.
- Cait.
- What happened?
- Training.
You came out of Flashtime in mid-air.
I think you got concussed.
Then again, I'm not the team doctor.
I mean, I don't feel nauseous.
Just hand me some acetaminophen,
and we can get back to training.
No, hold on.
We have to talk about what happened.
What do you mean?
You just lost focus, right?
- Yeah.
- No, it was...
I don't know.
Something pulled your focus.
No, I'm fine.
If this were the real thing,
you would have died.
- I'm not a liability.
- I know.
I am. I'm putting you guys in danger
doing this.
I mean, I realize you guys wanna
help, but I gotta stop training you.
Barry, come on, those hostages...
I'll find another way to save them.
You have to let us help you.
I mean, after everything DeVoe
did to us...
Killer Frost.
She's right.
We're running out of time.
It's worth the risk.
I'm not training you guys
just to get you killed.
I'm sorry.
West-Allen!
- Of course, he followed me home.
- West-Allen!
West-Allen!
- Apartment five.
Hi.
Oh, you moved.
- No.
- No, this...
- This is apartment four.
- Four.
- You're in apartment five.
- Yes.
So, look, I just came to say
you were right.
I was trying to put myself
in Marlize's shoes,
and I forgot I should also try
to put myself in your shoes, so...
Thanks. It's very big of you
to admit that you were wrong, Harry.
I don't know if I was the word you
said. It's more like I'm dumb.
I'm dumb now.
- Harry.
- Yeah.
Marlize is not gonna help us
fight her husband out of love.
Love, exactly.
Look, she...
Look, the Enlightenment
was not born out of love.
She's always been an activist.
Look at that.
Even before she met DeVoe,
she was trying to save people.
Yes, her earlier papers
were very optimistic.
She thought that technology
could liberate humanity.
Humanity. Right.
But she's not saving anyone now.
Not according to your perspective.
What about her perspective?
Put yourself in her shoes.
Come in, please.
You know, just put yourself
in her shoes. Okay?
- Harry, take your shoes off.
- Yeah.
Yeah, put on my shoes,
and I'll put on your shoes.
- We'll both trade shoes.
- No, Harry.
I don't wanna try your shoes on.
I want you to take your shoes off.
You're tracking mud all through
my house, please.
Oh. Right. Sorry.
This is kind of more of a loft...
This is my home, okay?
This is the first place
that I've lived in with Barry.
It makes me feel loved and safe.
And so we're gonna keep it nice and...
Clean.
What? What is it?
What are you thinking about?
I think I know where Marlize is hiding.
Apartment four.
No, not apartment four.
Babe?
What are you doing?
I gotta get this bag ready.
Uh... I got snacks. I got water.
I got a change of clothes for the baby.
I got a change of clothes for me.
You're me.
It's a whole new level of weird.
Stop. Give me this.
Sit down.
Okay.
Yeah.
Better?
Who the hell are you anyway?
Okay, not better. I'm calling Caitlin.
What are you doing in my house?
- Cecile, this is our house.
- Cecile?
Why do you keep calling me Cecile?
My name is not Cecile.
I'm Joe West.
Um... Okay, Joe. Joe!
Joe, sit down. Sit down.
Okay, I need you to take
a deep breath. In through your nose,
out through the mouth. Close your eyes.
Imagine that you're sitting
in a big, beautiful sea.
The waves are cresting over you.
Back and forth.
Those waves, that's Joe.
Now, look up, it's a big, dark,
beautiful sky
with one shining star.
That star is you, Cecile.
Great.
How do you feel?
Joe?
- Oh, God.
- You pulled me back.
How did you pull me back?
Lamaze?
I had to switch some things
up in my head, but... Hey.
Am I crazy, because you were...
Babe, trust me, there are far worse
heads I could have been stuck in.
I love you.
You figure it out yet?
No, I mean, I shut down the generator.
I could save the hostages,
but DeVoe still gets away.
And then, you know...
Actually, I meant,
have you figured out how come
you lost your damn mind?
Dude, I'm sorry. I'm just...
You're just trying to keep us safe.
I know.
That's starting to sound real
familiar coming out of your mouth.
You're not ready to use Flashtime.
Not like that.
We will be ready if you train us.
It takes more than 10 hours
to learn super speed. Okay?
You guys could die in there.
And if you don't take us,
we'll die anyway.
Our brains get wiped, and that's it,
that's the end of our world.
No, losing both of my best friends
and it being my fault,
that's the end of my world.
You may think it's worth the risk,
but I couldn't live with myself.
Barry, you cannot sideline us
because of what happened to him.
All right, I don't need
another therapist.
Look, we all lost somebody, okay,
but that never gives us an excuse
to shut each other out.
I said drop it, all right?
You think you're the only one
who feels bad about Ralph dying?
Guys.
You know, he came to see me
at Iron Heights?
He told me he was afraid.
He warned me he wasn't ready.
But I pushed him anyway.
I said go back out there
and do my job, my burden.
We made the bus metas.
We gave Ralph his powers.
You wanna talk about burdens?
I started this. I shot that bazooka.
I opened up the Speed Force.
And I didn't do it
so you could stand here
and tell me you're gonna save
the world alone again.
I know that.
And I know we're running out of time.
I can't do this by myself, but...
Everybody I've tried to teach
has ended up worse
than when I found them.
And what about Ralph? Was he worse?
You taught him that when his back
was against the wall,
and the world was ending around him,
he could always make the choice.
Make the choice to be a hero.
We deserve that same choice.
All we need is someone to show us how.
You guys really wanna do this?
It's not a burden
if we shoulder it together.
- We found her.
- You found Marlize?
I think so.
She's in England.
All right. That's our last extrapolator.
You set the coordinates,
it'll breach you there.
We have to stop DeVoe.
By the time you get back...
Hey.
I love you.
Go save the world.
Where are we at?
Borman's almost at 100,000 rads.
All right, we gotta go. Come on.
Thank you, subject seven.
Now, your fire will light up the world.
Perimeter's secure.
Once we're inside,
we'll have less than a second.
I'll activate the plates,
draw their charge.
I'll lay the breachlings.
And I'll protect the A.R.G.U.S.
agents from the blast using this...
- Ice shooter.
Do I have to call it an ice shooter?
I thought frost bite sounded good.
Guys, it solves the friction
offset problem by shooting ice.
Therefore it's an ice shooter.
- You call it an ice shooter.
- Relax.
It's just not that hard.
DeVoe must be
shrinking Borman's chamber.
We can do this.
Catch me if you can.
I've got the charge.
Breachling is go.
He's iced.
Five more to go.
Remember, stay focused.
We did it.
"Once upon a time in some remote
corner of that universe,
"there was a star upon which
clever beasts
"invented knowing."
You're quoting Nietzsche at me.
You destroyed a satellite.
Top marks, quick boy.
You can destroy 1,000 more,
and you will still march
closer to the Enlightenment.
I forget what Nietzsche said
about wiping minds.
I must have skipped
philosophy class that day.
Did I teach you nothing this year?
Has nothing pierced your thick cowl?
Think of it. Or rather don't.
You'll just end up hurting yourself,
so let me explain.
A world, enlightened.
Within a day all soldiers
will lay down their arms.
Every nuclear weapon will be disarmed
within six months.
Poverty, famine, disease eradicated.
We will clean up the streets.
People will put down their idiot phones
and become curious again,
and I will be there to teach them.
I, not you, will save this
godforsaken world.
No, you'd just control it.
You wanna take away free will.
A pittance for humanity to pay
to know peace.
But we wouldn't know each other.
Parents wouldn't remember their kids.
Husbands wouldn't remember their wives.
Good. You hit upon precisely the point.
Emotion is the father of all error.
Chemicals in our brain that distract us,
impede progress,
and the most destructive
and ridiculous imbalance of all
is that thing you feebles call "love."
I learned this from experience,
Mr. Allen.
And soon, you will too.
What happened in there?
All that matters
is that you're all safe.
But DeVoe. Where's DeVoe?
Hey. Hey, don't worry.
- The Flash is on it.
- Thank you.
What's wrong?
I need your help.
Back when we were training,
I had this fragment
of a memory.
I think it's something that I've been
repressing for a long time.
I don't remember much,
just that I was young,
and I was terrified.
Caitlin, are you sure you want me
to vibe you there?
I mean, maybe your brain
kept this memory under lock and key
for a reason.
I need to know what it was.
I can handle it.
Then focus on it
and hang on.
Caity. Oh, no! Caity!
Caity, are you okay?
Stay still, we're getting...
That's me.
- Right there.
- What are you doing?
Caity! Honey, don't!
Killer Frost, she was part of you.
Even then.
The particle accelerator
hadn't exploded.
How is that possible?
Empty.
But this is their first place together.
She would come here. I can feel it.
The pot's still warm.
That means...
- We can have tea.
- No.
- Marlize!
- Iris, she's not here.
- Come out.
- Iris.
It's rude to breach
into a person's home uninvited.
And dangerous when that person's
holding a grudge and a katana.
Why are you here?
I got this.
We're here, Marlize...
We're here because of you.
Because we... You...
You've...
I can't.
You can't verbalize it. Not anymore.
Just like we hypothesized,
but never observed before.
You're experiencing the penultimate
stages of the Enlightenment.
Your mind is being rebooted.
Soon you'll be without memories,
without relationships.
Just a blank slate
so that Clifford may reeducate you.
Soon, we'll all be just like you.
Marlize, we have to stop him.
Your husband has gone too far,
and I think you know it,
or you'd be with him right now.
Yes, I left my husband,
but that doesn't change the fact
that he's right.
If anything, his betrayal proves
his very point.
Man corrupts even the best of ideas.
Pessimism isn't smarter than optimism.
"In this life, the bravest thing
you can be is optimistic."
Familiar words.
You said them when you were at Oxford,
two weeks before you met Clifford DeVoe.
I gave a speech on technology
and the elimination of world hunger.
I truly believed it could be done.
He tried to change you, Marlize.
But I think deep down,
you are still an optimist.
You still believe in humanity.
And I believe in you.
You asked me what I was willing
to do for my husband,
and now I'm gonna ask you,
what are you willing to do
for the world?
Barry shot down one of the satellites.
He did it.
DeVoe didn't seem to care.
I'll try and see if I can track...
Uh, I don't like that sound.
It says a S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
has been activated.
It's DeVoe.
He's using our satellite to replace
the one you destroyed.
Well, can you stop him?
He's here.
Hello, Professor DeVoe.
No, no, no. Come on.
Come on.
DeVoe!
DeVoe! DeVoe!
Initiating Enlightenment protocol.
Let there be light.
He did it.
The Enlightenment.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
God saw. It was good.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::