- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Dr. Harrison "Nash" Wells.
- I'm searching
for an artifact
that just happens
to contain Eternium.
- The disappearance
of Sue Dearbon.
- I don't think I've ever seen
you this devoted to a case.
- HLH isn't just
my mother's disease.
Now it's killing me.
You're a dead man, too,
aren't you, Barry?
- The only timeline
where everyone survives
was the one where I died.
And none of you
can try and save me.
- Analysis
of Mitch Romero's blood
reveals that this substance
appears to heal
any and all weaknesses
in the human body,
including HLH.
I need more.
- [gasps]
Dr. Rosso.
- Didn't mean to sneak up
on you like that.
- Well, it's almost Halloween.
I guess we're all due
for a good scare, right?
What brings you here so late?
- I'm meeting up
with a colleague.
Yeah, I told him I'd be
here half an hour ago,
so...if you'll excuse me.
- Of course.
It's good to see you.
[dramatic music]
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
- [screams]
I wish it didn't
have to be this way.
- And you're okay
with all of this?
- No, but...
[sighs]
I have to accept
that there are still others
out there that we can save.
- Yeah, guys, look,
six weeks from now,
all of our lives
are gonna be on the line,
so we have to be prepared.
- Yes, but what about him?
I'm not just gonna wait around
for him to get vaporized
by anti-matter.
We should be doing something
to try to save his life.
- You can't.
You can't, Cisco.
That's why I need you
to stop worrying about me.
- If Barry had
any other option,
we'd be doing it.
I think you
gotta get behind this.
- Yeah.
I am.
♪ ♪
- How do you convince
your best friend
not to save your life?
- You're the teacher.
You'll find a way.
- Well,
he's gonna have to wait.
It's CCPD.
♪ ♪
- There he is.
So much for my day off.
- What do we got?
- It's a creepy one.
Somebody broke into this
facility last night,
and stole 10 liters of blood.
- There's no security footage?
- There's no cameras
in this part of the hospital.
- You think
this is meta-related?
- I'm asking you.
- I mean...
meta-thieves usually
make a way bigger mess.
See this lock?
The way this is sheared,
a power saw could've done this.
I don't know.
I mean, maybe it was just some
kids pulling a Halloween prank.
- Good.
I thought we were dealing
with some kind of meta-vampire.
- Just a normal criminal
with a diseased mind.
- Well, since I am captain,
I'm gonna go watch
the second half of the game.
I'm gonna leave this to you,
all right?
- Mm-hmm.
- You okay?
- Yeah. You know, just this
Crisis that's coming.
Cisco's not taking it so great.
- Let me guess which part.
Cisco is a whole lot like you.
It is in his nature
to want to save lives.
Especially under
these circumstances.
I'll see you later.
- Right.
Thanks, Joe.
- Thanks for what?
- I think I know how
to get through to Cisco.
♪ ♪
- Tests are conclusive.
The peculiar black blood
I absorbed from Mitch Romero
temporarily cured
the HLH cancer in my blood,
but it wasn't enough.
I need more blood
in order to create
a permanent cure
to save my life.
Adding Romero's cells
to this new blood
should be the key to rebuilding
my cellular structure.
♪ ♪
I only hope
I have enough time.
- Ramsey:Why didn't you tell
me?  It's brilliant.
- You're my son.
You're supposed
to be impressed.
You're going to do beautiful
things for this world.
[coughs]
- Are you okay?
Mom?
♪ ♪
- My condition is terminal.
- I got your text.
What is it now?
- I know you're upset
about this Crisis.
And I've been
thinking about it,
and you're right.
We can do more
than prepare for a fight.
You can save a life.
- I knew you'd come around.
- No, Cisco, not...
it's not me.
We're gonna save Ramsey Rosso.
- Here's the thing.
We've done some insane things
at S.T.A.R. Labs
over the last few years,
but curing a rare blood cancer,
that is beyond our resources.
- So we just shouldn't try?
- So we try
and somehow succeed,
are we supposed to spend
the rest of your time here
trying to save everyone who's
been diagnosed with cancer?
- We start with one man.
Look, you heard what
Caitlin said about Ramsey.
He's one of the most brilliant
doctors on the planet.
I need you to back me on this.
You'll understand soon enough.
Look, I...
what would it take to cure HLH?
- Honestly...
an act of God.
- Or...
An act of science.
And I know just where
to find one.
- I'm assuming
this is the Wells
that you were
telling me about.
- Yep. Nash Wells.
Multiversal explorer
and provider
of scientific miracles.
You, I'm guessing,
are Barry Allen, the Flash.
- How did he...how did you...
- Hidden surveillance device.
- You bugged S.T.A.R. Labs?
- No, no, not exactly.
I...
I bugged you.
- No, you didn't.
- Yeah, I did.
Fellas, I've been listening
to your conversations,
and I have a proposition.
Now I need an anti-vibrational
crypto-circuit
to complete my work
on this Earth,
You need help
with your mission, right?
Well, you build me my circuit,
'cause I know
you have the capacity,
and I will lead you
to something priceless
that will surely help
your mission.
- Your work?
What's your work?
- It's thermic excavation.
- You're a cosmic myth-buster
who also happens
to be a geologist?
- Sure.
- Sidebar.
Red flag city.
- Yeah.
Then again...
Wells usually shows up
for a reason.
- Fellas?
- Yeah.
- You're aware
he's still bugged, right?
- Where is the bug?
I don't see anything.
- Not in your shoe.
I can tell you that much.
- Let's just say
that we trust you.
- We don't.
- Which we obviously don't.
- Understood.
- What are you offering?
- I'm offering you
something that will help
save Ramsey Rosso's life.
♪ ♪
[knocking on door]
- Have I got
something for you.
- Amazon packages?
- No.
- You know that case
that you've been working on
for the last couple months?
The Dearbon woman?
Well,
I know it's been cold lately,
so I have a little
Halloween treat for you.
A lead.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I interviewed this accountant
in Midway City
that works
at the security firm,
and one of their guards
was working a charity event
and claims to have seen someone
that sounds like Sue Dearbon,
so Cecile pulled a favor
and got an eye witness report.
- Cool.
Thanks, Iris.
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
- Need something else?
- No.
No, that was it.
- Cool.
- All right, yeah.
Cool, I will see you later.
- Production of blood serum
is complete.
[panting]
It appears identical
to the substance
I absorbed from Mitch Romero.
If this works,
I could hold the cure
not just for myself,
but for all those suffering
from HLH cancer.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[groaning]
[liquid gurgling]
[yelling]
It's not working.
I failed.
- Wells: It's in there,
McCulloch Technologies.
- Cisco: What is?
- Well, this extremely rare
bio-regenerative serum
capable of healing
organic tissue,
no matter what the harm.
So for your purposes,
what you do,
you simply inject it into
your friend's healthy cells,
those healthy cells replicate,
they replace
the unhealthy cells.
Presto.
Instant miracle.
Although, don't wait till
your buddy's too far gone
because then it might not work.
- This sounds way too good
to be true.
- Yeah, he's right.
I mean, how did
McCulloch Technologies
develop something
this advanced?
- They didn't develop it.
They stole it.
It's from Swan Moon, the...
- The Dominator home planet?
- Yeah, that's the one.
Yeah, recovered from some
invasion three years ago.
Anyway, blah blah blah.
You guys in, or what?
- Well, how dangerous a weapon
could this be
in the wrong hands?
- On a scale of one to ten...
12.
- We gotta get our hands
on this thing.
- All right, I'm gonna disable
the exterior security cameras.
- He goes right
through the door.
Huh.
That's cool.
- How'd you know
the stuff was here?
- Kid, multiversal explorer.
We need to know things.
- And the serum?
Could it protect someone
from anti-matter?
- I expect
that goes without saying.
Whoo!
- Cameras are down.
- All right, boys.
Here's where the fun begins.
♪ ♪
All right.
Speedster, come on.
Speed us to the storage room.
- No, I can't.
- What do you mean you can't?
- There are localized
meta-dampeners
all over this building,
all right?
My powers are useless in here.
- It means you're useless here.
- We don't have
to make your circuit.
- Is that right, tough guy?
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do
if you don't make my circuit,
and I don't have...
- Hey, numbskulls,
knock it off.
- Freeze!
Both of you.
- Both of us?
♪ ♪
- So we can explain.
- I don't think they're gonna
ask questions first.
[high-pitched whir]
[loud humming]
[all grunting]
- Nash?
- Hey, fellas.
So your auditory nerves...
- What?
- Your ears will be fine
in a couple of minutes.
Unlike these two.
Now...
where were we?
- All right, let's hurry up.
There's another life
at stake besides our own.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Ralph.
Any progress
on that Dearbon lead?
You know, I really think that
there might be something...
to it.
- [muffled] No.
I decided to give it up.
- What?
Why?
- There's no point, Iris.
The whole Sue thing
is a lost cause,
so I might as well quit
before I waste any more time.
- Ralph, you can't quit.
You're obsessed
with finding her.
You have to keep going.
- Iris,
despite Team Flash's mantra,
sometimes you do have
to give up on things.
You know, if I were you,
I would be spending
a lot more time
with my husband...
while he's still here.
♪ ♪
[lock beeping]
- All right.
Let the search begin.
- Oh, man.
Without super-speed,
this is gonna take a minute.
- We don't have
to search every location,
just the cold ones, okay?
Because the serum
we're looking for,
it requires an environment
of -15 degrees.
- This says -15 degrees.
- Well, there you go.
- [chuckles]
- Okay.
- Convenient.
- Time to steal
our golden idol.
♪ ♪
[beeping]
Did you guys hear that?
- What?
No.
- I didn't hear anything.
[beeping]
- Wait, yeah, I did hear that.
Is that an alarm?
- It better not be.
I need more time to hack this.
- I'm on it.
- Hey.
- Yeah, yeah, I got.
- I'm gonna follow him.
[whispering] Nash, Nash.
Nash.
- [quietly]
Okay.
♪ ♪
[whispering] I don't know
where he went.
- I got it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- No.
- We're too late.
- No, this can't be happening.
- McCulloch must've
already sold it.
- We needed this
to save Ramsey.
- Boys...
we got company.
Always wanted to say that.
Here.
Catch.
- What is this?
- This...
this is our way out of here.
- What are you talking about?
What are we
supposed to do with this?
- It's easy.
You just throw it.
Like, now.
- [groans]
- Whoo!
Well, that was exciting,
wasn't it, fellas?
- The Lounge?
How did we...
- Worry less about
how we got to the Lounge,
and more about building
my crypto-circuit.
- That's not happening anymore.
Let me correct you,
Barry Allen.
Yes, it is.
We had a deal, right?
I would lead you
to something priceless,
which I did, not my fault
the serum was gone.
So now, you two...
are gonna build me a device.
- I don't understand.
Why won't this blood
work again?
[panting]
What am I missing?
I found it,
a cure for you.
- The bonding agent
in this cure is dark matter.
- So that's it.
You're just deciding
to give up and die.
- No one lives forever.
- No.
I won't give up.
That's your choice.
- Ramsey.
I'm not your enemy.
- I know.
The real enemy...
is death.
- You know,
Nash isn't going anywhere
until he gets
this crypto-circuit.
How's it coming?
- Almost finished.
- All right.
I don't know if you should.
- Okay, what do you mean?
- I mean,
doesn't something feel off
about all this?
- Yeah, I know.
The guys shows up
needing our tech,
makes a bargain to help us,
and conveniently,
the thing we need isn't there.
- Right.
So, I mean...
you think he's lying to us?
- It wouldn't be the first time
a Wells had a secret agenda.
- [sighs]
Yeah.
Yo, what's in here?
- That's storage
for Frost's stuff.
You know how she gets.
♪ ♪
- You haven't looked me in
the eye since I came in here.
♪ ♪
- Wait.
- What the hell
am I looking at?
Cisco.
- You know exactly
what this is.
I don't care
what powers you have.
You want it...
you're gonna have
to go through me.
- What are you talking about?
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm saving your life.
'Cause someone has to do it.
- Saving Ramsey...
saving Ramsey's my call.
- And it's a bad call.
- But it's the one I made.
Sometimes, as a leader,
you have to make tough calls
in order to serve
the greater good.
- You know,
I made a tough call.
And I made it for you.
- But I told you.
You can't save me.
- I'm not buying that.
- Well, you have to.
Sacrificing myself
saves everything and everyone.
I've seen it.
- And what does that give me
to look forward to?
Waking up to a world
without the Flash?
A life without my best friend?
- You get to live.
You all get to live.
- Don't.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Look, man, I...
I've been dealing
with this for weeks.
Wondering what's gonna happen
when I'm gone,
how everybody's gonna move on.
That's why I wanted us,
you and me together,
to save Ramsey today.
- You wanted us
to save a random person
so I'd be okay with you dying?
- No.
I wanted us
to save one person's life
so you could understand
the tough calls...
the sacrifices
that a leader has to make.
Because you're my pick.
You're the person that
I want to run S.T.A.R. Labs
and this team
when I'm gone.
All day,
I've been trying to teach you
how hard those responsibilities
can be.
And then you stole something
that was meant to save
another person's life.
You justified it, even.
- And I'd do it again.
♪ ♪
- Maybe I made
the wrong choice.
♪ ♪
- The serum's yours.
[knocking at door]
- Barry.
- Can we talk?
- Um, now's really
not a good time.
- It's important.
I have something
that I need to give you.
S.T.A.R. Labs
has been doing some research
into regenerative formulas,
and we've developed a serum.
We think that
this could save your life.
If you inject it
into your healthy cells,
they'll duplicate
and eventually overtake
your cells
that are affected by HLH,
but you have to use it quickly.
- Is it...
is it dark-matter-based?
- No, it's experimental, but...
we believe it'll cure you.
[breathes shakily]
- I'd given up hope.
[thunder rumbles]
- But why...why do this for me?
- A week ago,
you told me you felt like
you were falling off a cliff.
I want you to have a lifeline.
- You're dying, as well.
Don't you want
a lifeline for yourself?
- There's only enough of this
for one person.
And I've read about you,
Ramsey,
and I've talked to Caitlin.
You're a brilliant doctor.
From what she said,
if you had enough time,
you could cure HLH.
I'm giving you that time.
The world needs people like you
to save those
who can't save themselves.
Test it.
Verify what we believe
it'll do,
and then use it quickly.
We're not sure how long
the serum will be viable.
- Barry.
Thank you.
[knocking at door]
- Hey.
You busy?
- For you, Cap?
Never.
- Iris tells me
you've been having trouble
with the Dearbon case.
- Joe, I've been working
on this Dearbon thing
since last summer.
Then it dawned on me.
Digging into this right now,
it doesn't matter.
Why the hell
should I try to find her
and try to help her...
If I can't even save...
- Barry.
You can say it.
- Ralph.
Do you remember
my old partner Chyre?
He taught me
an important lesson.
He said, "You can't always
save everyone..."
"But you can always
save someone."
For you...
that's Sue Dearbon...
not Barry.
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna miss him, Joe.
- [sighs deeply]
- That's it?
Fully functioning
crypto-circuit?
You sure?
'Cause it kind of seems like...
seems kind of shoddy.
Shoddy workmanship.
I feel like I've seen
better workmanship on,
well, pretty much all
the other Earths out there.
This is subpar.
Subpar's being generous.
It...never touch me.
- Just take it.
- Sure, kid.
Thanks.
Till our next adventure.
Frosty.
- So...
how'd it go
with Professor Speedster?
You all ready
for life post-Crisis?
- I think our friendship
pretty much exploded.
- Ugh.
- Because it is impossible
to save him,
and yet, I still don't
think I should stop trying.
- You want some free advice?
- Sure.
- You can't save someone
who doesn't want to be saved.
And he's already
made up his mind.
And if you obsess over it,
it could lead you down
a dark path.
You might make
a mistake you can't fix.
- Commencing preliminary tests
on S.T.A.R. Lab's
proposed cure.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[warbling beeping]
Damn it!
Of course it's another failure.
Why would I expect anything
different from the universe?
My fate is sealed.
Death wins again.
Death.
There is one key difference.
- Too late.
- Between the blood I stole,
and the blood
from Mitch Romero's body.
Romero was afraid
for his life.
His blood cells were flooded
with epinephrine.
Adrenaline released
during the attack,
it's the bonding agent,
which means...
[sinister music]
In order to create
the substance I need to live,
I have to kill.
But first...
they have to be afraid.
♪ ♪
- Multiple alarms
at Central City General.
They're evacuating.
- Is it a bomb threat?
- Reports say a madman
is attacking patients.
All the staff and patients
are accounted for,
except for those
on this floor.
Ugh.
That one's fresh.
Whoever did this was just here.
- Why would someone do this?
- She's gone.
Maybe I can figure out why.
- [screaming]
- Go.
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
[shouts]
[grunts]
- Ramsey?
What the hell are you doing?
- Whatever it takes
to stay alive.
- These people.
You're the one that's killing.
S.T.A.R. Labs
gave you a cure.
Why didn't you take it?
- I did.
But it didn't work.
Turns out the disease in my
human blood was too far gone.
But if I was to become
something more than human,
that's when I realized
I could live forever.
As long as I feed.
- Ramsey, you're a doctor.
You're supposed to save lives,
not take them.
- I am saving lives, Flash.
Mine.
And right now,
you are in my way.
- [snarls]
- [snarling]
♪ ♪
[growls]
- [breathing heavily]
[all growling]
♪ ♪
[all shout]
- Ramsey, come on, let him go.
Please.
- I can't.
My blood brothers and sisters
are much more
than just the help.
They're making me stronger.
- You're using them.
- To survive.
[loud whoosh]
Hello, Cait.
Playing the hero now, are you?
- The bad guy was taken,
so yeah.
[all snarling]
- Please, help me.
- I know what you're thinking.
You're fast, Flash.
But as a doctor,
I know exactly where
this man's carotid artery is.
Even if I can't feed,
you will never
save him in time.
- Ramsey, don't do this.
Let us help you.
What you're doing, it's...
inhuman.
- It was my humanity
that was holding me back.
Preventing me
from becoming the man
Mum always knew
I was destined to be.
She always said that
I would do beautiful things
for this world.
And she was right.
Because the man I was,
that was the disease.
A frail human body
with a shelf life.
Rot.
But I found a way
to transcend all that.
To defeat death itself.
- Everyone dies, Ramsey.
Maybe the only thing
that makes it bearable
is to find some meaning in it.
- Well, that means I'm making
the greatest sacrifice of all.
Don't you see?
What I'm becoming,
this is the cure.
I am the answer, Flash,
to the greatest mystery of all.
Life eternal.
- Please, Dr. Rosso.
- I saved you for last
so you would be
the most afraid.
- Ramsey, please don't do this.
- You could've saved Mum,
but you didn't.
And that's why
I came here for you.
- Ramsey.
- [groans]
- [shouts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Stay with me, all right?
I got you, I got you.
[snarling continues]
[all growling]
- What the hell are they doing?
- I think they're trying
to follow Ramsey.
- [grunting, snarling]
- Wait.
- We have to help him.
- I don't think we can.
♪ ♪
- We lost.
Five people aren't going home
to their families tonight.
And the sixth, Ramsey.
We lost him, too.
He's out there somewhere.
We have to stop him.
I...
I have to stop him.
- Barry.
- You tried to save him.
- But he turned himself
into a monster.
- That's not on us.
That was Ramsey's choice.
- I swear,
if it is the last thing I do
on this Earth...
I'm gonna stop him.
- How did Ramsey do this,
anyway?
- He's using people
as incubators.
Using their bodies to create
what he needs
to keep himself alive.
- So he's turning people
into human blood banks.
- And as soon
as he gets hungry again...
- He's gonna make a withdrawal.
- Well, happy Halloween,
everyone.
Yeah.
- [sighs]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Ralph.
[sighs]
Look...
I know this Crisis news
hasn't been easy on anyone.
- Yeah.
[chuckles]
I'll say.
But look, Iris...
that's no excuse
for me being a jerk.
I'm sorry.
I know that you were
just trying to help me.
So I did want to say that
tomorrow I'm call Midway City,
see what I can find.
- That's great, Ralph.
Sue is very lucky to have
a master detective
like you searching for her.
- Give me a break.
It's just
a missing persons case.
It's not like
I'm looking to get married.
- He gonna be okay?
- Yeah, he is.
- Of all the nights for this
madness to be happening,
it had to be Halloween.
[sighs]
Babe,
we should probably head home.
- Would you mind if I catch up
with you in a couple minutes?
[mysterious humming]
- No.
It's fine.
Barry.
- Hey.
- [sighs]
- I'm sorry about
what happened at McCulloch.
- No, man, no.
Look, this...
this is not your fault.
- I should've been focused
on saving the right person.
- Well, I mean,
even though things didn't...
work out with Ramsey,
at least we tried...
to do the right thing.
- I still don't know
how you do that, man.
-Picking yourself up,
pushing forward.
- I'm just trying to...
teach you what it's taken me
years to learn.
- I know you're doing it
for all of us.
[somber piano music]
♪ ♪
That's what it means
to be a hero.
- I knew I picked
the right guy.
I'm gonna...
- Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Joe.
You all right?
- Mm.
I was just...
just wondering
where Ramsey was and...
just hoping to God
that we find him before...
this gets worse.
- Well, his description
has been circulated
to every precinct
from here to Gotham,
so we should find him.
- Then what?
More people are gonna get hurt.
Or worse.
- I know.
I tried to save him.
Tried to do some good
before I...
- Don't you dare
start talking like that.
You've done plenty of good.
Ever since you became
the Flash,
you've saved more people
than CCPD altogether.
Without you,
I would've...
I would've lost our family
a long time ago.
And this is what you get
for saving the world
over and over again?
How...
how is that right?
- You know it doesn't work
like that.
- Doesn't it?
I mean, I'm a cop.
If I risk my life
every day for 30 years,
I get to retire, Barr.
I get to go home
to the woman I love.
I get to proudly watch
my baby girl
grow up each and every day.
I get a life, Barr.
You're a hero.
What do you get?
Nothing?
It's just...
Damn it.
It's not right.
We...the world...
the world owes you.
You deserve better than this.
- No, I don't.
I'm grateful
for everything that I have.
All the blessings in my life.
For Iris, the team.
I mean, hell...
I'm the Flash.
I'm grateful for that.
♪ ♪
But you...
You're what
I'm most grateful for.
If it weren't for you...
your patience, your courage...
The will just to keep going.
I learned all that from you.
More than anyone else,
before the team,
before Iris...
you were the one
that showed me
what it takes just to...
be a good person.
You're one
of the biggest reasons
I was even able
to become the Flash.
For that,
I'll always be grateful.
- [sniffles]
[somber dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[crying]
Barr, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready for this.
It's not...
- It's okay, man.
It's all right.
- No.
I know you...
I know you say
it has to happen, but...
- It's all right.
It's okay.
I'm never gonna leave you.
Even when I'm gone.
♪ ♪
[electronic beeping]
- [exhales]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Let's try this.
[beeping]
[exhales]
♪ ♪
So this is where
you've been hiding.
[chuckles]
Time to pay a house call.
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.