You little brats, beat it!
Hey...!
It should have been me!
I should be the one
going to that Jap's house.
You'll miss the train.
Hurry.
PART ONE
'Kouzuki Noriaki'
Go back to sleep.
We're still far from the house.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Okju.
This property has
three buildings.
A Western-style wing
by an English architect
and a Japanese wing
form the main house.
Not even in Japan is there
a building combining two styles.
It reflects Master's
admiration for Japan and England.
Next is the annex
which Master
had furnished as a library.
Last, the servants' quarters.
As the Lady's handmaiden,
you won't sleep there.
You may eat her leftover food,
but tea leaves go
to the kitchen girls.
Used soap
is for the steward.
Anyone caught pilfering
is expelled that day.
I'm sure you wouldn't dare,
Tamako.
"Tamako" is you.
Your name Okju in Japanese.
- Call me Sasaki.
- Yes, ma'am.
The Lady's routine is simple.
Taking a walk, or reading for Master.
Among the richest men,
Master is the greatest book lover.
And among book lovers,
he is the richest.
His ties to the colonial government
even let us use electricity.
In such a home,
you know what's expected
of a maid like you?
Don't be alarmed at the blackouts.
I sleep in here?
Miss Hideko wakes easily
on account of her nerves.
She's behind this door?
Mother!
Miss!
Miss, are you alright?
Junko! Is that you?
Junko was kicked out, Miss.
I'm the new girl.
Seems you had a bad dream.
You see that big cherry tree?
My aunt went mad
and hanged herself there.
Sometimes on moonless nights,
my aunt's ghost
dangles from that branch.
Here, drink up.
When babies cry, my auntie
feeds them a spoonful of sake.
Sweet bird, sweet bird
My sweet bluebird
What scent is this,
that fills my nose?
You think I'm Tamako,
a poor Korean handmaiden.
But my real name's
Nam Sookee.
Raised by Miss Boksun,
top purveyor of stolen goods.
I was able at age 5 to tell
a real coin from a fake.
Then learned to forge stamps
from Gugai,
and studied pickpocketing
from Kutan,
but these babies will never
learn such useful skills.
Abandoned as newborns,
we'll wash and feed them,
then sell them to Japan.
Such meaningful work.
Instead of starving, they grow up
gentlemen and ladies.
Kutan only breastfeeds her own kid.
I wouldn't be so miserly.
I wish my breasts gave milk.
I'd breastfeed all of them.
I'll tell you the story
of an interpreter,
who bribed his way into
translating for high officials.
After helping Japan annex Korea,
he got rights to a gold mine.
Now he wants to turn
fully Japanese.
So he gets naturalized,
marries the daughter
of a fallen Japanese noble,
and adopts his wife's
family name Kouzuki.
Ba... Bas...
Bastard builds a mansion,
fills it with books and antiques.
He invites Japanese collectors
to his library,
holds readings of rare books,
and auctions the books off.
He loves books and paintings
like his own flesh,
but he can't help
parting with a few.
What to do, when he must sell,
but can't bear to?
He sells a fake.
He seeks out a specialist
to create intricate forgeries.
Unlike him this specialist...
is a real Japanese,
of noble birth!
Count Fujiwara from Nagoya.
So, who is this?
It's the wife.
His Japanese wife.
- You'll seduce her...
- Is she pretty?
The Jap wife died ages ago
with no children.
But the dead wife's
dead sister's living daughter
performs those book readings.
But is she pretty?
An orphan.
Her father was rich.
Soon she'll fall in love with me,
and we'll elope to Japan.
After marrying her there,
and inheriting her fortune,
I'll declare her insane
and lock her up in a madhouse.
Right!
Sookee will be my mouse,
work as her maid, eavesdrop on her,
stay by her side and gently
persuade her to fall in love.
Love?
What does a crook
know about love?
What of her fortune?
She's rich?
Each night in bed I think
of her assets.
1.5 million in cash.
300,000 in bonds.
The uncle is just a guardian.
It's Hideko's fortune.
That's why Kouzuki
schemes to marry the girl.
To his w...wife's niece?
What a s...sick f...f...
Right, a sick fuck.
So what's our share?
I'll share 50,000.
Sookee gets the
dresses and jewellery.
I'll do it! Take me!
My Japanese is better,
and I worked as a maid!
On top of the fifty,
I get dresses, jewellery
and my own 100,000.
She must be crazy...
Crazy? Not a bit.
I'll take my fortune
and flee this country.
Endure these country yokels
a bit longer.
Those fuckers.
This is Tamako.
I am at your service.
Miss...
Bloody hell.
He should've told me
she was so pretty.
I'm completely flummoxed.
A reference letter
from Lady Minami,
my last mistress.
Here's the letter.
Pay attention.
"Dear Miss Izumi Hideko,
Count Fujiwara has informed me
of your urgent need for a maid.
A maid is like
a pair of chopsticks.
Her presence is little noted, but
her absence causes much distress."
So is this place to your liking?
The sun scarcely ever shines here.
Uncle won't permit it.
Sunlight causes books to fade.
One could never grow fond
of such a dreary place.
Not a good liar, are you?
I'll take my leave.
My head aches before
every reading practice.
Would you read it to me?
Pardon?
Oh, how kind of her.
Lady Minami said such
nice things about me!
Is that so?
You're a Japanese lady,
why don't you speak Japanese?
I'm sick of it.
The books he makes me read
are all Japanese.
So read that for me.
"Dear Miss Izumi Hideko,
Count Fujiwara said
you're looking for a maid.
Maids are like...
a spoon... no...
are like chopsticks...
Is it a spoon?
I don't know how to read, Miss.
Not at all?
What about Korean?
This is your name.
Can't you read it?
Reading can be learned,
and I don't care if you
curse or steal.
But don't ever lie to me.
Understood?
Yes, Miss.
My mum.
She's beautiful,
quite the charmer!
And me?
Am I "quite the charmer?"
Everyone says I can't
compare to my mother.
Count Fujiwara said...
So you've met the Count?
Pardon?
No, I never met him...
My aunt!
I heard it from my aunt.
She was his nanny.
What did the Count
say about me?
He said your face...
Every night in bed he thinks
of your assets... your face.
Why in bed, I wonder?
What's with your foot?
I've nowhere to go.
I've just stayed in this house
since coming to Korea at age 5.
But in new shoes, even
well-trodden paths feel fresh.
The ones from here
up to here
should fit you.
Time for reading practice.
I'll go alone.
Miss?
But rain is falling.
At noon, come knock
on the door. Promise?
See you at...
See you later.
What's this?
Why would the lady
of such a big house...?
Did the big house
make her go mad?
My new handmaiden.
The snake, the snake!
You mustn't pass that point.
Be warned!
The snake marks the
'bounds of knowledge'.
A snake!
The Count?
Today?
That's why you insisted
on a bath.
My aunt, when she heard
a guest was coming,
dropped everything and
bathed her Baby Miss.
Nothing made her happier than when
guests praised her baby's scent.
You are my Baby Miss.
Auntie gave the babies
candy during baths.
To teach them that
bath time is sweet.
What's wrong?
One of my teeth is sharp.
It keeps cutting me.
So this was the scent.
All smooth.
Welcome, sir!
You are too kind to greet me
this way upon my arrival,
when the journey has
left me so unkempt.
Now your tedium is over.
I'll ensure your painting
lessons are stimulating.
This must be Okju.
At your service, milord.
You know if you fail, it'll put
me in an awkward position?
A decent bone structure
for a Korean...
So, are you carrying out
your duties faithfully?
Count Fujiwara asks Miss Hideko
to kindly allow her maid Tamako
to be sent to his Lordship
for a brief errand.
Did you call for me, milord?
You may enter.
Everyone's talking
about you in Eunpo.
How you'll be an even
greater thief than your mum.
Who believes the talk
of a swindler?
"fully ripe",
arrange for her and I
to be alone.
Then I'll gobble her up
to the pit.
She's so naive,
even if a man pulls on her nipples
she won't know what he wants.
So it's your job to tell her
that everything
is because of me.
"Oh my,
since the Count arrived,
your toenails
are growing much faster!"
That sort of thing, all right?
Here, a gift.
Oh, he's so thoughtful!
That'll be mine when
she goes to the madhouse.
It pains my heart
to see this poor girl.
Have you ever seen
sapphires so blue?
Let's take a look...
This isn't a sapphire,
it's blue spinel.
It's all right, Miss.
Spinels are expensive too.
How do you know...?
Oh, my Auntie... I mean,
Lady Minami taught me.
But it's fine!
No need to be
ashamed at all.
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart.
Is that so?
Of all the things
I've washed and dressed,
has anything been this pretty?
I'd like to show her to
the people at home.
What would they say?
Probably this?
Mesmerising!
S...Spellbindingly beautiful!
He's shameless.
B...b...beautiful!
I...I...I'm flummoxed
in your presence!
If you stutter like that
and make your face go red,
those uppity bitches
will feel superior,
and then they'll open
up to you, all right?
You try it.
One, two, three!
The Count kept pushing
wine on me.
Does it feel okay?
It's suffocating.
How do ladies wear such things?
You think this is suffocating?
Miss, you're killing me!
Dressed up,
you look like a lady, too.
I think I know
what the Count meant.
Your face...
Each night in bed,
I think of your face.
Don't be silly, Miss.
Ladies truly are
the dolls of maids.
All these buttons
are for my amusement.
If I undo the buttons
and pull out the cords,
then, the sweet things within,
those sweet and soft things...
If I were still a pickpocket
I'd slip my hand inside...
Miss, are you truly
going to marry your uncle?
That's what he raised me for,
knowing he'd need my fortune.
There's a famous collector
in France.
He'll be putting his entire
library up for auction.
The gold mine's proceeds
won't cover the cost.
If it were me, I'd sell books
to buy gold, not the opposite.
For now,
the Lady needn't go read
to the sick fuck
who wants to marry
his wife's niece.
Instead the fake Count goes to
the Library to make fake books.
The Lady waits for her
2 o'clock art class,
and waits...
Poor girl,
losing her heart to a fake.
Please, Count!
Sorry to be late.
It's no matter.
Maybe I need more practice
to give it dimensionality?
Dimensionality... perhaps.
Nonetheless, you have a vision
that transcends mere skill.
As if you see directly
into an object's essence.
For example, the fact that this
peach contains a lot of water.
I hesitate to stand before you,
for fear that you might
read my thoughts.
That's enough for today.
Almost fully ripe.
Already?
Damn...
Do you know what?
Since the Count arrived,
your cheeks have grown flushed.
Have they?
How did your mum die?
When I was a baby, at a
big house, she was hanged...
- I mean, she hanged...
- Hanged herself? Like my aunt.
Well, pretty much.
Still, while alive
she hugged you a lot?
My mother died
giving birth to me.
So it's as if
I strangled her myself.
I wish I'd never been born.
No baby is ever guilty
of being born.
If your mother thought you
could understand
this is what she'd have said.
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Did my mum cry
before they hanged her?
Your mother stole
a thousand times,
was caught just once,
and died once.
Did she cry?
She laughed.
Said she was lucky
to have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Wait here a moment, Miss.
I'll go pick mushrooms.
We'll have mushroom stew
tonight, you like that.
I'll go with you.
I'll be quick.
Before it rains.
Good girl...
What a coincidence.
Indeed.
May I sit by you?
The lady sits, shy and trembling.
The gentleman is persistent.
The perceptive maid
has stepped out for a moment.
All is well, Sookee.
Everyone's performing
their roles so damned well.
Fucking hell.
You know servants
can't use this entrance!
Hey!
I wish I'd never come here.
It was wrong to come.
Tamako, you brought
watercolours, right?
Of course, milord!
Watercolour paints and brushes...
Go and get the oils.
A day like this demands oils, yes!
A blackout!
Bring a lantern.
Yes, ma'am.
Hurry!
I need to think.
I need to become rich,
sail off to a distant harbour,
eat food I scarcely recognise,
buy my fill of
glittering baubles, and...
not think of Hideko.
Never think of Hideko...
I returned and you didn't
even come to me?
It was late, I must have slept.
My apologies.
You know how hard it is
to do those readings?
Must I remove makeup and
change clothes all by myself?
I feel a nightmare coming.
Sleep here.
He proposed to me.
Next full moon,
when my uncle visits his mine,
he wants to elope to Japan.
What did you say?
I said I wasn't sure.
Why?
I'm scared.
Of your uncle's anger?
Of the Count.
What's to be scared of?
He's so kind.
I don't know, I just feel it.
Like the reflex of pulling
your hand from a flame.
Tell me...
What is it that men want?
Pardon?
I mean after getting married,
at night...
How would I know?
I'm practically a child.
With no mother.
No one here to...
First,
I guess we'd kiss?
What the hell.
I'll show her one thing then
put her to bed.
Poor thing,
alone in a strange country,
reading those useless books,
without learning
a single useful skill.
Why does the candy
taste different?
The bitter turned sour,
the sour turned sweet,
the sweet turned savoury...
How do you know all this?
You must have experience?
My friend Kutan taught me.
Taught you?
In words?
Yes, only in words.
So this is how it feels.
That's what you will
feel for the Count.
Really?
The Count, truly...
He won't think
he's making love to a corpse?
You know about my
cold hands and feet.
Really?
Here.
Feels just fine.
You like it?
Do it to me.
I want to know how it feels.
I'm sure he'll want
to do this too.
And then...
It's so cute.
If the Count sees this...
Will he really be
so tender as this?
Of course.
And he'll touch you like this.
And like this...
Keep doing it
like the Count would.
And this is what he'll say.
It's so soft, warm,
wet, and...
s...s...spellbindingly beautiful!
Okju.
Hideko.
Mummy.
Daddy.
Now, the model must stay still.
Okju.
- Hideko...
- Wait.
Stop!
...doesn't like it,
you damned scoundrel!
Stop it!
I can't do this.
Come here, Tamako.
Find some other job to do.
You catch my meaning?
I've no other job to do.
My job is to
look after the Lady.
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's fully ripe! Fully ripe!
If I miss this fortnight,
I'm finished!
Can you feel it?
How much I want it?
After fighting so hard to escape
my garbage heap of a life,
you think I'll let you
fuck it up, you bitch?
Shall I tell the Lady you're
nothing but a lowly pickpocket?
Fine, I'll have something
to tell her too.
That you're nothing but the son of
a lowly Korean farmhand and shaman...
Sookee.
Think of your family at home.
Boksun raising babies with her
bad back, and those two halfwits.
How will they feel if
you go home empty-handed?
Want to shit
on your mother's legend?
You should go home in glory.
So don't push Hideko too hard.
She's got no one
on this earth.
If you frighten her,
she'll close up hard as a clam.
And please...
Don't ever again put my hand
on your tiny joke of a cock.
Oh my.
Your toenails have grown faster since
the Count arrived.
How curious.
Miss, doesn't it bother you
not to know?
How many ships sail
on the wide sea...
People leaving,
people returning,
those saying farewell
or welcome back.
What's the farthest
you've travelled?
The hill beyond the manor?
I could be content here,
if you were with me.
You're fortunate, Miss.
The man who loves you
has the power to protect you.
That's rare.
But I'm not sure...
if I love him.
You do love him.
How do you know?
You stare out the window all day.
Turn in your sleep and sigh.
And your toenails.
Even if I say I don't love him,
if I say that
I love someone else...
Me, who has no one
on this earth...
Do you still want me
to marry him?
You will love him.
Miss!
In the end,
Hideko accepted the proposal,
provided that I come to Japan too.
The Count, after feigning
annoyance for a bit,
nodded his head.
On the day her Uncle left
to visit his mine,
the Count pretended to go back
to Japan, and hid nearby.
You'll have a week of freedom,
but always remember
the basement.
Miss!
Thank you for travelling
on our ferry today.
We will arrive at Shimonoseki
at 7:30 pm...
Finally we're going home.
It's been three years...
To not steal...
To not commit adultery...
To not lie...
Spider thread pulled
into strings
Strumming makes
a zither sing
Thousand woes
Under the blue sky
Only the crows cry
How sorrowful my zither
My beloved zither
Did you sleep well?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
The Count paid the innkeeper to spy
on us, afraid we might run off.
Why get dressed?
I've nothing to do anyway.
Things are moving too slowly.
I fear Hideko might
truly go mad.
Shall we play 'maid',
like before?
From morning to night
we see no sign of the Count.
Certifying the marriage and
converting the inheritance to cash
require much work, he says.
How cruel can you be?
You plucked the flower,
now re-plant it.
What do you want?
Hurry up and throw her
into the madhouse!
A week here...
Then finally...
This way.
Who is that person?
The Countess Lady Fujiwara.
Her maiden name was
Izumi Hideko.
And who might you be?
I am the Lady's handmaiden.
Then, what kind of treatment
do you believe
your Lady requires?
She should be confined in a place
where no one can harm her,
and where she can do no harm.
Just a few tests, then let's have
lamb chops at the Peace Hotel.
Almost there.
Good work.
Don't be frightened.
Good day, Countess.
Do you remember me?
Countess?
What is this?
We mean you no harm, Countess.
We're going to look after you.
You've got the wrong person.
She is the Countess.
Tell them, Your Lordship!
She still believes
she's a Korean handmaiden.
It's because
her nanny was Korean.
You scoundrel!
Let go of me,
you filthy bitches!
We do not use such language here,
your Ladyship.
Miss!
My poor Lady,
she's gone nutty.
If it's any help,
this is from her mammy,
and she used to cherish it
before going mad.
Such a considerate maid.
You thought
Hideko a lamb.
Lamb, my arse.
I tell you, right from
the start Miss Izumi Hideko...
had always been...
Miss!
...a rotten bitch.
PART TWO
I'm not a rotten bitch!
No! No!
Put it in your mouth, Hideko.
Hold out your hand.
Next time you feel
like talking back,
remember the taste
of this metal bead.
You'll sleep alone from tonight.
All right?
Please give me a light.
We've been ordered to save oil.
You little brat.
Speak Japanese!
In there is a man
the size of an ogre
who can't stand the sound
of girls screaming.
If he hears you, he'll burst in
through that door after you.
And then?
He'll smother you
with his giant body.
So you can't make a sound.
Aunt.
My, my.
Scaring a little girl like that.
And me?
Am I pretty too?
Look closely.
Everyone says
I can't compare
to my big sister.
Day.
Night.
Man.
Woman.
Eye.
Nose.
Mouth.
Ear.
Shoulder.
Nipple.
Navel.
Eye.
Nose.
Mouth.
Ear.
Shoulder.
Nipple.
Navel.
Penis.
Vagina.
P...penis.
You think if you speak Korean,
I won't understand?
I was going a bit crazy,
so I made them crazy too.
When Mrs. Sasaki
looked as crazy as me,
life was more bearable.
I know you are a bit insane.
It runs in your mother's family.
That's why I'm training you.
To set your mind right.
If I fail, there's a place called
a "mental hospital" in Japan.
Established by
the rational Germans,
it's very effective
in treating lunacy.
They dig holes in the dirt,
put a patient in each one,
and put lids on top.
If patients improve
they get a leash,
so they can crawl
around like dogs.
The cherry tree that came
with me on the ship from Japan
bloomed twice.
"When Jinlian finally
took off her clothes,
Ximen-Qing-examined
her-Jade-Gate...
to-find-it-hairless-white-as-snow
and-smooth-as-jade..."
You must pause between words.
Don't read like a dog
lapping at his plate!
Listen to your aunt read.
"When Jinlian finally
took off her clothes,
Ximen Qing examined
her Jade Gate,
'Discovering the Secret Well'
to find it hairless,
white as snow,
and smooth as jade.
Tight as a drum,
and soft as silk.
Once he drew apart
the curtains of flesh,
a scent of well-aged wine
emanated from within,
and on fold upon fold
of the red velvet interior
beads of dew were forming.
Its centre was dark and void,
yet as if it had its own life,
it twitched and twitched."
Everyone wanted to cut it down,
but my uncle refused.
He said this tree from Mt. Fuji
had absorbed my aunt's soul.
The servants whispered it was
due to the tree's high cost,
but I think my uncle was right.
You can tell
from the cherry blossoms,
which turned brighter
and bloomed longer.
"Tell me, Juliette.
Do you wish this impetuous
young knight to save you?
The duchess shook
her head resolutely,
to my great disappointment.
Now...
...my brave knight."
Oh, it's a new face!
"Now...
...my brave knight.
When you see these old scars
and the fresh pink wounds,
what do you feel?
I pity the poor woman.
I wish to lick her and lick her,
caress her and caress her.
If you pity her so,
why not take her place
and let her whip you?
The duchess raised the whip
high in the air, and then...
And again...
My cock became painfully erect.
If she could be yours
for ten minutes,
what would you give
in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires.
Anything in this whole wide world.
Once the duke untied me,
I sat on the chair,
pulled her to me,
and slid my cock
into her cunt.
Oh, Juliette, Juliette...
As I felt the duke approach
from behind,
a rope slithered
around my neck.
The duke slowly
tightened the rope.
Like a drowning man
grasping at straws,
I pulled the swirling
currents of her hair.
Then the duke spoke.
The ten minutes are almost up.
Slowly, my dear,
said the Duchess...
I haven't yet
fully savoured his pain.
No, the knight cried,
don't stop!
Please let me die
in the midst of this pain.
In this suffocating pain."
Is it Sade?
It's Sade-esque.
Believed to be the same Japanese
man who wrote 'The Lizard Skin'.
Acquired from a Japanese sailor
on a ship from Hamburg.
Can you imagine my joy when,
after such a journey, it sat
on my shelf with its brothers?
These are the babes
to whom I feel the most affection.
It used to contain an elaborate
monochrome woodcut illustration,
but as you can see...
So unfortunate.
If that were intact,
you could've named your price.
The author felt words alone could
not fully describe the positions,
and so included an illustration.
In that regard,
before we start the bidding.
Hideko!
'Pain is a Garment'
Beautiful!
See you again.
Yes, thank you.
Today's reading was outstanding.
Especially the puppet!
You are of noble birth,
yet you engage in the lowly work
of copying paintings.
There was a time when
I dissipated my wit and skills
on gambling.
Imagine the torment
of having so many women
make advances on me,
when I couldn't afford to
buy them a glass of Burgundy.
Do the women here
advance on you?
I look at women's eyes.
Only the eyes.
They turn their gaze away,
but then they always look back.
If I were to slide under
someone's covers tonight,
only one woman here
would refuse me.
Does that include Mrs. Sasaki?
Is she not your former wife?
You left her to marry
a Japanese woman.
But the servants tell me
you still share a bed with her.
You went so far as to
abandon your wife,
why this urge
to become Japanese?
Because Korea is ugly
and Japan is beautiful.
Some Japanese say
Japan is ugly,
and Korea is beautiful.
Beauty is cruel by nature.
Korea is soft, slow, dull,
and therefore hopeless.
Does it include Mrs. Sasaki?
If I gave her the right signal,
she'd knock on my door
without her underwear.
My thoughts exactly.
Then who is it?
The one who would deny you?
I heard you own
the highest quality
antique bookmaking tools
of East and West,
but I don't see them here?
Who would deny you?
I met Hideko's eyes by chance,
but she didn't look away.
Indeed it was I
who shifted my gaze.
Will she make an appearance
in your lewd dreams tonight?
Even if honoured
with such a visit,
I don't think I could consummate.
Because her body
would be as cold as waterfowl.
The result of long training.
I heard you are engaged to her.
If I'm not mistaken,
you are yet to have intercourse?
Her eyes have no desire.
It means her soul
is dead inside.
You should go easy
on her training,
unless you enjoy
making love to a corpse.
My particular way
of possessing beauty.
Hideko too must have
received painting lessons?
I was too occupied teaching
her to read with correct diction.
Dear me!
In England, where I studied,
all ladies were expected to produce
vibrant colour and graceful lines,
even in the less noble families.
A phone call, sir.
At this hour?
It's the Iwamura Bookstore.
Is that so?
Excuse me a moment.
You are mesmerising.
Men use the word "mesmerising"
when they wish to touch
a lady's breasts.
I'm familiar with
Western conversational etiquette.
I do a bit of reading,
you know.
There was no calculation
in what I said.
It was a reflex, like pulling
one's hand from a flame.
I'm no flame.
I'm cold as waterfowl,
your Lordship.
He will return soon.
Mr. Iwamura only called
with a frivolous inquiry,
at my request.
There's an issue regarding
your future you should know.
I'll wait by the stone lamp
at midnight.
That Iwamura is a real fool.
My maid is asleep
in the room next door.
I don't fancy being in
scandalous rumours with you.
I saw Junko go to the
servants' quarters with her pillow.
Consider your reputation
as a nobleman.
I'm no nobleman.
I'm not even Japanese.
Think it was easy for a Korean
farmhand's son to reach here?
Fifteen hard years in Japan
before hearing about you.
Another three years to prepare.
I studied bookmaking
and learned to paint forgeries.
All so that I could meet you.
To seduce and marry you,
to possess your
father's inheritance,
and then probably
to get rid of you.
But I knew as soon as I met you.
For a man to seduce you
would be...
...impossible.
So in place of seduction,
I decided to propose a deal.
Most marriages are prison,
but this one will free you.
I'll rescue you from here,
take you far away,
and give you freedom.
Of course,
we'll split the money.
Nonsense.
Marrying an old man with a black
tongue at your tender age makes sense?
I won't marry anyone.
What have you in mind?
That's not proper.
There's no beauty in that.
If you kill yourself,
what of your fortune?
That will be the sum of your efforts?
Your fortune going to a pervert?
So he can buy 10 little girls
and teach them to read books?
My uncle will find us somehow.
Then he'll take us
to the basement.
Uncle.
The basement?
It says here
when people are hanged,
their tongues stick out
and faeces is expelled.
But that day,
Aunt's mouth was shut
and her bottom was clean.
Want to go somewhere nice?
I'll tell you in detail
what I did to your aunt
after I caught her
running away.
So don't you ever think
of running, understood?
That day I just
watched and listened.
But if I ever
end up there again...
Highly concentrated opium.
Three drops will make you
sleep all day.
Five drops will
knock down a horse.
If you crave death
within five minutes,
drink it all.
If you carry this, he can never
take you to the basement.
At least not alive.
It'll be my wedding gift to you.
It's more expensive than jewels.
Bring a girl to be my maid. One who
could disappear and not be missed.
If a bit dense, all the better.
We'll send her to a madhouse
under my name.
I can find you a new maid,
but what do we do
about Junko?
You really think I'm prettier
than Miss Hideko?
Sure, Hideko's pretty,
and you're pretty.
What?
You speak Korean?
You know...
I learned it.
To speak more easily with you.
I really wanted to
say this to you.
You are just mesmerising.
Oh my gosh!
You little tart!
I can't!
If they catch me with a guest,
I'll be thrown out!
Forget this wretched place.
Come live with me!
Oh, fucking hell!
Fucking hell?
Fucking hell...
The Count sent
exactly what I ordered.
Naive and a bit foolish.
Mother!
Show Sookee your clothes and
jewellery at every opportunity.
The material greed she got from her
mother will make her more gullible.
P.S. Don't worry if she reads this
letter, she's totally illiterate.
Would you read it to me?
Pardon?
'Countess Fujiwara Hideko'
This is your name.
Can't you read it?
What's with your foot?
Who did it?
Who took Tamako's shoe?
Apologise before all the servants!
If she ever runs away
because of one of you,
I'll strip you all naked
and throw you out!
Fucking hell.
All smooth.
You like the scent?
Want to come in?
Pardon?
No need to be
ashamed at all.
Your average fence
can barely tell them apart.
Is that so?
Returning the earrings
you loaned me.
A woman might wager her fate
on such an exquisite pair.
I'm sure that Sookee
will try her very best
in order to see herself
wearing these in the mirror.
I'll tell you how to keep her
from getting suspicious.
Keep her busy until
the day of the wedding.
Make her spend all her energy
on making you
fall in love with me.
In other words, don't fall
in love with me so easily.
Me?
Dressed up,
you look like a lady too.
How did your mum die?
That she was so lucky
to have you before dying.
That she had no regrets.
Is this the companionship
they write about in books?
Men are disgusting.
How can they be so
single-minded?
What's on my mind?
You don't really believe
that I crave your body?
You do!
You read too many
of those books.
If there's one thing
I'm after, Miss...
It's not your eyes,
your hands or ass,
it's your money, only that.
Of all that you have,
money is the best.
Feels great being so rude
to a noble lady.
What's with her?
Why does she stomp her feet,
expressing her anger,
sit up in the middle
of the night and sigh?
Every time she sees the Count,
her eyes seem to say...
I despise you.
Try to bear it. Only if she sees this
will she believe the proposal.
Think of me as that puppet,
and I'll imagine another woman.
What woman?
The duchess Juliette.
Lady!
Milord!
Lady...
"The lady's emotions
lay deep inside...
Jinlian could not fathom
their depths.
Knowing this, Lady Sun
gave Jinlian four
small silver balls.
These are 'minling',
or 'bells of passion.'
Place two in
the lady's Jade Gate,
and the other two in yours.
Spread your legs apart
and like two scissors
trying to cut each other,
put them together.
When the lips below
rub against each another,
you'll hear
a clear ringing sound.
A blackout!
Bring a lantern!
Yes, sir!
'The Sound of Bells
on a Windless Night'
When do I put this in?
asked Jinlian.
Does the lady breathe deeply
and swallow hard?
Does she whisper sweetly
in your ear,
and kiss you?
Does she embrace you tightly
and caress your nipples?
Does her secret part
become slippery
as she gently bites
your shoulder?
Then, put in the bells."
- Amazing!
- Indeed!
It's so cute.
If the Count sees this...
Will he really be
so tender as this?
Of course.
And he'll touch you like this...
And like this...
Tamako, keep doing it.
Like the Count would.
The Count...
He'll go crazy over this.
And this is what he'll say.
It's so soft, warm,
wet, and...
s...s...spellbindingly beautiful!
Shall I teach you more, Miss?
Yes...
Teach me everything.
I wish that I had breast milk
so I could feed you.
Do you like it when I do this?
Do you like me?
Can you promise
that you won't betray me?
I'll never...
never...
ever...
Miss, how could such an innocent...
You must be a natural.
Stop!
I spit it out without chewing!
All because of you!
She's got no one
on this earth.
If you frighten her,
she'll close up hard as a clam.
You see?
If you don't give the impression
you want this marriage,
she may throw another fit
and refuse to go forward.
Be more convincing
when you pretend to love me.
I can't do it.
What?
I want to quit.
What's with you all today?
You feel sorry for her?
What is it with women?
You know what that poor
Sookee said about your Ladyship?
That you're too dense to get it
if someone pulls on your nipples.
That she was nice out of pity,
but you ate it up.
That you were so gullible!
That naive servant's face...
Yes... you will love him.
If I say that
I love someone else...
Me, who has no one
on this earth...
Do you still want me
to marry him?
Yes.
Miss!
I wish I'd never been born.
Let go.
Miss, I'm sorry!
Let go!
I'm sorry, Miss!
Don't die.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
I tried to trick you into
marrying that bastard.
I was going to put you
in a madhouse and run off.
Don't die.
Don't get married, Miss!
Sookee,
are you worried about me?
I'm worried about you.
How do you know my name?
You think you're tricking me?
You're the one being tricked.
You're the one
bound for the madhouse.
I was going to lock you up
in there under my name,
then I'd become you
and run far away, with him.
I won't say sorry,
since you tried to trick me too.
That fucking son of a bitch!
Oh, sorry Miss!
"I hope this letter finds you well.
This is Sookee.
I'm writing to inform you
of a change in plans.
I decided to team up
with the Lady Hideko.
As such, I'm now in need
of all your help.
I'm enclosing an item
as advance payment."
Always remember
the basement.
Want to go somewhere nice?
You didn't teach me
to read Japanese.
Did that bastard draw this?
Is this what you've been reading
to that dirty old man
and those gentlemen?
The daughter of
a legendary thief,
who sewed winter coats
out of stolen purses.
Herself a thief,
pickpocket, swindler.
The saviour who came to
tear my life apart.
My Tamako.
My Sookee.
You scoundrel!
Let go of me,
you filthy bitches!
Miss!
Let go!
I'm hungry.
The first month, I ordered
a slim herringbone suit.
PART THREE
The next month, I wore it to
dine at the Imperial Hotel.
Me, a colonial boy working
as a tout at a brothel.
Some Englishmen who frequented
the brothel recognised me.
I thought they'd call the
matre d' and kick me out,
but what do you know?
They were amused
I'd spend a month's pay
on one dignified meal.
They started calling me 'Count'
and taught me manners
to go with the name.
Frankly, I'm not that
interested in money itself.
What I desire is,
how shall I put it...
The manner of ordering wine
without looking at the price?
Something like that.
Fourteen hours by train
from Vladivostok
is the summer home of a
genuine Russian noble family.
Shall we marry there?
In a few days I'll hear
from the hospital.
That my wife Fujiwara Hideko
has died.
You didn't just ask them
to keep her?
I doubt Sookee would want
to live there very long.
Fuck!
I arranged it with
a photography studio.
We'll replace this with
your photograph.
From tomorrow,
we'll give Sookee a new life.
I'm glad.
Marry me once again.
This time as Nam Sookee.
You want another wedding night?
I think I like you... slightly.
Poor Sookee,
in a place like that
all by herself...
Did such a thought
ever cross your mind?
Not at all.
Why should I pity her?
Where I come from,
it's illegal to be naive.
Where you come from, it's not naive
to fall in love with a business partner?
Of course. It's illegal.
So even if my love for you
leads me to ruin,
don't pity me.
Love?
What does a crook
know about love?
Fire!
C...c...come this way!
This way!
Because you desired me,
and overcame
all obstacles to reach me,
I have been born anew,
it's true.
I'm grateful for that.
I'll allow a kiss.
No.
Why not?
I don't like
kisses with conditions.
I never learned
how to stop halfway.
After this I'll thrust in deep,
to your navel.
Please do that.
Those aren't the eyes
of one who wants it.
You know you can't
deceive me in such matters.
If I could be yours
for ten minutes,
what would you give
in exchange?
Whatever your heart desires.
Anything in this whole wide world.
There's much
I want to teach you.
You'll become a
completely new woman.
It won't hurt.
You know from those books?
In truth, women feel
the greatest pleasure
when taken by force.
Now I'm going to
rip your underwear.
Would you fetch those for me?
Respected Uncle,
it always pained me
to see you straining
to speak flawless Japanese
before the Count from Nagoya,
and even to quiver your voice
like a nobleman.
So I'm happy to inform you
that you no longer need do so.
That man is the son
of a Korean farmhand.
Oh, did my gift arrive safely?
Please tell this to my gift,
in Korean.
I'm afraid that in real life,
no woman feels pleasure
at being taken by force.
But, for sending me Sookee
out of all the girls in the world,
I feel "slightly" grateful.
You wished to see
my bookmaking tools?
Don't just look,
experience them for yourself.
I'll choose five books
that I cherish...
...that I used to cherish
more than anything.
Let's see...
First,
'Confessions of a Whip'
'The Lizard Skin'
'Decadent Girls
Who Sell Lingerie'
May I please
smoke a cigarette, sir?
Sir.
'Bells and Balls'
'The Mortician's Bedroom'
How could you let
a little girl fool you?
But don't worry.
I'll catch them for you soon.
I arranged so that no two girls
travelling together can leave Kobe.
Please change the destination
to Shanghai.
Changing two tickets,
from Vladivostok to Shanghai.
Yes, that's correct.
Show me your passports.
Miss Nam Sookee?
Mr. Go Pan-dol?
You need to pay
an additional 3 yen.
All right.
I'm just an old man
who likes dirty stories.
Even listening to the same story,
people imagine different things.
Peering into each of
those fantasies
was this old man's
humble recreation.
What to do,
now that it's all over?
You should at least
tell me your story.
How did that bitch Hideko taste?
Was she fully ripe?
Tell me.
A cigarette might
help my memory.
Right, right...
You have that silly
penchant for cigarettes?
So how was Hideko?
You have no windows here?
Sookee could be listening in.
Let's do our best.
That's it, good.
What's this?
You can't stop there, dear fellow.
So, where did you touch first?
Her face?
Her breasts?
c...cunt?
Was it soft?
Did it tighten up?
Did it have many wrinkles?
Was it sufficiently wet?
The viscosity and transparency
of her vaginal secretion?
Please, one more cigarette, sir.
Spider thread pulled
into strings...
I dare say no book
has ever described
such a ferocious wedding night.
I thought I heard
a nightingale sing.
And... the clear,
bright crimson blood!
Thus the Lady
became my wife.
Coy one moment,
bold the next...
But how was she coy,
how was she bold,
tell it to me in detail!
A story is all about the journey.
You should know.
Did she resist?
So did you pinch her ass
as punishment?
Or did she spit at you
in contempt?
Or else...
Did she beg you to do it?
'The Widow's Lapdog?'
How dare you!
Hideko is my wife.
What kind of scoundrel rattles on
about his wedding night!
It's odd...
Your smoke.
It's cold, blue...
and strangely beautiful.
You too have become
soft, slow and dull.
Mercury is most deadly
in its gaseous state.
One cigarette
would have sufficed.
At least I will die
with my cock intact.
I hear a sound
in the distance
that sounds like
the steps of my love
An echo that
makes my heart
skip a beat
But I wait
all through the night
and my love never
comes to me
There is no end
to the heartache
that grips me
in this hour
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love
But then in
my waiting heart
suddenly
happiness overflows
There you are
in the distance
coming to me
Filled with dreams
of a new life
filled with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
flowers start to bloom
Come my lover,
come to me
I missed you so
Let's dream of
happy times
like long ago
Filled with dreams
of a new life
filled with happiness
Inside my waiting heart
flowers start to bloom
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love
Waiting for
the footsteps of
my dear love