What do we got, Chester?
Multiple fire alarms
at Ivo Labs.
You know, hopefully, it's not
an overcooked-chicken-tenders
in-the-microwave situation.
I said
I was sorry for that.
Roger that. Yeah, yeah.
It's just, you know, man...
...that smell took us forever
to get out of the lounge.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Fire's already been put out.
Flash, you're back.
I just got here.
No, you didn't.
You sped us out of the way
and then put out the fire
with a wind funnel.
Like you did with The Hotness.
I did?
If it wasn't for your super-speed,
seven years of research would have
gone up in smoke. Literally.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Hey, Flash, what's goin' on?
What are they talkin' about?
I don't know.
I think there may be
a new speedster in town.
A new speedster? You sure?
Those Ivo employees said
someone ran them to safety
and then used a wind funnel
to put the fire out, just like I would.
Well, that sure sounds like a speedster.
Do you have any leads on
to who it might be?
Not yet. August Heart's still
locked up at Iron Heights.
Thawne doesn't have his speed,
he's under heavy guard at A.R.G.U.S.
And all the Velocity-X vials
are secure at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And I still can't reach
Speed Force Nora.
Or any of the other Forces.
Is there more?
Just... Caitlin still hasn't
returned my calls
since I stopped her experiment
to resurrect Frost.
You did more than stop it.
I'm not saying it's wrong,
but Caitlin lost
the most important person
in the world to her,
and she could lose something
just as important.
Hope.
We are gonna be late.
- Oh! Hey.
- Hey.
We've got kindergarten interviews
for Jenna at every school all day.
The competition is crazy fierce.
Um... Oh! Great,
you've got Jenna's backpack.
I have the paperwork,
I have the interview questions.
You and I, we are gonna
go over that in the car. Um...
What are we missing?
Jenna?
Hey.
I need your notes on the profile feature
for Judge Hankerson's retirement.
Already in your inbox.
And here's the briefing I wrote up
for your next field piece.
They're closing Fort Delaney?
That's right up my alley.
Allegra, did you sign off on my...
Expense reports?
Yep, they're with accounting.
- Okay, then.
- Allegra,
I want to run an exposé on
the light meta who works with the Flash.
Okay, I'll leave you to it.
I've been pulling pictures.
Whoever this is,
her face is always hidden by light,
but I think I could ID her
with enough resources.
Maybe she doesn't want to be ID'd.
Well, we don't know that.
And a new hero in town is big news.
- That's why we should run this.
- No.
I mean, it's not right for CCC Media.
Says the temporary editor-in-chief.
I already ran the story by Iris
before she left.
What did she say?
That it was an interesting angle
and she would strongly consider it.
Well, maybe we hold off
on moving forward with it
until she's back.
I don't get it.
I thought you left the Arañas after you
were paroled from Iron Heights.
I did.
But our old gang's trying
to pull me back in.
The Arañas are expanding.
They've taken over
every square inch of Keystone,
and now they want Central City.
The gang's been dropping bodies.
What?
The Arañas aren't killers.
We used to just steal cars.
Not anymore.
Thanks to new leadership,
there's no line they won't cross.
Who are these people?
The kind you don't want to mess with.
Look...
You did me a huge favor
when you wrote that article about me.
And because of you, I was able to
make a new, better life in this city.
And I don't want to give that up.
But I have to leave.
Because the same reason
they want me to run things
is the reason
I won't survive if I turn them down.
Lydia, if what you're saying is true,
we have to stop them
before anyone else gets killed.
We can't.
What if you help
CCC Media break this story?
Like you said,
you know everything about them.
Where they keep their money,
their contacts, their stash houses.
Lydia,
you're the only one
that can help me take them down.
No way. You know what they'd do to me
for snitching?
CCC Media will treat you
as an anonymous source.
We'll protect you.
How?
I know someone who can
run you out of town quick
if something goes south.
Look...
I know you're scared,
but the Arañas,
they operate in the shadows.
The only way to take away their power
is bring them into the light.
Think about
all the other girls in the gangs.
The ones who are trying to get out,
but they can't.
Telling your story
could help them
get their lives back, too.
Okay.
But not here.
And after our interview,
I'm on the first bus out of here.
We'll keep you safe, I promise.
I found Lydia.
Looks like she's skipping town.
That's not all she's doing.
Rawlins,
Lydia's talking to Esperanza's cousin,
the reporter.
We can't let them expose us.
They won't.
No one defies the Arañas and survives.
So, I've been checking S.T.A.R Labs'
satellite readings all day.
Not a stray tachyon to be found.
Our new speedster
isn't using the Speed Force.
And now they're in the wind.
What's wrong?
The fire's origin is here,
but the only thing that
could have started it is this acetone.
Even with an incredibly low flash point,
it would still need an ignition source.
Chester, what if this speedster
was the combustion force?
Oh, snap. Yeah, no.
The friction from their super-speed
would totally be enough
to kick-start a reaction.
And it would explain how they arrived
on scene before you.
Because they started it.
But why?
Look at this biometric lock.
It's broken.
And whatever was inside is MIA,
just like our speedster.
But, man,
the only reason you would need
a temperature-controlled polymer case
like this
would be to hold
a very strong electrochemical cell.
Like Ivo Labs' Newton battery.
It's experimental,
but it's incredibly powerful.
What if the fire was a distraction
so they could steal this?
Damn.
Yeah, okay, I guess we can scratch them
off the nice speedster list.
What do we do now?
We get answers from the one person
who knows villainous speedsters
better than I do.
Which means I'm gonna be off the grid,
so Team Flash is on its own for a while.
You're gonna go see him?
You sure that's a good idea?
I have to know if it's him.
Okay. Yeah, you do you.
We'll be fine here.
This is the Arañas gang.
For years, their M.O. was stealing cars.
It was founded by a teenager in Keystone
who later became known
as the meta-human Ultraviolet.
Now, more recently,
UV has worked alongside Millie Rawlins
and Dr. Kimiyo Hoshi,
aka Sunshine and Dr. Light.
Collectively known
as "The Assassins Three,"
they've worked for Black Hole
and Eva McCulloch.
Only, according to rumors,
Ultraviolet died last year.
And why should we care?
Because I just found out
Sunshine and Dr. Light
are now running the Arañas.
We're talking extortion,
million-dollar thefts
that should be impossible,
and they're leaving a trail of bodies
made from anyone who gets in their way.
And you got all this from one source?
Is there anyone else
who can corroborate her story?
She is all we need.
Which is why we're doing
a live interview with her.
Tonight.
I mean, you can't be serious. We'd have
no time to fact-check her story.
And this source,
how do you even know she's reliable?
- I just do.
- I don't get it.
Why are you so passionate
about this story?
Look, I know this sounds crazy,
but I am telling you
it's the right move.
You just have to trust
that I know what I'm doing.
I'll, uh... I'll go call my babysitter.
I'll DVR the Sharks game.
Okay, let's do this.
Chester, meet Lydia.
Hi.
We've got a skeleton staff tonight,
to protect her identity.
And Lydia, don't worry,
I trust Chuck with my life.
Uh, what do you do around here?
Tonight I'll be running
an AI-generated filter
to conceal your voice and face
during the interview,
so, no worries.
Not even your mom
will recognize you.
I need some water.
Is, uh, she gonna be okay?
Yeah.
What about you?
'Cause reporting on the Arañas,
I know that's a big deal for you.
How did your staff react when
you told them about your connection?
I... I didn't tell them.
Allegra, are you sure
that's the right move?
I need them to trust me.
And if I tell them
I was in the Arañas...
No, I can't risk them
losing faith in me.
This story is too important.
I'm gonna go check on Lydia.
My stomach is doing flip-flops.
You're scared. I get it.
But the risk we're taking,
it's worth it.
Think about your life
before you joined the Arañas.
Hmm. It was rough.
I was on my own,
struggling to get by.
Always wishing to be
a part of something, a family.
And what I didn't know
was that it could get even worse.
Yeah, but somehow
you got out without getting killed.
I might not get so lucky.
- What's happening?
- Get down.
The Arañas.
I knew they'd find me.
Okay, we have to get out of here, now.
Hello, Lydia.
Come on.
Sorry, ladies.
It's the end of the road.
Quick, in here!
You can't keep me out forever.
Who the hell was that?
The Arañas are here. We're under attack.
She's hurt.
I'm on it.
This can't be happening.
We need to get to a secure location.
We're in one. I just activated
a photo-kinetic energy shield
around the whole building.
It's bulletproof, teleport-proof,
basically everything-proof.
How'd you know to do that?
You're just an IT guy.
Back when we were The Citizen,
Dr. Light attacked us.
That's when Sue Dearbon
hired him to secure the building.
Why isn't my phone working?
They must be using a signal jammer
to block communications.
- Frick.
- What is it?
My force field was only meant
to be a temporary shield
until we could call for help.
And now we can't.
Guys, she's back.
I've been in combat.
Knowing where your enemy is
is a good thing.
Now we need a plan.
Chuck, can you
MacGyver something together
to bust through their cell jammers
and call for help?
I can build an oscillating transmitter
to bypass their signals.
Sunshine just flipping disappeared!
Yeah, okay. We need to just remain calm.
Until this force field goes critical,
Hoshi can't fire her photon bullets,
and Sunshine can't teleport in.
How do you know so much about them?
Yeah, Allegra, how do you?
Oh, my God.
We need to talk, Thawne.
You took my speed.
What more do you want?
My body is broken.
I can barely think, I can't sleep.
I used to be able
to run around the world
in five seconds.
Now it takes me at least that long
to cross this stupid cell because...
you took my speed.
You did this to yourself, Thawne.
Armageddon was your plan.
And it should've worked.
But...
it didn't. And now...
I'll have to find a new way to kill you.
Well, you can try.
I've gotten what I need.
Wait, you're out?
Wait, you're leaving me
just like that?
No...
parting gift? No 411
on your precious
"Team Flash"?
And by the way...
it's just
too bad
what happened to Frost, isn't it?
Then again...
she was in over her head
from the beginning, wasn't she?
Yeah, this was a waste of time.
Wait, Allen, don't go.
Come on.
That's no way to treat an old friend.
What do you want, huh?
To see if you were responsible
for something impossible.
And now I know
you couldn't be.
Responsible for what?
What is it?
What scared you so bad
that you had to run all this way
just to be sure I was still here?
I found a new speedster.
Huh.
They can't have Lydia,
so we stick to the plan.
Chuck's working on the transmitter.
And what if they get in here
before he's done?
They threatened to kill us.
She's right. They're an invading force.
We need a plan B.
What, you're already
working on page one?
I'm writing a letter to my kids
in case I die in here, okay?
I give up!
- You hear me? I surrender!
- Lydia. Lydia, stop.
You can't give yourself up.
You...
Open the doors.
What? No. Lydia, they'll kill you.
They're gonna anyways.
Now open the door
so no one else has to die.
Good call.
Lydia, look,
I get what you're trying to do,
and it is damn selfless.
But there's got to be another way, okay?
Don't forget why you came here.
You came here to stop them.
I came here
so no one else would get killed.
Now let me out!
Hey, if she wants to go, let her.
No way!
We can't send someone
out there to die, Taylor.
So what? We're just gonna sit here
instead and wait for them to fry us
or shoot us
or whatever the hell it is they do?
Open the damn doors.
Lydia, I'm the only one
with the code to that shield.
And there's no way in hell
I'm giving it to you.
Which means
we're gonna help you survive this. Okay?
You ain't never getting in.
Now I'm mad.
Wait, wait, wait. Let me take this.
You people are
just as crazy as the Arañas.
We promised to keep her safe.
- You did. I didn't.
- Okay.
We all just need to take a step back
and figure out a new way out of this,
'cause that woman's life
depends on our next move.
And what about our lives?
The Arañas want Lydia, not us.
We turn her over, they'll let us go.
I like that plan.
No, it doesn't matter what we do,
they will not let us go. Not now.
You don't know that.
Look, I saw
the code Chester typed in earlier.
And this is what Lydia wants.
Hey, Lydia is our source.
It is our duty as journalists
to protect her, no matter what,
even from herself.
An ethics lesson from you, really?
Your whole past is unethical.
What's she talking about?
The reason Allegra knows so much
about the Arañas.
They need to know
what you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't.
This is my life, my decision.
Too late.
Right before we were attacked,
I had a contact
take a look at some of Allegra's
sealed juvie records.
And guess what they found?
Our ex-con co-worker
was in a gang
with her cousin, Ultraviolet.
The same gang
that's been killing people in Keystone.
Allegra used to be one of them.
One of the Arañas.
Is this for real?
I am so sorry
that I didn't tell you the truth.
But we have to stick together,
we have to protect Lydia.
Stick together? You lied to us.
And now it's gonna get us killed.
She's right. We can't trust you.
Okay. Once I finish this transmitter,
we can get out of here, okay?
Why couldn't you
just let me go out there?
'Cause you came here
to do something important.
You and Allegra are trying to drag
a bunch of killers out of the darkness
and expose everything they're doing.
And you still can.
Why do you think
Hoshi and Rawlins are still out there?
Because they're scared of you, Lydia.
We need to get that emergency signal
out now, Chuck.
Look, I just need a little more time.
Well, we don't have it.
Taylor just told everyone that I was
in the Arañas, and now no one trusts me.
Plus, she memorized your shield code.
They are this close
to opening those doors.
I never should've taken over
after Iris left.
No, no, this isn't your fault.
Yes, it is.
I am not a leader. I never have been.
You know how Esperanza
and I ended up in juvie?
I had an idea for a job.
We were gonna hit
a bunch of semis at a rest stop.
It was my idea,
so Esperanza put me in charge
of the whole thing.
And I checked the trucks.
And when it came time,
I told the girls it was clear.
But I missed a driver,
and he had a shotgun,
and one of my girls got hit
with a round.
You know what was in that truck?
Lawn furniture.
Chuck, a girl almost died because of me.
I am not cut out to lead anyone.
All I'll do is get people hurt,
or worse.
That's not true.
Look, I was lost when you found me.
I wanted out of the Arañas so bad,
but I couldn't actually do it.
And then you wrote that article
about me.
And seeing how you saw me,
as someone with a future,
it helped me reclaim my life.
And today, I was terrified,
but you inspired me to come here
because when you said
we could take down the Arañas,
I believed you.
I still do.
She's right.
You are a leader.
And not in spite of your past,
but because of it.
You're Allegra freakin' Garcia.
You always know who you are
and what you want to do.
But you can't lead
if you're trying to stay in the dark.
So, Allegra, what do you want to do?
They didn't leave behind
any tachyons after the fire.
Could you tell if they were
- tapping into the Negative Speed Force?
- How could I tell?
You severed my connection, remember?
But you time-traveled
before that. A lot.
Did you ever sense
another speedster in 2022?
Someone trying to hide their abilities?
Can you really not see
how obvious this answer is?
- Are you stupid?
- So enlighten me.
No.
Okay.
I get it.
You don't want to help me
because even after all this...
you're still jealous.
I'm not jealous of you.
- I pity you.
- I meant jealous of them.
- Who?
- This new speedster,
out there living a life you lost.
While you can barely move,
their journey is just beginning.
Yours is already over.
What's it like
knowing you've been replaced?
I won't be replaced.
I will never be replaced,
because no speedster
is ever gonna feel for you what I do!
Hate. Hate.
Hate. Hate!
Pure and infinite hate. I...
hid in plain sight for years
to be next to you,
to be close to you, so I could hurt you.
I devoted my life
so I could destroy yours!
No speedster will ever replace me!
No speedster will ever feel
what I felt.
And because they don't,
this new speedster...
doesn't care about you at all.
And so,
there's another reason
they don't want to be found.
So what is it?
You really don't see it?
I guess I am faster than you after all.
Think about it, Allen.
A new speedster
running through the city streets...
with frightening new speed.
Just like you...
eight years ago.
They're hiding because
they can't control their abilities.
The fire was an accident.
Look, I wish there was another way,
but if we want to survive,
we have to give Lydia over now.
- No.
- Lydia is not going anywhere,
because I have a plan to get us all out.
But for it to work,
I need you to trust me.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
Okay. We don't want to turn Lydia over,
- but Taylor is right.
- I know.
And the truth is, I was ashamed
of being in the Arañas.
And I was afraid if I told you
the truth about my past
that you would stop trusting me.
I thought there was too much at stake
for me to be honest
about who I really am.
But it was lying about my past
and keeping you in the dark
that lost your trust.
So, I'm done hiding.
I'm the light-meta in those photos.
And I've never really
told anyone that before.
You're the one who's always helping
the Flash, the one saving people?
And right now, I'm going to save us.
All you have to do is trust me.
Look,
Allegra is the real deal.
If she says she has a plan, then I'm in.
All in.
Me, too.
So,
who's with me?
This is a photo-kinetic energy shield.
It'll take time to split the bonds.
Not if we have the right weapon.
Give me your ammo.
And now we do.
This is gonna be fun.
Where are they?
Easy, ladies.
We can all still walk out of here
without a sunburn.
We made you a real nice offer, Garcia.
Give up the girl and live.
Yeah. Then when you slink
back into the shadows,
every other body you drop
makes CCC Media responsible?
Not happening.
Hurry, she's buying us time.
Camera and sound are up.
How's the transmitter coming?
- I just need to reset the encoder.
- Well, reset faster.
If this crazy plan of hers
doesn't work...
It will. We just need to trust Allegra.
Nice trick.
But I can feel how hard it is
for you to maintain so much power.
Because you can't beat me, Garcia.
I'm not trying to.
This is a Central City
Citizen Media Special Report.
We're here today
with a very brave young woman,
who's ready to come forward and talk
about the gang activity
in Keystone City.
Lydia Sanchez,
can you tell us about
a group called the Arañas?
I have been living in fear
of the Arañas for a long time.
And even when I agreed
to do this interview,
I didn't want to show my face at first.
But now I realize
they are the ones who should be afraid.
Because we're the ones
dragging them into the light.
So, to all the girls out there
struggling to break free
of their control,
look at me.
I did it.
So can you.
And who's running this gang?
Their names are Millie Rawlins
and Kimiyo Hoshi.
That interview is going out live
to millions of people across the city.
If either of you try
to go after Lydia again
or anyone on my staff,
the whole world will know it was you.
You can go now.
This isn't over.
Bring it on, bitch.
Mr. Runk just showed me
the damage outside,
and it looks like you two
had a rough night.
How are the both of you still alive?
I guess we're just lucky.
Well, Hoshi and Rawlins' luck
is about to run out.
I've got APBs out for both of them
across the whole state.
And the information you provided
helped us
freeze their accounts
and seize their assets.
Which means the Arañas
are out of business.
Do you mind if I ask you
a few more questions at the station?
Lydia, I think,
was trying to catch a bus.
Not anymore.
Twenty million views and counting.
This is our biggest story yet.
Wow.
Guys,
thank you.
I owe you.
Which is why...
Look, if you need to expose
the truth about me,
- I get it.
- Allegra,
you reminded us today
of the oldest rule in the book.
Always protect your sources.
And each other.
We're gonna keep your secret, too.
For as long as you want us to.
Thank you.
Hey, did you put a call
into the Keystone PD Commissioner
- to get a comment about the Arañas?
- Already did.
Let's hit our old contacts
at McCulloch Tech.
- Yes.
- Guys,
it's like 4:00 a.m.
Yeah, that's what the coffee is for.
Plus, we need to get a follow-up out,
right after I call my babysitter.
Probably gonna charge me
a fortune for this.
You're not gonna join them?
Seriously?
You're not firing me for,
you know, everything?
You were trying to save
the lives of your co-workers.
So, no.
Plus,
you're a great investigative reporter.
Thanks for keeping us safe today,
boss.
Hey, those photos of me and Flash,
where did you find them?
Chirper. It's not that hard, really.
Um, Allegra,
I know you're not hiding
from us anymore,
but how long can you hide
from the rest of the world?
Man, you should have seen her
last night.
She totally crushed the leadership game.
I'm talking Janeway-meets-AOC
meets-Angela-Davis-type leadership.
Well, I don't know about Janeway,
but, no, it was really nice
to just be myself.
Feel like I didn't have to hide.
Nice work.
You really stepped up. Both of you.
And if Hoshi or Rawlins
make any more moves,
obviously, I've got your back.
Thanks.
So, how did it go on Lian Yu?
Did you find any answers
on the speedster?
Uh... Yeah, not exactly. I did find some
perspective.
Incoming video message?
Hey, guys.
I wish I could've come back
to S. T.A.R Labs
to tell you all this in person,
but I can't go back there. Not yet.
Barry, when you left my apartment,
I wasn't sure how to feel.
And the truth is, I'm still not.
I just know it hurts.
So, I'm gonna go away
for a little while.
I'm gonna stay with Carla.
For real this time.
I just need some space to think.
And I don't know
when I'll be ready to come back.
So,
until then...
just know that I love you all.
Is she gonna be okay?
Yeah, I think she is.
That's something
you don't see every day.
Someone returning the tech they stole.
Listen, hey, I just want to talk to you.
Listen, I...
I just have some questions.
I can run at the speed
of sound, but you...
Can run a lot faster than that.
Look, the point is, you can't outrun me.
So why don't you just tell me who
you are and what's really going on?
Look, I'm not a super-villain.
That fire was an accident.
I know. But you risked people's lives
to steal a battery.
And I'm so sorry about that.
I'm not a natural speedster like you.
That's why you've been so hard to trace.
- Your speed's temporary.
- Exactly.
You see, my...
associate and I found a way
to generate my own speed source.
I'm still trying to work out the kinks,
so the effects only last a few minutes.
I thought maybe the battery
could help extend the window,
and I figured
why spend another four years
calibrating sodium nitrate cells
when I could just borrow
the one I'd already made?
I designed the original Newton battery
when I was a young engineer
working here at Ivo.
The Newton battery
was invented by Meena Dhawan.
It's Dr. Meena Dhawan, actually.
You're the CEO of Fast Track Labs.
Your book,
Quantum Gravity & the Universe,
I've read it three times.
You're a genius.
That's surprising.
And very flattering.
Unfortunately, this genius intellect
hasn't been any help
in mastering these new abilities.
That's why I've been trying
to take a low profile,
running trials with my team.
The truth is...
I just want to use my gifts
to help people.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
When I first got my speed, I...
I had a mentor.
Someone to coach me
on how to use my powers.
So, if you're interested...
You'd really do that for me?
Thank you.
I promise you won't regret this.