-Three of a kind, let's do this.
-That's it? Three guys?
Two guys on the roof. Every guy gets a share.
Five shares is plenty.
Six shares.
Don't forget the guy who planned the job.
He thinks he can sit it
out and still take a slice.
-I know why they call him the Joker.
-So why do they call him the Joker?
-I heard he wears makeup.
-Makeup?
Yeah, to scare people.
You know, war paint.
All right, everybody,
hands up, heads down!
I said, hands up, heads down!
Let's go, pal,
I'm making a withdrawal here.
-I said, hands up!
-No!
Here comes the silent alarm.
And there it goes.
Heads down!
All right, tootsie,
you're taking a dive with me.
-Down! I said, stay down there!
-Don't hurt me!
It's funny. It didn't dial out to 911.
It was trying to reach a private number.
-Is it a problem?
-No, I'm done here.
Sit down! Down!
Down! I said, stay down there!
Obviously we don't want you doing
anything with your hands...
...other than holding
on for dear life.
On the ground!
Stay on the ground!
Nobody make a move!
Nobody! Stay down!
Yeah!
You have any idea
who you're stealing from?
-You and your friends are dead.
-He's out, right?
What...?
Where did you learn to count?
They wired this thing up with like 5000 volts.
What kind of bank does that?
A Mob bank.
I guess the Joker's as crazy as they say.
Where's the alarm guy?
Boss told me when the guy was done,
I should take him out.
One less share, right?
Funny, he told me
something similar.
He what? No! No!
That's a lot of money.
If this Joker guy was so smart,
he'd have had us bring a bigger car.
I'm betting the Joker told you to kill
me soon as we loaded the cash.
No, no, no, no, no,
I kill the bus driver.
Bus driver?
What bus driver?
School's out. Time to go.
That guy's not
getting up, is he?
That's a lot of money.
What happened to the rest
of the guys?
You think you're smart, huh?
The guy that hired youse...
...he'll just do the same to you.
Oh, criminals in this town
used to believe in things.
Honor...
...respect.
Look at you.
What do you believe in, huh?
What do you believe in?!
I believe whatever doesn't
kill you simply makes you...
...stranger.
Mr. Mayor, you were elected
in a campaign to clean up the city.
-When are you gonna start?
-Oh, Mike, I believe I already have.
Like this so called Batman. We're hearing that he's
doing some good, that criminals are running scared.
-No, man. I don't like it tonight.
-What are you, superstitious?
You got more chance of winning
the Powerball than running into him.
That simply is not true. I'm told that our men in the
Major Crimes Unit are close to an arrest.
Hey, Wuertz, mayor says you're
closing in on the Batman.
The investigation is ongoing.
The process of cleaning
up the streets is a long one.
I pledged in my campaign,
uh, to have...
...ever intending to see
your wife again, lieutenant?
I thought you had to go look
after your mother, detective.
Checked her back
into the hospital.
I'm sorry.
-So he hasn't shown up?
-He often doesn't.
-I like reminding everybody that he's out there.
-Why wouldn't he come?
Hopefully...
...because he's busy.
That's why we bring dogs.
-My little princes.
-Please.
Please, they're crawling in my mouth.
Please, I beg you, get them off.
Look what your drugs
do to my customers.
Buyer beware.
I told you my compound
would take you places.
I never said they'd be
places you wanted to go.
My business, repeat customers.
You don't like what I have to offer,
you can buy from someone else.
Assuming Batman left
anyone to buy from.
My dogs are hungry.
Pity there's only one of you.
-What...?
-That's not him.
Loose the dogs!
That's more like it.
Don't let me find
you out here again.
-We're trying to help you.
-I don't need help.
Not my diagnosis.
What gives you the right?
What's the difference between you and me?
I'm not wearing hockey pads.
Everybody back now!
He can't resist
showing us his face.
What's he hiding
under that makeup?
Uh, can we get a minute,
people, please?
Him again. Who are the others?
Another bunch of smalltimers.
Some of the marked
bills I gave you.
My detectives have been making
drug buys with them for weeks.
This bank was another drop for the Mob.
That makes five.
-We found the bulk of their dirty cash.
-Time to move in.
We'd have to hit all banks simultaneously.
SWAT teams, backup.
What about this Joker guy?
One man or the entire Mob?
He can wait.
When the new DA hears about this,
he'll want in.
-Do you trust him?
-Be hard to keep him out.
I hear he's as stubborn
as you are.
Be nice when
Wayne Manor's rebuilt.
You can swap not sleeping
in a penthouse...
...for not sleeping in a mansion.
Whenever you stitch yourself up,
you do make a bloody mess.
Yeah. It makes me learn
from my mistakes.
You ought to be pretty
knowledgeable by now, then.
My armor.
I'm carrying too much weight.
I need to be... I need to be faster.
I'm sure Mr. Fox can oblige.
-Did you get mauled by a tiger?
-It was a dog.
-Huh?
-It was a big dog.
There were more copycats last night,
Alfred, with guns.
Why don't you hire them
and take the weekend off?
That wasn't exactly
what I had in mind...
-...when I said I wanted to inspire people.
-I know.
But things have improved.
Look at the new
district attorney.
I am, closely.
Need to know if he can
be trusted.
Are you interested in his character
or his social circle?
Who Rachel spends her time
with is her business.
I trust you don't have me
followed on my day off.
If you ever took one, I might.
Know your limits, Master Wayne.
Batman has no limits.
-Well, you do, sir.
-Well, can't afford to know them.
And what's gonna happen
on the day that you find out?
We all know how much you
like to say "I told you so."
On that day, Master Wayne,
even I won't want to.
Probably.
Sorry I'm late, folks.
-Where were you?
-Worried you'd have to step up?
-Harvey, I know these briefs backwards.
-Well, then...
...fair's fair.
Heads, I'll take it.
Tails, he's all yours.
Yeah? You wanna flip
a coin to see who leads?
It's my father's lucky coin.
As I recall, it got me my first date with you.
I wouldn't leave something
like that up to chance.
I don't.
I make my own luck.
All rise.
The Honorable Judge Freel presiding.
I thought the DA just played golf with the mayor,
things like that.
Teeoff's 1:30. More than enough time
to put you away for life, Sally.
With Carmine Falcone
in Arkham...
...someone must have stepped
up to run the so-called family.
Is that man in this
courtroom today?
-Could you identify him for us, please?
-You win, counselor.
It was me.
I have a sworn statement
from you that this man...
...Salvatore Maroni, is the new head
of the Falcone crime family.
Maroni? He's a fall guy.
I'm the brains of the organization.
-Order.
-Permission to treat the witness as hostile?
-Granted.
-Hostile? I'll show you hostile!
Carbon fiber, .28 caliber,
made in China.
If you wanna kill a public servant,
Mr. Maroni, I recommend you buy American.
-Get him out of here.
-But, Your Honor, I'm not done.
We'll never be able to link the gun to Maroni,
so we won't be able to charge him.
But the fact they're trying to kill you,
means we're getting to them.
I'm glad you're so pleased, Rachel.
I'm fine, by the way.
Come on, Harvey.
You're Gotham's DA.
You're not getting shot at,
you're not doing your job right.
But, you know...
...if you said you were rattled,
we could take the rest of the day off.
Can't. I dragged the head
of the Major Crimes Unit down here.
Oh, Jim Gordon? He's a friend, actually.
Try to be nice.
I hear you got a hell
of a right cross.
It's a shame
Sal's going to walk.
Yeah, well, good thing about the Mob
is they keep giving you second chances.
Lightly irradiated bills.
Fancy stuff for a city cop.
Have help?
We liaise with various agencies...
Save it, Gordon.
I wanna meet him.
Official policy is to arrest
the vigilante known as Batman on sight.
Mm-hm. And what about that floodlight
on the top of MCU?
If you got problems
with malfunctioning equipment...
...I suggest you take them
up with Maintenance, counselor.
I've put every known money launderer
in Gotham behind bars...
...but the Mob is still
getting its money out.
I think you and your friend have
found the last game in town...
...and you're trying to hit them
where it hurts, their wallets.
It's bold.
You gonna count me in?
In this town, the fewer people know something,
the safer the operation.
Gordon, I don't like that
you've got your own special unit.
And I don't like that it's full of cops
I investigated at Internal Affairs.
If I didn't work with cops you'd investigated
while you were making your name at IA...
...I'd be working alone.
I don't get political points for being an idealist.
I have to do the best I can with what I have.
You want me to back warrants for search
and seizure on five banks...
...without telling me
what we're after.
I can give you the names
of the banks.
Well, that's a start.
I'll get you your warrants,
but I want your trust.
Oh, you don't have to sell me, Dent.
We all know you're Gotham's white knight.
Yeah, well, I heard they have
a different name for me down at MCU.
I wouldn't know about that.
In China, Lau Security Investments
stands for dynamic new growth.
A joint Chinese venture with
Wayne Enterprises will be a powerhouse.
Well, Mr. Lau...
...I speak for the rest
of the board...
...and Mr. Wayne,
in expressing our own excitement.
Sir, I know that Mr. Wayne is curious
about how his trust fund gets replenished...
...but, frankly,
this is embarrassing.
You worry about the diligence,
Mr. Reese.
I'll worry about Bruce Wayne.
It's done.
The numbers are solid.
Do them again.
Wouldn't want the trust fund
to run out, now, would we?
Another long night?
This joint venture was your idea,
and the consultants love it.
But I'm not convinced.
Lau's company has grown by
8 percent annually like clockwork.
His revenue stream must
be off the books...
...maybe even illegal.
Okay. Cancel the deal.
You already knew.
Just needed a closer
look at their books.
Anything else you
can trouble me for?
I need a new suit.
Yeah. Three buttons
is a little '90s, Mr. Wayne.
I'm not talking fashion,
Mr. Fox, so much as function.
You wanna be able
to turn your head.
Sure make backing
out of the driveway easier.
I'll see what I can do.
Took me three weeks to get
a reservation here.
And I had to tell them I work
for the government.
-Really?
-The city's health inspector's not afraid to pull strings.
Rachel. Fancy that.
Yeah, Bruce. Fancy that.
Rachel, Natascha.
Natascha, Rachel.
-Natascha. Are you the prima...?
-Prima ballerina for the Moscow Ballet.
-Wow. Harvey's taking me next week.
-Really? So you're into ballet?
Bruce. This is Harvey Dent.
The famous Bruce Wayne.
Rachel's told me everything about you.
I certainly hope not.
-So, let's put a couple tables together.
-I'm not sure that they'll let us.
Oh, they should.
I own the place.
How could you want to raise
children in a city like this?
-Well, I was raised here. I turned out okay.
-Is Wayne Manor in the city limits?
Is...? Heh-heh.
The Palisades? Sure.
You know, as our new DA, you might wanna figure out
where your jurisdiction ends.
I'm talking about the kind of city
that idolizes a masked vigilante.
Gotham City is proud of an ordinary
citizen standing up for what's right.
Gotham needs heroes like you,
elected officials...
-...not a man who thinks he's above the law.
-Exactly. Who appointed the Batman?
We did. All of us who stood by and let
scum take control of our city.
But this is a democracy, Harvey.
When their enemies
were at the gates...
...the Romans would suspend democracy
and appoint one man to protect the city.
It wasn't considered an honor,
it was considered a public service.
Harvey, the last man that they appointed
to protect the Republic was named Caesar...
-...and he never gave up his power.
-Okay, fine.
You either die a hero...
...or you live long enough to see
yourself become the villain.
Look, whoever the Batman is,
he doesn't wanna do this for the rest of his life.
How could he? Batman is looking
for someone to take up his mantle.
Someone like you, Mr. Dent?
Maybe. If I'm up to it.
What if Harvey Dent
is the Caped Crusader? Hm?
If I were sneaking out every night,
someone would've noticed by now.
Well, I'm sold, Dent,
and I'm gonna throw you a fundraiser.
That's nice of you, Bruce,
but I'm not up for reelection for three years.
No, you don't understand.
One fundraiser with my pals...
...you'll never need another cent.
The hell is this?
As you're all aware,
one of our deposits was stolen.
A relatively small amount,
68 million.
Who's stupid
enough to steal from us?
Two-bit wackjob,
wears a cheap purple suit and makeup.
He's not the problem.
He's a nobody.
The problem is our money
being tracked by the cops.
Thanks to Mr. Maroni's well-placed sources...
...we know that police have indeed identified
our banks using marked bills...
...and are planning to seize
your funds today.
And since the enthusiastic new DA has put
all my competitors out of business...
-...I'm your only option.
-So, what are you proposing?
Moving all deposits to one secure location,
not a bank.
-Where, then?
-No one can know but me.
If the police were to gain
leverage over one of you...
...everyone's money
would be at stake.
What stop them getting to you?
I go to Hong Kong,
far from Dent's jurisdiction...
...and the Chinese will not
extradite one of their own.
How soon can you move the money?
I already have.
For obvious reasons,
I couldn't wait for your permission.
Rest assured,
your money is safe.
Oh, hee-hee, aha.
Ha, ooh, hee, ha-ha, ha-ha.
And I thought my jokes were bad.
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
have my boy here pull your head off.
How about a magic trick?
I'm gonna make this
pencil disappear.
Ta-da!
It's...
It's gone.
Oh, and by the way,
the suit, it wasn't cheap.
-You ought to know, you bought it.
-Sit.
I want to hear proposition.
Let's wind the clocks
back a year.
These cops and lawyers wouldn't
dare cross any of you.
I mean, what happened?
Did your balls drop off? Hm?
You see, a guy like me...
-A freak.
-Damn right.
A guy like me...
Look, listen.
I know why you choose to have
your little, ahem...
...group-therapy sessions
in broad daylight.
I know why you're afraid
to go out at night.
The Batman.
See, Batman has shown Gotham
your true colors, unfortunately.
Dent, he's just the beginning.
And as for the television's so-called plan...
...Batman has no jurisdiction.
He'll find him
and make him squeal.
I know the squealers
when I see them...
...and...
What do you propose?
It's simple.
We, uh, kill the Batman.
If it's so simple,
why haven't you done it already?
If you're good at something,
never do it for free.
How much you want?
Uh, half.
-You're crazy.
-No, I'm not.
No, I'm not.
If we don't deal
with this now...
...soon...
...little Gambol here won't be able
to get a nickel for his grandma.
Enough from the clown!
Ah, ta-ta-ta. Let's not blow...
-Shit!
-...this out of proportion.
You think you can steal
from us and just walk away?
-Yeah.
-I'm putting the word out.
Five hundred grand
for this clown dead.
A million alive,
so I can teach him some manners first.
All right. So, listen,
why don't you give me a call...
...when you wanna start taking
things a little more seriously?
Here's my card.
Mm-mm.
You're a hard man to reach.
Lau's halfway to Hong Kong.
If you'd asked, I could have taken his passport.
I told you to keep me in the loop.
All that was left in the vaults
were marked bills.
They knew we were coming.
As soon as your office got involved...
My office?
You're sitting down there with scum
like Wuertz and Ramirez and you're talking...
Oh, yeah, Gordon. I almost had your
rookie cold on a racketeering beat.
Don't try and cloud the fact that clearly
Maroni's got people in your office, Dent.
We need Lau back.
But the Chinese won't extradite
a national under any circumstances.
If I get him to you,
can you get him to talk?
I'll get him to sing.
We're going
after the Mob's life savings.
Things will get ugly.
I knew the risk when I took
this job, lieutenant.
How will you get
him back, any...?
He does that.
Our Chinese friends left town
before I could tell them the deal was off.
Well, I'm sure that you've always
wanted to go to Hong Kong.
What's wrong with a phone call?
I think Mr. Lau deserves
a more personal touch.
Now, for high-altitude jumps,
you're going to need oxygen and stabilizers.
Well, I must say,
compared to your usual requests...
...jumping out of an airplane
is pretty straightforward.
What about getting
back into the plane?
-I'd recommend a good travel agent.
-Without it landing.
Now, that's more
like it, Mr. Wayne.
The CIA had a program
back in the '60s...
...for getting their people
out of hot spots called Sky Hook.
-We could look into that.
-Yeah.
Okay. Now...
Hardened Kevlar plates over titanium-dipped
tri-weave fibers for flexibility.
You'll be lighter,
faster, more agile.
Perhaps you should read
the instructions first?
-Yeah.
-Now, there is a tradeoff.
Separation of the plates makes you
more vulnerable to knives and gunfire.
We wouldn't wanna make things
too easy, now, would we?
How will it hold
up against dogs?
We talking Rottweilers
or Chihuahuas?
Should do fine against cats.
I found one in Arizona.
A very nice man said he could have it
up and running in a week, and he takes cash.
-What about the flight crew?
-South Korean smugglers.
They run flights into Pyongyang,
below radar the whole way.
-Did you think of an alibi?
-Oh, yes.
I believe this
is your plane, sir.
You look tired, Alfred.
You'll be all right without me?
If you can tell me the Russian for
"apply your own bloody suntan lotion."
Yo, Gambol, somebody here for you.
They say they've just killed the Joker.
They've brought the body.
So, dead, that's 500.
How about alive? Hm?
You wanna know
how I got these scars?
My father was...
...a drinker...
...and a fiend.
And one night,
he goes off crazier than usual.
Mommy gets the kitchen
knife to defend herself.
He doesn't like that...
...not one bit.
So, me watching...
...he takes the knife to her,
laughing while he does it.
He turns to me and he says:
"Why so serious?"
He comes at me with the knife.
He sticks the blade in my mouth.
"Let's put a smile on that face."
And...
Why so serious?
Now...
...our operation is small but...
...there is a lot of potential...
...for aggressive expansion.
So which of you fine gentlemen
would like to join our team?
Oh. There's only one spot open
right now, so we're gonna have...
...tryouts.
Make it fast.
Welcome to Hong Kong, Mr. Fox.
Mr. Lau regrets he is unable
to greet you in person today.
I understand.
For security purposes, I'm gonna have
to ask you to check in your mobile.
Of course.
I must apologize for leaving Gotham
in the middle of our negotiations.
This misunderstanding
with the Gotham police force...
-...I couldn't let such a thing threaten my company.
-Of course.
A businessman of your stature
will understand and...
...with you here now,
we can continue.
Well, I do appreciate you bringing me
out here in such style, Mr. Lau, but I re...
We do not allow cell
phones in here.
I'm sorry. Forgot I had it.
No, I really came to tell you
that our business deal has to be put on hold.
You see, we can't afford to be
seen to do business with...
...whatever it is you're
accused of being.
I'm sure a businessman
of your stature will understand.
I think, Mr. Fox,
a simple phone call might have sufficed.
Mr. Wayne didn't want you to think
he was deliberately wasting your time.
Just accidentally wasting it.
That's very good, Mr. Lau.
"Accidentally." Very good.
Hey, sir.
There's a better view
from the peak tram.
How's the view
from LSI Holdings?
Restricted.
Lau is holed up in there
good and tight.
-What's this?
-I had R & D work it up.
Sends out a high-frequency pulse...
records the response time
for mapping an environment.
Sonar. Just like a...
Submarine, Mr. Wayne.
Like a submarine.
-And the other device?
-It's in place.
Mr. Wayne?
Good luck.
Look, give us the money
and we'll talk about making a deal.
The money is the only reason
I'm still alive.
Oh, you mean, when they find
out that you've helped us, they're gonna kill you?
-Are you threatening my client?
-No.
I'm just assuming your client's cooperation
with this investigation.
As will everyone.
No? Okay.
Enjoy your time
in County, Mr. Lau.
Wait!
I won't give you the money...
...but I will give you my clients,
all of them.
You were a glorified accountant.
What could you possibly have
on all of them that we could charge?
I'm good with calculation.
I handled all their investments.
One big pot.
Got it.
One minute.
RICO. If they pooled their money,
we can charge them all as one criminal conspiracy.
Charge them with what?
In a RICO case, if you can charge
one of the conspirators with a felony...
You can charge all of them with it.
That's great.
Mr. Lau.
What kind of details do you
have about this communal fund?
-Ledgers...?
-Immunity, protection...
-...and a chartered plane back to Hong Kong.
-After you testify in open court.
And I'm just curious.
With all your clients locked up...
...what's gonna happen
with all that money?
Like I said,
I'm good with calculation.
He can't go to County.
I'll keep him here in the holding cells.
What is this, Gordon,
your fortress?
Well, you trust them
over at County?
I don't trust them here.
Lau stays.
Well, I don't know about Mr. Lau's travel arrangements,
but I'm sure glad he's back.
Put word out. We hire the clown.
He was right.
We have to fix real problem.
Batman.
-I'm not aware of any participation by the Batman...
-Our boy looks good on the tube.
You sure you wanna embarrass
me in front of my friends, lieutenant?
Oh, don't worry.
They're coming too.
Have a nice trip.
See you next fall.
712 counts of extortion...
...849 counts of racketeering...
...246 counts of fraud,
87 counts of conspiracy murder...
...527 counts of obstruction of justice.
How do the defendants plead?
Order in the court.
549 criminals at once.
How did you convince
Surrillo to hear this farce?
She shares my enthusiasm for justice.
After all, she is a judge.
Even if you blow enough smoke to get
convictions out of Surrillo...
...you're gonna set a new record
at appeals for quickest kick in the ass.
It won't matter.
The head guys make bail, sure.
But the midlevel guys, they can't.
They can't afford to be off the streets long enough for trial and appeal.
They'll cut deals that include some jail time.
Think of all you could do with
18 months of clean streets.
-Mr. Mayor, you can't...
-No, get out. Both of you.
Sit down.
The public likes you.
That's the only reason that this might fly.
But that means it's on you.
They're all gonna come after you now,
and not just the Mob.
Politicians, journalists, cops.
Anyone whose wallet's about to get lighter.
Are you up to it?
You better be.
Because they get
anything on you...
...and those criminals are back on the streets,
followed swiftly by you and me.
I think your fundraiser
will be a great success, sir.
And why do you think I wanna
hold a party for Harvey Dent?
I assumed it was your usual reason
for socializing beyond myself...
...and the scum
of Gotham's underbelly:
To try to impress Miss Dawes.
Very droll, but very wrong.
Actually, it's Dent.
Police released video footage
found concealed on the body.
Sensitive viewers, please be aware.
The image is disturbing.
Tell them your name.
Brian Douglas.
Are you the real Batman?
-No.
-No?
Then why do you
dress up like him?
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Because he's a symbol that we don't
have to be afraid of scum like you.
Yeah. You do, Brian.
You really do.
Huh? Yeah. Oh, shh, shh, shh.
So you think Batman's made
Gotham a better place? Hm?
Look at me.
Look at me!
You see, this is how crazy
Batman's made Gotham.
You want order in Gotham?
Batman must take off his mask
and turn himself in.
Oh, and every day he doesn't,
people will die.
Starting tonight.
I'm a man of my word.
Harvey Dent,
scourge of the underworld...
...scared stiff
by the trust-fund brigade.
-I'll be back.
-Rachel.
A little liquid courage, Mr. Dent?
-Thank you. Alfred, right?
-That's right, sir.
Rachel talks about you all the time.
You've known her her whole life?
Not yet, sir.
Any psychotic ex-boyfriends
I should be aware of?
Oh, you have no idea.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
I'm glad to see that you all got started without me.
Now, where is Harvey? Where...?
Harvey Dent,
the man of the hour.
Where's Rachel Dawes?
She is my oldest friend.
Come here.
You know, when Rachel first told me that
she was dating Harvey Dent, I had one thing to say:
"The guy from those God-awful
campaign commercials?"
"I believe in Harvey Dent."
Yeah, nice slogan, Harvey.
But it caught Rachel's attention.
And then I started to pay
attention to Harvey...
...and all that he's been doing as our new DA.
And you know what?
I believe in Harvey Dent.
I believe that on his watch,
Gotham can feel...
...a little safer,
a little more optimistic.
Look at this face.
This is the face of Gotham's bright future.
To Harvey Dent.
Let's hear it for him.
Harvey.
Harvey may not know you well enough
to understand when you're making fun of him...
-...but I do.
-No, I meant every word.
You know that day that you
once told me about when...
...Gotham would no longer need Batman?
-It's coming.
-Bruce.
-You can't ask me to wait for that.
-It's happening now. Harvey is that hero.
He locked up half of the city's criminals,
and he did it without wearing a mask.
Gotham needs a hero with a face.
You can throw a party, Wayne,
I'll give you that.
Thanks again.
You mind if I borrow Rachel?
Lieutenant, that joker card pinned to the body?
Forensics found three sets of DNA.
-Any matches?
-All three.
The DNA belongs to Judge Surrillo,
Harvey Dent and Commissioner Loeb.
The Joker's telling us
who he's targeting.
Get a unit over to Surrillo's house.
Tell Wuertz to find Dent.
Get them both into protective custody.
Where's the commissioner?
-City hall.
-Seal the building.
-No one in or out till I get there.
-Got it.
Gordon. What are you up to?
We're secure. I want a floor-by-floor
search of the entire building.
Sorry, sir. We believe the Joker
has made a threat against your life.
These are dangerous people, judge.
-Yeah, but you're not giving me a lot of information.
-Even we don't know where you're going.
Take the envelope, get in, open it.
It'll tell you where you're headed.
You cannot leave me alone
with these people.
The whole Mob's after you
and you're worried about these guys?
Compared to this,
the Mob doesn't scare me.
Gordon, you're unlikely to discover
this for yourself, so...
...take my word,
the police commissioner earns a lot of threats.
I found the appropriate response
to these situations a long time ago.
Them gunning for you makes
you see things clearly.
Yeah, I bet.
Yeah. It makes you think about things
you couldn't stand losing...
...about who you wanna spend
the rest of your life with.
-That's a pretty big commitment.
-Well, not if the Mob has their way.
You get to explain to my wife...
...why I'm late for dinner, lieutenant.
Sir, the joker card had
traces of your DNA on it.
-Don't do that.
-All right.
-Let's be serious, then.
-Okay.
What's your answer?
I don't have an answer.
How'd they get my DNA?
Somebody with access
to your office or house...
...must have lifted a tissue or a glass...
Wait! Wait!
-Well, I guess no answer is a no.
-Harvey.
-It's someone else, isn't it?
Just tell me it's not Wayne.
The guy's a complete f...
What are you doing?
Oh, shit.
Get a medic!
They've come for him.
We made it.
Stay hidden.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
We are tonight's entertainment.
I only have one question:
Where is Harvey Dent?
You know where Harvey is?
You know who he is?
Hands up, pretty boy.
Do you know where I can find Harvey?
I need to talk to him about something.
Just something little, huh? No.
What's going on out there?
Wayne!
-Oh, thank God, you've got a panic room.
-Hey, wait...
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
You know,
I'll settle for his loved ones.
We're not intimidated by thugs.
You know...
...you remind me of my father.
I hated my father.
Okay, stop.
Well, hello, beautiful.
You must be Harvey's squeeze.
Hm?
And you are beautiful.
You look nervous.
Is it the scars?
You wanna know how I got them?
Come here. Hey.
Look at me.
So I had a wife.
Beautiful, like you...
...who tells me I worry too much...
...who tells me I ought
to smile more...
...who gambles and gets in deep
with the sharks. Hey.
One day they carve her face.
And we have no money for surgeries.
She can't take it.
I just wanna see her smile again.
Hm?
I just want her to know
that I don't care about the scars.
So...
...I stick a razor in my mouth
and do this...
...to myself.
And you know what?
She can't stand the sight of me.
She leaves.
Now I see the funny side.
Now I'm always smiling.
You got a little fight in you.
I like that.
Then you're gonna love me.
Drop the gun.
Oh, sure. You just take off your little mask
and show us all who you really are. Hm?
Let her go.
Very poor choice of words.
Are you all right?
Let's not do that again.
-Is Harvey okay?
-He's safe.
Thank you.
Jim, it's over.
As long as they don't get to Lau,
we've cut off their funds.
The prosecution's over.
Nobody's standing up in front of a judge...
...while judges and police commissioners
are getting blown away.
-What about Dent?
-He's got any sense, Dent's halfway to Mex...
So where do you keep your trash?
You're due in court.
I need you alive long enough to get you on the record.
You can't protect me.
You can't even protect yourselves.
You refuse to cooperate,
you're not coming back here, you go to County.
How long do you calculate
you'll last in there?
Targeting me won't get their money back.
I knew the Mob wouldn't go down without a fight...
-...but this is different. They've crossed a line.
-You crossed the line first, sir.
You squeezed them,
you hammered them to the point of desperation.
And in their desperation,
they turned to a man they didn't fully understand.
Criminals aren't complicated, Alfred.
We just need to figure
out what he's after.
With respect, Master Wayne...
...perhaps this is a man you don't
fully understand either.
A long time ago,
I was in Burma...
...and my friends and I were working
for the local government.
They were trying to buy
the loyalty of tribal leaders...
...by bribing them
with precious stones...
...but their caravans were being raided
in a forest north of Rangoon by a bandit.
So we went looking
for the stones.
But in six months,
we never met anyone who traded with him.
One day, I saw a child
playing with a ruby...
...the size of a tangerine.
The bandit had
been throwing them away.
-So why steal them?
-Well, because he thought it was good sport.
Because some men aren't looking
for anything logical, like money.
They can't be bought, bullied,
reasoned or negotiated with.
Some men just wanna
watch the world burn.
Your name, sir? Please state...
8th at Orchard.
You'll find Harvey Dent there.
Check the names.
"Richard Dent."
"Patrick Harvey."
Harvey Dent.
I need 10 minutes with the scene
before your men contaminate it.
-Us contaminate it? It's because of you these guys are dead...
-Detective!
Give us a minute, guys.
That's brick underneath.
-Gonna take ballistics off a shattered bullet?
-No.
Fingerprints.
Whatever you're gonna do,
do it fast.
Because we found his next target.
He's put it in tomorrow's paper.
I'm not sure you made
it loud enough, sir.
What can I do for you, Mr. Reese?
You wanted me to do the diligence
on the LSI Holdings deal again.
Well, I found some irregularities.
Their CEO is in police custody.
No, not with their numbers,
with yours.
Applied Sciences. Whole division of
Wayne Enterprises just disappeared overnight.
I went down to the archives
and I started pulling some old files.
Don't tell me you didn't recognize your baby
pancaking cop cars on the evening news.
Now you got the entire
R & D Department burning through cash...
...claiming it's related to
cell phones for the Army?
What are you building for him now,
a rocket ship?
I want...
...$10 million a year
for the rest of my life.
Let me get this straight.
You think that your client...
...one of the wealthiest, most powerful men
in the world, is secretly a vigilante...
...who spends his nights beating criminals
to a pulp with his bare hands...
...and your plan is to blackmail this person?
Good luck.
When...
Keep that.
This is your original scan.
Here it is reengineered.
And there's the thumbprint he left
when he pushed the round in the clip.
I'll get you a copy.
Mr. Wayne, did you reassign R & D?
Yeah. Government telecommunications project.
I wasn't aware we had
any government contracts.
Lucius, I'm playing this one
pretty close to the chest.
Fair enough.
With no word from the Batman,
even as they mourn Commissioner Loeb...
...these cops have to be wondering
if the Joker will make good on his threat...
...in the obituary column of
The Gotham Times to kill the mayor.
I've checked all the databases.
There are four possibles.
Cross-reference the addresses.
Look for Parkside,
overlooking the parade.
I got one.
Melvin White,
1502 Randolph Apartments.
Aggravated assault,
moved to Arkham twice.
What do you got on the roof?
We're tight, but frankly,
there's a lot of windows up here.
Commissioner Loeb dedicated
his life to law enforcement...
...and to the protection
of his community.
I remember when I first
took office...
...and I asked if he wanted
to stay on as commissioner...
...and he said he would,
provided I kept my politics out of his office.
Clearly he was not a man who minced words,
nor should he have been.
A number of policies that he enacted
as commissioner were unpopular.
Policies that flooded my office
with angry calls and letters...
-Who's that?
-What happened?
They took our guns.
And our uniforms.
And as we recognize
the sacrifice of this man...
...we must remember that vigilance
is the price of safety.
Stand by. Honor guard.
Attention. Port arms.
Ready! Aim! Fire!
Ready! Aim!
Stay down! Don't move!
Mr. Mayor. Get him out of here.
-I'll see you later.
-Why are you going back?
Get out of here.
Tell me what you know
about the Joker.
No.
I'm sorry, Barbara.
Jimmy, go play with your sister.
Go ahead.
If there's anything we can do,
anything you need, we're here for you.
Shh.
Are you out there?
Are you? You brought this
craziness on us. You did!
You brought this on us!
Switch it off, he ain't coming.
He doesn't wanna talk to us.
God help whoever he does
wanna talk to.
Can't we go someplace quieter?
We can't hear each other talk.
What makes you think
I wanna hear you talk?
What?
-Yeah?
-Second.
Okay.
-Harvey, where are you?
-Where are you?
I'm where you should be, at Major Crimes.
I'm trying to deal with all of this mess.
-Can I get the fingerprint analysis?
-Rachel, listen to me. You're not safe there.
-This is Gordon's unit.
-Gordon's gone, Rachel.
-He vouched for these men.
-And he's gone.
The Joker's named you next.
God, is there someone,
is there anyone in this town we can trust?
Bruce.
We can trust Bruce Wayne.
-No. Rachel, come on. I know you're his friend, but...
-Harvey, trust me.
Bruce's penthouse is now
the safest place in the city.
Then you go straight there.
Don't tell anybody where you're going
and I'll find you there.
I love you.
I want the Joker.
From one professional to another...
...you're trying to scare somebody,
pick a better spot.
From this height,
the fall wouldn't kill me.
-I'm counting on it.
-Huh!
-Where is he?
-I don't know where he is. He found us.
He must have friends.
Friends? Have you met this guy?
Someone knows where he is.
Nobody's gonna tell you nothing.
They're wise to your act.
You got rules.
The Joker, he's got no rules.
Nobody's gonna cross him for you.
If you want this guy, you got one way.
But you already
know what that is.
Just take off that mask,
let him come find you.
Or you can let a couple more people get
killed while you make up your mind.
You wanna play games?
How's that feel?
-You wouldn't.
-I wouldn't!
-You don't think I will?
-Mm-mm.
No. No, I wouldn't.
That's why I'm not gonna
leave it up to me.
Heads, you get
to keep your head.
Tails...
...not so lucky.
So you wanna tell
me about the Joker?
-Let's go again.
-I don't know anything! God, don't!
You're not playing
the odds, friend.
Let's do it again.
You'd leave a man's life to chance?
-Not exactly.
-His name's Schiff, Thomas.
He's a paranoid schizophrenic,
former patient at Arkham.
The kind of mind the Joker attracts.
What do you expect to learn from him?
The Joker killed Gordon.
He's gonna kill Rachel.
You're the symbol of hope
I could never be.
Your stand
against organized crime...
...is the first legitimate ray
of light in Gotham in decades.
If anyone saw this,
everything would be undone.
All the criminals you pulled off
the streets would be released...
...and Jim Gordon will have
died for nothing.
You're gonna hold a press
conference tomorrow morning.
-Why?
-No one else will die because of me.
Gotham's in your hands now.
You can't.
You can't give in.
You can't give in!
Harvey called.
He said Batman's gonna
turn himself in.
I have no choice.
You honestly think that's gonna
keep the Joker from killing people?
Maybe not.
But I have enough blood on my hands.
And I've seen now what I would have
to become to stop men like him.
You once told me that if the day
came when I was finished...
...that we'd be together.
Bruce, don't make me
your one hope for a normal life.
Did you mean it?
Yes.
Bruce.
If you turn yourself in,
they're not gonna let us be together.
Logs as well? Everything.
Anything that could lead
back to Lucius or Rachel.
People are dying, Alfred.
What would you have me do?
Endure, Master Wayne. Take it.
They'll hate you for it,
but that's the point of Batman.
He can be the outcast.
He can make the choice that no one else can make.
The right choice.
No, today I found
out what Batman can't do.
He can't endure this.
Today you get to say
"I told you so."
Today, I don't want to.
But I did bloody tell you.
I suppose they're gonna
lock me up as well...
...as your accomplice.
Accomplice? I'm gonna tell them
the whole thing was your idea.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for coming.
I've called this press conference for two reasons.
Firstly, to assure
the citizens of Gotham...
...that everything that can be done
over the Joker killings is being done.
Secondly, because the Batman has
offered to turn himself in.
But first, let's consider the situation.
Should we give in to this
terrorist's demands?
Do we really think that he's gonna...?
You'd rather protect an outlaw
vigilante than the lives of citizens?
The Batman is an outlaw.
But that's not why we demand he turn himself in,
we're doing it because we're scared.
We've been happy to let the Batman
clean up our streets for us until now.
-Things are worse than ever!
-Amen.
Yes, they are.
But the night is darkest
just before the dawn.
And I promise you...
...the dawn is coming.
One day, the Batman will have to answer
for the laws he's broken. But to us...
...not to this madman.
-No more dead cops!
-Yeah!
He should turn himself in!
-Give us the Batman! Come on!
-Where is he?
So be it.
Take the Batman into custody.
-What?
-Is he here?
I am the Batman.
What? Come on.
Alfred.
Why is he letting Harvey do this?
-He went down to the press conference.
-I know. And he just stood by.
Perhaps both Bruce
and Mr. Dent...
...believe that Batman stands
for something more important...
...than the whims of a terrorist,
Miss Dawes...
...even if everyone
hates him for it.
That's the sacrifice
he's making.
He's not being a hero.
He's being something more.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
Letting Harvey take the fall
for this is not heroic at all.
You know him better than anyone.
I do.
Will you give this to him for me?
When the time is right?
How will I know?
It's not sealed.
Bye, Alfred.
Bye, Rachel.
Sorry, I didn't have time
to talk this through with you.
-What are you doing?
-They're transferring me to Central Holding.
This is the Joker's chance,
and when he attacks, Batman will take him down.
Listen to me.
This is too dangerous.
We get this guy to County, he's their problem.
Streets will be cleared along your route...
...so let's go.
Convoys stop for no reason.
I hope you got some moves, pal.
He's using you as bait. He doesn't even know
if he can get the Joker. He's failed so far.
-How do you know what he's thinking?
-I just...I do. Anyway, Harvey, this isn't just about you.
What about all the people who are depending on you
to clean the city up and to do it honorably and...?
Harvey.
Tell everyone the truth.
Heads, I go through with it.
This is your life.
You can't leave something like that to chance.
I'm not.
You make your own luck.
Hey, you wait
like everybody else, pal.
What the hell is that?
Obstruction ahead,
obstruction ahead!
Damn it! All units divert down onto Lower Fifth.
I repeat, exit down.
Exit down!
Lower Fifth? We'll be like
turkeys on Thanksgiving down there.
Jesus. Come on, get us out of here.
Let's go.
Listen, we need backup.
We've got company.
We got trouble, guys.
Lock and load!
The hell was that?
-These are built for that, right?
-He's gonna need something...
...a lot bigger to get
through this.
What is that?
What is that, a bazooka?
I didn't sign up for this!
Look out.
Look out!
Hmm.
Come on, let's go!
Harvey, Harvey, Harvey Dent.
Oh, excuse me. I wanna drive.
Scanning all systems.
We gotta get topside.
We need air support, now!
I like this job. I like it.
Damage catastrophic.
Eject sequence initiated.
Goodbye.
We're on point, ready to give
them some of their own medicine.
That's what I'm talking about.
Air cav.
Okay, rack them up.
Rack them up,
rack them up, rack them up.
That's not good.
Okay, that's not good!
Now, there's a Batman.
Ooh, you wanna play. Come on.
Come on.
He missed!
You can't stop here.
We're like sitting ducks!
Come on, come on.
Come on. Come on. I want you to do it,
I want you to do it. Come on!
Come on.
Come on. I want you to do it,
I want you to do it. Come on, hit me.
Come on, hit me.
Come on, hit me!
Hit me!
Come on, come on. Aah!
Could you please just
give me a minute?
We got you, you son of a bitch.
Gor... You do like to play things
pretty close to the chest.
We got him, Harvey.
Mr. Dent! How does it feel to be
the biggest hero in Gotham?
No, I'm no hero.
Gotham's finest, they're the heroes.
But you and your office have
been working with the Batman all along.
-No, but I trusted him to do the right thing.
-Which was?
Saving my ass.
All right, people, that's enough.
Let him be. Let him be.
Thank you, detective.
I've got a date with a pretty
upset girlfriend.
-I figured, counselor.
-Mr. Dent, sir...
-How about one for the front page, sir?
-Mr. Dent.
Stand away! All of you!
I don't want anything for his Mob
lawyer to use, you understand?
Back from the dead.
I, uh...
...couldn't risk
my family's safety.
What do we got?
Nothing. No matches
on prints, DNA, dental.
Clothing is custom, no labels.
Nothing in his pockets
but knives and lint.
No name.
-No other alias.
-Go home, Gordon.
The clown'll keep till morning.
Go get some rest.
You're gonna need it.
Tomorrow you take the big job.
You don't have any say in the matter.
Commissioner Gordon.
I'm sorry,
I couldn't risk your safety.
Look at these ugly bastards.
-I don't feel good.
-You're a cop killer.
You're lucky to be feeling
anything below the neck.
-Please!
-Step away from the bars!
My insides hurt.
Did Batman save you, Daddy?
Actually, this time...
...I saved him.
Has he said anything yet?
Evening, commissioner.
Harvey Dent never made it home.
-Of course not.
-What have you done with him?
Me?
I was right here.
Who did you leave him with?
Hm? Your people?
Assuming, of course,
that they are still your people...
...and not Maroni's.
Does it depress you,
commissioner...
...to know just how alone
you really are?
Does it make you feel responsible for
Harvey Dent's current predicament?
-Where is he?
-What's the time?
What difference does that make?
Well, depending on the time,
he may be in one spot or several.
-If we're gonna play games...
-Mm-hm?
...I'm gonna need a cup of coffee.
Ah, the "good cop,
bad cop" routine?
Not exactly.
Never start with the head.
The victim gets all fuzzy. He can't feel the next...
See?
You wanted me. Here I am.
I wanted to see what you'd do.
And you didn't disappoint.
You let five people die.
Then you let Dent
take your place.
-Even to a guy like me, that's cold.
-Where's Dent?
Those Mob fools want you gone so they can
get back to the way things were.
But I know the truth.
There's no going back. You've changed things.
-Forever.
-Then why do you wanna kill me?
I don't wanna kill you.
What would I do without you?
Go back to ripping off Mob dealers? No, no.
No. No, you...
You complete me.
-You're garbage who kills for money.
-Don't talk like one of them. You're not.
Even if you'd like to be.
To them, you're just a freak...
...like me.
They need you right now...
...but when they don't...
...they'll cast you
out like a leper.
You see, their morals,
their code...
...it's a bad joke.
Dropped at the first sign of trouble.
They're only as good as the world
allows them to be. I'll show you.
When the chips are down, these...
These civilized people...
...they'll eat each other.
See, I'm not a monster.
I'm just ahead of the curve.
Where's Dent?
You have all these rules,
and you think they'll save you.
-He's in control.
-I have one rule.
Oh. Then that's the rule you'll have
to break to know the truth.
Which is?
The only sensible way
to live is without rules.
And tonight you're gonna
break your one rule.
I'm considering it.
There's only minutes left,
so you're gonna have to play my little game...
...if you wanna save one of them.
"Them"?
You know, for a while there,
I thought you really were Dent.
The way you threw
yourself after her.
Look at you go.
Does Harvey know about you
and his little bunny?
Where are they?!
Killing is making a choice.
-Where are they?!
-Choose between one life or the other.
Your friend the district attorney,
or his blushing bride-to-be.
You have nothing,
nothing to threaten me with.
Nothing to do with all your strength.
Don't worry, I'm gonna tell you
where they are, both of them.
And that's the point.
You'll have to choose.
He's at 250 52nd Street...
...and she's on Avenue X at Cicero.
-Which one you going after?
-Rachel.
We're getting Dent!
250 52nd Street!
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
Hello!
-Rachel?
-Harvey.
Oh, Harvey, thank God.
Are you okay?
I'm all right. I'm in a...
...I'm in a warehouse.
They got me wired to these oil drums.
I am too.
Harvey.
I want my phone call.
I want it. I want it.
That's nice.
How many of your friends
have I killed?
I'm a 20-year man...
...and I know the difference between punks
who need a little lesson in manners...
and the freaks like you
who would just enjoy it.
And you killed
six of my friends.
Six?
Please. My insides hurt.
I don't really care. Back away.
The boss said he'd make
the voices go away.
He said he'd go inside and replace
them with bright lights...
...like Christmas.
You're out of your mind, pal.
Back off.
Medic to the holding tank. Come on.
Get the door open.
You guys, back off!
Listen, we don't
have a lot of time.
They told me that only one of us
was gonna make it...
...and that they were gonna
let our friends choose.
Okay, Rachel.
It's gonna be fine. It's gonna be
all right. They're coming for you.
Listen to me. I'll help you.
Just talk me through what's going on with you.
-Can you find something, anything, sharp?
-I'm trying.
-What's...?
-Shit.
Harvey?
Harvey, what's happening?
All available units,
converge at 250 52nd Street.
Do you wanna know
why I use a knife?
Guns are too quick.
You can't savor all the...
...little emotions.
You see, in their last moments...
...people show you
who they really are.
So in a way, I knew your friends
better than you ever did.
Would you like to know
which of them were cowards?
What's that? Jeez.
He's got some kind of a...
-...contusion.
-I know you're gonna enjoy this.
I'm gonna have to try
and enjoy it even more.
Whoa!
Just put it down.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
Drop the weapon now!
-It's my own damn fault, just shoot him!
-Let him go now! Drop it!
-What? Sorry?
-What do you want?
I just want my phone call.
What...? What...?
What's happening?
Just talk to me,
just for one second.
-All right?
-Right.
Ow.
-Ow.
-Shh, shh, shh.
Is that a phone?
Mount the curb!
Harvey, just in case,
I wanna tell you something, okay?
Don't think like that, Rachel.
They're coming for you.
I know they are,
but I don't want them to.
I don't wanna live without you,
and I do have an answer for you.
My answer is yes.
No! No! No!
Not me!
Why are you coming for me?
No!
Rachel! Rachel!
-Harvey.
-No! No! Rachel!
Okay.
Rachel!
No! No!
Harvey, it's okay.
It's all right. Listen.
Somewh...
No, commissioner!
Rachel! No!
Hello there.
Back at the MCU,
the Joker's gone.
With Lau?
The Joker planned to be caught.
He wanted me to lock
him up in the MCU.
Dear Bruce:
I need to be honest and clear.
I'm going to marry Harvey Dent.
I love him, and I wanna spend
the rest of my life with him.
When I told you that if Gotham no longer
needed Batman, we could be together...
...I meant it.
But now I'm sure the day won't come
when you no longer need Batman.
I hope it does.
And if it does,
I will be there...
...but as your friend.
I'm sorry, Harvey.
I'm sorry to let you down.
If you lose your faith in me,
please keep your faith in people.
Love, now and always, Rachel.
Prepared a little breakfast.
-Very well, then.
-Alfred.
Yes, Master Wayne?
Did I bring this on her?
I was meant to inspire good...
...not madness, not death.
You have inspired good.
But you spat in the faces of Gotham's criminals.
Didn't you think there
might be some casualties?
Things were always gonna get worse
before they got better.
But Rachel, Alfred.
Rachel believed
in what you stood for...
...what we stand for.
Gotham needs you.
No, Gotham needs
its true hero...
...and I let that murdering
psychopath blow him half to hell.
Which is why, for now...
...they're gonna have
to make do with you.
She was gonna wait
for me, Alfred.
Dent doesn't know.
He can never know.
What's that?
-It can wait.
-That bandit...
...in the forest in Burma.
-Did you catch him?
-Yes.
How?
We burned the forest down.
He's credible source, an M & A lawyer
from a prestigious consultancy...
...and he says he's waited as long as he can
for Batman to do the right thing.
And now he's taking matters
into his own hands.
We'll be live at 5 with
the true identity of the Batman.
I'm sorry about Rachel.
The doctor says you're in agonizing pain,
but you won't accept medication.
That you're refusing to...
...accept skin grafts.
Remember that name...
...you all had for me...
...when I was at Internal Affairs?
What was it, Gordon?
Harvey, I...
Say it.
Say it!
Two-Face. Harvey Two-Face.
Why should I hide who I am?
I know you tried to warn me.
I'm sorry.
Wuertz picked you up.
Was he working for them?
Do you know who picked up Rachel?
Harvey, I need to know
which of my men I can trust.
Why would you listen to me now?
I'm sorry, Harvey.
No.
No, you're not.
Not yet.
This craziness, it's too much.
You should've thought about that
before you let the clown out of the box.
You want him?
I can tell you where
he'll be this afternoon.
Not so crazy as you look.
I told you,
I'm a man of my word.
Where is the Italian?
All tactical units will converge
on the location in 20 minutes.
I want auxiliary units to cover
all possible getaway routes.
Please.
Joker-man, what you do
with all your money?
You see,
I'm a guy of simple taste.
I enjoy...
...dynamite...
...and gunpowder...
...and gasoline.
What the...?
And you know the thing
that they have in common?
They're cheap.
I wann know how much they're paying
you to say who Batman really is?
This is our chance. I want Lau alive.
The Joker, either way.
Hey, Jim. Get a load of this.
Let's take the next caller.
Harvey Dent didn't wanna
give in to this maniac.
You think you know better than him?
I think that if we could talk to Dent today,
he may feel differently.
And we wish him a speedy recovery.
God knows, we need him now.
You said you were
a man of your word.
Oh, I am.
I'm only burning my half.
All you care about is money.
This town deserves a better
class of criminal...
...and I'm gonna give it to them.
Tell your men
they work for me now.
This is my city.
They won't work for a freak.
"Freak."
Why don't we cut you
up into little pieces...
...and feed you to your pooches?
Hm?
And then we'll see how loyal
a hungry dog really is.
It's not about money...
...it's about sending a message.
Everything burns.
-Who is this?
-I had a vision...
...of a world without Batman.
The Mob ground
out a little profit...
...and the police tried to shut
them down one block at a time.
And it was so boring.
I've had a change of heart.
I don't want Mr. Reese
spoiling everything...
...but why should I have all the fun?
Let's give someone else a chance.
If Coleman Reese isn't
dead in 60 minutes...
...then I blow up a hospital.
I want you to call in every officer.
Tell them to head to their nearest
hospital and start evac and search.
Call the transit authority, school board, prisons.
Get every available bus down to a hospital.
The priority is Gotham General.
Wheel everybody out of that place right now.
You, you and you,
you come with me.
-Where are we going, sir?
-To get Reese.
I need you plugged in,
checking Gordon's men and their families.
-Looking for?
-Hospital admissions.
Will you be wanting the Batpod, sir?
In the middle of the day, Alfred?
Not very subtle.
The Lamborghini, then.
Much more subtle.
Excuse me. Let me through.
Excuse me. Okay.
Sir, could you help, please?
I'm gonna find a bus for him.
Sir? Commissioner,
do you really think...
...an ordinary citizen
would try to kill this man?
Sir. Commissioner.
Get the cars around the back!
Go. Keep rolling, Sam.
I see O'Brien and Richards.
No immediate family member
admitted to a Gotham hospital.
-They're trying to kill me.
-Well, maybe Batman can save you.
Davis, they got space.
Bring him out.
Davis.
I saw Burns and Zachary.
Nothing on them.
And a patrolman I don't know.
Okay, so, what now?
What do we do now?
Where are we going?
Send the information to Gordon.
Get out of here.
Davis.
Ma'am, we're gonna
have to move him now.
-It's Berg, isn't it?
-Commissioner.
You okay, son?
Hi.
You know...
...I don't want there to be any hard
feelings between us, Harvey.
-When you and, uh...
-Rachel!
...Rachel were being abducted...
...I was sitting in Gordon's cage.
I didn't rig those charges.
Your men, your plan.
Do I really look
like a guy with a plan?
You know what I am?
I'm a dog chasing cars.
I wouldn't know what to do
with one if I caught it.
You know? I just do things.
The Mob has plans.
The cops have plans.
Gordon's got plans.
You know, they're schemers.
Schemers trying to control
their little worlds.
I'm not a schemer.
I try to show the schemers...
...how pathetic their attempts
to control things really are.
So when I say... Ah. Come here.
When I say that you and your girlfriend
was nothing personal...
...you'll know that I'm
telling the truth.
-I'm gonna need your weapon.
-What?
Why? Because
my wife's in the hospital?
Yeah, that'd be why.
It's the schemers that put
you where you are.
You were a schemer,
you had plans...
...and look where that got you.
Police are of course taking
every possible precaution...
...urging people not to take
matters into their own hands.
I just did what I do best.
I took your little plan
and I turned it on itself.
Look what I did to this city with a few drums
of gas and a couple of bullets.
Hm? You know what I noticed?
Nobody panics when things go
"according to plan."
Even if the plan is horrifying.
If tomorrow I tell the press that,
like, a gangbanger will get shot...
...or a truckload of soldiers
will be blowing up...
...nobody panics.
Because it's all part
of the plan.
But when I say that one little old
mayor will die...
...well, then, everyone
loses their minds.
Introduce a little anarchy...
...upset the established order...
...and everything becomes chaos.
I'm an agent of chaos.
Oh, and you know
the thing about chaos?
It's fair.
-You live.
-Mm-hm.
You die.
Mmm. Now we're talking.
Mr. Reese.
That's Mr. Wayne, isn't it?
-That was a very brave thing you did.
-Trying to catch the light?
-You weren't protecting the Van?
-Why? Who's in it?
Don't you think I should
go to the hospital?
You don't watch a whole lot
of news, do you, Mr. Wayne?
Southeast.
It's Gotham General.
-Did you clear the building?
-Yeah.
You must know how many were inside.
You have patient lists, roll call.
Right now we're showing
50 people missing. One bus.
All these other buses were heading off
to other hospitals. My guess is we missed one.
What's your guess
about where Harvey Dent is?
Keep looking. And keep it to yourself.
Anybody asks, we got him out.
Get me the mayor's office on the line.
We're gonna need the National Guard.
People are still missing,
including GCN's own Mike Engel.
I'm now being told that we're cutting
to a video GCN has just received.
I'm Mike Engel
for Gotham Tonight.
"What does it take to make
you people wanna join in?"
You failed to kill the lawyer.
I've gotta get you off the bench...
-...and into the game.
-Bench. Game.
-Come nightfall, this city is mine.
-Mine.
-And anyone left here plays by my rules.
-Rules.
Mr. Fox? Security is showing
a break-in at the R & D Department.
If you don't wanna
be in the game...
-...get out now.
-Get out now.
But the bridge-and-tunnel crowd
are sure in for a surprise.
"Ha-ha, ha-ha."
-Gotham P.D. has shut down...
-Sweet Jesus.
...the area's Bridges and tunnels.
Shouldn't you be out there,
you know, doing something?
It's my day off.
I gotta take a leak.
Keep an eye out for me, will you?
Now what? You need someone
to shake it for you?
Hello.
Dent.
Jesus. I thought you was dead.
Half.
Who picked up Rachel, Wuertz?
-It must've been Maroni's men.
-Shut up!
Are you telling me that you're gonna protect
the other traitor in Gordon's unit?
I don't know, he never told me.
Listen, Dent, I swear to God,
I didn't know what they were gonna do to you.
That's funny...
...because I don't know what's gonna
happen to you either.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Beautiful.
Unethical.
Dangerous.
You've turned every cell phone
in Gotham into a microphone.
And a high-frequency
generator-receiver.
You took my sonar concept and applied
it to every phone in the city.
With half the city feeding you sonar,
you can image all of Gotham.
This is wrong.
I've gotta find
this man, Lucius.
At what cost?
The database
is null-key encrypted.
It can only be accessed
by one person.
This is too much power
for one person.
That's why I gave it to you.
Only you can use it.
Spying on 30 million people isn't
part of my job description.
This is an audio sample.
If he talks within range of any phone in the city...
...you can triangulate
his position.
I'll help you this one time.
But consider this
my resignation.
As long as this machine is at
Wayne Enterprises, I won't be.
When you're finished...
...type in your name.
My officers are going over every inch
of the tunnels and bridges...
...but with the Joker's threat,
they're not an option.
-And land routes east?
-Backed up for hours.
Which leaves the ferries
with 30,000 ready to board.
Plus, I wanna use the ferries so I can get
some of those prisoners off the island.
The men you and Dent put away?
Those aren't people I'm worried about.
You should be.
Whatever the Joker's planning...
...it's a good bet that Harvey's prisoners
might be involved. I wanna get them out of here.
So where is Harvey?
-We haven't found him.
-Oh, Jesus.
How long can you
keep this quiet?
Don't stop for lights,
cops, nothing.
Going to join your wife?
-You love her?
-Yes.
You ever imagine what it would be
like to listen to her die?
Look, take it up with the Joker.
He killed your woman.
He made you...
...like this.
The Joker's just a mad dog.
I want whoever let
him off the leash.
I took care of Wuertz, but who was your other
man inside Gordon's unit?
Who picked up Rachel?
Must have been someone she trusted.
Look, if I tell you...
...will you let me go?
Can't hurt your chances.
It was Ramirez.
-But you said...
-I said it couldn't hurt your chances.
You're a lucky man.
-But he's not.
-Who?
Your driver.
Stand back.
Hey, that ain't right.
We should be on that boat.
You wanna ride across with them?
Be my guest.
Sir, they've stopped their engines.
Right, get on the radio.
Tell them we'll come back and pick
them up once we dump the scumbags.
Liberty, this is Spirit.
Come in.
What the heck was that?
What the...?
Liberty, come in, please.
This is Spirit. Come in.
Liberty, we have the same thing.
We've lost both engines.
-Liberty, come in.
-Fox.
There's something going
on on the ferries.
Get down to the engine room now.
Hey, buddy, what's happening?
Captain, we got a hundred barrels
down there rigged to blow. And this.
Oh, my God.
Looks like some kind
of detonator.
Why would they give us
the detonator to our own bomb?
Tonight, you're all gonna be
a part of a social experiment.
Through the magic of diesel
fuel and ammonium nitrate...
...I'm ready right now
to blow you all sky-high.
Liberty, come in, over.
It's dead.
If anyone attempts to get
off their boat, you all die.
I'm zeroing in.
Each of you has a remote
to blow up the other boat.
His voice is on the ferry...
...but it's not the source.
West.
-Gordon.
-I have the Joker's location.
Prewitt Building.
Assemble on the building opposite.
At midnight, I blow you all up.
If, however, one of you presses the button,
I'll let that boat live.
So who's it gonna be?
Harvey Dent's most-wanted
scumbag collection...
...or the sweet
innocent civilians?
You choose.
Oh, and you might wanna
decide quickly...
...because the people on the other
boat may not be quite so noble.
Stay back.
Well, now, who are you to decide?
We ought to talk this over, at least.
We don't all have to die.
Those men had their chance.
-We are not going to talk about this.
-Why aren't we talking about it?
They're talking over the same
exact thing on the other boat.
-Let's put it to a vote.
-Yes!
-Hello?
-Barbara, it's Anna Ramirez.
Jim needs you to pack up and put
the kids in the car right away.
But the units outside...
Those cops can't be trusted.
Jim needs you away from them
as soon as possible.
I'll call them off for 10 minutes,
and you'll have to move fast.
-But where am I supposed to take them?
-250 52nd Street.
-Leave as soon as the patrol car pulls out.
-Okay.
She believe you?
It's because she trusts you...
...just like Rachel did.
-I didn't know...
-You didn't know what they were gonna do?
You're the second cop
to say that to me.
What exactly did you think
they were gonna do?
They got me early on.
My mother's hospital bills...
-Don't!
-I'm sorry.
You live to fight
another day, officer.
We found the missing hospital bus.
Then we have a hostage situation.
It's a shooting gallery.
Why would he choose a spot
with such big windows?
We have clear shots
on five clowns.
Snipers take them out, smash
the windows, a team rappels in.
Team moves in by the stairwells.
Two, three casualties Max.
-Let's do it.
-It's not that simple.
-With the Joker, it never is.
-What's simple is...
...every second we don't take, those people
on the ferries get closer to blowing each other up.
-That won't happen.
-Then he'll blow both of them up!
-We don't have time for paper ballots.
-I want everybody to put their votes...
...on this piece of paper.
If anyone's got pens,
pass it along.
Thank you. Anybody else? Coming through.
Anybody else? Thank you.
We need to get these
votes in quickly.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
Push the button!
We're running out of time!
I need five minutes alone.
No! There's no time!
We have clear shots!
Dent is in there with them.
We have to save Dent!
I have to save Dent.
Get ready.
Two minutes, then we breach.
Fox, I need picture.
-Hello?
-Jim, we're in trouble.
Okay, you got POV on Alpha...
...Omni on beta.
Looks like clowns
and hostages on two floors.
There's a SWAT team
on the stairwell.
Another SWAT team on the roof.
Line's clear.
-Barbara, calm down.
-He has the kids!
-Hello, Jim.
-Harvey?
-Where's my family?
-Where my family died.
Blue team, acquire the target.
Entry team, set your charge.
Fox, the SWATs are targeting the wrong
people. The clowns are the hostages.
Red team, go! Red team, go!
Entry team, blow and go!
Don't move.
Take the shot.
Those SWATs are coming in hot.
Clowns, put down your guns.
Drop your weapons!
On the ground, now!
Doctors, get down! Clear the line of fire.
Drop your weap...
Freeze!
Stand down or you will be...
Look up.
See those bad guys
on the floor above?
They're waiting to ambush the
SWAT team coming up the elevator.
Sixty seconds.
The tally is 140 against, 396 for.
So go ahead. Do it.
We're still here.
And that means they haven't
killed us yet either.
Go, go, go!
Blue team, cover!
Uh-oh.
Trouble on the floor above.
Get down on the ground now!
Freeze! Stop or we will shoot.
We will shoot you.
Drop the officer.
-Release the officer right now.
-Let him go now! On your knees!
We got him.
He's out of the game.
Keep your hands in the air!
Step away from the edge!
Halt!
Stay down! Don't move!
Be advised. Clowns are hostages,
doctors are targets.
Ah, you made it.
I'm so thrilled.
-Where's the detonator?
-Go get him.
Put down your weapon!
Don't move!
You don't wanna die...
...but you don't know
how to take a life.
Give it to me.
These men will kill you
and take it anyway.
No one wants to get
their hands dirty.
Fine. I'll do it.
Those men on that boat?
They made their choices.
They chose to murder and steal.
Doesn't make any sense
for us to have to die too.
All the old familiar places.
Stand by.
Red team, floor secure.
Hostages are safe.
Give it to me.
You can tell them
I took it by force.
Give it to me, and I'll do what you
should've did 10 minutes ago.
We really should stop this fighting,
otherwise we'll miss the fireworks.
There won't be any fireworks.
And here we go.
What were you trying to prove?
That deep down,
everyone's as ugly as you?
You're alone.
Can't rely on anyone these days.
You gotta do everything yourself. Don't we?
That's okay. I came prepared.
It's a funny world we live in.
Speaking of which, you know how I got these scars?
No, but I know
how you got these.
Oh, you.
You just couldn't let
me go, could you?
This is what happens when
an unstoppable force...
...meets an immovable object.
You truly are incorruptible,
aren't you?
Huh? You won't kill me...
...out of some misplaced sense
of self-righteousness.
And I won't kill you...
...because you're
just too much fun.
I think you and I are destined
to do this forever.
You'll be in a padded cell forever.
Maybe we could share one.
You know, they'll be doubling up,
the rate this city's inhabitants are losing their minds.
This city just showed you...
...that it's full of people
ready to believe in good.
Until their spirit
breaks completely.
Until they get a good look
at the real Harvey Dent...
...and all the heroic
things he's done.
You didn't think I'd risk losing
the battle for Gotham's soul...
...in a fistfight with you?
No.
You need an ace in the hole.
Mine's Harvey.
What did you do?
I took Gotham's white knight...
...and I brought him
down to our level.
It wasn't hard.
See, madness, as you know...
...is like gravity.
All it takes is a little push.
Dent!
This is where they brought her, Gordon,
after your men handed her over.
This is where she died.
I know, I was here...
-...trying to save her.
-But you didn't.
-I couldn't.
-Yes, you could've. If you'd listened to me.
If you stood up against corruption...
...instead of doing your deal
with the devil.
I was trying to fight the Mob!
You wouldn't dare try to justify
yourself if you knew what I'd lost.
Have you ever had to talk
to the person you loved most...
...tell them it's gonna be all right,
when you know it's not?
Well, you're about to know
what that feels like, Gordon.
Then you can look me in the eye
and tell me you're sorry.
-You're not going to hurt my family.
-No.
Just the person you love most.
So is it your wife?
Put the gun down, Harvey.
Harvey, put down the gun.
Please. Please, Harvey. Please.
Oh, goddamn it.
Will you stop pointing
that gun at my family?
-No!
-We have a winner.
No, Jim, stop him!
Harvey. Don't let him...
Harvey!
I'm sorry!
For everything.
Please don't hurt my son.
You brought your cops?
All they know
is there's a situation.
They don't know who or what.
They're just creating a perimeter.
You think I wanna
escape from this?
There is no escape from this.
You don't wanna hurt
the boy, Harvey.
It's not about what I want,
it's about what's fair!
You thought we could be decent
men in an indecent time.
But you were wrong.
The world is cruel.
The only morality in a cruel world...
...is chance.
Unbiased.
Unprejudiced.
Fair.
His son's got the same
chance she had.
Fifty-fifty.
What happened to Rachel wasn't chance.
We decided to act.
We three.
Then why was it me
who is the only one who lost everything?
-It wasn't.
-The Joker chose me.
Because you were the best of us.
He wanted to prove that even someone
as good as you...
...could fall.
And he was right.
You're the one pointing
the gun, Harvey.
So point it at the people responsible.
Fair enough.
You first.
My turn.
Harvey, you're right.
Rachel's death was my fault.
Please don't punish the boy.
-Please, punish me.
-I'm about to.
Tell your boy he's gonna
be all right, Gordon.
Lie...
...like I lied.
It's going to be all right, son.
Dad? Daddy, is he okay?
-Thank you.
-You don't have to thank me.
Yes, I do.
The Joker won.
Harvey's prosecution,
everything he fought for...
...undone.
Whatever chance you gave us at fixing
our city dies with Harvey's reputation.
We bet it all on him.
The Joker took the best
of us and tore him down.
People will lose hope.
They won't.
They must never
know what he did.
Five dead.
-Two of them cops. You can't sweep that...
-No.
But the Joker cannot win.
Gotham needs its true hero.
-No.
-You either die a hero...
...or you live long enough to see
yourself become the villain.
I can do those things...
...because I'm not a hero,
not like Dent.
I killed those people.
That's what I can be.
No, no, you can't. You're not.
I'm whatever Gotham needs me to be.
Call it in.
A hero.
Not the hero we deserved,
but the hero we needed.
Nothing less than a knight...
...shining.
They'll hunt you.
You'll hunt me.
You'll condemn me.
Set the dogs on me.
Because that's what needs to happen.
Because sometimes...
...truth isn't good enough.
Sometimes people deserve more.
Sometimes people deserve
to have their faith rewarded.
Batman.
Batman!
Why's he running, Dad?
Because we have to chase him.
Okay, we're going in!
Go, go! Move!
He didn't do anything wrong.
Because he's the hero Gotham deserves,
but not the one it needs right now.
So we'll hunt him...
...because he can take it.
Because he's not a hero.
He's a silent guardian...
...a watchful protector.
A dark knight.