Hasta mañana, Stan.
Have a good one.
[door opens, closes]
[soft thumping]
Donna?
- [flesh sizzles]
- [screams]
[groans in pain]
If you're trying to scare me,
it won't work.
I told you I ain't paying you
a damn cent more.
[jukebox clicking]
[rock music playing on jukebox]
Come on, man. That's enough.
- [music continues]
- [beer bubbling]
[whooshing]
[low growl]
[screaming]
[sighs] Ooh!
- Fresh java. Thank you, baby.
- Yeah.
Hey, I was thinking that we could get
an early dinner reservation tonight.
Sure.
Actually, um,
you know what? Why don't we stay in,
have a quiet night, just the two of us?
That feels better...
Thank you. I'm okay.
You know, I got to get
used to it eventually.
It's just another day.
I can clear my schedule.
I'm fine, really.
Besides, things are...
things are busy at CCC.
You need to be there.
And I need to get to work.
I'm just a phone call away.
I know.
[exhales]
Is it that bad?
[clears throat] Sorry. The fire
just kinda weirds me out, is all.
[clears throat]
The vic's name is Stanley Mullen.
Uh... He's the manager
of this local watering hole.
[Barry] That's weird.
The body's burnt through, but the ground
underneath isn't even charred.
Yeah, this was definitely a meta attack.
Dark matter levels are off the charts.
Whoever the meta is, they produce fire
that ignores the laws of physics.
Oh, man. Now this is giving me,
like, Goodbye-Armageddon-But-Hello-
Dante's-Inferno type of vibe.
- Morning, Allen, Runk.
- [Barry] Morning.
Find anything that can help us
piece this together?
Uh, no, not yet.
Were there any witnesses?
The bartender, Donna Winters,
didn't see the crime,
but, she said our victim got into
a pretty nasty argument last night
with a recently paroled ex-convict.
Apparently, the guy had a bad temper.
Oh, and he was wearing a Lips concert
t-shirt. You know, as in the rock band.
I was gonna ask her
some follow up questions.
Would it be okay if I,
um, showed her a picture
of someone who could be our suspect?
Sure.
Donna, this is CSI Barry Allen
and C.C.P.D. Consultant, Chester Runk.
Miss Winters, the person you saw arguing
with the victim, was this him?
That's him. That's the guy.
Jaco Birch. I'll put out an APB.
This way, ma'am.
The Hotness did this?
I thought it was all about the moolah,
not cold-blooded murder.
Plus, how do you kill someone
without burning half the place down?
Looks like we're not
the only ones who leveled up this year.
Here you go, boss lady.
This is every suggestion
the Bullpen brainstormed for who should
be our first CC Citizen of the Week.
Nice work.
Only, this is every suggestion...
except the winning one.
- Rosie Levin?
- Hmm?
Uh... Boss, I don't think launching
our first profile section
on some shallow social media influencer
is the way to go.
I just thought we were supposed to be
the voice of the people.
I hear you.
But Rosie Levin is who
the people are interested in.
Five hundred thousand of them,
to be exact.
And if we can bring those eyeballs
to CCC,
then, hopefully, people will read
the stories that matter.
Is there something
that you want to tell me?
Yeah. Okay, fine.
Taylor brought this to me earlier,
and I told her it wasn't right for us.
And she went behind my back.
She believed in the story,
and she followed protocol
and made an appeal
to the editor-in-chief.
And I approved it.
Is that a problem?
Yes. I mean, no.
I just mean if the Bullpen
knows they can come to you
when I say no, my word means nothing.
Look, you're still their boss.
But I'm also yours.
And that means that sometimes
we are going to disagree on the stories
that we tell.
It's a part of the process.
Yeah, you're right. Of course, I...
Actually, you know what?
Why don't you both interview Rosie?
You want Taylor and me to work together?
You are my Supervising Editor.
Go supervise.
Plus, opposing perspectives
make for better stories.
And keep an open mind. I mean, you might
be surprised at what the two of you
can do together.
Yeah. You got it.
Whoa, whoa.
Easy with the guitars, roadies.
You're unloading the gilded weapons
of true rock gods. Come on.
Trust your old man, Harold.
Watching the Lips concert
is gonna blow your freaking mind.
Yeah. Whatever, dude.
Hey, I'm sorry I couldn't land
the backstage passes
I promised. All right?
I kind of ran into
a little bit of a cash flow issue.
You bribe me here with stuff
you couldn't even get, Jaco.
Even more lame than usual.
I know, right? [chuckles nervously]
But, uh, hey, look, maybe after
the show, we could grab some food. Huh?
I could tell you some stories
about these crazy things
these bands I'm working with get into.
You aren't with the bands, Jaco. You're
arena security. Anyone can do that.
I'm gonna go for a walk.
Look... Look, Harold...
[siren wailing]
Whoa.
Jaco Birch, you're under arrest
for the murder of Stanley Mullen.
I think you got the wrong guy.
What's going on?
Take him somewhere safe.
Hey...
Let go of me, jerk.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get your hands off my son!
Calm down and put your hands
behind your back.
Nobody's taking my kid away from me.
Never again!
[groans]
Thanks, Flash. We've got it from here.
Harold, I'm innocent, I swear.
I'm innocent.
Please, believe me.
Flash, you've got to help me. Please.
I didn't do anything.
Please! I can't lose my son! Please.
I didn't do this. I swear to God,
I didn't do this.
- Where's Mom?
- What's going to happen to my son?
- Dad!
- Barry!
Dad!
Harold, I didn't do anything, I swear.
I swear. Please, believe me. Please!
Okay. I got to be honest.
Eh... Based on these police reports,
I'd advise Mr. Birch here to start
thinking about a plea bargain.
[sighs] Okay.
I'm guessing you feel differently.
I... I just want to make sure
they got the right guy.
Well, it seems like they do.
He had an argument with the victim
hours before he was killed.
He's got no alibi.
The crime matches his powers,
and the guy is an ex-con.
Who was released early
for good behavior.
Korber and those other officers
could have been killed, too,
if you hadn't intervened.
[stammers]
I know how it looks for Birch,
but there isn't any hard evidence
that he's guilty.
And last night,
he supposedly killed a man.
And then, instead of laying low,
he went back to work this morning?
As a security guard, of all things?
It's just... It doesn't add up.
Yeah. Stranger things have happened.
I know. Look, I've worked
hundreds of cases like this,
and I'm telling you something about this
just... it doesn't feel right to me.
Okay. Okay, but you know
that Birch had motive
and opportunity to commit this murder.
You didn't see the look on his face
when they took him from his son.
He was...
He was begging for me
to believe that he's innocent.
And you do.
I'm not sure yet.
Look, would you be willing
to meet with him?
To get a read on his emotions?
Yes, of course, I'll meet with him.
Guilty or not,
everyone deserves proper representation.
But, Barry...
using my powers to read a client?
It's an ethical line that I can't cross.
Yeah, of course. I'm sorry. I...
I just don't want to see someone
go to prison for a murder
they might not have committed.
[Taylor] So, Rosie,
dropping out of Cornell to become
a social media influencer took guts.
What inspired you
to make such a bold decision?
Let's just say
institutionalized learning
felt like a total prison.
Uh! Mm-hmm.
Trust me, it's not.
What my supervisor means
is that our readers are just so eager
to get to know the real Rosie Levin.
So sorry. Will you excuse me?
Uh... [sighs]
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what her problem is.
Uh, now, uh, why don't you take me
through a typical day?
Lydia.
Garcia.
[scoffs]
Oh, my God, it's so good to see you.
How are you?
[chuckles]
Well, look who decided to come say hi.
I haven't seen you since Iron Heights.
At least, not in person.
Then, again, your face is plastered
all over that news website.
CCC Media. Yeah, I... I work there now.
These days, I'm writing the headlines,
not starring in them. [chuckles]
Must be nice.
So, you've been working here
since you got out?
No. Um, my first gig was cleaning out
porta potties. That was fun.
I guess this is kind of like
a promotion for me.
Not that you care.
What's that supposed to mean?
I get it. You're too busy
to help out old friends.
You're mad because I'm a reporter now?
Look. You got out, walked into
a legit career. Good for you.
Meanwhile, I busted my butt
to get my GED in prison
and look where it got me.
[chuckles nervously]
This is just temporary.
I mean, I'm sure you can do better.
Gee, thanks.
I didn't mean it like that.
I know what you meant.
The truth is, cleaning floors
is the best job I can get
with a record like mine.
People like you don't see
who I'm trying to be, only who I was.
Makes it really hard, you know.
No. I don't know.
Not yet. But...
I'd like to try and help you.
How could you possibly help me?
Let me share your story with the world.
Trust me.
Before we get into this,
I need to know my son's okay.
The cops won't tell me anything.
Yeah, Harold is fine.
He's with Social Services
just until they can track down his mom.
Good luck with that.
She's been in and out of his life
since he was born.
No telling when she'll turn up again.
Harold's mother, she took care of him
while you were in Iron Heights, right?
Barely.
That's why I got my act together
and got the hell out of that place.
But Harold, he never forgave me for
abandoning him, and I don't blame him.
Every second of the four years
I spent in that prison,
it was like he was serving time, too.
The thing is, Harold's a good kid.
I don't know what he did
to deserve a father like me.
Okay. Why don't you tell me
what happened last night?
Stan and I got into it at the bar.
I sold him a guitar
so I could buy Harold
backstage passes to the Lips concert.
And, at the last minute, Stan decided to
only pay me half of what we agreed on.
Then what happened?
Sure, we argued.
And, yeah, I told him this wasn't over.
But then I went home.
That's the last I saw of Stan.
Is there anybody that can confirm that?
Anybody? Was your son home
with you last night?
No, he was out with friends.
So, unless my vinyl collection
can talk...
I got nothing.
All right.
Listen, I've been around long enough
to know
you're about to tell me I'm screwed.
But I'm telling you, I'm innocent.
Jaco, the bartender
places you at the scene
moments before the crime.
Any jury is going to see that
as more than enough evidence to convict.
No!
I won't leave my son
without a dad again, okay?
You got that?
[Cecile] Look, I wish I had
something better to tell you, Barry,
but Birch just doesn't have the pieces
that you need to build a strong defense,
and all of the evidence, it's still
pointing to him as the killer.
I... I know you didn't use
your abilities in there,
but what does your gut tell you?
It's telling me that whether
he is actually innocent or not,
he definitely believes that he is.
But it's not nearly enough.
Yeah, but look, if there is any chance
he is innocent, we have to help him.
[gate opening]
What's going on?
Jaco Birch just escaped custody
en route to holding.
- Was anybody hurt?
- Thankfully, no.
But so much for
his "I'm innocent" sob story, huh?
[Donna gasps]
You told the cops I killed Stan?
Come on, man.
I only told them what I saw.
And when you think about it,
I really didn't see anything.
Hey, you and me are... are good, right?
I'm gonna lose my son because of you.
Because of what you said!
Hey, man, relax.
Maybe I didn't see anything.
Damn straight,
'cause you're gonna take it back.
You're gonna take it all back right now!
Wait, man, please! [screams]
[system beeping]
- Nothing on the satellites yet.
- Okay, keep trying.
We have to figure out where Birch
is going before C.C.P.D. does.
It's the only way we'll have a chance
to prove he's innocent.
I'm sorry, are we talking about the guy
who just burned his way
through a C.C.P.D. transport convoy?
The fact that Birch ran away
doesn't change the evidence.
There's still nothing directly tying him
to Mullen's death.
Sure. Barry, sure, but fleeing custody
is not exactly exculpatory.
And I'm saying that as his lawyer.
She's right, Barr,
if Jaco Birch is innocent, why run?
Why did Frost run
when Chillblaine framed her?
Because, unfortunately,
sometimes people don't get a fair shot
from the justice system.
Yeah, and, as a former DA, I know.
I know that sometimes it's true,
they don't.
Okay, but how do we know Birch isn't
the same hothead he's always been?
I mean, he'd be halfway across
the country by now.
No, he didn't skip town.
Not without his son.
And you know this how?
- I just do.
- Okay.
Uh, guys, emergency dispatch
is getting calls about a fire
right outside O'Shaughnessy's.
[Cecile] What?
Why would Birch go back
to the scene of the crime?
If it's really Birch.
Yeah, I'll find out.
I'll go with you for backup.
Holy crap.
What kind of fire is this?
I think I know who this is.
Is that the witness who pinned it
on Birch? The bartender?
You know, your innocent man, Barr,
is not looking so innocent anymore.
I thought we were supposed
to be working together on this.
Next time. Right now,
I am in the zone.
I thought I saw you two were back.
How'd the interview go?
Great. I feel like the story
is exploding out of me.
So, everything went well?
[sighs in exasperation] Yeah. Peachy.
Seriously, you're gonna love
what I'm doing here. I promise.
[clears throat] Excuse me,
I just need to get some air.
[chuckles awkwardly]
All right.
Well, I'll let you get back to it.
I'm looking forward
to reading the finished product.
Roger that.
I got back the tomography reports
from the crime lab.
Donna Winters, the bartender who died,
the thermal lesions on her body match
the marks on Stan Mullen's body exactly.
Too exactly.
I mean, there's no pyrokinetic meta
who could replicate burns like that
even if they tried.
I... I... I told you. Something about
Birch's case just wasn't adding up.
Barry, we're the ones who told Birch
that Donna blamed him
for the first murder
and now Donna is dead.
She's dead.
You have gotta see
how that looks, right?
Yeah, but the facts are still
on Birch's side.
Neither crime scene
has any direct evidence tying him to it.
No DNA, no fingerprints, no witnesses...
That are still alive.
Barry, you gotta admit,
Birch has motive.
And the more emotional he gets,
the stronger his powers are.
Like, you know, earth-shattering.
Thank goodness
he wasn't in a bad mood today.
That doesn't make him a killer.
[Cecile sighs]
Okay, look, we know that you're just
trying to do the right thing here,
we do.
But, Barry, we can't help but wonder if
just maybe you're not thinking clearly
about this case.
Oh, so that's it.
You've already decided.
You're giving up on him.
No, we're just looking at
the facts, man.
So am I.
And two exact fire signatures
makes me think Birch is not our guy.
Chester, could you please
at least take a look at this
and see what you can find?
Yeah, okay.
Look, I know that you've all thought
Birch was guilty from the start...
[Cecile] No, we haven't.
That's not true.
Each of us have been trying
to help him from the beginning.
But then Birch ran off.
He was just trying to protect his son.
What about other suspects?
There are none.
Both victims worked at O'Shaughnessy's.
Maybe they, uh, owed somebody money
or pissed off the wrong person.
I... I get Birch is a known fire-meta
and an ex-con.
That also makes him
the perfect fall guy.
Okay, now you think he's being framed.
I'm saying it's possible.
Look, Birch is the freaking Hotness
and a bad guy.
It feels like he's changed.
Not to us.
And, honestly,
it feels like you're asking us
to believe in something impossible.
Yeah, I am.
'Cause if anyone had when I was a kid,
my dad wouldn't have gone to jail.
Barry.
Barry, honey.
Look, we're... We're sorry.
We weren't thinking.
Look, here's the deal.
I believe Birch is innocent.
So, with or without your help,
I'm gonna do everything
within my power to clear his name.
[Joe] That looks familiar.
It's been, what, seven, eight years
since I've seen this board.
Except, the last time it was covered
with photos of a different man.
Cecile told me what happened.
The team is worried about you.
No, they don't have to be. I'm fine.
No, you're not.
They don't know what today is.
I do.
February 1st. Henry's birthday.
You remember, when he was turning 45...
and your mom threw that surprise party?
The whole block showed up,
and you were baking cupcakes for weeks.
And when the big night came,
before he can even take off his coat...
his pager went off.
A patient needed him.
He had to miss his own party.
And you were disappointed,
of course, but you understood.
He was helping save
people's lives, right?
Yeah.
But Henry, he was crushed.
He was worried that he was missing
all these moments
with you and your mom.
But I told him,
"Those cupcakes might be stale now,
but... you'll have more birthdays
with both of them."
Only, there weren't.
That was the last one
before it happened.
- Barry!
- Dad!
Stay out of the house!
Barry!
Joe, the look in my dad's eyes
that night...
it was the same look in Birch's eyes
when they arrested him.
Look of an innocent man
desperate not to lose his son.
Begging someone to believe him.
And you do?
Yeah, I do.
I just keep thinking about
all the time my dad lost.
[sighs wearily]
All the birthdays we spent
separated by Plexiglas.
I can't let Birch and his son
go through that if he's innocent.
I don't know, maybe the team's right.
Maybe I'm making something
out of nothing.
Do you think maybe I've had blinders up
this whole time?
Maybe.
Or...
you can see something they can't.
Look...
what you went through,
I wouldn't wish on anyone.
But what it did was it gave you
the ability to believe in the underdog
when no one else is willing to.
So...
if your gut tells you...
to not give up on Birch...
then, for Henry's sake, don't.
Not yet.
[cell phone chirps]
[Allegra] So, what do you think?
I think the lede is in the second graph,
not the first.
But, besides that, it is a very engaging
and beautifully written article.
I think it's gonna open a lot of eyes.
Seriously, you like it?
Yes, I do.
But, Allegra,
as strong as that article is,
that's not what I assigned you.
I know, but I have
a unique insight into Lydia,
and me connecting
with the story so much
is what's gonna make it connect
with our audience.
Agreed.
But I wanted you
to make this special
and to help support a colleague.
There's some decent writing in Taylor's
article, but it's all surface.
There's no context.
There's no examination
of Rosie's influence on young women.
Allegra, you could have made
this story so much better
if you would have helped her,
like I asked you to do.
Yeah, Iris, I'm so sorry.
The interview with Rosie,
it wasn't going anywhere.
So, you abandoned it?
I followed my instinct.
I... I thought that's what
you'd want me to do.
What I want is for you to learn
how to be a supervisor.
That's why I'm trying to teach you
how to mentor her.
Instead, you did just the opposite.
But... I have an obligation
to our readers
to publish the best articles that I can,
and your profile on Lydia is amazing.
I think it's gonna start
an important conversation.
So, we're gonna go with it.
But, next time, please run
any changes this big by me first.
And another thing,
I want you to talk to Taylor.
You're her immediate boss,
so it's up to you to fix this,
not the other way around.
[Barry] Chester, what'd you find?
- You were right.
- Yeah, check this out.
[Chester] So, I cross referenced
the heat signature from O'Shaughnessy's
to the one in the alleyway
from the second victim, like you asked.
Guess what I found.
Both signatures produced
an anomalous heat effect
created by non-composites reacting
to hydrogen isotopes.
Nuclear fusion.
What you're describing is cold fusion.
But Birch's powers come
from absorbing heat, not nuclear fusion,
meaning...
He's innocent.
Yeah. We get this data to C.C.P.D.,
we can clear his name.
Okay, Chester,
put everything you have on a drive.
I need to get this
to Captain Kramer fast.
I need to find Birch.
[computer chirping]
Let's hope he doesn't do
anything else stupid
before we can clear his name.
Harold, I know this is tough, but we're
gonna find you a place to stay.
I'm here to make sure your transition
is as easy as possible. Okay?
Whatever.
I'm used to Jaco being a screw up.
Especially since he got his powers.
I want my son!
Now!
Harold, get out of the car.
Get down on your knees
with your hands above your head.
I'm not letting you cart my son off
to a bunch of strangers. Harold!
Birch, I said get down.
Why won't you leave me alone?
C.C.P.D. scanners have Birch
at Hastings Avenue and Nicola Lane.
Oh. Man, satellites just picked up
a city vehicle at the exact same spot.
It's a Social Services SUV.
He's trying to get his son.
Barry, C.C.P.D. still doesn't know
that Birch is innocent.
- If he tries to take his kid by force...
- We have to stop him...
before he does something he'll regret.
- Birch, listen to me.
- No, you listen.
I just want my son.
Now get out of my way.
[low rumbling]
Wait. Wait. No, wait, wait.
- Harold, stay back.
- She's right, son.
- It's too dangerous.
- I'm not scared of him.
[rumbling continues]
Look, Harold, I know how bad this looks,
but I swear I'd never hurt anyone.
What's wrong with you?
You get that
you're a total loser, right?
I am a total loser.
Have been since the day I was born.
I thought having powers
would change all that,
but all they did was make things worse.
And now they've turned the only
good thing in my life against me.
My own kid!
[rumbling intensifies]
All I wanted
when I got out of Iron Heights
was a clean start,
to get my life together
so we can be a family.
This is your final warning.
Who cares? No matter what I do,
you'll always think I'm a killer.
And now you want to take
my son away forever?
Well, I won't let you!
[panting]
You can't keep me from my family, Flash.
No one's taking Harold away.
I know you didn't kill anyone, Birch,
your lawyer found evidence
to prove you're innocent.
But you have to stop what you're doing
before anyone gets hurt.
Okay.
All right?
[loud rumbling]
[car alarm ringing]
Oh, come on.
I'm not doing anything.
It's not what you're doing,
it's what you already did.
Officer, get them to safety!
Thanks for the save.
Birch, your heat abilities,
they're connected to the earth
beneath wherever you're standing.
Yeah, science is not my strong suit, but
yeah, okay, I'll buy that for a dollar.
He means emotionally.
Ooh.
- Right.
- Chester,
can you scan
for thermal activity below us?
Yeah, yeah.
[device beeping]
Mary Mack Gibson Jr.
Okay, there's a volcano's worth of magma
erupting beneath the city's lower crust.
When Birch was upset,
he must've absorbed so much heat
from the planet's core that
he opened up a lava channel.
Flash, if you can't stop this
in the next 30 seconds,
Central City's gonna turn into
Mount Doom.
Officer, get them back!
Flash, you got to do something.
I know this is all my fault.
But everyone in this city,
my son, he can't die because of me.
You got to save him.
No, you have to save him.
Look, I've got an idea.
If it works, there's gonna be a huge
release of pressure forming beneath us.
When that happens, I need you
to absorb the remaining heat.
I've never done
anything like that before.
You can do this.
I know you can.
Okay, ten seconds.
Time to ride or die, people.
Let's rock.
[rock music playing]
Where'd he go?
I don't know, but I'm detecting
new activity right under the surface.
Fifty meters down.
No, no, wait, 90 meters down.
One hundred and ten meters. 120 meters.
Whoa! Flash is doing his thing
underground, y'all.
So get ready.
[screaming]
Yes!
Yes. Yes.
You don't see that every day.
Not that I'm complaining,
but how did you do that?
[panting] I phased into the water table
under the city,
then released it
directly into the lava channel.
I stopped the meltdown,
but not the massive heat exchange
that was being released.
What I couldn't stop,
but knew Birch could.
Otherwise, everybody within
a ten block radius...
...would've been fried like
a Bananas Foster's
in the French Quarter.
Mark and I are
going to Mardi Gras next year.
Okay.
Wait. So, saving hundreds of lives...
Try thousands.
...saving that many lives
is what I just did?
Yeah.
Looks like you're
the father Harold deserves after all.
You okay?
You used your powers again.
I know. I know...
To save us.
Thanks, Dad.
I love you. I love you.
Okay. Okay.
Social Services is
on their way with Harold.
They should be here any minute.
[exhales]
I can't believe they're actually
letting me have custody of my son.
That evidence you found saved my ass.
Plus, Harold is almost 18
and Judge Hankerson
let him decide where he wanted to be.
- And, you know, with his mom being...
- MIA as always?
You and Harold are getting
another chance. A real one this time.
It's all because of you two.
And The Flash.
Yeah, but...
[sighs]
you're the one
who told him not to give up on me.
[chuckles]
- I'm just really grateful.
- Yeah.
Thanks. Thank you.
And if there's ever anything
I can do for you, just let me know.
Uh... Just be there for Harold.
- Are you okay?
- I will be.
Hey there, kiddo.
Hey.
Come on.
Dinner is on me.
We've got a lot to catch up on.
[exhales]
Barry, they are gonna be all right.
I guess the real question is...
are you?
Come to gloat?
No. Kind of the opposite.
I guess you saw the first article
for our new profile section.
- You mean yours?
- Taylor,
I know how this looks and...
I want to apologize.
Yes, Iris loves the Sanchez story,
but we are running
your piece on Rosie Levin next week.
And our audience deserves to read it.
Thanks.
So, tell me, what did I do to deserve
getting stabbed in the back
by my own supervisor?
Iris assigned you to help me,
not run me over,
which is exactly what you did.
I didn't mean to. And you're right,
I shouldn't have done that.
I just... I got excited,
and I guess I felt like
Lydia's story was something
our readers needed right now.
And that's how I felt about my story.
Iris did, too, until you called in
a favor with the boss.
Guess you learned that in prison.
[scoffs]
You're right.
I got lost in a great story.
You stole my byline.
Taylor, we are still publishing
your article.
Because Iris is a journalist
with ethics.
Something you are clearly lacking.
Fine. Good to know.
Look, I messed up. I said I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
But I am still your supervisor.
So I'm hoping we can get past this.
Okay?
I'm gonna destroy you. Yeah?
Shouldn't we be toasting with champagne?
Mm-mm. Plain old light beer,
that was Henry's favorite.
And I used to give him hell about it.
I'd say,
"You're a doctor,
you should have better taste."
Then he'd laugh and he'd say,
"Well, I'll drink something
more expensive when you buy it."
[all laughing]
Do you guys remember when Henry
filled in on Dad's softball team?
Oh, my gosh, what a disaster.
What? What happened?
Well, even as a kid,
I knew that you're not supposed
to catch a ball with your face.
[Cecile] Oh, no.
No. Really?
Yeah. Right in the nose.
Good thing he was a doctor.
He was able to reset it himself.
Hey, babe, are you okay?
Yeah, no, it's... you know, it's nice to
hear everybody remembering him this way.
What do you remember the most?
Yeah, little things, mostly.
[chuckles]
Um...
Like, [stutters] he never made me
clean my plate at dinner,
even when all I'd eat were carbs,
like mac and cheese
or those Hawaiian dinner rolls.
[Iris West] Mm.
I... I kept asking him
to read me the same bedtime story
over and over.
It was one about
the hippo who went to school
and made cookies for everyone,
and then became their friends.
I can see how ridiculous
that must have been now.
No, I'm sure he enjoyed it.
[exhales]
Mostly, I just remember being loved.
I still miss him, every day.
And that is okay.
Yeah.
Well...
happy birthday, Dad.
So if Birch didn't kill those two,
then who did?
I've checked
every fire-based meta human in here,
everyone's either still at Iron Heights
or alibied up.
So, what do we do now?
I know what Joe would say.
No suspects? Then shift your focus
to where it matters.
The victims.
But Stan and Donna were different ages,
races and genders.
But they both worked at O'Shaughnessy's.
So the killer's a disgruntled employee?
Or they were chosen at random,
and we're still missing something.
What are you thinking?
Chester, the cold fusion data
we pulled off the bodies,
could you program those variables
into the satellites?
Sure. What am I looking for?
More victims.
If there's a meta serial killer
out there, we need to find them...
...before somebody else gets hurt.