Get out.
I am so sick and tired of his bullshit.
On and on. Pompous prick.
A long time ago, when we first
came here, it was so different.
He was so different.
He was like you.
I'll give you what you want,
but you have to give me something.
- What?
- A kiss.
Excuse me?
I want you to kiss me
as if you were kissing her.
- Why?
- You love her. She loves you.
It's all over you both.
A long time ago,
I knew what that felt like.
I want to remember it.
I want to sample it. That's all.
Just a sample.
- Why don't you sample this instead?
- Trinity.
Such emotion over something so small.
It's just a kiss.
Why should we trust you?
If I don't deliver you to the Keymaker,
she can kill me.
All right.
But you have to make me believe
I am her.
All right.
Terrible. Forget it.
Wait.
Okay.
Yes.
That's it.
I envy you. But such a thing
is not meant to last.
Come with me.
Not again.
It's all right, boys. They're with me.
These fellas work for my husband.
They do his dirty work.
They're very good, very loyal.
Aren't you, boys?
Yes, mistress.
They come from a much older version
of the Matrix.
But like so many back then, they caused
more problems than they solved.
My husband saved them because
they're notoriously difficult to terminate.
How many people keep silver bullets
in their gun?
You can either run and tell my husband
what I have done...
...or you can stay there and die.
He's in the ladies' room!
Hurry.
- My name is Neo.
- Yes. I'm the Keymaker.
I've been waiting for you.
My God! My God, Persephone,
how could you do this? You betray me.
- Cause and effect, my love.
- Cause?
There is no cause for this. What cause?
What cause? How about the lipstick
you're still wearing?
Lipstick? Lipstick.
What craziness are you talking about,
woman? There is no lipstick!
She wasn't kissing your face, my love.
Woman, this is nothing.
- It is a game. It is only a game.
- So is this.
Have fun.
All right.
Let us find out where this goes.
You two, get the Keymaker.
That's a nice trick.
I cannot go back.
I'll handle them.
Handle us? You'll handle us? You know,
your predecessors had much more respect.
Okay, you have some skill.
Kill him.
You see? He's just a man.
Goddamn it, woman,
you will be the end of me.
Mark my words, boy,
and mark them well.
I have survived your predecessors,
and I will survive you.
- Where are you going?
- Another way. Always another way.
Close it, quick!
Could we move along?
Run!
Step away from the door.
We owe you for that.
Just like new.
Drop your weapon.
- Stay with him.
- What about Neo?
He can handle himself.
Get in back.
Shit.
- Operator.
- Link, where am I?
You won't believe this,
but you're way up in the mountains.
- Really?
- It'll take me a while to get an exit.
- Shit!
- What?
The twins are after Morpheus and Trinity.
They don't have a way out.
- Where are they?
- Middle of the city, 500 miles due south.
- Operator.
- Get us out of here.
- Won't be easy.
- I know. We're inside the core network.
The only exit I got
near you is the Winslow overpass.
- Off the freeway.
- Yes, sir.
- Fine, we'll make it.
- I should- Oh, shit! Look out behind you!
- Incoming fire.
- Down!
Hold on!
Oh, no. This is getting real ugly
real fast.
Are you watching this, Link?
Yes, sir. There's an all points on you.
Eight units headed your way.
Any suggestions?
- Turn right.
- Right, now.
Straight here.
You'll hit a connecting tunnel to the 101.
- Got it.
- You sure about this? The freeway, I mean.
- In 14 years of operating, I've never seen-
- Link, what did I tell you?
Yes, sir. I do, sir. Winslow overpass.
- I'll be ready for you.
- Good man.
You always told me
to stay off the freeway.
- Yes, that's true.
- You said it was suicide.
Then let us hope...
...that I was wrong.
- Operator.
- Link, it's Niobe.
We've been sent to bring you in.
- I need to talk to Morpheus.
- Believe me, Niobe, he needs you.
- Where is he?
- Just follow the sirens.
Repeat, they're approaching the-
- We have them now.
- The exile is the primary target.
Shots fired.
Move!
- We are getting aggravated.
- Yes, we are.
Trinity.
Get him out of here.
Come on!
Crush him.
Morpheus.
He's okay. Keep moving.
Let's go.
I need a download
to hot-wire a motorcycle.
No problem.
One crash course on motorcycle-
Wait.
Cancel that.
You are handy.
Jump on.
She means nothing.
- Find the exile.
- We have them.
One-Adam- 12, please respond.
Get down.
Gotcha.
She's good.
You are no longer necessary.
We do only what we're meant to do.
Then you are meant for one more thing:
deletion.
Go kick his ass.
Neo, if you're out there,
I could use some help.
What is that?
Yes! Yes!
We have confirmation from the Icarus.
First two ships
are in position for counterattack.
Good.
Any change?
They hit some iron ore here.
Slowed them down a little.
- How much?
- An hour, maybe.
That would give them
a little over nine hours.
Yes, sir.
There is a building.
Inside this building, there is a level
where no elevator can go...
...and no stair can reach.
This level is filled with doors.
These doors lead to many places.
Hidden places.
But one door is special.
One door leads to the source.
This building is protected
by a very secure system.
- Every alarm triggers the bomb.
- Bomb? Did he say bomb?
But like all systems,
it has a weakness.
The system is based on the rules
of a building.
- One system built on another.
- Electricity.
- If one fails, so must the other.
- No electricity, no alarms.
You'd have to take out a city block
to kill the power.
- Not one, 27.
- Twenty-seven blocks?
There is a power station.
It must be destroyed.
- There must be some kind of fail-safe.
- Yes, there is an emergency system.
The core network of the grid
must be accessed.
The emergency system
must be deactivated.
What do you need us for?
Neo could take them out
easier than we could.
- There's no time.
- Why?
Once the door is unprotected,
the connection will be severed.
But another connection
must first be made.
- How long will that take?
- Exactly 314 seconds.
Just over five minutes.
That is the length and breadth
of the window.
Only the One can open the door...
...and only during that window
can the door be opened.
How do you know all this?
I know because I must know.
It is my purpose.
It's the reason I'm here,
the same reason we're all here.
Neo, I know something's wrong.
You don't have to tell me.
I just want you to know that I'm here.
All must be done as one.
Can't hurt.
If one fails...
...all fail.
At midnight, there is a shift change
in the security of both buildings.
At midnight, we will strike.
Hey!
- You count sheep at home.
- Why? I get paid to count them here.
Okay, they're inside.
- How much time?
- Twelve minutes.
Oh, shit.
All of our lives, we have fought this war.
Tonight, I believe we can end it.
Tonight is not an accident.
There are no accidents.
We have not come here by chance.
I do not believe in chance.
When I see three objectives,
three captains, three ships...
...I do not see coincidence.
I see providence.
I see purpose.
I believe it is our fate to be here.
It is our destiny.
I believe this night holds
for each and every one of us...
...the very meaning of our lives.
I want to ask you to do something,
but I don't know how.
I promise you, if I can, I will.
What if I asked you to stay out of this...
...no matter what...
...to stay out of the Matrix?
Why?
Please.
All right.
What is it, Niobe?
I can't help it, Morpheus. I can't
help thinking, what if you're wrong?
What if all this, the prophecy,
everything, is bullshit?
Then tomorrow we may all be dead.
But how would that be different
from any other day?
This is a war, and we are soldiers.
Death can come for us at any time...
...in any place.
Incoming. Incoming!
Incoming!
Now consider the alternative.
What if I am right?
What if the prophecy is true?
What if tomorrow the war could be over?
Isn't that worth fighting for?
Isn't that worth dying for?
- Time?
- Three minutes.
Almost there.
It is done.
Find the others.
I got Niobe there.
They're out of the station.
- What about Soren?
- There.
They're still inside, but...
They're not moving.
That's it, let's go.
Call Neo now.
- I lost them. They're inside the portal.
- What about the grid?
Everything is operational.
The emergency system is rerouting power.
Jesus.
Soon as they open that door,
it's all over.
The hell it is.
What are you-? Trinity!
I will not wait and do nothing.
I will not watch them die.
We're talking less than five minutes.
In five minutes,
I'll tear that building down.
- How much further?
- Here, just here.
I'm sorry, this is a dead end.
It's gotta be the ugliest hack
I have ever done.
That's as close as I can get you.
You better grow wings.
- Operator.
- I'm in.
Keep moving. Sixty-fifth floor.
You look surprised to see me again,
Mr. Anderson.
Well, that's the difference between us.
I have been expecting you.
- What do you want, Smith?
- You haven't figured that out?
Still using all the muscles
except the one that matters.
I want exactly what you want.
I want everything.
Would that include a bullet
from this gun?
Go ahead, shoot.
The best thing about being me,
there's so many me's.
Christ! What the hell happened in here?
Hold it right there, little lady.
If you can't beat us...
Join us.
Morpheus!
Still no sight of them.
They only got two minutes left.
One minute.
Come on.
Please.
Kill them.
They're in.
I don't believe it.
It was meant to be.
Morpheus, that door will take you home.
You will know which door.
Hurry, Neo.
Trinity, I got some serious activity
headed your way.
Hello, Neo.
- Who are you?
- I am the Architect.
I created the Matrix.
I've been waiting for you.
You have many questions. Though the
process has altered your consciousness...
...you remain irrevocably human.
Ergo, some of my answers you will
understand and some you will not.
Concordantly, while your first question
may be the most pertinent...
...you may or may not realize
it is also the most irrelevant.
Why am I here?
Your life is the sum of a remainder
of an unbalanced equation...
...inherent to the programming
of the Matrix.
You are the eventuality of an anomaly,
which despite my sincerest efforts...
...I've been unable to eliminate
from what is otherwise...
...a harmony of mathematical precision.
While it remains a burden
assiduously avoided...
...it is not unexpected and thus
not beyond a measure of control...
...which has led you, inexorably...
...here.
- You haven't answered my question.
- Quite right.
Interesting.
That was quicker than the others.
Others? How many?
What others?
The Matrix is older than you know.
I count from the emergence of one integral
anomaly to the emergence of the next.
In which case, this is the sixth version.
Five before me?
He's lying. Bullshit.
There are only two possible explanations.
There were five before me.
Either no one told me...
- ... or no one knows.
- Precisely.
As you are undoubtedly gathering,
the anomaly is systemic...
...creating fluctuations in even
the most simplistic equations.
You can't control me!
I'm gonna smash you to bits!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
You can't make me do anything.
You old, white prick!
Choice.
The problem is choice.
The first Matrix I designed
was naturally perfect, a work of art.
Flawless, sublime.
A triumph equaled only
by its monumental failure.
The inevitability of its doom
is apparent now...
...as a consequence of the imperfection
inherent in every human.
Thus, I redesigned it
based on your history...
...to more accurately reflect
the varying grotesqueries of your nature.
However, I was again frustrated
by failure.
I have come to understand
that the answer eluded me...
...because it required a lesser mind.
Or perhaps, a mind less bound
by the parameters of perfection.
Thus, the answer was stumbled upon
by another, an intuitive program...
...initially created to investigate
certain aspects of the human psyche.
If I am the father of the Matrix,
she would undoubtedly be its mother.
- The Oracle.
- Please.
As I was saying, she stumbled upon a
solution whereby 99 percent of subjects...
...accepted the program, as long as they
were given a choice...
...even if they were only aware
of the choice at a near unconscious level.
While this answer functioned,
it was fundamentally flawed...
...thus creating the otherwise
contradictory systemic anomaly...
...that, if left unchecked,
might threaten the system.
Ergo, those that refused the program,
while a minority, if unchecked...
...would constitute
an escalating probability of disaster.
This is about Zion.
You are here because Zion
is about to be destroyed.
Its every living inhabitant terminated,
its entire existence eradicated.
Bullshit.
Denial is the most predictable
of all human responses.
But rest assured, this will be
the sixth time we have destroyed it...
...and we have become
exceedingly efficient at it.
The function of the One...
...is now to return to the source, allowing
a dissemination of the code you carry...
...reinserting the prime program.
After which you will be required to select
from the Matrix 23 individuals...
...sixteen female, seven male,
to rebuild Zion.
Failure to comply with this process
will result in a cataclysmic system crash...
...killing everyone connected
to the Matrix...
...which, coupled with the
extermination of Zion...
...will result in the extinction
of the entire human race.
You won't let it happen. You can't.
You need human beings to survive.
There are levels of survival
we are prepared to accept.
The relevant issue is
whether or not you are ready...
...to accept the responsibility for the
death of every human being in this world.
It is interesting reading your reactions.
Your five predecessors were, by design,
based on a similar predication...
...a contingent affirmation that was meant
to create a profound attachment...
...to the rest of your species,
facilitating the function of the One.
While the others experience this
in a general way...
...your experience is far more specific...
...vis-à-vis love.
Trinity!
Apropos, she entered the Matrix
to save your life at the cost of her own.
No.
Which brings us at last to the moment
of truth, wherein the fundamental flaw...
...is ultimately expressed
and the anomaly revealed...
...as both beginning and end.
There are two doors.
The door to your right leads to the source
and the salvation of Zion.
The door to your left leads back to the
Matrix, to her and the end of your species.
As you adequately put,
the problem is choice.
But we already know what
you are going to do, don't we?
Already I can see the chain reaction,
the chemical precursors that signal...
...the onset of an emotion designed
specifically to overwhelm logic and reason.
An emotion that is already blinding you
from the simple and obvious truth:
She is going to die and there is nothing
you can do to stop it.
Hope. It is the quintessential
human delusion, simultaneously...
...the source of your greatest strength
and your greatest weakness.
If I were you, I would hope
that we don't meet again.
We won't.
We got a serious situation, sir.
Oh, no.
- What was that? - It's moving
faster than anything I've seen.
Holy shit, he caught her.
Neo, I had to.
I know.
The bullet is still inside.
Trinity...
...don't you quit on me now.
I'm sorry.
Trinity.
Trinity...
...I know you can hear me.
I'm not letting go.
I can't.
I love you too damn much.
I can't take this.
I guess this makes us even.
I don't understand it.
Everything was done
as it was supposed to be done.
Once the One reaches the source,
the war should be over.
- In 24 hours, it will be.
- What?
If we don't do something in 24 hours,
Zion will be destroyed.
- What?
- How do you know that?
- I was told it would happen.
- By whom?
It doesn't matter. I believed him.
- That's impossible. The prophecy tells us-
- It was a lie, Morpheus.
The prophecy was a lie.
The One was never meant
to end anything.
It was all another system of control.
I don't believe that.
But you said it yourself.
How can the prophecy be true
if the war isn't over?
I'm sorry.
I know it isn't easy to hear, but...
...I swear to you it's the truth.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
Oh, no!
- What are they doing?
- They're just out of EMP range.
It's a bomb.
We have to get out of here. Now.
I have dreamed a dream...
...but now that dream
has gone from me.
Here they come.
Let's go, Morpheus.
- We won't make it.
- We have to try.
- Come on!
- Something's different.
What?
I can feel them.
Neo!
- What happened?
- I don't know.
It's the Hammer.
He's in some kind of coma...
...but his vitals are stable.
What about you?
I'm fine.
You could use some rest.
No, I'm gonna stay with him.
Lock was right.
He guessed that the machines...
...would cut off the mainlines
in and out of Zion.
He thought a counterattack
might surprise them.
It sounded good.
I figured we had a shot...
...until someone screwed it up.
An EMP was triggered before
we got in position.
- Five ships were instantly downed.
- When the machines broke through...
...it wasn't a battle, it was a slaughter.
Was it an accident?
Some sort of malfunction?
- No one knows.
- Someone does.
Who?
Once the machines were done with us,
they started digging again.
We made a quick pass
to look for survivors.
You found one?
Only one.
Everything that has a beginning...
...has an end.
I see the end coming.
I see the darkness spreading.
I see death.
Mr. Anderson, welcome back.
We missed you.
It ends tonight.
You are all that stands in his way.
If you cannot stop him tonight, then
I fear that tomorrow may never come.