My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
How many more terrible things
are you gonna do to protect me?
That's my job. That's all that matters.
It's my turn to go out on my own.
Don't come looking for me.
Everything seems to be telling me
that Barry and I are meant to be together.
Somebody, please help!
There's only one person
who can help you now.
The Flash.
Barry, I know you can't give up your speed
to that monster...
That's not your decision.
Hand him over and it's yours.
He's slowing down.
He's becoming human again.
I know some piece of you did care for me.
Please, let him go.
Caitlin!
It's a regular day in Central City.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
People wake up, roll out of bed,
suit up for the day.
Get to work as fast as they can.
Make sure they get a caffeine fix
along the way,
so they can make it through
the mountain of work that awaits them.
Yeah.
Yep, it's just a regular day.
And I'm just a regular guy.
I really wish we didn't have to keep
Jay's helmet around.
- I hate this thing.
- Well...
Just wanna put a dent in it.
Cisco, did you see Caitlin in your vibe?
Zoom's got her in his lair.
She's scared, but she's okay.
Thank God.
All right, we need to get her back.
I know, but without your speed,
there's no way any of us
can get through that breach
that Cisco found at the hospital.
I just don't think there's anything
we can do right now.
That's right.
And it's thanks to you, Allen.
Enough, we're all suffering here.
That's right, that's right, Detective.
We're all suffering.
We've lost Snow, you've lost your speed,
and now?
Now, Zoom can come through that breach
any time he wants.
And that, Allen, that's on you.
Hey, that's on all of us, okay?
We made these decisions as a team.
No, we didn't.
And where are you going?
I'm gonna go find Jesse before Zoom does.
Again.
Wait, you found her? How?
Cellular dead zones, Ramon.
People from my Earth
vibrate at a different frequency
than people from your Earth.
They leave cellular dead zones
wherever they go.
That's why
I'm always dropping calls around you?
Okay, so, wait. How did that help?
I track the dead zones created by Jesse
since she got here
and I follow the trail, it's easy.
What?
So, you think you're gonna need that gun
to convince her to leave with you?
You're full of questions today,
aren't you, West?
The gun is not for my daughter.
She's not the only person from
a different Earth hiding out on this one.
If I run into them, I'm gonna need this.
Okay, but you're also gonna need
some help.
Really?
You know anyone
with the speed to help me, Ramon?
Well...
Great. I'll be in my workshop.
Don't listen to Wells, Barry.
This ain't all on you.
Yeah, I know.
You need a ride back to the station?
No, I'm good.
I'm gonna stick around, actually.
Finished all my cases this morning.
Damn, that was fast.
That was a poor choice of words.
You do know it's okay to ease back into
the way you used to do things, right?
Well, this is the only way
I can fight crime.
If I'm not The Flash,
that's what I gotta do.
You need to eat.
Caitlin.
If you wanna speak to me,
then take off that mask.
Does this make you feel better?
Nothing you could ever do
would make me feel better.
You don't need to be afraid.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I care too much about you to do that.
You only care about yourself.
Hunter.
You're gonna wanna see this, son.
No!
I know you think that I'm a monster.
I understand why.
But that'll change.
- Please, Cait.
- Do not call me that!
Why are you keeping me here? You're cured.
You don't need me for anything.
You're here because I love you.
It may take a while, but someday
you'll start feeling that way
about me again, too.
Make yourself at home.
You're gonna be here awhile. Okay?
I don't understand.
Well, hello, doppelganger of mine.
What do you know,
I can still pull off brunette.
Dad.
Oh, hey, son. What a surprise. What's up?
Uh, I, I wanted to ask you
about something. Someone, actually.
Uh... The Flash.
What about him?
Well, he showed up at my street race
when Iris got hurt,
then when that man-shark thing
attacked our house.
And when Zoom took me, he said
someone The Flash knew cared about me.
Yeah, it doesn't take a genius
to figure out that that's you.
If you want me to tell you who he is?
I can't do that.
No, I know, I know.
I was actually hoping
that you could set up a meeting for me.
A meeting? Between you and him?
I... I don't know
if I can do that, either, Wally.
Well, why not?
Joe? Singh wants to see you.
Okay. Um...
Look, maybe one day, but not now.
Look, I gotta get to work.
See you at home? All right.
The laser tag club's in 2D.
- The? Oh, no.
- Uh, I'm looking for Jesse.
Come on in.
Thanks.
Jesse!
You're the first person
who's ever come to visit her.
- What? Oh.
- How'd you find me?
Jess. Uh, cellular dead zone.
I told you I'd find you wherever you went.
Wait, so, you're a runaway?
So you're her dad.
Great. Let me know
if I need to find a new roommate.
Listen. We need to go.
So, what?
You think I'll be safer with you?
Yes.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna pass.
Jesse, we need to leave.
No. Okay? No, I'm not going anywhere
with you, ever again.
You are...
You're in danger. Do you understand?
You're in grave danger.
I know! I'm in danger because of you.
- Because of me?
- Yeah!
Okay, everything that's happened,
it's your fault.
Zoom hunting us, the metas, moving here.
I'm done with it, okay?
You wanted me to start a new life
and that is exactly what I'm trying to do.
- No, Jess. Jess.
- You killed a man!
I can't just forgive you for that.
And I may be afraid of Zoom,
but... I am just as afraid of you.
Please, just go.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
And a new report shows
that petty crimes have risen slightly,
sparking concern that The Flash...
Don't watch that.
Cisco, everybody's gonna realize
sooner or later,
that I don't have my speed.
The later, the better.
The last thing we need,
is every criminal in this city
thinking they're untouchable, right?
- What is that?
- Case in point.
What? What is that?
- It's Harry.
- What about Harry?
The camera in the lab van
recorded an accident.
See, this is my version of Crash Assist.
It's like those Russian dash-cams,
but, you know,
without attack helicopters
and bad pop music on the radio.
That does not look like an accident.
First, Caitlin's taken. Now, Wells.
This is where he got taken,
but there aren't any traffic cams
in that area.
I'm gonna head out there,
see what I can find.
I'll analyze this footage
and see if we can figure out who this is.
All right. Wait, uh, where's
the last place the van stopped?
Woodman and Shore for about 15 minutes
before heading back to Central City. Why?
That's where Jesse must be.
She should know
if something's happened to her dad.
Iris, hey. Need your help with something.
You're Killer Frost.
And you're Caitlin Snow.
Your little friend Cisco
wouldn't shut up about you.
Made you out to be some kind of a saint.
So, tell me. Why hide the girls?
I mean, you've seen our body, right?
If I could get my powers
to work through this carbyne wall,
the first thing lwould do is shut him up.
Who is he?
Don't know, don't care.
But if he's here,
Zoom must need something from him.
So, what does Zoom need you for?
That is an excellent question, Caity.
You know,
I've been asking myself the same thing.
But doesn't matter now.
I'm not gonna stick around much longer.
Wait, I thought you said
your powers don't work inside this cell.
They don't, you're right.
So, you're gonna help me get out of here.
Why would I help you?
Listen, honey, there's no way
you are making it down that cliff
all by yourself.
So, let's make a deal.
You get me out of this box,
and I'll help you get home.
Might even throw in
some wardrobe tips for free.
So, what do you say, Caitlin?
Do we have a deal?
I don't understand.
There's nothing around here.
What did the van hit?
I don't know.
Something strong enough to exert
an equal amount of force back on the van.
Someone was definitely here, though.
You think maybe a meta-human?
Yeah.
And if it's a meta that's after Wells...
Then they could be from Earth-2.
Probably.
We gotta get Jesse, find Wells. Fast.
Dr. Harrison Wells.
Yeah. And who are you?
Name's Griffin Gray.
Griffin Gray?
Do I know you?
No. But you should.
I'm one of your mistakes.
One of your sins coming home to roost.
All right, you think I...
I'm from... I'm not who you think I am.
I know exactly who you are!
And you're gonna fix
what your particle accelerator did to me.
What did the accelerator do to you?
That.
Well, that's impressive.
And all things considered,
I don't know that
having that kinda strength
is the worst thing
you could have been given.
Yeah, that's what I thought at first.
And it was a lot of fun.
Till I learned
it did something else to me, too.
That's me.
Last year.
You're... You're aging.
If this keeps happening,
I'll be dead in a few months.
How old are you, Griffin?
I'm 18.
Look.
I'm sorry this is happening to you.
There's nothing I can do to fix it.
Well, that sucks.
'Cause if you can't figure out a way
to help me, Dr. Wells...
You're gonna die soon, too.
I never should have left.
No, this isn't your fault.
D0 you know who took him?
That's where things get interesting.
That fingerprint that you guys brought in?
- The one from the van, I mean.
- Yeah, yeah.
Belongs to this guy.
Griffin Gray.
A senior at Central City High School?
No, wait.
I've seen this kid's picture before.
He went missing like six months ago.
That's right.
That doesn't make any sense.
An 18-year-old didn't kidnap Wells.
That's what I thought at first,
but feast your eyes on this.
Wow!
It's the same guy!
Yeah, the blood sample confirms it.
How is that even possible?
I'm not sure yet. Without Caitlin here,
I can't really analyze the cells
on a molecular level
to see what we're dealing with here.
You know,
I might actually be able to help.
- How?
- Bio-chem was one of my majors in college.
One of your majors? How many did you have?
Five.
What? ls that not common here?
Girl, no. That is not common anywhere.
All right, let's search for that Gray,
see what we come up with.
I'll see if facial recognition
brings him up
and I'll have Joe check
C.C.P.D.'s database.
Cool. Let's see what you can do.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Well, you'd better go faster.
Zoom will be back any minute.
I could just leave you in there,
you know.
Oh.
But you want to go home so badly.
So, how did this happen to you?
Woke up one day,
cold, pale,
thought I was sick.
Turned out it was something else entirely.
You got hit by the dark matter
from the particle accelerator explosion?
Yes. Right after I flunked out
of med school.
Had to move back in with my mother.
That couldn't have been fun.
If she's anything like mine, I mean.
Why, is yours a frigid narcissist, too?
Cold as ice.
Yeah, Mom was like that
ever since Charlie died.
Who's Charlie?
My brother.
I never had a brother.
No? Then why was Mom such a bitch
on your Earth?
Honestly, I couldn't say.
So, how is this
going to get me out of here?
The electrical current in the cable
should heat up the carbyne,
which, in turn,
should speed up the electrons.
And the faster they go...
The weaker
its molecular structure becomes.
Exactly.
Hmm.
I studied every once in a while.
Well, when it gets hot enough,
it should make the carbyne
as fragile as glass.
And then we can both get out of here.
Wally.
Hey, Joe.
What's up? You look like
you got something on your mind.
Yeah, I do.
Please don't tell me you drove all the way
over here to ask about The Flash again.
It's not happening, Wally.
Wha... It's just one time,
that's all I'm asking.
It's impossible.
He saved my life, Joe.
I owe him a thank you.
Look.
I've been reckless my whole life.
Racing cars, pushing limits.
I did everything at full speed
without a care in the world.
But it wasn't until Zoom took me,
that I really thought I was gonna die.
And I was going to die
if The Flash didn't do what he did.
He gave up his powers to save me,
a guy he didn't even know.
No one's ever done anything like that
for me before.
I need to tell him
how much that means to me.
Well, all right.
Uh.
Just give me a little while,
I'll see what I can do.
L gotta go.
Hey, Dad.
Thanks.
- Yo.
- In here.
I got your text. What's up?
All right,
facial recognition just picked up Gray
breaking into Ace Chemical
down on Newbury Road.
- Is my dad with him?
- I don't know yet. But we have to go.
- Uh, you sure about that?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Look, we can'tjust sit here.
Regardless of whether
I have my speed or not,
I have to try to help,
that's never gonna change.
Okay. I'm with you,
but we're gonna need some backup.
- Joe's on his way.
- And I'm coming with.
No, look, uh, pleasejust stay here.
We don't know what we're dealing with yet.
Just finish running the tests
on the blood sample.
I'm sorry. Thank you, Jesse.
Griffin Gray, C.C.P.D.!
Stay right there.
The man that you kidnapped,
Harrison Wells.
You need to let him go.
I can't do that. Not yet.
Then we'll have to do this the hard way.
I guess so.
Okay, He-Man's got some power.
And accuracy.
- All right, keep him distracted, okay?
- What?
Barry! Barry!
Ican do this all night.
We just want Wells. Just let him go!
Not until I'm done with him!
Too slow.
- Barry!
- Hey.
I think I need some medical attention.
So, his genes have actually mutated.
I ran the DNA from the blood sample
Barry found
and the functional myostatin in his cells
is essentially gone.
I mean, giving him super-strength.
Guys, there's something else.
Um, I saw him age. Right in front of me.
Yeah, he's suffering from
oxidative stress.
It means the protein and the DNA
in his body are being ravaged by oxidants.
So, what?
He needs to up his blueberry intake?
No, it means, the more he
exerts himself, the faster he ages.
So, if we can get him
to exert too much energy, then...
Then he'll become old and weak.
And how do you think
we're gonna do that?
I can't watch you be a human punching bag
until he turns into Grampa Simpson.
I think we can fix that.
Jesse, I'm gonna need
some of that quick thinking of yours.
Iris.
I gotta get back to the station.
You Okay?
No, not really.
You know, you were the first person
I saved after I got my powers.
We were out on a walk
and we were talking about Eddie
- Hmm-mmm.
- And how you were with him,
and I was thinking to myself how
I'd missed a lot while I was in that coma.
And then, all of a sudden,
those cars came at us,
and it was like the world froze.
Like you and I
were the only two people in the world.
I didn't even know what I could do yet.
But I knew that I could save you.
And I did.
And now, I don't know, I don't...
I Just don't even know who I am anymore,
or who I'm supposed to be.
Barry, you're supposed to be the same guy
that you've always been.
Suit or no suit,
that guy is a hero.
That's everything you asked for.
How do you sleep at night,
knowing you've destroyed
so many people's lives?
I don't.
Do you have anyone in your life
that you care about?
I have a daughter.
I used to have someone in my life
that I cared about.
My girlfriend, Jenny.
We were gonna get married,
have kids someday.
But after I got hit by that wave
from the particle accelerator,
all my dreams ended.
You know, I see her sometimes,
walking down the street.
She doesn't even recognize me.
Why would she?
I look as old as her dad.
You robbed me of her.
Griffin, stop talking.
So I can concentrate.
Wake up, man.
This city is screwed up because of you.
It was quiet and normal,
until you rode in on your high horse
talking about science
and changing the future.
You didn't stop to think
about what your particle accelerator
could do to others.
You only thought about
what it could do for you!
Enough!
Enough.
I hope it was worth it, "Doc."
Stay away from the wall.
Let's give it a whirl.
Well, looks like
you have a little badass in you after all.
What are we gonna do about this guy?
Oh, Caity, I don't think
he's ever going home,
and neither are you.
What are you doing?
I thought we had a deal!
Oh!
Is everyone on your Earth this gullible?
Heels aren't the best on ice, are they?
You know, once I saw you,
I realized why Zoom didn't kill me.
Because I lookjust like you.
Now, he won't need me anymore.
No, I don't.
Try that with him, he dies, too.
I'm not picking up anything
from facial recognition.
The only cellular dead zone
I can find is the one in here. No offense.
No, wait a second, was he wearing
his watch when he left to get me?
I already tried that. GPS isn't working.
Okay, no, but the meta-human activity
would be.
I mean, the watch is designed
to track metas, right?
And since Griffin Gray is one,
it'll keep sending a message to a sewer
until it goes through.
But since we're on a different Earth,
it'll never go through.
So itjust keeps sending the same signal.
There he is, Central City Amusement Park.
Yeah, and I'm coming with, this time.
Okay, great, we found Harry,
but how are we gonna stop Gray?
I'm so glad you asked.
Jesse and I
upgraded the internal lining of the suit.
Felicity hooked us up
with some dwarf star alloy.
Wait, dwarf star alloy?
It's the same compound
that's used to protect Ray's Atom suit.
That's right.
Super strong, super lightweight.
Only thing is, we couldn't get much of it.
All right, what does that mean?
We could only cover
the chest portion of the suit.
- Oh.
- Yeah, sorry.
Uh, here's the other thing,
probably not a big deal.
Um, I'm guessing the suit will only absorb
- one of Gray's punches.
- Hmm!
Anything more than that,
you'll be like a pinata,
only it won't be candy coming out.
It'll be...
- Me.
- Your... Yeah, you.
Yeah. All right.
Hopefully, one gimme punch
is all I'll need.
All right, then.
Finished.
This is gonna cure me?
As we say in science,
I'm cautiously optimistic.
You know, I learned a lot about chemistry
in the past two years.
That right?
And I know all you've been doing
is diluting that compound
for the past half hour.
You don't know how to help me, do you?
There is no helping you.
I told you you were gonna fix me,
or you were dead!
Why is it that bad guys always
insist on having the creepiest hideouts?
Because they're crazy.
Right.
Hey, Barry, Gray's headed your way.
All right, come on. Hey, come on.
You ready?
Okay, Iris. On my mark.
Three...
Two, one. Now!
Is that all you got, Flash?
We just want Dr. Wells.
And I wanted him to fix me, but he can't.
So once I finish you,
I'm gonna finish him.
Freeze.
Come on!
You Okay?
Come On.
Okay, I think, one more punch
and we get this guy a walker.
Hey, guys, we got him.
He's over by the Ferris wheel.
Look, we can help you.
It's too late for that.
Not everyone got the powers
you did, Flash.
Some of us weren't so lucky.
That was the "gimme."
Griffin, please, stop.
I might be getting older,
but I'm stronger than ever.
Barry!
You Okay?
Oh! Yeah, I'm good.
Could've used more
of that dwarf star alloy.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Oh! Home, sweet home.
Yeah, well.
To be honest,
hasn't felt much like a home in a while.
At least, certainly not since you left.
Yeah. Look, I'm sorry, Dad,
forjust leaving like that.
But... I mean.
You have to understand.
I'm the reason you killed that man.
And that's a really heavy burden to bear.
I know.
I know. I also know that what I've done,
it's unforgiveable.
When your mother died, honey,
something inside me broke.
I couldn't protect her.
And I swore, I swore on her grave,
no less, that I would protect you.
And then Zoom took you and I snapped.
I just snapped.
I couldn't breathe, I...
I couldn't lose the only other person
that I love.
Yeah, yeah, I get that.
I understand why
you did everything you did to protect me.
I mean, you were only missing one day
and I would have done anything
to find you.
But... I mean.
I need to know that
that's never gonna happen again, okay?
Every time I stay out late,
or get in trouble,
you can't track me down, or hurt someone
'cause you're trying to save me.
Yeah, but you're in danger.
- I know.
- Okay.
I will make you a promise.
I promise you I will be the kind of father
that you can be proud of,
if you promise me
you will never run away from me again.
Okay. Okay, deal.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too.
My little Jesse Quick.
Relax, he'll be here.
What should I say?
I mean, I don't even know where to start.
Just be honest. Speak from your heart.
Okay.
Wally West.
I'll see you at home.
You wanted to see me.
Uh, yes. ldid. I mean, I do.
Um...
I just wanted to thank you
for saving my life.
And I know that
that came at a huge price for you.
And I don't know how I'll ever repay that.
I guess what I wanted to say was that
I'm not gonna waste this chance
that you've given me.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Wally.
You okay?
Stay away from me.
Killer Frost tried to kill you, Caitlin.
I saved your life.
You should thank me.
I just wanna go home.
No. Stay.
I want to leave!
Stay, boy!
No!
Please, take me back to my Earth.
You know,
I've always measured my success by
counting the number of victims I've had.
But now I think I'm gonna widen my scope
and start counting the number of Earths
I conquer instead.
You wanna go home?
Let's go. After all,
this Earth has already been
brought to its knees.
Well, you're here early.
Yeah, I couldn't sleep.
Me, neither.
I know that we just took down Gray
without my powers, but...
I have no idea
how to get Caitlin back without them.
We can't, Allen.
Then what are we gonna do?
Gray...
Gray kidnapped me
because he thought I was Harrison Wells
from this Earth.
I know he was talking about another guy,
but I just...
I can't help but think.
I still haven't paid for what I've done.
What does that mean?
I thought, you know, when you...
When we closed the breaches,
I could just forget
about everything I've done, but I can't.
I realize what I can do.
You are gonna get your speed back, Allen.
And I'm gonna help you do that.
How?
By creating
another particle accelerator explosion.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::