Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- Grodd. He's got my dad.
- Harry's my friend.
I'm not gonna just abandon him.
I'm going back to Earth-2.
- [deep voice] Now I am
the ruler of Gorilla City,
and all the gorillas
will follow anything I order.
- Grodd the gorilla,
he's talking through Wells?
- Yeah.
- Who is this gorgeous intruder?
- Her name is Gypsy.
She's a Collector.
- Open a breach!
- Time to warp out
of this madhouse.
- You will open the breaches,
and Central City will fall
before Grodd.
[lively music]
[whooshing and shuffling]
- Barry?
[bell dings]
- Good morning.
You're in a good mood
for 6:30 in the morning.
- Yes, I am.
Was I too loud?
I did make breakfast.
We got pancakes and waffles,
some French toast,
bacon and sausage,
perfectly cooked.
And I picked up some of that
dark roast
that you love so much.
- Barry Allen,
what has gotten into you?
- Being with you makes me
want to do things like this.
- Come here.
[sweet music]
♪ ♪
I love you.
- I love you.
Um, so do you actually
want any of this, or...
- Um, yes.
And some of the food too.
- Yeah.
Whoa-ho-ho-ho, nice.
- What...
are you doing?
- [laughs] I'm decorating!
Look at this place!
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- You're decorating
the Speed Lab?
- Yes, I'm decorating
the Speed Lab.
You know, 'cause Francisco,
you know,
he wouldn't let me
decorate the cortex,
'cause I made it look
oh-so-jolly for Christmastime.
- What are the balls for?
- Do you know what those are?
Lanterns.
You know what I always say:
a fella that can't tell
the difference between
balls and lanterns
is in trouble
when the lights go out.
Ohhh...
You go front to back.
Toothbrushing.
You go front to back?
'Cause I'm a small
circles kind of guy.
I wonder how the other
Wells brushes his teeth.
- The murderer?
- I'm fascinated
by the subtle differences
between us, you know?
- And the not-so-subtle ones.
- Like what?
- Like the fact
that I'm a genius
and you're a moron.
[spits]
- Okay.
See you at the party.
[mellow lounge music]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
What a transformation.
Again!
- [laughs]
- So this is H.R.'s
contribution to the team?
Being Martha Stewart?
- Guys, he's just trying
to do something nice.
- Heads up!
[bowstring twangs]
I'm not really good
with this kind of thing.
You know what I got to do?
I got to take some lessons
from that guy
in the green elf suit
over there in Star City,
what's his name?
- Green Arrow.
Hey, what is all this?
- Friend's Day!
Ba-da!
- What?
- Yeah.
- Friend's Day.
- Friend's?
- Oh, it's
my Earth's equivalent
of Valentine's Day.
- Valentine's Day.
- And I thought,
like, after, you know,
our success with the gorillas,
that we should, like,
celebrate the love.
- Was all this necessary?
- Yeah, Joe.
Speaking of, where is your...
your lady friend?
'Cause I would like to...
- No, you wouldn't
like to do anything.
She's at work, which is
where I should be going.
- Yeah, I...
- Look what I have,
ladies and gentlemen.
I have your own personal
Friend's Day card.
- Wow.
- For yours truly, Ms. West.
- Thank you, H.R.
- Captain.
- Thanks, H.R.
- Leader of the ship.
- Thank...thank you.
- You're so welcome.
Oh, hi, Jesse "So Quick."
Yeah, I also made one
for your grumpy old dad.
Ah, you know what I like?
Yo' vibe.
- Thank you.
- Caitlyn.
Oh! I forgot the coffee!
- "You have sped into
my heart, Jesse Quick."
- Oh, well, I guess
that makes two of us.
- Wow, H.R. is nothing
like my dad.
He's so sweet and thoughtful
and understanding.
We should tell him.
- Tell your dad
about you moving here?
- Yeah.
- Um, now?
- Yeah, I mean, H.R. said
there'd never be a perfect time.
Just got to rip
the Band-Aid off.
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do it.
- H.R. does make a good point.
- Yeah, what's that?
- It was a really big win
for the team, beating Grodd.
I mean, we stopped a gorilla
attack from happening.
- Yeah, look at you,
changing the future.
- We're all changing the future,
one headline at a time.
- Look, I don't know what
the future's gonna bring,
but I hope every
day is with you.
Which is why
I wanted to ask you...
Barry Allen,
will you be my friend?
- Always.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- H.R. made this for you.
- H.R. is an idiot.
- So there's something I've been
meaning to tell you.
- Okay.
- So I-I'm just gonna say it.
- I think that's wise.
- I'm gonna move to Earth-1.
[objects clattering]
- [clears throat] What?
- I'm gonna stay here.
- Why would you do that?
Grodd is no longer a threat.
- No, it's...it's not that.
Uh...
I want to be with Wally.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
This whole thing
has made us realize
that we have no idea what's
gonna happen, you know, and...
- And if we're gonna
go through something,
we want to go
through it together.
- Yeah.
- This guy?
You like him?
- Yeah.
- He makes you happy?
- Dad...
- Okay.
- That's it?
You're not gonna yell?
You're not gonna throw that
over there?
- Your happiness
is what matters to me.
You're both adults.
I respect your decision.
Don't screw it up.
- Okay, that was weird.
- I guess that this means that
we gotta find you a place.
- Me? More like us.
- You know, sometimes
it seems like everybody else
gets to have their
love doughnut.
Where's my love doughnut?
- Oh, love is complicated.
- Mm.
So, uh, where's Julian?
- He's taking care of some
family matters in London.
Just so you know,
we are just friends.
- Yeah, the friend zone.
I know it well.
Pretty sure I have
a permanent residence here.
You know, maybe I should
just swallow the pill.
Maybe my game
just ain't strong.
- Your game is so strong!
For what it's worth,
I think Lisa Snart
was totally into you.
- Lisa Snart.
- Not that I would
actually let you date her.
Cisco, I promise,
there is a beautiful,
intelligent woman out there
who's gonna challenge you
to be your best
version of yourself.
In fact, she could be
right around the corner.
[energy surging]
- Gypsy!
[energy blasting]
[electricity crackling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oof!
[blast fires]
♪ ♪
- Who the hell is this?
- [exhales heavily]
- Where am I?
- Ohh...
[chuckles]
- Why am I locked up?
[energy whooshing]
- Oops.
- My powers don't work in here.
- Yeah, it's kind of the point
of the cell.
What happened?
I thought we were all
on the same page.
I spared your life, and you said
you'd go back to Earth-19
and tell everyone
you killed H.R.
- That's exactly what I did.
I told the council
you were dead.
- I don't believe you.
- I didn't come here
to take you back!
I'm telling you!
- Then why are you here?
- I don't know.
The last thing I remember,
I was on Earth-2...
hunting down another breacher.
- Wait, you were just
on Earth-2?
Where?
- In the African jungle,
where I saw...
- Let me guess, a gorilla?
Super tall?
Anger management issues?
- Grodd must have
taken control of her
and sent her here to kill us.
- Yeah, but she's on
a different Earth than him,
and Grodd's telepathy can't
cross dimensions like that.
- Grodd said he always
thinks ahead.
Just like the Reverse-Flash.
He didn't have you
to open a breach,
so he used Gypsy instead.
- So that means...
Grodd's here.
- Something tells me
he's not alone.
♪ ♪
[footsteps thudding]
- [snarling]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Any sign of him yet?
- Not since you asked
30 seconds ago.
- Okay, he's a giant gorilla,
who's probably leading
an army of giant gorillas.
How can you not find him?
- He's probably
figured out a way
to scramble our satellites.
- Satellites.
- We're talking about
a genius super-ape here.
- And a master strategist
who successfully
fooled us on my Earth.
- We Wellses, we don't
fool easy, do we, hard hat?
- Don't call me "hard hat."
- We have to find him
before he hurts somebody else.
- Don't worry, Barry, we will.
- Every time I think
we've beat him,
he comes back
stronger, smarter,
and more dangerous.
He's evolving.
I keep trying to fight
him the same way.
- Okay, guys, look,
we just have to come up
with a different way
to beat him.
- What we need to do
is get ahead of him for once.
- We can.
You've seen the future.
You know there's an attack.
If we just figure out
where that attack happens,
we can launch a preemptive
strike against Grodd.
- We can stop the attack
before it ever starts.
- And fortunately,
we have someone
who can foresee future events.
- Before they happen.
- Okay, okay,
there's only one problem.
I can only vibe
what Barry saw,
and a ticker
on the side of a bus stop
doesn't give us
a whole lot of info.
- What if we widen the scope
of your vibe?
Then you can see
more of the future.
- Yes. I can do that.
Just need to borrow
your vibe gear.
- Harry, that's my only pair.
- I'll be careful.
- It's my only pair.
- West, come with me.
You have an engineer's mind.
- Yeah, sure.
Happy to help.
- We're gonna need all the help
we can get.
Can you talk to Joe,
see if he can rally CCPD?
- Yeah, yeah,
I'll let him know that
an army of sentient gorillas
is about to storm the city.
He's gonna love that.
- Yup.
- What about Gypsy?
She's a really powerful meta.
- Yeah, but how do we know
she's not a Grodd sleeper agent?
- She's not.
I checked her out.
- Can you convince her to help?
- Bro, she won't say no to me.
- No way.
You've got three
speedsters, an ice queen,
and a guy who vibes
almost as well as I do.
You don't need my help
to stop Grodd.
- Need I remind you,
you're the one
who brought Grodd here
in the first place.
- Not by choice!
I was chasing a fugitive
from my world on Earth-2
when Grodd ambushed me
and turned me into
his damn puppet.
- Okay, so then this
is the perfect opportunity
for payback, right?
Don't tell me you're
gonna run away from this.
- I never run.
- Then stand and fight with us.
We need you.
- [laughs softly]
You need me?
Are you trying to
Luke Starkiller me?
- [laughs]
What if I am?
Is that what it's gonna
take to get you to stay?
Here's a bonus:
you get to spend
extra time with this face.
And look at this face.
Come on.
Who doesn't want to getto spend
extra time with this guy?
[light music]
♪ ♪
What?
- The things I saw,
when Grodd was in control
of my mind,
the horrors
in that monster's head,
I can never un-see them.
- What horrors?
- The city in ruins.
People in pain.
Death everywhere.
That's what Grodd wants,
what he's planning.
I'm sorry, Cisco.
This is your fight.
Not mine.
♪ ♪
Now, if you don't mind,
I still have a fugitive
to catch, so...
- Okay.
I understand.
♪ ♪
[door opens]
- Take care of yourself, Cisco.
♪ ♪
- Admit it.
You are so into me.
♪ ♪
- West.
How are we coming along
with that gear?
- I've made all the adjustments
you asked for,
so we should be good to go.
- Good. Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Great.
- Um, how exactly is this gonna
help Cisco vibe
any differently?
- Ah, simple science.
We just broaden the
overall harmonic resonance
of Cisco's
vibrational frequencies
all while focusing them
on a fixed temporal locus.
Couldn't be easier.
- Yeah.
You know, I got to admit Harry
I was super surprised
at how cool you were
with Jesse
staying on this Earth.
I thought, for sure,
you were gonna freak out
and throw something
or throw someone.
[laughs]
- Well, my daughter's happiness
is of the utmost
importance to me.
And you make her happy.
- I'm gonna do everything in
my power to keep it that way.
- I appreciate that, West.
I'm sure Jesse
will too, after I'm...
gone.
- We're gonna come visit you
on Earth-2 a bunch,
so you don't have to worry
about that, Harry.
- Yeah, right.
Uh, well,
means the world to me,
seeing as I don't know
how much time I have left.
- Wait, y-you're sick?
- I'm not as well
as I once was.
- Have you seen a doctor?
- Yes.
I have seen a doctor, West.
- Is it serious?
- [sighs]
- Oh, man, Harry.
Man. Um...
I'm sorry.
- Me too.
- Does Jesse know?
- Appreciate
you keep this between...us.
She doesn't know, and we
wouldn't want to upset her.
[somber music]
- Hey, SWAT's ready to roll
whenever y'all are.
We find Grodd yet?
- [sighs] We're about to.
Cisco, you ready?
- Harry, this thing,
if it fries my brain...
- [gruffly]
"It's an improvement."
- Was that "Rocky"?
- Yeah, Burgess Meredith.
- [chuckles] Yeah, I'm ready.
- Word of warning.
Vibing blind,
it's like surfing
a monster wave.
You need to stay
above the temporal flow,
otherwise your consciousness
can get sucked under.
- And then what happens?
- I don't know.
Guess we'll find out.
- Wait, what?
[whooshing]
[foreboding music]
- Where are you, Ramon?
What do you see?
♪ ♪
[distant traffic]
- I'm at an intersection.
State and Oakhill.
I think this is where
it goes down.
♪ ♪
- That's a block away
from the bridge.
That leads right
to the heart of town.
If those gorillas
get over that bridge...
- They'll overrun the city
in no time.
- Not if we stop them first.
♪ ♪
- Eyes wide, everybody.
Grodd's army could be here
any second, all right?
- There's no sign of them.
- You sure this is
the right place?
- According to Cisco,
this is it.
- Was it the right time?
- We're too early.
[high-pitched tone rings]
- [deep voice] No, Flash.
Too late.
- Grodd.
- I remember,
this human is important to you.
Now...
he's all mine.
- No! Hey!
Do not hurt him.
I'm the one you want!
Right?
- I warned you, Flash.
And now I'm here
on First Earth
to make good on my promise.
And when I'm finished,
this city
and all the puny humans
will die.
[high-pitched tone]
[gunshot]
- No!
♪ ♪
- Joe!
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
- [panting]
I don't get it.
How is attacking
Detective Joe West
a part of Grodd's plan?
- It wasn't.
- Then what was it?
- A distraction.
♪ ♪
- I don't care if
Senator Ford is having doubts.
If the secretary
doesn't approve that budget
first thing in the morning,
we're gonna
have to make some serious cuts...
[crashing]
[groans]
The hell was that?
- [roaring]
[roaring]
- That damn gorilla
almost got me this time.
- Shouldn't even have a scar.
- Do you remember anything
from when Grodd
was controlling you?
- Not really.
Just some flashes.
- Flashes of what?
- They were, like,
these images...
places I've never seen before.
It was like I was seeing
what he was seeing.
- Gypsy said the same thing.
Uh-oh, here we go.
I know that look.
That's the "I have
a genius idea" look.
- A couple years back
on my Earth,
there was a neuroscientist
that was able to achieve
memory recovery
using transcranial magnetic
simulators on brain-damaged...
- We use that here but more
as a depression treatment.
- Well, in this experiment,
the neuroscientist
focused all the energy
on the occipital cortex
of the patients,
allowing them to achieve
almost full memory recollection.
- So you think the
connection Grodd creates
in the brains
of those he mind-controls
goes both ways?
- Could be.
- Maybe we could use
Grodd's memories
that he left behind in Joe
to figure out what his plan is.
- We'd just make
some TCM simulators.
All it takes is some...
- Magnets.
- Throw together some magnets,
make a helmet out of 'em.
- Hold on. Y'all want to put
a bunch of magnets
against my skull
to look into the mind
of a psychotic, murderous ape?
- Yeah.
- Fine.
- Let's make it happen,
before Grodd tries to kill
somebody else.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [whispering]
It's gonna be okay.
- Hey.
Is everything okay?
- Just tired of seeing
the people I care about
be put in harm's way.
- Yeah, but like always,
we're gonna work together
and come up with a plan.
We're gonna stop Grodd, Barry.
[somber music]
- And then what?
We just send him back?
He's just gonna
come here again.
We have to end this
once and for all.
- Wait. What?
You want to kill Grodd?
♪ ♪
- Why not?
That's how their society
in Gorilla City works...
kill or be killed.
That's why he wanted me
to kill Solovar.
And you know what?
I should have.
I showed too much mercy.
- No, you did
what was right, Barry,
as you always do.
That's what makes you a hero.
- Oliver has killed.
He's still considered a hero.
- Yeah, and he lives with
the weight of that decision
every single day.
- I think that sometimes,
the only way to stop
bad things from happening
is to just get rid
of what's causing them.
- What is this really about?
Grodd or what happens to me?
- I kill Grodd,
his attack never happens,
that changes the future, and...
you live, yeah.
- [sighs heavily]
Your humanity,
showing mercy,
that is what separates
you from everyone else.
That's the reason that
everyone looks up to you.
Don't compromise who you are...
ever.
Losing what makes The Flash
The Flash...
my life isn't worth it
if that's the cost to save me.
♪ ♪
- There you are.
Hey, you know your dad's
gonna be all right.
What's wrong?
- Look, I've been
thinking, and I...
I don't think
you should stay here.
I think... [sighs]
It was a bad idea.
- Um...
Wally, you asked me.
- Yeah, and I shouldn't have.
I think you should
go back to Earth-2...
spend as much time
with your dad as you can.
- Spend as much time
with my dad as I can?
Wally, what are you
talking about?
- Your dad is sick, Jesse.
He's really sick.
He doesn't have much time left.
- Did he tell you that?
- I'm so sorry.
- He is...
unbelievable.
- So all you have to do
is concentrate
on your memories
of Grodd, okay?
- Yeah,
that won't be a problem.
- All right.
- Hey, dead man.
Seriously?
- Hm?
- You told Wally you were dying?
- Dying?
- You're dying?
- I didn't say I was, uh...
I-I said I didn't know
how much time I had left.
None of us...
- Okay, what is wrong with you?
- Um...
- Is there seriously nothing
you won't say to get me
to stay by your side?
- I don't...
- Look, whatever.
I'm moving here,
whether you like it or not.
- [sighs softly]
So all you have to do
is concentrate
on your memories of Grodd.
- Yeah.
- You ready?
- Waiting on you, dead man.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, if I start
to Grodd out at any point,
cut the power off immediately.
- Of course.
- All right, Joe, you ready?
- [nervously] Yeah.
- All right, then.
- So here...
we...
go.
[electronic buzzing]
- Joe?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I didn't know he could draw.
- Well, that's the thing.
Anybody can actually draw.
It's just that some have
more developed visual cortex
and manual ability,
as you know.
And right now, these magnets are
taking that part of his brain
and lightin' it up.
♪ ♪
[electricity powers down]
- Well, it worked.
Now we have a new problem.
We have to figure out
who the hell this is.
♪ ♪
- Good evening, General.
Color and number of the day.
- Purple 246.
- Are you all right, sir?
- Sick.
[coughs]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
Good.
- General.
♪ ♪
[blows landing]
[sand pouring]
- [sighs] Great.
- Yo, Rocky.
♪ ♪
How you doin'?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just...
No matter what I do
to stop Grodd,
he just keeps finding
new ways to attack,
new ways to destroy, and I...
Iris doesn't think I should,
but the only way this ends
is if I kill him.
- Kill him.
That might be
the most idiotic thing
I've ever heard you say.
- Wait, what?
- Iris is right.
If you don't want to listen,
go ahead,
keep being an idiot.
- I don't understand.
- Don't. Kill. Grodd.
- Harry, you of all people
should understand.
I mean, you would have killed
to save Jesse.
You were gonna kill Zoom.
- Barry,
there's a thousand things
I've done
that I'm not proud of.
[laughs bitterly]
Some of them recently.
Every time I do
one of those things,
it makes it easier to do it
the next time.
I look at you, out there
battling the darkness,
with honor and hope,
and I'm reminded
there's always another way,
always.
Killing Grodd
is not your answer.
Saving one life doesn't
justify taking another.
- Find the other way.
[intercom chirps]
- Guys.
We need you in the cortex.
- What's up, Cisco?
- We've got a behemoth
of a problem.
- [sighs] Terrific.
[computers beeping]
- So we ran our John Doe image
through every database.
- And it was tough.
I mean, the guy's a ghost.
We've been calling him
Jason Bourne.
- But then H.R.
noticed something.
- Well, at first,
it was a real brain-twister,
but then I remembered a quote
from a renowned poet from
my Earth, Alfred Yankovic...
- Are you talking about
Weird Al?
- Why? 'Cause of the hair?
- Get to the point already,
if you have one.
- I can, hard hat.
It's his hair.
Standard military cut.
- So we ran the image through
the Department of Defense
database,
and, as Cisco would say,
"Yahtzee."
- I would say that.
- Nice work, H.R.
- I know.
- DoD has him listed as
Air Force General
Matthew McNally.
- General Matthew McNally,
and I'll give you one guess...
just guess...
what he's in charge of.
- I know you're gonna say
military weapons,
but I really hope you
don't say military weapons.
- It's worse, Barr.
- [exhales]
- Nuclear missiles.
- McNally has
the highest clearance.
He can have a rocket in the air
in less than ten minutes.
- So are the satellites
back to functional?
- We ran a full diagnostic.
Any nuclear weapon
that's authorized to fire,
an alarm will sound
- Okay, good.
[alarm blaring]
[moans]
- Does it sound like that?
That's an alarm.
- Yeah, it's that alarm, H.R.
Okay.
Short-range ballistic missile
authorized to fire
from Fort Reynolds.
- How much time do we have?
- Minutes.
- Grodd, what have you done?
- Can we stop it from here?
- Military weapons
are basically analog.
I mean, they still
use floppy disks.
- I'm going after it.
Guys, no look. I appreciate it
but I need you
to stay here, okay?
If I can't stop it,
I need you to get
everybody to safety, okay?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
All right,
I'm with the missile.
- Barry, to access the keypad,
remove the panel
at the base
of the missile vehicle.
♪ ♪
- All right.
All right, that's done.
What's next?
- Well, the good news is,
this missile
has a built-in
five-digit kill code.
- Great. What is it?
- That's the bad news.
We don't know.
- For real? Ah, well,
then what am I supposed to do?
- You have to try
every combination, Barry.
It's okay;
with this type of launcher,
you won't set off the nuke.
- Barry,
simulators are projecting
that hundreds of thousands
will die.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, let's hope not.
Come on.
♪ ♪
- Five digits.
How many combos is that?
- I'm guessing it's about...
- Precisely 90,000,
which you would know
if you weren't a moron
and you were an actual genius.
- Two missiles
are locked on target.
- Guys, we need something else.
This isn't working.
- Plan B, anyone?
♪ ♪
[buttons beeping]
Work!
- How much time does he have?
- 15 seconds.
- Guys, I need something!
This isn't working!
Something else!
- You just got to keep
going, Barry.
You just...just
got to keep trying.
- Six missiles
are locked on target.
- [muttering]
[buttons beeping]
♪ ♪
[electronic warbling]
It worked.
[dramatic music]
It worked!
We did it!
♪ ♪
[laughs]
- [scoffs]
- Oh, thank God.
- Flash stopped the weapon.
But he can't stop us all.
[roars]
Attack!
[electronic beeping]
- Found them.
They're right outside the city.
[dramatic music]
- Heading for
State and Oakhill, fast.
- Which leads
right into downtown.
- All right, so what do we do?
- Barry, I know we're
speedsters and everything,
but we are way outnumbered here.
- Yeah, I mean, he's right;
how are the three of us
gonna take on
all those gorillas?
- We have to.
- As much as I hate
these gorillas,
especially Grodd,
if you kill him,
the other ones
might stand down,
but you might not be able
to come back from this, Barry.
You know that, right?
- I know.
But there's another way.
It's not gonna come to that.
Cisco,
I'm gonna need your help.
- Tracked her down on Earth-2.
Breach is taken care of.
[dramatic music]
- Thank you.
- Risky move
coming to an Earth
where interdimensional travel
is punishable by death.
Especially when I'm the one
who's supposed to uphold
that law.
- I need to talk to you.
- I don't do
long-distance relationships.
- Don't get me wrong;
this is something
I'd love to talk about
in more detail,
especially if distance
is your only hesitation.
But I'm here
to talk about Grodd.
- Okay, I see you don't
take no for an answer.
- Gypsy, please.
He's gonna destroy my city.
And he's gonna hurt
the people I love.
- I told you before,
that's not my problem.
Look, just go back to Earth-1
before someone sees you
and I have to do something
that I don't want to.
- You know, you told me I could
do things with my powers
I'd never even imagined,
and you're right,
'cause I'm not just
vibing people anymore.
I'm vibing what they feel.
And you know what
I'm getting from you,
right here, right now?
You're more than this.
You're like me.
You want to do
something good.
Look, we need
something to stop Grodd,
and I'm gonna need
your help getting it.
Please, be the hero
I know you want to be.
- Wells, how long do we have?
- Two minutes, Barry.
- Two minutes?
Ten seconds!
Can you not even tell time?
- That's what I said.
Ten seconds.
- So got any pointers
on how the three of us
are gonna save everyone
and stop a few hundred gorillas?
- Go for the legs?
[footsteps thudding]
Just try not to get caught,
'cause, trust me,
they won't let go.
[gorillas snarling]
[thrilling music]
♪ ♪
[weapons clashing]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Well, that was not
the start we're looking for.
Because...
- How long
do they have to last?
- Hopefully not much longer.
♪ ♪
- Your city will fall, Flash.
There's only one way
to end this.
You kill me.
But you won't do that.
All you care about is mercy.
- Yeah, you're right.
Except I'm not the only one
that wants to stop you.
- [snarls]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- [howling]
- Solovar!
[gorillas grunting, growling]
- I challenge you, Grodd!
- And you will fall again!
♪ ♪
[weapons clashing]
- [growls]
- [roaring]
♪ ♪
- [roars triumphantly]
[roars]
Good-bye, Grodd.
- Stop!
Stop...
- [growls]
- Death isn't the way.
- He betrayed me.
- I know, so leave him here,
where he's from.
We won't let him go back
to Gorilla City ever again.
- [growling]
- Just spare his life,
like I spared yours.
- [huffs]
Send us home...
all of us.
- How long is it gonna take
to put 100 gorillas
through a breach?
We're gonna be here all night.
You know what I ought to do?
Whip us up some cappuccino...
ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
- All the gorillas
are back on Earth-2.
- And Grodd?
- I called Lyla.
He's with A.R.G.U.S.
- Good.
I don't know about y'all,
but I don't ever need to see
a super-smart, telepathic
gorilla again.
- I'm with you.
- Not that Grodd didn't have
some justification
for mistrusting humans.
- Whatever good was in Grodd
is gone.
As far as I'm concerned,
they can throw him
in the same cage as King Shark.
- Mm, I'd pay money
to see that fight.
- All right, well, if the city
doesn't need my help anymore,
I'm gonna head back to Earth-19.
- Oh, really?
So you did all this
for the city, huh?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
there's a different reason
you chose to help us.
- That's right;
I was the only one
who knew where Solovar was.
- Oh, right, yeah.
How could I forget?
- Mm.
- Don't front.
You're into me.
- [laughs]
Look, Cisco, I mean,
even if I was...
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
You couldn't handle me.
Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'll marry that woman.
Yeah.
- Okay, I better get this story
in before I lose my job.
- Okay.
- You sure you still don't
want to look into the future
and see what's changed?
- No.
Think I'm done with that.
- Good.
- I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
- Hey, I'll walk out with you.
I got a date with Cecile.
- Oh.
- Come on, guys.
Let's go find Harry.
♪ ♪
- To review:
this is my daughter.
There's nothing
more important to me.
So you do right by my daughter,
or there is nowhere
in the multiverse
I won't find you.
- Dad.
- They'd have to kill me.
[warm music]
- Bye.
♪ ♪
- [softly] Bye.
- Bye, Jesse Quick.
♪ ♪
Always another way, Flash.
Always.
♪ ♪
- Babe?
Is that Grandma Esther's
noodles?
- Mm-hmm.
And there's mint
chocolate chip in the freezer.
- [exhales]
- And these are for you.
♪ ♪
What is all this?
- I've been really busy
recently with...
trying to avoid the future.
And I forgot that
there's always another way.
- What is that?
- Making the future...
our future.
♪ ♪
My great-grandfather gave this
to my great-grandmother
after World War II.
He wanted to propose
before he was shipped out,
but he...he didn't
have the money.
And he bought this
three years later
when he was stationed
in London.
Fought his way across France,
all the way to Berlin,
and this ring...
around his neck
with his dog tags.
And when he got back, she was
waiting for him on the dock
of the Brooklyn Navy Yards.
He proposed on the spot.
After my mom passed away,
Joe held on to this for me...
until tonight.
- Barry...
- Iris West,
will you marry me?
- [exhales sharply]
- Inside of us, we both know
you belong with Victor.
You're part of his work,
the thing that keeps him going.
If that plane leaves...
- Okay, I'm so confused.
Is it supposed to be about
the War of the Americas?
- Do you not like it? 'Cause
this is my favorite movie.
- No, no, I didn't say that.
Um...
I guess we just have
more wars on my Earth.
- Well, we can just
watch something else.
- Or we don't have
to watch anything at all.
- Mm.
- You know what I could go for?
[whispering]
Big Belly Burger.
- Wow!
Wow, ow.
Um, I'll be right back.
- Thank you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- Greg, move your head.