THE GREAT WALL HAS STOOD FOR CENTURIES
AS ONE OF MANKIND'S MOST ENDURING WONDERS.
IT SPANS OVER 5500 MILES
AND TOOK MORE THAN 1700 YEARS TO BUILD.
IT PROTECTED FROM MANY DANGERS.
SOME ARE KNOWN. SOME ARE LEGEND.
THIS IS ONE OF THE LEGENDS.
THE GREAT WALL
Najid, cut the horses loose!
We have to turn back.
We have been riding
for six months.
- And we've lost twenty men.
- But we survived.
Yes. By chance.
Any one of us could have
met that same fate.
We were the strongest.
Remember why you're here.
In the West, we would be enemies,
and I wouldd have to kill you.
At least here we
have a common goal.
Oh, yes.
This black powder.
It turns air into fire.
And kills a dozen men at one time.
- It is a weapon of our dreams.
- What if it's just a myth?
Men have sent word
that it's real.
And those men are dead.
And we are next.
We have no maps,
no medicines,
and no food.
No one is going back.
We take inventory
of what we have left
and finish what we started.
There's not much here.
The moon is strong.
When the horse are fresh, we move.
- To where?
- North.
If they keep after us,
we'll kill them in the mountains.
The magnet.
Too heavy.
- Useless.
- I'll have it.
It's all yours.
Amigo, only you would carry
a stupid magnet through the desert.
I can use it to make a compass.
Rizzeti won't make it.
The wound is festering.
- We'll be dragging a corpse.
- I heard that.
He's earned the right
to die where he wants.
I've been left for dead twice.
- It was bad luck.
- For who?
The people who left me.
Where are they?
Hill tribes?
It's no man.
Then what is it?
Whatever it is...
it's hunting.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
I took its hand.
We need to move.
Agreed.
I'll take the hands with us.
What the hell for?
So someone can tell me what I just killed.
Persistent bastards,
aren't they?
We'll take the rise,
make a stand there.
What a long shitting way to go to die.
Mother of God.
Fire!
I have no need to
go down fighting.
Agreed.
I say we take our chanches
with the gents in front of us.
I haven't surrendered in a while, eh.
It'll come back to you.
Follow my lead.
We'll be fine.
Of course, my friend.
Where you go, I follow.
You're doing such a
great job already.
All commanders to
the great hall!
All commanders report
to the General!
Make way!
All commanders to the large hall!
Commander Lin is needed immediately!
Calling Commander Lin!
They know what it is.
And they don't look
so happy to see it.
All the more reason to get
the hell out of here.
Our weapons are on that table.
Have you lost your mind?
I can take the guards on
the perimeter with my bow.
You cut the legs out
from under the officers.
I must confess this is
not my favorite plan.
Where was this found?
You speak English.
Fantastic.
Where was this found?
It wasn't found.
It was taken.
That thing killed three men
before we took it down.
Where?
Two days ride.
North, in the mountains.
He says two days ride north,
in the mountains.
- They claim to have killed it.
- Two days?
Earlier than we expected.
Strategist Wang!
I'm listening, General.
The two of them killed it?
- Two of you, you did this?
- Well...
- I killed it.
- Alone?
- He claims to have killed it alone.
- By himself?
Impossible.
Tell me how.
A swing of the sword.
The hand came away clean.
The beast fell
back into a chasm.
- Why are you here?
- We came to trade.
We were ambushed.
Guards!
You are soldiers.
Commander Lin.
Wait.
General.
They claim to be traders
who were ambushed.
These barbarians are liars.
Perhaps not.
They brought the claw here.
The wound is fresh.
There is green blood
on his sword.
Those prove his story.
To protect our secret,
we must kill them.
- Eliminate the possibility of trouble.
- I agree.
We should kill them!
General.
Until we find the truth,
- I advise we keep them alive.
- Alert!
General, signals from
the smoke towers!
We are under attack!
Take them to the stockade.
- All stations on full alert!
- Yes! All stations on full alert!
Are you killing us, Sister?
Two lost travelers?
What's happening here?
Is this bitch going to kill us?
I think she'd like that.
If it is death, my dear,
we need time to pray.
I'm trying here.
Sister, I know a siege when I see one.
What comes at you so hard
you need a wall like this?
- What the hell did we kill out there?
- Tao Tei.
You killed a Tao Tei scout.
You killed it alone.
You are correct.
We are under siege.
But we did not expect the
attack for another nine days.
Attack?
- Tao Tei?
- What the hell is a Tao Tei?
Many things about your
story have importance.
You are not to die today.
Hurry!
I'm sorry, sir.
I can not find the key.
Forget it!
Bring them to the wall.
Keep an eye on them!
General.
It's finally happening.
Yes.
Sixty years preparing for this moment.
Stop! Stop!
Go. Go!
Inside!
Stand still!
Get down! Get down!
The black are the foot soldiers.
- And the red?
- Those are the archers.
- And the blue? - They're all women.
- What the hell do they do?
Look at this army.
- Have you ever seen anything like this?
- Incredible.
Catch it!
They look nervous.
It's a big wall to be so nervous.
Do you hear it?
- Long distance weapons!
- Yes! Drums signal long distance weapons!
Grab it!
Light it!
Aim for the eyes! Aim for the eyes!
Crane Corps attack!
William, over there.
Why isn't he tied up?
There's our escape.
General. There's the queen.
She commands them.
Attack the queen!
- Close combat!
- Yes! Close combat!
Drums signal close combat.
We need to move!
We need to move or we die!
Go, go!
Go and fight!
Cut me loose!
- Fight or run?
- Run where?
Aim for the eyes!
William!
Hey! Bitch!
- William.
- I need a shot.
What god made those things?
None that we know.
- Think they'll hang us now?
- I could use the rest.
- You fought well today.
- You've earned General Shao's praise.
- Will they come back?
- Yes.
All we can do is prepare.
Take them to the barracks.
- They need rest.
- Yes!
Thank you for saving my life.
Commander Lin.
You grew up in the
Nameless Order.
I've taught you many things,
and you have been learning,
but they have been learning also.
Strategist Wang warned
they are evolving.
No one listened.
The enemies we're facing today
are more intelligent than 60 years ago.
Watch the foreigners closely.
They can never leave.
- We must protect the secrets of the Wall.
- Yes sir!
Who are you?
Easy.
I'm Ballard.
William.
This is Tovar.
What are you doing here?
- We came looking for black powder.
- I bet you did.
I came with merceneries for the same thing,
25 years ago.
And did you find it?
Finding it and leaving with it
alive are two different things.
You saved the west turret.
That was extremely diplomatic.
We weren't being diplomatic.
We were trying to stay alive.
- You smell like animals.
- Thank you.
Clean up and they'll feed you.
He knows where the powder is.
Then why is he still here?
He needs help getting out?
Right.
We play our part,
take the powder and go home.
- I didn't sign up for this.
- Which part?
Well... All of it.
But mostly the monsters.
There's a lot of them.
We really do smell.
General Shao welcomes
you as honored guests
of the Nameless Order,
and thanks you for your skill and courage.
We are honored to be honored.
Is that the best you've got?
General.
I couldn't help wondering,
why would such an
accomplished archer
used such a primitive bow.
Commander Chen thinks your bow
is not worthy of your skill.
Tell him there's no better weapon here.
He claims his weapon is second to none.
Let him show us.
Give him some space!
- They wish to see you shoot.
- In here?
Unless he's afraid.
It's a large audience.
- What was that?
- He thinks you have fear.
Too many people.
- Get one of the cups.
- Now?
- I want to eat.
You remember how to do this?
Last Time didn't go so good.
- We were drunk.
- How high?
Ten yards. Six hands
to the right.
- Turn around.
- No. I'll do it this way.
- On my count.
- Amigo...
One.
Two.
Three.
Pull.
Good luck with that.
I want food.
- Who taught you English?
- Sir Ballard.
English and Latin.
Heard he's been here
for twenty five years.
You won't let him leave.
He must stay here.
What about us?
Pace yourself.
The meals are regular here.
I hope not to stay that long.
I like your thinking,
but I suggest you keep your plans private.
You aren't the first Westerners to
come here looking for black powder.
We'll discuss it tonight.
Bring your partner.
- How long have you been here?
- Always.
I was not five years
old when I came here.
I have no other family.
We're the same.
I was given to an army
before I can remember.
- As a soldier?
- Worse. As a gleaner.
Packs of children,
we'd clean the battlefields.
After, when the fighting's over,
I became a page.
- a pikeman's boy.
- For Your country?
No. I fought for food.
You fight to eat.
You live long enough,
you fight for money.
How many flag do you fight for?
I don't know.
I fought for Harold against the Danes.
I saved a Duke's life.
I fought for him until he died.
Fought for Spain
against the Franks.
Fought for Franks
against Boulogne.
I fought for the Pope.
Many flags.
We are not the same.
Meet me on the Wall.
I have something to show you.
He should be careful with her.
She's very powerful here.
Then it is a fair contest.
Come.
You wish to try?
Men are too heavy.
Do you think we can pull him up?
She says men have so much to teach us.
I don't think
that's what she said.
You know what I think?
I think you're afraid.
You said that this morning.
And yet,
here I am.
Yes.
Here you are.
Will you jump?
Or not?
- These men know what they're doing?
- Wrong question.
Whether or not the cable is attached,
that is the question.
- And the answer?
- Xin ren.
Xin ren?
Xin ren means trust.
To have faith.
Here, in this army,
we fight for more than food or money.
We give our lives to something more.
Xin ren is our flag.
Trust in each other.
In all ways, at all times.
Well, that's all well and good,
but I'm not jumping.
I'm alive today because I trust no one.
A man must learn to trust,
before he can be trusted.
Then you were right.
We're not the same.
Stay vigilant!
The next attack is coming!
My god!
A taste, a glimpse,
a few pilfered grains
from Strategist Wang's
supply of black powder.
He's mastered the transmutation
of these elements.
People speak of a weapon.
There are many weapons here.
Why have we not seen them?
There are many things you have not seen.
And many things you should pray
will not be needed
before the siege is through.
The Tao Tei will return.
When the drums call to battle,
the guards leave their post and
take their positions on the Wall.
That is our moment.
We want to be riding away
as the battle rages.
And the armory doors?
- You have keys?
- I have black powder,
enough for several doors.
He brings us in.
We get us out.
Strategist Wang request your presence.
As you fought, where was this stone?
In my bag.
Its unseen force is powerfull.
I believe this strange
stone could help us.
We try everything.
- Where are the Tao Tei now?
- The mountains, regrouping.
Where do they come from?
About 20 centuries ago,
There was an emperor whose greed
brought deep suffering to all of China.
The heaven sent a meteor
that struck Gouwu Mountain
turning it green and
releasing Tao Tei.
From that day on,
the Tao Tei rise every sixty years,
to scourge the north of China.
They come to remind us of what happens
when greed is unchecked.
They eat anything, alive or dead,
and take food to their queen.
She depends on her soldiers to feed her.
Only with the food they
provide is she able to multiply.
The capital and its 2 million people,
is only 800 li away.
If the Tao Tei ever had
that much nourisment
no corner of the world would be safe.
- You cann't hunt them?
- Men try. They disappear.
We never find their bones.
Troops unaccounted for at the West Tower!
Why did they leave the bodies?
Dismount!
Formation!
Advance!
Stop.
Commander Lin.
General...
They led us into a trap.
We underestimated their intelligence.
The Nameless Order...
- is yours to command.
- General...
Commanders, this is
my final order...
from this day forward,
Commander Lin will lead you.
The soldiers of the Nameless Order
will stand firm.
The wall must not fall!
We will defeat the Tao Tei!
- Rest in peace.
- Rest in peace!
This is envoy Shen from the palace.
He has brought important records
to help with the coming battle.
- This is a 900 years old batte report.
- A 900 years old battle report.
At the Hans Gate,
three beasts mounted the wall.
They killed many men as they went forward.
Then, by the grace of the ancient gods,
the beasts stopped
and sat peacefully,
as we slaughtered them.
There was a magnet on
site just like this one.
At the Hans Gate,
was a magnet just like this one.
I believe that magnet was
the reason the two of you Westerners
killed the Tao Tei so easily.
I believe the magnet
makes the Tao Tei deaf.
Without instruction,
they fall still.
- How to prove that?
- How can we be sure?
Why not try it?
Capture a Tao Tei.
See if it works.
- He wants to try. He wants to catch one.
- How?
No net is strong enough.
Hunt them. Like a whale.
You know what that is.
A water beast.
A hundred times the size of a Tao Tei.
A spear that grabs.
Hook the bone.
Pulled them up.
Use a spear, hook them.
So we can catch them.
I've seen it done in Spain.
He claims to have seen
it done in Spain.
What the hell are you doing?
We need to be free when
the attack comes.
How many chances do you think we will get?
Be injured. Be missing.
Be a coward.
Get out of this.
We did enough.
The mixture must be strong
to put the creature to sleep.
- Spread it on evenly.
- Yes, Commander!
Snap out of it!
Useless idiot! report to the kitchen
where you belong!
- Yes, Commander.
- Go!
- He'll be here.
- When? When it was over?
- We will start and he will find us.
- Start?
We're jumping off a cliff here.
I have everything.
Powder, tools, maps.
It's all hidden and
arranged along the route.
Once we start, there's no going back.
- Death Squad ready!
- Yes! Death Squad go!
Blades ready!
Blades forward!
- Attack!
- Go!
Left! Right!
- I'll find him.
- Forget him.
He'd rather die trying
to impress the new general
than grab the key to every counting room
and brothel in the world.
Good God, man. The time is now.
I can't go without him.
- More the spoils for us!
- We need his bow!
Harpoons!
- Harpoons, Now!
- Yes! Harpoons, fire!
Fire!
There!
- Move!
- It's the last one!
- Pull!
- No, no, no. Stop!
Hold!
There's too much tension!
Chain will break.
- That way. That way.
- Let him run!
Stop! Stop! We need longer
for the sleeping potion to work.
That way. That way.
We need to isolate it.
Sparate it from the others.
- Ring of Fire!
- Yes! Ring of Fire!
- The chain won't hold much longer!
- We're losing him!
- William, wait. Screaming arrows!
- Yes! Screaming arrows!
These arrows will scream
as the Tao Tei run.
Aim for the sound.
Aim inside the circle.
Blanket the whole area.
Fire!
Pull!
I'm only saving you
so I can kill you myself.
Grab the axe, we're fighting blind.
- Not yet!
- I know what to do!
- The fire is not holding them back here.
- Die well, brother.
- What the hell are you doing?
- She's listening.
- Prepare black powder weapon!
Prepare to light the fuses!
Yes!
- Did it work?
- Yes.
The beast was captured.
- My friend...
- He was unharmed.
Why did you go over the Wall?
Xin ren.
Did I say that right?
Thank you.
Black powder.
It is a terrible weapon.
It would be better if you had never see it.
I know very little of the outside world.
But it seems to me, the greed of men
is not that different than the Tao Tei.
Is that true?
The strong take what they want.
Forget what you have seen.
Excellent! Send it to the
capital immediately.
No! We need to study it here.
If a Tao Tei is captured alive,
it must be sent to the emperor.
This is an Imperial Order.
You're much braver than they think.
You're wounded?
I was looking for you.
To say thank you.
You feel good, huh?
Maybe you sing a little song, eh?
I will join you.
We can sing together
how you saved the gratefull Chinos.
You saw what happened out there,
and that's what you say?
I see black powder.
- I see a man forget his friends.
- The black powder's not going anywhere.
What goes nowhere is you.
You'll never get what
you want from this.
You think they see you
as some kind of hero?
A man of virtue?
Maybe you can fool them,
but I know what you are.
You know what you are.
A thief, a liar,
and a killer.
You can never undo things you've done.
and you will never be anything.
Good to see you again, amigo.
Tao Tei movement!
All troops to the Wall!
- Nothing?
- No.
- How do you know he won't betray us?
- I don't.
They'll kill him.
They'll kill him no matter what.
The time they spend killing him,
is time they are not chasing us.
Careful with that.
There's powder here.
Tovar.
General, it goes all the way through.
Tao Tei have breached the wall.
They're smarter than we thought.
- Summon my commanders immediately!
- Yes, General!
Have a look.
See if it's gone out.
- Is it safe?
- Of course it is.
Shake it off, man.
To work.
I thought you said it was safe?
We're in, didn't we?
- You're here.
- We've come to our senses, eh?
Ballard has planned well.
Getting out is easy.
There's a gate. Twenty miles west.
We dodge the hill tribes.
- We can make it.
- They need us here.
They need more than us.
- These people are doomed.
- Don't be a fool.
I've been a fool.
I'm done with it.
Brother, please.
We've been fighting for nothing.
For greed.
Amigo, after all the blood,
the cold, and pain,
with this black powder
in our saddle bags, we win.
You come with me.
I can't do that now.
- Stay and fight.
- William...
- Think he's dead?
- It'd take a lot more than that.
All of the attacks have been a diversion,
while they dug this tunnel.
They have breached the wall.
Once they reach the capital,
nothing in the world can stop them.
At a full gallop,
it's two days to the capital.
- There's no way we can catch them.
- The wind is strong now.
It blows from the north all day tomorrow.
We have to use the balloons.
- If it works, how long to Bianliang?
- Six hours if the wind hold.
If we make it alive.
General, none of the tests have worked.
Get ready!
Come on!
THE CAPITAL
BIANLIANG
- How did you capture it?
- Your Excellency!
Your Excellency, It's the magnet.
It keeps the beast under control.
This is the most important discovery
in the history of the Tao Tei.
- We will investigate immediately.
- Bring him here!
- I tried to stop...
- You dare to speak to me?
- I didn't do this.
- And you came here to trade.
And you knew nothing of black powder.
What a fool you must think I am.
If I was with them, why would I be here?
I tried to stop them.
Liar!
You lie.
- Some part of you knows that's not true.
- If I were not the General,
I would kill you myself.
General!
- General.
- Speak up.
I was there when it happened.
I saw him try to stop them.
Are you sure?
If you're lying, I'll have your head!
I swear on my vow to the Nameless Order!
Lock him up.
Send the cavalry.
Go after the two that got away.
Yes, General.
Which way, left or right?
Go up and take a look
from the high ground.
No! Bastard!
- Keep it steady!
- Yes, General!
- Watch the powder!
What happened?
We have failed.
The Tao Tei are in the kingdom.
You are free to leave.
Take what you wish and go.
- This was the General's final order.
- Where is she?
To do what? To fight?
- Is there a chance?
- There's only one.
Kill the Queen.
Kill the Queen, or we all die.
Leave.
Tell the world what you have seen,
and tell them what is coming.
I'll need my bow.
If I'm to join you, I'll need my bow.
Strategist Wang!
Please take me with you.
He wishes to join us.
The distance is the key.
The magnet is only effective
when close to the beast.
Therefore, the effect
weakens as it gets further away.
You see I have it
under complete control.
Write down nine feet.
- Steer to the rear of the palace.
- Yes! To the rear of the palace!
Above you!
- Light a grenade!
- Yes, sir!
Behind you!
I set you free.
And here I am.
There's the queen!
They will not attack while
the queen is feeding.
We have a chance!
Hold on!
State your purpose!
General Lin Mae from Nameless Order.
At your service!
What took you so long?
The Tao Tei overrun the city!
Thousands of soldiers
and innocent are dead.
You're too late!
Where is the captured Tao Tei?
- In the dungeon!
- We need it to kill the queen.
Once she is dead,
The Tao Tei can not function.
Without her signal, their
whole army will freeze.
There is an underground canal here.
Has it been breached?
The Tao Tei should all be above ground.
And the one we captured?
We load it up.
We feed him.
And it will return to its queen.
Good.
You'll have one hell of a scar,
- but you'll live.
- He says you will live.
We'll come back for him.
They've broken through!
Patience, William.
And it will go to the Queen when it's done?
It should.
It will.
Let it in.
I can get a shot from above.
Go!
I'll hold them back.
Wait. Not yet.
Hit.
Go higher.
I'll get a better shot.
General! It's up to you now!
We have one black powder weapon left.
Give me the spear.
I've trained for this my whole life.
Trust.
I'll get you the shot.
I've got you.
So, how's life without me?
A little slow.
- You're a hero after all.
- Oh, it looks that way.
You seem pleased with yourself..
And what are they giving you
for all your troubles?
A bag of gold?
A victory parade along the top of the Wall?
All the black powder I can carry.
And a cavalry escort
to get me home safely.
- Well, congratulations.
- Thank you.
So what is this?
- You're here to rub my nose in it?
- Well, would you blame me?
The last time I saw you,
you left me for dead.
And the time before, I saved your life.
True.
You know, the Emperor gave me a choice.
I could take the black powder
or I could take you.
Please tell me you chose the powder.
I don't even know you anymore.
The horses are saddled and waiting.
Best we ride before nightfall.
I'll be inside.
Don't leave without me.
I came to say goodbye.
I understand congratulations are in order.
General of the northwest territory.
Quite an honor.
Seems you've made your choice.
Oh, him? Believe me, I'm already think
about trading him back for the powder.
I heard that.
Perhaps we were both wrong.
We are more similar than I thought.
Thank you General.
- Are you sure you don't want to go back?
- Of course I do.
I just don't trust you
to make it out of here alone.