- Previously on "The Flash"...
- The Flash is back!
- How did you get your powers?
- Oh, you're not
gonna believe it.
And do you two want to
know the best part?
I wasn't the only one.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes.
- This isn't good-bye.
- No.
More like, "See you later."
- He's right where
you wanted him.
What do we do now?
- We find the others.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Begin recording.
Observations on
subject number two.
Name, Rebecca Sharpe.
Or as she prefers,
the plebeian sobriquet
Becky.
- It's Becky with a Y,
not, um, an I-E,
or an E-E, just Y.
And you heard me say
"no milk," right?
'Cause I am severely
lactose intolerant, like...
- Subject was born
in Sarasota, Florida,
the first indignity in a life
full of unfortunate
circumstances.
- Mmm, mmm.
[quirky music]
[gasps]
Oh, that is definitely not soy.
Oof.
- Subject lives
with her boyfriend.
- Almost there, almost there,
almost there.
Oh!
- [moaning]
- Kenny!
[gasps] We are going
to deal with this...
[groans]
In five...five to ten minutes.
- Correction...
[door closes]
Subject previously lived
with her boyfriend.
- Oh, I don't know.
- Subject's occupation...
- Should I stay?
- Blackjack dealer.
- Or should I hit?
- Subject's temperament...
- I...I don't know, man.
I think you should just hit.
Why don't you hit?
- Defeatist.
- Okay, I'll hit.
- Great, perfect.
And...
- Got 21!
[laughs]
- There it is.
Here, ahh.
Oh, ahh.
- [laughing]
- Here you go, sir.
Congratulations.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Sure.
- There you go.
- Oh, that's...that's nice.
Thank you.
- Looks like I found
my good luck charm.
- [gasps] Hey!
- [screams]
- [gasps]
- My appletini.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Can I...can I maybe just...
can I get a reference,
you think?
No?
- Subject believes
no matter what she does,
the universe will conspire
to punish her.
- Another job.
Ow! Okay.
- Or as she writes
on her Myspace page,
"I am jinxed."
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[screams]
Great!
There goes another car.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
- Subject's low
self-esteem suggests
she will be easily manipulated.
- Wait, wait!
Wait...ow!
Oh, jeez.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait!
Ow!
Oh, come on.
I'm here!
Hey, oh, yes!
Thank you, universe!
Finally, some good luck.
Hi.
Okay.
Ow, ow, ow.
Hey.
[panting]
Hi.
Hey.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
[rumbling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [slo-mo] Barry!
Where are you?
- I don't know.
I lost Caitlin.
There's too many of them, man.
- No, you can take them.
Just listen to me.
You just need to do one thing.
Run, Barry.
Run!
- [screams]
Oh, come on.
[lasers firing,
alarm blaring]
They got me.
- Oh, you have failed
this city.
[screams]
[alarm blaring]
- [exhales]
- For real, Chad?
In the back?
- Suck it, old man.
[together]
Oh!
- Wait, did you
guys die already?
- Well, Chad...
- He just told us...
Come on. Come on.
- I don't know what's wrong
with kids these days.
Churlish.
[laser firing]
You better watch yourself,
Chad.
Come at me at the paintball
field next time.
I'll kick your little...
[laughs]
Hey!
Mrs. McConnell.
How you doing?
Chad's a treasure.
He really is.
- Pretzel for Caitlin.
Corn dog for Iris,
two franks for Cisco...
- Yes, thank you.
- Three burgers, five churros,
and six funnel cakes for Barry.
- Look at all of this junk.
Guys, I'm really sorry.
If the pipes in the house
weren't making
this weird, annoying sound,
I would have just actually
had you all over for dinner.
- Squeaky pipes
at the West house.
What a surprise.
- Mm-hmm.
- Really? You're familiar
with this sound?
- [chuckles]
- Oh, yeah.
You mean the...
[mimics creaking noises]
Yeah.
- It's been doing that for...
18 years?
- Yeah.
- Every house has
a personality, Iris.
Just likes to be heard.
- Hmm.
[phone buzzes]
- Oh, my gosh.
They broke up.
The Wexler-Waclawiks broke up.
- For real?
- Yes.
- Hell yeah.
- Yes!
- Uh, who are the
Wexler-Wa-claws-wilix,
and why are we happy
that their love is dead?
- They're a couple that
were getting married
at the Propizio the
weekend of the 2nd.
Which means now
the venue is open.
- That's amazing.
What good luck.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So now we just have
to put a deposit down.
- I'll run it over.
- Nope, already covered, babe.
- Oh.
[phones buzzing and beeping]
- Oh, God.
Breach alert, guys.
We gotta go.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[static crackling]
- Uh...
♪ ♪
Hey, Harry, um,
is Jesse not coming?
- [sighs]
So, um...
- I thought Jesse and I
were having date night.
- Yeah,
that's what you thought.
Let me just...
okay.
[quirky music]
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Just let me...
- [clears throat]
- Okay, so...
- Hey, Wally.
It's me.
- Good to see you.
- So, I've, um...
I've been doing some thinking.
And...
[static interference]
You know, we've both been
so busy...
You and Earth...
[static interference]
- Stupid hologram.
You know, it's that darn
Atlantean plastic.
It's really shoddy workmanship.
Sorry about this.
- What is...what is this thing?
- Break...
breakup cube.
You don't have breakup cubes
on your Earth?
Oh, that's not good.
Okay.
A breakup cube is, uh...
kind of what it sounds like.
You know, you record a message
for the person you want to...
the person, and you, uh,
pick a music setting,
and then there's a tissue that
pops out if you need that.
You know,
a breakup cube.
- Jesse's breaking up with me
with a cube?
- Seems like a really convenient
way to break somebody's heart.
- Exactly.
- What did she say
in the message?
- You know, you heard.
You...you're a great guy...
I don't remember.
- Don't you have total recall?
- Yeah...no, no.
Don't...I did.
I don't.
I did, but I don't.
♪ ♪
Come on, don't make me...
she...you heard.
She said that you're
a great, great guy
and that she was busy
on our Earth,
and that you're busy here
filling in for...
you know...
[mimics whooshing sound]
On this Earth,
and she just felt that you guys
were a little out of sync.
You know, and that
she thought she needed
some time, you know,
to work on her stuff.
You know, it's not you,
it's me.
Not me.
Her, me.
Her, not me.
Her.
And...and she said, you know,
"I'll never forget you,
Wally West,
because you're amazing,"
and then, uh,
that you were her...
[clears throat]
First.
♪ ♪
And a bunch of other stuff.
Not important.
So...but he's tough.
You don't need that, right?
You're a tough guy.
Right, West?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, um...
♪ ♪
- He doesn't want the cube.
I don't blame him.
[alarm beeping]
- 211s at First National
and O'Sullivan Bank.
- Could be a spree.
- Central City Bank's
on that avenue, too.
I'll check it out.
- We're not done.
- What?
[Frank Sinatra's
"Luck Be a Lady"]
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry, I don't know
why the app crashed.
But, uh, this one's
on the house.
♪ Luck be a lady tonight ♪
- Oh.
Find a penny,
pick it up,
then all day you'll
have good luck.
So true.
- Ah, afternoon, ma'am.
- It is a good afternoon,
Mr. Security Man.
- [choking]
- [screams]
- ♪ Luck let a gentleman see ♪
♪ ♪
♪ How nice a dame you can be ♪
[electricity sparking]
- Please, don't touch
the oven, Mom.
- ♪ I know the way
you've treated ♪
♪ Other guys
you've been with ♪
♪ Luck be a lady with me ♪
♪ ♪
- Aww, you waited for me.
- [gasps]
- I see her.
- She's getting away in a Prius.
- Last time I checked,
the Flash is faster
than a Prius.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Luck be a lady ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
- What the hell?
- That's the least secure
security footage
I've ever seen.
- Yeah, that's not even
the strangest thing
she made happen.
I mean, I slipped
on a barrel of marbles.
It was like I was in a cartoon.
- That's some seriously
bad luck.
- Yeah, there's no such
thing as luck.
- Yeah?
Tell that to my cousin Hector.
He got jinxed by an ex.
Hasn't been able to find a mall
parking spot for three years.
- Hey, so we ran
the sketches you made us
through the CCP database,
and...
- Her name's Becky Sharpe.
She's 24 years old, no priors.
- No priors?
Then why is she in the database?
- Because
in the last three years
she's lived in Central City,
she's been rear-ended
four times,
her identity stolen twice...
- A cat burglar literally
burgled her cat.
- [chuckles]
- Okay, you see, Harry?
That is bad juju.
- Okay, Ramon,
what you call juju,
I call quantum entanglement.
Discrete quantum particles
are connected,
and when triggered,
they simulate a synchronicity
that, to the untrained eye...
to the common eye...
could seem like luck.
- So if Becky can affect
the particles around her
in a positive way,
then their connected particles
start spinning negatively.
- So when good things
happen to her,
bad things happen
all around her.
- Great, she's got
a good luck field.
- She's a meta.
- Well, except she can't be.
I mean, she's only been in
Central City for three years.
- Yeah, so there's no way
she was affected
by the particle accelerator
explosion.
- Well, neither was Kilgore.
We saw firsthand
what he could do.
- Not to sound like
a broken record,
but where the hell are all
these new metas coming from?
- You know what?
Maybe the scanners
in the suit picked
something up.
- You said you took
all the tech out.
- Okay, well,
I left something in.
- Okay?
Sue me.
- Wow.
- Cecile needs me at the house.
You guys let me know
what you find out, all right?
- All right.
- There.
- Yeah, I-I see it, okay?
Yeah, the suit definitely
registered trace amounts
of dark matter on Becky.
- So if there was another
dark matter incident...
- We need to figure out how
and where it happened, ASAP.
- I'll calibrate your satellite
to scan for the same dark matter
found in the suit.
- Uh, no, you won't.
- Yeah, I will.
- Don't touch the sat...
don't touch the satellite!
- I'll be touching it.
- Don't!
[phone buzzes]
- Oh!
Um, something just arrived
for me at the loft.
I gotta go.
♪ ♪
- What?
- You called the plumber.
- Joe West, I cannot keep
living with that sound.
- You know, this house is, uh...
- Bitchin'?
- No.
It's in need of some work.
In my certified opinion,
you need all new piping.
Now, it'll set you back
15 thou.
- Hmm.
- Oh!
O-okay.
Thank you...so much.
You've, uh...you've given us
a lot to think about.
And I mean a whole lot.
[sighs]
- 15 thou.
My great uncle paid less
for this whole place.
I guess I'm gonna have
to break open the piggybank.
- Or, you know,
we could take that 15.
We could put it towards
a down payment on something new.
- Ooh.
You're suggesting that
we sell my house?
- Babe, I'm just saying,
you know, this is...
this is a really big place
for a couple
of empty nesters like us,
and there's always
gonna be something
that's gonna need replacing.
- Let me think about it, okay?
- Mm-hmm. Think about it.
[softly] Think about it.
- I'll think about it.
- Mm-hmm, think about it.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Barry!
Oh, my God.
Turn around!
- I did!
- Did you see?
- No, I didn't see.
- You saw!
- I did...see.
But just for a second.
- Which is like an eternity
for a speedster.
You know it's bad luck
to see a bride in her dress
before the wedding day.
- Too late.
- What happened?
- Um, the Propizio called.
We're not gonna be able
to have our wedding there.
- What?
Why?
- Well, um,
the villa burned down.
I guess a crème brûlée
competition
got a little heated.
- Okay, well, thankfully
we have our backup.
- No, another couple
booked it this morning.
- [sighs]
- It's okay, though.
It's okay.
If we can stop evil
time-traveling speedsters
from destroying the planet,
we can find a wedding venue.
- Barry, our wedding
is in six weeks.
- It'll work out.
Okay?
I would marry you anytime,
anywhere.
[soft music]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- Ah, Kobe beef.
My favorite.
[giggles]
- Becky.
What are the chances
I'd run into you?
- Is this your secretary?
Funny, you said
she was haggard.
- No, I...I never said...
- I'll get that for you.
- Whoa, whoa!
[grunts]
[screaming]
- I don't understand.
Your plan revolves around
this dolt?
- What's wrong
with all of you?
Who makes soup so hot?
[beeping]
- As lusterless as Rebecca is,
she may be the most
formidable of them all.
- Then why don't we
get her now?
- The capricious nature
of her powers
warrants further observation.
- [sighs]
[beeping]
- [screaming]
Oh, man,
are those live lobsters?
- Give me that. You're not...
- Stop hovering, okay?
- You're not holding it right.
- I know how to read
a dark matter scan, Harry.
- Well, not from where I sit,
you don't.
- Oh yeah, good one.
Don't you have
somewhere else to be,
like breaking another
speedster's heart?
- Sorry I'm late.
Iris and I just lost
two wedding venues
in less than 24 hours.
- Ah, bad juju.
- Give me that, okay?
Test, all right.
Here we go.
And adjust.
[scanner beeping]
- Sorry.
- Ah, sorry.
- Here, here. Right here.
This is where Becky Sharpe
was exposed to Dark Matter.
- Here?
- Yes.
- It can't be. This is
the middle of the street.
It's not even
an interesting one.
- My scans are accurate.
- Your scans are accurate?
- My scans are accurate!
- Explain how there's nothing
within miles of here
capable of even
creating dark matter.
- There was three weeks ago.
[rumbling]
This is where I came out
of the Speed Force.
[electricity crackling]
- No, it isn't.
You came out in Ivy City.
- No, I ran there after.
But I remember now.
This is where I came out.
This is where
the portal opened.
- And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
I can only imagine how many
meta-humans you created.
[engine rumbles]
- My best guess?
A busload.
- We did it?
We brought dark matter
into Central City?
- When you pulled me out
of the Speed Force, yeah.
- All the people on that bus,
we turned them into metas.
- Every time we try
to do something right,
it goes horribly wrong.
- We're cursed.
- Maybe we should
burn some sage.
- Guys, we're not cursed.
- You're not cursed.
You should be cursed at.
- Okay, why should we
be "cursed at"?
- You should be cursed at
because you opened
the Speed Force
without consulting me.
- Okay, I don't think
we need to rehash...
[all exclaiming]
- All right.
- Okay, I did consult you,
and you're the one
who gave me the calculations
in the first place.
- Yeah, I told you not to use
them without consulting me.
I said, "Ramon,
don't use the calculations
without consulting me."
- Guys.
- Yeah, yeah, I heard you.
I didn't see the need for that.
- And that's why
you should be cursed at.
- What does that even mean?
- What does it mean?
It means you're a...
- Okay, you know what?
This is exactly why
we didn't contact you,
'cause the last thing we need
around here is more
of your salty-ass attitude.
- If you don't need
my salty attitude,
then maybe you should
carry on without me.
I'll let myself out.
- Oh, are you going back
to your Earth?
I'll breach you there
right now.
- "I'll breach you there
right now!"
- That's not what I sound like.
- That was really high.
- Listen, Cisco,
I know Harry could stand
to work on
his bedside manner, but...
- You know what?
We don't need him.
What we need is to focus
on catching this meta.
Am I right?
- Yeah, you're right.
But Becky doesn't seem like
one of our typical villains.
I think if we could
track her down,
maybe we could get
through to her.
[phone buzzing]
- Hey, Cecile.
What?
I'm on my way.
I need you to run me
to the house.
- You said you never wanted...
- I need you to run me
to the house.
- Yes, sir.
[whooshing]
[water dripping]
- Oh.
- What happened?
- [sighs] The ceiling went from
clanking to howling,
and then it just started
pouring all this stuff down.
- Yeah. We need to turn
the water off, stat.
- Yeah.
So, the water valve
is in the crawl space.
Um, don't ever go
into the crawl space.
- I hear you,
loud and clear.
- Barry, thank you
very much for your help.
I'm gonna go check upstairs.
- Man, why is this happening?
That girl jinx us?
- No, no.
Nobody jinxed us.
This house is just...
what's another word for "old"?
- Vintage.
- Cecile thinks
I should sell it.
- Yeah?
What do you think?
- I think she's got a point.
Life would be a hell of a lot
easier in a brand-new house.
- Sounds like an easy decision.
- It should be.
But this house has got
one thing
no other house will ever have.
- [chuckles]
- Remember I'd measure you kids
at every birthday?
- Yeah.
I outgrew Iris at 12.
She kept saying she'd catch up.
- All my memories of you kids
are tied into these walls.
How can I give that up?
- Well, you don't have
to give that up, Joe.
We'll always have
those memories,
no matter where you live.
Trust me.
When I came to live here
after my mom died,
I learned that
it doesn't matter
where you live.
Only matters that you have
people that love you.
[phone buzzing]
Hold on.
What's up?
Great.
Okay, I'll go there now.
Thank you.
We're not jinxed.
If we were, Cisco
wouldn't have found Becky.
She is at Jitters.
I'm going there now.
[whooshing]
- Winner, winner!
Another winner.
- Becky?
Hi, you mind if I sit here?
- Oh, today's my lucky day,
but you're not my type at all.
- Can I sit?
- Um...
- Um, Becky,
well, you're probably wondering
how I know your name.
- Mm, it's written on my cup.
- Right, um, yeah,
but that's not how I...
You see, I work
for the CCPD as a CSI.
I investigate
very special people.
- Celebrities?
- No, not celebrities.
Um, meta-humans.
- Oh.
- Which is what I think
you are.
- [scoffs]
- See, I think you were exposed
to dark matter on a city bus
three weeks ago.
- [scoffs]
I think I would know if
I was exposed to dark matter.
That's weird.
- Becky, I know you've been
having a lot of luck lately.
- [exhales]
- And that you took some money
from a Central City bank
that doesn't belong to you.
- How do you know all that?
- I just do.
Look, getting powers
is overwhelming.
I'm sure you don't know
how they work
or what you should do
with them.
- I have some idea.
- Uh-uh-uh.
Do you really want to
test your luck?
Bad things happen to people
that get in my way.
[steam whistling]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Listen, CSI guy.
My entire life has been
one piece of crummy luck
after the next.
- Look, we all have ups
and downs in life.
- Oh, not Becky Sharpe.
I have only ever been dealt
bad hands.
But I knew one day
the universe would see
it made a mistake.
And then I'd have
the run of the table.
I got on that bus,
and Lady Luck smiled on me.
- Becky, this isn't some higher
power fixing a miscalculation.
You have powers,
and they're affecting
everyone around you,
making them feel as awful
as you used to feel.
- I'm sorry about that, but...
maybe it's just their turn.
Maybe for once,
everyone else can feel
for a second how bad I felt
my entire life.
Anyway, there is nothing
you can do
to stop me.
[steam hissing]
♪ ♪
[baby crying]
[tool clicking]
Toodles.
- So what are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
I mean, I'm not sure yet.
I can't get close enough to her
without triggering bad luck.
- Seriously,
that girl's a hazard.
Hazard, that's the one.
- [gasps]
- Maybe that means
the jinx is gone.
- Her powers only work
in her immediate vicinity.
She didn't jinx us.
- And the house is still
falling to pieces.
- It's been falling apart
for years,
just, like, really slowly.
- Well, plus,
Jesse dumped me, too.
- I...I know, dude.
And, you know, that sucks.
- And we're up against a meta
we can't even touch.
And we're the ones who made her
in the first place.
- Guys, do you have any idea
how ridiculous you all sound?
We have not been jinxed.
Or cursed, all right?
We make our own luck, right?
So what do you say we focus
and we figure this out?
[phone buzzing]
Hey, Iris.
You're where?
[organ music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, come on.
- Hey.
- Why did you want me
to put on a shirt
and meet you at a funeral?
- No, no, no.
I wanted you to meet me
at this church.
- What?
- We're getting married.
Here, put this on.
- Excuse me?
- Barry, we've had the worst
luck, okay?
From the Dominators
to Savitar to gorillas
and now these bus metas.
And on top of everything else,
now we're cursed.
- Iris, we're not cursed.
- Barry, look.
You said that you would
marry me anytime, anyplace.
- Well, this is...
- Right?
And I just feel like if
we don't get married now,
it's never gonna happen.
- That's not true, okay?
I mean...
- Oh, it's our turn.
- Our turn.
Go, go, go, go, go.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Sorry, excuse me.
Beautiful service.
- So sorry.
- I love this coffin.
Is that cedar?
- Hey, let's...come on.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Can I help you?
- Uh, yes.
Uh, we would like
to get married.
- Yes, we would.
- Oh.
- Right now.
Well, would you give us
a moment
to, uh, reset the altar?
- Oh, no, no,
that won't be necessary.
Look, we'll just...watch.
Watch.
- Okay.
- We'll just...
[chuckles]
She's excited.
Sorry.
- Flip that around.
- Yeah, probably shouldn't
have done that.
- I know, it's fine.
- Okay. We are here today
to join, um...
- That's you.
- Me?
Bartholomew Henry Allen.
- And...
- Iris Ann West.
- In holy matrimony.
[coughs]
Excuse me.
- You okay?
- Thank you.
[coughs]
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God.
- Jameson! Oh!
- [hacking cough]
- Kevin, did you use
the cinnamon incense?
You know he's allergic to it.
Shame on you.
- I don't know if we need to
shame the little boy, but...
- No, you're fine.
You're fine. Walk it off.
Father...
- [coughing]
- It's fine.
- That did not just happen.
- You know, it was a...
very nice funeral.
- Really, Barry?
[playful music]
- Ahh! Ow!
- [laughing]
That was golden.
Don't shoot, okay?
I'm here to apologize.
I know you're trying to help us
fix our own colossal screw up.
- Yeah, like always.
- Yeah, I know.
I mean, I actually thought
you'd be at home by now,
but here you are working away.
- Well...
things are a little complicated
on Earth-2.
- Oh.
Everything okay with Jesse?
- Yes.
I mean, yes.
If you must know,
I spent the summer
assembling a support staff
for her, so...
- Oh, like a Team Quick?
- No.
- Team Jesse.
- Jesse and the Quicksters.
- They're not called that.
- Well, they should be.
That sounds like
an awesome team.
- It is an awesome team,
because I assembled it.
But then, Jesse goes and kicks
me off the team, all right?
Apparently I'm too much
like me, whatever that means.
I push too hard.
You know, too many tests.
Too many training sessions.
You know, I don't allow
the team enough time
for their personal bonding.
I don't understand millennials.
Anyway. They took a vote.
I'm out.
I don't even have a home
to return to now.
I can't even go back
to my own Earth.
I'm sure you can empathize,
right, Ramon?
Because you know what I'm like.
Well, you know what?
We'll handle Sharpe,
and then I'll be
out of your hair.
[sighs]
[alarm beeping]
[dramatic music]
- Guys, there are low
probability events happening
all over the city.
- Becky's quantum field
is expanding.
- Okay, that's not possible.
- Yeah, no, her powers
are localized.
- Not anymore.
♪ ♪
- Babe, you in there?
The door's jammed.
- One sec.
[sighs]
[water dripping]
[screams]
- Guys, the quantum field
is getting higher.
♪ ♪
- My pals said you
were bad luck, sir,
but I figure,
what are the odds
a pilot has a goose
fly into his engine twice?
♪ ♪
[goose honking]
- Bird strike.
[alarms blaring]
- Mayday, this is
Flight 512 to tower.
Lost an engine
and are coming down.
- When did Hazard
get so powerful?
- Every action has an equal
and opposite reaction, so...
- The more good luck
she experiences,
the more bad luck she spreads.
- She must be experiencing
an extreme level of good luck
for her quantum field
to be expanding like this.
- Where is she now?
- She went back to work.
[together]
Snake eyes!
- For the 37th time.
- [cheering]
- Bringing your winnings
to 1.2...
both: Million.
- [laughs]
Give me those babies.
Hi.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, come on, Mama.
- Guys, if Becky keeps winning,
then bad luck will
keep spreading.
This could destroy
the whole city.
- Okay, keep calm, all right?
- Keep calm.
- Nothing's going wrong here.
[loud whirring]
- Guys, the particle
accelerator turned back on.
It's gonna explode.
- Four minutes to particle
accelerator activation.
Harry, Cisco,
status report.
- The generators turned
themselves on.
We got to shut 'em down.
- [grunts]
[engine sputtering]
- Flight 512 to tower,
we are attempting
a water landing.
- Cecile!
[handle clatters to ground]
Damn it.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[coins clinking]
- Barry, you've got to
find Hazard.
- I'm almost at the casino.
- Hazard's quantum field
is increasing.
- How much worse can it get?
- Hello, my old friend.
Let's keep this winning
streak going, shall we?
♪ ♪
[cheery electronic beeping]
Yes.
Okay, Cherry.
Here we go, cherry.
Cherry, cherry, cherry.
Cherry, cherry, cherry,
Cherry. Cherry.
Cherry!
Cherry.
It's a cherry.
Give it to me, give it to me.
Cherry, cherry,
cherry, cherry, cherry.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
How is that even possible?
- Wait, no!
[electricity sparking]
- [groans]
- Starboard fan blades
just disintegrated.
We're not gonna make it
to the water.
- Barry, what happened?
- Well, she's playing
the slots, and, um,
I cuffed myself.
- [laughs]
Oh, honey.
- Yeah, no, I know.
We need to get 'em off.
They're dampening my powers.
[electricity sparking]
- Yes, yes, yes. I'm trying.
- The hydrogen particle hatch.
We need to seal it.
♪ ♪
- There you go.
- Cherry bang bang.
Cherry bang bang, cherry.
[cheery jingle]
Cherry bang bang!
That's two cherries.
- Come on.
- Hey, look.
It's the Flash.
- [grunts]
[alarm blares]
- No, no, hey.
There's no fire.
There's not a fire!
Someone set off the alarm.
Calm down!
♪ ♪
- Babe, you okay?
- I think so.
[screams]
- Damn it, out back.
Out back, out back. Be careful.
- Okay, okay.
- One minute to activation.
- Got it.
- Nope.
both: Don't got it.
- That just opened up
the electron hatch.
[people screaming]
- Yes, I am on fire.
I know.
- [screams]
- There's no fire!
[grunts]
- Come on.
Come on, cherry pop.
Cherry pop, cherry.
[both scream]
- Damn!
- [screams]
[electricity sparking]
♪ ♪
- Barry, I can't get
the cuffs off.
- Now we got a sign
to get off of me, too.
- Cherry number three,
pop cherry, pop.
- Brace, brace, brace!
- 30 seconds to activation.
- Nope, nope.
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
Come on.
- No, wait.
Wait.
Let it go.
- What?
- Let the accelerator turn on.
- Harry...
Trust me.
- Ten seconds to activation.
- This is it.
Last one.
- Five, four, three, two...
- Here we go.
[explosion]
♪ ♪
- Cherry pop, cherry.
Ah!
[rumbling]
[dull beep]
No. What?
Star?
No, I...I don't understand.
I lost?
[electric rumbling]
[engine roaring]
- The starboard thrusts
are alive.
We're gonna make it.
- Good.
- What just happened?
- [exhales sharply]
The hydrogen electron collision
released a charge
that temporarily negated
Hazard's quantum field.
We did it.
You did it.
How did you know to do that?
- Lucky guess.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- [gasps]
Okay. Hi.
- Hi.
- Um, is there, like,
any chance that you're not
gonna arrest me?
No?
I understand.
- Come on.
- Sure.
Ow!
- Okay.
- Okay. Yep.
- Right this way.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[knocks]
- [clears throat]
Ramon...
I owe you an apology.
- Okay.
- No, that was it.
- Okay, all right.
How about something like...
"I'm sorry for blaming
everything on you?"
Or, "I'm sorry
for 'cursing at' you."
- Yeah, that's good.
That's good, that...yeah.
Pretend I said that.
- Guess I'll take it
where I can get it.
- All right.
Good talk.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
- You don't have
to go back to Earth-2.
♪ ♪
- What?
- You saved the day.
That's your "Get out
of jackass jail free" card.
- Hmm.
- Plus, you're family.
You'll always have a home here.
♪ ♪
- Thank you, I...
I appreciate the sentiment.
It's just that...
This is not my world.
- Oh, and Earth-2 is?
Did you make a bunch of friends
there that I don't know about?
What, are they all tall,
brooding dudes
with bad haircuts?
- [scoffs] I have...
I have colleagues.
Work colleagues.
And, uh...
Some of them I don't dislike.
- Exactly my point.
You've spent so much time
worrying about Jesse
and talking to dead people that
you've never even stopped
to make a life for yourself.
- What are you saying, Ramon?
Are you literally saying
I don't have a life?
- That's exactly
what I'm saying.
You don't have a life.
But you can make one.
With us, right here.
We'll help you.
'Cause God knows you're
gonna need that help.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
- I don't think so.
- I don't think so, either.
- Becky is locked up in
the meta wing at Iron Heights.
- Something tells me
our bad luck streak
has come to an end.
- Good.
We can't afford to blow
this place up a third time.
- So, look at these heat scans
taken from the satellite.
This is three weeks ago.
- It's a Central City bus?
That's the bus?
- That's the bus.
- Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
- 12 markers,
12 metas.
Now that we know
how many there are,
we won't have to wait
for them to come to us.
We can go right to them.
- Well, two down.
- Yep.
We got this.
- Yeah, you do.
- What's wrong, Wally?
- You guys tell me.
I mean...
the city was about to blow up.
No one realized I wasn't here.
- Where did you go, Wall?
- I went to Earth-2.
I had to talk to Jesse.
Hear it from her.
She told me she needs to focus
on herself, and I get it.
And I think I have
to do the same, right?
So...
I'm leaving Central City.
- Where...where are you going?
- I'm gonna go stay
with a friend
in Blue Valley
for a while.
- Every hero has
their own journey.
If yours is taking you
on a new path,
you owe it to yourself to go.
- Yeah.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Good luck.
- Kid Flash.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- I don't want anything more
than for you to find
what you're looking for.
But I've...
I've spent so much time
without you in my life.
I don't want to lose you.
- You'll never lose me, Dad.
Plus, I'm a speedster.
You need me,
and I'll come running.
- Love you, son.
- Yeah. Love you.
♪ ♪
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- Well, don't forget,
Central City will always
be the home of Kid Flash.
I won't.
Don't be a stranger.
- I won't.
I love you.
- I love you more.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- West leaves,
Allen returns.
West leaves.
Move, counter move.
- What's your point?
- Simply that...
a mysterious stranger
comes to town,
seeks out the Flash...
- Causes us to open
the Speed Force.
- Which causes the creation
of a dozen new metas.
- Right.
- Hold on.
You think the guy behind
the Samurai Robot...
- Samuroid.
- You think he wanted us
to create a busload of metas?
- I think it's all connected.
- Why would anyone want
to create metas?
- I don't know.
Whoever they are, they've got
a seriously warped way
of thinking.
[electronic humming]
- They identified the targets
sooner than we planned.
Perhaps they're smarter
than you gave them credit.
[whirring]
- Perhaps.
[ominous music]
But I'm smarter.
♪ ♪
- Oh!
Just when I thought it was safe
to get back in the house.
- Hi.
I may not be a Craftsman expert
such as yourself,
but I can handle plastering
a couple of holes in the wall.
- Baby, you didn't have to...
you didn't have to do this.
- Oh, this is our home,
and it is a disaster zone
right now,
so I am doing my part
to fix it up.
- Well, I appreciate that.
- Mm.
- [laughs]
- But, little Cecile...
you were right.
- Hmm?
- It's time for me
to let this place go.
I...It took me a minute
to get there.
I'm not good with change.
You know that.
But once I did,
I realized that
whatever house I'm in with you,
I'm gonna love.
So we might as well get one
with a dishwasher.
- [laughs]
- And a Jacuzzi.
- [gasps]
Jacuzzi.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
- I love you.
- Funny thing, babe.
- Hmm?
- I've actually had
a change of heart.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
- You want to stay?
Really?
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
- You told me that you couldn't
have asked for a better place
to raise your kids,
and it made me
look at this house
with new eyes.
- Mm.
- Especially after
I found out...
[clears throat]
Joe...
I'm pregnant.
Joe?