- Previously on "The Flash"...
- So this is where
you've been hiding.
I think you're afraid
to use your powers
because you think you'll
become like someone you hate.
- I know you're doing it
for all of us.
That's what it means
to be a hero.
- I knew I picked
the right guy.
- He's gonna die.
- Frost, how do we save him?
- I don't know!
I can't fix this.
- Accepting Ramsey's blood
would save your body
but not your soul.
You would lose the best of you.
The part of you
that Iris loves.
- That's not Barry.
- Barry.
- [snarls]
[dramatic music]
- [distorted]
The entire world will embrace
Bloodwork!
[electricity crackles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Are you guys okay?
- [exhales deeply]
Yeah.
♪ ♪
- I don't understand.
That wasn't Barry.
- Yeah, it was.
Ramsey turned him into one
of his Blood Brothers.
♪ ♪
[force field crackles]
- Babel Protocols initiated.
- What's Babel Protocols?
I thought that was just
some defense stuff
that you added to Barry's suit.
- That was version one.
Version 2.0 puts up a force
field around S.T.A.R. Labs.
Nothing gets in,
nothing goes out...
not even our comms.
I built them just in case...
just in case the Flash
ever went dark.
- Barry said that
Ramsey gave him a choice.
Why...why would he choose this?
- Maybe he decided
eternal life was better
than dying in Crisis.
- Ramsey's using Barry.
And whatever he's having
him do, he's got a plan.
[goo gurgles]
♪ ♪
- You have a police scanner?
- I'm hoping that since
this thing transmits in analog,
we can figure out what's
going on outside S.T.A.R. Labs.
- I don't get it.
Why didn't Ramsey
just have Barry kill us
as soon as he woke up?
- I don't know,
but don't count us out yet,
You know that tech
I've been working on?
Meet the Photon Emitter.
- So what, you built a ray gun?
- It's not a ray gun,
it's a weapon that can deliver
megadoses of photon radiation...
the same kind of radiation
typically administered
to cancer patients.
- What exactly does it do?
- My theory is that these
photons could be strong enough
to destroy Ramsey's
sentient infection.
If I get close enough
to blast him,
he should revert back
to his human form.
He'd still have HLH,
but at least he wouldn't be a
gooey zombie overlord anymore.
- What about everyone else
that was infected?
Would they be cured?
- Yes.
They'd lose the goo,
they'd go back to normal.
But since Ramsey's the only one
that can create
more Blood Brothers,
I say we hit at him first.
Then Dark Flash.
- And you've tested this?
- Well, I haven't even
finished building it,
so no, no I haven't tested it.
- So let me get this straight.
You wanna shoot radiation
at my husband
out of some crazy
powerful device
that you've never tested?
- Iris, this is
the only plan we have.
- This could kill Barry, Cisco.
- Anyone there?
Please help me.
The city's being overrun.
I'm using
a police officer's radio.
He's turning
into some kind of monster.
His eyes are black.
[radio clicks]
- Ramsey's spreading
his infection.
- That's why he took down
communication citywide.
Caitlin once said
Ramsey's infection samples
indicate he needs his victims
to be afraid
before he attacks them.
- [gasps]
[otherworldly reverberations]
[tense musical spike]
- Hey,
is your Internet working?
[light bulb crackles]
What's with the lights?
- I don't know.
- Who's that?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [snarls]
- Get inside, get inside.
- He looks like he has rabies
or something.
- Mitch Romero...
you remember the mobster
that Ramsey turned
into a Blood Brother?
Well, Joe said that
he looked just like that.
- [snarls]
- [whispering] Come here.
- What...what do we do?
- We gotta get
out of this building.
[all panicking]
[zombies snarling]
- Remember, these people
are innocent!
Nonlethal force only!
[dramatic music]
[snarling and grunting]
♪ ♪
- Your efforts are in vain,
Captain.
I'm going
to transform this city by dawn,
and you can't stop me.
[pistol hammer clicks]
[civilians shouting]
Stand down, Dr. Rosso.
Rosso is my human name
and he has human blood.
My name is Bloodwork now,
and I am not alone.
- [gasps]
- [snarls]
♪ ♪
- Flash, this isn't you.
Whatever happened
to you, we will fix it.
- [distorted] It's humanity
that needs fixing.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Why would he
let that happen?
- 'Cause this isn't Barry
anymore.
- [snarls quietly]
- Ramsey, whatever the hell
your plan is, we will stop you.
- I've already done it.
I've cured death...
but not for you.
- [snarls]
- Continue our mission.
Kill them.
♪ ♪
[all snarling]
[power grid thrums and clicks]
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply]
I'm coming for you.
- You seek the truth.
[suspenseful choral music]
♪ ♪
- Novu.
- If you wish to know all,
show your allegiance
and all will be revealed.
- Yeah, that sounds great.
Oh, wait.
No, I don't barter
with false gods!
- Bow down to me and
all you desire shall be yours.
- Let me in.
Let me in!
- Bow down to me!
- [chuckles]
Planet after planet...
Earth after Earth
I've tracked you, Novu,
and you think
some paltry mind games
and a little rock wall
is gonna stop me.
You've got
another think coming.
I'm coming for you.
And you can't stop me!
[low rumbling]
[electricity crackles]
Hmm.
What's this now?
Punishment from an angry god...
or simply faulty wiring?
I say, let there be light.
- [snarls]
[phone chimes negatively]
- Still nothing.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [whimpers and sniffles]
- Hey, girl. We got this.
We just need to get
to the end of the hallway
and into the stairwell.
- I'm sorry.
[inhales deeply]
I'm so sorry. I can't.
I can't even move.
- What's wrong?
- Fear.
There's so much fear,
and I can feel it,
and I think there must be
other people in the building.
- The place is empty.
No one else
is working this late.
- It's everywhere and I can't...
- Okay.
- I can't stop it and
I can't keep it out of my head.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I believe you. I believe you.
Cisco told me that Ramsey
needs his victims to be scared
for the infection to take.
Something about
a fear-related amino acid.
What if you're feeling
what those zombies are feeling?
The fear inside them?
- Whatever it is,
just make it stop.
- Cecile, don't you get it?
You're a fricking
zombie detector.
You're our way out of here.
♪ ♪
- We've got another 207
downtown.
All available units respond.
[static blasts]
- 207 is an abduction.
There's been ten of those
in the last five minutes.
- Iris, I know
you're listening.
I need to see you.
Meet me where
our life together began...
where you said yes.
[radio clicks]
- Iris...
that's not him.
That might sound like Barry,
it might even look like him,
but that is Dark Flash.
- You don't know that.
What if Barry
is still alive in there?
- What if it's a trap,
all right?
We don't even have comms.
It's too risky.
- Listen to me.
I just need
to look him in his eyes.
- If the Emitter doesn't work
on Ramsey,
I get to come back
and try something else.
But if you go out there
and that's not Barry,
you could get infected
or worse.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
Please.
- "In sickness and in health."
- Iris.
Iris!
[breach whooshes]
[suspenseful music]
- Barry?
- [voice reverberating]
Yes, Iris?
It's me.
[Ramsey's voice]
And so much more.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Come on.
♪ ♪
- Ramsey.
- Neat little trick, huh?
Don't you see now, Iris?
- Come on.
♪ ♪
- My control over
my Blood Brothers and Sisters
is absolute.
As more cured souls
accept my lifeblood,
they become extensions
of one collective body...
mine.
- You asked me here.
Why?
- To offer you a chance.
Barry would want you to follow
him down this path he chose.
- No.
- The path of life.
- You aren't saving lives,
Ramsey.
You're destroying
what makes one beautiful.
- [snarls quietly]
- Barry...
I know you can hear me and
you can hear what I tell you...
that I love you.
And after everything that we've
been through together...
♪ ♪
I know that this
is not how our story ends.
Come home to me.
♪ ♪
- Why would Barry
come home to you?
You accepted his death
in Crisis as inevitable.
What kind of wife
is willing to bury her husband?
- Iris, get out of there.
♪ ♪
- [snarls quietly]
- [breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
- In good time.
This is not over.
Trust me, Iris.
[whooshes]
♪ ♪
[breach whooshes]
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- No.
- I piggybacked the audio
off the extrapolator.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
- I have to try again.
- Iris...
he almost killed you.
- We can't just give up, Cisco.
- We're not.
But if we're gonna take down
Bloodwork and Dark Flash,
we need to do it
with the Photon Emitter.
- You haven't even tested
that thing.
- We have no time.
Maybe you don't remember,
but we actually have been
preparing for this for weeks.
- No, we've been preparing
for the Flash to die
trying to save this world,
not...not helping to destroy it.
- It doesn't matter!
We were gonna lose him anyway!
♪ ♪
This is the moment
he prepared us for.
♪ ♪
- We still have four hours.
That is 240 minutes,
and I am not letting Ramsey
take a single one
of those from me.
I am not giving up on Barry.
He's my husband.
- He was.
And he was my best friend.
And no one's
giving up on anybody
because there
is nothing left to give up on.
Iris, he's gone.
♪ ♪
He was always gonna leave us.
And whether or not
the Emitter works,
it's not gonna change that.
♪ ♪
The Emitter's almost ready.
And when it is
I'm gonna use it on Bloodwork,
and I'm gonna use it
on Dark Flash.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- [screams]
[groans]
- Joe!
[zombies snarling]
♪ ♪
[vapors boom and echo]
[epic music]
♪ ♪
- Just lie still.
- [snarls]
- [bellows courageously]
Get the hell away from her.
- Allegra!
- Frost!
Is Captain West okay?
- No.
We need
to get the hell out of here.
[breach whooshes]
Let's go.
[tense music]
- [snarls]
♪ ♪
[distant siren wailing]
- Get right back.
Get right back.
♪ ♪
- [snarls]
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
- [snarls]
- [breathes heavily]
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[eerie ringing]
- [snarling]
♪ ♪
[growls]
[music starts]
♪ ♪
- [snarling]
[stapler clatters loudly]
[snarls]
[grunts]
- Come on!
Oh, wait!
[snarling]
[crunchy thud]
♪ ♪
[snarling]
Oh, my God.
Help me!
- Oh, my God.
- [shouts]
[heavy breathing]
[zombies smashing against door]
That's not gonna hold
for very long.
- S.T.A.R. Labs
is still ten blocks away.
- Ten blocks?
Ten blocks?
We can do it.
Let's go.
- Rise, my Blood Brother
and Blood Sister.
You are cured.
Now you will never die.
[raspy breathing]
[dramatic music]
- [shouts]
- [grunts and groans]
♪ ♪
[distorted groaning]
- Feel the burn, Bloodwork!
[liquid gurgling]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[sparks crackle]
[breathes heavily]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [growls]
Is that all you've got,
Mr. Ramon?
Too bad.
- Cisco!
- My lifeblood is a gift.
Are you ready to receive it?
♪ ♪
No.
You have another purpose
to serve.
The reckoning is near.
My army is almost ready
to march on S.T.A.R. Labs.
- What the hell do you want
with S.T.A.R. Labs?
- [chuckles darkly]
[imitates explosion]
♪ ♪
- The Particle Accelerator.
- The very tech you helped
to create
will be the vessel
carrying my glorious cure.
Soon all of Central City
will be granted eternal life,
and I choose you, Mr. Ramon,
to be my messenger.
Go, tell your team
the great S.T.A.R. Labs
Particle Accelerator
is ready to fulfill
its true purpose.
Salvation is nigh.
- An ass-whipping
is nigh, pal...
[chuckles]
And you're gonna lose, Ramsey.
You're gonna lose.
- Plucky right up
until the end.
I knew I picked the right guy.
Iris!
If you're listening...
I'm coming home.
♪ ♪
- Look at this.
[computer chimes]
Ramsey wasn't lying.
Barry hacked
the Particle Accelerator.
- He was getting it ready
for Bloodwork.
That's why he was pretending
to be Barry.
But why?
- If Ramsey drops
even just a tiny amount
of his blood into the core
and it explodes,
the infectious cells
will aerosolize
and it would affect
all of Central City in seconds.
All you'd have to do
is take a breath.
[breach whooshes]
- [groans]
- Dad!
[dramatic music]
Do something, Frost.
- I can't...
I can't handle this.
[ice crackles]
♪ ♪
- There's a lot of blood loss.
Looks like a nicked spleen.
Frost, I don't have
the equipment I need
to close up this complicated
of a wound,
but you can
with your ice powers.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Frost, come on.
- After Ralph and Barry?
- Frost, take control.
- How?
- Let yourself feel the fear,
count to three,
and do it anyway,
because that's what heroes do.
One, two...
♪ ♪
- Three.
[icy vapors whoosh]
- [snarls]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[shovel blade clangs]
[snarls]
[high-pitched whir]
- [chuckles]
You like that?
[shouting]
[laughs]
- [snarls pitifully]
- [laughs]
[high-pitched whir]
[whirring stops]
♪ ♪
[snarl echoes]
[multitude of snarls echoing]
♪ ♪
[force field humming]
[tranquil ambient music]
- For the record,
both our plans failed.
- Yeah.
- [sighs]
- I just went in one direction
while you went in the other,
instead of figuring out
a plan together.
- Yeah.
- I should've made that happen.
I should've led the team.
- It's not too late.
Barry chose you for a reason.
Don't doubt yourself, Cisco.
- [chuckles quietly]
- What?
- Something Ramsey said...
"I knew
I picked the right guy."
Barry said those words.
♪ ♪
Barry said
those exact words to me
when he made me team leader.
Ramsey could've infected me.
He could've killed me.
But he didn't...
instead he just did
a complete 180 for no reason.
[dramatic music]
- There's something else.
Ramsey said, "I'm coming home."
I begged Barry to come home
the last time I saw him,
but I didn't think
that I was getting through.
- Iris...
what if that was Barry?
What if you were right
and he's still alive
inside Dark Flash?
- Then he could be trying
to tell us what to do.
- We gotta take down Bloodwork.
[computer chimes]
Someone's at the barrier.
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- I have arrived
to fulfill my destiny.
And yes, my army is coming.
- Iris...
Cisco...
let the light in.
♪ ♪
- I think I just figured out
Barry's plan...
And he just told us
the next step.
- We need
to lower the defenses.
Let them in.
[suspenseful music]
- It's time to put an end
to death once and for all.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[snarling]
- Find the humans who rejected
my lifeblood and kill them.
[snarling]
♪ ♪
- You want me to do what?
- Barry's plan is
to let the light in.
It isn't for Ramsey to spread
his infection to the city,
it's for you
to spread the antidote...
with one hell of a UV blast.
- But I can't do that.
- Don't worry, I've done
all the calculations.
We'll walk you through
the whole thing.
Just get to the pipeline now.
♪ ♪
[keyboard clicks]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Good evening, Team Flash.
I have tried repeatedly
to bestow upon you
eternal life,
yet you've refused.
So now, instead of continuing
to offer you the gift of life,
I've ordered my Blood Brothers
to take it from you.
Now as you run
for your worthless lives,
do keep in mind
that your leader, Flash,
belongs to me now.
I have his access codes,
his handprint, his knowledge.
My objective will be achieved.
[tense music builds]
♪ ♪
[computer chimes]
[servos whirring]
♪ ♪
[servos whir]
- Bring me Iris and Cisco.
[whooshes]
[both gasp and grunt]
- [snarls]
- [gasps and chokes]
♪ ♪
- I want you to know
the scope of your failure.
- [gasps]
- [coughs]
- My lifeblood
is circling the accelerator.
♪ ♪
And when
it gathers enough speed,
it'll collide
with the energy inside
and the resulting collision
will cure this city...
and you.
- [hoarsely]
Barry...
[wheezes]
I trust you.
- [breathes heavily]
- [struggles to breathe]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing?
Kill her.
- [gasps]
- [snarling quietly]
- [gasping]
♪ ♪
Barry...
[tense music]
[coughs]
- We are one, you and I.
♪ ♪
It's pointless to fight it.
I know you want
to execute my will.
I can feel it inside you,
Flash.
- [snarls resolutely]
♪ ♪
- Much better.
[pulse rifle blasts]
- [distorted groaning]
♪ ♪
[zombies snarling]
- Get ready to run.
- What are you gonna do?
- What I do.
- [distorted groaning]
- Barry?
- [groans]
- We only have
about five rotations left
before collision.
- How long is each rotation?
- A few seconds if we're lucky.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[alarms chiming]
- Allegra,
where the hell are you?
- Right here!
♪ ♪
- When I open this door,
you need to hit these particles
with all the UV rays
you've got.
♪ ♪
- [groaning]
- You got this.
Don't hold back.
♪ ♪
- One rotation left!
[alarms chiming]
Now!
- [shouts]
♪ ♪
[energies combine and explode]
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
[disoriented groaning]
♪ ♪
[snarling]
[energies whoosh]
♪ ♪
[snarling and grunting]
[energies whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
Barry.
♪ ♪
[tense musical spike]
[gasps]
Hey.
[calming orchestral music]
- It's me.
- [gasps in relief]
♪ ♪
- Hey, uh...
where's the scary guy
who tried to kill us all?
♪ ♪
- He won't get far.
[whooshes]
- I won't be denied!
- Okay, just stay here.
[epic music]
You can't control me anymore.
and I'm not gonna let you
hurt anybody else.
♪ ♪
- For the last time...
I am trying to save everyone!
Don't you understand?
You're not the hero here, I am!
[goo gurgling]
[growls deeply]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[roars]
[pained snarl]
♪ ♪
[meaty thuds]
[wheezy growl]
[calm music]
- Cisco, you with me?
- Always.
Babel's been lifted,
comms are up.
We are back.
- What do we have
that can hold Ramsey?
- After Mitch Romero, we know
a pipeline cell won't work.
- The M.A.C.
It contained Chester's
black hole energy.
- So Ramsey should be
a walk in the park.
- [snarls]
- [grunts and groans]
- Flash, you okay?
[tense music]
[glass shatters]
♪ ♪
- Stay down!
[goo thuds]
♪ ♪
Any last words
before your death?
- I just want
to enjoy the time I have left.
- I felt the same way.
[music softens]
My beautiful boy...
Ramsey.
[goo gurgling]
[suspenseful music]
What have you done?
♪ ♪
My son...
I've missed you so much.
♪ ♪
- Mom?
How is this even possible?
- I brought her.
You entered my mind
to bring out that doubt
that was hidden inside.
I left you infect me
so I could return the favor
and bring out yours.
- Impossible.
I have no doubt.
Only conviction.
- Ramsey.
I would give anything to have
just one more day with my mom.
You have that chance right now.
Listen to her.
♪ ♪
- He's right.
You were born to heal.
But you've become
an angel of destruction.
- No.
This isn't happening.
This isn't real.
- My dear son...
♪ ♪
You wanted so desperately
to save me.
Now let me save you
from yourself.
- I just wanted
to help them all.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- [grunts]
[whooshes]
- No!
Perhaps she was wrong.
I was born to save the world!
♪ ♪
And I still can.
[force field zaps]
♪ ♪
Can you hear me, Flash?
I was chosen to save the world.
And when I escape these chains,
I will complete my destiny.
And you will all
accept my cure.
- Containment protocol's
holding.
It worked.
- We did it.
We beat him.
[dramatic music]
- Now it's time
for our next fight.
♪ ♪
- Lyla says Ramsey
is officially
in A.R.G.U.S. custody.
- And I called
the local hospitals...
Ramsey's infection doesn't seem
to have
any long-lasting effects.
- So everyone's gonna be okay?
- Everyone except Ramsay.
Frost ran some tests,
and it looks like
his condition is, um...
pretty permanent.
- Joe's resting in the lounge,
and I think
I am gonna go check on him.
[peaceful music]
- [takes deep breath]
What was it like
being Dark Flash?
♪ ♪
- I knew what was happening,
but I couldn't stop it.
Honestly,
it took everything I had
just to keep
from hurting you guys.
But as the night went on,
I could tell I was...
I was getting to him.
I could feel him
doubting himself more and more.
Thank you for what you did.
You saved the city.
- Right back at ya.
But you should really
thank Frost.
She got me there.
She's badass.
- Yeah, she is.
- Speaking of,
where is the Ice Queen?
- Caity, I know
the last couple of days
have been a roller-coaster,
but I just wanted to say thanks
for believing in me
even though
I didn't believe in myself.
- No thanks needed.
And for it's worth,
I'm really proud
of how you've grown
these last few months.
I can't wait
to see where you go next.
- Me, too.
But for tonight,
I think you should take over.
It's only right
that you're with the team
for whatever Crisis
is about to bring.
♪ ♪
[watch ticking]
- Guys?
[inhales deeply]
Sitting in silence really
isn't how I want to spend
the next few minutes.
[chuckles]
Joe...
when you gave me your watch,
that meant...
that meant the world to me.
I wanna give you mine.
So I know wherever I go,
part of me is with you.
- I love you for that.
But you're not
going anywhere yet.
So you hold on to it.
- All right.
- H.R. Wells told me once...
"Barry Allen's superpower
isn't speed.
"It's hope.
It's hope, and that kid has
an endless reservoir of it."
I didn't know how right he was
until I really got
to know you, Barry.
Whatever is about to happen,
this world's a better place
for having you in it.
- You know, when you
first came into my life,
I had lost faith
in just about everything.
[pensive music]
You saved my life, Barry.
♪ ♪
- God, I remember
the old days.
- [laughs]
- No doppelgangers,
no Flashpoint, no time travel.
It was just us
against the bad guys.
♪ ♪
I miss that.
- I don't know,
I kinda like time travel.
When you were stuck
in the Speed Force,
I would have Cisco
vibe me to the Waterfront
so I could watch
our first kiss.
You know, the one you had
to erase from the timeline
to save the world.
- Why'd you do that?
- I don't know.
I guess when you're filled
with sadness,
happy thoughts are what
get you through the day.
♪ ♪
And what's happier than getting
half your first kiss
with the love of your life
other than getting
to do it twice?
♪ ♪
Our love story never ends,
Barry.
Not even with Crisis.
- Iris, it's inevitable.
- Maybe.
But whether you vanish or...
or worse, I am gonna
be there with you.
I'm gonna be right there
with you to the very end, okay?
Because the only thing
more inevitable than Crisis
is us.
[inspiring music]
- Iris is right.
Whatever's in store for us,
it can't change what we mean
to each other.
♪ ♪
Can't erase
what's in our hearts.
As long as we hold on
to that...
we've beaten Crisis
before it even begins.
[music fades]
[watch ticking]
[rumbling sounds]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- For so many years,
I've traveled across worlds,
across the multiverse,
to do one thing.
Kill you.
And now here...
you saved my life.
- Submit
and begin your life anew.
- Show me.
- The knowledge is within you.
[wondrous music]
- [exhales deeply]
♪ ♪
[glyph tinkling]
[energy hums]
[gasps]
[yells]
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪