[somber music playing]
[imperceptible]
[alarm sounding]
- [tires screeching]
- [police siren wailing]
[dramatic music playing]
[female police officer] Freeze!
Put your hands in the air!
[grunts]
[Blockbuster in robotic voice]
Well, hello, officers.
Now, that was fun.
[sighs wearily]
I'm so not in the mood for this.
[breathing heavily]
All right, big guy.
I'm gonna give you
one chance to stand down.
I'll give you one chance to beat it.
Chester, what's he wearing?
[Barry] Chester.
Sorry. Just give me a second to, uh...
Okay. Okay, I got it.
The armor matches the description
of an exo suit stolen from Ivo Labs.
It's charged by amplifying
the wearer's biochemistry.
So everything from his movements
to even his emotions...
Are fuel that makes him stronger.
You should have run away
when you had the chance, Flash.
Now, this has to happen.
[grunts]
- [ground rumbling]
- [Cecile gasps]
[ground cracking, rumbling]
- [windows shattering]
- [people screaming]
There's a lot of people in there.
[Chester] Okay, Flash.
He just compromised
two steel girders in that substructure.
That building's gonna collapse.
Allegra, Cecile,
I'm gonna use my lightning
to weld those girders back together.
Take this guy down.
Okay, Let's do a classic
corral and contain.
Allegra, charge up
and hit him with a UV burst.
- Hey, snow pants. Over here.
- [powers charging up]
And then, Frost, you swoop in...
[dramatic music playing]
[car explodes]
Allegra!
The blast knocked her out,
but she's still breathing.
[hesitates] I am so sorry.
[Cecile] Chester,
I need you to focus.
You've got to help me figure out
how I'm going to stop this guy.
Your friend should learn how to aim.
If you can try to calm his emotions,
that could depower the suit.
- [breathes deeply]
- [powers whooshing]
You trying to mess with my head?
[screaming]
[gasps]
What just happened?
[voice shaking]
It's all of my grief from Frost,
[breathing heavily]
and all the panic inside the building.
[crying] I can't take it,
it's overloading me.
I can't use my powers.
Pathetic. Worst heroes ever.
[breath trembling] Allegra. Allegra.
[softly] Hey, hey.
You guys okay?
Yeah.
Chester, where'd he go?
I don't know. He just vanished.
[suspenseful music playing]
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
[device beeping]
[inhales sharply]
The CCC tip line still has nothing
on Mark Desmond, aka Blockbuster.
Keep digging, please.
Chester says his suit has some kind
of cloaking tech we can't track,
which means... [sighs]
we're not going to see him again.
Until he attacks.
And when he does?
[softly] Iris, we can't go
back out there like this.
I mean, we should have
easily stopped Desmond,
but Allegra and Cecile
were almost killed.
We're all still pretty
messed up about Frost.
I think with any normal job,
we would take time off to grieve.
- But with Team Flash...
- This isn't a normal job.
[Barry breathes deeply]
Iris, how am I supposed to tell people
who just lost a family member,
they need to find a way to mourn
and still get the job done?
I don't know.
But if there is anyone
who can find the right words
to inspire us right now, it's you.
Thanks for taking the time
for this meeting, guys.
Yeah. We realize it's a crazy time
with everything going on.
[Cecile] Of course.
Yeah. We need to be together.
Now, more than ever.
Speaking of, where's Caitlin?
[Barry] I didn't want to bother her.
I think she's preparing
for the funeral tomorrow.
Maybe we should do the same thing.
[sighs]
Look, while your satellite
is looking for Desmond,
Kramer put out an APB
and she's got a unit
placed at every bank in town.
And luckily, we have the time
to take a break.
In a perfect world, it would be great
to take some time off.
God knows we all need it.
But at any moment,
we could face something worse.
And, whether we like it or not,
we're this city's first line of defense.
We all saw what happened out there.
Yeah, if it had been
Bloodwork or Despero...
You know, Frost is gone.
And we all need to mourn her.
But we also need to find a way
to protect this city.
I didn't realize
we were having a team meeting.
We figured you might need
some alone time.
It's fine.
I haven't been sleeping very much,
so I could use the distraction.
Are you sure? I know
you must be dealing with a lot,
and I know how hard it can be
to organize a funeral.
Actually, my mom is handling
all the arrangements.
Okay. I mean, if that's what you want,
but we're all happy to pitch in.
Like I said, my mom's got it covered.
But if you've got a problem with that,
feel free to give her a call.
Offer your help.
'Cause I'm not going
to any damn funeral.
[somber music continues playing]
- Caitlin.
- Barr.
Give her some space.
Dad, she's hurting.
Baby girl, I know. We all are.
But like Barry said,
we just lost a family member,
and that pain will keep us
from protecting those in need.
It will cloud everything we do
until we face it,
and heal.
Yeah, but how are we
supposed to do that?
By honoring Frost.
Look, I just...
took watercolor classes
at the community center
because Frost made me promise
that I would try to
express myself through art.
And I got to admit,
when I saw the first canvas...
[chuckles softly]
[shakily] I felt Frost
smiling down on me.
And we all have to find our own ways
to honor her.
'Cause it is the only way,
we are going to heal as a family.
There's still zero hits
on the tip line about Blockbuster.
It's already tough
knowing that people almost died
because we weren't ready to face him.
But knowing that he could reappear
at any moment,
it makes what we're going through
that much harder.
I know.
Which reminds me,
I think I've decided how I'm going to
take Joe's advice and honor Frost.
After her court battle last year,
wrongly imprisoned metas?
That became a cause
really close to her heart.
So, effective immediately,
I am going to dedicate
25% of my caseload
to pro bono work in her honor.
Frost would love that.
Yeah?
[sighs] I'm going to write
a special obituary for her on CCC.
That's a great idea.
Yeah, but every time
I sit down to write it, I can't.
Because...
I mean, to write about her
in any meaningful way,
like how she died
saving her sister, I...
You risk exposing yourself
as a member of Team Flash.
Yeah.
But this is my job, so,
why can't I push through?
Hey, Aariz.
When you interviewed last year,
you mentioned writing obits once.
[Aariz] For Stars and Stripes.
When I was on active duty
with the Army in Afghanistan,
sometimes I'd help write obits
for soldiers who died
on classified missions
or had no family.
If I wasn't privy to all the details,
I'd find other ways
to honor their memory.
That's amazing.
Do you think that you could
take over Frost's obit
for tonight's headline?
I always admired how she handled
those ridiculous charges against her.
I could have it ready in, say, an hour.
Yeah, that would be great.
- Thank you.
- [Aariz] You got it.
[softly] Hey, Iris.
Honey, are you sure you want
to hand over something so personal
to somebody who never even met Frost?
Well, I think an objective point of view
is exactly what I'm missing.
[Iris West] So, does it do her justice?
Well... [sighs]
You think Aariz did a terrible job?
It's well written
and factually accurate,
but it feels cold.
Like it was written by someone
who didn't know Frost.
But that's not why I wanted to talk.
I could have read this over email.
I wanted to see how you're doing.
[exhales sharply]
I feel the same way.
[breathes deeply]
Iris,
why didn't you write this?
I mean, you've known Frost
longer than I have.
I guess, at first,
I felt like if I wrote it,
I wouldn't be able to say everything
that I wanted to say.
But the more I think about it,
the more I realize that...
I don't know what to say. [chuckles]
Carla, I may have known Frost longer,
but I didn't...
get to know her.
And now you're angry at yourself
for lost opportunities,
because you thought you had
all the time in the world.
[sighs] I felt the same way being
estranged from Caitlin for so long.
And then I almost made the same mistake
when Frost came around, but...
[chuckles softly]
Luckily for me, she didn't let me.
[clicks tongue]
And in the end,
I got to know her just a bit...
and I'm... I'm better for it.
So, what do I do now? [chuckles]
[Dr. Tannhauser] Well, here's one thing
I do know.
Frost wouldn't care about some obituary
that sung her praises.
She didn't give a damn
what people thought.
She just wanted to protect them.
That was her legacy.
[Dr. Tannhauser whispers] Yeah.
Thank you, Carla. [sniffles]
Yeah.
- I think I know what to do now.
- [softly] Okay.
[sucks teeth]
[softly] Thanks.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- [softly] Yeah.
Oh, excuse me.
Could I get that iced drink? The Frost.
Sure, but it's actually called
Killer Frost.
[sighs]
Well, it shouldn't be.
Never mind. Thanks.
[sighs wearily]
Welcome to Citizentopia,
where you, the citizens of Central City,
share your stories.
I am here today
to talk about a fallen hero.
Someone who was often misunderstood.
A woman that you all know as...
[inhales deeply]
Killer Frost.
But to the people who really knew her,
she was no killer.
Frost saved lives
and she changed them for the better.
And I am here with two people
who are proof of that.
Kamiko, Jamal, thank you for joining us.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Sure.
- Thanks for having us.
So, I understand that you both
had a unique encounter with Frost?
It was during Bloodwork's attack
on the city
and, uh, we were in the subway.
It was just completely overrun
by his blood brothers.
I was so scared.
[Kamiko] We all were.
It was a bunch of strangers trapped,
while those things
picked us off one by one.
Until Frost showed up.
Seeing her courage in court,
I knew I was on
the wrong side of the bench.
So, when she was released,
I reached out,
asking for forgiveness.
She caught me right in the middle of it.
But she didn't turn me in.
[Kamiko] It was amazing.
Frost froze those blood brothers
and helped us escape.
We owe her our lives.
And what did Frost say?
[woman] That I did my job.
But maybe I should get a better one.
[chuckles]
[man chuckles]
Man, I was a tagger.
If it wasn't for Frost,
I'd be in jail right now.
Instead, I got my first
gallery exhibit next week.
So, the next day,
I quit the State Prosecutor's Office.
Now I'm defending metas in Star City.
If it wasn't for Frost, we... [chuckles]
would have never gotten married.
[Kamiko] So, wherever you are, Frost,
thank you.
[exhales sharply]
There must be one perfect thing
to do to honor Frost.
Just because Joe handed out
some greeting card advice
doesn't mean it's the right thing to do.
I don't know.
It sounded pretty on point to me.
How can one thing honor someone
as amazing as Frost?
[scoffs]
Barry told us about
the eternal flame for Oliver Queen.
[chuckles]
What if we made, like,
a Frost-ified version?
Yeah, yeah,
like if I took her superhero costume
and I put it in a glass case
with cryo coolers,
so that it could create
a self-sustained blizzard.
So, it'd stay frozen forever.
You mean a snow globe?
[playful music]
You know, it'd help if
I wasn't the only one
coming up with good ideas.
Passive aggressive, much?
No, no, not passive...
Passive aggressive
is getting Hirschfield's
to put hummus on our sandwiches.
Oh, wow. I didn't see you
getting butt-hurt over a sandwich
on my bingo card today.
Also, you love hummus.
I do. I do.
Hummus is wonderful,
but it's not a condiment.
Ketchup, is a condiment.
Mustard, also a condiment.
Hummus is like a side dish.
No, no. Hummus is a dip.
Easy, Condiment King.
I don't need you
Runk-splaining hummus to me.
I don't need you being so cavalier
with our sandwiches.
Don't worry, because I am never
bringing you lunch ever again.
- [scoffs]
- [air whooshing]
[gasps]
[panting] Sorry. Sorry.
Do you guys know
where the Arctic parkas are?
The cozy ones?
Yeah.
Starchives.
[softly] Right. Thank you.
[breathing heavily] Gotta run.
- [air whooshing]
- Ah!
- [cell phone buzzing]
- [Allegra sighs]
[inhales sharply]
CCC tip app's blowing up.
Something crazy is happening
at O'Shaughnessy's.
Is Blockbuster here
to settle his late fees?
No, it's not Blockbuster,
but I have a feeling
we're going to wish it was.
[upbeat music playing]
Aw, come on, man!
[music ends abruptly]
[rock music playing]
[yells] I am a party god!
[bottle shattering]
- [Mark grunting]
- We can never unsee this.
[bartender] Hey.
Is that your friend?
Uh...
Because that jerk just froze
half the bar.
[Allegra sighs] Sorry.
He's had a rough week.
- Here.
- [powers whooshing]
[exhales sharply]
I'm going on break.
If he's not gone by the time
I get back,
I'm having him arrested.
[chuckling] Hey, Chuckles, Garcia.
Come to join the party, have you?
Yeah?
[gruffly] Yeah, you did.
[Mark grunts]
- [utensils clinking]
- [glass breaking]
What's your poison?
You look like a Fuzzy Navel man.
- Coming right up.
- [glasses clinking]
Thanks, but I actually... [chuckles]
I actually don't drink.
Awesome. More for us.
[humming]
[people laughing]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Oh, big night out, huh?
Yeah, I've been there myself.
Sure.
Right now, love is all
cupcakes, puppies and monster trucks.
But just you wait until one of you dies
battling an interdimensional
death demon.
Oh, yeah.
Pain is coming.
[Chester] Okay, okay. Yeah, yeah.
Use your knees.
There you go. No, no. Oh...
You're okay, buddy.
All right. You guys want to rob
a tech facility or something?
It might quiet the voices.
This man needs Vibeaccinos,
lots of them. I could run to Jitters.
And leave me here with Chillbooze?
No way.
You know, you can't just shoot down
my ideas without offering another.
Fine, let's get some food in him.
Do they serve fries here or something?
[Chester] They must.
Ketchup bottle, see.
Mustard bottle.
[gasps] Ooh, look.
- [scoffs]
- No hummus bottle. Case closed.
- It's a condiment.
- [Chester] It's a dip.
- [Allegra] You're a dip.
- Well, call me hummus, then.
- Ugh! You are impossible.
- I can't believe...
Hey!
- What?
You two are really killing
my party's vibe.
All right?
Besides, you're not even fighting.
You're just doing what friends do,
baby.
Helping each other to see the world
in your own unique way.
That's what Frost did for me.
She shared her real self with me.
Only I was too dumb to share me
with her, and now it is too late.
But I'm glad
I got to see things her way.
[Mark snoring]
[powers whooshing]
[Chester groans]
Oh! All those muscles are heavy.
Sweet dreams, party god.
[both panting]
[both breathing heavily]
- AI, I am so sorry.
- Chuck, I'm sorry.
[both chuckle]
- I can't believe we're fighting.
- Over a dip.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, I miss her, too.
You know, even though Mark
might be drunk as a skunk,
he was right.
We are really good friends.
The best.
So if we listen to each other,
I'm sure we could find
that one perfect thing to honor Frost.
Yeah, actually,
now that I'm listening to you,
I think that your costume idea
was on to something.
- Yeah?
- Can I suggest one tweak, though?
- For sure. Yeah.
- Okay.
[triumphant music playing]
She told me she first felt
like a hero wearing this jacket.
Now that's how we'll remember her.
Always.
[triumphant music continues]
[wind blowing]
[winds howling]
[soft music playing]
[saw whirring]
[woman speaking French]
[air whooshing]
[crowd cheering]
[in English] Hold on to your badges.
We have a tight one.
CSI Barry Allen and reigning champ,
Officer Daisy Korber,
down to their last dog.
And...
[crowd cheering]
[buzzer sounds]
Allen wins it
in the upset of the century!
[officers laughing]
Thank you.
[exhales sharply] Fine.
But I want a rematch next year, Allen.
Sure.
[exhales]
[snorts]
[trilling]
[objects clattering]
[Barry] How long were you in there?
[Mark breathing heavily]
I was hoping you could tell me.
Hey, do you mind telling the contractors
to knock off all the hammering
or whatever that is?
Uh... That's not construction.
[gasps] Great.
Guess I overdid it with the bourbon.
[breathing heavily] And the tequila,
and the vodka.
[pills rattling]
[Mark] Hey, what's that?
Uh, satellite scans
looking for Blockbuster.
No sign of him yet, but... [inhales]
he'll show up sooner or later.
This team still isn't ready to face him.
Not all that. I'm talking about this.
Did you do all of these already?
How are you doing?
I never even got to tell her how I felt.
Did she ever tell you about the time
that she signed us up
for a couples' tag-team
wrestling tournament?
We crushed it, obviously.
But then she gave
our championship belts away
to some kids at the ramen joint
where we were celebrating.
Because it wasn't about winning.
It was about the experience.
- You really knew her well.
- I thought so. Yeah.
[exhales sharply]
I also thought finishing this list
would be a way to honor her memory.
But even with everything crossed off,
it still doesn't feel complete.
Look, man.
As wild and crazy
as her lust for adventure was,
what my Snowflake lived for
more than the thrills,
was taking care of the people she loved.
That's what she really wanted
to do with her life.
Hell, she was literally born
to be Caitlin's savior.
She never lost sight of that.
[chuckles silently]
I know how to honor Frost's memory.
[uplifting music playing]
But right now, it seems impossible.
What's impossible for the Flash?
'Cause I'm not going
to any damn funeral.
[Barry] Caitlin.
[melodic sad pop song playing]
[sighs deeply]
[knock on door]
[door creaks]
- I'm still not going.
- I... I just came to apologize.
And to listen.
I suppose it's no use shutting the door
on someone who can phase through it.
Look, Caitlin, um... [exhales sharply]
about yesterday morning in the lounge...
It's fine.
I know you were just trying to help.
You know, trying and knowing the right
words to say aren't the same thing.
And I'm sorry.
I said everything wrong.
We've both been through a lot
over the last couple of days,
so I think it's okay
to let ourselves off the hook.
But you don't have to worry about me.
I'm good, honest.
[suspenseful music playing]
You're still having trouble sleeping?
I've had a lot on my mind.
So, yes, I've had
a few sleepless nights,
but medically speaking,
I'm not in any danger.
So, thank you for coming.
Caitlin,
I know you'll regret
not going to your sister's funeral.
Unbelievable.
I mean, do you hear yourself right now?
This isn't even about me.
This is about you
and your need to be the hero.
I am not one of your missions, okay?
And not everything can just
be fixed with speed healing.
But I need to grieve Frost
in my own way.
So if you don't mind,
will you please leave?
[Barry sighs]
Look, Caitlin, I will leave you alone,
if that's what you really want,
but before I go,
just ask yourself one thing.
What would Frost want for you?
You knew her better than anybody.
Would she want you to pull away?
Would she want us to let you?
[Frost] But you have to promise me
something, all right?
You will never shut yourself off from me
or the rest of the team, all right?
She'd tell me to stop being an idiot.
Get off my ass and live my damn life.
Hmm.
That does sound like her.
You know,
Frost was the voice inside my head
before I even knew she had a name.
She was the one telling me to be brave.
To be strong when I felt weak.
That I was never as powerless
as others made me feel.
[sighs]
[crying] Barry, when Frost died,
her singing died, too.
Her laugh.
[sniffles]
[softly] That voice...
That voice that made me whole.
[sniffles]
[crying] So I can't go to the funeral...
because if I do,
if I see her in that casket...
[breath trembling]
I'll know that she's gone for good.
- [Caitlin sighs]
- What if that's not the case?
[softly] What do you mean?
Her voice is still inside you.
As long as that's true...
She's not really gone.
[Barry breathes deeply]
Joe suggested that we all... [exhales]
find a way to honor Frost.
It was pretty hard finding my answer.
But you?
You just have to listen to her.
So what's Frost saying
she wants you to do?
[solemn music playing]
[sighs gently]
Most of you know that I did not want
to be here today.
Not at first.
I was afraid that seeing her here
would make her death seem more real.
[inhales deeply]
And I was scared.
You see, Frost was always
the fearless Snow sister.
Like that time
she went swimming with sharks
and picked a fight with a shark.
Or when she was at Jitters
for their Slam Poetry open mic night,
and just grabbed the mic
and read a poem she'd scribbled
on a napkin five minutes before.
[sighs] See, Frost was always honest.
[crying] And the truth is...
[breath trembling]
I thought that if
I saw my sister laying here,
that I would have to say goodbye.
[sniffles]
But then...
a friend of mine reminded me that
that's not true.
That she lives on in all of us.
Not just in me.
In her selflessness...
[crying] her unique way
of seeing the world...
[breathes deeply]
[softly]...and her deep love
for her family and friends.
[inhales deeply]
So if we keep those parts of her
alive in us,
then she's not really gone.
And I can't think of a better way
to honor her memory.
I'll keep you alive, Frost.
I promise.
[somber music playing]
[lighthearted music playing]
[Joe] It normally works.
Dad, what were you thinking?
Bleach takes out stains
and the curtains were dirty. So...
[chuckling] I'm sorry, but no. No.
This whole retirement thing,
he's still real new at it.
Look, this is the cleanest spot
in the whole house,
and I would have done a whole lot more
if Frost hadn't taken
- my cleaning supplies for her collages.
- [all chuckling]
Oh, yeah. I still don't know
how she carried that stuff
while ice-bridging across town.
She didn't. People were finding sponges
and yellow gloves for miles.
Actually, I think Wild Dog uses
one of Joe's mops as a bo staff.
- [all laughing]
- Really?
This feels good.
Remembering Frost like this.
Your advice worked, Joe.
That had more to do with you
than with me.
It was a beautiful eulogy.
More than anything we did to
honor Frost, you helped us heal today.
Thanks for putting us back together.
I didn't make it easy on you guys.
So, thanks for telling me
what I needed to hear anyway.
- [devices beeping]
- [Joe] Ooh.
That Blockbuster jerk's back.
I'll have Kramer call C.C.P.D.
No way. This guy's ours.
Plus, we all wanted a rematch, right?
And this time, we're ready.
Barry?
Tell Kramer to warm a holding cell.
Let's go get this guy.
[whooshes]
I will tell the troops
to prepare an early headline.
- Hey.
- [door opens, closes]
Do you have somewhere to be, too?
Nope.
Because I'd love to hear
some more stories about Frost.
- I'd like that, too.
- I'm going to make us some coffee.
Perfect.
[sighing softly]
[dialing]
Hey. We need to talk.
- [whistling]
- Hey.
Hey, you know
it's rude to keep your guests waiting?
I got a bar I'm supposed to be
getting thrown out of right now.
Sorry. I thought I had time for one more
supply run before you got here.
Is that a genome sequencer?
- Yes.
- And did you steal it?
I borrowed it.
Whatever, Caitlin.
Game recognizes game.
Look, you called, I'm here.
What do you want?
Your help.
Oh.
Did you forget
to pay your electricity bill?
[thuds, groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay.
That's not too creepy or anything.
Caitlin, what is it that you want?
I'm going to bring Frost back.
And you're gonna help me.
[exhales sharply]
[staff member] So, what do you think?
[clicks tongue]
I think we just found
tomorrow's front page.
[gasps] Crushed it!
Uh... I mean, thank you.
I will interface with publishing and get
this out the door ASAP. [chuckles]
It's okay. Own it.
This is a great article.
You should be proud.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I still have a ton of work to do.
It's gonna be a late night.
Sure. [chuckles softly]
By the way, it's really good
to have you back from Coast City.
CCC Media was not the same without you.
You guys had Allegra.
I hear she did great filling in.
From who? [laughs]
I'm, uh... I'm gonna leave now.
[chuckles nervously]
But, hey, about
the Flash's latest takedown,
I know he worked with Frost,
but there have been reports
of him working with other people, too.
Only no one knows who they are.
Shouldn't we investigate them?
Hmm, um...
I will think about it.
[groans, clicks tongue]
I forgot my... phone.
Iris?
[suspenseful music playing]
Hmm.
[crackling]