So, we built a machine
powerful enough to big-bang
a new Speed Force into existence,
based solely on the teachings
of history's most evil speedster.
Are we sure we wanna hit this switch?
Do it.
Uh, what's happening?
It didn't work.
Guys, you in there?
Hey. Sorry to interrupt.
- Oh, um, how did the machine test go?
- Well, it didn't.
That's the problem.
How did Thawne manage to build
a Speed Force machine on his own
without a journal to guide him,
but all the brainpower in S.T.A.R. Labs
can't even get this thing to work?
It's like we built a 12-ton paperweight.
Okay, okay, but, hey, uh,
maybe getting out of here for a minute
might clear your heads.
I myself was on my way over to
The Citizen right now. Does anybody...
Barry, wanna come with me?
No. Look, every day
that the machine is off
is another day I can't
protect this city.
I have to keep working.
Barry, wait.
Are you sure you don't want to see Iris?
Can I tell her anything for you?
Tell her I miss her.
His speed has been draining nonstop.
Your plan was a success.
You've done an amazing job.
Is everything okay?
You seem...
distant.
Sorry, um...
I'd just like to know if you want us
to proceed with the next phase.
Yes.
Go join your brother and prepare,
because tonight,
I will finally have my liberation.
- Success is assured.
Come in.
- Hey, you busy?
- Hey, what's up?
I just wanted to...
You're here about me and Barry?
Yeah.
He's in a really bad place, Iris.
His heart is breaking.
He won't talk to anybody about it.
He promised me after he took Nora
to the future,
that would be the last time
that he made a decision
about our family without me.
But then he took my dad into WITSEC
and didn't even tell me.
I had to find out from Singh.
How do you get over that, Cecile?
Well...
I don't really know, Iris,
but I would think
the first step is wanting to.
What do you want?
I... I don't know.
Can you feel what I want?
Can you tell me?
You feel... sad.
Sad and concerned.
I think what Iris needs right now
is space
to focus on what's really important.
Right, uh...
It's important for me to take care
of myself right now, Cecile.
Okay, yeah, um...
Your husband wanted me to tell you
that he misses you.
Barr?
- Hey.
- There's something blocking the door.
Yeah, um...
I thought you were still
at the speed lab.
Uh...
- Hey, Barry...
- Hold on.
- Why can't I get inside my own house?
- Sorry. Hold on.
- Give me a sec, okay?
- Geez.
Cecile, I can explain.
What the hell is this?
Iris isn't Iris.
Okay, so then I thought, well,
obviously this can't be
an Iris doppelgänger from another Earth,
because doppelgängers
don't exist anymore,
because the multi-verse
doesn't exist anymore,
- because Crisis blew it all up, right?
- Uh-huh.
Exactly. So, if that's true,
who else do we know
that could be pretending to be Iris?
- I... But...
- Shapeshifters.
All right, so Everyman
was my first suspect.
And Cisco's reports show
that he is alive, post-Crisis.
Then, I remembered something
that Breacher said about Plastoids,
which made me realize...
there could be shapeshifting Martians
on this Earth now.
This... This fake Iris doesn't even
have to be from our planet.
But then, it hit me
that J'onn J'onzz would sense
if there was a Martian hidden among us,
so that was a dead end,
but it led me
to my biggest breakthrough yet.
Okay, Cecile.
The night that this all started,
Iris left to investigate a story.
I analyzed her phone's GPS, and it shows
that she went to McCulloch Tech.
Cecile, I think that something happened
to Iris that night.
Barry.
All of this, is this the reason
you've been avoiding Iris?
That's not Iris!
Okay, look, I didn't want to...
tell anyone else about this
until I gathered more evidence,
but now you know, so I...
What do you think?
Uh...
What do I think? What do I think?
I think... I think that this sounds...
I know how it sounds,
but look, we've seen crazier.
We've seen crazier.
And look at all the clues.
Okay, I mean, she speaks Italian,
all of a sudden.
She smashed a bottle
over some guy's head.
She made incredible pancakes.
Cecile, trust me.
Iris can't make pancakes.
All right? But the biggest clue was...
her throwing me out.
The real Iris would never
stop fighting for us.
Okay. Okay, uh...
Sweetie, do you think
that maybe, just maybe...
you're feeling a little scared?
You know, because your marriage
is going through a rough patch,
and maybe what you need to do
is just go see Iris.
That's not Ir... Cecile, look.
Do you know why
my Speed Gauge is still glowing red?
It is because the moment
that I stepped out of the loft,
I realized Iris, the real Iris, my wife,
she is somewhere else,
probably in danger.
And if that's true,
I need my speed back,
my lightning, all my powers,
if I'm gonna save her.
It's all I've thought about ever since.
No matter how insane this all sounds...
I know in my heart that the real Iris
is out there somewhere,
waiting for me to find her.
I won't let her down.
Polar bear's a little on-the-nose,
don't you think?
Well, it's not like the stores have
a "get well soon from
dual light-assassin attacks" card.
What'd you bring?
I got a mobile bio-lab,
so she can catch up on her work
while she recovers in bed.
Don't be jealous.
It's a scientist thing.
Come on, snowpoke. It's us.
It's ice-cold.
Caitlin.
Help me.
Since when is Caitlin the frosty one?
She's not.
Hang on, Caitlin. We're on the case.
I think I've come up with a new idea
to get us out of this place.
Stop! What are you doing?
Eva, think about it.
This is the only mirror
that you can control,
so there's gotta be something
different about it.
And until we can figure out what that
is, we're just working blind. Move.
So, to examine it, you want to smash it?
Yeah. I mean, we both know
that you can put it back together,
so let's just take this thing down,
dissect it piece-by-piece,
and learn what its secrets are.
Fine. You do what you wanna do.
I'm gonna go to my lab,
and work on a plan
that would actually help us.
Oh, my God.
Can you, uh, maybe hurry up?
You know, when Iris gave me a spare key,
it was to water her plants.
It wasn't to hack her computer.
It's not hacking Iris' computer
if it's not really Iris.
What are you even looking for, anyway?
Anything that might be suspicious
from the past few weeks.
- Bingo.
- What'd you find?
This photo.
It was deleted from Kamilla's camera,
but not before it was uploaded
to The Citizen's cloud server.
Do you see this text?
"Prismatic Filter."
What is that?
It's the science that we're gonna use
to test our imposter's identity.
Expose her for good.
That's better. Much more homey.
"Closer" is how I'd describe it.
Closer to our Mother.
It's time for our next move.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Are you?
Yes.
All that matters is Eva's will.
We follow orders and assure her success.
That's all I want.
We need to focus.
There's still one item Mother needs
to obtain for her liberation.
And it's the most dangerous yet.
Hey, I saw your text.
I got here as fast as I could.
What's the emergency?
You are, apparently.
What's going on?
You're not Iris. That's what.
And you're not leaving here
until you tell us who or what you are.
What the hell are you talking about?
And why are you pointing
that gauntlet at me?
This photo was taken on
Kamilla's camera.
You see the prismatic fragmentation?
Only your image is affected.
I think that the camera's filter
is revealing a dimensional shift,
showing us things in the picture
from another dimension.
Things that don't belong in ours.
Cecile, you actually believe this?
You seemed off in your office earlier,
and that photo...
That could have been anything!
A glitch in the camera tech.
Guys, this is insane.
This Prismatic Scanner is just a more
powerful version of the camera's filter.
If I'm wrong,
and you are from this dimension,
then when the prismatic wave hits you,
you'll look completely normal.
But if I'm right,
you're gonna look just like that photo.
And you're gonna tell us
where the real Iris is.
Barry, how could you do this?
For God's sake, I'm your wife.
Okay.
You wanna see who I really am?
Fine.
I'll show you.
No.
I have to know. I have to know.
Someone else must have heard
the good news, too,
because they sent you a gift.
I had it delivered.
Hello, Joseph.
This is your last chance, Joseph.
Threats are for real people, Eva.
Not phantoms.
Because that's what you are.
And no one saw you?
- Thank God you're safe.
- I'm not. Neither are you.
Black Hole isn't what we think.
Mirror.
Shh.
I know.
The truth hurts.
Barry.
I just want you to know
that if anything happens, I...
I forgive you.
What's happening?
Nothing.
Okay, okay. That's enough.
No, something...
something's wrong, all right?
Just... Just give it a minute.
Look...
I don't know how she did this,
but you have to see
that this isn't my wife.
No. You're not my husband, Barry.
And you wanna know
what the real test is?
The real Barry would have fought harder.
He would have fought to come back home.
A whole week went by,
and you never even tried.
You used to say
that I was your lightning rod.
Now let's see if you're still mine.
Guys...
I'm me.
I... I'm the real Barry.
- Hey.
- Wait! Nash, no.
Back up.
Cecile.
You believe me?
Yes. I do.
And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Barry. I'm... I'm sorry.
Nash! Cecile!
Don't listen to her. That's not Iris!
You know, you can stop playing this game
or rot in there, I don't care.
Either way, I'm gonna find my husband.
Ah, I should've noticed something.
I should've figured something out.
- I should've...
- No. No one's to blame.
He or it was pretty convincing.
If that's not Barry, then what is he?
He's like some mirror version
of himself.
Guys, Joseph Carver.
Wait. You think that...
this is related to Black Hole
and their reflective-chip technology?
Yeah.
- I don't know. That seems almost...
- No, it's possible.
I've seen the McCulloch tech up close,
and reflective-chip technology,
it's far-reaching, to say the least.
Okay. Well, um,
then this might be our best lead.
Why don't you see what you can find,
Nash?
I will regroup with Kamilla
and do some digging of our own.
Are you okay, Cecile?
Um...
Yeah. No, um...
Something just doesn't feel right.
Yeah. No, I understand, um...
But we're gonna get
to the bottom of this
and get the real Barry back. I promise.
Caitlin's body essentially
self-induced an ice coma
to force her to hibernate.
She's like a cold battery.
We just need to wake her up.
That's where you come in.
Since we don't have
any ionized conductive wiring,
you'll have to be the jumper cables.
Got it.
Okay.
Ralph, are you all right?
Is she good?
Cisco, is she okay? Did it work?
Ah...
Oh, thank Elsa.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
You scared us for
a minute, there.
Yeah.
Can you tell us what happened?
I was home alone,
and the wound from the light bullet
was getting worse.
I'm sure your run-in
with Sunshine didn't help.
Yeah. So I tried to ice-heal it,
and that's when the wound ruptured.
It must have been my immune system's
way of protecting me.
- Guys, I need help.
- You just tell us what you need.
I mean, who do we know who can help
with a light... ice wound?
There's only one person we can call.
My mother.
Here she comes.
Everything went according to plan?
Yeah. Yeah, we're fine.
Everything went as planned.
You guys go to the rendezvous.
I'll handle this
and I'll meet you there.
I've been watching Barry Allen.
He's planning on exposing you.
- Tell me what to do.
- Go. Meet him.
Leave the rest to me.
You're not Iris.
And you're not leaving here
until you tell us who or what you are.
Now, let's get what we came for.
One of the benefits
of being Chief of Police
is I can request prisoner interviews.
Even for press.
Well, if it isn't Kamilla Hwang,
Chief Singh...
and Iris West-Allen.
To what do I owe the honor?
If you help us,
we can get you out of there.
And why would I trust
the wife of the Flash?
Because I'm not Iris West-Allen.
I'm a reflection of her.
We're all reflections.
Faster, stronger than our human
counterparts whose faces we share.
And our only will
is to serve our Mother.
The real Iris would never
offer to release me.
Tell me more about your Mother.
Eva McCulloch. She was the sci...
I am a scientist.
I know who Eva McCulloch is.
But she disappeared years ago.
She's been trapped in another dimension,
a mirror one,
and she needs something from you.
You need my blood. How grand.
Even in here, fate continues to cast me
in the role of savior.
We just need one drop.
But you need to decide now.
I accept.
Release me, and you shall indeed
have my lifeblood.
However, this is no crude
meta-cell in Iron Heights.
How do you propose to disrupt
a bio-degenerative containment matrix
with triplicate backup protocols?
Mother has a theory.
I am the answer.
Wait.
You'll die.
Then it is Eva's will.
Code zero. Facility-wide power failure,
all levels. Check the cells.
We have 60 seconds
until the guards arrive...
You're almost human...
Maybe something more.
You follow your Master Eva's will,
but I see hesitation in your eyes.
You have a modicum of will.
Are you planning to trick me?
Tell me now!
What do you want?
- Only Eva's will.
- Lies!
Last chance.
What do you want?
To be alive.
And you're worthy of it.
Power restored.
Cell containment re-initialized.
What are you doing?
We had a plan. Don't you want to escape?
There are walls beyond these walls.
I was never gonna just walk out of here.
But there's more than one way
for me to be free.
Let's just call this... the long game.
Now, go.
I'll stay here and cover our tracks.
Now.
Run, Iris. Run!
Cecile?
I don't have all the facts...
and the ones I do have tell me
that you're not who you say you are.
But you are Barry.
I know it in my heart.
And I'm willing to bet my life on it.
Now go get Iris back.
Good work.
You'll apply Ramsey's blood
on your side of the mirror.
Once it is fully absorbed,
I will activate the R-CEM on my side.
Together, they will reconfigure
the molecular stability
of the dimensional barrier
that burns organic matter,
creating a safe passageway
between the two worlds.
Next time I speak to you,
I will be standing right next to you...
- liberated.
- Success is assured.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Where's my wife?
I'll ask you one more time.
What are you doing?
I saw everything.
You targeted me from the very beginning.
You suffered a fraction of my pain.
But in just a few, I will be liberated.
Barry is gonna stop you. We both will.
I used to think my love
gives me strength, too.
The mirror showed me the truth.
Let me do the same for you.
She says you're always
gonna be in her way...
and now you're too slow to stop me.
Whose way? Who is making you do this?
You should really
mind your surroundings.
Where's my wife?
She's all you can think about, huh?
What do you think about me, Barry?
All those days...
weeks.
It wasn't her, it was me.
Enjoying meals together.
Talking about our day.
- Sharing your bed.
- Shut up.
I am going to kill you.
Unlikely. I have been working
on this plan for half a decade.
This is my creation.
She is me and I am her.
What she feels, I feel...
and we cannot lose.
Do they feel what you feel for Carver?
What?
Do they still love him?
I don't love my husband.
I want to end him.
Then why do you still call him
your husband?
You are just as blinded
as you were before,
and he is going to trick you
in the exact same way.
- Stop talking.
- Because you still love him.
No, I don't!
Your brilliant mind couldn't figure out
that he didn't care about you.
Shut up!
How long did you sit here, Eva,
pining for rescue...
before you realized
that you had been abandoned?
I hate him! I want him to suffer!
Suffer! Suffer!
Suffer!
Iris?
Suffer! Suffer! Suffer!
Suffer!
Suffer.
Iris.
I won't fight you.
I won't fight you anymore.
You were made from Iris.
Part of her heart is inside you.
I've seen you be kind.
I've seen you laugh.
I know that wasn't all a lie.
You can be more than this.
Not Iris...
Yourself.
You have to want it.
No.
You have to choose it.
I choose me.
Go find Iris.
Go find her, Barry.
Go save Iris.
Go.
Hey...
Barry.
I feel alive.
Look what you made me do.
No! I'm sorry!
This didn't have to be like this, Flash.
You don't know what it's like in there.
I had to get out.
Iris.
Where...
Where is she?
She's still in the world
I left behind.
Along with the rest
of my insurance policy,
Chief Singh and your friend, Kamilla.
They're safe. How long is up to you.
So, what...
now you're gonna kill me?
There's no need for that.
You're wounded.
You lost your speed...
and your healing
is not what it used to be.
You're not much of a threat, are you?
You just stay out of my way, Flash,
and I'll stay out of yours.
I have unfinished business
to attend to...
and a whole world to liberate.
Thank God.
Iris, I...
I don't know if it's crazy to think
that you can hear me.
I guess right now,
I just need to believe it.
I miss you...
so much.
I know you probably can't hear me,
Barry, but...
being away from you
hurts more and more every day.
But I still have hope,
because I know that you are out there,
fighting to get me back home.
If you can hear me...
I guess I just need you to know that...
I love you.
And that love is constant.
Across dimensions...
Across time.
To the end of the world and back.
And if I know you...
I know you aren't just fighting
to find your own way home.
And I'm gonna find Kamilla,
and I'm gonna find Singh.
But most of all...
I'm gonna get you back.
I'm gonna find my way back to you.