Barry, we're in position
to attack. Where are you?
Sorry, I saw
a few things to take care of on the way.
So, just the banana?
Grandma got run over...
You okay?
Don't worry about that guy.
I just dropped him off at C.C.P.D.
Saved by Mr. Flashy himself!
Oh, I gotta give you a nice, big reward.
No, that's not necessary.
I can't accept your money.
But it's butterscotch.
Oh.
Thank you.
That's very sweet of you.
Hey, Flash,
we're getting hit hard.
We're not gonna make it.
Hold on, Chester.
I'm on my way.
Nineteen! Critical hit.
Urvakk the Cleric
attacks with the Sacred Flame.
Way stronger than my glaive.
Urvakk vanquishes the Lich,
saving our merry band of adventurers.
Radiant damage. Am I right?
What the hell is going on?
The Dungeon Kraken is awoken
by Thodris' fear and pounces...
...pinning the warrior to the ground.
There's no escape for him now.
Save him! Somebody save him!
Help me, Karash the Orc.
You're my last hope.
My turn?
Use your vorpal sword.
My what?
What do you do, Karash?
I tell the thing
to raise its little claws
and read its Miranda rights.
- Come on.
- Guys, this game is not for me.
- I'm sorry.
- All right, Joe.
- All right. Let's take a break.
- Don't be like that, Joe.
Let's take a break.
Refill our goblets.
Man, you were acting, brah.
Sorry.
No, I get it. I get it.
It is a little different
for family game night.
A little? It's got
a 600-page instruction booklet.
Well, I read the whole thing
in, like, two seconds.
"Well, I read that in,
like, two seconds."
I don't sound like that.
Look, I was a little intimidated, too,
but Iris made me give it a try
and we wound up having
a great time that night.
That sounds like my baby girl.
Any sign of her?
Nora says that Iris is still
in the future, which means she's okay.
The path we're on now
should lead us to her.
Well, the timeline has split
you and Iris up before
and it never holds. So...
I need to have faith
in that just like you do.
Hey, uh...
I gotta go to C.C.P.D.
Kramer needs you?
No, not Kramer.
You're trying to make me feel like
I ran back in time?
What can I say, Allen?
This will always be home.
Don't worry, I covered for you.
While the Flash was out
stopping robberies in Central City,
Barry Allen has been
in his lab all day with me.
Captain Kramer
will never suspect a thing.
Thanks, Chief, but it's fine.
She already knows I'm the Flash.
What? You told her already?
She just got here.
Actually, she figured it out on her own.
Well, I figured it out first.
You did.
I mean, good for her.
Uh, so you said you had a case for me?
Yes.
A high-profile theft
at Mercury Labs came across my desk.
What is it?
We thought it was a simple
smash-and-grab job by a thief
who wiped the security cameras
clean before they left.
But the inventory report says they
made off with a gamma absorption array.
And Mercury tech unit says
a device like that in the wrong hands
can cause all kinds of damage.
Yeah, they're right.
I mean, arrays like this
use bursts of gamma radiation
to interact with cellular structures.
It could be used for almost anything
from growing super crops
to taking out an entire army.
So the only way to solve
our mystery is to catch our thief.
I will never get used to that.
So, tire prints from the crime scene
have traces of residual calcium plates.
It's most commonly found in barnacles,
which grow directly onto
a hard substrate,
like a boat or a dock.
So the perp is probably hiding out
somewhere near the shipyard.
Okay. I will get
Captain Kramer up to speed.
Great work, as usual.
Thank you.
So you know what happens now?
Oh, I bring in our mystery thief.
That I'm used to.
Chester, bring up the plans
for the shipyard warehouses.
Our perp is hiding somewhere out here.
Might as well list the whole area
on villainhideouts.com.
These warehouses
haven't been in use in seven years.
I think I found something.
Tire treads match those
from the crime report.
Great gamma gadget.
Barry, that van must have been shielded
'cause as soon as you opened it up,
radiation readings
spiked through the roof.
It's the gamma array.
Whoever stole this
made some seriously advanced mods.
I'm gonna run it back
for a full analysis.
Oh, you won't be running anywhere
much longer.
Hey.
You're the bad guy, aren't you?
You wanna save us both some time
and tell me what these mods do
before I take you to prison or after?
Why don't I show you?
Flash, are you okay?
Flash!
Enjoy what time you have left, Flash.
Oh! What hit me?
Gideon, run a full diagnostic.
Commencing
full-body diagnostic scan.
Multiple biological abnormalities
detected.
What?
What kind of abnormalities?
Moderate signs of arthritis,
hearing loss, osteoporosis,
high cholesterol and heartburn.
That's what that is.
Holy Benjamin Button, Barry!
Every cell in your body
has deteriorated suddenly.
It says here that
you've aged 30 years overnight.
How is that possible?
He looks exactly the same.
It looks like the blast that hit Barry
was mostly absorbed
by his internal biology.
Organs, cardiovascular system,
bones, joints.
He may look young on the outside,
but on the inside,
things are very different.
Can we reverse it?
Maybe, but I'd need the device
that whammied you to even try.
All right, let's find
Dr. Creep-face and get it.
But why build an "old gun" anyway?
I don't know, but whatever
the reason, it's probably dangerous.
I'm gonna go back
to his warehouse and search for clues.
Hang on. Hang on.
Do you really think it's a good idea
for you to go out in the field
like this?
Do we even know...
has this affected your powers?
Gideon run a meta efficiency test.
Test initiated.
We'll start with phasing.
Oh.
Come on.
Phasing unsuccessful.
Phasing's pretty advanced.
- Yeah.
- Um, yeah.
Okay, let's try something easier.
Wind arms.
Wind arms are easier.
Oh, my.
Come on!
- Test complete.
- I almost had it.
Meta ability has decreased by 29%.
Okay, Barry, honey,
why don't you come sit down?
I'm fine.
I can...
I can feel the Speed Force inside me.
I just need to stretch my legs,
get them moving...
Figure out what I can still handle.
I'm okay.
I already updated the software.
Now I've got to give
the damn thing a name.
How about "vacuum"?
There's the Joe West I know.
It's good to see you, man.
Hey, David.
Hey.
Barry told me you'd be around.
Sorry, I've just been screaming
at electronic equipment
for the last couple hours.
I wanted to see
how retirement was treating you.
I was expecting all-day football
or a wine and jazz room,
not an appliance minefield.
Yeah, ever since
Jenna's been to pre-school,
I've had more time on my hands.
A lot more.
You know, you could just use
some of this time to find ways to relax.
When Rob's mom retired,
she took up meditation.
That sounds like a whole lot
of sitting around doing nothing.
Plus all these little projects
keep me busy.
The problem is, each one of them comes
with a novel-long instruction booklet.
I mean, you have to learn how to program
a computer to just use a mop.
You know what?
Rob and I got his mother
one of these last Christmas.
Let's see what you're working with.
- Hey!
- Hi.
You look better. How do you feel?
I'm just a little tired.
But as long as I keep it under Mach 10,
I can maintain control of my speed.
And that's more than
fast enough to catch this guy.
Right, but we know that Allegra
can handle herself out in the field.
So when crazy scientist guy comes back,
then she and Chester can handle it.
And I can even help out...
Cecile, I can't risk any of you
getting hit with that machine.
And you heard Chester,
the only way to cure me
is to get the gamma array back,
and the best way to do that
is with my speed.
But are you sure that
this is the right way to do it?
It just feels like you're racing
past some red flags here.
I mean, is everything okay?
Guys, we've got a break-in
at Magnus Labs.
Another tech facility.
Guess we found our guy.
Chester, get ready to adjust
that gamma array when I get back.
I won't be long.
High velocity object incoming.
I assumed correctly you would
recognize a thermal detonator, Flash.
Barry, that's no ordinary grenade.
It's got major bad energy
emanating from it.
He modified it to pack a serious punch.
This isn't the answer
to getting what you want.
There is only one way
to get what I want,
and it's in here.
I am going to obtain a power
more precious
than any ever wielded by a "superhero."
How's this for power?
Cute.
My turn.
His heart rate's spiking.
Barry?
Barry!
Well, there's no permanent
damage, but you're nearsighted now.
Why did your vision go bad?
You didn't have this problem earlier.
That's not the only new thing.
It's just, like...
I thought he was only supposed
to be old on the inside.
Hey, Chester, run my scan results
through Gideon's bio-algorithm
and let's take a detailed look.
Done. And if I'm reading this right...
Um...
You aged another ten years.
What?
How? Was it the grenade blast?
I don't think so.
It looks like the gamma radiation
inside Barry's cells
is activated by his Speed Force energy.
Chuck, are you seriously saying
that the more the Flash runs...
The more he ages.
Barry, you gotta stop using your speed.
Cecile, I have to find this guy.
Hold on. Maybe Cecile's right.
You almost had a heart attack
back at Magnus Labs.
Plus, if your aging's
showing on the outside,
I can't even imagine
what's going on inside your body.
Guys, I won't let this guy get away.
We still don't even know
what he's planning.
What if he uses this device
on someone else?
And what if you die of old age
before you can stop him?
I won't.
Look, we just need to
track this guy down
as soon as possible and end this.
And I think I know how to start.
You found out who he is?
Yeah, he wiped the security cameras
at his first crime scene,
but I showed up
before he had a chance to do it again.
Pulled this photo from the footage
and ran a background check.
Dr. Pytor Orloff.
Former technician at a small R & D lab,
Corbin Taft Industries.
Says here he was fired
for using company resources
on unsanctioned research.
I'm gonna check his old lab at Taft.
See if Dr. Olsen left any clues.
Barry, it's Dr. Orloff, remember?
That's what I meant.
And I'm gonna need
those contacts, Chester.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Okay, I'm gonna go with you.
Cecile...
Look, this guy has surprised us
a couple of times already,
and my powers will feel him coming
if he decides to show up
while we're at his lab.
Okay.
Great! Oh! Uh...
Real quick. This time...
We're gonna take my car.
"Now, use the provided
triangular hex bracket tool
to fasten the side brushes."
Yeah, I couldn't find
whatever the hell that is.
So I'm using my trusty,
dusty socket wrench.
Are you sure
that it's going to fit the...
Uh...
Just a little elbow grease.
All right,
let's see if this thing works.
Oh!
Damn it!
Why do we need robots
for a man's job, anyway?
Jenna's going to have
to learn what chores are.
Joe...
I love you, man, but...
I've not seen you
this frustrated since...
Do you remember the Steve Palmer case?
Look, man, I would spend months
and months and months on a case
if that's what it took, right?
I mean, obviously it wasn't easy,
but I loved it.
I loved it.
Now, I'm...
Uh, okay, that's enough of that.
I'm calling in a 10-85.
Delay due to coffee break.
You, my friend, need to
get out of this house badly.
Man, let me just clean up
this vacuum mess.
Oh, no, Joe, I'm not asking.
This is an order
from the Chief of Police.
Let's roll.
All right. You're buying.
Don't I always?
True.
Look for Orloff's
old work files.
Maybe they could tell us where he's
hiding or what he could be planning.
Usually, these facilities
have strict record-keeping.
I got it.
Okay.
What was that?
I think it was a facial ID scan.
Like how your phone unlocks.
That's a countdown
to wipe the hard drive.
If we don't hack past this now,
all the data's going to be erased.
I need to run this to Chester.
Wait, no, Barry, you can't.
I don't have a choice. We need
to find out what's on this hard drive.
Well, then there's gotta be another way.
Let's just take a second and think...
I don't have time.
We need to run this to C.C.P.D.
C.C.P.D.?
You mean S.T.A.R.?
Barry, that's the second time
you forgot something.
I didn't forget it. I misspoke, okay?
We need to go right now.
Where did you take us?
Barry...
We are a long way from home.
Barry!
How did we get here?
Connections in the hippocampus
are showing gradual decay.
While cognitive functions
have returned to normal levels,
Barry Allen's memory loss
will likely be a recurring event.
Barry...
How you feeling?
I feel like we don't have time for this.
I'm fine now.
Barr, I don't think you get
how serious this is.
Look, according to your latest
bio-scan results from Gideon,
if you use that much speed
again, it could kill you.
Okay.
Then we need to find Orloff
more than ever.
Getting his gamma array
is still the only way to cure me
and stop whatever he's planning.
Chester, were you able
to save his laptop?
I managed to stop the countdown,
but it's going to take
some more time for me to hack inside.
Okay. Well, let me know when you do.
In the meantime,
everyone watch satellites
for gamma ray spikes in the city.
Right now, that's our only
other means to find Orloff.
I'm gonna visit the Starchives.
See if I can find anything
to safely hold the gamma emitter
when I bring it back.
Sometimes I feel like
time's chasing me.
I spend half my day
trying to keep up
with the changes all around me.
Like I had to set a reminder on my phone
to pick up Jenna
from her playdate an hour from now.
It's like I don't recognize my life.
All right.
Maybe that's what happens when
you have more years behind you
than you have ahead of you.
You spend so much time looking back that
it is really hard to move forward.
Hmm.
Joe...
Um...
Your life isn't the problem.
Retirement isn't the problem.
It's you.
You don't want to move forward.
You've always been like this.
Stuck in your ways.
Not really willing
to embrace anything new.
My ways put hundreds
of criminals behind bars.
Mm.
Do you know why it took us so long
to close the Steve Palmer case?
It wasn't just 'cause of the dead ends.
It was because you refused to learn
the new C.C.P.D. computer system.
Listen now,
my file folders worked just fine.
Maybe.
And maybe you spent a lot
of extra time filling out forms.
Time you could have spent
doing the job you love instead.
Joe, your life has always been changing.
Think about it.
You were a single father
who took in a traumatized boy
who just lost both of his parents.
And you raised that boy to be
one of the most extraordinary humans
to ever walk the Earth.
Joe,
you raised the Flash.
And he didn't get his greatest
superpowers from a bolt of lightning.
He got them from the man who embraced
an unexpected time in his life.
He got them from you, Joe West.
Now imagine all the amazing new things
Joe West can still do with his life.
Yeah.
Hey.
I've been looking for you. I thought
you were going to the Starchives.
Barry?
I... Forgot where it was.
Okay. All right. Come on, talk to me.
Barry, what's going on with you?
You're not normally this stubborn.
And what are you trying to prove, honey?
You know you're scaring all of us.
I'm scared, too, Cecile.
Orloff's still out there and I can't...
I feel myself withering.
When I run, my bones ache,
like they're made of glass and...
My hands won't stop shaking.
I'm always out of breath
and it's getting harder.
It's getting harder
to remember the people I love.
My friends.
Nora, Bart, Joe.
Even Iris.
What if I forget who she is
before she comes back?
I thought I had plenty
of time to get Iris back...
And live my life with her.
Now it's all fading away, like my body.
And now, with my mind going, too,
it's like losing everyone you love...
all at once.
You know, you're not the first superhero
that I've seen go through this.
No... I knew one badass fighter
through and through.
My grandmother.
And, just like you, she was always
running from one adventure to the next.
Not just when
she was young and spry, either.
Oh, no, no. I mean, I'm talking
well into her golden years.
She never lost her love for life and...
that inspired me to do more with my own.
She sounds like an amazing woman.
Here's the thing, though.
She never feared getting old.
Mm-mm.
She made a choice.
She knew if she was gonna
run out of time, then, damn it,
she was gonna use the time that she had
to live exactly the life
that she wanted.
See, she knew... She knew
that no one could outrun time...
But you can embrace it.
Barry, nobody's saying that
you can't go get the bad guy,
but don't let your fear
of running out of time
cloud your ability
to see the right way to do it.
Guys, I finally broke
the encryption code on Orloff's laptop.
So I took a look through
Orloff's notes on the gamma array.
He is a next-level genius, no doubt,
but unfortunately he's planning
something seriously dangerous.
This is what he stole
from his second lab raid.
It's an energy amplifier that could
boost his machine's output 100-fold.
So he wants to make everyone old? Why?
His research is obsessed
with finding the scientific equivalent
of the Fountain of Youth.
He just wants to be young again
and I think he's figured out how.
By taking it from other people.
Can you pull up the security footage
I used to run his background?
Look at his hair.
It's not gray anymore.
His machine works.
Only it needs to absorb a lot of energy
just to make him
even a few years younger,
which is why he stole the amplifier.
Chester, what happens
when he finishes connecting
the amplifier to the gamma array?
He becomes immortal.
And the city, everyone in it, all age
hundreds of years in an instant.
We'll all be dust.
We've got a massive radiation spike.
I'm reading 2,000 millisieverts.
Wait, no, 3,000.
Orloff just activated his machine.
Okay, we know where he is.
Let's take him down. Pull the plug.
No, it's not gonna be that easy.
I mean, look at these readings.
If we shut it down too suddenly,
there'd be a cascading
degradation cycle in the gamma isotopes.
Meaning we can't just turn it off.
It's already built up
too much of a charge.
Shutting it off now would cause
the gamma rays to explode out,
affecting hundreds of people.
We better think of something quick.
In a few minutes, it'll be
charged enough to affect the whole city.
Is there any way we can slow it down?
No.
We have to speed it up.
Guys, the gamma radiation
siphons energy from human cells
speeding up the biological aging process
like what's been happening to me
all day.
But if we fed it more energy
than it can handle...
The amplifier would have
to kick into overdrive
to match the high energy
consumption rate.
It would burn out the machine.
Okay, what do we got
that can put out that much energy?
Me.
No.
Barry, you remember what Chester said?
If you use your speed again,
it could kill you this time.
I have to try.
If I die or it ages me to 100,
I'm not afraid anymore.
You are right, Cecile,
I can't outrun time,
but I can embrace it.
And I can choose to spend
every moment I have left
trying to save innocent lives.
Then run, Barry.
Run.
You don't...
You can't...
Yes, I can.
And I am.
Orloff's machine just hit
100,000 millisieverts of radiation.
That's fully charged, Barry.
Whatever you're gonna do,
you gotta do it now.
You're out of time, Flash.
And slower than ever.
It looks like everyone in Central City
is running out of time, except me.
I don't understand. What's Barry doing?
He just matched
the gamma machine's energy output,
stopping it from expanding,
but if he's gonna overcharge it,
he's going to have to hit
some savage velocity.
Oh, no, no, no!
He's having a heart attack.
How much longer can he hold out?
Biologically, he's over 100 years old.
No...
No!
He did it!
Wait, what's wrong?
Wait.
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
Barry? Barry, what happened?
My readings are saying that you're...
Better than ever.
My years...
My time...
It's all gone!
What do I do now?
My advice...
Embrace the time you have left
in prison.
He looks... good!
Is he good?
Yeah. Now that boy's doing
better than good.
Barry forcing
the gamma array's field backwards
completely inverted its energy charge.
So young man Orloff became old.
But not only did old man Barry
become young again,
you completely regenerated
and then some.
Hold on, are you saying I'm...
Sorry to break it to you, kid,
you're not in your 30s anymore.
How old am I?
Twenty-nine. But y'all know
what that means though, right?
Thirtieth birthday party next year.
Party next year.
I gotta tell you,
a party is the least we can do
for the man who saved us all today.
I just... I stopped being stubborn.
And found the best way
to use the time I had left.
Well, you'll be happy to know
Dr. Orloff is going to spend
the rest of his time in Iron Heights.
That's thanks to you guys.
You watched out for me even when
I wasn't watching out for myself.
Don't sweat it, boss.
Why don't you keep getting some rest
and we'll see you later?
Yeah.
Hey, Cecile.
I owe the most to you today.
I'm sorry I didn't listen sooner.
I know your grandma
would be proud of you.
I hope so.
I would consider myself lucky
if one day I could be half
of the role model that she was.
You already are.
So you're a meta, too?
Yeah, I used to be
like a human light bulb, but now...
She's a hell of a lot more.
So what's your code name?
Uh...
You know, Barry used to be the Streak
and then he became the Flash.
What do people call you?
I don't know. I've never really
thought about it before.
But I like to keep a low profile. So...
Okay, Joe, I'm thinking
we tweak the quest.
We can set it in C.C.P.D.
Maybe we solve a homicide.
We could do that or...
Yes!
What if Karash the Orc
used Vorion root-induced Barbarian rage
and his vorpal sword
to kick some Dungeon Kraken ass?
Yes!
I've been doing a little light reading
in that handbook there, children.
And once I show you all
how to play this game,
I'mma teach you all spades and
you're all gonna need a manual for that.
That's my man!
I'm sorry, I gotta take this.
Hold on, you guys keep...
Okay.
You shall not pass!
Carla, hey, what's up?
No, I thought Caitlin was with you.
Caitlin?
Barry?
Caitlin, are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Your mom called, trying to find you.
You said you were staying with her,
but she says
she hasn't seen you since the funeral,
that you haven't returned her calls.
I changed my mind.
Okay. What is going on?
I've been working on some stuff.
What is it?
You know you can ask
for my help with anything.
I know I can, but...
But what?
Caitlin, talk to me.
- Okay...
- What's this doing here?
I know how this looks.
Caitlin, what's this doing here?
Barry, just listen to me.
The Mirror Gun split Frost and me
into two people once before.
It took her from my subconscious
and gave her a body.
So I've been running tests
over and over again.
And there must still be
a piece of Frost inside of me,
so if I can access those latent pieces
in my subconsciousness,
then I can bring her back.
Okay,
I know what you're thinking,
and frankly, if I was in your shoes,
I'd probably be thinking the same thing.
But just for one second,
imagine this isn't Frost
that we're talking about.
What if we could bring your mom back?
Or your dad?
What would you do to make
that possibility a reality?
We don't have to say goodbye to Frost.
Caitlin, losing someone you love
can make it really hard to move on.
But as difficult as it is,
you have to accept that Frost is gone.
And that she's not coming back.
But I don't want to.
I know.
But it's the only way
to start living again.
I can do this.
I have to.
I'm sorry.
Barry... Barry, please.
Barry, don't!
I'm sorry.