- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Together, you and Cynthia
could be an unstoppable duo.
- You wanna be
the new Breacher?
- Your Thinking Cap
and the dark matter
is what caused this.
- I know!
How long before
everything I know is gone?
- DeVoe has taken out everyone
who's gotten in his way.
- He created 12 meta-humans,
just so he could
steal their powers.
- Why does he need
their powers?
- The fire that burns down
Team Flash
will also light the path
to the Enlightenment.
Marlize:Since the age
of Enlightenment,
when reason, debate, and the
search for truth flourished,
the world has improved
by nearly every measure
in human advancement,
and continues to do so.
There is no doubt in my mind
that as technology
continues to bloom,
so will all of humanity.
- [chuckling]
- Professor DeVoe?
You disagree?
- Well, uh,
yes, I guess.
Just, I have
a more realistic view
of humanity whenever technology
is concerned.
- What do you mean?
- Well, you spoke
of the Enlightenment.
One only has to look at history
to find the answers.
- Okay, let's.
Life expectancy
over the past two centuries
has increased from 30 years
to nearly 70 years.
- And-and we should assume
that's a good thing?
Each new day,
we have to share
very limited resources
with anything up to
200,000 newborn babies,
most of whom
will end up living
in abject poverty and famine.
- Well, thank you very much,
Professor Doom and Gloom.
Remind me never to take
one of your history classes.
[crowd laughs]
- Perhaps you should.
There's much I could teach you.
[crowd murmurs]
[suspenseful music]
The Taoists,
in pursuit of immortality,
discovered gunpowder.
Alfred Nobel created
the Nobel Prize
so he wouldn't be remembered
as the man
who invented dynamite.
History has shown us
time and time again
that whenever
a technological advancement
can be used to hurt humanity,
it will be.
- You can't blame technology
for the way
men choose to use it,
Professor.
- You can't ignore
that the best of ideas
by the smartest of men
often have a way
of becoming corrupted.
♪ ♪
[computer beeping]
- You've located
everything we need.
- And now the time has come
to retrieve it
so we can finally...
enlighten the world.
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
[crackling]
- Uh-oh.
[energy humming]
[uncertain orchestral music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, babe.
Uh, it's me.
Just checking in.
For my dad.
He... really wants to know
your answer
about taking
the Breacher job.
I think his exact words were:
"That little son of a Breach
better tell me,
or they will never
find the body."
Yeah.
But you know what?
He's retired.
He can wait.
So just take
as much time as you need.
Okay? It's, um...
- Don't say it's fine.
- You know.
- It's fine.
- Oh, God.
- Okay.
- So, just five me.
Whenever.
Okay.
Bye.
Harry:Ramon, speed lab.
Now.
- Good!
Good, good, good.
Good, good, good
good, good.
- Thing we're gonna do
to get Killer Frost
to appear,
get that massive spike
in your adrenaline production
that we need,
is, Ramon is gonna use
his vibes
to shake you up
on the cellular level,
and let's see if we can't
get your old friend
Killer Frost
to come out to play.
- Are you sure
this is gonna work?
- Well, I mean,
like any hypothesis,
you have to test it
to get an answer.
It's what we've
all done since
the fourth grade,
known as the...
- Scientific method?
- Right you are, Allen!
Of course.
Ah, here he is.
Okay, good.
So get in position.
- Don't worry, I lowered
the amps on this thing.
- Ramon, you set?
- Yeah.
- Snow, you ready?
- I'm ready.
- Three, two, one, and...
[energy warbles]
- Nothing.
- All right.
Ramon, more power.
♪ ♪
Set?
Three, two, one...
[energy warbles]
All right,
this isn't working.
You know what, Ramon?
Full power.
- Wait, hold on, hold on.
What do you mean,
full power?
We don't want to blast Caitlin
across the speed lab.
- Well, you need to get
a spike in her adrenaline.
- Harry, she could get injured.
- Yeah.
- God, this is...
look, this is
gonna work, okay?
Nothing has changed.
All right?
Snow's DNA tests,
they confirm it.
Her meta-DNA
was not spliced
by Noah's powers.
- You mean
Melting Point's powers.
- Right, that's what I said.
- No, you didn't.
- I did say that.
- But, Harry,
there's no dark matter
in her system anyway.
We're just trying to
spike her heart rate.
- What do you mean,
there's no dark matter?
- Harry, you knew that.
We all did.
- We did? We did.
No, I know.
I just, I think I just,
you know, forget.
I forgot.
- You forgot?
- Harry, are you okay?
- [sighs]
- No. He's not.
♪ ♪
- Harry, you're...
- Losing my intelligence?
Yes.
The injection of dark matter
from the Thinking Cap
apparently overwhelmed
my synapses.
Instead of making
my brain faster, it's...
slowing it down.
- Why didn't you
tell us this sooner?
[restrained piano music]
- How long until...
- No way of knowing.
I mean, there are days
I can think clearly
and other days...
I... I can't.
♪ ♪
- The good news is, um,
from what I can see,
the regression
seems to be reversible.
- Okay, great.
I'll start working on it
full-time.
- No, you won't.
I did this to myself,
and I-I thought
"Oh, you know what?
"Use that Thinking Cap,
and then I can
outthink Devoe
and then stop DeVoe."
I was wrong.
Now here we are.
- Okay, well,
we're gonna fix this.
- You and I both know
there's a ticking clock...
and I can't help
anyone like this.
- Yes, you can.
- How?
- [sighs]
[dramatic music builds]
Look, guys.
Ralph...
Caitlin's powers,
now this.
DeVoe knew how to
break us apart, but...
I mean,
we're all still here.
We're a family.
That's how
we're gonna beat DeVoe.
- All right, Allen.
All right.
[foreboding music]
[loud electronic static]
- Vandermeer Steel.
Smaller than I expected.
♪ ♪
The first step
to our Enlightenment
is as simple...
[electronic pulsing]
As opening a door.
[finger clanking and whirring]
[lock beeps]
♪ ♪
Alloy 1771.
Now, the gallium antimonide
substrates within these
can harness power
at 400% efficiency.
♪ ♪
The precise amount,
I calculated.
You can pick 'em up.
♪ ♪
- Freeze!
[suspenseful music]
- You should let us leave.
- I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
[intense music builds]
- How are you...
[grunts]
[gasps, pants]
♪ ♪
- We have what we need.
- I suppose we do.
[energy warbling]
[walkie-talkie beeps]
- Code Red! Code Red!
[crying out in pain]
♪ ♪
- Clifford.
This is unnecessary.
- You knew there were
gonna be casualties
when we began.
This is his own doing.
- Yes, my love.
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
- What are we dealing with?
- First of all,
we're trying to determine
what was in that vault.
Watch your step right here.
There was no drilling,
there was no lock picked.
And the only thing
anybody would tell us
about what was in
the vault was that
it was some sort of
secretive technology.
Also, security guard here
was a 24-year-old,
apparently shot himself.
- Wait, a robbery
and a suicide?
- He was newly married.
Has an infant at home.
This is smelling like
some meta madness to me.
- Who else can
"Kilgore" a retinal scan
and "Dibny" a vault lock?
- Okay, well, I'm gonna
go interview some people,
see what I can find out.
- All right,
Cisco and I will try
to figure out what DeVoe stole.
- All right.
I'll be over here.
- Okay, so.
Where should we start?
I'm thinking:
if we can gain acc...
[dramatic music]
...to their files...
- Alloy 1771?
It's the only item missing
from the inventory files.
- Or I can just...
stand here and look pretty.
- Hey, know what
you can do, actually?
You could vibe the gun.
The file didn't say
what Alloy 1771 was.
So we need another way
to learn
why DeVoe would want it.
- Uh, vibing and DeVoe
do not mix, remember?
- Yeah, I know, man.
But I mean,
what are we supposed to do?
It's the only way.
- Barry, I don't
really feel like
getting blasted
into a wall right now.
I'm sure there's
another way we can
find out what
this is that doesn't
require me
getting a migraine.
- It is a solar panel.
Constructed of metal
that absorbs
and multiplies
the sun's energy
at 400% efficiency.
- What would DeVoe be doing
with a solar panel?
- Nothing, on its own.
He's gotta be building
something.
Look, I-I need you
to vibe the gun.
- Maybe I should put this
in movie terms for you.
Everything in DeVoe's wake
is like the "Home Alone" house.
Okay?
It's booby-trapped.
I would need to
double my powers
just to even attempt
to vibe the gun.
- Well, hold on.
I mean, could...
could Gypsy double your powers?
- That's a good idea.
- No, not.
- Not what?
- Gypsy's busy.
Her dad just retired.
She's having to do
double the work.
Earth 19 is a mess right now.
She's swamped.
- Cisco.
Combining your powers
could make it
so we know DeVoe's next move.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
Joe:Thanks for meeting me.
I need a favor.
- Okay.
- I need you to distract
Cecile for a while.
- What for?
- Well, that's the thing.
I can't tell you,
because if I do,
she'll read your mind
and find out.
- Why can't Iris do it?
- Because Iris knows
exactly why
I'm trying
to distract Cecile.
- Ah.
- And therefore Barry knows.
Which means that Cisco knows,
Kid knows.
- Whatever you need.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right.
Lose my mind,
become a babysitter.
- Oh, come on.
Listen, if anybody's gonna
reverse what's happening,
it's gonna be those kids
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I mean, they love you, Harry.
And they will never stop
trying to help you.
So don't lose hope.
- Right.
[woman laughing]
[old-timey vocal music plays]
- And that is how I aced
my intro to heat transfer
my first year at university.
- Bravo.
Ducked and run.
- [laughs]
I miss those days.
I was young and foolish
and brave.
- And now you're just foolish.
- To agree to a date
with someone
I first met
as they were so rudely
disagreeing
with my professional opinion.
Foolish, maybe.
♪ ♪
Yeah, no one's ever
challenged me like that.
♪ ♪
It was refreshing.
- ♪ Well, I think I'm going
out of my head ♪
[phone ringing]
Ah, maybe you are right
about technology's
distracting us.
It certainly can
destroy moments.
- Although, sometimes...
technology...
can create them as well.
[romantic music]
- ♪ I want you ♪
♪ To want me ♪
- [laughs]
- ♪ I need you ♪
♪ So badly ♪
♪ I can't think of anything ♪
♪ But you ♪
♪ And I think
I'm going out of my head ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't explain
the tears that I shed ♪
♪ Over you ♪
- Thanks for coming
to help us, Gypsy.
- You two are up.
- So, how do we do this?
- Okay, so to co-vibe,
we have to be totally in sync.
All right?
Our minds have to be on
exactly the same page.
- Just like always.
- Yeah.
[energy warbling]
- Oh. So that was weird.
- Why? What did you see?
- I don't know, a-a dock?
- Um, looked like
a shipping container.
- Number 16.
- That must be what DeVoe
is gonna steal next.
- He's gonna have to
steal it from us.
[dramatic music]
[loud electronic humming]
- All right.
It looks like
we made it in time.
Whatever's in this container,
we can't let DeVoe have it.
- Actually...
it's what's in...
this container
you can't let me have.
Well...
what was in this container.
[energy rushing]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[yells]
- Hit him!
- Gratitude...
for the workout,
brief as it was.
♪ ♪
Later.
[both panting]
- Damn it.
Damn it!
Why didn't we see
the right container number?
- Someone's vibe
wasn't clear enough, Cisco.
- Are you blaming me?
- You lost your focus,
what can I say?
- Yeah, getting hit
against a metal container wall
sort of does that.
- You know,
I hit that wall too.
I'm perfectly focused.
- Oh, well,
if you're so focused,
then why'd you let him
get away?
- Don't even try
and put that on me.
- I'm sorry,
I didn't put that on you.
You put that on you.
- I'm gonna put my fist
in your face,
is what I'm gonna...
Barry: Guys.
- Is that how
we'd work together
if I took the job?
- Guys.
What job?
- I brought that metal piece
from the shipping container,
in case we want to try
co-vibing later, but...
think we both saw
where that led us, so...
- So you said...
Breacher retired.
He offered you a job on Earth
19 to replace him, didn't he?
- Mm-hmm.
- You know,
another shot in the dark,
but you haven't actually
given Breacher
or Gypsy an answer yet.
- Mm-mm.
- Which way you leaning?
- I wanna be with Gypsy
more than anything.
It's just complicated.
- Hey, no, man, I get it.
[dramatic music]
But look, I mean...
maybe...
you guys working together
to end this
will make the decision easier,
for both of you.
- What if she doesn't want
the same thing as me?
- I mean, you're never
gonna know unless you ask.
♪ ♪
And listen, Cisco, I mean...
we can't beat DeVoe
without you.
You're our secret weapon.
You and Gypsy just need to be
on the same page
for that weapon to work.
- Yeah, and I don't know
that we can be.
- All right, well...
let me help you.
- Barry.
- No, I... hold on.
- So that's gonna end well.
- Last one.
- [laughs]
- Okay, we, uh, need food.
We need wine.
- Lots of both.
Go.
I'll unpack.
Clifford!
[giggling]
Go.
Hurry home.
- I can stay, if...
you're sure?
- Yeah.
- I really should.
Last chance.
- [giggling]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Me, hunter!
Me hunted feast
for my queen!
- You don't believe
these things you wrote
in this journal, do you?
This reads like some
radical's manifesto, Clifford.
♪ ♪
- It is a realist's awakening.
- You declare war against every
technological philanthropist.
- Men, men, men.
Pushing us to the brink
of Armageddon
with their "inventions."
- No, they want
a better mankind.
- Don't be naive, Marlize.
[dramatic music]
The severity
of our society's failings
require extreme ideas
if ever we were to
restore some semblance
of balance.
- "Technology has become
a cancerous cell
"in our social biology.
"Exercising it...
would require a total purge,
"not only of
the material world,
but also human consciousness"?
This is not balance!
This is lobotomizing people!
- It is rebooting
the masses' brains,
to let them forget
their technological crutches!
They are babies with pacifiers!
- Oh, and who will teach them?
You, Professor?
How does any of this
help humankind?
- Don't you see?
Marlize...
♪ ♪
Our technology is killing us.
You and I, we can fix this.
Together.
As partners.
We can lead them,
all of society, humanity,
on the true path
to Enlightenment.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Harry.
- [sighs]
DA Cecile Horton.
- Joe said you needed to adjust
my mental activity dampener.
- Yes. Joe... yes.
I have to do that.
It's, uh, it's not a big deal.
It's a standard procedure.
- [grunts]
That's, yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I'm in.
- Well, it's installing, so...
now you just...
you just sit.
And wait.
For a long time.
[clears throat]
[psychic whirring]
- Okay.
What is happening
with your thoughts right now?
- With my... okay.
So... there was an incident
with dark matter...
- Yeah, I know, I know,
Joe told me about that.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
- What do you mean?
- Your thoughts
are screaming at me.
It's like they start to form,
and then, it's like,
the more the ideas appear...
- The more they disappear.
- Exactly.
- Well, that explains
my "can't" days.
- What does that mean, Harry?
- It means, DA Cecile Horton,
that the more I try
to use my brain...
the sooner
I'm going to lose it.
[horns honk in the distance]
- Barista.
Another one, please.
Uh, make it a double.
Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
- I've been looking
everywhere for you.
- Can't a woman
caffeinate in peace
around here?
- Hey. Look.
Hey!
I know why you're upset,
but it's all right.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, Cisco just thinks
if he takes the job,
he'll be letting us down.
but, I mean,
he just needs to follow
his own heart,
do what he needs to do,
not worry about us.
He knows that.
- Wow.
That's actually really great.
- So now...
all you guys have to do
is talk to each other.
- Yeah. Well, that part's
not so easy, so...
- Yes... it is.
- What are you doing?
- What?
- Don't even think
about it. No!
- Okay.
- Don't ever "whoosh"
me again, all right?
- Totally, I'm sorry.
Um, Cisco.
- What is going on?
- Just getting 'em back
on the same page, okay?
Cisco, Gypsy is upset,
because, frankly...
I mean, it's taking you
too long to accept
Breacher's job offer.
Duh. And Gypsy.
Cisco, he's-he's just worried
about abandoning his team.
I mean, it's not that
he doesn't want the job.
Right?
Okay, so...
Now you both know, right?
And you can dive in and...
work this out...
let's talk about this.
[upbeat music]
[alarm blaring]
- CCPD is reporting
two more break-ins
at tech manufacturers...
Boeing Lab
and the Jamison Institute.
More hardware was stolen.
- DeVoe.
- Was anybody hurt?
- Three fatalities,
all of them security guards
in high-level clearance areas,
just like at Vandermeer.
- He's taking
whatever he wants,
killing anybody
that gets in the way.
Guys, I-I'm sorry,
but we have to figure out
what kind of machine
he's building,
right now.
Cisco: Look, we have to try.
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
♪ ♪
- Oh, God, are you okay?
- I saw that one coming.
♪ ♪
- You okay?
- I'm good. Thank you.
♪ ♪
- They okay?
- Tests show,
physically, they're fine.
As a couple, not so much.
[solemn orchestral music]
- Where are you going?
- I need to get these two
back in sync.
I mean, we gotta get ahead
of this somehow.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
slow down, cowboy.
- What do you mean? Why?
- Maybe you've done
enough already, okay?
Cisco and Gypsy
are clearly going through
something, and, you know,
it's not up to us
to counsel them through it.
- Well, then who
is it up to, Iris?
- Just stop for a second...
- We can't stop.
The second we do,
everyone could fall apart.
The team's hanging on
by a thread.
- But we are hanging on, Barry.
- For how long?
I mean,
look at what's happening.
DeVoe is killing
innocent people.
He's stealing pieces of tech,
for God knows why.
Just trying to keep up with him
is tearing us apart.
- Babe...
you can't put it on yourself
to hold everyone together.
- [sighs]
[melancholy piano music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco is family.
And when family hurts,
we all hurt.
I get that.
But sometimes you can't answer
their questions for them.
Sometimes,
you just have to support them
while they find them
on their own,
whether they're together
or they're apart.
♪ ♪
What?
- That's it.
The pieces of tech
don't fit together...
because they're not
supposed to.
He's not building one thing,
he's building multiple.
[dramatic music]
- Harry, I know this is hard.
- Well...
it is hard, DA Cecile Horton,
because my brain,
the one thing
that has defined me
for, well,
pretty much my entire life,
is about to...
[snaps fingers]
...vanish,
and then who will I be?
- You'll be the exact same man
you've always been.
- Yeah, but dumb.
Same man.
Way less intelligent.
- Harry.
There are lots of ways
to be intelligent.
Not just using your head.
[uplifting orchestral music]
- Right.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[psychic whirring]
- Wait.
Do that again.
Harry!
- Do what?
- Do it again! Do it again!
[exhales noisily]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Right?
- How did you do that?
- I saw it!
Inside your mind,
before it vanished.
- In... wait.
So you can...
- Write down
what you're thinking.
- Before it...
- Disappears.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Marlize?
I brought the sample.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- Okay.
- All right.
- Fingers crossed.
- Yep.
- Here we go.
Cheers.
Yes!
- Yeah?
- Show the others.
- Got it.
[both laugh]
[phone ringing]
[foreboding music]
- Hello?
- Marlize.
It's me.
[solemn music]
- Clifford.
- I need you to come home.
- I can't.
I'm making a difference here...
I'm changing lives
for the better.
These people need me.
- I need you.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
I can't be with someone
that thinks
that society is a disease,
that believes
that our world
is being plagued by technology.
- I am nothing without you.
- You're a brilliant man
with a great future
ahead of you.
- What kind of future
do I have
if you are not by my side?
- I just wish
that you could show
the same compassion
for the rest of humanity
as you do for me.
- Listen to me, Marlize, I...
my thoughts, I cannot...
- I-I just...
I just don't think that...
[tires crunching on gravel,
man shouts indistinctly]
[gunfire, screaming]
[explosion booms,
indistinct shouting]
- Marlize?
[gunshots, distant screaming]
Marlize?
♪ ♪
Marlize!
[distant gunshots]
[intense music builds]
- So...
what were you gonna say?
Before we were so
alarmingly interrupted.
[hushed strings and piano]
♪ ♪
- Look, I just...
- Cisco, I...
both: Don't want you
to take the job.
- Oh.
[laughs]
That is such a relief.
Because I don't
want anything to change.
♪ ♪
- Not only have we not
been on the same page,
we haven't even been
on the same planet.
Literally.
We've been doing this
back-and-forth thing
for almost a year,
negotiating who gets to go
to whose Earth
and when,
just to see each other,
and on the off-chance we do
get to see each other,
there's, like, a countdown
until one of us has to leave,
and I'm tired of it!
I don't want to have to Breach
to see the woman I love.
I want to wake up next to her.
Every morning.
- So what are you saying?
♪ ♪
- I'm saying I want more.
I'm saying I don't
want Breacher's job,
but I do want you.
- I want you too.
What am I supposed to do?
Pack up my entire life,
everything?
Forget about my job,
my responsibilities...
- No, no, no...
- Move here?
- No, no, that's not
what I'm asking you to do.
I would never ask you
to leave the Agency.
I know how important
that is to you.
But tell me,
and tell me honestly...
this, what we have...
♪ ♪
Is this enough for you?
- Yes.
It is.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
Well, it isn't for me.
Barry:Hey, guys?
I need you both in the Cortex.
both: Why?
- I know what DeVoe's doing.
It's not one machine.
They're machines.
Machines that work together,
but they're still separate.
Satellites.
- Separate satellites
working together
for a single purpose?
- So this guy really is
a Bond villain.
- DeVoe would need
a massive amount
of computational power
for them to be able
to talk to each other.
Something to triangulate
navigation
between each satellite.
- So, like,
a quantum computer?
- Mercury Labs just put
a whole system
of quantum computers online,
at their home base.
That's where he's going.
- Okay, great. This time,
we catch DeVoe by surprise.
[dramatic music]
[energy warbling]
- Behold.
The key to communicating
our message
of the Enlightenment.
♪ ♪
- Polynomial time computing.
- And a dream shall soon
become... reality.
[loud whooshing]
[energetic droning]
♪ ♪
[sinister music]
- Clifford!
♪ ♪
- Uh-uh.
Don't move.
- Barry! Knock him out,
and then cuff him!
- On it!
[dramatic music]
- Gypsy, now!
- Stop it, you're killing him!
- [yells]
- Cisco, look out!
Barry, hit him again!
♪ ♪
- Enough!
- Caitlin.
- Caitlin,
what the hell are you doing?
- Bringing her back.
[ice cracking]
- DeVoe is creating
a sonic pulse.
You need to get out of there
before...
♪ ♪
- Oh, I get it.
You'd like me to frighten you
into becoming your better half.
Gladly.
- DeVoe!
- Ugh.
Children should be seen,
not heard.
I'm very sure
seeing your bestie die
would be frightening enough,
but I can't kill the Flash.
Well, not just yet.
My plan for the Enlightenment
requires his
further participation.
You, however...
are a lot less fortunate.
- Barry, he's gonna kill Gypsy!
- [grunts]
[intense music builds]
- Now, do you feel that?
- [choking]
- Around your throat?
That is
the gravitational equivalent
of my boot
busting your windpipe.
♪ ♪
- She's innocent.
Leave her alone!
- Clifford...
[suspenseful music]
This isn't part of our plan.
- Cisco, wake up!
Wake up!
- Our plan is to save them.
- Well, you can't save
everyone, my love.
- DeVoe!
- [choking]
- Perhaps.
But I won't watch you
kill an innocent life again.
♪ ♪
- Yes, you will.
- Please.
Clifford.
♪ ♪
Remember who you are.
Is this truly the lesson
you wish to bestow today?
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
[intense music builds]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Get the case.
[all gasp]
- Cynthia!
What happened?
Come on, it's okay.
Cisco:What did he do to her?
♪ ♪
Hey, talk to me.
Come on, it's okay.
- [gasps]
[panting]
♪ ♪
- You're okay.
You're okay.
- No thefts have been reported
in the last 12 hours.
- So DeVoe managed to get
everything he needed.
And we still don't know
what his next step is.
- [sighs]
- You know, he said something
about the Enlightenment.
The hell's that
supposed to mean?
- I know what he's thinking.
I know what he's planning.
We know what he's planning.
- Harry, wait.
- What?
- I can give them
the CliffsNotes version.
- No, no.
The component parts stolen
to create each satellite
will possess a 30...
cubit quantum system, okay,
and each system...
is c-capable of...
- Each system is capable
of redirecting
concentrated dark matter
back to Earth
in 10-million-megawatt bursts.
- Which...
level of which
is toxic enough to affect
each and every human brain
on the planet
and reboot them back to a...
- Reboot them.
Back to a simplified state.
- Just like mine.
- DeVoe wants to remove
the intelligence
of everyone on Earth?
- Yes.
Exactly, Barry.
Exactly right.
[helicopters whirring]
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
[energy warbling]
♪ ♪
- I'm really gonna do this.
- You treat me...
like I am the only woman
in the multiverse,
and I want more.
What is wrong with me?
♪ ♪
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
- Nothing's wrong.
- [laughs]
- Nothing at all.
♪ ♪
- I guess maybe sometimes,
one plus one just equals two,
you know?
What are you gonna do?
[chuckles]
[both laugh]
♪ ♪
Wait.
[crying]
♪ ♪
- Good-bye, Cynthia.
- Bye, Cisco.
♪ ♪
[vocal pop music plays]
all: Surprise!
- What is this?
- It's your baby shower, baby!
- This is why you were singing
"The Girl From Ipanema"
in your head all day.
- He has been planning this
for days.
- Oh, this is so sweet!
- I feel really guilty
pulling everybody away
at a time like this, but...
- It's the perfect time
to celebrate.
Surrounded by family.
- You guys!
This baby is gonna be so loved.
- Aww.
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[music playing]
♪ ♪
- Why don't you go talk to him?
[introspective piano music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, man.
Are you okay?
♪ ♪
- Not really, no.
- Do you want some space, or...
- Actually, I got plenty
of that right now.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I'm sorry for pushing
the two of you.
♪ ♪
I think you both did
the right thing, though.
♪ ♪
- Then why does it
hurt so much?
♪ ♪
- Caitlin.
Look, I don't think
you should do that again.
You could have gotten
yourself killed.
- I have to get her back.
- We will.
- No. I will.
♪ ♪
- Clifford.
Clifford.
Ow! It's fine.
It's fine.
- When the line cut out,
I came.
Immediately.
I thought I'd lost you.
- You'll never lose me,
Clifford.
You were right.
Technology has become a cancer.
Driving civilization
to consume itself.
A militia group found out
about the water purifier
that I created.
And they just killed
dozens of-of people to take it.
[dramatic music swells]
Women and children slaughtered.
For a simple piece
of technology.
♪ ♪
Your journal.
wrote of a world
where humanity forgot
that this technological menace
was capable.
But what I didn't tell you...
♪ ♪
...was that I saw the truth
in it even then.
And it frightened me.
♪ ♪
And that's why I ran.
And I'm not frightened anymore.
- You believe.
- I believe in you.
♪ ♪
Enlighten them, Clifford.
You're the only one who can.
♪ ♪
- I'm nothing without you.
- The chair will rejuvenate
your fractured scaphoid.
Prepare the satellites
for assembly.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I said, prepare the...
- No!
♪ ♪
Initially, we set out
to enlighten the world.
Now you want to rule it.
♪ ♪
I am leaving you, Clifford.
Nothing can get in or out.
- You dare orchestrate
an exodus
on the eve of humanity's
greatest reckoning?
You made a vow.
- To my husband!
♪ ♪
But my husband is dead.
The Thinker's first victim.
- The Enlightenment will come
for you too, Marlize.
I will be all that remains.
- Oh, Clifford.
You are nothing without me.
♪ ♪
- Special delivery!
Wow!
You're super pregnant!
Looks like you're due about
21 days from tonight, I'd say.
I-I mean, if I were guessing.
- Sweetheart, who is it?
- Uh, someone sent us
a diaper bag.
- It looks like
it's a gift from someone
who wanted you both to know
how special you are.
Someone who understands
that time is precious
and right now is all we've got.
- Aww.
- Relatively speaking.
- Dad?
- Hey, look what we got.
- Oh!
Who sent that? Wally?
- Wally already sent us
a bassinet,
which apparently was owned
by Moses.
- Wow.
- Was there a note?
[uncertain orchestral music]
- Who was it?
- Some delivery girl.
♪ ♪
[door closes]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head!