- Previously on
"The Flash"...
- That dagger he had negated
our powers.
- I just lost my speed.
- I'm gonna make this right,
Gracie.
Every meta will die.
- So we're dealing with
a meta-human Jack the Ripper.
- I give you Orlin Dwyer,
also known as...
- Cicada.
[camera shutter clicks]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- How many you shoot?
- [scoffs]
Shot like a hundred.
- Any of them good?
- Bof.
- Guess we'll just have to keep
shooting till we get it right.
- I guess so.
Orlin Dwyer.
- Near as we can tell,
he grew up in the Midwest.
In and out of juvie,
pretty much fell off the map,
and then popped up in
Central City a few years ago.
- Part-time employee
of Szrek Chemicals
for the last two years.
- Foreman says he keeps
to himself,
pretty much a loner,
gave a fake address.
- Did take custody of
his niece.
both: Grace Gibbons.
- After her parents were
unfortunately murdered
by a meta-human, now...
- So now we know why
Dwyer hates metas.
Once he got his powers,
he started targeting them.
- Powers he got the night of
the Enlightenment,
as we all know,
and he was struck
by a shard from the S.T.A.R.
Lab satellite explosion.
- Which was also the same
night
that Grace went into a coma.
- Where Dwyer visits her
every day, every night,
for the last three weeks.
- So he's there now.
- Yeah.
- Oui.
[rising music]
- Then let's go get him.
- "Let's go get him."
[scoffs]
How are you going to do that?
Look, as always,
I respect your spirit,
Barry Allen,
but as long as Cicada has his
dagger to dampen your powers,
there's no stopping him.
- So let's destroy his dagger.
- How are we gonna do that
unless we have some kind of
power-dampening dagger
power dampener
hidden away in storage?
- We don't,
but if we did
we'd come up with a much better
way of saying that.
- Sure, I mean, just, like,
dagger-dampener...
- Wait, yeah, that's actually...
that's decent,
'cause, you know,
you're running into...
- Just abbreviate.
P-D-P-D.
[incoherent bickering]
- Guys.
What if we could make one?
- Make one what?
- What if we can make a weapon
more powerful than his weapon?
Cicada can control his dagger,
so what we would need would be
something more powerful
than his connection to it.
- Wait, like...
like some kind of
supercharged magnet?
- Exactly.
- I don't know
if we have anything
strong enough for that.
We made Sally out of
a micro-composite alloy.
As far as satellite's go,
she's...
she was heavy-duty.
- And even if we could get
our hands on the dagger,
we'd still have to figure out
how to take the dark matter out
to negate its powers.
- Well, exactly right.
I mean, what you're suggesting
is we find an alloy...
No, no, indestructible alloy
that has super-magnetic
properties
but also has the ability
to negate dark matter.
I mean, where are we going
to find such a thing?
- The past.
- The past?
- You've already come across
everything that we need, right?
A strong alloy with
magnetic properties.
- Savitar's suit.
- Something to remove
dark matter.
- The Speed Force transmitter
that Zoom used
to steal Barry's speed.
- Yeah, but that was
his Speed Force.
- Yeah,
but those are exotic particles,
which are basically the same
thing as dark energy,
so we would just need some
of that to recalibrate it.
- Can...can you do that?
- I mean, you'd have
to infuse the transmitter
with the same kind of
dark matter.
- Like the DeVoe kind?
- More like
the Particle Accelerator kind.
- I'm sorry, we...we need to
blow up S.T.A.R. Labs again?
- No, no, not again.
We just need to go back to the
first time that it happened,
- This is gonna mess with
the timeline too much.
- No, it's not. Savitar's suit,
the transmitter,
these are all just
discarded objects in time,
so if we steal them, it won't
affect anything at all.
- Even if all of that worked,
we can't just waltz
into the hospital with
our soon-to-be-named
dampening device.
Dwyer smells us coming,
he's gone.
- Then we do a time hack.
- A time hack?
- Is when you...
- Plant something in the past
so it's available in
the future.
You go back,
you take the device,
and you hide it near
the hospital.
Somewhere it won't be found
for five years.
He won't even know it's there.
- So you and your father
go back to the past
to defeat Cicada
in the future.
[scoffs]
Quite an off-the-cuff plan
you've come up with.
- We can do this.
- No.
I can do it.
Can you guys figure out
the best dates to go back to?
- We're on it.
- You're not coming with me.
- Why?
- Every time I try something
like this I nearly get killed.
- Well, yeah, all the more
reason for me to come with you,
so that I can watch your back
so you don't get hurt.
- It's too risky
with the timeline.
All right, look, time travel,
it's complicated.
- I know,
I've already done it.
- And look what happened.
- Look.
I just want to fix what
I screwed up.
Okay, what I did.
Please, let me come with you.
- Not today.
You think she should
come with me?
- Yeah, Barry, I do.
- Iris, if I do this,
I'm going back to some
crazy times.
Savitar, Zoom, Thawne,
Speedsters...
- Who you've all outsmarted
and defeated.
Look, this was her idea, Barry.
Her solution.
And it's a good one.
So, unless you have
a better reason
why she should stay back...
let her do this.
- Okay, these are
the best of times.
Incidentally, they were also
the worst of times,
but in terms of going back,
this is it.
Savitar.
When we defeated him,
Barry phased into his suit,
destroyed it,
sending pieces of it
flying far enough away
that our past selves
wouldn't notice
if Barry took
one or two pieces of it.
What do you think?
- Absolutely,
Barry just has to get back into
the Speed Force
before the timeline catches up
and those pieces get erased
from existence.
- I'm fairly optimistic.
- Okay, what about the
Speed Force transmitter thingy?
- The night that Zoom injected
the speed force into himself,
he left the Speed Force
transmitter
in the viewing room.
- Yes, that's brilliant,
all he has to do
is make sure no one's in there
when he takes it.
- What about when the Particle
Accelerator exploded?
- Well, right before everything
went sideways,
Wells was in the cortex,
and we...
We were in the pipeline intake.
- Ronnie!
That's the best time for Barry
to go into the time vault.
He can put a piece of Savitar's
suit in the plinth,
and when the Particle
Accelerator explodes
it should infuse it with
dark matter.
- Right.
So once that's done,
we'll have all the pieces
we need to make the device.
We plant it in the hospital,
the rest is history.
- Great, let's go show Barry
and see what he thinks.
- I'll be right behind you.
Where did I leave...
[grunts]
Aha.
[screams]
- What is this?
- What is that?
Nora's journal?
What, are you stealing now?
- No...
yes, but for good reason.
Look at this code.
Have you seen this code before?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, when?
- Right after Barry came out of
the Speed Force a year ago.
- And did you decipher
the code?
- Well, my computer did
just one sentence.
- Ah, well...
- Hey, listen here,
space invader.
Why don't you try returning
the thing to her,
and then asking her?
- Of course.
Of course.
- Right.
- Makes sense.
Just return the...
- All right,
let's do it.
- Cool.
You're not gonna want
to forget this.
Had to make some adjustments
to the suit,
but I finally figured it out.
For emergencies only.
You don't want to get caught
running around the past
in your future Flash suit.
- Right.
- You might get ideas.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- [sighs]
Come on.
[optimistic music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Okay, look, follow my lead.
Don't go off book.
If anything goes wrong,
do exactly as I say.
- Do things usually go wrong?
- [scoffs]
♪ ♪
["Back in Time" by Huey Lewis
and the News plays]
♪ ♪
- What?
When am I gonna get the chance
to do that?
- Hey, game face.
- All right, so what do we do
while they're gone?
Do we stake out the hospital?
Get everything ready here
or what?
- Nothing.
They're gonna return
to the exact same moment
that they left.
- Wait, so,
they're gonna go,
but to us it'll be like they
never left?
- Yeah, time travel's weird,
isn't it?
- Here they go.
- Good luck.
- ♪ So take me away ♪
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ But you better promise me ♪
♪ I'll be back in time ♪
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Get ready.
Now!
- Are you sure
we're in the right place?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Is that Savitar?
- That's him.
♪ ♪
[groans]
Come on.
[Wraith wailing]
[ominous music]
- I only have
a few minutes left.
If I am going to die,
then everything you love
is going to die too.
- Holy shrap.
- [screams]
- [gasps]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- How's it feel to get so
close to your ascension,
and end up on the ground?
- Now I see.
It's written.
- Nothing's written.
[Wraith wailing]
- What was that?
- Time Wraith.
They protect the timeline.
I've got to get it out of here.
Nora, you're gonna have to get
the shard, okay?
Meet me in the forest where
we first arrived.
[dramatic music]
[gunshot]
♪ ♪
- Mom?
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Nice job getting that into
the Speed Force on time.
- Nothing to it.
Dad, about Savitar...
- This is right. 2016.
- How do you know?
- Because that was Zoom
with Wally.
I'm about to lose my speed.
Come on.
- [screaming]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Barry, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
- Thank you, Flash.
- Jay, stop!
If you have any humanity left,
then please let him go.
- Caitlin!
- We gotta get Caitlin back.
- Stay here.
Don't move.
Okay?
Stay.
No.
What?
- Barry...
You can't let your losses
stop you.
[pensive music]
You're the one who taught me
that.
You have to keep moving.
You have to...
push through.
You have to find a way.
You have to fight.
So that nothing, ever,
will hold you back, Barry.
Do what you can, and I know
you lost your speed,
but everyone's here to help.
My dad, Cisco, Harry...
me.
- Come on. Come on.
[energy hums]
- Well, you change quickly.
- What?
- Out of your suit.
- Yeah, no, I...
Yeah, it was, just too weird
being in it without my speed.
- Well, that's your own
damn fault, isn't it?
- I guess so.
- I know so.
- What are you looking for?
- I'm looking for anything
to help me find my daughter.
- All right, just...
♪ ♪
I don't have my daughter.
You don't have your speed.
Zoom has Caitlin,
and this whole thing...this
whole thing...
is going to hell
in a hand basket...
- No, no, wait, wait, wait!
Her frequency.
- What?
- Jesse's frequency.
People from Earth-2 vibrate
at a different frequency.
Maybe you could track her
that way.
- Figure out how to find Snow.
- [sighs]
- Did you get it?
- I got it.
Let's build this thing.
♪ ♪
- You're not going anywhere,
Flash.
- You got what you want,
Solomon.
- And who is this?
Another Speedster.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[glass cracks]
- No, no, no!
Damn it!
I knew we shouldn't have
done this.
Now we have no way to stop
Cicada.
I mean, I don't even know
when we are.
- Dad, Dad, we can fix this.
- I can't fix this, Nora.
Cisco can't even fix this.
This is Wells' tech.
- Well, let's go back to Wells.
- We can't.
Harry's...
Harry's mind isn't
what it used to be.
- No, I don't mean that Wells.
I mean the one that built
the Particle Accelerator.
- That's not Wells.
That is Eobard Thawne,
the Reverse-Flash.
- I know, it's just,
he's really smart.
So I thought maybe we could
convince him to help us.
- No, okay, look, no.
The only person Thawne ever
helps is himself.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, I just thought
that maybe...
What?
- I know when we are.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Oh...
- Leave him. Leave him.
The less we mess...
- Mess with the timeline.
I know.
- I know what this is.
Three years ago
I traveled back to this day
to get Thawne's help.
- So you have done it before.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- Well...
things just got a lot more
complicated, didn't they?
♪ ♪
Barry Allen.
But which Barry Allen?
Clearly you're...
from a lot later than this one.
- Way later.
Who's your friend?
Let me guess.
Jesse Chambers.
No.
Maybe Lawrence.
Wait.
Danica Williams.
- It doesn't matter who she is.
- She's your daughter.
You've brought me
your daughter.
It's, um...
Dawn, if I'm not mistaken.
- Nora.
Oh, that's nice.
At least you still have one.
What, Nora,
time travel's so weird.
What do you want?
- I need you to fix this
for me.
- No...
No, if you're here...
And he's here...
that means...
- You don't get home.
- I get home!
I get home.
I go home!
I get everything...
- You don't go home, Thawne.
Unless you help me.
♪ ♪
- What do you want?
- Like I said,
you're gonna fix this for me.
- To do what?
- Drain dark matter.
- Who's dark matter?
- None of your business.
- It is my business.
- No, it's not.
- There's no chance
that I help you...
- It's none of your business...
- Cicada's!
- Cicada's.
The one who got away.
You want to destroy
Cicada's dagger, don't you?
- We want to save lives.
- [laughing]
You want to save lives.
[laughs]
I bet you do.
Especially your own, right,
Barry Allen?
- Look, that me,
he's gonna wake up soon.
He sees me standing here,
your whole timeline
is gonna be blown to hell.
You're never gonna get home.
You know that's true!
- I know!
I know!
♪ ♪
Where are my manners?
Can I get you a cup of water?
So who made this?
- Someone smarter than you.
- [laughs]
I doubt that.
You know, Allen,
for your plan to work,
you're gonna actually
gonna have to have his dagger
in your possession...
- We've got that covered.
- You got that covered.
How's that?
- With this.
- Is that...
- It's a piece
of Savitar's suit, yeah.
- Hmm.
You know what's funny about
your dad, Nora,
is he hates me.
Hates me with a passion,
and yet a version of him,
this Savitar,
is a much bigger jerk
than I ever was.
Did you see the face?
Did you...[laughs]
did you see the, like,
pizza face.
- Can you hurry up?
- Yeah, I'll hurry up.
I gotta tell you, Allen,
using Savitar's suit,
it's a smart idea.
- It was hers.
- Clever girl.
Oops.
Gotta go.
[sighs]
I still look forward to seeing
how this all pans out.
Nora.
- Hey, Dad...
- It's time to go back to
the night it all began.
Come on.
- Tonight, the future begins.
The work my team and I
will do here
will change our understanding
of physics,
will bring about
advancements in power,
advancements in medicine,
and trust me, that future will
be here faster than you think.
[applause]
[bell dings]
- Uh, why are we going
this way?
Why don't we just speed into
the time vault?
- Because it's a big moment,
Nora.
Thawne's been planning
this night for 14 years.
If we use our speed,
he'll feel it.
- Feel a disturbance
in the Speed Force.
- I wouldn't do that.
[creature growling softly]
- Dr. Wells,
the accelerator is primed
and ready for
particle injection.
- I feel I should say
something profound like,
"One small step for man."
- What's happening?
- Wells is about to blow up
the city.
- All I can think of to say
is I feel like
I've waited for this day
for centuries.
Without further ado.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Dr. Wells?
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm great.
[sighs]
I'm...
Caitlin, do you think
you could have Ronnie
run the Particle Accelerator
parameter numbers
just one more time?
Just for good measure.
- Sure.
- Great.
And, Caitlin,
the bottle of Dom
we've been saving.
- Is today the day?
- I think today might be
the day.
- I'll go grab it.
- Great, be along in a minute.
- You got us on pins
and needles here, Dr. Wells.
- Exciting isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Well, it's all thanks
to the team, right?
Caitlin, fiancé Ronnie,
Hartley.
- Hmm.
- Hartley contributed.
Especially you, Cisco.
I have to say I have a vibe
about you.
About what you're destined
to become.
I want you to know
I'm very eager
to be along for that adventure.
- Thank you, Dr. Wells.
That means a great deal.
♪ ♪
- Oh, did you...
- I didn't.
Shall we just go turn
on an accelerator
and pop some champagne?
- I think...
- Okay.
- He's gone.
♪ ♪
- Good evening, Barry Allen.
I was not expecting you
this soon.
- She knows you?
- I know you as well,
Nora West-Allen.
Also known as XS.
Fifth recruit in the rebooted
Legion of...
- Gideon,
the particle accelerator
is about to explode.
I need you to recalibrate
the system's chain reaction
so some of the dark matter is
repositioned into this vial,
and record no reports of
this...
♪ ♪
Nora!
[sighs]
- You really hate him,
don't you?
- Do you not know what he did?
- I know he was your archenemy.
- He killed my mother...
in our home
when I was 11 years old.
An 11-year-old boy.
You know why he did it?
He thought if I suffered
a tragedy
that was horrific enough,
I'd never recover
and never become The Flash.
- I...I didn't know that.
- There's probably a lot
that's happened to me
that's not in The Flash museum.
- It's why you didn't want me
to come with you, isn't it?
It's not because
it was dangerous
or because of the timeline
but because you didn't want me
to know these awful things
about you
so it's not what I would
remember most when I went back.
You don't have to protect me
from this stuff.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
- Yes, yes, I do.
You're my daughter.
- Yeah, and you're my father,
and I just want to know
my father.
[nostalgic music]
♪ ♪
- Recalibration complete.
[ground quaking]
- Here we go.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Dark matter retrieval
successful.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Let's go get our time
back in place.
- Spinal cord trauma,
he's lost all feeling
to his lower quadrants.
- That's Harrison Wells.
Dr. Wells, I need you
to squeeze my hand.
That's a good sign.
- 24-year-old male,
struck by lightning.
- Need a full trauma panel.
Get him to bay one.
What is happening to
this city?
- Grace's room is on
the fourth floor.
- This should work.
Let's put it right here.
♪ ♪
- We did it.
- Come on.
["Back in Time" by Huey Lewis
and the News]
- ♪ Gotta be back in time ♪
- Did you even go?
[both laugh]
- Told you time travel
was weird.
- Everything worked?
- Yeah.
- Is Dwyer still at
the hospital?
- Hasn't left her side.
- Did you plant
the transmitter?
- Yeah, we sure did.
- Let's go get Cicada.
- ♪ Back in time ♪
[cautious music]
♪ ♪
[tapping on metal]
- You ready, Barry?
- I'm ready.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Cicada.
- Is that what you call me?
- Not all meta-humans
are responsible for what
happened to Grace.
- Yes, they are.
The destruction they cause,
the death,
the pain.
- I know about pain and death,
taking it out on the world.
That's not gonna help.
Think about Grace.
- She's all I think about,
Flash.
And I'm making the world safe
for her.
Every meta-human must go.
- Then what about you?
You're a meta-human now.
- I am,
and after you're gone,
I'll join you.
All four of you.
♪ ♪
- Come on, work.
- It worked.
- Let's see how you like it.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Cisco, now.
- Breach it out of here!
- [laughs]
- Gotcha.
- Oh, man.
You look like you're having
a day.
Is it 'cause I just threw
your dagger into outer space
or 'cause you're just now
realizing you didn't kill me?
- We stopped you.
- You stopped nothing.
[roars]
- The satellite's tracking
the dagger
back through the exosphere.
- Guys, Cicada's recalling
the dagger back from space.
♪ ♪
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
- This ends now.
- Barry!
- No!
Let's dance, cricket freak.
♪ ♪
- Dwyer's not popping up
in facial recognition.
- And there's no dark matter
traces from his dagger.
- Well, he won't stay away from
his niece for long,
and when he returns,
we'll be ready.
- Yeah, we will,
thanks to Killer Frost.
- I don't understand.
How can she still come out?
- She didn't come from
dark matter,
so I guess she's immune
to Cicada's dagger.
She just might be the key
to stopping Cicada for good.
- Maybe we should go
check in with her.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
- Cricket freak, huh?
- Just came out.
[soft music]
- Proud of you.
♪ ♪
- Hey, "Sher-loke."
- Sherloque.
Tea?
- No, thank you.
Have you see my...
- Journal.
- Yeah.
- Forgive me,
but couldn't help but notice
this composition.
- That's really nothing
special.
- But it...
feels like something special.
I don't like to brag,
but I speak a lot of languages
and yet this one...
this one I don't recognize.
- It's a time language.
- Time language, really?
- It's used to record events
regardless of changes
in the timeline
so no matter what happens
I'll always remember my dad.
- Hmm, where does one learn
something like that?
Time travel school?
- I created it, actually.
- You created it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Clever girl.
I forget myself.
This is yours.
♪ ♪
[indistinct conversation]
[laughter]
[nostalgic music]
♪ ♪
- They were the best.
- Dad.
Dad, I didn't...
- It's all right.
I understand.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Do you ever think
about stopping
what's about to happen?
- Every day.
- Thanks for bringing me
with you today.
It meant a lot.
- I'm glad you came.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Old Man,
come on.
Come on.
[comforting music]
♪ ♪
- Old Man?
- Good evening,
Nora West-Allen.
- Gideon, another data entry.
- Entry uploaded and recorded.
Shall I send it to
the same recipient?
- Yes.
- Entry sent.
Would you like assistance
with anything else?
- Yes, send a personal message
from me.
- What would you like it
to say?
- Actually, I'll deliver
it myself.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
We need to talk.
- Yes, Nora.
Yes, we do.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[explosions booming]
- [groaning]
♪ ♪
- You failed.
- Why are you doing this?
- You did this to yourself,
and now,
all of you will perish.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.