My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
I'm in full-on vibe mode right now.
I wasn't fast enough
to protect Iris.
- I felt slower.
- I did it.
I stole your speed. I gave it to Zoom.
Give me back my daughter.
Bring me the rest of Flash's speed.
I told you we're a team.
We're going to help you save Jesse.
We're going to Earth-2.
Journal log entry one-fifteen.
My last entry on this earth.
We're closing the breaches. All of them.
Soon, every portal between this earth
and mine will no longer exist.
I've become distracted by this earth.
By its problems. Its people.
Twenty-nine.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-seven.
Twenty-six.
But the one thing I never
lost track of was you, Jesse.
You are my conscience. My beating heart.
You're the reason I've made it this far
in my fight against Zoom.
And now, I Just need you to hang on,
hang on a little bit longer.
Because I'm coming to get you.
And this time,
I'm not coming alone.
Bam! Uh! That's how it's done.
Whoo!
He shoots. He scores.
- Not bad for a guy who got a C in gym.
- D plus.
Straight up F. Right here.
I can't believe it.
We closed all the breaches.
All except the one.
Our last way to Earth-2.
Ready?
Yeah. I just have a few things
to take care of first.
Just a reminder, Allen. Clock's ticking.
It always is.
You know, you haven't made lasagna
since I left for college.
Well, college is a hell of a lot closer
than another Earth.
- Ah.
- Hey. Did you tell Henry?
No. All right, look, if he knew,
he would just try to talk me out of it,
and he probably would so...
Dad, can you give us a minute?
Yeah. I'll make us some coffee.
Look, Iris, I know that this is...
Nuts is the only word
I can think of right now,
but it's not like I've never done
anything dangerous before.
Look, I, I get why you're doing this.
Innocent people are in danger.
That's always been the direction
that you've run in.
Even, even when you ran
a little bit slower.
I Just... I want to make sure
that you're not doing this
because you think that you don't have
anything left here anymore.
This isn't about Patty.
It's not.
I mean, of course,
you know, I miss her. A lot.
But I know what I have here.
I love my life.
I love myjob, being the Flash.
I love you and Joe.
I'm not trying to escape.
I promise.
Go win, Barry.
And then come home.
I will.
All right, Barry, listen to me.
You're about to go through
the looking glass.
You're gonna see things that look
and feel familiar, but they're not.
Up is down, black is white.
And do not let yourself
get sucked in emotionally.
And good luck.
Yeah. Look,
ifwe're not back in forty-eight hours,
that means that Zoom has us.
If that happens,
you have to close the breach.
We're not gonna do that.
You get yourself back here
in one piece, all right?
- Don't make me come and get you.
- No.
I wrote this for my parents and Dante.
If I don't come back,
make sure you get it to them?
Cisco, you're coming back.
Caitlin, please.
- Okay, I will.
- Thank you.
- Be careful, okay?
- Yeah.
- You too, Harry.
- Thanks, Snow.
I hope you get your daughter back.
I'll make sure you get your son back.
You don't have to do this.
Yeah, I do.
Is anybody else feeling panic right now?
I chickened out of bungee jumping
when I was eighteen.
But this is categorically a lot scarier.
Once I turn the speed cannon on,
the three of you will be
able to pass through unharmed.
But Barry, you need to make sure
you keep your speed up.
Mmm-hmm.
- I got no spit.
- Jaws.
And I'm not quoting Jaws. I mean
my mouth is really dry right now.
Do not get distracted by
anything you see along the way.
What are we going to see?
Everything.
Do it, Jay.
Okay. Let's go.
Caitlin, look out!
- Are you okay?
- Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
What happened?
With the rest
of the breaches closed,
the energy surge to this last remaining
breach must have destabilized it.
What does that mean?
As long as it's unstable, Barry and Cisco
will be trapped over there.
Holy 2001.
I feel like
I just opened my third eye.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
Wow.
Welcome to Earth-2.
Toto, I've got a feeling
we're not in Kansas anymore.
This is amazing.
Half these things are
just ideas on our earth.
- Come here.
- I mean...
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
- Ramon.
- What?
Not a sight-seeing tour.
Speak for yourself. We want our grandkids
to know we did cool stuff.
- Doctor Wells. Welcome back.
- Henry.
- We weren't expecting you.
- Aah!
Yes, I didn't tell anyone
I was coming back.
Well, I thought you might've left town
with all that's been happening.
- Right.
- Are your friends okay?
Yes, they're...
They're fine. They're excitable.
- This is...
- Henry Hewitt. Lab assistant.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
And, you. I'm Barry. This is Cisco.
I'm Cisco.
And you are just a nice, normal guy.
Okay. Um...
Doctor Wells, will you and your visitors
be needing the conference room?
Not necessary, Henry.
Our visit will be short.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you, sir.
He's a bad guy on Earth-1.
He looksjust like him.
A reminder that a
city-wide curfew has been issued.
No unauthorized person
is to be out after 9 p.m.
A recent increase in Zoom attacks
has led Mayor Snart to extend the curfew.
The curfew was first issued
after a series of terror attacks
throughout the city...
It's worse.
It's worse than when I left.
Zoom's turned up his reign of terror.
All right. Then let's find Zoom. Fast.
Cisco, do your thing.
All right, Zoom.
You can run, but you can't hide.
All right. You know what?
You guys are crowding
my space a little bit.
I can't perform like this
under pressure. Okay?
If you could you just step back
just a little bit?
- I need to do my thing.
- All right.
- My mojo. Thank you.
- Yes, all right.
Take two.
Hmm. Ha.
All right, Zoom.
You can run...
- Ramon! What's happening?
- You know, I don't know, okay?
I can't see anything.
I don't know what's wrong.
Maybe I lost my powers.
I didn't lose my powers.
Why would you lose your powers?
Here we go.
The wavelength trigger's not responding.
- But that only happens if...
- The frequency is imbalanced.
What?
Our earth vibrates
at a different frequency than yours.
Harry, without that frequency...
We're up a creek.
The latest attack
was orchestrated by Zoom.
And we understand that
citizens of Central City are scared
but I can assure you,
the CCPD has been working diligently
- That's me.
- On thwarting the meta-humans
- Yeah, it is.
- Under the leadership of Detective West.
We will stop Zoom. That's a promise.
The leadership of Detective West.
So Joe's still a cop here.
Yeah, but more importantly,
I'm still a CSI.
I have a plan.
Whatjust happened?
Doppelgénger!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How did I get here?
Who are, who are you?
How do you look like me?
Allen, what are you doing?
Harrison Wells.
The Harrison Wells!
Oh, my God, am I in S.T.A.R. Labs?
Okay, I have no idea
what is going on here,
but I've always wanted to meet you.
Your thesis on string phenomenology
was revolutionary to me.
Oh, man.
I had the magazine laminated
so I could keep it. I Just wanna emulate.
That's incredible.
I won an award for it. Right over there.
Do you see?
Oh, it's beauti...
What did you do? What's wrong with you?
Have you turned into an evil you?
Relax. I Just knocked him out.
Oh. But why'd you even
bring him over here?
So he could become him.
While you guys work on the goggles,
I will go to CCPD as him,
see if I can figure out what information
they have on Zoom's previous sightings.
We can use those sightings
to triangulate Zoom's hideout.
Okay, that's a good plan.
Just remember what Jay said, okay?
Things here are all sorts of trippy.
Look, I'll be fine.
I can handle it.
Easy.
Whoa!
Whoa.
This is crazy.
Get your hands off me!
Captain?
Look, I don't know nothin'
so I ain't sayin' nothin'!
- Okay.
- Deadshot, wh...
That's not funny, Allen.
I hate that nickname.
Okay, look, I know I'm not, I'm not
the best shot in the department but...
Not the best? Lawton, you are
the worst shot in the entire department.
Hey, why don't you book Singh here
and I'll be in there in a moment.
- Whatever you say, partner.
- Mm.
Come on.
Oh, and, just for the record,
My marksmanship proficiency ratings
went up by two points last month.
All right?
Two points! Whoo!
Iris.
You're Detective West?
The one, the only.
- Yeah.
- Can I see you for a second CSI Allen?
Mm.
What are you doing?
What?
I think a little office PDA between
a husband and wife is okay.
Husband and wife.
Yeah, that's what happens
when you do the vows, exchange the rings.
- Where is your ring?
- I...
People should know
that you're a taken man.
That's so weird.
- What's that?
- My meta-human alert app.
It thinks that you're a meta-human.
That is so weird.
Yeah. Must be on the fritz.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
Home.
Come on.
Where do you people get off
robbing Central City's Royal Bank?
This town belongs to Zoom.
And those of us he deems worthy enough
to enforce his will.
Here! Take it!
Thanks a million.
Or should I say two?
No. Wait.
Please don't hurt me.
Hurt you? I Just want to give you a kiss.
Now, what did I tell you about
watching that behind?
I thought that was your job.
Good thing, the only man I can kiss
is the only one I want to.
Just got word.
Some breachers came through.
Ooh, you know my favorite thing
to do is kill people from other Earths.
Today's your lucky day.
Oh, my gosh.
This is nice.
Our home, I mean. I forgot, I guess.
What is wrong with you?
You've been acting weird all day.
Um,
I'm just not myself, I guess.
Your mom called.
Allen residence.
Hello?
Uh, hello?
Mom.
Well, you certainly took your time
calling back.
Yeah. I'm sorry about that.
Thank you so much for
the anniversary tickets to Atlantis.
Your dad and I have always wanted to go.
I'm really glad you liked them.
Are you okay?
You sound kind of strange.
I'm fine. I'm...
Hey, lknow. Maybe Ishould give
the plane tickets to you and Iris.
A nice little romantic getaway.
You two could get started on
giving me a grandchild.
No, I want you to use them.
I'm really glad to hear you happy, Mom.
Aw. I love you, Barry.
I love you, too.
Okay. Bye-bye, honey-
Baby, what's wrong?
Um, nothing.
I was just, uh... I mean,
it was just good to talk to my mom.
We should get ready, yeah?
Yeah. All right.
Where is he? Where is he?
I don't know. I can't find him anywhere.
Yeah, well, he better show up soon
because he's been gone for hours.
We only have so many of those left
before Zoom needs the speed.
You're talking about Barry.
Yeah.
Yeah, don't worry about him.
He'll be fine.
Who'd you think I was talking about?
- I thought you were talking about me.
- You?
Yeah. 'Cause we found Barry's double,
so where the hell am I?
You know, I always thought,
in another life, I was, like,
I don't know, like, a really wealthy,
famous inventor.
You know, sort of
like the Earth-2 Elon Musk.
Only with less RBF, obviously.
Well, here's some advice for you.
How about spending
more time looking for Zoom
and less time worrying about what someone,
who is not you, is doing with their life.
Some things that happened
for the first time
Seem to be happening again
And so it seems that we have met before
And laughed before
And loved before
Whoa. Joe can sing.
- He's the best.
- Right.
But who knows, baby now, who knows
Yeah, who knows
Where or when
Whoo.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
Mm. Oh, yeah.
- Joe, hey!
- Lt's Joseph, Bartholomew.
Pop, be nice. You too, babe.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
So you're a singer!
So you're still an idiot.
Are you upset with me?
Or you just don't like me.
Have you lost your mind?
Central City is going to
hell-in-a-hand basket
because this lunatic, Zoom,
is running around, killing folks,
and you got my daughter
on the front lines.
Wait, wha... Me?
It is always been about you, Bartholomew.
You're the most selfish person
I've ever met, and I'm a musician.
We're all selfish.
You wanted to get your PhD
so you could further your career,
she had to become a police officer
to pay your tuition.
We both know that she'd be safer
going back to write at the newspaper.
Oh, Dad, please stop.
CCPN was an internship.
All I did was get coffee for real writers.
Being a cop, like Grandpa, is what I love.
You raised me to be tough, and I am.
Everything's fine.
I mean, we're here to have fun, right?
Right. Everything's great.
How's it going?
Uh, slow. Which is not a good adjective
when it comes to a speed cannon.
Well, we got another problem.
Why do we always have to have
another problem?
You've gotta see this!
Somebody call the Flash!
His name is Adam Fells
but he calls himself Geomancer.
So this meta-human is a breacher?
No. Fells died on my Earth.
This must be his Earth-1 doppelganger.
Well, at least now that we know his name.
Might be a little easier
to track him down.
Yeah, but with Barry gone,
how are we gonna stop him
even if we do find him?
Jay, if you could shoot yourself up
with that stuff, or was it Velocity...
- Velocity-Six?
- I cannot take V-Six.
But it gave you your speed back
long enough to get that bullet
out of Wells. Saved his life.
Joe, don't ask me
to take Velocity-Six again.
Look, Jay, I'm not trying
to tell you what to do.
But Barry is protecting your world,
and our world needs
a Flash right about now.
Jay.
Caitlin, I like the way
you look at me.
With warmth and pride.
And I'm not, I'm not worthy of those.
- Yes, you are.
- No. I did a terrible thing, Caitlin.
When my world's
Particle Accelerator went off,
I became a speedster.
I became the Fastest Man Alive.
Only, only it wasn't enough for me.
I wasn't fast enough.
So I figured
with my scientific background,
I could increase my powers.
I did.
So you've taken Velocity-Six before.
Yes.
But there were some
unforeseen side effects.
This is why
you didn't want Barry to take it.
Or even know about it.
Zoom never stole your speed.
This is what's making you sick.
Velocity-Six is killing you.
I wasn't lying when I said
that stuff was dangerous.
I've made so many mistakes.
You have something now
that you've never had before.
Me.
And I'm going to figure this out.
My funny valentine
Sweet comic valentine
Can we talk some more about
why Joseph doesn't like me?
What's there to talk about?
I mean, you can't stand him either.
- Right.
- Look...
I can love you both
even if you don't love each other.
My meta-human warning app.
Don't stop singing, old man.
That's our song.
So,
which one of you lounge lizards
is in the wrong universe?
Hmm? Show of hands.
Don't be shy.
Hey, no, no. Hey, no, no, don't.
Hey, handsome.
You got something you want to tell me?
- No.
- No?
Baby, no one's talking to me.
What if I make them scream?
CCPD! Everyone get out of here!
- All right, go, go.
- You are both under arrest!
Ladies first.
Caitlin.
I haven't heard that name in a long time.
But that is your name, isn't it?
Your real name. Please.
I know you. Don't do this.
If you knew me at all,
you would know
that I hate the name "Caitlin."
I'm Killer Frost.
Go, all right. Go, go!
Iris, look out!
Dad! Oh, my God.
Well, hello, breacher.
He's a speedster, babe.
Oh, I'm shivering.
I've been dying to kill the Flash.
I don't want to hurt you.
Trust me. You won't.
Kill him!
Come on.
God, this is making me so hot!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
This ain't over, breacher.
Barry!
Oh, my God.
Dad. Barry.
- Killer Frost and Deathstorm.
- You know them?
More importantly, they know you now.
They know that you're here.
So Caitlin and Ronnie's
doppelgangers are evil?
Those are some dope names, though.
This was supposed to be
a surgical mission, Allen.
Find Zoom's lair. Rescue Jesse.
Get in, get out. Not get involved.
All right, well look, I am involved, okay?
Joe is in the hospital.
They nearly killed him.
No, he isn't. Joe West, your Joe West,
is alive and safe on your earth.
So is Caitlin, so is Iris.
These people, Barry,
they're mere reflections.
As far as your life is concerned,
they don't exist.
Killer Frost, Deathstorm,
they know that you're here,
and it's not long before Zoom does too
and then my daughter's dead.
And that's on you.
Jesse still has time, okay?
Iris and Joe need me now.
- She is not Iris!
- I have to get back to them.
She is Iris! Okay? She is to me.
No matter what Universe I am in,
they are my family.
I would think by now, you should get
how important family is.
I'm going, Wells. I have to.
Find Zoom.
Iran Adam Fells through BCI.
Not exactly a model citizen
before he was a meta-human.
Multiple counts of robbery and assault.
Well, if he thinks he's gonna use my city
for a steel cage death match
with the Flash,
he's got another thing coming.
Hey, what are you doing here? Wait.
Were we supposed to meet up or something?
Nah, I was just nearby.
Everybody Okay?
Fells has been spotted.
Pasko and fourth. Go.
I got to go, son.
Joe...
Mm.
Dad, are you okay?
Damn meta-humans.
Only thing I hate more...
Is hospitals.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm just worried about you.
There's a first.
Baby...
Yeah, yeah.
You ever notice every time,
just before I do a number,
I close my eyes for a hot second,
and I take a deep breath.
You ever wonder what I was doing?
Trying to remember the lyrics?
I say a little mantra to myself
every time before I sing.
"This one is for Iris."
"My baby girl."
Every song's for you, baby.
Every single one.
Dad, don't talk like this, okay?
Barth... Barry.
Yeah.
You take care of her.
Dad!
Dad! Nurse!
Doctor! Nurse! Dad!
Iris.
No! No! No!
No! No!
It's okay.
Oh, damn it. Ugh.
You don't have to do this, Lawton.
We're partners, right?
You've always had my back.
And I've got yours.
Oh, Iris.
- Do I know you?
- Does she know me?
Uh, this is my good friend, Cisco Ramon.
- "Good friend"?
- Yeah.
Cisco works at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and he has built a weapon that he believes
we can use to neutralize, um,
Killer Frost's powers.
Great. Thanks. I'll take it.
Uh, please, I should really take this.
All right.
One of my snitches gave me a lead
on Killer Frost and Deathstorm's location.
We're going to bring them in.
Okay. I'm coming with you, Iris.
No, Barry. I Just lost my father.
I cannot lose my husband too.
All right. Well, Cisco is the only one
that knows how to operate the device.
So you have to take him.
I can't put a civilian in harm's way.
Look, I've seen fire and I've seen rain.
I can handle myself, okay?
Mrs. West Allen.
I love you.
I love you too.
- Lawton, let's move!
- Yeah.
Uh...
We got to work on finding Jesse.
Are you sure this is
what you want to be doing?
Iam, all right?
Right now, we have to help Iris.
Just make sure no one else gets hurt.
CCPD! It's over, Fells.
No offense to you boys in blue
but I'm waiting on the man in red.
You better hope the Flash doesn't show up,
or you're finished.
See, that's funny.
I don't think he will show.
I've been causing tremors for days
and no sign of him.
I think he's gone.
What is it they say in boxing?
Let's get ready to rumble!
What the...
I heard you were looking for the Flash.
Looks like the Velocity-Seven is working.
Now go get him!
- That's a new one.
- Is that all you have?
You don't ever want to see all I have.
The Velocity-Seven's wearing off!
You've heard what an eight
on the Richter scale can do to a city.
Imagine what it's going to do
to your skull.
Are you hurt?
Only my pride.
And my body.
Pride and my body.
Are you really sure this is the place?
Maybe you should stay in the car, Lawton.
Look alive, gents.
Hey, maybe, maybe your snitch was wrong.
I mean, maybe they're not even here.
No, they're here.
You didn't knock.
How rude.
Drop them.
Ronnie?
Is Martin Stein in there?
Oh, I haven't let him out in years.
He doesn't talk much anymore.
You killed my father, you evil bitch.
He shouldn't have pal-ed
around with a breacher.
That's a big no-no
as far as Zoom's concerned.
I can't believe you two work for Zoom.
No, they work for me.
Iwork for Zoom.
Who the hell are you?
Well, that's funny.
I wasjust going to ask you
the same thing.
D0ppel... '... 93r1ger.
What the hell is going on here?
Are you two related to each other?
Oh, I knew there was another "me" here!
And I knew you were coming, Cisco.
Even before you entered the breach
and set foot on this world.
See, we're all connected, Francisco.
The name is Vibe.
Reverb.
Actually not the worst name
you could've come up with.
But not the best.
I've been watching you, Vibe.
And I have to say,
I am extremely disappointed.
Yeah? I know the feeling.
I'm not sure what's worse.
The fact that you're part of Zoom's gang
or that weird samurai situation you got
going on on the top of your head there.
Listen to this.
What if Zoom wasn't
running the show anymore?
- What do you mean?
- You don't even know how powerful you are.
All you use your powers for
are these cheap parlor tricks,
when you, you could be a God.
We could be Gods.
Are you Cloud City Vadering me right now?
Are you out ofyour mind?
Let's turn them over to Zoom.
Speak to me like that again
and I will shatter your entire nervous
system without breaking a sweat.
So...
Vibe...
D0 you wanna run Central City?
What do you say?
I say...
Flash save us!
Hey. That didn't hurt you, did it?
- No. Why would it?
- I don't know.
And who the hell are you?
Look, Detective,
just get out of here, all right?
No. Not without them!
Stay here!
Round two.
Look, Mirror Mirror, I already told you.
I'm not going to the dark side with you.
You're a rotten shot.
I'm not.
Are you telling me I can do that?
I can show you.
No!
Stop! The both of you!
Zoom wanted him alive!
You know what Zoom will do
if you don't obey him!
No!
That.
What did I say you should do
if you encountered a speedster?
Leave him unharmed.
Does this look unharmed to you?
I'm happy to see
at least one of you knows their place.
Barry!
No.
Sorry. Did I forget to say
this might sting?
It's not my first road rash.
I'm a speedster, remember?
You made sure
no one will forget that tonight.
Thanks to you.
Velocity-Seven held up pretty well.
Moving on to Velocity-Eight.
I'm gonna figure it out. I swear.
I just need you to figure out
how to restabilize the breach.
Barry, Cisco, and Wells
still have twenty-four hours to go.
So we have one day,
or they could be stuck there forever.
Jesse.Jesse.
Hey. I'm here with your dad.
We're gonna get you out of here,
all right? I promise.
It's not wise to make promises
you can't keep, Flash.
Look around.
This is the last place
you'll ever see.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::