Cleaned, corrected, HI removed
and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on the Flash...
if you love me,
You'll tell me
what is going on with you.
Keeping her in the dark
keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
Harrison Wells is
the Reverse-Flash.
15 years ago, Harrison and I
were thick as thieves.
We were promising
young scientists,
And then everything changed
after Tess died.
- Who are you?
- My name is Eobard Thawne.
In the year 2020,
you and your wife
Successfully launched
a particle accelerator
That changed the course
of history.
I need it to happen
a bit sooner
If I'm going to get back.
After that day,
Harrison Wells became
a completely different person.
I'm getting faster,
faster than I've ever been,
And I wonder if it's because
lately something's chasing me.
I know what it is
that's stalking me.
It's my past.
It's getting closer,
and as fast as I am,
I can't help but feel like
my past
Has almost caught up with me.
- Where's Barry?
- He should be here any second.
I sent him out for...
Pizza!
- What?
- From Coast City?
Supposedly the best
in the west.
Why did I not
think of this before?
Come to papa.
Caitlin?
I'm not hungry.
Okay, six months
of investigating Harrison Wells
Has led us nowhere,
so we're going back
To the beginning to see
what we can find out.
What does that mean?
Road trip, baby.
Joe and Cisco are going
to go to Starling City.
Starling City?
What for?
To investigate
the car accident
That Dr. Wells was in
with Tess Morgan 15 years ago.
I-I don't understand.
Why?
Dr. McGee said that
after Wells's accident,
He became like
a complete stranger.
Just a different person
entirely.
Because the love
of his life died?
You of all people
can understand how grief
Can change a person.
Caitlin, we believe
that Dr. Wells
Is the Reverse-Flash
and killed Barry's mother,
And he may have done
the same thing to Tess Morgan.
We have to learn everything
we can about that night.
See where it leads us.
Oh, um, can you cover for me
With Dr. Wells?
You mean lie?
Yeah.
I need some air.
Whoa... hey, Caitlin...
Doesn't look like
Caitlin's with us.
No, she's with us.
I'll talk to her.
What do you
want us to do here?
Business as usual
while we're gone.
Copy that.
Well, I want to wish you
good luck over there,
But I'm also scared
of what you might find.
Scared is a good thing.
Scared keeps us alive.
Can you get the door, Nina?
- Nina?
- Oh.
Sorry.
Wrapped up
in my own little world.
Late night?
Just one more thing to do
before I make my escape.
- See you tomorrow.
- Night.
So let's go over this again.
This is you on the
surveillance footage, correct?
It looks like me.
But it's not me.
I left work early yesterday.
Ask my husband.
Footage doesn't lie.
Your husband might.
That's not me.
No priors, no arrests,
not even a speeding ticket.
And everyone who knows
this woman,
Coworkers, neighbors,
Say she's the kindest,
nicest,
Most honest woman
they've ever met.
So, unless she woke up
this morning
And out of nowhere
decided to become a criminal...
Maybe we should be
looking for a meta-human.
Yeah.
One that can control
people's minds.
Coerce them into
becoming thieves.
Is that possible?
Is that a real question?
Hi, Barry.
Hey.
Have you, um, seen my dad?
Captain Singh says he took a
couple of days off,
And he hasn't been home.
I didn't ask.
Apparently he's taking
a couple of personal days.
Like father, like daughter
I guess.
I'm sorry.
When are you coming home?
When it starts to feel
like a home again.
You better pray Joe and Cisco
find something on Wells
At that accident site, Barry,
Because I am just about done
lying to Iris.
About all of this.
Yeah.
I recently inherited
the entire collection.
Beautiful.
Let me grab my microscope.
Of course.
9-1-1.
Emergency.
This is Dominic over at
Abbott jewelers.
I've got a guy in here
trying to sell stolen diamonds.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
Hey, look, uh...
Can we talk about last night?
There's nothing
to talk about.
Yeah, there is actually.
Caitlin, look,
I know after everything
Dr. Wells has done
For all of us, it's hard to wrap
your head around this,
But I need you
to see the truth.
The truth?
The truth is that he saved
your life multiple times.
Look, I know.
But if I'm right about this...
If, Barry, if.
And before I can believe
any of this,
I'm gonna need to
see some proof.
Proof?
Proof of what?
W... we may have another
meta-human case on our hands.
Ah. We are always happy
to help, Barry, as you know.
Have you heard from Cisco?
He hasn't arrived yet.
Uh, he has to help Dante,
his brother.
He might need a few days off.
Ah, well.
All right.
Eddie.
Hey, I got a call about a guy
Selling some of the jewelry
Stolen from the bank
last night.
Could be the teller's partner.
I think he's made me.
I could use the Flash's help.
Be right there.
Oh!
You can't outrun me.
I won't have to.
Well, that was new.
A shape-shifter?
Yeah, I literally saw
a grown man, like,
M... morph into
a teenage girl.
That's fascinating.
Today's physicists have
always regarded
Programmable matter
as nothing more than a theory,
But I guess your shape-shifter
proves it can be done.
Wait, so he, or she,
or I... whatever.
This person
can actually transform
Into anyone they touch?
Yes, it appears so.
That includes you,
Mr. Allen.
Dr. Wells is right.
If you are touched while
You're the Flash,
and he transforms into you,
We run the risk of him exposing
That Barry Allen
is the man behind the mask.
Because at this point
we don't know
If the shape-shifter
is capable of absorbing more
That just
your physical characteristics.
Like he might be able
to copy my speed?
That would be bad.
Got it.
Hands off the meta-human.
So how do we find someone
who can transform into anyone?
Well, I guess
like any problem,
You just go back
to the beginning.
In this case, that would mean
finding the first person
The shape-shifter
morphed into
When they discovered
their powers.
Yeah, can you pull up
the CCPD records
Of cases where the perpetrator
plead innocent,
Even thought they were caught
on camera committing the crime?
You're good, Barry Allen.
You're very good.
Look at this.
Multiple crimes of this manner
All dating back to a month
After the particle accelerator
explosion.
And the first one was?
Jacob Fisher. A teller at the
federal credit union.
Claims he was innocent, and was
framed by his best friend,
A Hannibal Bates.
I'll pass this along
to the CCPD,
See if they can
track him down.
- Good.
- Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Always here to help, Barry.
There it is.
This is all you have?
Well, it's a pretty
cut and dry case, Detective.
Harrison Wells, Tess Morgan
are out on a Sunday drive,
the tires blow,
Wells loses control,
and, uh... sadly Tess dies
on the scene.
Couldn't imagine carrying
that kind of guilt around.
So, uh... what are you two
hoping to find?
We're not exactly sure yet.
You come all the way
from Central City,
You don't know what
you're looking for?
Just following a hunch.
Uh, can you take us
to the accident site?
It's been 15 years.
I think the pictures will
Serve you better.
Still, we'd appreciate
a look.
Whatever you need.
Captain, I need those
witness statements
For the Joshua Brown trial.
Um, yeah, well,
like I told you, end of day.
Sorry, uh, Detective West,
Cisco Ramon,
this is ADA
Laurel Lance.
Related?
Daughter.
Hi.
Hey there.
You work at S.T.A.R. Labs
with Barry Allen, right?
Uh, yeah.
Can I talk to you privately
for a minute?
Sure.
So, uh... How is Allen?
Not too messed up from getting
hit by that lightning, I hope.
No, no.
How do you know Barry?
Are you guys, like,
friends or something?
Not really.
We met last time
he was in Starling City
Visiting my friends.
John Diggle, Felicity Smoak,
and Oliver Queen.
Three people who have
absolutely nothing in common.
As far as I know.
Cisco, I know Barry's
the Flash,
And Oliver's the Arrow.
How do you know that?
Because I'm the black canary.
- Stop playing.
- It's true.
You stop it right now.
No.
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
I love you.
I mean, I love the way
that you beat up criminals.
Wait.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I need some
technical expertise.
I've been using
my sister's sonic device.
I was hoping you could
help... modify it.
Yeah.
I think I've got some ideas.
Great.
What... are you
spying on me now?
Caitlin, what were you doing
at Wells's house?
I was gonna talk to him
and get some answers of my own.
You can't.
You cannot talk to him.
Oh, so I'm just supposed
to stand by
And watch all of you ruin
this man's life?
Ruin my life?
What are you talking about
"your life?"
Those nine months
that you were in a coma
Were the worst of my life.
I lost my reputation,
my fiance,
And through all of that,
Harrison Wells stood by my side.
He told me everything
was going to be okay.
If Dr. Wells is
who you say he is,
Everything I've done
since the minute
I stepped foot
in S.T.A.R. Labs
Has been a lie.
Caitlin.
If I am right
about all of this,
And you tell him
what's been going on,
I'll never be able to get
my dad out of prison.
Barry.
If not for me,
just do it for him.
I can't believe
you're pulling the dad card.
That's dirty pool, Barry.
Just until Joe and Cisco
get back.
Please.
Turns out Hannibal Bates hasn't
been seen in well over a year.
Only remaining relative
is his grandmother.
She took out
a missing person's report
A couple of days after
the Jacob Fisher arrest.
Figure we could ask her
a few questions.
Like why anyone
in their family
Thought that naming a kid
Hannibal
Wouldn't mean he'd grow up
to become a criminal?
Have you heard from your
grandson, Hannibal, recently,
Mrs. Bates?
- Recently?
- Uh-huh.
No.
Why do you ask?
Oh, please.
Um...
Because you filed
a missing person's report
Over a year ago.
Oh, yes, I certainly did.
You'll have to
forgive me, Detective.
My memory is not quite
as it used to be.
Of course.
Uh, neither apparently
are my manners.
May I get you two something?
Coffee, tea?
Uh, no thank you, ma'am.
We're fine.
Oh, please.
It'll only take a minute.
It's nice to have visitors.
Coffee'd be nice.
Thanks.
Ma'am, would you happen
to have a recent photograph
of Hannibal?
Ma'am?
She's gone.
I'll take the front.
Hey, we located Bates.
He was impersonating
his grandma.
Barry, do not let him
touch you.
Or let him see you
use your super speed.
Well, how am I supposed
to catch him?
The old-fashioned way.
Run like a normal person.
Okay, all right.
Oh, man.
What do you want
us to do, Thawne?
Die.
Barry, call 911.
What do you want us to do,
Thawne?
Die.
I know what this
looks like, Cecile.
It looks like
one of your Detectives
Shot two of your cops,
Both of whom are now
fighting for their lives.
That's not what happened.
David, I am
the district attorney.
I can't ignore
what I just watched
Because you want me to.
We both know
there are things going on
In this city
that can't be explained.
Come on, David.
Until you show me something
incontrovertible,
the best that I can do
is promise to keep him out of
gen pop at Iron Heights.
Do you have any way
of explaining this, Allen?
I'm working on it.
- Barry.
- Iris.
What is going on?
Everyone at CCPN is saying
That Eddie shot two cops.
How is that even possible?
We're not sure yet.
You don't think he did this,
do you?
- No, of course not.
- I need to see him.
You can't...
you can't see him, all right?
They're not gonna let you.
Look...
I'm gonna do everything
I can to help him.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay, I'm so sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
- Okay.
- I promise.
All right?
This is definitely the place.
Cisco, let's see
what we can find.
What is that?
A, uh, metal detector?
Uh, essentially.
Only instead of listening
for metal objects,
I'm listening for anything
That emits
a abnormal sound wave.
Right.
Where'd you find this kid?
It's a long story.
So, it must be interesting
having a daughter
who is also the DA.
Yeah, interesting's the word.
- I have a daughter of my own.
- Same line of work?
No, I wouldn't let her
anywhere near this nonsense.
Smart guy.
Overprotective.
You two get along?
We don't always see
eye to eye,
But no matter how mad
she gets at me
Or how mad I get at her,
There's a strong bond.
Why?
You two have a bit
of a rough patch?
Yeah, she, uh...
She kept something from me,
You know,
something important.
Lied to me about it
for months.
Hard to come back
from something like that.
Mm.
She give a reason?
Not one I could accept.
Ah. Well,
sometimes we lie for love.
Especially when it comes
to family, right?
- Joe!
- Yeah?
I think we got something.
Tachyons.
Little bits of time travel.
You sure?
Pretty sure, yeah.
I didn't shoot those officers.
Yeah, the Captain certainly
plead your case.
The results of the GSR swab.
Detective Thawne's hands
are completely free
Of lead, barium, and antimony.
Yet no one can seem
to explain
how the surveillance video
clearly shows
Thawne firing his weapon.
It only looked like
Detective Thawne.
Mr. Allen, no.
Aren't you supposed to be
the scientist around here?
It's hard to blame her.
That video is pretty damning.
No. No, we just have to
convince her.
Seeing is believing, Barry.
They're gonna put me away.
Okay, look,
you get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
They'll set you up
with a burner phone.
- I'll contact...
- No.
I run now,
that surveillance video
is the least of my problems.
No way I don't smell guilty.
No way they'll let me
stay on the force.
Look, you said it yourself,
If we don't find
Hannibal Bates,
You go to prison.
For a crime
you didn't commit.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Not again.
This isn't like your dad,
Barry.
Eddie, look.
When you dad was put away,
You were a kid.
There wasn't anything
you could do.
But you're not a kid anymore.
You're a scientist.
Hell, you're the Flash.
You are going to find Bates,
And you are going
to clear me.
So go do it.
All right.
Get me out of here
the right way.
I promise, Iris.
Now, I'm just here
to shower and change,
And then I'm going
right back to my lab.
I swear I'm going to get
Eddie out of this, okay?
I'll call you later, all right?
Eddie? What in the world?
How did you get out?
Captain Singh called in
a favor.
Got a judge
to sign my release.
I was just on the phone
with Iris.
Why haven't you called her?
Hold on.
I have no idea who she is.
Barry, it's me.
Hello... you.
I think I figured out
a way to stop our shapeshifter
From morphing into
other people.
Oh, really?
What if I create a serum
That will terminate
the polymerization reaction,
Essentially forcing the bonds
to revert to their original form
Stopping him from being able
to control his power.
You can do that?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Look, about last night,
I can't imagine
how hard this must be for you.
I mean, I know how desperate
you are
To solve your mom's murder.
But let's just
bury the hatchet,
And we'll go back
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Figure out how to catch
this everyman.
"Everyman?"
Bad nickname?
No.
No, I kinda like it.
Okay, good.
Me, too.
Wait, hold up, Cisco.
Please tell me that's not
what I think it is.
Okay, that is definitely
a hand.
Okay, see, I thought
it was a foot,
But a hand is just as bad.
That is freaky.
That is proof, Cisco.
I'll need to test it
to be certain.
I'm gonna grab my kit.
Okay, I'm gonna have to
call this one in.
I can't let you do that.
Now I'm asking you,
cop to cop,
Keep this under wraps.
Forget you ever saw it.
- West, I can't do that.
- Listen, Lance,
If this is who I think it is,
Anybody that knows about this
Is in a hell of a lot
of danger,
Including my daughter.
As mad as you are at Laurel,
I can't imagine
you wouldn't do anything
To protect her.
Hey.
Good to go.
Just need to give it
a little spin.
Oh.
Right.
Yes.
A spin.
So this, uh...
Serum that you're making,
Is it a temporary fix,
Or will it take away
his power permanently?
Not permanently.
Just long enough
so we can stop him.
And how long is it
going to take?
Not long.
We just need...
What are you doing?
Something I think
I should have done...
A long time ago.
Mm.
Barry, uh...
Oh, my god.
Look who's here.
Yes.
Her.
Hi, I have been looking
for you everywhere.
Here I am.
What's up?
Look, whoever is framing Eddie,
I got to thinking.
What if they've done
something like this before?
I went through CCPN's
crime archives,
And in the last 11 months,
there have been six crimes
Committed by people
who later swore
That they were innocent.
None of them had priors,
All of them had
rock-solid alibis.
- All right.
- So...
I hacked into my dad's
CCPD account,
And went through the footage
of Eddie shooting those cops.
Look.
What do you want us to do,
Thawne?
Die
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
Nothing.
I didn't do anything.
I don't know.
Seems pretty convincing to me.
Look again.
Eddie is not left-handed.
Look, Eddie is being framed,
and we need to figure out
Who is behind this.
And believe me,
when I get my hands on them,
They are going to be...
Oh, my god.
What did you do?
Your observations about the
shooter were spot on, Miss West.
He was indeed left-handed.
As is this man.
Our Barry...
Is right-handed.
Oh, I knew it.
- Never mind.
- Then this is him.
It is indeed.
I need to take him in
to the police.
If they can see what he can do,
Then maybe they'll let Eddie go.
Perhaps it might be best
if Dr. Snow and I handle this.
Mm.
What are you two going to do?
No. No, no, no.
I'm taking him in.
Of course.
Well, at least let me help you.
There is a reporter at work
who kept a file
Of these sorts of things.
You know, all of the unexplained
events in the city.
This guy...
Definitely belongs
in that file.
That's gonna be
a pretty big file.
You know who else
is in that file?
The burning man.
Oh, really?
What about him?
I thought he was just some
urban legend.
Help me!
Help me, help me, help me!
- Oh, no.
- Someone, please, help me!
Help! Help! These bad ladies
have kidnapped me!
- What's going on here?
- I need help!
I need help!
These bad ladies kidnapped me!
We did not kidnap her.
- No.
- Iris, drive.
- I can't.
- Call the police.
No. No, no, no.
She's dangerous.
Hey!
No!
Where are you going?
Oh, Barry.
Aah!
For real?
Why did you slap me?
Because you were unconscious.
Smelling salts
works just as well.
Sorry.
You okay?
I think so, yeah.
Wait, Caitlin.
Bates, he was here.
Uh, yes, I know.
Okay, let's go.
You sure there's nothing else
I can do for you, Detective?
You have done
more than enough.
Thank you for everything,
Captain.
Listen, I should be
thanking you
For getting me
out of the office for a day.
Pushing papers,
reviewing budgets
Public all over my ass.
It's been a nice change.
I'd still be Detective
if I could, but, you know,
Body just can't
take it anymore.
What you gonna do
when you got a bad heart?
I can think of something
that might make things better.
Cisco.
Laurel, hey.
Uh...
We're just about
to head back to Central City.
Were you able to
make that item?
I think this will
do the trick.
I bumped up the specs.
Quadrupled the range,
tripled the resonance.
You should be able to do some
serious damage with this thing.
I can't believe you were able
to make it so quickly.
Eh. I've had some practice
with sound waves recently.
I think you should call it
"the canary cry."
I like it.
Thank you.
As promised.
Hey, you show this to anyone,
I'll kill you.
That's just an expression,
Right?
Nope.
Cisco?
You good?
Oh, I'm good.
So this Hannibal Bates
has turned into
Quite the meta-human.
Take a look.
His cells have the ability
to transmogrify
At quite the rate.
Which is how
he can become anyone.
Which is how he can
look like anyone.
Because he cannot appropriate
your memory or your powers.
Got it.
Hands on the meta-human.
And to help you do that,
Dr. Snow has concocted
a solution we believe
Will stop him.
Yes. I've made a serum
that will create
A cortical reaction
around his cells.
Deprive those cells
of their electrical charge,
His shape-shifting days
are over.
Wow, that's great work.
Thank you.
Um... No need
for a hug
Or anything like that.
Okay.
Oh, Barry.
We got a ping
from your cell phone.
Looks like Hannibal Bates
is at the airport.
Payback time.
Guys, are we sure
he's at the airport?
According to the GPS
on your phone, he's there.
Yeah, but...
He could be any
of these people.
I'm not seeing him.
Gotcha.
Hannibal Bates.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
Wait.
It's me.
Please don't hurt me.
Not so hero-like.
Treat all your women
like that?
Well, look at that.
I'm the Flash.
You may look like me...
But you're not as fast.
You're done imitating
innocent people.
Aah!
- Barry?
- Yeah.
The one and only.
Detective Thawne
has been released.
I have to admit
this is new territory for me.
This is new territory
for all of us.
I certainly don't think
the law is prepared
To deal with this kind
of criminal.
Hopefully we can
catch up fast.
It's hard to believe
we live in a world
Where this kind of impossible
even exists.
Luckily it's also a world
where the Flash exists.
Uh, speaking of...
He left this list
of all the robberies
That Hannibal Bates
was involved in.
That's a long list.
With just as many
innocent people
Whose names
need to be cleared.
You know,
I saw the Flash once.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I was on my way
to the courthouse.
He blew past me.
It was...
It was just a blur of red
and a gust of wind.
But it was pretty damn cool.
Iris.
Oh.
All charges
have been dropped.
I'm clear to go.
Oh, thank god.
Iris...
I need to tell you something.
You know what?
It can wait until we get home.
You were right.
I was hiding something
from you,
And you deserve to
know the truth.
The reason I've been
so distant lately...
I've been working
with the Flash.
Let me out of here!
Hey, cutie.
Want to let me out of here?
Like anyone would be
dumb enough to fall for that.
Seen a lot of things
that you can become,
But who are you,
Hannibal Bates?
I, uh...
I can't remember.
Well, let's lock up shop.
Good night, everyone.
What about Dr. Wells?
Come here.
I need to show you something.
This isn't possible.
Caitlin, I ran
the DNA test twice.
It's a perfect match.
This body is the real
Harrison Wells.
If this is Dr. Wells,
Then who have we been
working for this whole time?
Dr. McGee said that
after the accident,
Wells became
a completely different person.
It's because he is
a different person.
Dr. Wells.
You here on business?
Business, no.
I came to give my regards
To Detective Thawne.
Glad it all worked out.
Yeah.
Crazy day for him.
Crazy day for us all.
Oh.
Detective, did you enjoy
your time in Starling City?
Not much time
for sightseeing.
I was working on a case.
- Oh.
- You used to live there.
I did.
You ever go back?
No.
Too many memories of Tess.
That's right.
Sorry.
You, Detective, are one of
the few people I know
That truly understands
that kind of loss.
Iris's mother, you never
talk about her, do you?
No.
I don't.
No?
You and I, Detective,
Are members of a rather
exclusive club, I suppose.
One who's membership
is too expensive.
Maybe we should have
another drink sometime.
Talk about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, we should do that.
What are you doing?
After the accelerator
exploded,
I built a 3-D model
of S.T.A.R. Labs
so that I could pinpoint exactly
what caused the malfunction.
And you never ran this test?
Of course I did.
I just never had any reason
to look at any areas outside
of the pipeline or the cortex.
It's a big building.
Lots of places
for Wells to hide something.
What is that?
That shouldn't be there.
I'm picking up more activity
around here.
Tachyons.
There.
Oh, my god.
Guys.
What the frak?
Greg, move your head.