[Caitlin] Previously on The Flash...
Dr. Harrison "Nash" Wells.
[Nash] I'm searching for an artifact
that just happens to contain Eternium.
[Dibny] The disappearance
of Sue Dearbon.
I don't think I've ever seen you
this devoted to a case.
HLH isn't just my mother's disease.
Now, it's killing me.
You're a dead man, too.
Aren't you, Barry?
[Barry] The only timeline
where everyone survives...
was the one where I died.
And none of you can try and save me.
Analysis of Mitch Romero's blood
reveals that this substance
appears to heal any and all weaknesses
in the human body, including HLH.
I need more.
Dr. Rosso.
Didn't mean to
sneak up on you like that.
It's almost Halloween,
I guess we're all due
for a good scare, right?
What brings you here so late?
I'm, uh, meeting up with a colleague.
[coughs] Yeah. I told him
I'd be here half an hour ago,
so if you'll excuse me.
Of course. It's good to see you.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
[screams]
[Barry] I wish it didn't have to be
this way.
And you're okay with all of this?
No, but...
I have to accept that there are still
others out there that we can save.
Yeah, guys, look. Six weeks from now,
all of our lives
are gonna be on the line,
so we have to be prepared.
Yes. But what about him?
I'm not just going to wait around
for him to get vaporized by antimatter.
We should be doing something
to try to save his life.
You can't. You can't, Cisco.
That's why I need you
to stop worrying about me.
If Barry had any other option,
we'd be doing it.
I think you gotta get behind this.
Yeah. I am.
How do you convince your best friend
not to save your life?
- [cell phone chimes and vibrates]
- You're the teacher. You'll find a way.
All right, well, he's gonna have
to wait. It's CCPD.
There he is.
[sighs] So much for my day off.
- What do we got?
- It's a creepy one.
Somebody broke into this facility last
night and stole ten liters of blood.
There's no security footage?
There's no cameras
in this part of the hospital.
- You think this is meta related?
- I'm asking you.
I mean...
Meta thieves usually
make a way bigger mess.
Ah, you see this lock?
I mean, the way this is sheared,
a power saw could've done this.
I don't know, I mean, maybe it was just
some kids pulling a Halloween prank.
Good. I thought we were dealing with
some kind of meta-vampire.
Just a normal criminal
with a diseased mind.
Well, since I am captain, I'm gonna go
watch the second half of the game.
- I'm gonna leave this to you. All right?
- Mmm-hmm.
You okay?
Yeah, you know.
Just this Crisis that's coming.
Cisco's not taking it so great.
Let me guess which part.
Cisco's a whole lot like you.
It is in his nature to wanna save lives.
Especially under these circumstances.
- I'll see you later.
- Right.
- Thanks, Joe.
- Thanks for what?
I think I know how
to get through to Cisco.
[Ramsey] Tests are conclusive.
The peculiar black blood
I absorbed from Mitch Romero
temporarily cured
the HLH cancer in my blood,
but it wasn't enough.
I need more blood in order
to create a permanent cure
and save my life.
Adding Romero's cells to this new blood
should be the key
to rebuilding my cellular structure.
[breathing heavily]
I only hope I have enough time.
[Ramsey] Why didn't you tell me?
It's brilliant.
You're my son.
You're supposed to be impressed.
You're going to do beautiful things
for this world.
- [coughing]
- Are you okay?
- Mum?
[Rachel] My condition is terminal.
[Cisco] I got your text. What is it now?
Look, I know you're upset about
this Crisis.
And I've been thinking about it,
and you're right.
We can do more than prepare for a fight.
You can save a life.
I knew you'd come around.
No, Cisco, not... It's not me.
We're gonna save Ramsey Rosso.
Here's the thing.
We've done some insane things
at S.T.A.R. Labs over
the last few years,
but curing a rare blood cancer,
that is beyond our resources.
So we just shouldn't try?
So we try and somehow succeed,
are we supposed to spend
the rest of your time here
trying to save everyone
who's been diagnosed with cancer?
- I mean...
- We start with one man.
Look, you heard what Caitlin said
about Ramsey.
He's one of the most
brilliant doctors on the planet.
I need you to back me on this.
You'll understand soon enough.
Look...
What would it take to cure HLH?
Honestly? An act of God.
[Nash] Or...
An act of science.
And I know just where to find one.
I'm assuming this is the Wells
that you were telling me about?
Yep. Nash Wells. Multiversal explorer
and provider of scientific miracles.
And you, I'm guessing,
are Barry Allen, the Flash.
How did he... How did you...
Hidden surveillance device.
You bugged S.T.A.R. Labs?
No, no. Not exactly.
I, um... I bugged you.
- No, you didn't.
- Mmm, yeah, I did.
Fellas, I've been listening
to your conversations,
and I have a proposition.
Now, I need an anti-vibrational
crypto-circuit to complete my work
on this Earth, and you need help
with your mission, right?
Well, you build me my circuit,
'cause I know you have the capacity,
and I will lead you
to something priceless
that will surely help your mission.
Your work? What's your work?
Thermic excavation.
You're a cosmic myth-buster
who also happens to be a geologist?
Sure.
- Sure.
- Sidebar.
- Red-flag city.
- Yeah.
Then again, Wells usually
shows up for a reason.
- Fellas?
- Yeah.
You're aware, um,
he's still bugged, right?
- Where's the bug? I don't see any...
- Okay, look. All right...
Not in your shoe.
- I can tell you that much.
- Let's just say that we trust you...
- We don't.
- ...which we obviously don't.
Understood.
What are you offering?
I'm offering you something that
will help save Ramsey Rosso's life.
- [knocking at door]
- [door opens]
Have I got something for you.
- [Dibny] My Amazon packages?
- No.
You know that case you've been working
on for the last couple of months,
the Dearbon woman?
Well, I know it's been cold lately,
so I have a little
Halloween treat for you.
- A lead.
- Yeah?
Yeah, I interviewed this accountant
in Midway City
that works at this security firm,
and one of their guards
was working a charity event
and claims to have seen
someone that sounds like Sue Dearbon.
So, Cecile pulled a favor
and got an eyewitness report.
Cool. Thanks, Iris.
[clears throat]
Need something else?
No.
No. That was... That was it.
Cool.
All right. Yeah. Cool.
I will see you later.
[Ramsey] Production of blood serum
is complete.
It appears identical to the substance
I absorbed from Mitch Romero.
If this works,
I could hold the cure
not just for myself,
but for all those suffering
from HLH cancer.
[groans]
[gasps in pain]
[groaning]
[yelling]
[grunts in pain] It's not working.
I failed. I failed.
[Nash] It's in there.
McCulloch Technologies.
[Barry] What is?
Well, it is extremely rare.
A bio-regenerative serum capable of
healing organic tissue
no matter what the harm.
So, for your purposes, what do you do?
You simply inject it
into your friend's healthy cells,
his healthy cells replicate,
they replace the unhealthy cells.
Presto, instant miracle.
Although, don't wait till
your buddy's too far gone
because then it might not work.
This sounds way too good to be true.
No, he's right.
I mean, how did McCulloch Technologies
develop something this advanced?
[chuckles] They didn't develop it.
They stole it. It's from Swan Moon-
- The Dominator home planet?
- Yeah, that's the one.
Recovered from some invasion
three years ago.
Anyway, blah-blah-blah.
You guys in, or what?
Well, how dangerous a weapon
could this be in the wrong hands?
On a scale of one to ten... 12.
We gotta get our hands on this thing.
All right, I'm gonna disable
the exterior security cameras.
[Cisco sighs]
Oh, he goes right through
the door. [chuckles]
- That's cool.
- How did you know this stuff was here?
Kid, multiversal explorer,
we need to know things.
And this serum, could it protect
someone from antimatter?
I expect that goes without saying.
[Nash] Whoo!
Cameras are down.
All right, boys.
Here's where the fun begins.
All right.
Speedster, come on.
Speed us to the storage room.
- No, duh, I can't.
- Wait, what do you mean, you can't?
There are localized meta dampeners
all over this building, all right?
My powers are useless in here.
That means you're useless here.
Hey, we don't have to make your circuit.
Oh, is that right, tough guy?
Have you thought about
what you're gonna do
if you don't make my circuit...
Hey, numbskulls, knock it off.
- [guard] Freeze! Both of you.
- [guns cocking]
Both of us?
So, we can explain.
I don't think they're gonna
ask questions first.
[device whirs]
[emitting high-pitched wail]
[all grunting]
- [Cisco] Nash?
- Hey, fellas.
- So your auditory nerves...
- What?
Your ears will be fine
in a couple of minutes.
Unlike these two. Now, where were we?
All right, let's hurry up.
There's another life at stake
besides our own.
Hey, Ralph. Any progress
on that Dearbon lead?
You know, I really think that
there might be something...
- to it.
- No. I decided to give it up.
What? Why?
There's no point, Iris.
The whole Sue thing is a lost cause,
so I might as well quit
before I waste any more time.
Ralph, you can't quit.
You're obsessed with finding her.
You have to keep going.
Iris, despite Team Flash's mantra,
sometimes you do have
to give up on things.
You know, if I were you,
I'd be spending a lot more time
with my husband while he's still here.
All right. Let the search begin.
Oh, man. Without super speed,
this is gonna take a minute.
We don't have to search every location,
just the cold ones.
Okay? Because the serum
we're looking for,
it requires an environment
of minus 15 degrees.
This says minus 15 degrees.
Well, there you go.
[Barry chuckles]
- Okay.
- Convenient.
Time to steal our golden idol.
[alarm chimes twice]
Do you guys hear that?
- What? No.
- I didn't hear anything.
[alarm chimes]
Wait. Yeah, I did hear that.
Is that an alarm?
It better not be.
I need more time to hack this.
I'm on it.
- No. Hey.
- Yeah, yeah, I got it.
I'm gonna follow him.
[whispers] Nash. Nash.
Nash.
[sighs] Okay.
I don't know where he went.
- I got it.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
No.
- We're too late.
- This can't be happening.
McCulloch must've already sold it.
We needed this to save Ramsey.
Boys! We got company.
Always wanted to say that. Here, catch.
- What is this?
- This? This is our way out of here.
What are you talking about?
What are we supposed to do with this?
It's easy. You just throw it.
Like now.
- [Nash] Whoo!
- [Barry and Cisco groan]
Well, that was exciting,
wasn't it, fellas?
[Cisco] The lounge?
How did we...
Oh, worry less about how
we got to the lounge
and more about
building my crypto-circuit.
That's not happening anymore.
Let me correct you, Barry Allen,
yes, it is. We had a deal.
Right? I would lead you
to something priceless, which I did,
not my fault the serum was gone.
So, now you two are
gonna build me a device.
I don't understand.
Why won't this blood work again?
[breathing heavily]
What am I missing?
[Ramsey] I found it, a cure for you.
[Rachel] The bonding agent in this cure
is dark matter.
So that's it? You're just deciding
to give up and... and die.
No one lives forever.
No. I won't give up. That's your choice.
Ramsey,
I'm not your enemy.
I know. The real enemy
is death.
You know, Nash isn't going anywhere
until he gets this crypto-circuit.
How's it coming?
Almost finished.
All right. [sighs]
I don't know if you should.
Okay. What do you mean?
I mean, doesn't something
feel off about all this?
Yeah, I know. The guy shows up
needing our tech,
makes a bargain to help us,
and, conveniently,
the thing we need isn't there.
Right.
So, I mean...
You think he's lying to us?
It wouldn't be the first time
a Wells had a secret agenda.
[sighs] Yeah.
Yo, what's in here?
That's storage for Frost's stuff.
You know how she gets.
You haven't looked me in the eye
since I came in here.
Wait.
What the hell am I looking at?
Cisco.
You know exactly what this is.
I don't care what powers you have.
You want it,
you're gonna have to go through me.
What are you talking about?
And what the hell are you doing?
I'm saving your life
'cause someone has to do it.
Saving Ramsey...
- Saving Ramsey is my call.
- And it's a bad call.
But it's the one I made.
Sometimes as a leader,
you have to make tough calls
in order to serve the greater good.
You know, I made a tough call.
And I made it for you.
But I told you, you can't save me.
- I'm not buying that.
- Well, you have to.
Sacrificing myself saves everything
and everyone. I've seen it.
And what does that
give me to look forward to?
Waking up to a world without the Flash,
a life without my best friend?
You get to live.
You all get to live.
Don't.
Look, man, I've...
I've been dealing with this for weeks.
Wondering what's gonna happen
when I'm gone, how everybody
is going to move on.
That's why I wanted us, you and me,
together, to save Ramsey today.
You wanted us to save a random person
so I'd be okay with you dying?
No, I wanted us
to save one person's life
so you could understand the tough calls.
The sacrifices that
a leader has to make.
Because you're my pick.
You're the person that
I want to run S.T.A.R. Labs
and this team when I'm gone.
All day I've been trying to teach you
how hard those responsibilities can be.
And then you stole something that
was meant to save another person's life.
You justified it even.
And I'd do it again.
Maybe I made the wrong choice.
The serum is yours.
[knocking at door]
- Barry.
- Can we talk?
Um, now's really not a good time.
It's important.
I have something that
I need to give you.
S.T.A.R. Labs has been doing some
research into regenerative formulas,
and we've developed a serum.
We think that this could
save your life.
If you inject it
into your healthy cells,
they'll duplicate
and eventually overtake
your cells that are affected by HLH.
But you have to use it quickly.
Is it, um... Is it dark matter-based?
No, it's experimental,
but we believe it'll cure you.
Oh.
I'd given up hope.
Why... Why do this for me?
A week ago, you told me you felt like
you were falling off a cliff.
I want you to have a lifeline.
You're dying as well. Don't...
Don't you want a lifeline for yourself?
There's only enough of this
for one person.
And I've read about you, Ramsey.
And I've talked to Caitlin.
You're a brilliant doctor.
From what she said,
if you had enough time,
you could cure HLH.
I'm giving you that time.
The world needs people like you
to save those who can't save themselves.
Test it. Verify what we believe
it will do,
and then use it quickly.
We're not sure how long
the serum will be viable.
Barry.
Thank you.
[knocking at door]
Hey.
You busy?
For you, Cap? Never.
Iris tells me you've been having trouble
with the Dearbon case.
Joe, I've been working on
this Dearbon thing since last summer.
Then it dawned on me.
Digging into this right now,
it... it doesn't matter.
Why the hell should I try to find her
and try to help her,
if I can't even save...
- Barry. You can say it.
- Barry.
Ralph, do you remember
my old partner, Chyre?
He taught me an important lesson.
He said you can't always save everyone,
but you can always save someone.
For you, that's Sue Dearbon.
Not Barry.
I'm gonna miss him, Joe.
That's it?
Fully functioning crypto-circuit?
You sure? 'Cause it kinda seems like...
It seems kind of shoddy...
shoddy workmanship.
I feel like I've seen better workmanship
on pretty much
all the other Earths out there.
This is subpar.
Subpar's being generous. It...
Never touch me.
Just take it.
Sure, kid.
Thanks. Till our next adventure.
Frosty.
[sighs]
So, how'd it go with
Professor Speedster?
You all ready for life post-Crisis?
I think our friendship
pretty much exploded.
Oh.
Because it is impossible to save him.
And yet, I still don't think
I should stop trying.
You want some free advice?
Sure.
You can't save someone
who doesn't wanna be saved,
and he's already made up his mind.
And if you obsess over it,
it could lead you down a dark path.
You might make a mistake you can't fix.
[Ramsey] Commencing preliminary tests
on S.T.A.R. Labs' proposed cure.
Damn it! Of course it's another failure.
Why would I expect anything
different from the universe?
My fate is sealed.
Death wins again.
Death...
There is one key difference...
Too late.
...between the blood I stole
and the blood from Mitch Romero's body.
Romero was afraid for his life.
His blood cells were flooded
with epinephrine.
Adrenaline released during the attack,
it's the bonding agent. Which means...
in order to create the substance
I need to live,
I have to kill.
But first,
they have to be afraid.
[alarms chiming]
Multiple alarms at Central City General.
They're evacuating.
Is it a bomb threat?
Reports say a madman
is attacking patients.
[Killer Frost gasps]
All staff and patients are accounted for
except for those on this floor.
That wound's fresh.
Whoever did this was just here.
Why would someone do this?
She's gone.
Maybe I can figure out why.
[distant yelling]
Go.
[squelching]
[grunts]
Ramsey? What the hell are you doing?
Whatever it takes to stay alive.
These people,
you're the one that's killing them.
S.T.A.R. Labs gave you a cure,
why didn't you take it?
I did, but it didn't work.
Turns out the disease in my human blood
was too far gone.
But if I was to become
something more than human...
That's when I realized
I could live forever.
As long as I feed.
Ramsey, you're a doctor.
You're supposed to save lives,
not take them.
I am saving lives, Flash. Mine.
And right now, you are in my way.
[snarls]
[gasping]
[snarling]
[grunts]
[all snarling]
Ramsey, come on. Let him go, please.
I can't. My blood brothers and sisters
are much more than just the help.
- They're making me stronger.
- You're using them.
To survive.
[creature snarls and groans]
Hello, Cait.
Playing the hero now, are you?
The bad guy was taken, so, yeah.
[snarls]
Please, help me.
I know what you're thinking.
You're fast, Flash.
But as a doctor, I know exactly
where this man's carotid artery is.
Even if I can't feed,
you will never save him in time.
Ramsey, don't do this. Let us help you.
What you're doing, it's inhuman.
It was my humanity
that was holding me back,
preventing me from becoming the man
Mum always knew I was destined to be.
She always said I'd do beautiful things
for this world.
And she was right.
Because the man I was,
that was the disease.
A frail, human body
with a shelf life. Rot.
But I found a way to transcend all that.
To defeat death itself.
Everyone dies, Ramsey.
Maybe the only thing that makes it
bearable is to find some meaning in it.
Well, that means I'm making
the greatest sacrifice of all.
Don't you see? What I'm becoming,
this is the cure.
I am the answer, Flash,
to the greatest mystery of all.
Life eternal.
- [inaudible]
- [doctor] Please, Dr. Rosso.
I saved you for last,
so you would be the most afraid.
Ramsey, please don't do this.
You could've saved Mum, but you didn't.
- And that's why I came here for you.
- Ramsey!
- [doctor gasping]
- [yells]
Stay with me, all right? I got you.
What the hell are they doing?
I think they're trying to follow Ramsey.
[growling]
Wait.
- We have to help him.
- I don't think we can.
We lost.
Five people aren't going home
to their families tonight.
And a sixth, Ramsey.
We lost him, too.
He's out there somewhere.
We have to stop him. I...
I have to stop him.
- Barry...
- You tried to save him.
But he turned himself into a monster.
That's not on us.
That was Ramsey's choice.
I swear, if it's the last thing
I do on this Earth,
I'm gonna stop him.
How did Ramsey do this, anyway?
He's using people as incubators.
Using their bodies to create
what he needs to keep himself alive.
So he's turning people
into human blood banks.
And as soon as he gets hungry again...
He's gonna make a withdrawal.
Well, happy Halloween, everyone.
Yeah.
Hey, Ralph.
Look. [sighs]
I know this Crisis news
hasn't been easy on anyone.
Yeah. [chuckles] I'll say.
But, look, Iris.
That's no excuse for me being a jerk.
I'm sorry.
I know that you were just trying
to help me.
So I did wanna say that tomorrow
I'm gonna call Midway City,
see what I can find.
That's great, Ralph.
Sue is very lucky to have
a master detective like you
searching for her.
Give me a break.
It's just a missing persons case.
It's not like
I'm looking to get married.
He gonna be okay?
Yeah, he is.
Of all of the nights for this madness
to be happening, it had to be Halloween.
[sighs]
Babe, we should probably head home.
Would you mind if I catch up
with you in a couple of minutes?
No. It's fine.
Barry.
Hey.
[sighs]
I'm sorry about what happened
at McCulloch...
No, man, no. No, look, this...
This is not your fault.
I should've been focused
on saving the right person.
Well, I mean, even though
things didn't work out with Ramsey,
at least we tried to do the right thing.
I still don't know how you do that, man.
Picking yourself up,
just pushing forward...
I don't know, I'm just trying to...
teach you what it's taken me
years to learn.
I know you're doing it for all of us.
That's what it means to be a hero.
I knew I picked the right guy.
- I'm gonna...
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Hey, Joe.
- You all right?
- Mmm.
I was just...
just wondering where Ramsey was
and just hoping to God
that we find him before...
this gets worse.
His description has been circulated
to every precinct from here to Gotham,
so we should find him.
Then what?
More people are gonna get hurt.
Or worse.
I know.
I tried to save him.
Tried to do some good before I...
Don't you dare start talking like that.
You've done plenty of good.
Ever since you became the Flash,
you've saved more people
than CCPD altogether.
Without you, I would've...
I would have lost our family
a long time ago.
And this is what you get for saving
the world over and over again?
How is that right?
- You know it doesn't work like that.
- Doesn't it?
I mean, I'm a cop. If I risk my life
every day for 30 years,
I get to retire, Barr.
I get to go home to the woman I love.
I get to proudly watch my baby girl
grow up each and every day.
I get a life, Barr.
You're a hero. What do you get?
Nothing?
It's just...
Damn it. It's not right.
We... The world...
The world owes you.
You deserve better than this.
No, I don't.
I'm grateful for everything that I have.
All the blessings in my life.
For Iris, the team...
I mean, hell, I'm the Flash.
I'm grateful for that.
But you...
You're what I'm most grateful for.
If it weren't for you,
your patience, your courage,
the will just to keep going,
I learned all that from you.
More than anyone else,
before the team, before Iris.
You're the one that showed me
what it takes just to be a good person.
You're one of the biggest reasons
I was even able to become the Flash.
For that, I'll always be grateful.
[sniffles]
Barr, I'm not ready.
I'm not ready for this.
[sniffles]
I'm just not.
- It's okay, man. It's all right.
- No. No.
[sniffs] I know you... I know you...
you say it has to happen, but...
It's all right.
It's okay.
I'm never gonna leave you.
Even when I'm gone.
[gauntlet beeping]
Let's try this.
[beeping]
So this is where you've been hiding.
[chuckles]
Time to pay a house call.