Previously on "The Flash"...
You never come back.
You are not stuck here, are you?
- Bye, Cisco.
- Bye, Sandy.
My father's death certificate.
The ME who signed off
on it, he doesn't exist.
- So this death certificate...
- Is a fake.
- Who the hell are you?
- What do you want?
For all of you
to die.
What the...
Damn, man.
Another fight?
Yeah.
I'd hate to see the other guy.
See you on the floor.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So you're not stuck here.
No, I'm not.
So they will reverse
tachyons in your system?
Were put there because of me.
Are you kidding?
You know how many credit
card points I just blew
trying to get rid of
your negative tachyons?
I just bought a brand
new spectral tachyeometer
when I could have my Fiji get away.
Not that I have anyone
to go with, anymore.
I'm not taking you to Fiji, Ralph.
Why didn't you guys tell
us about this before?
Oh, my God!
Barry never returns?
That's why you came here.
To see you father,
because you were raised without him.
So what?
Iris.
So what that that article
says that you never come back.
So what if the other one
says that you vanished.
I mean, it's said other
things before, right?
We made it say other things before.
So whatever the future brings
we are gonna deal with
it when it gets here.
And change it if we need to.
She has a point.
If there's anything
Team Flash is good at,
it's handing the future
its own ass and then some.
What he said.
Well, looks like Nora's
gonna need more training after all.
- Oh, okay.
- She's hungry.
Yeah, why don't we, uh,
all meet back at
S.T.A.R. Labs, all right?
Wow, first you meet your
adult daughter from the future
and now this.
I mean, it's a lot.
Yeah.
Well, I guess now I know why
she never wants to leave her dad's side
and why she...
Never wants to be by mine.
Nora will reach out at some point.
The trick is you gotta
keep yourself busy.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Dad.
Joe!
- Cecile?
- Cecile, what's wrong?
I can't hear what she wants.
I can't hear anything.
I think I'm losing my powers.
Hey babe, uh, it's me,
just checking in, for my dad.
He...
- Hello there.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- I was just trying to get
Barry's new suit into this ring.
Oh, it's... it's tiny.
Yeah, you weren't watching
old holograms of Gipsy.
- Why would I be doing that?
- Because you miss her.
We just had something so special.
Shouldn't it have work?
Of course now it's
not so special anymore
now she's just rattlin'
around inside my head.
I'm sorry this is so hard for you.
But it's okay that you are
still thinking about her.
I don't think you understand, Caitlin.
I mean, she's literally...
inside my head.
I can't vibe.
Everything I vibe connects to her.
I put some music on, I hear
her voice singing along.
I'm painting my
figurines, I see her face
on Captains Kirk's body. Shh...
Do you smell that?
Of course you don't.
'Cause that's her perfume
and I'm only one smelling it.
- Of course.
- Your powers linked you guys
over pan-dimensional spacetime,
so it makes complete sense
that your vibes echoes would still be...
Connecting us to each other.
Yes, I know. Thank
you for the diagnosis.
- I'm sorry.
- You don't need a doctor.
You need a friend.
I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm a mess.
- Oh, perfect.
- Been looking for you two.
We need to talk.
I've hit a real wall
trying to figure out
who forged this death certificate,
so I was thinking maybe
Cisco could give this
a little bit of a...
Cisco is not available right now.
Please leave a message.
Oh, hey, Cisco, it's Ralph.
Hope you are doing well.
Just get back to me.
I need to vibe this as soon as possible.
Bye, bye.
Ralph, um, Cisco can't vibe right now,
so we're just gonna have to
deal with this a little later.
- Why can't he vibe right now?
- What's going on?
Because we need to
help him get over Gipsy.
I mean, like you said,
Cisco get his vibe back,
- we can crack this case.
- Please, stop caring about me.
Ralph, I mean, you don't
have any ideas about
how to help a man get
over a heartbreak, do you?
Oh, my God, you stop it, girl.
You know I have plenty.
Cisco, you wanna know
why I'm perfect guy
to help you get over this and
get back into the game of love?
Because trust me, buddy,
nobody, I mean nobody,
has been kicked out
of that more than me.
- Hello, Bobby.
- Vanessa Jansen.
You got out of the slammer.
Now I'm gonna loosen up that chokehold
you and that punk-ass brother of yours
have on all the big
arms deals in this city.
I don't think so.
What the hell?
Do you know what four
years in Iron Heights
will do to you, Bobby?
It makes you very, very, angry.
Vanessa, you Cain't gonna do this.
Vanessa, please.
Okay.
So this is where the Moretti brothers
- have been running guns.
- Yeah.
Stealing from these
guys takes some cojones.
Any idea who our bold thieve might be?
- Not yet.
- Made my rounds too.
So far the only prints belong
to Bobby and Bruno Moretti.
Well, whoever did this,
they're running fast and loose.
- Mm-hmm.
- If we don't stop this,
a lot of high powered weapons
are gonna flood the streets.
Central City is gonna be a war zone.
Don't worry about the city, friend.
CCPD's finest are on the case.
- And you are...
- Nora, CSI intern.
- Who are you?
- The captain of CCPD.
Captain David Singh. Oh I've
read so much about you.
It's really nice to meet you.
You hired an intern, Allen?
I am very sorry, sir,
but I needed help with, um,
the cases that accumulated
while I was suspended
and you said the Mayor wasn't going
to give us any money to help solve them,
so I hired an intern to help for free.
Mm.
Well, make her official
when you get back.
- Yeah.
I know you're surprised to see me
but I found this badge and
this jacked and thought,
"I'm a CSI too" so I should help my dad.
Right, okay.
You said you were still a rookie, right?
Well, yeah, but forensic
sciences in the future
is like way advance, so I can
totally handle a robbery scene.
- Like, not a prob.
- Ah, got you.
- That's great.
- What is that?
That I haven't gotten to yet.
But it looks like somebody
wanted their pound of flesh.
- Nora, wait.
- Wha...
- What are you doing?
- You can't touch that.
You'll contaminate the evidence.
Sorry, you mean you don't have
a scene-wide modified
bosonic frequency field
to avoid cross-contamination?
I don't even think we have
some of those words yet.
Oops. Well... ugh.
It's just this seems way
denser than human tissue.
Yeah, you're right, actually.
I can't even move this thing.
This isn't a pound of flesh.
This is a whole human body.
That is so schway.
Let's hold off in telling
the Mayor about this
until we have some more info.
She's still be upset
about the Lang homicide.
Hey, Captain, did you mean Gridlock?
I thought he was locked
up in Iron Heights.
Iris, it's a pleasure to see you.
Can we secure the crime scene, please?
You know I can't make
a comment on the record.
Okay, well, how about off the record?
Just once and that's it,
and only because it's you.
Okay.
While in transport to Iron Heights
the convoy was attacked.
Lang was killed by something strong.
- We think maybe a meta.
- Were there any survivors?
Four guards, they are
still in the hospital.
- So if you hear anything...
- Yeah, I got you.
Thanks.
Put this away, and, hey.
- Here, put these on.
- Okay.
You do have...
The book of Ralph.
Yep, and we are gonna
start with a page of Ralph
'cause he's nowhere near
ready for this whole book.
"Ralph Dibny's 27 steps
to getting over the love of your life."
Are you kidding me with this?
We just want to help you get past Gipsy.
And if this has worked for Ralph...
Multiple times I will add.
Then I think it's worth trying.
Come on, what's step one?
Shark cage diving.
- What's step two?
- Affirmations.
- Oh.
- Okay.
Ralphy is kind. Ralphy is great.
Ralphy is a brilliant detective.
Yeah, buddy, I mean, I know all that.
But it works a lot better
if you use your name instead.
Cisco is creative. Cisco is good.
Cisco is smarter than your average bear.
That's Yogi's. You
stole Yogi's affirmation.
Yeah, I did, 'cause it's a winner.
You don't see him moping
over any lady bears.
Okay, you know what, Caitlin?
I changed my mind, all right?
I... I don't care about the Gipsy vibes.
I'll just muscle through them,
let's just help you with your thing
and just get me the
hell out of here, please?
No, Cisco, after Ronnie and Jay
you helped me get back past it.
Now it's my turn to help you.
Okay? So...
We don't have time to
find ourselves in Thailand.
And we are certainly
not watching "Beaches"
while painting each others toes.
That's a really important one, though.
But step twelve isn't so bad.
Holy Kafka.
Come on, Cisco, change is good.
No, no, no.
Change is pain.
It's not as painful as
seeing you like this, buddy.
Fine.
Whatever you say, doc.
Um, Officer Matthews?
Yes.
Hi, I'm Iris West-Allen.
I'm reporter, and I'm doing
a story about William Lang.
- Gridlock.
- Pardon?
You call him Gridlock.
In your blog I've read it. It's good.
Thanks.
Um, I understand that you
were part of the convoy
that was escorting him to Iron
Heights when you were attacked.
- Something like that.
- What do you mean?
I mean I really don't
remember what happened.
One minute I was in my
vehicle there was a pile up,
I got out to see what's going on.
Everything went black.
Finally came to and Lang's
laying there on the ground,
beaten to a pulp.
He was beaten to death?
Beaten, then stabbed.
- Was anyone else hurt?
- No.
Everyone else on SWAT
was concussed like me.
So, Lang was the only target?
Looks like it.
Thanks for your time.
- Oh, hi, sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Hey.
- I just...
- I got a little too excited.
Okay, guess what?
You know my powers have
been fading in and out.
Mostly out.
Well, I am definitely losing them.
You weren't that excited
about that this morning.
- No.
- No, I was not.
But I'm excited now
because I have a fix.
I have a fix!
Mental activity dampener 2.0.
2.0.
Harry altered it so that
you can hear the thoughts
of whoever is wearing it.
And why would we wanna do that?
So we can make sure it works
before we put it on Jenna.
Uh-uh.
Oh, honey, it's completely safe,
Harry used it on his own daughter,
It doesn't mean we
have to use it on ours.
Oh, ok... okay. Honey, listen.
I have had a constant
telepathic connection to our child
since before she was born.
It's been constant.
Babe, now when she cries half
the time I don't know why.
Look, she's an infant.
They cry and you always get to know why.
No, not... me.
You don't understand.
I haven't been the mother
to a newborn in a long time.
When I got pregnant,
baby, I was so scared.
But then I got powers.
These powers that...
gave me a chance to be a perfect parent.
The parent that our child deserves.
And now they're going away?
I'm scared I can't live up to that.
I know you're struggling, babe.
But that device...
isn't the solution.
We'll figure out, okay?
But...
I got it.
Ugh, these old-timey computers
are even slower than the ones
in storage at the Flash Museum.
DNA analysis used to take a lot longer
even just ten years ago.
So, Mom took the news
about you being gone
better than I thought she would.
Iris is as though as they come.
I'm sure you know that.
Got a match. Vanessa Jansen.
Low level weapon dealer
affiliated with the
East Street Skulls gang.
I ran into a couple of
them when I was in prison.
- You were in prison?
- Mm-hmm.
That wasn't in the museum.
The Skulls make the Hell's Angels
look like a knitting
club, drug trafficking,
armed robbery.
Any places Jansen's known to frequent?
East Street Auto Haven.
Looks like it's probably a
front for Skull's activities.
Yes, time to take down my first baddie!
Uh, with your permission, of course.
Let's do it.
What is the hold up? These
you are gonna move fast.
Well, I guess, I heard right.
You got something you're selling.
Too late, another interested
customer just showed up.
You're looking to buy, Bruno?
From the broad who killed my
brother and stole our stash?
This is way out of your league, Vanessa.
See, I would've agree with you...
before prison.
But then I got out and it hit me...
I'm tougher now, Bruno.
I got connections with people
that would pay big money for my weapons.
Except, they're not your weapons.
Like I said...
I'm tougher now.
All right, I'm gonna take
Vanessa and the gangster.
Why don't you just scan the perimeter
for any back up she might have.
- I can do better than that.
- What?
Whoa, what're you...
Crap.
Sorry, I can't let you hurt him.
Or take this.
Didn't know I was a meta.
Don't feel bad, it's my new look.
- Vanessa!
- The Flash!
I guess I better put my hands up.
How long do you think it will...
I think Nora is good to go.
She didn't even need an Ibuprofen.
- You sure you feel okay?
- I'm totally okay.
Come on, let's get back to work, Flash.
Okay.
All right, well let's figure
out where Vanessa went.
If she sells those stolen
weapons to the wrong people I...
Um, Cisco, were you
able to get the satellite
up and running? Cisco?
We weren't able to track Vanessa,
but we did find a scientific anomaly
that we've never seen
before, right, Cisco?
- Han shot second.
- That doesn't even make sense.
Ralph, it's you.
Sorry to lie like that, man.
- We just... we need the CCTV...
- CCTV, yes.
Vanessa Jansen's concentrated
air squares are dense
very dense, stupid dense.
The kind of dense reserved for
people who still believe...
In love.
I think what Cisco is trying to say
is that Vanessa can manipulate
the movement of atoms
to created concentrated
air molecules in cube form.
The space between the
molecules is so compact that...
That there isn't enough
room for a speedster
to vibrate trough them.
What do you call someone who
can compress air molecules
- into solid blocks?
- I don't know, Block.
So, I guess Cisco is still
taking the Gipsy thing pretty hard?
Well, we're working on it.
But you can't expect real progress
till you hit step 17.
It's this thing we're
working on with Cisco.
You can do without us
for a little while, right?
I mean, we are blind
without our satellite
so we're just gonna have to wait
until Vanessa makes
her next move anyway.
What about you? Gonna
hang out here for a bit?
Actually, I am working on a lead.
- Huh.
- Can I use your lab?
There's something I wanna follow up on.
- Yeah, of course.
- Okay.
Okay.
Uh, what kind of training is this?
Well, speedsters need
to know about physics,
aerodynamics, trajectory formulas.
And after your last
encounter with Jansen,
I think is time for you
to get back to basics.
- My training is math?
- Yeah.
I think chapter one is
probably a good place to start.
Al right, you're in for a real treat.
He initially said no,
but after I told him
that your cousin was John Stamos.
My cousin is not John Stamos.
He agreed to you on.
I proudly present my
personal stylist, Bruce.
This guy does it all, hair, makeup.
He picks everything I wear.
- That explains that.
- Come on.
Bruce is gonna help us
accomplish step twelve.
Metamorphosis.
Does that mean you think
there's something wrong
with me?
Even a Ferrari needs a
tune-up every once in a while.
This feels like purgatory.
You cut my hair, I cut you.
My work here is done.
So...
I hate it.
I hate it all.
Great, now that that's
over and done with.
Why don't we focus on
the death certificate?
Well, I mean, we need to vibe it.
Or we can ask Joe to do some
good old fashion police work.
Did you ever think of that?
Let's not worry about it, okay?
No, I mean, it's a good idea.
- We'll just ah...
- Let's give him a call.
Guys, stop. Seriously, cut it out!
Okay?
Forget about the death certificate
and let's just focus on
helping our friend, okay?
I need a break.
Okay, so the key with Higgs
particles isn't the math per se
but the effect they have on
the mass of other particles.
- Yeah.
- Question.
How would one go about
performing a supersonic punch
on one of those particles?
- Nora.
- Dad, I'm sorry,
but I already know all of this.
My high school textbooks
had laws of physics
that this time hasn't even discover yet.
I don't need this kind of training
I need to learn how to be like you.
What do you think it
means to be like me?
You know, running so fast
you can stop a tsunami.
Or vibrating something
bigger than a plane.
Or how about defeating a sand demon
by throwing lighting at him.
Nora, look, all those things
are way behind your current skill level.
You gotta stick to what
you can handle right now.
Uh, just because I'm your daughter
doesn't mean you have to baby me.
I can handle way more than you think.
Watch.
Dad!
- Dad, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I've been hit with lighting before.
Ow.
- It's okay.
- It's not okay.
I guess greatness isn't hereditary.
Body cam footage.
Officer Matthews.
Bingo!
What the hell was that?
Stay where you are. Freeze don't move.
What was that?
Hey, I need your help.
- That's blunt.
- Yeah, so Nora,
isn't really spending
any time with Iris.
So she's kind of with me
all the time, you know?
And I've been training
her a lot by myself
and I just don't get it.
I mean, it's like...
She keeps taking things on
that she can't handle yet.
It's like she wants
to go big for big sake
and I try to walk her back, but
it's like she's not listening
to what I'm teaching her, you know?
It's actually that
she hears the opposite
of what I'm saying. Why are you nodding?
Are you agreeing with me?
Do you remember your
4th grade science fair?
Yeah, but what does that
have to do with this?
All you had to do is make
a baking soda volcano.
- And what did you do?
- I...
You built a robot with wheels,
pretty much set the gym on fire.
Almost got Mrs. Dumas too.
- But that was different.
- How so?
That was the first year you took me in.
I mean, you took me when I had no one.
I looked up to you. I
mean, you were my hero.
I...
I really wanted to impress you.
Bar, all the information
this girl has on you
comes from that museum.
There're literally statues
of you on pedestals.
How do you think she
wants to impress her hero?
So what do I do?
Well, show her it's
okay not to be perfect
coming out of the gate.
There's no shortcuts.
Takes time to get things
right and that's not a failure.
That's life.
And also show her that no matter what
you're always gonna love her.
That's what parents do.
Yeah.
- Yeah, thanks, Joe.
- Mm.
See you later.
Mm. Mm.
Mm.
What was that for?
Just 'cause.
Uh-uh. I got her.
Yeah, you do.
Ah, yes, the sugary pastry.
I think as far as avoiding
your feelings goes,
cinnamon bun was a solid choice.
You look nice.
Yeah, well, I think Bruce
burned all my clothes, so...
Hmm.
Why don't you want to investigate
your dad's death certificate?
Because...
if it's true...
if he has been alive this whole time...
I just means he didn't want to see me.
Step 27:
Accept that she isn't
the love of your life
because if she were,
she'd still be in it.
- Pretty deep for Ralph Dibny.
- Yeah.
Granted it took him 26 swings
before he could hit the ball.
I don't know...
I think he might of knocked
out of the park with that one.
Gipsy isn't the one.
I know that.
And there's no amount
of new clothes or...
crazy makeover distraction
that can change that fact.
Because some truths you
can only hide for so long.
The truth is, it's too late for
me to change things with her.
But it's not too late for you.
It's not too late for you to
change things with your dad.
But what if he doesn't
want anything to do with me.
Maybe he doesn't.
But wouldn't you rather face that truth
instead of spending the
rest of your life wondering?
- Is this part of my training?
- Just watch.
- Schway, is that you?
- Yeah.
A few weeks after I got my powers.
OG Flash. God, look at you move.
Yeah, just wait for it.
And this.
- Yeah.
- Oh!
It takes time to hone your skills, Nora.
You can't just can't just
skip rungs on a ladder
or jump right to the big
stuff. It's not how it works.
All right, that's enough of that.
Look, when you first got here
you said that you
weren't a great speedster.
But obviously neither was
I when I first started.
Um, do you think one day
I will be great like you?
You punched out a satellite
while I was falling to
the earth and on fire.
And you were moving so fast
even I couldn't see who you were.
- Yeah, that was pretty epic.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you today.
I just wanted to make you proud.
Sometimes for people with our abilities
the most impressive feat is restraint.
I want what's mine, Vanessa.
Now step aside.
Because you brought a
bigger gun this time?
Not happening.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
I'm sure.
Hey, guys. Any luck with Block?
Nothing. No. Anything at the lab?
Uh, maybe. It's still a
little too early to tell.
Unit 7-5-2 requesting a 10-61.
- What is that?
- Nothing.
An officer requesting
to go on a coffee break.
Not having our satellites is killing us.
I mean, we can't scan
the city for dark matter
we don't have facial recognition.
All we'd need to do is
see if there any pockets
of compressed air around
the city and we'd have her.
You mean gauging atmospheric
pressure like a barometer?
Yeah, but it would have
to be a big barometer.
You mean like channel
52 Doppler radar relay?
Yeah, I mean, Vanessa's
blocks are constructed
of highly dense air, so they'd
have the same composition
as an extreme atmospheric system.
So, we track the
weather and we find her.
- That's so schway.
- Okay, yeah.
Let's do it, yeah.
- Go Team West-Allen.
- Yeah!
Okay, look, there's a
high-density low-pressure zone
in a six block radius
around Pacific and Davies.
Okay, cool. All right, let's go.
Hey, maybe I should just stay here.
Or you could put some
of that training to use.
Last chance, Vanessa.
To do what?
Just give me the keys
so I can drive my weapons out of here.
Come on.
Just hand them over nice and easy.
Yeah, right.
Light her up!
You two. I swear...
She's getting tired.
We got her.
Yeah, we did.
- Gotcha.
- Uh-oh.
- Flash is trapped!
What's wrong? What's happening?
Barry's in trouble.
She gets tired.
Hey, blockhead! Try that on me!
Bit off more than you could chew, huh?
Well, my work here is done.
Looks like she's a regular
chip off the ol' block.
- Am I...
- Don't.
Okay, yeah, I know.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get her to a hospital.
XS! Now!
Barry? What is it?
- Who's there?
- I don't know yet.
I just lost my speed.
- I got nothing.
- Negative, Ghost Rider.
Guys, I know we're
three against one, but
something tells me this
guy's got the advantage.
Barry!
What is that sound?
Oh, my God.
Barry!
Barry, you got get out
of there right now!
Dad!
Dad.
- Dad, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
I mean, this is definitely dark matter,
but these levels of
concentration are unlike
like any dark matter levels
I've ever seen before.
Yeah, well, that wasn't
quite like any ass kicking
I've ever gotten before either.
That dagger he had,
I think that negated our powers.
And he control it too, like Mjolnir.
That's Thor's hammer.
I'm just glad you guys are okay.
This could've been a lot worst.
Yeah.
Careful. Those cuts are pretty deep.
It could take a while for them to heal.
Cisco, that's not important right now.
Look, if you wanna know,
this is your chance.
I support you either way, Caitlin.
I'm sorry. I don't know what happened.
Caitlin, did you see something?
Yeah, I did.
My mother.
Hey, guys.
Let's go.
Hey, we got a big problem.
So I talked to Captain Singh
and he said that Gridlock
was killed during his
transport to Iron Heights.
- Gridlock's dead?
- How?
I'm not sure.
I interviewed everyone that was there
and no one knows.
But I did some digging...
What the hell is that?
Stay where you are! Freeze! Don't move!
Okay, so what are we looking for here?
Not looking. Listening.
It sounds like the guy
who just attacked us.
Sounds like an insect.
Yeah, it does.
- Like a...
- Like a cicada.
Who's Cicada?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --