10-38 on Dayton Boulevard
at Second Street intersection,
unit en route.
Routine traffic stop downtown.
Oh, yeah.
It looks like it was a good day
to pull monitor duty, Chester P.
Ooh. Snack time.
Damn!
I was supposed to make
the egg salad this morning.
Grandma Runk
is going to be epically mad.
Now I got nada for lunch.
Although, legally, I am entitled
to break every four hours,
and it's only gonna take me,
like, four minutes
because the kitchen
is just right down the hall.
Then again, that is time enough
for a nuclear meltdown
and an alien invasion in this town.
- So...
- Hey, Chuck.
Oh, what up, A?
I thought you'd be working.
I was. And then I remembered
it's Wednesday,
and that place I told you about at
last week's D&D game, Hirschfield's.
Today is when they have their amazing
chicken Parmesan sandwiches.
So I thought, "It's lunchtime.
Why not surprise you with the treat?"
Wow, thanks.
Guess I'm lunch date worthy now, huh?
Chuck, you are date worthy
in all the major categories.
I am?
Yeah, definitely.
I mean, that's good.
That's good to know, you know,
and I, too, think that you are also,
um, what you just, like, worthy
of what you just said a second ago.
Holy Alice H. Parker.
Okay, we've got a mugging
in progress up at 119.
And a carjacking at
the Edwards Center parking lot.
And a hold up at Jitters.
And they're all happening right now.
Don't worry, guys, already on it.
Uh, all of it, Boss?
You heard me.
I want everything in the register,
and a triple shot latte
with oat milk, not soy!
I think these guys could use
some help finding their cells.
Thanks, Flash.
Yeah.
What's going on out here?
- I didn't do nothing.
- I want to see my lawyer.
Yeah, what they said.
Hey...
Any chance Flash brought
that latte I ordered?
Officers, take these gentlemen
to holding, please.
Ow.
Captain. Hey.
Staff meeting's canceled, Allen,
and for the record,
you'd have been late.
Sorry, I, uh, was just... I got caught up
with a little blood spatter analysis,
but it looks like
you've had a busy morning.
Yeah, and it's about to turn into
a busy afternoon, evening and night,
thanks to this generous donation
from the Scarlet Speedster.
But the Flash caught those guys,
that's a good thing, right?
How can I press charges when
I don't know what crimes were committed,
how they were done and where?
I forgot that file's on my desk.
I'll be right back.
And it's not like we can just
call up the Flash and ask.
Yeah, like on a Flash phone or...
Yeah.
That's a terrible name.
Uh, but Captain, C.C.P.D.'s never had
a line to the Flash before.
Yeah. But, for once,
I would like to feel
like the Flash and law enforcement
are on the same page.
Instead of us just
always playing catch up.
But, since that's not happening,
cancel any plans you have for tonight.
We've got a lot of legwork to do.
You're welcome.
Sounds like Kramer has a point.
Uh, look, maybe I could do
a better job communicating
when I'm dropping off criminals.
But giving C.C.P.D.
a direct line to the Flash,
you don't really think
that's necessary, do you?
I don't know, Barr. When I was captain,
I had a direct line to the Flash.
Mm, I mean, me, too.
When I was district attorney,
if I had a question on a case,
all I ever had to do was call you
and get the details.
That's because you're family.
Which she is not, and I get that.
But what she and I went through
when we were tracking down Craig,
I... I trust her with my life.
And maybe you should consider
letting her in a bit more.
Give her one of the alert apps
that we all have on our phones.
Joe, look, I get it.
She's a good cop.
She's a great captain.
And when I first got my speed.
I needed a lot of help.
Not just from Caitlin and Cisco,
but from you and
everybody at C.C.P.D.
- But now...
- Now you've leveled up.
Yeah.
Which means I can find other ways
to solve Kramer's Flash problem,
like doing extra C.S.I. work to collect
what she needs for processing.
I mean, that'll ease
the burden for her, right?
It sounds like it, and I get how
keeping church and state separated
is the easiest choice,
but I also know Kramer,
and if she's asking
for a line to the Flash,
she probably has a good reason.
Just saying.
Maybe you want to think about it
before you decide what to do, Barr.
Waddup, party people!
It's your boy, Chester P,
and I'm ready to rock your world
with knowledge
for free, free, free, free.
Hey, today we have a self-flying drone
based off of an AI algorithm
created by yours truly.
I'm gonna upload the specs online
because here at the Runk Yard,
we keep tech openly sourced,
and classy.
All right,
how is this even possible?
I have silenced my phone,
I have turned off all the notifications,
and look at what keeps popping up.
This all from Frost and Mark?
Oh, you mean my sister
and her ex-con-boyfriend?
Yes, they are.
Look at what they're doing.
Looks cool.
No, it looks dangerous.
Hey, hey, Caitlin, do you mind just
taking a wee little step to the right?
Are you live streaming?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
WookiLover77 says,
"Who's the girl?
Her sister seems cooler."
Okay, that's it for today.
Smash that "Like" button.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm just so annoyed.
Mark keeps taking Frost
on all these ridiculous dates.
Well, maybe tonight will distract you.
Don't you have a date, too?
Yes. Yeah. Marcus is taking me
to the Spanish Hamper.
How'd he get you guys a reservation
for the hottest place in town?
That's impressive.
Is it turning serious?
I mean, he's really nice,
and I like nice.
So, that's nice. It's nice.
Oh, man. I can see it now.
He doesn't know we're on Team Flash.
But soon, you and Marcus
are gonna fall in love,
and then he's going to join us for,
like, some crazy adventure.
Then, boom! He's on the team.
Hey, hey, maybe he'll learn
how to control plants.
It's their third date, Chuck.
So maybe just slow your roll.
You're right, right. Reel it.
Reel it back.
Yeah, speaking of,
I should go get ready.
Good night, guys.
- Have fun.
- Bye.
Fancy date night.
- Sounds expensive.
- Yeah, right.
Could be fun, though.
Yeah, I have to go write, article...
I gotta type things,
algorithms and such. Mm-hmm.
Oh, that's a typo.
- Huh? Oh.
- No, uh, I'm just thinking out loud.
I'm just gonna...
Hey, Captain, you got a sec?
I'm on my way to Processing.
These will come in handy.
Um, I cross referenced the 911 calls
from this morning
with the description of the perps
that the Flash brought in.
And then I hit the crime scenes,
fingerprints, security footage.
Korber even interviewed witnesses.
So, this should be everything you need
to wrap up these cases.
Wow, I appreciate the hustle, Allen.
I just wish it was more than
a band aid on a bullet wound.
Well, you have more than enough
to charge all three suspects.
What about the suspects
the Flash drops off tomorrow,
or the day after that?
Respectfully, Captain.
I mean, this is the way
we've done things the past seven years,
ever since the Flash showed up.
You know, the system works.
From your perspective.
But there are things
you don't need to worry about
as a forensic scientist
that I need to consider as Captain.
I understand that.
But you know, the Flash
is just trying to help this city.
And he does, all the time.
But together,
we could help it even more,
humans and meta-humans alike.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Time to get to work.
What the hell?
What are these?
They're meta dampening bracelets.
I've seen these before.
Wakey wakey, ladies and gents in blue.
Folks call me Goldface.
That's because if it's made of gold,
it's mine to control.
From your dental fillings
to 0.35 grams of gold
in your cell phones.
Don't even bother
trying to phone a friend.
Because we knocked out
the nearest cell phone tower.
But, if anyone does come calling,
they'll find a couple of
Central City's finest outside
telling them there's a gas leak.
What are you doing? What are you... Hey.
Goldface.
This is my precinct.
You have a problem,
you take it up with me.
But my officers go.
Ah.
If it isn't the famous Kristen Kramer.
I loved you
on the Citizentopia podcast.
Very inspiring.
Thanks.
Captain, I'm guessing
you want to play hero.
Let me let my man Carver here
show you what happens
to anyone that gets out of line.
Now, you may have all noticed that
you're sporting a new piece of jewelry.
Well, since Captain Mimic here
outed herself as a meta,
I figured she may not be
the only one of you.
But these bracelets,
they don't just dampen powers,
they also do this.
You feeling me now, Captain?
Hold on.
Don't I know you?
You're that rat that cost me
the organ printer.
The chemist!
Yes. Um, yeah.
Look, I was on an undercover assignment.
Look, why don't you just tell us
what it is you want?
Nobody has to die tonight.
You know, my lady, Amunet Black?
Not only is she the finest female
this side of the Mississippi,
she's got some intel
that there are some very rare
and valuable items in your armory.
I want what's in there.
So I'mma go get it.
And if anyone tries anything...
We get the belt.
Good memory, chemist.
Keep an eye on this one.
He smells of trouble.
Seriously, Marcus, I am so sorry.
I cannot believe I made
a dinner reservation for next January.
Please don't feel bad.
Last week at work,
I screwed up the blooming cycle
for the Selenicereus grandiflorus
I've been growing.
Should've seen all the pollen.
Thank you. I mean, you're really,
you're just such a trouper.
This first round is on me.
This place is a little seedier
than I remember.
It's fun. Plus, they got karaoke.
Next up,
The Ice Pack.
- There is that.
- Yeah.
You're as cold as ice
You're willing to sacrifice our love
Hey! Way off-key but they're committed.
We need to leave.
Caity?
What a coinkidink.
What are the two of you doing here?
We are just grabbing a casual drink,
but it's too crowded in here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Is this
the infamous Marcus, as in Dr. Ficus?
- Um... Yes.
- Holy crap!
Hey, you two are here.
Mark and I are here.
We should totally make this
a double date.
Yes!
Oh, no, we'll let you
get back to it.
Hey, they've got great food here.
- Um, if you like to live dangerously.
- We don't.
But you want to stay, right?
- We can workshop some plant-y ice puns.
- Um...
Um, well, I've heard a lot about Frost.
It'd be nice to have a person
to go with the stories.
Yeah, yeah.
Great.
Let's double date.
I count three hostiles
guarding us here, two at the exits.
Carver's with Goldface
in the armory.
We have the numbers
to take back the building.
Except everyone on our side
has a bomb strapped to their wrist.
These things are ultra-sensitive.
You tamper with them, they'll blow.
The same goes for Goldface's belt.
We've got to do something.
Whatever it is, we've got to do it fast.
Captain, do you have any idea what
Goldface wants in the armory?
All I can tell you, Allen,
is if he gets in there,
things are gonna get a lot worse.
Open sesame.
According to Amunet's intel,
the target should be in there.
I love my woman.
Not what you're expecting, Boss?
Of course it's not. It's empty.
Go get Kramer.
And her little chemist, too.
Where the hell are they?
I don't know what you mean.
The meta-bullets.
Remember, Captain? The ones you had
commissioned for your task force?
One shot takes away
any meta's powers forever.
Am I ringing any bells?
That's what you're stealing?
That's what I'm selling.
The power to take down
any meta in this city,
including, say it with me...
The Flash.
Well, that's going to bring me
a lot of gold.
But those bullets
aren't where they're supposed to be.
Captain, any thoughts on that?
Yeah.
Those bullets belong to C.C.P.D.
for only the most severe emergencies.
Also, I'd die before betraying
the metas of this city,
and putting them in any danger.
Mm.
I'm willing to bet you'd risk
your own life, Captain, but...
How about this fool's?
Let him go!
Tell me where the meta-bullets
are hidden, Captain.
You have till three.
One, two...
I can help you.
Oh, yeah, chemist?
Like you helped me steal that printer?
The meta-bullets have trace elements
of the dark matter.
- I've got a scanner in my lab.
- Let me guess.
I let you go, you go get it
and bring it right back to me?
Allen, what are you doing?
I can adjust the scanner.
It will find the bullets.
They have to be here somewhere.
When we first met,
I knew you couldn't be trusted.
Plot twist. You're not only
untrustworthy, you're a coward.
Watch Kramer.
I'm gonna take the chemist here
on a little field trip.
One last chance to live up to his name.
All right.
We got a Dark 'N' Stormy for Marcus,
Chardonnay for Caitlin,
and a whisky for Mark and me,
on the rocks, of course.
Thanks, Snowflake.
You know, there's a cactus plant
that makes great cocktails.
The pads of the Opuntia cacti
pair perfectly with an agave spirit.
I bet it would really cover the taste
of strychnine, too.
- Strychnine!
- Wow.
A genius botanist,
who can mix drinks, I like him already.
So, how did you two meet?
Oh...
Well, we met here, actually.
Mark was...
Pouring beers by day
and murdering delivery men by night.
- What? It's true.
- She's exaggerating it.
Well, not exactly.
Okay, fine.
Mark and I each spent some time
on the wrong side of the law.
But I paid for my crimes,
and Mark turned state's witness
against some really bad guys.
Yeah, and the DA expunged my record.
So now, clean as a whistle.
Well, seems like you've
turned over a new leaf.
Hey, Dr. Ficus.
- There he is.
- So good.
Hey, I kind of like that.
Listen, Frost and I are going skydiving
again next weekend.
Double date round two?
What do you say?
I mean, you seem cool, man.
I don't know, I've...
I've always wanted to go skydiving.
I'm game. What do you say, Caity?
Marcus, did you know
that when Mark got out,
he seduced my sister
so that he could steal a weapon out
from right under her nose.
- After he helped us save the day.
- And she was so upset
that she just kept moping and crying
and even needed to take a sabbatical.
- Caitlin...
- I apologized for all of that.
And I accepted it.
Frost, I mean, how naive can you be?
He's already betrayed you.
And yet you're out there live streaming
the two of you
jumping out of airplanes
and making out on cliffs.
- Remember Mount Shasta?
- Hell yeah.
Frost, what is wrong with you?
You're acting like some stupid teenager
falling in love with this guy,
who's already hurt you.
And, guess what,
is definitely going to do it again.
And you know what?
When that happens,
I am not picking up the pieces
because I am done with broken hearts.
You got that?
You know, we get it.
You don't like me, but Frost
is an adult with her own life,
and so long as she's choosing
to spend it with me,
then you need to deal with it.
Are you really going to let him
talk to me that way?
- Your sister?
- Yeah, I am.
Because he's my boyfriend and anything
else is none of your damn business.
Hey.
I think I'd like to go home.
- I'll pull the car around.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. Do you mind?
Oh. My bad.
Maybe I should just take
a leisurely stroll down the hallway.
I'm gonna watch you like a hawk
watching a juicy vole.
Do you need to take that?
Baby girl, what time is it now
in London town?
You eating a nice balanced breakfast
like we discussed,
not just the bangers and mash?
Meta-bullets?
Yep, not exactly.
Yeah, uh-huh. Yeah, baby...
I know the buyer's schedule, baby.
Yes, baby.
No, we just hit a teensy little snag.
But you know me.
I got it all worked out.
Okay, I love you, too.
I said, I love you up top,
Ammy Whammy.
I lub, lub, tub, Ammy Whammy.
I say something funny?
No. No, you just...
You seem to have a great relationship
with Amunet.
Police reports
say you work together now.
Damn right,
we have a great relationship,
- and it's because we work together.
- Hmm.
Ammy and I used to have separate crews,
separate heists, separate hideouts,
but it's like Dr. Finkel says,
"If you want your partner
to enter your heart,
you can't just open the doors.
You gotta open the windows."
So, you see Dr. Finkel?
Sharon sees us, man.
Okay? And she helped us realize
that we never were truly committed.
But now we're not just partners in love,
we're partners in crime.
And since we stopped holding back
and have gone all in,
our relationship's never been better,
or more lucrative.
And if I don't have those meta-bullets
in hand, within the next hour,
Ammy Whammy says
our buyer is going to walk.
So, you... look, the dark matter
we're looking for is microscopic.
So, I'm sorry,
I'm going to need more time.
No. You need incentive.
Barry, you don't have to help him.
Finish the scanner now.
Or your Captain gets to meet
the white whale.
Hell yeah.
She's gonna
walk the plank, y'all.
Ahab didn't... I'm sorry,
do you not know Moby Dick?
"To the last I grapple with thee."
What about Wrath of Khan?
"From hell's heart I stab at thee.
For hate's sake I spit my last..."
I bought you a first edition
for your birthday.
BA in Literature from Yale.
I'm surrounded by Philistines.
Time's up. Waste her.
No. Wait, wait, wait.
Um, look, it might not be perfect,
but the scanner is done.
Now, there's that service
with a smile I've been waiting for.
Uh...
So, all you have to do
is touch this button right here.
Put these in. Put these in.
How did you...
I've reset the scanner from infrared
to infrasonic.
Come on. We gotta go. Come on.
Time to make them go boom, boss?
Not when she's the only one
who can tell me
where the bullets are hidden now.
Find them.
Nobody hides from Goldface.
Nobody!
What does it look like out there?
Clear.
But it's only a matter of time
before we're discovered.
We need to figure out
our next move fast.
Okay. This is a storage room
for junked equipment.
So, let's look for anything
we can patch up and use,
tools to get these bracelets off,
anything.
Hold on.
- Captain, look.
- It's deactivated.
How is that possible?
Your powers work by mimicking the powers
in nearby metas, right?
Yes. Whenever I'm in high stress
situations around other metas
it just happens.
For about 30 seconds,
I gain their powers. Why?
These bracelets release RNA
energy pulses that repress meta genes.
Your DNA is constantly morphing
based on your adrenal levels,
and your proximity to other metas.
The cuffs weren't designed
to handle erratic gene fluctuations.
So...
So, my mimic powers
short-circuited the bracelet.
This is great.
Okay, now you can mimic
Goldface's powers and take him down.
He'll never see you coming.
No, I am not ready for that.
Why not? This is the chance
we've been waiting for.
I said I can't do it, Allen.
Let's just stick with your plan.
Find something here that can help us.
We don't have much time.
Pardonne-moi, madame.
Room here for two to pay their tab?
Don't want this fine establishment
to think I'm a thief.
So, you disappear when people
want you to stick around,
but you stick around
when people want you to disappear?
I'm all kinds of complicated, Caitlin.
Maybe that's why you can't see
how much we have in common.
Yeah, believe it or not,
both of us care about Frost.
Yeah, and that's why you abandoned her.
I...
Fine, I screwed up before,
but Frost is special,
and so I'm making up for it
as best I can.
I'm even putting in time
with the family.
Yeah, well,
what do you know about family?
Uh, I know that mine's
dysfunctional as hell.
And the way you went off in there,
you kind of reminded me of them.
Yeah, you sounded just like
my frumpy, backstabbing nana,
at every Blaine family reunion ever.
I mean, talk about cold.
Congratulations.
You actually gave me flashbacks.
I'm sorry I blew up.
But if you care about Frost
as much as you say you do,
then you'll agree that she deserves
someone who...
Accepts her, warts and all,
just like I do?
Caitlin, like it or not,
Frost and I are all in.
There is no holding back
or hiding pieces of ourselves.
Like you.
What are you talking about?
Come on, I used to tend bar, remember?
This isn't about Snowflake and I.
This is about you
being more focused on hating me
than focusing on your own date.
You've been holding back all night
because you're afraid
to go all in with Marcus.
Am I wrong?
Look, it's...
It's okay to be scared.
But at some point
you've got to take a leap of faith
like I did with Frost
and like she's doing with me.
Trust me, it's the best decision
that either of us have ever made.
Hmm.
And one more thing...
Marcus is a really good guy.
So maybe stop thinking about
what it is you have to lose
and start thinking about what it is
you might gain.
You know?
Thanks.
- For what?
- Gotta go.
You find anything?
No, not yet.
Let's just keep looking.
Captain, your powers are
our only hope of stopping Goldface.
I told you, I can't.
- Why not?
- Because I can't control them.
Barry, the other day,
I ordered an iced coffee,
but when I picked it up,
it boiled in my hand.
Turns out the barista was a heat meta
and I mimicked her powers
without even realizing it.
Well, I...
I understand, but you can work
on controlling your powers.
I have tried.
But I can't figure it out,
and no one can teach me.
That's why you've been so anxious
about getting in touch with the Flash?
You want him to train you.
Why didn't you just say
that was the reason earlier?
Because it's hard for me
to ask for help.
And...
When I mimicked
that other meta's abilities,
if they had been more lethal,
I could have killed someone without even
realizing what was happening.
I was hoping Flash
could help me learn to control them,
but he's out of reach.
I am madness maddened.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are, Captain.
Because if you don't
I'm going to do this
the old-fashioned way
and start squeezing your brave officers
until they pop.
Two minutes, Captain. Tick-tock.
Clock's ticking down, Captain.
Captain, you have to go down there
right now.
Don't you think I know that?
Look, I did two tours
on a Kandaki battlefield,
I am not afraid of dying.
And I won't let any more women
or men under my command get hurt.
But, right now, I don't know
how to prevent that.
You have to use your powers.
Look, I know you're worried
about losing control,
but the military gave you
all the training you'll ever need
to harness your own instincts.
So, instead of worrying about trying
to control Goldface's powers,
just let it in.
Let it take over, and then go all in
on trusting your instincts.
Believe me, you can do this.
Even if I could, what good would it do?
It will give me the 30 seconds I need
to get this cuff off.
- What?
- O Captain, my Captain.
Just stall Goldface
until I can get us help.
Barry, you saw what happens when someone
tries to take off that trinket.
- Do you have a death wish?
- No. I can do this.
And you can handle Goldface.
You know why?
You are one of the bravest people
I've ever met.
Let's take back our house.
I'm done playing, Captain.
You've got 30 seconds
to give me what I want,
or Officer...
What's your name again?
Korber.
Is that with a C or with a K?
- K.
- K, thanks.
It's Bye, Felicia,
for Officer Korber here.
And for every minute
I'm empty-handed after that,
another person dies.
Thirty.
Twenty nine.
Twenty eight. 27.
Boss, you could just skip
the counting and kill her, you know.
You have no sense of drama.
Where was I?
Twenty seven, 26...
Twenty six, 25...
Let her go.
You don't disappoint, Captain.
What the hell!
Give me back my chain.
You want it? Take it from me.
Why isn't your bracelet working?
Didn't match my outfit.
Wow. You have seriously leveled up.
Looks like the chemist
wasn't so smart after all.
That just leaves you.
Time to bring the pain.
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
- Oh, my God, Allen, he must...
- No, he's okay.
I got him out just in time,
thanks to you.
Now, what were you thinking
breaking into a police station?
Who's bad idea was that anyway?
Seriously?
What can I say?
I'd do anything for love.
One of you guys get this?
Take this evidence to Processing.
- You're late.
- Yeah, I know.
- Again.
- I'm sorry.
You were amazing.
You went toe to toe with Goldface.
So I heard.
Uh, I mean, Korber told me all about it.
Yeah, I held my own, long enough
for the Flash to arrive.
Of course, he left before I got a chance
to say thank you, again.
But at least I can thank you, Allen.
I never could have stood up to Goldface
that way if it weren't for your advice.
Oh, it was all you.
I just aimed you in the right direction.
By the way, I got to ask,
where are the meta-bullets anyway?
I had them transferred to A.R.G.U.S.
35 weeks ago.
And you kept that secret the whole time?
Goldface was about to kill you.
It's called a poker face, Allen.
I should get started on the paperwork.
At least this time
I know what the charges are.
- Can we talk?
- Mark's downstairs.
We have tickets to an underground rave
in Keystone City.
It'll just take a minute, please.
I acted like a total bonehead tonight,
and I was rude to you and to Mark.
I am so sorry.
Bonehead? Try "Jackass."
What is your deal?
I guess I have a lot of baggage
to unpack when it comes to dating.
You think?
The reason I've been afraid
to go all in with Marcus is
because the last time I did,
I lost everything.
And I think that's why it's so hard
for me to see you with Mark,
because I envy how honest and free
and effortless your relationship is.
Effortless?
I'm sorry.
That's not exactly what I call
the roller coaster that is Frost-Blaine.
You're aware I stabbed him, right?
Yeah.
You make it seem easy, at least.
And Mark helped me realize something.
Mark? My Mark?
Yeah.
Mark showed me that if I'm gonna have
a chance at finding the same thing,
then I need to take
the same leap with Dr. Ficus.
So I'm gonna do it.
Hmm. That's great. I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
And I'm happy for you and Mark.
Even though, he is himself.
So does this mean we can do
that whole double date thing for reals?
I need to patch things up with Marcus,
but, after that, I'd love to.
Great.
Mark and I signed up
for a roller derby on the weekend,
and we need two extra players.
So, you have a mouth guard, right?
Uh, I could probably find one, maybe.
Cool. Practice starts
tomorrow at 8:00 a.m.
Don't be late.
Love what you've done with the place.
It's...
It's different than the last captain's.
Flash, on behalf of this
whole department, I wanted to thank you.
We couldn't have stopped Goldface
without you.
Hey, if it wasn't for
your smart thinking,
a lot of people
would have been seriously hurt.
So, from now on, if you need me,
you can call me on this.
If we're going to keep this city safe,
we need to do it together.
Which is why I want to share
something else with you.
My true identity.
Allen, I know it's you.
Wait, what?
How did you find out?
I found this charred bracelet
in the storage room.
There is only one way
you could have escaped
a bomb exploding on your wrist.
Super speed.
You know, Joe was right all along.
You really are a great cop.
And I'd be more than happy to train you
to become an even better meta.
Since when do you know
how to make a Doro Wat?
Did you spend a year in Ethiopia
that I don't know about or...
It's called retirement.
I am learning to cook whatever I want.
Of course, all your little sister
wants to eat is chicken nuggets.
Hey, don't knock the nuggies.
I should check on her,
and make sure she's still asleep
and not trying to make a break for it.
Mm.
Yeah, I'm gonna pack Barr
some leftovers. He's working late.
But, first, I am going to have
a little bit more.
Dad.
Uh...
Uh, weren't you just upstairs?
Yeah,
and then I went to the garage
because you asked me to get the files
from the old Scarpola case.
Remember?
Um...
Yeah. I must have just
checked out for a second.
Mm. I get it.
That's a food coma, baby girl.