BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster, Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him
murder the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power to change the future.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am the Flash.
CISCO: Previously on The Flash...
JESSE QUICK: Grodd, he's got my dad.
Harry's my friend.
I'm not gonna just abandon him.
I'm going back to Earth-2.
Now I am the ruler of Gorilla City,
and all the gorillas will follow
anything I order.
Grodd, the gorilla?
He's talking through Wells?
Yeah.
Who is this gorgeous intruder?
Her name is Gypsy. She's a collector.
Open a breach!
Time to warp out of this madhouse.
GRODD: You will open the breaches,
and Central City will fall before Grodd.
Barry.
- BARRY: Good morning.
- Good morning.
You're in a good mood
for 6:30 in the morning.
Yes, I am. Was I too loud?
I did make breakfast.
We got pancakes and waffles,
some French toast,
bacon and sausage, perfectly cooked.
And I picked up some of that dark roast
that you love so much.
Barry Allen, what has gotten into you?
Being with you makes me
want to do things like this.
Come here.
I love you.
Um, so do you actually want
any of this, or...
Um, yes.
And some of the food, too.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Nice.
What are you doing?
Ah! I'm decorating.
Look at this place.
- You're decorating the speed lab?
- Yes, I'm decorating the speed lab.
You know, 'cause Francisco, you know,
he wouldn't let me decorate the cortex
'cause I made it look oh-so-jolly
for Christmas time.
- What are the balls for?
- Do you know what those are? Lanterns.
You know what I always say,
"A fellow that can't tell the difference
between balls and lanterns"
"is in trouble when the lights go out."
Oh!
You go front to back. Toothbrushing.
You go front to back?
'Cause I'm a small-circles kind of guy.
I wonder how the other Wells
brushes his teeth.
The murderer?
I'm fascinated by the subtle differences
between us, you know?
- And the not-so-subtle ones.
- Like what?
Like the fact that I'm a genius,
and you're a moron.
Okay. See you at the party.
Wow, what a transformation.
Again.
So, this is H.R.'s contribution
to the team,
being Martha Stewart?
Guys, he's just trying
to do something nice.
Heads up!
I'm not really good with this kind
of thing. You know what I've got to do?
I've got to take some lessons
from that guy in the green elf suit
- over there in Star City. What's his name?
- BARRY: Green Arrow.
- What is all this?
- Friends Day. Ta-da!
- What?
- Yeah. Friends Day.
"Friends"?
Oh. It's my Earth's equivalent
of Valentine's Day.
And I thought, like, after, you know,
our success with the gorillas,
that we should, like, celebrate the love.
- Was all this necessary?
- Yeah, Joe.
Speaking of, where is your lady friend?
- 'Cause I'd like to...
- No, you wouldn't like to do anything.
She's at work,
which is where I should be going.
Yeah. I...
H.R.: Look what I have,
ladies and gentlemen.
I have your own personal Friends Day card.
- For yours truly, Ms. West.
- Thank you, H.R.
- Captain. The leader of the ship.
- Thanks, H.R. Thank you.
You're so welcome.
Oh, hi, Jesse So Quick.
Yeah, 'cause I also made one
for your grumpy old dad.
- Ah, you know what I like? Your vibe.
- Thank you.
Caitlin. Oh. I forgot the coffee.
"You have sped into my heart,
Jesse Quick."
Oh, well, I guess that makes two of us.
Uh, H.R. is nothing like my dad.
He's so sweet and thoughtful
and understanding.
- We should tell him.
- Tell your dad about you moving here?
- Yeah.
- Um, now?
Yeah, I mean,
H.R. said there'd never be a perfect time.
- Just got to rip the Band-Aid off.
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Okay.
- H.R. does make a good point.
- Yeah, what's that?
It was a really big win for the team,
beating Grodd.
I mean, we stopped a gorilla attack
from happening.
Yeah, look at you, changing the future.
We're all changing the future,
one headline at a time.
Look, I don't know
what the future's gonna bring,
but I hope every day is with you,
which is why I wanted to ask you,
Barry Allen,
- will you be my friend?
- Always.
Hey.
H.R. made this for you.
H.R. is an idiot.
So there's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
Okay.
- So I'm just gonna say it.
- I think that's wise.
I'm gonna move to Earth-1.
- What?
- I'm gonna stay here.
Why would you do that?
Grodd is no longer a threat.
No, it's not that. Uh...
I want to be with Wally.
This whole thing has made us realize
that we have no idea what's gonna happen,
you know, and...
And if we're gonna go through something,
we want to go through it together.
Yeah.
This guy?
You like him?
Yeah.
He makes you happy?
Dad.
Okay.
That's it?
You're not gonna yell?
You're not gonna throw that over there?
Your happiness is what matters to me.
You're both adults.
I respect your decision.
Don't screw it up.
Okay, that was weird.
I guess that this means
that we've got to find you a place.
Me? More like us.
You know, sometimes it seems
like everybody else
gets to have their love donut.
- Where's my love donut?
- Love is complicated.
Hmm. So, uh, where's Julian?
He's taking care
of some family matters in London.
Just so you know, we are just friends.
Yeah, the friend zone. I know it well.
Pretty sure
I have a permanent residence there.
You know,
maybe I should just swallow the pill.
Maybe my game just ain't strong.
Your game is so strong.
For what it's worth,
I think Lisa Snart was totally into you.
Lisa Snart.
Not that I would actually
let you date her.
Cisco, I promise, there is
a beautiful, intelligent woman out there
who's gonna challenge you
to be your best version of yourself.
In fact,
she could be right around the corner.
Gypsy.
Who the hell is this?
Where am I?
H.R.: Oh!
Why am I locked up?
H.R.: Oops.
My powers don't work in here.
Yeah, it's kind of the point of the cell.
What happened?
I thought we were all on the same page.
I spared your life, and you said
you'd go back to Earth-19
and tell everyone you killed H.R.
That's exactly what I did.
- I told the council you were dead.
- I don't believe you.
I didn't come here to take you back.
- I'm telling you.
- Then why are you here?
I don't know.
The last thing I remember,
I was on Earth-2,
hunting down another breacher.
Wait. You were just on Earth-2? Where?
In the African jungle,
- where I saw...
- Let me guess. A gorilla?
Super tall? Anger management issues?
Grodd must have taken control of her
and sent her here to kill us.
CISCO: Yeah, but she's on
a different Earth than him,
and Grodd's telepathy
can't cross dimensions like that.
Grodd said he always thinks ahead,
just like the Reverse-Flash.
He didn't have you to open a breach,
so he used Gypsy instead.
So that means Grodd's here.
Something tells me he's not alone.
- Any sign of him yet?
- Not since you asked 30 seconds ago.
Okay, he's a giant gorilla,
who's probably leading
an army of giant gorillas.
How can you not find him?
He's probably figured out a way
to scramble our satellites.
We're talking
about a genius super-ape here.
And a master strategist
who successfully fooled us on my Earth.
Yeah, we Wellses, we don't fool easy,
do we, Hard Hat?
Don't call me "Hard Hat."
We have to find him
before he hurts somebody else.
Don't worry, Barry. We will.
Every time I think we've beat him,
he comes back stronger, smarter,
and more dangerous.
He's evolving.
I keep trying to fight him the same way.
Okay, guys, look, we just have to come up
with a different way to beat him.
What we need to do
is get ahead of him for once.
We can. You've seen the future.
You know there's an attack.
If we just figure out
where that attack happens,
we can launch a preemptive strike
against Grodd.
We can stop the attack
before it ever starts.
And fortunately, we have someone
who can foresee future events.
- Before they happen.
- Okay, okay, there's only one problem.
I can only vibe what Barry saw,
and a ticker on the side of a bus stop
doesn't give us a whole lot of info.
What if we widen the scope of your vibe?
Then you can see more of the future.
Yes, I can do that.
- I just need to borrow your vibe gear.
- Harry, that's my only pair.
- I'll be careful.
- It's my only pair.
West, come with me,
you have an engineer's mind.
Yeah, sure. Happy to help.
We're gonna need all the help we can get.
Can you talk to Joe,
see if he can rally CCPD?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll let him know
that an army of sentient gorillas
is about to storm the city.
He's gonna love that.
Yeah.
What about Gypsy?
She's a really powerful meta.
Yeah, but how do we know
she's not a Grodd sleeper agent?
She's not. I checked her out.
- Can you convince her to help?
- Bruh, she won't say no to me.
No way.
You've got three speedsters, an ice queen,
and a guy who vibes
almost as well as I do.
You don't need my help to stop Grodd.
Need I remind you, you're the one
who brought Grodd here in the first place.
Not by choice.
I was chasing a fugitive
from my world on Earth-2
when Grodd ambushed me
and turned me into his damn puppet.
Okay, so then this is the perfect
opportunity for payback, right?
Don't tell me you're gonna run away
from this.
- I never run.
- Then stand and fight with us.
We need you.
You need me?
Are you trying to Luke Starkiller me?
What if I am?
Is that what it's gonna take
to get you to stay?
Here's a bonus, you get to spend
extra time with this face.
And look at this face. Come on.
Who doesn't want to get to spend
extra time with this guy?
What?
The things I saw,
when Grodd was in control of my mind,
the horrors in that monster's head,
I can never un-see them.
- What horrors?
- The city in ruins,
people in pain, death everywhere.
That's what Grodd wants,
what he's planning.
I'm sorry, Cisco. This is your fight,
not mine.
Now, if you don't mind,
I still have a fugitive to catch, so...
Okay.
I understand.
Take care of yourself, Cisco.
Admit it. You are so into me.
West.
How are we coming along with that gear?
I've made all the adjustments
you asked for,
so we should be good to go.
- Good. Thank you.
- Yeah.
Great.
Um, how exactly is this gonna help Cisco
vibe any differently?
Uh, simple science.
We just broaden
the overall harmonic resonance
of Cisco's vibrational frequencies
all while focusing them
on a fixed temporal locus.
- Couldn't be easier.
- Yeah.
You know, I've got to admit, Harry, I was
super surprised at how cool you were
with Jesse staying on this Earth.
I thought, for sure, you were gonna freak
out and throw something or throw someone.
Well, my daughter's happiness
is of the utmost importance to me,
and you make her happy.
I'm gonna do everything in my power
to keep it that way.
I appreciate that, West.
I'm sure Jesse will too after I'm gone.
We're gonna come visit you
on Earth-2 a bunch,
so you don't have to worry
about that, Harry.
Yeah, right.
Well, means the world to me,
seeing as I don't know
how much time I have left.
Wait. You're sick?
I'm not as well as I once was.
- Have you seen a doctor?
- Yes.
I have seen a doctor, West.
Is it serious?
Oh, man, Harry.
Man. Um...
- I'm sorry.
- Me, too.
Does Jesse know?
Appreciate it if you keep this between us.
She doesn't know,
and we wouldn't want to upset her.
Hey, SWAT's ready to roll
whenever y'all are.
- We find Grodd yet?
- We're about to.
Cisco, you ready?
- Harry, this thing, if it fries my brain...
- "It's an improvement."
- Was that Rocky?
- Yeah, Burgess Meredith.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Word of warning. Vibing blind,
it's like surfing a monster wave.
You need to stay above the temporal flow.
Otherwise, your consciousness
can get sucked under.
- And then what happens?
- I don't know. Guess we'll find out.
Wait. What?
HARRISON: Where are you, Ramon?
What do you see?
CISCO: I'm at an intersection.
State and Oakhill.
I think this is where it goes down.
That's a block away from the bridge.
That leads right to the heart of town.
If those gorillas get over that bridge...
- They'll overrun the city in no time.
- Not if we stop them first.
Eyes wide, everybody.
Grodd's army could be here any second,
all right?
- There's no sign of them.
- You sure this is the right place?
- According to Cisco, this is it.
- Was it the right time?
We're too early.
No, Flash.
Too late.
- Grodd.
- I remember,
this human is important to you.
- Now, he's all mine.
- No! Hey, do not hurt him.
- I'm the one you want, right?
- I warned you, Flash.
And now, I'm here on First Earth
to make good on my promise.
And when I'm finished,
this city and all the puny humans
will die.
No!
Joe!
- Are you okay?
- I think so.
I don't get it. How is attacking
Detective Joe West a part of Grodd's plan?
- It wasn't.
- Then what was it?
A distraction.
GENERAL: I don't care if Senator Ford
is having doubts.
If the secretary doesn't approve
that budget first thing in the morning,
we're gonna have to make
some serious cuts...
The hell was that?
That damn gorilla almost got me this time.
Shouldn't even have a scar.
Do you remember anything
from when Grodd was controlling you?
Not really. There's just some flashes.
Flashes of what?
They were, like, these images,
places I've never seen before.
It was like I was seeing
what he was seeing.
Gypsy said the same thing.
Uh-oh.
Here we go. I know that look.
That's the "I have a genius idea" look.
A couple years back on my Earth, there was
a neuroscientist that was able to achieve
memory recovery using transcranial
magnetic simulators on brain-damaged...
We use that here
but more as a depression treatment.
Well, in this experiment,
the neuroscientist focused all the energy
on the occipital cortex of the patients,
allowing them to achieve
almost full memory recollection.
So you think the connection Grodd creates
in the brains
of those he mind-controls goes
- both ways?
- Could be.
Maybe we could use Grodd's memories
that he left behind in Joe
to figure out what his plan is.
We'd just make some TCM simulators.
All it takes is some...
- Magnets.
- Throw together some magnets,
- make a helmet out of them.
- JOE: Hold on.
Y'all want to put a bunch of magnets
against my skull
to look into the mind
of a psychotic, murderous ape?
- Yeah.
- Fine.
Let's make it happen,
before Grodd tries to kill somebody else.
CAITLIN: It's gonna be okay.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
Just tired of seeing the people
I care about be put in harm's way.
Yeah, but like always, we're gonna work
together and come up with a plan.
We're gonna stop Grodd, Barry.
And then what?
We just send him back?
He's just gonna come here again.
We have to end this once and for all.
Wait.
What? You want to kill Grodd?
Why not?
That's how their society in Gorilla City
works, kill or be killed.
That's why he wanted me to kill Solovar.
And you know what? I should have.
I showed too much mercy.
No, you did what was right, Barry,
as you always do.
That's what makes you a hero.
Oliver has killed.
He's still considered a hero.
Yeah, and he lives with the weight
of that decision every single day.
I think that,
sometimes, the only way to stop
bad things from happening
is to just get rid of what's causing them.
What is this really about?
Grodd or what happens to me?
I kill Grodd, his attack never happens,
that changes the future,
and you live, yeah.
Your humanity, showing mercy,
that is what separates you
from everyone else.
That's the reason
that everyone looks up to you.
Don't compromise who you are, ever.
Losing what makes the Flash "the Flash,"
my life isn't worth it
if that's the cost to save me.
Here you are.
Hey, you know your dad's
gonna be all right.
What's wrong?
Look, I've been thinking, and I...
I don't think you should stay here.
I think it was a bad idea.
- Wally, you asked me.
- Yeah, and I shouldn't have.
I think you should go back to Earth-2.
Spend as much time with your dad
as you can.
Spend as much time with my dad as I can?
- Wally, what are you talking about?
- Your dad is sick, Jesse.
He's really sick.
He doesn't have much time left.
- Did he tell you that?
- I'm so sorry.
He is unbelievable.
So all you have to do is concentrate
on your memories of Grodd, okay?
Yeah, that won't be a problem.
All right.
- Hey, dead man. Seriously?
- Hmm?
You told Wally you were dying?
- Dying?
- You're dying?
I didn't say I was... I said I didn't know
how much time I had left.
- None of us...
- What is wrong with you?
Is there seriously nothing you won't say
to get me to stay by your side?
- I don't...
- Look, whatever.
I'm moving here,
whether you like it or not.
So all you have to do is concentrate
- on your memories of Grodd.
- Yeah.
- You ready?
- Waiting on you, dead man.
Hey, if I start to Grodd-out at any point,
cut the power off immediately.
- Of course.
- All right, Joe, you ready?
- Yeah.
- All right, then.
So here we go.
Joe?
- I didn't know he could draw.
- CISCO: Well, that's the thing.
Anybody can actually draw.
It's just that some have more developed
visual cortex and manual ability,
as you know.
And right now, these magnets are taking
that part of his brain and lighting it up.
Well, it worked.
Now we have a new problem.
We have to figure out
who the hell this is.
Good evening, General.
Color and number of the day.
Purple 246.
Are you all right, sir?
Sick.
- Good.
- General.
- Great.
- HARRISON: Yo, Rocky.
- How you doing?
- Yeah, I'm fine. I just...
No matter what I do to stop Grodd,
he just keeps finding new ways to attack,
new ways to destroy, and I...
Iris doesn't think I should, but
the only way this ends is if I kill him.
"Kill him"?
That might be the most idiotic thing
I've ever heard you say.
- Wait. What?
- Iris is right.
If you don't want to listen, go ahead,
keep being an idiot.
- I don't understand.
- Don't kill Grodd.
Harry, you of all people
should understand.
I mean, you would have killed to save
Jesse. You were gonna kill Zoom.
Barry, there's a thousand things
I've done that I'm not proud of,
some of them recently.
Every time I do one of those things,
it makes it easier to do it the next time.
I look at you,
out there battling the darkness
with honor and hope,
and I'm reminded
there's always another way.
Always.
Killing Grodd is not your answer.
Saving one life
doesn't justify taking another.
Find the other way.
CISCO: Guys,
we need you in the cortex.
- What's up, Cisco?
- We've got a behemoth of a problem.
Terrific.
So we ran our John Doe image
through every database.
And it was tough.
I mean, the guy's a ghost.
- We've been calling him "Jason Bourne."
- But then H.R. noticed something.
Well, at first,
it was a real brain-twister,
but then I remembered a quote
from a renowned poet from my Earth,
- Alfred Yankovic.
- Are you talking about Weird Al?
Why, 'cause of the hair?
Get to the point already, if you have one.
I can, Hard Hat. It's his hair.
Standard military cut.
So we ran the image through
the Department of Defense database,
and, as Cisco would say, "Yahtzee."
I would say that.
- Nice work, H.R.
- I know.
DoD has him listed as
Air Force General Matthew McNally.
General Matthew McNally,
and I'll give you one guess...
Just guess what he's in charge of.
I know you're gonna say military weapons,
but I really hope
you don't say "military weapons."
It's worse, Barr. Nuclear missiles.
CAITLIN:
McNally has the highest clearance.
He can have a rocket in the air
in less than 10 minutes.
So are the satellites back to functional?
We ran a full diagnostic. Any nuclear
weapon that's authorized to fire,
- an alarm will sound.
- Okay, good.
- Does it sound like that? That's an alarm.
- Yeah, it's that alarm, H.R.
Okay.
Short-range ballistic missile
authorized to fire from Fort Reynolds.
- How much time do we have?
- Minutes.
- Grodd, what have you done?
- Can we stop it from here?
Military weapons are basically analog.
I mean, they still use floppy disks.
I'm going after it.
Guys, no, look, I appreciate it,
but I need you to stay here, okay?
If I can't stop it,
I need you to get everybody
to safety, okay?
All right, I'm with the missile.
HARRISON: Barry, to access the keypad,
remove the panel
at the base of the missile vehicle.
All right.
All right, that's done. What's next?
Well, the good news is, this missile
has a built-in five-digit kill code.
- THE FLASH: Great. What is it?
- That's the bad news. We don't know.
For real? All right,
well, then what am I supposed to do?
You have to try every combination, Barry.
It's okay. With this type of launcher,
you won't set off the nuke.
IRIS WEST: Barry,
simulators are projecting
that hundreds of thousands will die.
Yeah, let's hope not.
Come on.
Five digits. How many combos is that?
- I'm guessing it's about...
- HARRISON: Precisely 90,000,
which you would know
if you weren't a moron,
and you were an actual genius.
CAITLIN:
Two missiles are locked on target.
Guys, we need something else.
This isn't working.
Plan B, anyone?
Work!
- CISCO: How much time does he have?
- Fifteen seconds.
Guys, I need something!
This isn't working! Something else!
You've just got to keep going, Barry.
You've just got to keep trying.
CAITLIN:
Six missiles are locked on target.
It worked.
It worked. We did it.
We did it!
Oh, thank God.
GRODD: Flash stopped the weapon,
but he can't stop us all.
Attack!
Found them.
They're right outside the city.
Heading for State and Oakhill, fast.
- Which leads right into downtown.
- All right, so what do we do?
Barry, I know we're speedsters
and everything,
- but we are way outnumbered here.
- Yeah, I mean, he's right.
How are the three of us
gonna take on all those gorillas?
We have to.
As much as I hate these gorillas,
especially Grodd,
if you kill him,
the other ones might stand down,
but you might not be able to come back
from this, Barry.
- You know that, right?
- I know.
But there's another way.
It's not gonna come to that.
Cisco, I'm gonna need your help.
GYPSY: Tracked her down on Earth-2.
Breach is taken care of.
Thank you.
Risky move coming to an Earth
where interdimensional travel
is punishable by death...
Especially when I'm the one
who's supposed to uphold that law.
- I need to talk to you.
- I don't do long-distance relationships.
Don't get me wrong. This is something
I'd love to talk about in more detail,
especially if distance
is your only hesitation.
But I'm here to talk about Grodd.
Okay, I see you don't take no
for an answer.
Gypsy, please.
He's gonna destroy my city,
and he's gonna hurt the people I love.
I told you before, that's not my problem.
Look, just go back to Earth-1
before someone sees you,
and I have to do something
that I don't want to.
You know, you told me I could do things
with my powers I'd never even imagine,
and you're right 'cause
I'm not just vibing people anymore.
I'm vibing what they feel.
And you know what I'm getting from you,
right here, right now?
That you're more than this.
You're like me.
You want to do something good.
Look, we need something to stop Grodd,
and I'm gonna need your help getting it.
Please, be the hero I know you want to be.
- Wells, how long do we have?
- Two minutes, Barry.
"Two minutes"? Ten seconds.
Can you not even tell time?
That's what I said. Ten seconds.
So got any pointers
on how the three of us
are gonna save everyone
and stop a few hundred gorillas?
Go for the legs?
Just try not to get caught.
'Cause, trust me, they won't let go.
Well, that was not the start
we're looking for.
- Because...
- How long do they have to last?
Hopefully, not much longer.
GRODD: Your city will fall, Flash.
There's only one way to end this.
You kill me.
But you won't do that.
All you care about is mercy.
Yeah, you're right,
except I'm not the only one
that wants to stop you.
GRODD: Solovar.
- I challenge you, Grodd!
- And you will fall again!
SOLOVAR: Goodbye, Grodd.
Stop!
Death isn't the way.
He betrayed me.
I know, so leave him here,
where he's from.
We won't let him go back
to Gorilla City ever again.
Just spare his life, like I spared yours.
Send us home, all of us.
How long is it gonna take to put
100 gorillas through a breach?
We're gonna be here all night.
You know what I ought to do?
Whip us up some cappuccino...
Whoa!
All the gorillas are back on Earth-2.
- And Grodd?
- I called Lyla. He's with A.R.G.U.S.
Good. I don't know about y'all,
but I don't ever need to see
a super-smart, telepathic gorilla again.
- H.R.: I'm with you.
- Not that Grodd didn't have
some justification for mistrusting humans.
Whatever good was in Grodd is gone.
As far as I'm concerned, they can
throw him in the same cage as King Shark.
Hmm. I'd pay money to see that fight.
All right, well, if this city doesn't need
my help anymore,
I'm gonna head back to Earth-19.
Oh, really?
So you did all this for the city, huh?
'Cause I'm pretty sure there's
a different reason you chose to help us.
That's right, I was the only one
who knew where Solovar was.
- Oh, right, yeah. How could I forget?
- Hmm.
Don't front. You're into me.
Look, Cisco, I mean, even if I was...
Oh!
You couldn't handle me.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
I'm marrying that woman. Yeah.
Okay, I better get this story in
before I lose my job.
Okay.
You sure you still don't want to look
into the future and see what's changed?
No. Think I'm done with that.
Good.
- I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
I'll walk out with you.
I've got a date with Cecile.
Ooh!
Come on, guys. Let's go find Harry.
To review, this is my daughter.
There's nothing more important to me,
so you do right by my daughter,
or there is nowhere in the multi-verse
I won't find you.
- Dad.
- They'd have to kill me.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Bye, Jesse Quick.
Always another way, Flash. Always.
Babe?
Is that Grandma Esther's noodles?
BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
And there's mint chocolate chip
in the freezer.
And these are for you.
What is all this?
I've been really busy recently
with trying to avoid the future,
and I forgot that
there's always another way.
What is that?
Making the future our future.
My great-grandfather gave this to
my great-grandmother after World War ll.
He wanted to propose
before he was shipped out,
but he didn't have the money.
And he bought this three years later
when he was stationed in London.
Fought his way across France,
all the way to Berlin,
and this ring around his neck
with his dog tags.
And when he got back,
she was waiting for him
on the dock of the Brooklyn Navy Yards.
He proposed on the spot.
After my mom passed away,
Joe held on to this for me until tonight.
Barry.
Iris West, will you marry me?
MAN: Ilsa,
we both know you belong with Victor.
You're part of his work,
the thing that keeps him going.
- If that plane leaves...
- JESSE: Okay, I'm so confused.
Is it supposed to be about
the War of the Americas?
Do you not like it?
'Cause this is my favorite movie.
No, I didn't say that.
Um...
I guess we just have more wars
on my Earth.
Well, we can just watch something else.
Or we don't have to watch anything at all.
You know what I could go for?
Big Belly Burger.
Wow. Wow.
Ow. Um...
- I'll be right back.
- Thank you.