- Injustice?
Damn.
Look, Barry, those protocols
are a one-way trip.
A bad one.
- I know that.
- All right, all right.
Just take a deep breath.
Tell me what happened.
- In the last 24 hours,
I've lost my job, my home base.
I've started having blackouts.
I destroyed my apartment
at superspeed.
I attacked my team, my family.
Jefferson,
I attacked innocent people,
dozens of them,
and I don't remember doing it.
I'm out of control!
- Easy.
In my experience,
there's almost nothing
that can't be undone,
but I'm gonna need you
to calm down for me.
- Calm down?
I'm losing my mind!
Look, you know
the contingency plan.
The Injustice Protocols were
put into place for a reason,
to protect the world
when one of us goes rogue.
It's happening, Jefferson.
You have
to take away my powers.
♪
- Look, we need
to call in the others.
- We don't have time.
No, no.
Kara, J'onn, Sara--
we all designed this plan
together after Faust.
- And we all made
the same promise.
If anyone ever lost control,
a designated teammate
would step in.
For me, that's you.
- And I don't carry
that weight lightly.
What if this
is all temporary?
What if your mind
starts healing?
- It's--it's not gonna heal.
It's only gonna get worse.
- But how can you say that
for sure?
- I forgot Joe died.
The man who raised me...
he passed away six months ago,
and I can't remember it
at all.
Look, I know
you have questions,
but I'm losing myself.
You took an oath,
if I ever said
the word "injustice,"
you'd listen.
Please.
We have to do this now.
♪
- My father had a saying,
one that I even
teach my students today.
"Where's the future?
Right here.
"Whose life is this?
Mine.
"What are you gonna do with it?
Live it
by any means necessary."
So don't worry.
I will honor my promise.
I will do whatever is necessary
to keep folks alive.
But remember...
when we take away your powers,
they are gone permanently.
♪
It's happening again.
Another world lost.
♪
Another failure.
Armageddon waits for no man.
♪
And it won't wait for me
to find you, Flash.
♪
So you think
Despero's right,
that Barry's gonna destroy
the world or something?
- No, no, hey,
what Barry did today was scary,
and the things that he said--
they really, really hurt,
but someone that we love
is going through
a mental health crisis,
so I don't care
what he may or may not do
ten years from now.
We need to take
care of him today
just like he did for me.
- Okay, we'll follow your lead.
What do you want to do?
- Okay, I've been
sensing Despero all day.
He's using his mind's eye
to scan the city.
Now, he hasn't found him yet,
but if Barry's
not thinking clearly--
- What if he's the only one
thinking clearly?
- Boss,
what are you talking about?
- Look, I know
how this is gonna sound,
but when Despero showed up,
he said that Barry
would suffer tragedy,
and then on cue,
he lost his job,
he lost S.T.A.R. Labs,
and now he's lost his mind.
Doesn't that seem
like a big coincidence?
A little too big?
- But Despero's
from the future.
Wouldn't he know what happened?
- But what if he didn't know
that someone
secretly caused it to happen?
- You think he's being framed.
- Iris, he forgot about Joe.
Nobody was framing him then.
- Yeah, I'm not so sure.
Look, when Dad died,
CCPD said that his death
was an accident.
He fell on the tracks
at Scott Railway.
Kramer left me
with the evidence,
but for the last six months,
I haven't been able
to look at it,
but then I thought
about what Barry said,
that we have to investigate
what happened.
So I finally started looking,
and this is what I found.
- Joe.
- Why are you showing us this?
- Just trust me.
♪
- See, one second he's there,
and the next, he's gone.
I haven't figured this
all out yet,
but if somebody framed Barry,
then he doesn't
cause Armageddon.
And, Cecile,
Dad could be alive.
- No.
No, it's impossible.
- Is it?
I mean, what if a meta-human
abducted him at the last second
or--or he got swapped
with, like, a mirror clone?
- I saw them bury his body.
So did Barry,
and so did you.
- Okay, guys,
how about we take five, yeah?
- I'm not trying to upset you.
- What are you trying to do?
- I'm trying to find out
if my dad is still alive.
I'm trying to prove
my husband's innocence.
- Iris, it does not matter
if he is innocent
if we can't find him,
which is what we
have been trying to do
while you have been living
in a fantasy world!
- Hey.
Iris has trusted Barry
against the odds before,
like when Bloodwork
infected him,
and she was right.
If there's even a chance
that this could be real,
I can't give up,
and you wouldn't want me to.
- Is that what you think?
You think I gave up?
Oh, my God.
You think I don't wake up alone
every morning in our bed
praying to God that all of this
was nothing but a bad dream?
Iris, I have done everything
that I can
to just keep moving forward
since I lost Joe.
I did it so that I could
be there for you and for Jenna,
for this team,
and you come in here
and you want to shove
his death in my face?
He was the father of my child!
- And my father!
♪
- Fine.
If you insist
on pursuing this lie,
then we will save Barry
without you.
- Fine.
You save him your way.
I'll save him mine.
♪
- Okay, Cecile.
What do you want to do?
- We find Barry
before Despero does first,
no matter what it takes.
How are we supposed
to find Barry now?
- Okay,
this is gonna sound wild,
but Despero's scanning
the whole world
for Barry's brainwaves, right?
Like a needle in a haystack.
I know him better
than almost anyone.
- So you should be able
to pinpoint Barry's mind
faster than he can,
only Despero's psychic radius
is exponentially
higher than yours.
- Alex Danvers
says he gets a power boost
from his power source,
the Flame of Py'tar.
- Okay, I just need a boost
of my own, right?
So you can build something,
something that can amplify
my psychic powers.
- You want me
to build a Cerebro
out of the trash in my garage?
I mean--
♪
Oh, frak yeah, I can do that.
- Okay, there's
still one problem.
Kalanorians like Despero
have four hemispheres
to their brain.
The human brain only has two.
So even if we amplify
your empathic radius,
you'd still be
at a disadvantage.
- Then we're gonna need
some more brain power.
And I know just who to call.
So things got
a little intense back there.
You okay?
Yeah, look,
I don't want to hurt Cecile,
but if someone's framing Barry
and my dad might be okay,
then I have to figure out
the truth.
Just glad I don't
have to do it alone.
- Team Citizen forever, Boss.
So what are we looking for?
Signs of a meta-abduction?
- What the hell?
- What is it?
- I'm not sure.
Do you see anything?
- Well, I'm not
picking up anything
on the electromagnetic
spectrum,
but your time sickness makes
you see stuff sometimes, right?
Could it be acting up?
- Must be.
Deon's treatments
are probably wearing off.
I'm supposed
to see him tonight.
the fiber optic aura
for these cameras leads
to a security booth inside,
so if someone wanted to alter
the footage of Joe's accident
to make it seem like he died--
- That'd be where they'd start.
- I'll never forget that day.
People were screaming
someone fell.
I--I tried calling
the emergency line,
but it was too late.
- What about
before it happened?
Did you see anyone suspicious
on the platform?
- It was pretty empty
when Mr. West died.
The Red Line
came in 15 minutes early.
Hang on.
Iris West-Allen?
Were you his daughter?
- I still am.
What about after?
Was there anyone there
who had access
to the scene
before CCPD arrived?
- Ma'am,
your father took a bad step.
It happens sometimes.
- Well, the reason I'm asking
is because the video files
that you sent over to CCPD
were missing
some very important frames
from the moment of incident.
That doesn't just happen
unless you're saying
someone got into your system.
- Or because we're on the same
power grid as Sharks Stadium.
Whenever there's a game,
like there was that day,
our automatic CCTV upload
gets interrupted,
and we end up
losing chunks of data.
It's a good thing
we back up our files locally.
♪
- Is this the only angle?
- No, it's okay.
I was wrong.
It was just an accident.
♪
♪ I don't know
♪ Where to start
- So who wants next game, boys?
Think you can end up on top?
- I think
you're done for today.
♪
- Horton,
I'm surprised you showed.
Figured you'd still be crying
over your boyfriend somewhere.
You should have heard
the cheers at Iron Heights
when that news broke out.
- Well, that's funny 'cause
I figured you'd already be
running Scudder's
entire criminal enterprise,
not hustling morons
in a dive bar.
Guess you probably shouldn't
have sold him out after all.
- Fine.
- Aw.
That means you're available.
- For what?
You got a job for me,
Miss meta-attorney?
- Look, I need help.
Psychic help.
Someone that I care about
is missing.
- Let me guess.
He runs real fast.
It's all over the news.
Flash went bad.
It's the feel-good story
of the year.
And even if I did want to help
return the Scarlet Speedster
to the side of angels,
during our last go-round,
you messed with my head.
I don't know
if I can trust you.
- Can you trust me to help get
your parole restrictions
lifted?
- Quid pro quo, huh?
♪
When do we start?
- Damn it, I--
I can't get this last conduit.
- You know what?
You know, sometimes I like
to work with a little music on.
- Yeah.
Monk?
Okay, trying to impress me.
- I kind of grew up
on this stuff.
♪
Joe always had something
spinning on the turntable,
Miles Davis, Johnny Hartman,
Ella Fitzgerald.
It's his favorite.
♪
Was his favorite.
- Yeah, I lost someone too
a while back.
Bill Henderson.
Actually, he was a cop
like your old man.
Well, we had our ups and downs,
but through it all,
he was my best friend.
My brother.
♪
Bill died saving my life...
So I could get home
to Atlanta and the girls.
Yeah, he made that sacrifice.
Just like you sacrificing
a big part of yourself
here today.
You know, if Joe was here,
I think he'd be real proud
of the hero
you've been all along.
- It's been you
all along, Flash.
♪
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
That was the last conduit.
Now,
when your suit materializes,
you'll be able
to generate enough voltage
to disrupt
my Speed Force connection.
- Giving Gambi a run
for his money, huh?
All right,
let's go blow this fuse.
♪
- I'm ready.
- This is gonna hurt.
- Mm-hmm.
♪
- Boss, you got to see this.
Okay.
Do you remember
what the security chief said,
that the day Joe died,
the Red Line was running early?
Well, back
in my car thief days,
I'd take the Red Line home
from the chop shop,
and it was never early.
It was always late.
- So my dad was just unlucky?
- Well, that's
an understatement.
- The train that hit Joe
passed a routine inspection
two days before the accident,
yet somehow,
the hydraulics failed.
Iris, there are dozens
and dozens
of coincidences like this.
Do you know what the odds are
that they all happened at once?
Million to one.
The events
that led to Joe's accident,
they line up perfectly.
Too perfectly.
- So what are you saying?
- That you're right.
That--that someone
was pulling the strings.
Barry's not crazy,
and your dad's not--
- Look, Allegra,
I was wrong about everything.
These last six months
have been the worst
six months of my life.
♪
- Look, I get it.
I do.
When Esperanza died...
I lost hope too.
But what saved me
from the darkness
was remembering
the words of a hero.
"As long as we keep
the loved ones
we've lost in our hearts,
there is always hope."
♪
- Are you seeing this?
- Seeing what?
♪
- I have to get back
to the station.
- I thought
that was a dead end.
- It's not.
We just couldn't see
all the evidence.
♪
- Ladies,
may I present the solution
to all of our
Flash-finding problems,
the Neural Conjoiner.
- Both of you have
the natural ability
to access people's brainwaves
like an antenna.
Cecile as an empath,
and Rosa as a psychic
who can spin people's emotions
out of control.
- So with the Telepathic Crown
as an amplifier,
we'll be able
to conjoin your psychic powers
and pick up way more brainwaves
than you'd ever be able
to pick up on your own.
Like, all over the continent.
Now all you need to do is focus
on the Flash's brainwaves,
and the N.C.
will transmit them here
while I use the visual data
to triangulate
his location with this.
- I'm sorry, but does that TV
have rabbit ears on it?
- Yeah, yeah,
it's 'cause it's my grandma's,
which means we'll
have to be done by 7:00
'cause she doesn't want
to miss her stories.
♪
- You ready?
- It's too much.
It's too much!
I can't--I can't!
- Chester, turn it off.
- No, we can do this.
So many minds to reach out
and touch.
I can't.
It's too many thoughts.
I can't do this.
- No, there aren't!
Horton, listen to me.
Together, we are strong enough
to handle this,
but you're letting your own
feelings hold you back.
Now focus!
-
- Horton, you're letting your
own emotions bring you down.
That sadness you got?
Get over it.
You want to find your hero?
- Yes.
- Then lose the weakness,
just like I lost those
gushy feelings for Scudder.
Forget about your grief,
your guilt, your sadness.
Forget about
your damn dead boyfriend.
Bury it!
♪
I still have
some of my speed.
Connection's not
fully severed.
- I found him.
- Oh, keep it going.
Keep it going.
We almost have a clear signal.
- Oh!
- Ah!
- What happened?
- You overloaded the crown.
- Damn, Horton.
I knew I was good,
but color me impressed.
- Okay,
if the amplifier is busted,
then maybe we should try
a different way.
- No, no.
Chester, you can fix it, right?
You can fix it.
- Well, I need about an hour
to recalibrate,
but then we should
be good to go.
- Do it.
We finally made some progress.
We're not gonna stop now.
Those humans.
Their emotions
blind them to reason,
yet give them power.
♪
They'll find Flash first,
and I'll be
right behind them.
♪
- You forget we had
an appointment in the books?
'Cause usually
we meet in the Speed Lab.
Then again, I am a Force god,
so I can work with this too.
Ready for your treatment?
- I didn't forget
we had an appointment.
I--I wanted you
to find me here.
- Why?
♪
This is where your dad died.
I can sense him walking
through here six months ago.
- I came here earlier today,
and I saw these particles near
the tracks where my dad fell,
and then I saw them again
when I was going through
evidence from his death.
This is a sign
that there's something wrong
with my dad's death,
proof that someone
is altering reality
and--and leaving
particles behind.
- But nobody screwed
with the timeline.
All right?
I would have sensed that.
- Then someone's
hiding something.
I need you
to undo my treatments,
all of them.
- You can't be serious.
- Deon, please.
Whatever is happening,
it's connected
to these particles.
Look, if I absorb all of that
temporal matter out of you
and that sickness you got
starts spreading too fast,
you're gonna start moving
in and out of timelines again,
or worse.
- I'm not afraid of that.
- Well, I am.
- Look, if there's a chance
that I can save my husband
and bring my dad back,
I'll risk it.
♪
My God.
What are they?
- Temporal isotopes,
but decaying
instead of growing.
That's why
I couldn't sense them before.
Oh, damn.
♪
Someone tapped into
the Negative Still Force
to rewrite the timeline.
♪
Your dad
wasn't supposed to die.
- But someone changed the past
to make sure that he did.
♪
Cecile, we need
to talk about Dillon.
- Look, I know.
I get it, okay?
Dillon can be
a little intense,
but we're trying
to beat Despero here.
- She wants you
to forget about Joe.
That's more
than a little intense.
And honestly,
it's not the first time
I've seen you repress
your feelings.
- You have no idea
what it's been like for me.
None.
- Actually, I do.
Because it's what
I went through with Ronnie.
After the particle
accelerator exploded,
I was so traumatized
by his death
that even thinking about him
would send me spiraling.
Rather than facing my grief,
I started fearing it.
I just--I can't help thinking
you're heading
down the same path.
- Look, I know.
I know I don't talk about Joe.
It's because I think about him
every second
of every hour of every day.
And it's not just my grief
that I have to feel, Caitlin.
Barry and Iris
and little Jenna--
because of my powers,
whenever they're near me,
I feel all of their grief too.
♪
It's everything that I can do
to push it all down
just so that
I can keep moving forward,
because if I don't,
I will drown.
And that cannot happen again.
I know it's hard,
but your strength as an empath
doesn't come
from burying your emotions.
It comes
from feeling the feelings.
Even the hard ones.
♪
- Oh, let me guess.
Dinner's ready.
- Oh, sweet Joseph Winters.
Okay, my phone is still plugged
into the S.T.A.R. Labs
emergency sensors.
Someone just turned on
the particle accelerator.
♪
- The hell's going on?
- The power's spiking, sir.
- Impossible.
It's like the particle
accelerator turned itself on.
- Not exactly.
I may have given it
a little push.
♪
- Susan?
Damn, what in the world!
- Checkmate.
♪
And with this power,
no mind
will shut its doors on me!
- Why would Despero
turn on
the particle accelerator?
- He's into alternative energy.
Who cares?
- Guys, look, she's right.
We need to do this.
- Okay.
- Remember what
we did last time.
Remember that power.
- Come on.
Where are you?
- I can see Flash.
He's with Jefferson Pierce?
Where are they?
- Let me try and find out.
- I can feel
your grief again, Horton.
I told you to bury it.
- Cecile, you don't
have to listen to her.
You know your powers
better than she does.
- Oh, yes.
It's like meta-juicing,
only ten times better.
♪
- You should be proud
of the power
you've displayed here.
Now, open your minds to me
and show me the Flash.
- Leave us alone.
- Uh, guys.
Who are they talking to?
- Despero.
He must be here.
♪
- Dillon, what are you doing?
- Causing a little vertigo.
It's an oldie but a goodie.
Okay, big boy.
How about
a little quid pro quo?
I let you inside my mind,
show you where the Flash is,
and then you and I
go kill him together.
- What makes you think
I came here to bargain?
- Okay.
How about I let you peek
inside my mind for free?
We'll call it even.
♪
- Dillon.
Dillon!
♪
I can't feel her anymore.
What did you do?
- I looked inside her mind,
but I could only
partly reconstruct
the Flash's location.
The other half
must be in yours.
Don't be afraid.
It's a necessity.
I am trying to save the world.
- By killing us and Barry?
- A few lives
to spare billions.
That's a trade
I'm willing to make,
but one
that you won't even stomach.
Your mind's strong
for a human empath,
but it's kindling compared
to the Flame of Py'tar.
♪
- Stop fighting me
and show me where he is.
You have no allies left.
You're weak,
and you're alone.
♪
- You're wrong.
I am not alone.
♪
- Oh.
Ugh.
- Hey, hey, you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- She's alive, but barely.
- Despero--he attacked us.
- How did you survive?
- I thought about Joe.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
I found Barry.
He's at the Hall.
- What?
- Guys, guys,
Despero was in my head.
That means he knows
where Barry is too.
♪
- All right,
maybe we should take a break.
- No, we have to finish
before Despero finds me.
- Who the hell's Despero?
♪
If you're keeping
something important from me,
I suggest you remedy it.
- He's from the future.
He says that,
ten years from now,
I'm gonna destroy the world.
- You believe him?
Do you remember what we said
when we first met
during Crisis?
We're not quitters.
You can change your future,
just like you did back then.
- That's what I'm trying to do.
If I get rid of my speed,
I can keep Despero's future
from happening.
- What will this Despero do
if you don't?
- He's gonna kill me.
- You didn't think
that was important to mention?
- I knew if I told you,
you'd want to go after Despero,
but I need you to follow
the Injustice Protocols.
I'm not acting out of fear.
I'm trying to do
the right thing.
- Yeah, I thought I was, too,
but I wasn't,
and you aren't either.
You're just afraid of becoming
this man
that Despero says you are.
- I've already hurt people!
I'm already a liability!
- No, what you are is a hero!
Doesn't that mean something?
- I've seen what happens,
what I end up doing.
It's going to happen.
Getting rid of my speed is
the only way to save the world.
Damn it, Jefferson!
It's the only way
to save your family too!
- I suggest you
keep my family out of this.
- After everything
we've done today,
everything I've told you,
you're just giving up.
♪
- Barry, you need to think
very carefully right now.
- I'm asking you
to save the world,
and you won't even listen!
♪
You're gonna hear me now,
'cause one way or the other,
you're gonna help me
finish this.
♪
- Look at what I just did,
the damage I can still cause!
You made a promise
to keep this world safe.
♪
- I am keeping the world safe
by saving one
of its protectors.
♪
- Fine, you want
to ignore the protocols?
Now imagine millions dead
all because of me!
♪
- It's your lightning.
You keep it.
How about we stop
this insanity?
Hmm?
- Do you remember why we call
our safety plan "Injustice"?
Because if one of us
goes rogue,
the rest of the world
doesn't stand a chance.
♪
You think this is what
he would have wanted?
You told me that before Crisis,
Oliver went to the Monitor
to trade his life for yours.
Now, I never met the man,
why'd he do that?
'Cause he was afraid?
Nah.
A man like him lays down
his life for a man like you
because you are the best of us.
Now, Oliver Queen
wasn't a quitter.
He'd never quit on you.
So don't you dare
quit on yourself.
♪
- Jefferson, I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
♪
Just tell me this.
Where's the future?
♪
- It's right here.
- Whose life is this?
- Mine.
- So what are you
gonna do with it?
- Live it...
by any means necessary.
♪
- I told you, Flash,
if I found any trace
of your true nature,
I'd end your existence.
- Leave him alone.
He's innocent.
Someone changed the timeline
to kill my father
and make Barry seem insane.
- You really believe
you're telling the truth.
How tragic.
♪
- Hurry!
I'll hold him off.
- You need to go and figure out
who is trying to frame you.
- I need to go to the future,
see who really causes
Armageddon.
- I can't hold him much longer!
- I'm not gonna make it there.
I don't have
enough Speed Force left.
- How about some Still Force?
My isotopes will pull you
toward any
weird temporal activity.
- Run, Barry.
Run.
♪
- You all
just killed this world.
♪
If I could have
everyone's attention
for a moment.
I have been waiting
for this moment
for a very, very long time.
When you find
the love of your life,
it's like electricity
pulsing through your veins,
giving you a shock that you
absolutely never want to end
because--because now...
♪
Now you're part
of something greater.
You're part
of something wonderful.
♪
And, frankly, surprising
because you never know...
what face fate will be wearing
when she shows up
to knock on your door
and change your life forever.
When it does, for you,
my wish is that that face...
Is as beautiful as the one
standing next to me.
To Iris West,
the love of my life...
And to our future together.
♪
- What the hell
is he doing here?
♪
- Greg, move your head!