My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and
find other meta-humans
like me.
But when my daughter came
back from the future to help,
she changed the present
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- Is my dad even really...
- Caitlin, your father is dead.
- Dad?
- You found me.
I want to make it up to you, Caity.
I really should've been there for you.
Icicle wouldn't have
gone to all this trouble
to kill my dad if there wasn't
a piece of him still left.
We got Dwyer, we gave him the cure,
but another Cicada showed up.
She wants to tell you her secret.
Someone instructed you to do it.
Eobard Thawne.
Dad, please don't do this!
Nora, if you try to
run back in time again,
I will feel it in the Speed Force.
Good-bye, Nora.
You took our daughter
back to the future?
I didn't have any other choice.
I? It's we, Barry.
We. She's our daughter,
- not just yours.
- I know that.
But you left her there anyway?
I can't trust her, Iris!
That puts all of us in danger!
That's how you feel, Barry.
What about asking how I feel?
I didn't think I had to!
Of course you didn't.
Of course you didn't, Barry!
You always see one way through a problem
and damn what I think.
Wait, wait, what the
hell does that mean?
You know, we have been
through so much crap,
we have been through so much therapy
and you are still...
Still making decisions
based on your emotions!
'Cause I'm right this time!
Flashpoint?
Going to the Speed Force and leaving me?
Were you right those times too?
You think I wanted to do this?
That this was easy?
Seeing Nora looking at
me, asking for forgiveness
knowing it might be the
last time I ever see her?
What about the last time
that I get to see her, Barry?
I didn't even get a
chance to say good-bye!
Damn it, Iris, she
lied to us for months!
And she explained why!
That she was working with Thawne?
That doesn't bother you.
No, it doesn't.
Maybe if he killed your
mother in front of you,
you'd feel differently.
Maybe you feeling differently, Barry,
is why we should have made
this decision together.
She just wanted to meet you, Barry.
The father that she never knew
and there was one person who
could teach her how to do that.
Is it really so hard to understand
why she would go to him?
Doesn't matter if I understand it.
Thawne is manipulating her.
He's on death row, Barry.
How is he manipulating her?
You know, if this were
anybody else, you'd back me.
But because it's Nora,
because it's our daughter,
the person who finally
stopped hating you,
you refuse to see how dangerous this is.
I mean, you talk about making
decisions based on emotion.
Look in the mirror.
All those years without my father
and you gave me a second chance.
And now I've lost him all over again.
I failed you, Little Runner.
No, this is my fault.
I should've never lied to
them about working with you.
Well, perhaps not.
I screwed everything up.
And now I can't even
help them catch Cicada
because my dad will know if
I run into the Speed Force.
Mm-hmm.
He most certainly will.
Hey...
Wait.
You've run into the Speed
Force hundreds of times.
And my father, other speedsters,
they never felt you coming.
How did you do that?
Thawne, tell me how you did it.
- Nora.
- Tell me. Thawne!
It's not for you.
I need to see my father.
Please, if there is a way
I can go back in time
to see him undetected,
you have to tell me how.
I used to idolize your father.
I wanted to be just like him.
But that was not my fate.
I was to be the reverse.
Opposite of him...
in every way.
So instead of tapping
into the Speed Force
to access my powers...
I created my own.
You created your own Speed Force?
Yes, I did.
And I can access it to go back in time?
That and more.
Can you teach me how to use it?
Well, I... I have to warn you, Nora.
It's a little bit negative.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Hey, where is Cecile and Cisco?
Cecile's relieving the nanny.
And Cisco went to talk to Breacher
about how to track Cicada II.
Okay.
Where's Iris?
Uh, I honestly don't know.
We're not really seeing
eye to eye right now.
Because?
Because I took Nora home for good.
- Nora's gone?
- Just like that?
Well, only thing to do, really,
because Nora can't be trusted.
I can deduce from your
faces that you're upset,
but you understand the
truth need to be exposed.
Yes, we understand that.
What you don't understand
is that this is a family.
You didn't include anyone in this.
Oh, look. Baby Giraffe...
Sherloque, you've done enough.
- All right?
- Oh, I have not done enough.
We still have another Cicada to catch.
Man, he says you've done enough.
Well, perhaps I have.
I got to take this. Yeah?
Look since Cisco
didn't take me with him,
I'm gonna round up the Cicada II files.
Cecile and I are going
to go over them tomorrow,
see if anything makes my nose wiggle.
Are you gonna be okay?
I honestly don't know.
Guys, this is CCPD.
We've got a big problem.
The nurses heard a crash
in the middle of the night
but nobody saw anything.
By the time they got here,
Grace was gone.
Judging by the thermal
warping in this glass,
an energy blast with a lot
of heat took out the window.
But I don't really
think we need any clues
to know who took her.
Future Grace steals past Grace.
I don't even know if
there's a police code
for kidnapping yourself.
Hey, what's it say?
Grace's coma is stable.
As long as future Grace is
looking after younger Grace,
her life's not in any danger.
We still have no way
to find either of them.
Could things get any worse?
Working late, Dr. Tannhauser?
Or working early,
depending how you see it.
Well, I stopped by to say good night.
So I guess I'll say good morning.
Good morning, J.P.
Get back! Hold it right there!
Thomas?
I don't suppose Icicle
left any frozen fingerprints behind?
No, but this docking station
is lined with a
carbon-filled Kapton polymide.
NASA uses it to build probes
meant for the coldest reaches of space.
There's a lot of fresh puddles in here.
You think he stole whatever
kept this place cold?
- Try way beyond cold.
- Why would he want it?
You're going to have to ask Carla
when she's done filing the theft report
or Caitlyn when she gets here.
I'm not sure about much lately.
Hey, Barr.
Have you talked to Iris since she left?
I'm just giving her some space.
All right, just make sure
you don't give her too much.
The right choice? What the
hell are you talking about?
You lied to me for 20 years
and told me my father was dead.
How the hell is that the right choice?
Your father is trapped inside
an ice monster, Caitlyn.
What was I supposed to do?
Split custody with him on the weekends?
I don't know. You could
try telling me the truth.
But why tell your daughter anything?
Funny, I don't recall you telling me
that you let the monster
out of the prison.
Because you never told
me he was in a prison!
And now all these years that
I could've been working on
a cure for dad are gone!
We may never get him back.
Well, at least you
have someone to blame.
Moms are always here for that.
Are you okay?
I will be as soon as we find Icicle.
My mom told me what he stole.
It's a prototype Cryo-Atomizer.
- And what can he do with that?
- Nothing good.
My contacts upstate got nothing.
I even tried Kritschgau
at the DOD. Nada.
Nobody can spare the manpower
to help find Cicada 2.0.
Hey, what about The Citizen?
Any fresh leads on Cicada? Iris?
Hello? Um, Earth to Iris?
Ralph, wait!
"Barry, I don't know if I can
ever forgive you for this."
I think you missed a comma there.
Can you stay out of it for once?
She's not kidding. Super mad.
No. Look, um, Iris,
I know how Barry can be.
But you guys are like
the Meghan and Harry
of superhero royalty.
Your love is eternal.
- You two will talk and... and...
- We did talk.
I want Nora to stay here, he doesn't.
How do we solve that?
Okay, Iris, honey.
I haven't always been in
the near-perfect relationship
that I'm in now.
So take it from someone with experience,
the only way you two solve
this problem is together.
And you're not going to
find your answers here.
Yeah, you're right.
- You need to go after her.
- Oh, come on.
Give me a break. Have
you seen her right hook?
Ralph, she's hurt, I know.
But there's something more. I feel it.
She's determined.
Reprogramming complete.
The Time Sphere's navigation
core is now locked
onto Nora West-Allen's
temporal signature.
And you disabled the
tracker that Cisco installed
- into the Sphere?
- Yes.
However, there are still
alarms in S.T.A.R. Labs.
If you wish to use the Sphere undetected,
you must activate it off-site.
Planning a trip?
How did you get in here?
Followed you then
stretched under the door.
By the way, was anybody ever gonna
tell me about this secret room?
What else do we got in here?
A bowling alley or something?
Ralph, I don't have time for this.
Actually, it looks like you
have all the time in the world.
You're not gonna stop me.
Who said anything about stopping you?
I'm in position.
Thawne, I said I'm ready.
We shall see if you're ready.
Now run.
Now listen to me, Nora.
Breathe. Breathe.
You're reaching out and nobody's there.
The loneliness is pain.
Pain racing through your mind.
Crushing you, wrecking you,
shattering your soul into
a million little pieces.
And suddenly, you are no longer you.
You're part of something different now.
Part of a negative force.
It didn't work.
Thawne, why didn't it work?
- Are you ready?
- All set to hit
88 miles an hour!
Here we go.
Open the time breach!
Ralph, hurry up!
So the Cryo-Atomizer has the ability
to disperse particles
into the atmosphere.
Particles that slow down
atoms to a grinding halt.
- And the slower they get...
- The colder they get.
- How cold are we talking?
- Absolute zero.
And if we combine them
with Icicle's meta-powers...
He could plunge Central
City into a new Ice Age.
There is some good news.
I think we can track
the nano-cryoparticles
inside the atomizer.
We just have to reprogram an
oscillating inversion scanner.
Do you mind running to
the downstairs storage area
- and grabbing it?
- Mm-hmm.
Wait. You should use
a modified field array.
There's one in the upstairs archives.
No, no, actually the inversion scanner
would work best. Thank you.
No, no. Not since we upgraded
our field arrays last year.
You know you would know
that if you visited more,
not just when you needed something.
Apparently, only when
I need the wrong thing.
- The inversion scanner.
- The field array.
I'll get both.
Might take my time.
You need help?
No.
Is it me or is it getting
really cold in here?
Run!
Two for one.
So who wants a family reunion?
Hm?
Adieu, Team Flash.
Barry. Barry, come on!
Come on, Barr!
I can barely feel his pulse.
He has hypothermia. His
heart rate's dropping.
We only have seconds to save him.
- What are you doing?
- Well, this...
this machine has a large power source
I need to access to save Monsieur Allen.
Watch out.
That'll work. Stand back.
All right.
This current should
heat up the copper wiring
of his suit's circuitry and
we need to heat it up enough
so that his speed healing kicks in.
- Is this safe?
- Safer than dying.
- Come on, Monsieur Allen.
- Barry?
- Come on!
- Barr!
Icicle. He has them.
- No, no, no, no, Monsieur.
- No, no, wait. No, wait.
In time. In time. First, you rest.
Then we bring them home together.
Where are we?
In another decommissioned
Tannhauser site.
This site is a little more
off-the-grid than usual.
It's where we kept our
most classified projects.
Great. I guess we are
Icicle's next project.
We need to get out of here.
Well, there's a circuit panel over here.
I think we can hack
it and open the door.
Neither one of us knows
about electrical engineering.
Our best bet is to break
me out of these meta-cuffs
and let Killer Frost do the rest.
Don't be foolish.
You'll never break those.
Well, it's no more foolish
than you electrocuting
yourself, but if you want
to, knock yourself out.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
How did we get here?
I mean, you're my mother
and I'm your daughter.
But it has never felt like that.
You've always been cold, distant.
You never wanted to
be a part of my life.
Not then and certainly not now.
Why?
I mean, what did I ever do
to get treated like this?
- What?
- Why did you leave me?
You left me first.
You went to school across the
country to get away from me.
You took a job in Central City
instead of working in the
same zip code as my lab.
Caitlin, you were married
to a man I never even met.
I got the hint,
but don't you dare mistake things.
I didn't leave first.
What are we doing here?
What do you want with us?
I want what you could be.
- Stop it!
- Just a small blood sample.
See you soon, Snow Pack.
- What?
- Snow Pack.
That was your father's
nickname for our family.
I remember, and why is that scaring you?
He said he wanted what we could be
and then he took a sample of your blood.
Theoretically, he could
use the Cryo-Atomizer
to recreate the process
that created Killer Frost.
- So if he did that to you...
- I would gain an ice persona.
And now with a sample of my blood...
He can create a serum
that will permanently
suppress our human sides.
He wants an ice family
and he's willing to erase us to get it.
- Hold my suit.
- Oh, my God, Ralph.
- Do you ever wash this thing?
- Focus, okay?
You sure you're ready to talk
to "he who shall not be named"?
Well, whether I am or not, Gideon said
that these were Nora's
last known coordinates.
You're up.
Hey, bro.
Uh, what a day. Am I right?
You mind if I get a quick word
there with Hannibal Speedster?
It's just going to take, like, a second.
Is that right?
Well, unless you got a
signed Shift Change Order,
nobody goes in there but me, bro.
Only you, huh?
Okay, if you insist.
Hm. Oh, shrap.
Oh. Ooh.
You need to hurry.
This guy's such a dick, I got to think
super douchey thoughts
just to keep this face on.
Douchey, douchey, douchey.
I did everything
exactly like you told me.
How come I can't do this?
Listen, not harboring
enough rage to fuel your trip
is not something to be ashamed of.
You're just like your father.
Your light is your greatest strength.
- Nora.
- Mom?
Step away from him, please.
Mom, it's okay.
Eobard is helping me.
He has a way for me to get back home.
Nora, step away from him now.
Nora, listen to your mother.
Where's Dad?
It's just me.
It's probably for the best.
Come on, we have to hurry.
What do you mean it's
probably for the best?
Nora, the last thing your father needs
is to see you here with him.
She's right about that.
No.
No, she's not, and neither is my dad.
Nora, your dad was wrong,
but he still cares about you.
Why are you here and he isn't?
Look, I understand how you feel...
Do you?
Do you know what it's
like to want something more
than anything else in your whole life?
To know your father?
To do your best to
follow in his footsteps?
To make him proud?
How could he leave me?
- Wait, wait! That's enough!
- Nora.
How could he stop loving me?
No!
It's always the same condescending
"I know better than you" crap.
And you never change!
She's trying to kill me.
- Who else knows?
- Everyone.
It's time for you to go home.
Good-bye, Nora.
Goodbye, Nora. Goodbye, Nora.
She's gone.
What the hell do you mean she's gone?
- Gone where?
- I don't know where.
I only know when. 2019.
When Nora said you
showed her a way back...
she meant your way.
Yes. And I made a mistake.
She wanted to go home,
I tried to help her.
But listen, Iris, you have to find her.
She needs her family.
And that family does not include you.
But it does include Barry.
She needs you both united.
I'm only going to say this once.
You don't get to comment on us.
You stay the hell out of our business
or you won't even make it
to the end of that timer.
I like your anger,
but don't let it drive Barry away.
The only way for you to help Nora
is by doing it as a family.
Otherwise, you're simply leaving Barry
the exact same way he left Nora.
Iris, we got to bail.
They found Officer Jackass.
Think about it.
Iris, please.
What's it like having
another person in your head?
Pretty crazy.
I mean, when she first showed up,
I couldn't wait to get rid of her,
but when she disappeared,
I tried even harder to get her back.
What finally brought her back?
Family.
She protected us.
Well, I'm glad you had
someone there for you.
Hey, Mom, that was pretty
clever what you did.
Figuring out Icicle's plan.
Well, I recall you helped with that too.
It's amazing what we can do
when we're not trying to
rip each other's heads off.
Stay away from her.
I'll come back for her later.
First, we have some catching up to do.
What?
No!
Caitlyn!
There's no leads.
There's no hits on
Icicle's cryosignature,
no reads on facial recognition, nothing.
Barr, we'll find him. We always do.
How, Joe? How are we gonna find them?
Caitlyn's kidnapped.
We need Caitlyn to find Caitlyn.
Cisco's on another Earth
and Iris won't even answer my calls!
I...
I don't know how to fix any of this.
If I might?
It occurs to me that hiding
a needle in a haystack is good.
Hiding a needle in a stack of needles?
That's better.
These are all the
cold spots in the area.
You think Icicle is
masking his cryo-signature
with someplace that's already cold?
Giving him the perfect cover.
So we just refocus our search,
look for temperature anomalies
in already existing
cold spots, et voila.
This is great. I'll start
retasking the satellites.
- Hey, thanks for your help.
- The least I can do.
I've got a cold spike.
That's quite a stack of needles.
Thomas, are you in there?
Thomas, please.
Now it's time to meet your better half.
Perfection.
Boo.
How did you get out?
Me? I just raised my hands.
You were the one who froze my cuffs
so they shattered like glass.
Clever, Caitlyn.
I'm almost gonna miss
her when she's dead.
No turning back now.
Time to make a choice.
You either save her...
Or fight me.
Save her.
I'm gonna go get him.
Okay, explain again
why I'm here doing this
and not anybody else?
It appears we're a bit
short staffed at the moment.
All right, if it's
just us, it's just us.
- Let's do this.
- Let's do this thing.
- What's happening?
- Oh, great timing.
Oh, yeah, good timing. Oh, you do this.
Okay, Icicle has Caitlyn
and her mom in some caves
north of the Badlands.
Well, the Flash is already on the scene.
So for all we know, the
problem is already solved.
- Guys, I have a problem.
- Or not.
I need to phase Carla
out of a cryo-chamber
but it's too cold. I
can't even touch it.
All right, we need heat fast.
What if he generates a lightning bolt?
He can't throw a bolt.
That would kill her.
Then why doesn't he
just, uh, hold onto it?
- That could kill him!
- No, no. He's right.
The lightning cannot hurt
you if you are in phase.
If half my molecules are in phase,
the electricity would
hop from stable molecule
- to stable molecule.
- Creating an electronic bridge
that will generate the heat
that you need, et viola.
Without electrocuting
him, he can phase in,
grab her, and then phase out.
All in 3/10s of a second.
Uh-huh.
I got you. I got you.
I'm going to warm her up, all right?
What a waste.
I wanted to make you perfect.
Now I must end you.
Impossible.
Caity?
Dad?
Are you okay?
Is it you? Is it really you?
It's me.
- It's really me.
- Oh. Oh, my God.
You're going to be okay. You
just need to take it slow.
Thomas?
My God!
- Are you...
- I'm okay.
I took a beating but Killer Frost
ice healing kicked in.
I'm going to be fine thanks to Dad.
Well, how... how is this possible?
Well, I saw Icicle
about to kill Caitlyn,
and I found the strength
to break through.
Just like Killer Frost, Dad saved me.
Well, you saved me too, Caitlyn.
I mean, thanks to you, I think
I may have finally
banished this monster.
That's good.
That just leaves one more
monster for me to kill.
Run!
Get out of here. I'll take care of this.
Cool knife. I've got two.
Caitlyn, run!
Dad? Dad. Please.
Caitlyn.
Dad, I told you to go.
I already left once before.
Left both of you.
Worst mistake I've ever
made in my entire life.
I wasn't going to make that again.
Family shouldn't leave family.
I'll always love you.
How's Caitlyn and her mom?
Caitlin's still running some tests,
but she thinks Carla's gonna be okay.
I mean, as okay as she can
be given the circumstances.
Why was Cicada II even there tonight?
I mean, why attack Icicle and Caitlin?
Perhaps the ice meta were
not the primary target.
What could Cicada II want
with the Cryo-Atomizer?
Well, we're not gonna
figure it out tonight.
So let's rest tonight.
Are you coming back to the house?
Um...
No, I'm gonna stay at the loft tonight.
You are?
Yeah.
We should talk.
Awkward a bit.
So you went to the future?
Yeah. John Stamos still handsome.
He'll never not age.
No, never. Man, he looks good.
So this endothermic litmus test
would've created a
stoichiometric reaction.
If there was any residual
meta DNA in your system, it...
Would've turned white. I know.
And it's still green, so you're clean.
You're not a meta.
Those were all the clues
that I used to find dad.
Including some files
that I may have stolen
from your file room.
Aww, Caitlin and Thomas
infamous Periodic Table.
Nerdonium.
You know, he stole that one from me.
Really? I thought he came up with that
while he was fixing the kitchen sink.
No, I thought of that.
Come to think of it, I
also fixed the kitchen sink.
Well, I... I better be going.
Good night, Caity.
Mom? Um...
Do you want to maybe go get a drink?
You can tell me more about
elements you invented.
Now or whenever.
No, actually, now would be perfect.
There's a little wine
bar around the corner.
Mm-hmm.
Heading home?
Well, it's like Barry said... and Joe...
- I've done enough.
- They did say that.
But you hung around anyway.
Oui, I did.
You were there for
Barry when he needed you.
Oui, I was.
And you helped saved Caitlyn's mom.
Yes, that's right. I
did all those things.
I should not have done those things?
I'm just saying maybe
you have more to do...
For your family.
I just wanted my family back together.
Even if that meant
doing something drastic
like time travel.
Yeah, I get that.
More than anyone.
You were right about Thawne.
I think he's manipulating Nora,
but I also believe him.
Nora is back here in our time.
I was...
Wrong.
I shouldn't have left Nora
or made that decision without you.
Whatever it is that
we have to figure out,
we should've done it together.
Family doesn't leave family.
Well, I mean you weren't the
only one to make that mistake.
I shouldn't have gone to
the future without you.
I shouldn't have left you like that.
I mean, that was the same thing
that I got so mad at you for.
But I know now that we can't solve this
if we don't stick together.
I can barely solve things with you,
so without you...
Are we making jokes already? Really?
Let's bring our kid home.
There's something else
that I wanted to tell you.
Barry, the way that Thawne
looks when he talks about Nora.
I've only ever seen
that in one other person.
You.
What are you saying?
I think Thawne might
actually care about Nora.
Soon, Grace.
Soon.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --