Feels like my shift started
100 years ago.
Drink more coffee.
You're around it all day. Duh.
Besides, that place is so boring.
- Wait. What's that?
- Um...
Yeah, just some guy cosplaying.
What's he doing now?
I don't know. Must be some sort of
Comic-Con thing or something.
What in the world?
Natalie? Natalie, what's that noise?
Natalie, what's that noise?
Natalie? Natalie?
My beautiful boy.
I'm giving him all the strength I can
to heal him.
Which means I'll be weak
for a bit longer.
Because Psych
and Fuerza attacked you?
Exactly.
Do you remember what happened?
Only some of it.
When I was reborn,
I was surrounded by light and love.
Then came the pain.
I could feel these Forces of Nature
were like me. Only... evil.
If they're like you,
then why are they trying to kill you?
I'm not sure,
but I think it's to feed.
That's why I had to find Barry Allen.
I thought he could keep me safe
until I fully recovered.
But if the other Forces find me
in this condition,
I wouldn't survive another attack.
Don't worry.
We are gonna figure out a way
to keep you safe.
Somehow.
Holy Henry T. Sampson...
Wow. So you're the actual,
all-encompassing,
immeasurably interstellar,
and mind-bendingly cosmerific...
Yes, Chester P. Runk.
I am the Speed Force.
Woo-hoo. Chessman...
How's that isotope detection system
coming along?
Yeah, actually...
- She knows my name.
- I think she does.
Okay.
Behold, believers...
This puppy I designed
can boost isotopic signals
for our satellites to scan.
Now all we need to do
is build a few units,
place them around the outskirts
of the city, and...
Eureka!
And then we would
get an early warning
if Psych or Fuerza
decided to come back.
And they can detect
foundational isotopic signatures.
So, we won't just know
they're coming...
We'll know, whoever it is,
Psych or Fuerza,
which one is headed our way.
Chester, that is amazing.
Could we use this
to follow the other Forces?
Perhaps find them
before they find us?
Not yet.
Right now they only work
in close proximity, so...
But at least now we have a way
to help protect you.
Cisco, how long would it take
to make enough amplifiers?
We have everything we need
in the S.T.A.R. Labs van.
So, we could build them as we go.
So let's do this, baby.
- 'Cause Team Chesco is on the case!
- Ah!
- Let's get it.
Separated at birth.
Hey.
What's all this?
Norvok finally brought the rest
of my stuff over
from one of Amunet's stash houses.
I was gonna throw everything away
but then muse struck.
Oh, wow. It's great.
Yeah, this'll really give the place
some attitude when I'm done.
I'm sorry.
You wanna hang that in here?
Yeah. That empty wall behind you,
it's been driving me crazy.
Well, you know what they say...
Great minds...
What do you think?
Um... It's missing something.
Ah.
Much better.
You know, art should always provoke
a strong reaction.
It does.
And... sensor is ready.
Excellent.
Once the amplifier goes live,
then our early warning system
will be a go.
And that means it's time for...
Coffee and a cronut.
Coffee and a cronut...
Actually, you know,
there's a Sip-n-Dash in Masonville.
Or was, back in the day.
Oh, I used to live there,
but Grandma Runk and I moved
to Central City
when I was done with high school.
All right.
- Looks like we're ready to go.
- Okay, cool.
- What?
- Why?
Look at this.
What do you think?
You think it's the neutrino
filtration glitching on us?
Cisco, Cisco, Cisco...
What?
We're okay? We're okay.
What was that?
I have no idea.
Well, looks like
the sensor's working.
Did I give you my phone?
No.
Mine's gone, too.
Okay, hold up.
Where's the van?
It was just here.
Does the van have a secret cloaking
mode that I don't know about?
Asking for a friend.
That's no van.
Whoa.
Ches...
we've just been Under-the-Domed.
Nora?
You all right?
Yeah.
Just making sure
nothing happens to Barry.
How do you deal with all this?
Well, it's never easy
dealing with a threat.
Especially when it affects someone
that you care about.
But don't worry, okay?
By this time tomorrow,
Barry will be back
to his old self, healed,
wrapped up on the couch,
full BBB-style.
BBB. Barry's Blanket Burrito.
It's hard to explain.
No, I understand.
It's something
between the two of you.
Actually, you know what?
It doesn't have to be.
I wanna show you something.
Come with me.
We made it.
Now we can find a phone and call
S.T.A.R. Labs before...
Tell me you're seeing
what I'm seeing.
Does it have anything to do with
Space Jam being back in stock?
At that Blockbuster Video
that doesn't exist anymore?
Yeah. And get this.
I saw a Sip-n-Dash store back there
that got torn down
when I was in high school.
I think we just time-traveled.
Really?
So, tonight we're gonna party
like it's 1998?
None of the pay phones work.
We don't have cell phones.
And we're trapped
in an invisible barrier.
We are stuck...
in the '90s?
This is so epic! Epic!
Wait. No, no, no.
It is off the heezy-fo-sheezy.
Okay, Cheesy,
why don't you calm down?
Look. Is this frickin' awesome?
Yes.
Do we desperately need to figure out
a way to get back home?
Also yes.
Well, how are we supposed to do that
without a DeLorean hot tub?
By looking at what brought us here.
A green energy wave
that looks like it came straight out
of Turtle 2.0, White Whale's Revenge.
Coincidence? I think not.
Look, I know you and Turtle 2.0
kinda have this thing...
I'll say.
Maybe we're not dealing with
a meta at all.
The amplifier showed
an isotopic surge when the wave hit.
So it's one of our Forces.
Wait. Check the signatures.
Was it Fuerza or Psych?
Neither. The sensor detected
a temporal energy.
So there's a new Force
in town, and...
And it can control time.
Yeah, okay, we got to get outta here
and warn the team.
- The Speed Force isn't safe.
- Not so fast.
We need to know exactly
who we're up against.
Remember how the Speed Force
asked if the amplifiers
could track the Forces?
Yeah.
If we added a transmitter diode
to the sensor...
It could localize
the isotopic circuits enough
to detect a new Force
within a 20-yard radius.
Right, but we need
the kind of maxed-out receiver
that just doesn't exist yet.
Time to go shopping.
Man, there's a Tech Station
right here.
Ches, hurry up. This is embarrassing.
See?
One man's trash is another man's...
Another man's reason
for a tetanus shot?
I already got my tetanus shot.
I can't believe you just used junk
to fix our sensor.
Just think of it as one
repurposed Force Finder.
Rest in peace, Ultrafax 4000.
Damn, they don't make 'em
like you anymore.
All right.
Let's find ourselves a time god.
The high school, huh?
The sensor seems to think
they're in here somewhere.
Let's do this.
Yo, yo, yo. For real?
Masonville's principal
suffers zero fools. Feel me?
All right,
then we just sneak in, simple.
We gotta blend in.
We got to kick it up a notch.
This is how we do it
Come on.
Check it out!
Once upon a time in '94
Montell made no money
And life sure was slow
There lived a DJ
And Paul was his name
He came up to Monty,
This is what he said
You and Oji are gonna make some cash
Sell a million records
And we're makin' the dash
I'm buzzin' because...
This is how we do it...
All right. Here's the plan.
We ask people questions.
See if anybody has any
diabolical plans to alter the future.
- Yes.
- And then we check the sensor.
If it spikes...
Then we've found our time god.
Let's get it.
This for the yearbook?
Yeah. "Future
Falcon Forecast" section.
- Mm-hm.
- What's the question again?
Where do you see yourself
in 23 years?
Mm.
Shorty's eyes be rollin'
When I start to flow
Fallen on the stage
But my boo's a no-show
My girl complains, my verses be weak
She shakes the 8-ball
"See? Outcome looks bleak"
Yeah
Yeah.
Twenty-three... Yeah.
In 23 years, I'll be like everyone
else in this dumb high school.
A zombie. Totally dead.
But I'm the bomb
I'm gonna kill in the future
Blowin' all them rap minds
You'll be needin' a suture
Dead inside from slaving away
at a thankless job.
Oh...
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
- Jobs are bad.
- That'll be all.
- Uh...
- Yeah. Keep going.
- Keep spittin'.
- Yeah, you got it, boy.
Blowin' all them rap minds
You'll be needin' a suture
Boom
And that's my Falcon Forecast
It's Reggie Q., I'm out the past
Oh!
- Drop the mic.
- Yes.
- He's spittin'...
- No.
- No? Okay.
- Carry the two...
- No, you don't carry the two.
K-Dog. Check it out.
Parents got it for me.
Said they want the NFL
to be able to hit me up anytime.
- It's hella cool, right?
- Yeah, yeah. Nice, Deon.
Yeah, man.
You know, in the future,
I want to be just like Deon.
You know he's gonna kill it
in State Championship tomorrow.
Yo, K-swizzle, it's time to bounce.
Well...
That's not him.
Wait till those dumb jocks see what
the future has in store for them.
Yo. Parker, right?
Listen. Do you have
a couple minutes to spare
so we can ask you a few questions?
Who are you?
- We're students.
- Students.
- Just like you.
- Yeah, you guys talk like my dad.
Come on. Don't be whack.
- All right, we are 17.
- I'm 16.
We love The Real World.
We like Beanie Babies and The Matrix.
The Matrix hasn't come out yet.
Ah, shoot! See? I had a feeling...
Wait a second.
- How did you know that?
- This isn't right.
You gotta help me. Please.
We're trapped in the same day.
No, wait.
It knows I broke free.
It's gonna start over. Oh, God!
Oh, not again!
Okay.
That was freaky.
You all right, dude?
Who are you?
Where am I?
Did you take my headgear?
Dude, it's me. Chester.
No.
No. I don't know you.
Stranger danger!
Stranger danger.
Uh... Cisco?
How old are you?
I'm seven, you predator.
Because you still think it's 1998.
Oh, no, no.
- Cisco.
- Don't chase after me.
I don't wanna get in your van.
I'm not trying to hurt you.
Listen, just listen. Okay?
You're not seven.
You're 30. And you're a scientist
at S.T.A.R. Labs. Remember?
What about visiting Atlantis?
Or King Shark versus Grodd?
Oh, God. Please tell me you remember
Game of Thrones.
- Littlefinger.
- Yes.
- The Iron Throne.
- "The Rains of Castamere."
- "The Rains of Castamere." Yes!
Chester.
How did we get here?
Last thing I remember,
Parker was going all Get Out on us.
No, no. Parker's not our Biff Tannen.
A modern reference jolted him awake,
just like you.
We're back on Main Street.
Right before the wave hit,
Parker said, "It's gonna start over."
Gotta go.
- It's a time loop.
This isn't about changing the future,
it's about reliving one day
over and over.
When Parker woke up,
it reset the loop.
But why didn't you get whammied?
I think the sensor absorbed
the temporal energy
and shielded me.
I mean, by the looks of it,
that's not happening again.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We have to fix this.
Otherwise, if the loop resets,
we won't be shielded.
We won't remember
that we're stuck in the past,
and we'll be trapped here
like everyone else.
We have to fix this now.
Okay, you know, I think I have the
parts to fix this at Grandma Runk's.
Perfect. Let's go there right now.
And while we're on our way
maybe we can figure out
what's so special
about December 4th, '98.
Uh...
You know what?
These parts ain't at Grandma Runk's.
Someplace better.
Please don't go dumpster-diving.
This blanket is quite well-loved.
He's had it for years.
How does swaddling himself help?
Well, it's not about the blanket.
It's more like wrapping himself
in the memories and the comfort
associated with the blanket.
It's like being hugged
by warm, loving arms.
His mother made it for him.
He doesn't really
talk about her much. So...
Not even with you?
They were so close.
Being reminded of what happened,
he's forced to think
about that night.
The violence of it all...
it stays with him.
And I wish that I could take
that away from him, but...
I can't.
TI-82. Girl, you still fine.
Stop flirting with the calculators.
- We got a problem.
- What?
The X-76 power converter,
they just sold the last one
to that guy.
Okay, chill.
It's not that big a deal.
He actually looks pretty reasonable.
I say we just offer to buy it back
from him.
No, no, no. We can't go after him.
Okay. Why not?
Ches, what's going on?
We can't go after him because...
he's my dad.
I'm the last person
he'd wanna help right now.
Ches, you wanna
tell me what's going on?
My pops was a very smart guy,
who traveled all the time,
trying to get rich
off his latest invention. So...
He never had time for me.
It was always, "Sorry, son.
I don't believe in quitting."
- Look, whatever happened...
- Tomorrow, my dad dies
in a car accident on his way
to some big meeting in Coast City.
Today's the last day I see him alive.
I'm sorry.
That's heavy for anyone.
Let alone a kid.
What if...
What if you're here for a reason?
This could be your chance
to talk to your dad.
What good would that do?
I can't save his life.
That would just reset the time loop.
No, I just got to stay firm.
Keep doing my thing.
I understand.
Don't worry about
the converter, all right?
I'll get it from him.
You're gonna go talk to my dad?
Just long enough to get the X-76.
Then I come back here,
we fix everything
and it all goes back to normal.
That is what you want, right?
Oh, thank God.
I thought you might go
somewhere Barry knows,
but you weren't at S.T.A.R. Labs
and C.C.P.D. seemed unlikely.
Yes, and I know how
he loves the coffee here.
I never took into account
how much his mother's death
might still weigh on him.
What have I done?
I'll change my appearance.
Appear in my true form to all of you
from now on,
as lightning, because
I can't keep hurting him like this.
You're not causing him pain.
You're giving him a gift.
How?
It's like how his blanket
reminds him of his mom.
And that memory gives him comfort
and peace.
It's the same thing with you.
So I'm not a painful reminder?
No, not at all. You are a happy one.
I may be his lightning rod,
but you are his lightning.
Thank you.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Can I help you, kid?
Me? Yeah.
I'd like to buy your X-76 converter.
What makes you think
I have one, Mister...
Boyega, John Boyega.
The clerk at the tech shop
said that you bought the last one
and they don't get another shipment
for a week. So...
Look, I'd like to help you,
but I need this X-76
power converter, too.
You need it for some
important invention, right?
Nope. Throwing it away.
Uh...
My son, Chester,
is working on a project.
I've looked at his plans.
Two days from now,
he's gonna need that part,
but I'll be back on the road by then.
I'm throwing it away now
so that he can find it later...
when he needs it.
Do you have kids, Mr. Boyega?
If you do some day,
you'll understand.
Wait. So why not just give it to him?
It's my way of teaching him to be
resourceful and a problem solver.
- It's kind of brilliant.
- I know.
Plus, he gets the joy
of learning to see treasure...
where other people see trash.
Do you do this kind of thing
a lot for him?
Everything I do is for him.
He's the reason
I get out of bed in the morning.
But don't you ever resent
having to work so hard, 24/7?
I'm the boy's father.
Chester is worth any sacrifice
I have to make.
Besides...
when it comes to him...
I don't believe in quitting.
So...
You don't care about your work
more than your son.
You care about your work because...
I'm just a man
trying to do the right thing.
Make my son proud.
Yeah, this is weird.
Sorry. Uh...
It was pretty inspiring.
And I hope I can be
a great dad too someday.
Something tells me you will be.
Still not selling you
that part, though.
But if you really need one,
I think I have an idea.
Hold that.
Cisco,
my pops is pretty cool, man.
Yeah. Sounds like it.
I'm just really glad
we had a day to hang out.
I didn't even realize that my pops
isn't just smart.
Dude's a genius. Check it.
Pops and I built it, together.
Wow.
You know what this means?
Now we can disrupt
the temporal isotopes...
- ...and go home.
- Yes!
- Yo, nerds, been looking for you.
Hey, yo, Deon.
We were just going to...
- Thinking of going to Blockbuster.
- Blockbuster.
- You ever seen Space Jam?
- Four times, man.
Oh, man. It's so good.
Now it's time to kick you wannabe
Urkels to the curb.
Because whoever you two are...
you don't belong here.
This is my time...
and you two got to go.
Time god.
Thanks for ruining
my perfect day. Not.
Yo, Deon.
Why bum around 1998?
Man, I thought you left
the small town life
for college and the NFL...
That wasn't me!
You will have 30 minutes
to create an amuse-bouche...
Another woman
Oh, crap.
Caity, I think we got a problem.
What do you mean?
Grandma Runk said
that after you won State...
It was the second string quarterback
that led the team to victory.
Not me, dumbass.
I got injured and taken out
in the first quarter.
He got all the victory.
Me,
I got four pins in my knee
and a job selling used cars.
I came back to the past
because I have no future!
That's weird...
because your future looks
bright to me!
You dweebs really think
you can stop me?
You trippin'.
- Oh, not good.
- Oh, snap.
I just erased it from time.
My bad.
Could somebody please tell me
what this green energy
is doing to my city?
There are geothermic isotopes
all over the city,
which means
we know it's one of the Forces.
We're just trying to figure out
which one.
This used to be a tablet.
So, it's not just me.
Baby girl.
You look incredible.
So do you, Dad.
Frost.
Caitlin.
Thanks for trying.
Nora, Iris told
you were here, but...
it's so good to see you.
It's good to see you too, Captain.
Scans show that
the isotopic foundation is unstable.
The green wave is spreading
and heading toward downtown.
What's that noise?
Natalie. Natalie. Natalie.
Oh, my God.
I was able to trace the energy
to a nearby town.
Masonville?
Cisco and Chester were installing
an early warning system by there.
Looks like something triggered
the amplifier sensor?
If I can access the data drive,
I might be able to figure out
what set this off.
"Temporal," as in time travel?
Yeah, but this energy doesn't match
Psych or Fuerza, which means...
Which means that we're dealing with
a new Force of Nature that can...
alter time.
Buckle up, fools,
because once I reset my time loop,
you'll forget everything.
We've got to get out here.
He's too powerful.
We can't fight him on our own.
Come on.
Ches?
I don't believe in quitting.
These isotopic signatures
are moving at speeds
that should be impossible.
This new Force is rewinding time
at random.
We can't stop it.
What happens if we get stuck
in one of these time pockets?
We could end up in the Stone Age.
Oh, my God. It's up to Cisco
and Chester now.
Hey, yo, Deon.
Listen to me.
You can make us forget our futures...
but there's no power in the world
that will make you forget yours.
Yeah, tell me about it!
Tried to rewrite that night
100 times.
No matter what I try to do,
I can't change what happens.
What happened to you
must be a fixed point.
You can't change it.
So maybe you should stop trying
and instead, choose to see
the possibilities in every new day.
Look, your future's
still not written, Deon.
I hate my future!
I'm supposed to be
the next Patrick Mahomes, man.
Look, I know it's easy...
to hold on to the bad stuff.
Ever since I was a kid,
I thought that my pops
cared more about his job than me.
Boo-hoo, man.
And I carried that hurt
around with me for years.
But today, when I looked
at my past with fresh eyes...
I saw that my dad worked hard
to give me a better life.
And once I saw that, it helped me
let go of that pain, Deon.
You can do the same...
but not until you stop letting
one moment in your past
define all the moments
in your future.
Future's on me?
Yeah.
So I get to figure out
what it looks like?
So I get to decide
what happens from now on?
Not just for me...
but for everyone.
Time to bounce.
Well, Barry, looks like
your vitals have stabilized.
How you feeling?
I feel fine.
So, no luck finding Deon yet?
So far, satellites haven't found
any traces of his
temporal energy signature.
And he's a time god. So who knows
where or when he might be hiding?
Plus, I think Deon's only just now
starting to realize
the full scope of his powers.
But I don't get it.
Not once did he mention
chasing after you.
Well, unlike the others,
he might not know that I survived.
That makes sense.
You know, it's weird. Every time
you and Chester talk about Deon,
he sounds a lot more reasonable
than Psych,
and a lot less lethal than Fuerza.
Even so, being able to control time
makes him the most powerful
Force yet.
He could stop you in your tracks
anytime, anywhere. That's his power.
It's like he's the opposite
of the Speed Force.
He's the Still Force, which I guess
would make Fuerza the Strength Force.
And that would make Psych
the Sage Force.
If this new Force
is more powerful than me,
then how did you defeat him, Cisco?
I didn't defeat him.
Chester P. did.
I got lucky.
Yeah, I'm going to leave the going
mano-a-mano with Big Bads
to the Flash, you know.
Oh. That's Kamilla.
Supposed to meet up at Jitters.
Caitlin, you still in?
Absolutely. Let me grab my bag.
What about you, Ches? You still down?
No. I actually have an errand to run,
but bring a brother
back a Vibe-accino?
Duh.
Hey, you didn't get lucky.
All right? What you did out there...
I'm proud of you.
Yeah.
I guess I'm just a man
trying to do the right thing.
Make my pops proud.
Caitlin, hurry up. I'm trying
to get this coffee and a cronut.
Iris...
thanks to you, I'm seeing things
a lot clearer now.
Well, I imagine you two are anxious
to get home,
so I'll see in the morning.
Wait. You're staying here tonight?
Well, I want to know right away
if the satellites
find the other Forces.
Yeah. No, I get that,
but we'll get an alert
if that happens.
Nora, we have clean sheets
in our guest room
and plenty of blankets.
Sounds cozy.
Yeah, it is.
You should stay with us tonight.
Right, Barry?
Um...
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
You have no idea how much
that would mean to me.
- Really.
- It's our pleasure.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
I got you, Pops.
I'mma finish what you started.
Okay.
Oh... No. No. No, no, no.
Is that damn time bubble back?
Oh, no. I just like the look.
So I decided to swing
by a thrift store.
Picked up these bad boys, too.
Listen, we need to talk.
Ugh. Nothing good ever starts
with "We need to talk."
This new state liaison
that's auditing C.C.P.D.,
her name's Kristen Kramer.
I just found out that she's here
to catch a dangerous fugitive
- meta-human.
- Hm.
She's here for Killer Frost.
That's not who I am anymore.
I know. I just got to find a way
to make her see that.
In the meantime, you need to lay low.
Yeah, that's not going to happen.
She's former Army
Intelligence, Frost.
I don't care if she's
Xena, Warrior Princess.
I am finally free
to live my own life,
and no one is going
to take that away from me.
So if this Kristen Kramer wants
to come after me,
then I say, "Bring it on."
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::