- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
- Previously,
on "The Flash"...
Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
- 12 markers,
12 metas.
- They identified the targets
sooner than we planned.
- Perhaps.
- There's nothing
within miles of here
capable of even creating
dark matter.
- There was three weeks ago.
This is where I came out
of the Speed Force.
- And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
- You think the guy behind
the samurai robot...
- Samuroid.
- He wanted us to create
a busload of metas?
- I think it's all connected.
- Hello, gorgeous.
You ready to get
your schmoopy on?
- Joe, I'm pregnant.
[Lee Williams &amp; Cymbal's
"I Need You Baby"]
- ♪ I've been lonely ♪
♪ For such a long, long time ♪
♪ I've been lonely ♪
- Look, I was thinking...
- No, no.
Less thinking, more kissing.
- [moans]
- Okay, but hold on a minute.
This thing we got going on,
this is real good.
- It's okay.
- What?
- No, I'm just kidding.
It's better than okay.
- Yeah, that's right.
But because of that,
I think we're at a place
in our relationship
where the guy says to his girl
those three magic words.
- What...what three words?
- What's your name?
- Um, oh.
Well, that is technically
four words.
- Mmm, actually, technically
it's three words
'cause contractions are
one word
and that's how grammar works.
That's not the point, though.
What's your name?
- Gypsy.
My name is Gypsy.
- For real?
So, you were born,
and somebody was just like,
"I'm gonna name you Gypsy?"
- Gypsy is what
I like to be called.
It is mysterious.
And it's moody.
- Hmm.
Moody's right.
- All right.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
And when I get back,
you'd better stop asking me
my real name.
And be wearing less clothes.
- I don't need
to know your name.
♪ Mmm, this girl,
she 'bout to rock your world ♪
[rumbling]
- You're a dead man.
[grunting]
[dramatic music]
- Those are collectibles.
Aah.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[both grunting]
Who are you?
- Daddy?
- [laughs]
Pleased to meet you, sir.
[laughs]
Is he gonna put me down?
[camera shutters clicking]
- You know,
some of you may not realize,
but before I was mayor,
I was a cop
in this very precinct.
And it's because of
these men and women
every family in Central City
can sleep comfortably at night.
- What's happening?
- Mayor Bellows is
on his reelection campaign.
- Detective Joe West.
Keep up the good work.
What do you say, Joe?
[quirky music]
- I'll do that.
- And that's why
he's not a politician.
- I hate that.
- Yeah?
Thought about
running against him?
Can't you picture yourself
shaking hands
and kissing babies?
- What?
Ain't nobody talking
about babies.
You said you had a lead on
this meta bus situation.
- Yeah, I do.
Come here.
- Fellow for Bellows!
[applause]
- You took the photos down
from your mother's case.
- Yeah, well,
the case was solved.
This one isn't.
We got these two.
Kilgore and Hazard.
But that still leaves ten
meta-humans that were created
when I came out of
the Speed Force.
- How hard can it be to track
down ten bus passengers?
- Well, according to the
Department of Transportation,
over 900 people rode that bus
that day.
- What about the bus driver?
- That's where things get
more interesting.
He's dead.
Drowned in his own bathtub.
- That's not too suspicious.
- Harry said it was
all connected.
I think he's right.
I mean, the Samuroid
pushing you guys
to bring me back,
me not coming out
of the place
you thought I would,
the bus being
in the exact right place
to be hit by dark matter...
- It was planned.
- Yeah.
By somebody smart.
- We're pretty smart.
- Well, I think so.
- Okay, let's look closer
into the bus driver's death.
It may give us a lead.
- I'll have Iris pull up
the autopsy report
from the coroner's office.
- Sounds good.
What?
- I don't know.
This morning, you're, like...
glowing.
- What do you mean,
"glowing?"
- I just mean, like, you got,
like, a warmth about you.
Like a Lite-Brite.
- There's no warmth.
No glow.
And I ain't no damn
Lite-Brite.
You're wasting time.
S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Glowing and irritable.
[calm music]
♪ ♪
How's Cecile?
- Fine.
The same.
I mean, nothing's changed.
If something changes,
I'll let you know.
- All right.
[elevator chimes]
- This facility
is poorly guarded.
- Clearly.
- Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey.
Okay.
Power down, buckaroo.
Oh, good.
You're both here.
- Cisco, who is this?
- This is Breacher.
AKA Gypsy's father.
- Oh.
Yeah, I, um, can see
the resemblance.
- There is no resemblance.
- So, you know how Gypsy's
kind of a big deal collector
on Earth-19? Well,
her boss is her dad...
who decided to pay us a little
surprise visit
at the perfect time.
Which is why I decided to show
him around where I work.
You know?
- I'm Barry Allen.
- Cisco's personal assistant.
- His what?
- And he is the best
personal assistant
I've ever had.
He stays late,
starts early.
One day, I'll be
working for him.
- What are you doing?
- I wanted to impress him,
and now I can't stop.
- Joe West.
- A fellow law man.
You, I can respect.
- And Harry Wells back there.
- You look like someone I once
sent my daughter to kill.
- I get that a lot.
- Uh, I thought maybe someone
would want to give him
the, uh, the old look-see.
- Great idea.
Um, Allen, Detective West,
why don't you give Gypsy's
father here
the nickel tour of
the facilities?
- Joe.
- I've had to pee for,
like, three hours.
- What is wrong with you?
- Have you seen his face?
The guy's killed people with
that face.
I'm not even joking.
Gypsy said that
literally happened.
- You want his approval, right?
- Yes, I want his approval.
He's my girlfriend's father.
- Of course.
Cisco, listen.
You're a fine, upstanding,
smart, well-groomed young man.
Any father would be happy
to have you date his daughter,
except me.
Can't date my daughter,
all right?
Can't date Jesse.
Jesse's off limits.
- Went for the compliment,
did not stick the landing.
- Just take him for coffee,
okay?
Go for coffee,
get to know him
a little bit better.
I bet that you'll be
pleasantly surprised
at how much
you have in common, right?
You both have
the same powers.
You're breachers.
You have ridiculous hair.
He has ridiculous hair.
- Okay, but...
- And you both love Gypsy.
- Are you actually giving me
decent relationship advice
right now?
- I am.
You'll be fine.
- I don't wanna be here
anymore.
- And we're leaving.
[quirky music]
- Have fun storming the castle.
- Why is the scariest person
I've ever seen
roaming our halls?
both: Cisco.
- Oh.
- Okay, so, I've got
the coroner's report
for the death of
the bus driver,
but it doesn't seem like
there's any signs of foul play.
- Aside from him being the one
guy that could have told us
who else was on that bus.
- They logged his
personal effects, let's see...
Credit cards, cash, receipts,
um...
- Wait, go back.
Ralph Dibny.
- I'll be damned.
- Who is Ralph Dibny?
- He used to be a cop.
- Dirty cop.
He got kicked off the force.
- For what?
- It's a long story.
[tense music]
- That's him.
- Oh.
He's handsome in a square-jawed
Oliver Queen kind of way.
- For real?
- Babe, you know
I've only got eyes for you.
- The I.O.U. is dated
the same day
that I came out
of the Speed Force.
- You think Dibny was
on the bus that day?
Maybe he's a meta-human now?
- Let's pay him a visit.
- Hey.
You seem...something.
What's up with you
and this Ralph guy?
- It's like Joe said.
It's a long story.
♪ ♪
- Oliver Queen is hot.
- Amen, hallelujah.
- I promised there wasn't
a single case I couldn't crack.
And a promise made is
a promise kept.
Dibny detects.
Your husband didn't die in that
plane crash, Mrs. Broome.
- He didn't?
Then where is he?
- Well, that brings us to
the difficult part.
Turns out he got remarried
and moved to Minnesota.
Has two kids now.
Twins.
[chuckles]
Twins in the twin cities.
- [crying]
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't.
Don't cry for that jerk.
He doesn't deserve it.
The sun still shines.
The birds,
they still chirp.
Chirp, chirp.
Mrs. Broome, you are
a very attractive woman,
and you will find someone else.
Someone who will hold you.
Someone who will
wipe away those tears.
Do you like shrimp?
[slap]
Ow!
- Uh...
- This is definitely his place.
[knocking]
- Reconsidered, huh?
- Ralph.
- Joe West.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Barry Allen.
Been a long time, rookie.
- Well, I'm not a rookie
anymore, Dibny.
You look healthy.
- Yeah.
Got the spare tire
out of the trunk.
It happens.
Might even happen to you, too,
one day, Slim Jim.
So what brings you boys to
Casa de Dibny?
- Were you on the 405 bus
four weeks ago around noon?
- That's a very
specific question.
- We found your I.O.U. from
the deceased bus driver's
personal effects.
- Deceased?
Hey.
That's one less "U" I owe.
What's it to you two?
- It's a simple question.
Why don't you just answer it?
- You walk into my office
after five years
like nothing ever happened,
and ask me for a favor?
I smell a mystery.
- It's not a favor.
It's information.
- And how much is
this information worth?
- Are you shaking us down?
- I know something you don't.
And you need to know it badly,
otherwise you'd never
swallow your pride and face me
after what you did.
- After what I did?
- Ralph.
The people on that bus
were exposed
to a dangerous substance.
- Dangerous?
♪ ♪
Dangerous like what?
Like...Ebola?
- Were you on the bus?
- No.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- Hey, I heard you shacked up
with that hot D.A.
She got a sister?
Okay.
Good luck.
All the best.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[knocking]
So, what's it worth?
Ah, crap.
[screaming]
♪ ♪
Guys,
you don't want to do this!
I don't know what you want.
Let's talk about this.
Put me down.
both: Whoa!
- Don't put me down!
Don't put me down!
[flesh stretching]
♪ ♪
[whimpering]
- That guy hasn't changed
a bit.
- You really expect him to?
- Whoa!
♪ ♪
- I guess he was on that bus.
- [humming]
[screams]
[groaning]
[all shouting]
Hey, guys?
What the hell?
- Yeah, yeah, well,
you're welcome.
- What happened to me?
- Breathe, okay?
- I am breathing.
- Okay.
- Clearly this guy
is a bus meta.
- This is interesting.
The dark matter has
polymerized Dibny's cells.
- What the hell is dark matter,
and why is it in my cells?
- You're saying
the walls of every cell
in his body have elasticized?
- I'm saying they formed
an unbreakable bond
at the atomic level.
Now you can stretch these cells
and stretch these cells.
- Like Silly Putty.
- I'm Silly Putty?
both: No.
- Kinda.
- I'm Silly Putty?
- Ralph.
Who were the guys on the roof?
- Is that really the issue
right now?
Look at me!
Allen, you
and your S.T.A.R. Labs nerds
better put me back together.
-We're trying to help you.
- You're not trying to help me.
- Shut up.
[all shouting]
- Come on!
Oh, come on!
- You can do this later.
I just need a sample of blood.
[gasps]
- Whoa.
- [gasps]
- Ow!
[sneezes]
Oh, is that my face?
- [vomits]
- [groans]
- Four years seeing this stuff,
I finally puked.
[rock music playing]
♪ ♪
- Can I plug in?
- Daddy.
I know you love me,
and I love you.
I really like Cisco, and
I need you two to get along.
So do you think that
you can try to do that?
- I'll do anything for you,
petal.
- Ah, three coffees.
How about you, huh?
Ready for some hot java?
- We don't have coffee
on my Earth.
Crops were destroyed.
My world was attacked...
invaded...by the worst,
most evil creatures
in the multiverse.
I'll never drink coffee again.
- Two for me.
- It's okay.
Daddy, why don't
I get you a tea?
- Like a relaxing tea?
- Yeah.
- Please.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Pop a squat.
Uh...
I know from a friend...
who is also a father...
how important his daughter
is to him.
And I just wanted to
let you know how important
your daughter is to me.
And that after you and I get to
know each other a little,
maybe we might find that...
we're not so different.
- I'm going to hunt you.
- [choking]
- You're not worthy of her.
- Isn't that for her to decide?
- Ten.
- Also, I could have
sworn you said,
uh, you were gonna hunt me.
What, like a deer?
- I have hunted
some of the worst
breach criminals in history.
Marla the Dark Lord.
Soolunga of Sheerdra.
The Sand People of Scar.
You will be easy prey.
Nine.
- Listen, I have tried to be
polite with you,
but this is going
a little too far.
I get that you're
overprotective...
- Eight.
- Are you counting?
- For the next 24 hours,
I will be hunting you
throughout this city.
We will not use our powers.
But when it's over,
my daughter will be free
of you.
Seven.
- Do you do this with
all her boyfriends?
- I hunted her last one, yes.
- Where is he now?
- I don't know.
- He got away.
- I don't know
where you go when you die.
Five.
- You just skipped six.
- I know.
Four.
And don't try to breach.
[chuckles]
I'll know it if you do.
You can't hide from me.
So if I were you,
I would start running, Cisky.
[dramatic music]
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Three, two, one.
- Damn.
He's hunting him.
- I finally calmed him down.
Amazing what 50 milligrams of
Lorazepam can do
when you get it
in aerosol form.
- Is there anything you can do
to put him back together?
- Please, my stomach can't take
much more.
- I think I could stabilize
his cells if I had a sample
of his DNA from prior to when
he was exposed
to the dark matter on the bus.
- Why?
So he can go out
and start hurting people,
like our other friends here?
I think we should lock him up
in the Pipeline.
- He hasn't done anything.
- Yet.
Trust me.
I know this guy.
He's a bad guy.
- Barry, I took an oath
to help people.
I'm a doctor.
I can't just leave him
in there like spaghetti.
- Villains?
- Yeah.
Every person that was on that
bus is now 1,000 times
more dangerous than
they were before.
Dibny included.
- What if he's changed?
- People don't change.
- I did.
When I became Killer Frost,
you still believed in me.
- You're a good person.
He's...
not.
- Barry, how about you and I
go back to Dibny's office?
Find a DNA sample for Caitlin?
Dad, you go back to CCPD,
see what you can
dig up on Dibny?
- Yes, boss.
[rumbling]
- Looks like someone tossed
this place.
- Yeah. Probably
the same guys
that hung Dibny off the roof.
- Why do you think?
- I dunno. Guy like
that probably has
a long list of people that
wanna toss him off rooftops.
- Why do you want to?
- [chuckles]
- No, seriously.
What happened between
the two of you?
- It was one of my first cases
when I was a junior CSI.
Dibny was the lead detective.
- What case?
- A woman named Judy Gimlin was
stabbed to death.
Her husband, Reagan,
was the prime suspect.
But there was no evidence...
nothing to tie him
to the crime scene.
And then, Dibny miraculously
found a knife
with the husband's
fingerprints.
Case closed.
Dibny was a hero.
I don't know, maybe because
my mom was stabbed,
I wanted to be sure.
So I analyzed the knife.
The serrations on the blade
did not match
the wound on the vic.
- So Dibny planted the knife.
- Yep.
And then he lied about it.
Under oath.
- And you busted him?
- I mean, he didn't just
bend the rules, Iris.
He committed perjury...
evidence tampering.
He was thrown off the force.
Point is, he was crooked then.
He's crooked now.
- Hey, how much DNA
do you think Caitlin needs?
- Not much.
- Okay.
Oh, think this will work?
- [chuckles]
[beeping]
- Barry!
[whooshing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I guess someone hates him
more than you do.
- And that's what
it feels like
to vibrate
through solid matter.
- I'm just glad
you two weren't hurt.
- No thanks to
your new buddy in there.
- He's not my buddy.
He's my patient.
- Caitlin, I just
don't understand
why you're defending him.
- Because I know what it's like
to suddenly find yourself
with extraordinary powers
and be totally freaked
out by it.
And so do you, for that matter.
You and I both woke up in this
lab once knowing that our lives
would never be the same.
So how about you give the guy
a little sympathy?
- Hey.
- Guys.
- I pulled the LUDS
on Dibny's phone.
There were 15 phone calls
between him
and the Mayor's office.
- What is Mayor Bellows doing
talking to Ralph Dibny?
- [scoffs]
[tense music]
- Oh, look. It's my good
buddy Barry Allen.
- Someone just blew up
your office.
- Sweet.
Insurance claim.
- My fiancee and I almost died.
- You landed West's daughter?
Wow.
Everything's coming up Allen.
The job.
The girl.
- Who's trying to kill you,
Dibny?
- Do you know how many people
I have pissed off
in the last five years?
Angry husbands.
Angry wives.
Not exactly dealing
with high society
taking photos of
cheating spouses.
- Then why are you
talking to the Mayor?
- Who says I am?
- Your phone records.
- Did...did you get
a warrant for that?
'Cause I know you're all
by-the-book.
- What's your business with
Mayor Bellows?
- Nothing.
Just calling to tell him
what a swell job
I think he's doing.
- 15 times?
- 12 of those were
butt dials.
- All right, look,
whatever.
Maybe we'll go talk
to the Mayor ourselves.
You know,
he's a huge fan of Joe's.
- Yeah, you go do that.
- All right.
- I'm gonna stay here.
Stretch my legs.
- Ramon, do you think it's wise
to be sneaking around
a technologically weaponized
facility?
- It's a lot safer than what
I'm up against out there, so...
- Coffee didn't go well,
I take it?
- Well, Gypsy's dad wants to
hunt me for 24 hours
to see if I'm worthy
of his daughter...
no powers...so, don't know what
the hell I'm supposed to do
about that.
- Fight back.
- I swear, it's like
you're trying to listen,
but you just nod while you're
thinking of something else.
You're doing it right now.
- Fight back.
Ramon, what did you say?
You said no powers?
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, in addition
to being Vibe,
you have another superpower...
you're smart in here.
All right?
Outwardly, you're weak.
Too much.
But use your outwardly
weak appearance
to your advantage.
He's gonna anticipate
a pathetic target.
Well, you're pathetic.
You're pathetic.
You're weak.
- Not helping,
just hurting.
- All I'm saying is,
set a trap, okay?
Beat him at his own game.
Set a trap.
- Set a trap.
- That's right, a trap.
- A trap, I can do.
'Cause he may be the Predator,
but I'm the Schwarzenegger.
- Where is he?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
He was here.
- Uh, he went that way.
[door opens]
- I farted.
I'm not sure everything's still
where it's supposed
to be down there.
- Drink this.
- What is it?
I don't just drink stuff.
My body is a temple.
- Clearly.
Drink it.
- I wanna know what it is.
- It's 17% alcohol.
- You should have lead
with that, sister.
[gulps]
Ugh!
What was that?
- It's a serum of sulfur,
zinc oxide, and steric acid
to cross-link
your polymerized cells.
- In English.
- It's gonna fix you.
- [groans]
[gasps]
Oh.
You did it.
I'm cured.
- Well, not cured.
All I did was introduce
a stabilizing enzyme to reset
your body to default shape
through vulcanization.
It's like muscle memory.
- Muscle memory, huh?
Huh.
How far back memory,
you think?
- I don't know.
Uh, think about the shape
you want to be
and just be it.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- I'm back.
I look like a Hemsworth.
[knocking]
- Joseph.
- Thank you for meeting us.
- Quick stop on my way
to a hospital ribbon cutting.
No problem.
What's with you?
You're glowing.
- N-no, I'm not.
- You are.
- Well, how can I help you,
gentlemen?
I've got a lot on my schedule
today.
- Ah, we won't take up much of
your time, Mr. Mayor.
Uh, do you know a man named
Ralph Dibny?
- Doesn't ring a bell.
Who is he?
- Well, he's a former cop
turned private investigator.
- I don't think so.
- Really?
He called your office over
a dozen times.
- Oh, I'm gonna have to check
with my secretary.
[tense music]
- Anthony,
you used to be a cop.
We're not talking to the mayor,
here.
It's three cops talking.
Whatever cops say
to each other,
they don't say
to anybody else.
What's going on
with you and Dibny?
- I, uh...
Made a mistake.
- A mistake?
You mean like the kind of
mistake you make with a woman
who's not your wife?
♪ ♪
- It was only that one time,
Joe.
I regretted it
the moment I did it,
and I broke it off right away.
And then Dibny shows up,
and he's got pictures of us.
And he threatens to show them
to my wife unless I pay him.
- How much?
- Not enough.
All those phone calls,
it was him negotiating
for a bigger price.
I love my family, Joe.
Just let me pay him,
and I'll be done with it.
- No, Mr. Mayor, you're not
gonna have to do that.
We're gonna take care of it.
- Joe, Barry.
Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
So much for Dibny changing.
- Dibny's alive and talking.
Find him.
I want those pictures
and his head.
- And the cops?
- What do I care about cops?
Waste 'em.
♪ ♪
- Your vitals are fantastic.
- Yeah.
- You're blackmailing
the Mayor?
- Classic Barry Allen.
Enters room and accuses wildly.
- We know about the photos,
Ralph.
- Bellows told us everything.
- Hey, I'm not the one
who told him
to step out on his wife.
- That's your defense?
It's his fault that
you're extorting him?
- Isn't that a little easy
for you to say?
Your fancy lab,
your good job,
and your hot girlfriend?
People like me are just
trying to get
from one bill to the next.
And I wouldn't have to be
living like that
if you hadn't cost me my job.
- You got yourself fired.
You tampered with evidence.
You framed that guy.
- Because he was guilty.
And he was gonna get away with
killing his wife,
and then you let him go.
I was a good cop.
I was a good detective.
I lost everything.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
Mayor's got plenty of money.
He can afford
to spare a little.
Consider it the pension
you cost me.
- Good people don't destroy
lives and call it noble.
You were dirty then.
You're dirty now.
Live with that.
You're not going anywhere.
- Get off me.
♪ ♪
[garbled]
Are you kidding me?
[grunts]
♪ ♪
Thanks for ruining my life
twice, Allen.
♪ ♪
Breacher: Cisky.
Show yourself.
No one can avoid me forever.
- I'm not going to.
[weapon clicks]
Are you kidding me?
- Say good-bye,
my little enemy.
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
What the Sheol?
♪ ♪
- Guess who's got a hologram?
Ho, ho, ho.
Bet you're wondering
what this is.
This is an anti-vibrational
force field
with an oscillating power grid.
It's good enough for
the Reverse-Flash,
good enough for you.
So you might as well
wave your white flag,
'cause you aren't getting out
of this thing
until the clock strikes
Cisco's victory.
Oh, victory.
Feels good.
- I pulled this from the body
of an Earth-48 hunter-killer.
You can't trap a trapper.
[grunts]
[static]
♪ ♪
[doorbell rings]
- [sighs]
[mellow pop music playing]
[sighs]
I just needed to cool off.
- I figured.
Dibny seemed to have gotten
under your skin.
Why is it so important to you
that he be the bad guy?
- When I first started at CCPD,
all I cared about
was the rules.
But, you know,
these last few years,
we've locked up meta-humans
without a trial.
Played with time and space,
messed with other worlds.
- Yeah, but what does that have
to do with Dibny?
- Just that everything
that we've done we did
because we were trying
to help people.
Keep them safe.
- Hm.
- Is that all Dibny was
trying to do back then?
- Good people don't destroy
lives and call it noble.
- Did I make a mistake
back then?
Did I cost a good man his life?
- I don't know, Bare.
He did break the law...
cross the line.
But you didn't make him
do that.
And you didn't make him
blackmail the Mayor.
But, maybe Caitlin was right.
Everyone who's gone through
what you and her
and now Dibny's gone through...
maybe he deserves
a second chance.
[doorbell rings]
- I got it.
- Allen.
Detective West.
- Aren't you two
on the Mayor's detail?
- Sorry to bother you at home,
but dispatch just radioed.
Captain Singh needs you down
at station ASAP.
- All right,
let me get my jacket.
- Bare!
[gun shots]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
That never gets old.
- Those two work
or the Mayor.
They just tried to kill us.
- Dibny's next.
- Cisky, Cisky, Cisky.
♪ ♪
Cisky.
Come out.
Come out and meet your end.
- [yawns]
- Plastoid.
You creatures destroyed
my planet.
Now I will kill
every last one of you.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
Barry:Guys, anyone there?
- Barry, I'm here.
It's me.
What's up?
- I need you to activate
the tracker I put on Dibny.
- You put a tracker on Ralph?
♪ ♪
Plastoid.
- Cisco, do you know
where he is?
- He's at City Hall.
♪ ♪
- You lost weight.
- Lap band surgery.
Heh.
♪ ♪
- Since killing you
didn't work out,
what we agreed upon.
200K.
Let me have the photographs.
- Here's the pictures.
Keep the money.
- What?
- I take it back.
- Take it back?
- I take my blackmail back.
- Is this some kind of a trick?
- I'm not dirty.
And I don't want any part
of this anymore.
And don't you forget,
I can tie you to that bomb
you had your goons
plant in my office,
so if you don't walk away,
I will go to the cops.
- That's still blackmail.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
You're telling me if I don't
give you this money,
you won't go to the cops.
- Okay, fine.
I am blackmailing you
into not being blackmailed.
- So, we're good, then.
- Yeah, we're good.
[gunshot]
[rubber stretching]
Bullet booger.
Super gross.
[whooshing]
- Sorry, Mr. Mayor.
It's over.
[electric buzzing]
♪ ♪
- Die, Plastoid, die!
- You will not infest
this world
as you did mine, Plastoid.
- Plastoid, what?
Is he talking to me?
- Breacher, stop.
[electric shocks]
[grunting]
- Okay.
- He dies, speedster.
- Get in there, Joe.
You're coming with me.
- Flash!
- [grunts]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Look,
you don't have to do this.
- Yes, I do.
[electric shocks]
[heroic music]
- Leave him alone.
This guy didn't invade
your planet.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He's like this
'cause of me and my team.
So if you've got a problem
with him and his powers,
then you deal with me.
♪ ♪
- Hey, are we good here?
Because I definitely
gotta change my drawers.
[helicopter flying]
- The Mayor took Joe.
I can't run fast
enough right now.
I'll never have enough speed
to jump off a building.
Can you breach me up there?
- No way.
The event horizon would rip
that helicopter apart.
- But we've gotta save Joe.
- What do we do?
♪ ♪
- You can get me up there.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- How?
- You can stretch.
Grab it.
- Are you...are you crazy?
I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
All right?
I know that you have it
inside you
to help someone
other than yourself.
I know you, Ralph.
- How could you
possibly know me?
♪ ♪
Dude, are you kidding me?
You're the Flash?
Everyone else gets struck
by lightning and dies,
and you get super powers?
- Ralph, yeah, that's right.
- Your assistant's a speedster?
- I liked the Flash.
Now I have to hate the Flash.
- Ralph, focus.
I need you to do this.
Joe needs you to do this.
Please.
Show me I was wrong about you.
You said you were a good cop.
Be one right now.
♪ ♪
- Aah!
[rubber stretching]
♪ ♪
- What the hell?
- I got it!
[laughs]
Ooh.
Ooh-oh...
Help!
- Hold on, Ralph.
♪ ♪
- Ooh.
- Cecile's pregnant.
[Outasight's "I Got You"]
- ♪ Anything you need
anything you need ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You already know
you already know ♪
♪ That I got you ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪ Never let them tell you
that you can't do your thing ♪
♪ I got you ♪
♪ ♪
- Well, we've reached
the end of our road.
We had some stumbles
along the way,
but we pulled it together.
We made it home.
- I hate you.
- Wow.
Really thought
that one would work.
- But I respect you.
You're a steadfast warrior
who would fight the fiercest of
enemies to protect your friend
and the only person I love.
- With my dying breath, sir.
- I know that,
but I still hate you.
- I have never seen him gush
like that.
- That's gushing?
I'm terrified to experience
him loving me.
[whooshing]
- Well, that's my job.
- Oh, that's right.
It is.
- I feel a code-17 breach
in progress.
We have to leave now, Cynthia.
- Cyn-Cynthia?
Cynthia.
What's your dad's name?
- Josh.
- [laughs]
Cynthia and Josh.
That's great.
Not so scary now, Cynthia.
- Keep calling me that.
See what happens.
- All right.
See you around...Gypsy.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- [sighs]
- I fixed up your office.
- Sweet fancy Moses.
Thanks for screwing up
my insurance claim.
No payout,
no mayor money.
I gotta pick up a case soon.
- What if I had a job for you?
- I wanna laugh really hard
right now,
but I'm afraid my face
will fall off again.
- I can't change
what has happened
between us in the past,
but I can offer you a chance
to change what happens
in our future.
- How?
- Let my team and I study
your powers,
figure out how to improve them,
see what your limitations are.
And let me train you.
- Train me?
For what?
- To do what I do.
To be a detective again, Ralph.
A real one. Like, it's
not gonna be easy.
I'm gonna push you
to your limit.
I think it's safe to say some
days you're gonna hate me.
- Allen, it's safe to say that
I always hate you.
- [laughs]
- Do I get a cool
super hero name?
- What do you think about...
Plastic Man?
- I think that's the dumbest
name I've ever heard of.
- Yeah, Cisco comes up
with the names.
- It's better that way.
- What do you say?
- There's just one thing
I gotta ask you.
What made you look into Mayor
Bellows in the first place?
- Oh, it was a client.
Asked me to follow the Mayor.
Never met him, though.
He did everything
over the phone.
- Who was it?
- Only gave me his last name.
DeVoe.
- You and I have been enemies
for years.
Oh, you've had others,
of course.
There's Thawne. Zoom.
DeVoe.
- This is where we came up with
the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
♪ ♪
- What's wrong?
The name DeVoe
mean something to you?
♪ ♪
I smell a mystery.