BARRY: Previously on The Flash...
Next time you decide to release
my friend's inner ice demon,
you do it sometime in July.
I was trying to save her life, Cisco.
When I became Killer Frost,
Savitar appeared to me
and showed me the way.
If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
You trapped Savitar in the Speed Force.
Just tell me how you did it.
- I had help.
- Help from who?
A physicist. Her name is Tracy Brand.
I know who you are.
Cecile,
most people quit
their New Year's resolutions by now.
Uh-uh.
Central City Marathon is in two months,
and I've got to shave...
Oh! I've still got half a minute
I've got to take off my time. You?
A lot more than 30 seconds.
Look, I am going to wait for you
at the end of the marathon.
No, you're not pulling out of this thing.
I am not as easy with running
as some other members of my family.
I'm gonna let it slide. I'm gonna let it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Are you getting mad?
I would never get mad.
I love you too much to be mad.
Uh... Yeah. That's... I...
I didn't really mean to...
No, absolutely, it's...
I was looking at you, and it came out,
and I don't want you
- to feel uncomfortable.
- I'm sorry. Sorry. Hold on.
- Sorry, I've got to take this.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah, go for it.
Yeah? Okay, I'm on my way.
Yeah.
Sorry. I've got to head out.
Her name is Tracy Brand.
She's one of the world's
top theoretical physicists.
You know, or at least, she will be.
No kidding.
Girl Scout earns her merit badges.
2021 Nobel Prize,
Copley Medal, presidential commendation...
She's a genius. What's that to us?
She's the key to stopping Savitar.
Future me said that four years from now,
Dr. Brand invents the technology
that traps Savitar in the Speed Force.
Four years too late?
Yeah, but if she invents the tech then,
then maybe she's working
on the prototype now.
That's exactly right,
so we should find her.
Agreed.
Sorry, why are we not looking
for Caitlin, again?
Easy, Romeo and Julian.
None of us have forgotten about Caitlin.
Right, but Future Flash already confirmed
that she teams up with Savitar.
We should be doing everything in our power
to stop that from happening.
- We know.
Right, so what is Wally doing swanning off
to Earth-3 to be with his girlfriend?
He could be here right now
looking for her!
- It's like no one's doing a thing!
- CISCO: No one's doing a thing?
Barry and Wally searched the city
half a dozen times.
No one's doing a thing?
Every chance I get,
I try to vibe where she is.
We're using facial recognition technology.
We're using the meta-human app,
the satellite.
- We're doing everything we can.
- I just wanna her back, okay?
Yeah, well,
if you wanted her here so badly,
maybe you shouldn't have ripped off
that necklace
- and turned her into a killer.
- BARRY: Okay.
- Okay. All right.
- CISCO: Just saying.
We got a hit.
Tracy Brand, currently enrolled
in C.C.U.'s Theoretical Physics program.
So our hopes
of defeating an evil speed god
- hinge on a grad student?
- Yep.
Could be worse.
B.A., Cisco, let's do this.
Let's go.
CISCO: Ah... The soul-sucking
fluorescence of academia.
Yeah, this is exciting, though.
It's like meeting Norbert
before he was Einstein.
- Albert.
- Norbert, Albert...
Do you guys smell that?
Toast?
Holy...
WOMAN: Hey!
What are you doing?
You mean,
save you from a painful, fiery death?
I had it under control.
- Come on!
- Okay, you know what?
Let's put this down
while you still have your eyebrows?
Did you set the fire on purpose?
Yes, I'm burning everything.
- What?
- Everything? What...
My work.
Well, I don't know why they call it "work"
because none of it works.
Well, this isn't exactly what I expected.
Me, neither.
- Dr. Brand?
- Oh, no, just Tracy.
I failed my dissertation.
Nothing like 10 years down the drain
and a pile of debt as a legacy.
Tracy, we were just hoping
that you'd have a moment to talk.
Oh, no, my bus leaves in five minutes.
Oh, please tell me
I didn't burn my bus ticket.
That's hot.
Your bus... Where are you going?
Big Belly Burger. I hear they're hiring.
What, you're...
What about all your research?
Oh. No, you mean my "unsubstantiated
and transactional inquiry"
"into the purely suppositional nature
of extra-dimensional energy"?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
A waste of time, or as Dr. Hersh puts it,
"a total misapplication
of the university's resources."
I might as well start practicing,
"Do you want fries with that?"
- Yes.
- No.
- B.A.
- BARRY: Stop.
Look, don't let the naysayers
get you down.
Your doubts, they're traitors.
Don't believe them.
Your mind is too fine to waste
turning tubers into finger chups.
- Finger chips?
- Finger chups, it's like a...
- He's from out of town. H.R.
- Stop.
Look, you can't give up.
Your work
on relativistic quantum mechanics
and its application to interspatial theory
to manipulate matter on a subatomic level,
it's ground-breaking.
I haven't shared that hypothesis
with anyone other than my therapist.
- Who are you?
- BARRY: We're therapists.
CISCO: No.
H.R.: No.
Admission here is so easy.
Get her out of here. Go!
So you've gone full-on Killer Frost, huh?
New threads and everything.
No more pencil skirts for me.
I don't wanna hurt you.
You won't, but I will hurt her.
Cisco! Hey! Hey! You good?
- Yeah. That's gonna leave a mark.
- Come. Come on.
- Caitlin's after Tracy.
- BARRY: Yeah.
That means she's working with Savitar.
That's definitely her, Detective,
icy eyes and all.
Yeah, that's her.
So I'm gonna spread this around
so everyone knows to look for her.
- Can you give me one second?
- Mmm-hmm.
All right.
So, if Caitlin wants Tracy dead,
I guess what you saw in the future
was true.
She's teamed up with Savitar.
I just didn't think
it was gonna happen this soon.
It certainly makes things
more complicated.
Makes what more complicated?
Uh... There was a meta-attack at C.C.U.,
and we just don't have much to go off of.
Really? It's a college campus.
Isn't there video footage?
Uh... No, it got erased.
Uh, well, I'm sure
you two will figure it out.
Joe, can I...
- Yeah.
So I'm feeling weird about this morning.
I...
Look, when I told you that I loved you,
I didn't mean to make you feel pressured.
No, no, no, I didn't feel pressured.
Okay, so we're good?
- We're great.
- Great.
Okay. Um...
In that case, good luck with your meta.
Um... So I totally heard that.
Do you wanna talk?
No. Hey, where are you going?
Oh, nearest bus stop.
No, you should stay here. Um...
With Detective West for a little bit.
Why? That sketch artist
was like freaking Michelangelo,
and you've got your woman.
Not yet, and until we do,
you could be in a lot of danger.
You really think Jack Frost's sister
wants to kill me? I'm no one.
In my experience,
if she's come after you once,
she's likely to do it again.
Look, this whole witness-overprotection
thing is totally unnecessary.
It was just a random attack.
Oh, the bus is coming. I've got to go.
We need to keep an eye on her.
Yeah, we do.
She got away.
I told you exactly where she'd be.
Barry and Cisco were there when I arrived.
As I told you they would be.
Maybe there's more Caitlin Snow inside you
than you led me to believe.
Are you saying I let her go on purpose?
Did you?
You call yourself Killer Frost,
but you haven't actually killed
anyone yet.
You and I can both be gods,
free of the pain and suffering of man.
All you have to do is kill the girl.
Okay. Look, I might not have any cash,
but I have one of those Jitters cards
that has 10 stamps on it,
which means you owe me a free drink. Okay?
Allow moi to help out
a damsel in distress.
I will pay for myself and the lady.
I will have a triple-shot,
no whip, mocha-Flash
and anything this young lady desires.
Yeah, I need to calm down, so a Zoom.
- A Zoom? Never heard of it.
- Mmm.
- Oh, it's on the secret menu.
- Secret menu?
Triple espresso with a shot of cayenne.
- Marry me.
- Hey, wait.
You were at the college this morning.
- No. This morning? Oh, yeah!
- Yeah.
No, I remember you now. Yes, I was. H.R.
Wait. What is with you people?
Did the C.C.P.D. send you to find me?
No, no, no. No, the reason I am here is,
my team and I are very interested
in your research.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're interested in
my theories on quantum mechanics?
Your ideas of wave-particle duality,
your quantization of energy,
and your time-symmetric formulation
of quantum theory, and...
how the boundary conditions
lead to principle causality
and the psychological arrow of time.
And the psychological arrow of time.
You really know your stuff.
Well, je suis smart.
Lay off the French,
and lay off the improv, too, please?
Just keep her talking.
Ah, thank you, Misha.
- Please, the Zoom.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Let's zoom.
Mate, was it just me, or did it sound
like H.R. was trying to flirt?
Hmm. Didn't notice.
Listen, the security footage today
from C.C.U.,
the stuff that we wiped
to protect Caitlin's identity? I saw it.
As in I saw the two of you squaring off.
Okay.
Well, from the angle that I saw,
it looked like
you had a pretty clear shot.
Okay.
You had a clear shot, Cisco,
and you didn't take it. Why?
Julian, I'm trying to focus on
what we're here to focus on.
I suggest you do the same.
Gents, how we doing?
Uh, all good.
I don't know about this one, Barr.
H.R. isn't exactly our best closer.
He'll be fine.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, just...
BARRY: Cecile?
She's just...
She caught me off-guard.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Just didn't think we were there yet.
Well, obviously, she is.
- Are you'?
- I care for her a lot.
It's just, with everything going on
with Iris and Savitar
and now Caitlin, just feel
like I lie to Cecile all the time.
Then maybe you should stop.
You're gonna have to tell her about Wally
and me and all this at some point, right?
So why not now?
Well, just so you know, you don't have
to keep her in the dark for us.
If you love her,
you should be honest with her.
At least, that's what you'd tell me to do.
Okay, so here's the thing
that I could never get them
to understand at the university.
See...
- Yeah?
- I've been studying speedsters.
Uh-huh.
And so you know how, when they run,
they generate
a trail of lightning behind them?
Right. Lightning.
I don't think all of that is generated
by them running.
- I think...
- No?
Some of it comes from somewhere.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Like some sort of a... Like a...
Speed Force?
Yeah. Wait. That is a great term for it.
- "Speed Force."
- Well, thanks.
Anyway, so I've been doing
some calculations.
I think there might be
a way to manipulate it.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Maybe even control it.
Maybe even turn it into a prison.
Maybe. Um, yeah.
Yeah. Just a random thought.
How do you think
one would accomplish that?
- See, I don't know.
- Okay.
Because the university
wouldn't fund my research.
Why are you so interested in this?
Because everybody thinks I'm a crackpot.
I certainly don't think you're a crackpot.
I...
What's wrong?
- We should go.
- Wait. What?
I think we should go. Yep.
Guys, guys, we need a little help here.
We've got a little trouble here!
Flash?
- Where is she?
- FROST: Right here.
Her again?
Caitlin. Caitlin, stop!
- Get her out of here!
- Wait, wait. What did I ever do to you?
So, what, you're Savitar's lackey now?
More fun to reign in hell, and all that.
All right.
I'm gonna get her to head back this way.
When she does, you've got
to knock her out, okay? Okay?
Yeah.
Now, Cisco!
Savitar says I'm not allowed to kill you,
but I can't have you following me around.
It was the left leg last time, right?
What?
Scar tissue's a lot more sensitive
than regular tissue.
This isn't you.
It is now.
Cait. Cait!
This is where
the Flashy Flash goes to, huh?
It's not exactly what I imagined,
but it's cool.
So I always wondered how you kept
the friction from building up
a lethal dose of static charge.
Yeah, that's vulcanized Teflon.
It neutralizes any electron imbalance.
Okay, and the White Witch?
I'm guessing you know why she's after me?
Well, she's teamed up
with an evil speedster from the future,
and, apparently,
you develop the technology
to trap him for an eternity, so...
You can't be serious.
Totally serious.
An evil speedster?
He calls himself Savitar.
- "Savitar," and he's from the future?
- IRIS WEST: Yep.
- And I build a trap for him? Me?
- You.
BARRY:
He wants to kill you before you build it.
That's why he's sending
Killer Frost after you.
"Killer Frost"? Her name is Killer Frost?
- H.R.: Yeah.
- We know it's a lot to take in.
Well, to be fair, you're basically
telling me I'm Sarah Connor in Terminator.
- More like...
- Well, Miles Dyson.
Yeah. But good effort, though.
So, wait.
You're telling me my ideas about the...
The Speed Force.
Speed Force, being able to control it,
manipulate it, all of that...
I'm right?
It appears so.
That's me.
Nobel Prize? All of that?
In the future, yeah.
Look, Tracy.
We need your help.
We need you to build this trap now.
What happens if I don't build the trap?
Someone very important to us
is going to die.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I know that normally one of you fellows
goes out for the chat,
but I got this one.
Tracy? Oh, Tracy?
Working.
I can see.
I thought you'd like to be informed
that H.R.'s managed to talk Tracy around.
Oh, perfect.
That means we can get to work.
Yeah, there's one thing
I need to know first.
Outside Jitters earlier,
you could've stopped Caitlin with a vibe,
but just like C.C.U., you didn't.
- I'm not doing this again with...
- No, no, no.
You are.
I need to know, Cisco.
Tell me why you couldn't do it.
Get out of my way.
Caitlin could be home now.
Had you stopped her, she would be here.
But you didn't. You couldn't.
- Tell me why!
- Because I'm afraid!
- Afraid of what?
- Afraid of killing her!
I'm walking around with
two loaded guns here, ready to go off.
And what if she's hurting
Barry or Joe or you,
and I have to save you,
and I can't control my powers,
and I end up killing her?
She's my best friend,
and I'd rather it be me than her.
Hey.
How's Tracy holding up?
We'll see.
Um...
Have you told Cecile about us yet?
Cecile is the only thing normal
I have in my life right now,
and I like having something normal.
If I tell her about all of this,
that goes away.
But if you don't tell her...
- There may not be an "us."
- Mmm-hmm.
Joe, there's no such thing as normal.
Love is the only thing
that makes the fight worth it,
and it's the only thing
that's gonna get us through it.
Guys. Guys, there you are.
We've got a big problem. Tracy's gone.
I checked C.C.U., her apartment,
and Jitters. Tracy's not at any of them.
I'll bet you Savitar and Killer Frost
are hunting her down as we speak.
H.R., you were with Tracy last.
How did she seem?
Rattled, Ms. West. Rattled.
But I gave her a rousing
and reassuring pep talk,
so I think she's okay.
- Oh, that's why she left.
- That's not why... I'll...
Look, I'll have you know,
my book on motivational speeches,
All's Wells that Ends Wells...
Tracy is in danger.
- You're right. Iris, focus.
- What?
- We need to find her. Now.
- Yeah, we've got to find her.
Where else could she be?
Oh...
Why don't we start
with her future hologram, right?
That'll give us insight
into her psyche, no?
Of course, yeah.
- That's pretty good.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- She's cute.
- This is creepy, right?
- Yeah.
- I find her charming.
Do you think you could
screenshot a hologram?
Go back to that last one.
Yeah, there's another one like it.
- Whoa! Whoa! Look at that. Zoom in.
- Yeah.
Eppur...
Eppur si muove.
Tracy, you blessed paramour of science.
Gang, I know exactly where she is.
Eppur si muove.
"And yet it moves."
Galileo's famous statement,
uttered moments
after being forced to recant his theory
that the Earth revolves around the sun.
"And yet it moves." Mocha-Flash for me.
A Zoom for my lady.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
How did you know I was here?
Um, I might have done
a bit of holographic stalking.
I stalked you holographically.
You mean in the future I'm still obsessed
with a 500-year-old Italian polymath?
H.R.: Yes, it would appear so.
- I'm sorry I ran off. I just...
- No.
- Just needed to clear my head and think.
- Of course.
And this is where I do it best.
I can see that.
That statue is nothing if not inspiring.
Concrete beard, foreboding, smart.
- Totally inspiring.
- Yep.
You know, Galileo's peers
thought he was a crackpot, too.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
- And I used to find that comforting.
- Oh.
But then when your team
showed me the future,
showed me that my crazy ideas
aren't so crazy after all,
I just felt more intimidated than ever.
Well, I can see that.
It's like you're sitting
in the shadow of greatness.
- Your own greatness, right?
- Exactly!
It's like I've failed so many times,
that's all I know how to do.
I don't know how to be
that brilliant woman in the hologram.
But you wouldn't understand.
You are a born genius.
Yeah, about that,
I'm not technically a genius.
That was a cheap thing to do. I'm sorry
I misled you about me being a genius.
The point is, you are a genius.
You are. I know it. I can...
I can feel it.
It's right there. It's right there
just brimming just below the surface.
- It is?
- Yes, absolutely.
Yes, it is, Tracy.
And you can defeat Savitar.
All you need is
to just believe in yourself.
For what it's worth,
I already do.
Hmm.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I didn't know you were dropping by.
Yeah, well, if you'd read
any of my texts you'd know.
Yeah. Um...
- I'm sorry.
- I know.
It's why I'm here. Look, I...
You know, it doesn't take a detective
to see that something's not right.
Look, Cecile...
Is it because I said,
"I love you," this morning?
Because, Joe, it's... It's okay
if you're not ready to say it back.
No, no, it's not about that.
No? Well, then what's going on?
'Cause you've been acting weird all day.
I mean, not just with us this morning,
but at work with that meta case. I...
You've got to give me something, Joe.
All I can say is that
part of my life is very complicated,
and if you were to become part of that,
your life would be very complicated,
and it would change us.
And I mean change us forever.
It's not a bad thing, you know.
It's called growth.
And then I was thinking
about what you said this morning,
and it told me where you were.
It also showed me where I was, and...
And you add those complications
and I think we should stop
seeing each other.
Really?
That's what you think we should do?
I... I think it's the best thing
for both of us.
Here I was thinking that being together
was the best thing for both of us.
I guess I'll... I'll see you
around the station, Joe.
- Cecile!
- Joe.
- No, I guarantee you I'm faster.
- Joe, help.
Caitlin, we can talk about this.
FROST: I'll talk. You listen.
In an hour, you're gonna get a message
with an address.
Bring me Tracy Brand,
or I will kill your little sweetheart.
Joe.
Wait.
So you're saying that if we
don't turn Tracy over to Killer Frost...
She's gonna kill Cecile.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but Tracy is our key
to finding Savitar, right?
Yes, but what are we gonna do?
We're gonna just let Killer Frost
live up to her name and kill somebody?
Not if I have anything to say about it.
All I'm saying is, we need to do
whatever it takes to save her.
No one's gonna die, all right?
We're gonna get her back, I promise.
That's them.
They're at the old Dressler Factory.
Okay, we know where they are.
That's something.
So what do we do?
I have a plan.
- Cisco, can I have a quick word?
- Not now, Julian.
Listen, please, mate, just...
Just hear me out.
I know you're terrified of losing her.
So am I.
I know you're... You're worried about
not being able to control your powers,
but I know you can.
I don't think your abilities have ever
come from a place of negativity or hate.
They come from somewhere good.
They come from love.
If you can find it in you to stop her,
then I really think we can save her.
Cheers, mate.
H.R.: Hi.
Yeah, you know how I said, you know,
we were gonna keep you safe?
Um, yeah.
So now I need to ask you
to do something dangerous.
Cecile. Are you all right?
Joe, I'm okay. She didn't hurt me.
FROST: That's because
killing you does nothing for me.
Killing you, Tracy, that's everything.
Hand her over.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Why? Because Savitar commands it?
He's not a god.
He's just a man that's using you.
- Come on. You're one of...
- "One of us"?
- We're...
- "We're a family"?
- We protect each other till the end.
- "We protect each other till the end."
How are you doing that?
Savitar told me everything you'd say.
You two are more alike than you realize.
You see, that's how Savitar knows
every move you're going to make.
He's always one step ahead of you
because this is all history to him.
That's how I know
Cisco's in the rafters right now.
Oh, no.
No!
It's over, Caitlin.
Caitlin is dead.
Not to me.
Go, go, go.
Caitlin. You're alive.
I'm sorry. I had to stop you to save you.
My ascension is nearly at hand, Flash.
As I rise, you will fall.
How do we keep surviving these things?
'Cause we're in control of our fates.
And how did she know
I was up in the rafters?
Is she psychic now, too?
And that thing where you guys
were talking at the same time,
how do you think she was doing that?
I don't know. She said Savitar told her
what was gonna happen.
No way, man, this wasn't
just brushing up on days to come.
This was precise. Scary precise.
- Like Savitar was there.
- Mmm-hmm.
IRIS WEST: What I don't understand is
why Savitar wouldn't kill Tracy
when he showed up.
I mean, why would he choose
to rescue Caitlin?
He needs her for something.
We've got to figure out what that is.
Agreed. Well, thanks to Cisco,
we now have a sample of her blood
when she was fully mutated
as Killer Frost.
This, it could be the key
to reverse-engineering a cure,
- so it's good work, mate.
- You, too.
There you are.
I brought us some coffee treats.
Unfortunately, we're all out of cayenne.
Careful, that's hot.
Yeah. Hot cup. Sorry. How are you...
- Careful.
- How are you holding up? Oh, it's hot!
- Well, I'm processing.
- Mmm.
That was really...
I mean, the voice and the...
Killer Frost. Savitar.
You know some people
with really scary names.
Yeah, but is it too much?
All of us here would understand,
and personally, I just...
I just wanna make sure that, you know,
you don't get hurt.
As a matter of fact,
I was thinking that we should...
- I was thinking, too. About Savitar.
- Mmm-hmm.
The way the light reflects off his suit,
it's unlike any other metallic compound
I have ever seen.
Hmm. You and I were thinking
about different things.
- What do you think it is?
- In Fermi-liquid theory,
any sort of non-Fermi liquid
is called "strange metal."
It's a theoretical compound capable
of dispersing heat at high temperatures.
I think Savitar travels so fast
that he needs that suit to neutralize
the charge he builds up around him.
Ha! Interesting. So without the suit,
he's just a dude
with a bad case of static cling.
Yeah. So if we could build a device
capable of harnessing that power,
theoretically, we could use
his own velocity against him.
And trap him in the Speed Force.
Tracy, you are indeed a genius.
- I'm getting there.
- Well, yes, you are.
That means you're gonna stay and help us.
Is that what that means?
If I do, does that mean
the future's changing?
I think it means mine certainly has.
- Hey.
Thanks for seeing me. Come on in.
So how are you doing?
Joe, I'm fine. I just...
You know, I wish that you would've told me
what was going on with you.
Although I obviously have some idea now.
Yeah, it was my fault
that you got caught up in all of this.
I'm so sorry, Cecile.
Joe, me, too. Look, I...
When you told me
that you loved me this morning,
- I froze.
- Yeah.
I knew that it meant that
we moved up a level in our relationship,
and, for me, that level
comes with a lot of baggage.
Like Killer Frost and the Flash.
Yeah.
So you thought that pushing me away
was the thing to do?
I thought that I was protecting you.
Clearly, I was wrong
because not only did I lie to you,
I lied to myself.
And you know what?
I'm done with that.
And I'm done with this.
Thank you for not making a big deal
about me wearing this.
Cecile Horton...
I love you.
I love you with all my heart.
And I'm sorry
that I was dishonest with you,
and from now on,
there will be no secrets between us.
CECILE: Mmm.
- Okay?
- Mmm.
I should have told you a long time ago.
It's not bad.
- Wally!
- Hey, Dad.
Hey.
How was it?
It was... Yeah, it was great.
Jesse says hi.
So you talked to Cecile?
I did. Told her everything.
Told her I love her.
I told her that you were the Flash,
and that Wally was Kid Flash.
Don't worry, she promised me
that she wouldn't tell Joanie.
- What changed your mind?
- You. All of you.
Love's the only thing
we've got in this world.
- Without it, nothing really matters.
- Hmm.
And who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
How was Earth-3?
Yeah, um... Hanging outwith Jesse
was awesome. She's...
JOE: Love's the only thing
we've got in this world.
Without it, nothing really matters.
And who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
SAVITAR: You did this to me, Barry.
BARRY: I created you?
I created myself.
BARRY: You're even gonna create time
remnants of yourself,
but he's gonna kill them all.
FROST:
Savitar told me everything you'd say.
You two are more alike than you realize.
Savitar knows
every move you're going to make.
He's always one step ahead of you.
This is all history.
CISCO: This wasn't
just brushing up on days to come.
This was precise.
Like Savitar was there.
JOE: Who knows what we'd become
if we didn't have it?
FROST: One step ahead of you. All history.
I am the future, Flash.
FROST: One step ahead of you.
IRIS WEST: Barry? Barry?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'll be... I'll be right back, all right?
I'm here.
I'm here!
I know who you are.
It's about time.
Yes, it is.
Everything with you
is about time, isn't it?
The past, the present, the future.
You know all of it, right?
And you know everything about me!
About Joe, about Wally, and Iris!
You know our strengths.
You know our fears.
You know how much we love each other.
And you know
how to use that love against us.
All this time,
we thought that we couldn't stop you
because you were one step ahead,
but that's not it.
You don't just know
what's gonna happen to us.
You were there.
You lived it. You remember.
When you were me.
Like I told you from the beginning,
I am the Future Flash.