[light music]
♪ ♪
- Dad?
- Nora?
How...how are you...
- Don't worry, Dad.
I know we've
been through a lot,
but everything's gonna work out
like it's supposed to.
I promise.
- It's really you.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
We've missed you so much.
♪ ♪
[music heightens]
Iris, hey.
This is gonna sound crazy,
but...
I think we're pregnant.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
This must be why you're
feelin' so sick, you know?
And since meta-DNA signatures
can misrepresent HCG levels,
I gotta...
Hey, do you know
where my keys are?
I gotta drive these samples
to S.T.A.R. Labs
otherwise the chemical
integrity could be compromised.
Of course, right here.
I'll call you as soon as
I know the test results.
Cecile!
- Oh, hey!
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
- Oh, uh,
I have a file that Iris needed
for the Kord case.
Is she in?
- No...um, she is...
at work already.
- Isn't that her work computer
right there?
- Yes, it is.
But she's been more of a...
pen and paper kind of reporter
lately, you know?
Old school.
- You're feeling very nervous.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
You're feeling
nervous and excited...
ecstatic, even.
Barry, what's going on?
- I'm just...
running late for work.
It makes me kinda nervous...
and ecstatic,
'cause I love my job, so...
and I'll make sure
she gets this,
and I'll see you later!
- Hey, I thought we were
having lunch today.
- Us?
- Yeah.
- Th...oh, uh, y...
No, our monthly
Tuesday lunch date!
- Yeah.
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
No, I'm really
looking forward to that.
As always.
This is just a...
bag of...protein bars.
It speeds your metabolism.
I'm always hungry, so, um,
see you later.
Bye.
- Uh, okay, I...
- [exhales]
[Okenyo's "Women's World"]
- ♪ Clink your glasses,
melt the eyes like ice ♪
♪ Raise your glasses,
melt the thighs like ice ♪
♪ Clink your glasses,
hot flashes ♪
♪ You weren't ready
for it to feel this nice ♪
- Girl, you gettin' your
art mojo on.
I can dig it!
[laughs]
Ooh.
Okay, well, my bad.
I did not mean to disturb
the artist at work.
But a friend of yours
is out and about.
- Who, Mark?
- Yeah.
And I just figured it was
something you should see.
- Why?
What do you know?
Caity told you everything,
didn't she?
- Nothing, I just remembered
you two fought
at that bar
the night you got arrested?
- Yeah, and again
the night of the Force Storm.
- Well, says here that
he handed in state's evidence
and got parole, so,
maybe he's turned over
a new leaf.
[gasps]
Like Captain Cold!
- Uh-uh, I don't buy it.
Not for a second.
I'm just waiting till
he shows his true colors,
and then I'm gonna
kick his butt
right back to Iron Heights.
- Sounds kinda like you're
gonna stalk him or something.
[laughs]
You know, like,
watch his every step.
That would be crazy.
- Great idea, Chester.
- Wait, what? No.
I said that sounds
like it's crazy.
I said "crazy," right?
[Kramer]Well, you're
a damn good detective.
You dug up more on
Operation Griffin
in one week
than I did in years.
- And hit the same dead end.
So the last we saw your perp,
Warrant Officer Adam Creyke,
was on a security camera
stealing five
M18 Claymore Mines
from the barracks armory.
- Which he used
to eliminate my unit.
- One thing I don't get:
the explosive output
in close proximity
of five Claymores?
That would have been lethal.
Creyke would have known that.
How did you survive?
- Honestly, I have asked myself
that same question
over and over.
- Well, what exactly
do you remember
about the attack?
- Fragments.
Just...
[explosion and shouting
echoing]
Screams, mostly.
[screams and explosions
continue]
The heat of the explosion.
[fire crackles]
Adam's eyes.
[mysterious tone]
Somehow, I could tell
he knew he'd survive,
thanks to whatever his
damn meta ability is.
- Creyke was like
a brother to you.
What...
what drove him?
- Adam and I are both
Wet'suwet'en First Nations.
Adam loved open waters.
He wanted to join the navy
and followed me into the army.
Said he didn't trust
anyone else to look out for me.
- I had an uncle who used to
take me fishing every summer
on a schooner.
Sailors take
naming their vessels
as seriously as they name
their firstborn.
Did Adam have a call sign?
- Yeah, "Rasputin."
- "Rasputin."
Yo, a schooner named "Rasputin"
is registered in Midway City
six weeks after
Operation Griffin.
- He's been a few hours away
this whole time.
There's no way in hell
I'm letting him get away again.
- Kramer.
What are you gonna do
when you find him?
This has to be about justice.
If this is gonna be about
vengeance,
you can do this by yourself.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Lead the way.
[intriguing music]
♪ ♪
[exciting music]
- [buzzing in modem-speak]
- [replying in modem-speak]
- [speaking in modem-speak]
- [exhales]
[gasps]
- Did you drive here?
- What's up, party person?
- Yo! [laughs]
So, why is the Flash
driving a car?
Oh, wait.
Do you have a Flashmobile?
- No, i-it just isn't safe
to zoop these samples.
- Samples for what?
- Blood and urine
for my annual physical
with Caitlin,
who is my GP.
- Right...
isn't it kinda weird to have
a teammate as your doctor?
- [laughing] Yeah, yeah, no.
I mean, it was at first,
but it's cool now.
I should get to the med lab.
- Hey, good luck.
'Cause Caitlin's in there
running a medical consult
with...Ultraviolet.
- Oh.
- I guess she accidentally
double-booked
your appointments.
- Yeah.
- Catch you later.
- Not if I catch you first!
[laughs]
- I get it, 'cause you're fast.
Right, yeah.
- Yes, yeah.
[phone line trilling]
Iris, Caitlin's in the med lab
and we don't want anyone to
know yet until we're sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
you're right.
My lab at CCPD
has everything I need
to create a neutralizing
meta-gene variant
that'll track your HCG levels.
All right, thanks.
Love you too, bye.
- What did they do to me?
- Black Hole introduced a
deliberate irregularity
into your vascular system,
one that creates
a 40% decrease
in your body's ability
to maintain oxygen intake.
- He made it so the mask
keeps her alive
to ensure her loyalty.
- Actually, the mask
is hiding the real damage:
implantation circuitry
grafted to your vocal cords.
- Okay, how do we help
my cousin?
- So the software in the chip
requires
regular software updates
just like your smartphone.
But no Black Hole means
no more software updates.
So pretty soon,
it'll stop working
and I won't
be able to repair it.
- [speaking Spanish]
- No. [speaking Spanish]
Caitlin thinks she has a way
to fix this.
Permanently.
- Right.
It's risky, but I think
I can repair the damage.
- It doesn't matter.
I won't do it.
- I'll leave you two alone.
- Esperanza...
why won't you
let Caitlin operate?
- But you trust me.
And I know this team.
I fought with them.
Suffered losses alongside them.
They're good people.
So if Caitlin thinks she can
help you, let her.
- I don't need help.
Unlike you, I don't fear dying.
- Maybe so.
Look, I get it.
Surgery is how this
nightmare started for you.
But Caitlin isn't Black Hole.
- It's my life, not yours.
- Then why am I the only one
who gives a damn about it?
Don't you get it?
This isn't about
saving Ultraviolet.
It's about saving
Esperanza Garcia.
Mi familia.
[slam]
- Oh!
[grunts]
[intense electronic music]
[breathing heavily]
You boys really know how to
throw a "welcome home" party.
- Yeah, well,
the only rats welcome here
are the ones in the kitchen.
- [laughs]
Yeah, that's funny
coming from you, punk.
[Frost] Leave!
Now.
- [exhales sharply]
[groans]
Snowflake.
As always.
Perfect timing.
- So what happened?
Came to ask your old boss
for your job back?
Didn't go so well?
- [pained laugh]
That...
[inhales sharply]
Plus something about
"snitches get stitches."
- Oh,
no one's buying this whole
"turned over a new leaf" crap.
- Look...
[grunts]
You ready for
that dinner date yet?
I mean...
I should probably
be a gentleman
and change first.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. No.
Come on, I'm taking you
to Danville General.
- No.
No, no, no.
They're probably
still pretty upset
about the CAT scan machine
that I sabotaged
a few years back.
- Okay, fine.
Leawood Med, then.
- Kinda blew up
their bio-chem lab.
- Okay, um...
fine, there is a shady vet
down on Fairview.
He won't ask...
- [laughs] Hey.
Dr. Haley.
Yeah, I love that guy.
He's wanted to kill me
ever since Tijuana, though.
That's actually a really funny
story for some other time.
- I can't believe
I'm about to say this.
I will take you
to S.T.A.R. Labs
and have Caity fix you.
But if you step out of line...
I will let you bleed out.
- I wouldn't expect
anything less.
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Is that urine?
- Hey! Um...
Is it lunch already, or...
- Yes, and I'm starving.
Please tell me you're not still
in the middle of something.
- No. Um...
Yeah, I'm just waiting
to see if this
chemical compound reacts
and turns blue.
- Oh, cool.
What does blue mean?
[mysterious tone]
[squeals excitedly]
Barry.
- Cecile.
- Are you and Iris...
- No.
N-n-n...oh, no, no, no.
We...we're not...
[low rumble outside]
[boom]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[car alarm blaring outside]
Are you all right?
[Barry] It was Godspeed?
He must have broken out
of Iron Heights.
Either that or there's another
clone in Central City.
- Great.
Why would they attack downtown?
I thought they wanted
to steal your speed?
- The last one did.
When Rathaway and I
took him down,
he said whoever sent him
wants infinite velocity.
- Well, now it looks like
he wants infinite chaos.
[monitor beeps]
Oh, man.
I just picked up two different
reports in progress.
One has Godspeed causing
a multi-car collision
near City Hall.
- And the other one
has him at a gas station,
like, three miles away.
- Man, he's fast.
Even you can't
be in two places at once.
- Neither can he.
There's two of them.
Frost, if I run you downtown...
- I'm already ahead of you.
- All right,
I'm gonna take the gas station.
- Wait.
Where'd they go?
Satellites aren't
picking up anything,
They're just...gone.
- Okay, maybe Iris can rally
Team Citizen.
They can canvas the sites,
find out what
they were looking for?
- No.
Uh, what I mean is...
there's two of them, so,
that means they have
the advantage now.
So anybody that's not
a speedster
should stay put
where it's safe.
And Iris is already
home sick anyway,
so she's already
in the safest place possible.
- Okay,
what are we supposed to do?
- I've been thinking
about that.
A cryptographic algorithm
might help us decode
their modem-speak
and figure out why
they're back.
- All right, do it, yeah.
I'm gonna search the city.
[Mark]So here's a question.
Confidentially speaking,
I mean,
what is your sister into?
Is it horror movies, Westerns,
single malt, blended?
"Cardigan" or
"Blinding Lights"?
Go.
- Confidentially speaking?
- Uh-huh.
- You can't handle her.
- [grunts]
- Rest up.
- Hey, what's with
our sonic booms?
- Don't mind me.
Let's play...
[grunts]
a guessing game.
Shall we?
Let's see.
A sonic boom at ground level.
And with this being
Central City, AKA meta heaven,
I am guessing a speedster's
behind it.
And since there have been
one, two...that's math.
Five Godspeeds running around
Central City
in the last
year and a half alone,
I am also guessing another one
just showed up to the party.
- I hate you.
There's two more.
- Yup, you heroic types
have quite the dilemma.
- How are we gonna stop
both of them at the same time?
- [yawns]
That's a good question.
- "We" aren't doing anything.
You need to focus
on Ultraviolet's surgery.
- Who's Ultraviolet? Is sh...
- Will you just be quiet?
- Shut up.
Stay here.
I've got a job to do.
- Do you need any help?
I could stay, you know.
C'mon, put me in coach?
- You just got patched up.
You're benched.
- Right.
You, Caitlin,
and whoever else is part of
your S.T.A.R. Labs posse
think you get to just sit
up here in your ivory tower
judging who's good
and who's bad.
Well, guess what?
Life. Isn't. Binary.
It's everything in between.
Now, you don't trust me?
That's fine.
But you cannot decide
who someone's gonna be today
based on
what they did yesterday.
And you should know that better
than anybody else...
Killer Frost.
I'm sorry
I-I just wanna help you.
- No.
[door pad beeps]
- Okay.
Is this really necessary?
Great.
[sighs]
[monitors beeping]
- She's gonna be okay, right?
- Of course. Hey.
She's in good hands.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[alarm sounding]
[whooshes]
- They're back, aren't they?
- One of the Godspeed clones is
attacking
the Central City
power plant,
and if he takes it out like he
did with the gas station,
the blast radius will be
over 40 square miles.
- All right.
- You should take Allegra
and Frost with you.
- No,
if the other Godspeed attacks,
they're our
last line of defense.
[whooshes]
[alarm blaring]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
Look, I know you're not
the real Godspeed,
but I won't let you harm
this city anymore.
So why don't you just
tell me who sent you.
- [roars in modem-speak]
- Barry, my algorithm is
translating what Godspeed said.
- What is it?
-[modem-speak]
- "I have him."
Oh, frak, it's a trap!
[Chester]Get out of there!
[whooshes]
[intense music]
[Chester]Barry,
get out of there!
[whooshes]
- Chester, initiate
Babel Protocols!
- But Barry, if I drop the
force field,
you'll be locked out.
- Do it now!
♪ ♪
- [shouting in modem-speak]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[distant bangs]
- So what?
They couldn't phase through,
so now they're trying
to punch through?
- How long will
the force field hold?
- At the rate they're going,
an hour maybe?
- [exhales sharply]
- Wait, what are you gonna do?
- Get reinforcements.
Maybe.
- [breathing heavily]
- Barry, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm just...
just thinking I'm glad Iris
is home and not here.
At least she's safe there.
But I still put
the rest of you in danger.
- Hey, man.
Look, we're Team Flash.
Hey, we can handle this.
Plus, look at it this way:
With all the clones here,
the city's safe.
- Wait, Chester,
is there a way to evacuate
without raising
the force field?
- Even if there was,
Caitlin's mid-surgery with
Ultraviolet right now.
So if she stops...
Allegra's cousin might die.
[distant booms]
- All right,
we need a new plan.
Fast.
- Yeah, on it.
- I'm gonna check in with Iris.
[Barry] Hey, Iris.
You must still be resting,
that's good.
Um...
I'd come check on you
in person, only it's kinda
turned into a hell of a day
here at the ole office.
Anyway, um...
I know it's supposed to be
one of the happiest days
of our lives,
and I don't want you to worry.
Just rest.
But know that
whatever happens,
I'm gonna do everything I can
to keep you and the baby safe.
- [gasps]
A-ha!
[laughs]
I knew it!
You're having a baby!
- I'll check in with you later,
love you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, Chester,
but we haven't
told anybody yet.
So if you could please
help me keep it that way...
- Oh, no, no,
I got you, I got you.
Consider it locked and zipped.
- Okay.
- But whoa...
a little baby speedster!
[chuckles]
Maybe his first steps will be
a "fathwoom."
- It's a girl, not a boy.
- Wait, have...have you
already met this kid?
- Um...
- Is this like a
"Back to the Future"
type thing?
- Yeah, well, not exactly.
- Then how do you
know the gender?
'Cause relatively speaking,
you just knowing you have a kid
introduces a whole new set
of temporal variables,
all of which can have an effect
on present
and future timelines...
and change what was once
predetermined outcomes.
- I guess I don't know
for sure.
I mean, I have seen so many
different versions
of our future.
[rumbles]
- Just like the Godspeeds.
- If it looks like those clones
are gonna break through,
I want you to hide
in the Time Vault.
Cisco turned it into
a panic room before he left,
just in case I ever went
Dark Flash again.
Nothing can get inside.
- Oh, snap, I completely
forgot why I came here!
I have a plan.
So, remember that trap
from earlier?
- Yeah?
- That was the Godspeed clones
creating a set of variables
designed to predict
a fixed outcome...
that you would come to save
the power plant.
But they didn't predict
that you'd get away.
Which means that our best
defense against them would be...
- The unpredictable.
[rumbling]
- H-how much longer?
- Allegra, honey,
she's gonna be fine.
[rumbles]
- Okay, but...
how can you do that
with all hell
breaking loose out there?
- I don't have a choice.
[rumbles]
[door whooshes]
- Oh,
like you're really surprised.
[distant booms]
Well, that's getting worse.
Guess those two Godspeeds
need a place to crash, huh?
Can't be good.
- There's six of them now.
And if they get in here,
they could kill us all.
- You brought Derek and Nancy.
It's worse than I thought.
- First,
I need you to promise me that
if I give these to you,
you won't stab me in the back
the first chance you get.
- [sighs]
- I'm serious, Mark.
Today, you need to be
a good guy.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
- Because I'm not a good guy.
Don't you know that?
It's why you're
attracted to me.
- Please, can we not do that
right now?
- Fair enough.
[distant boom]
If you really want my help,
then you need to at least try
to speak to me
in a way that someone like me
can understand.
'Cause I'm no hero.
I'm never gonna be.
- Fair enough.
If those six speedsters
get in here, we're screwed.
So I need all the backup
I can get.
'Cause I don't wanna die,
and I'm pretty sure
you don't either.
[distant booming]
-  Alright, I'm in.
- It takes a lot
to gain my trust.
Break it,
you won't get it back.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
So what's the plan?
- So here's the plan.
You know how those
Godspeed clones use that
modem-speak to communicate?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well...
I can take audio of it,
and then I can transmit
that sound through CCPD's
emergency alert system.
Like this.
[modem-static blaring]
- Yeah, okay, now,
imagine one of these
staticky clone voices
coming through
every speaker, every radio,
and every cell phone
in Central City.
It would be like trying to
talk to a friend over
a loud dance floor.
Impossible, right? And...
- They wouldn't be able to
predict where to go first.
And in the confusion,
Frost, Mark, and I
would have a chance to
take them down one at a time.
- And I can
boost the signal loud enough
to scramble their brains
like eggs for good measure.
But first,
I gotta prep the CCPD server
by uploading the signal.
- How long will that take?
- Five minutes?
[rumbles]
- Make it four.
- Got it.
[keys clacking]
[monitors beeping]
- Is...is that supposed
to be happening?
- No.
Whatever Black Hole did,
removing the chip
has caused some sort of
systemic neural trauma.
I-I don't understand.
The anesthesia
should be working.
- W...she's hurting,
you have to do something.
- What I have to do is finish
this and close the wound.
- Okay, hey,
Caitlin...
can I try something?
[music builds]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
[monitors beeping]
[music softening]
♪ ♪
- Her reaction's stabilizing.
- What did you do?
- The only thing I could.
I can share my feelings
with others now.
So I gave Esperanza
the peace that I feel
knowing that you and Caitlin
and the rest of Team Flash
are out there
saving the world,
one day at a time.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[alarm beeping]
- Barry, we have a big problem.
Brute force and phasing
didn't work, so now...
- They figured out
something better.
Draining energy from the
forcefield itself,
like they would with my speed.
[power shutting down]
[intense music]
[monitor beeps]
[alarm blaring]
- We have a perimeter breach.
[whooshes]
- [triumphant modem-speak]
- He's calling the others.
- Chester, get out of here.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
Gideon.
Gideon, secure the room!
- Tachyon nullifiers
activated,
Chester P. Runk.
Time Vault secured.
[whooshes]
- Can I change my mind
about helping?
- Too late.
- [modem-speak]
- Chester P. Runk,
multiple Godspeeds
are assaulting S.T.A.R. Labs.
Do you need assistance
formulating a plan?
- I already had one, Gideon.
I was gonna pipe their
clone-speak into CCPD systems
and confuse the hell
out of them,
but, you know,
I'm stuck in a room.
- Would you like
to play the signal through
S.T.A.R. Labs'
intercom system instead?
- Yes, Gideon!
[laughs excitedly]
Yes, I would!
And hopefully, this will give
Barry and the others
the distraction that they need.
Okay, Gideon,
pipe audio file number 2808
into every room
in this facility.
And crank it...
I mean, "P. Funk" loud.
- Of course.
[modem-static blaring]
[modem-static continues]
[The Prodigy's "Diesel Power"]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yo, I used to check out
lyrics upon the format ♪
♪ Built with skill,
with technique ♪
♪ Computer ADAT ♪
♪ My lyrical form
is clouds on your brainstorm ♪
♪ I get hyped
think, thought, flow ♪
♪ Acrobat, sink the track,
pump the track ♪
♪ Dance missions,
clubs like spores react ♪
♪ By strobe visions ♪
♪ And hurrying more reflects ♪
♪ On the dance floor ♪
♪ Blowing up and having
mad people showing up ♪
♪ Packing crowds,
jam packed venues ♪
♪ Needles collapse
while atmosphere continues ♪
♪ Sprinkle that,
Win it like that ♪
♪ Move it like that,
hitting like that ♪
♪ The melody is phat ♪
♪ Yo, I'm on
the energy source ♪
♪ The cosmic boss
with Prodigy ♪
♪ Flipping astrology ♪
♪ My intellects devour ♪
♪ ♪
♪ With diesel power ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[modem-static blaring]
♪ Mono 7-0-6 ♪
♪ 8-0-7-3,
4-21 ♪
♪ Robot-sonic ♪
[driving hip-hop beats]
♪ ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
- [grunts]
- ♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[modem-speak]
♪ Blows your mind
drastically, fantastically ♪
[music stops abruptly]
- Oh, crap.
Oh.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[whooshes]
- Come on!
- [modem-speak]
- [breathing heavily]
- [panting]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[whoosh]
[all shouting in modem-speak]
- [yells, winces]
[pained grunting]
[sonic boom]
[pants]
[energy booms]
What the hell?
[Caitlin] Ultraviolet's
recovering,
but she's gonna be okay.
[Barry]  Good.
- Thanks, both of you.
Without that chip,
she's free.
Now I just have to help her
adjust back to...
you know, normal.
- Yeah, well,
with you in her corner,
that'll be easy-peasy.
- Thanks, Chuck.
'Cause with everything
that's going on,
we're gonna need
all the help we can get.
- Allegra's right.
How do we stop
a dozen Godspeeds?
- Oh, yeah, Barry, how much of
your speed did they steal?
- Barely any.
The other clones attacked
the first ones
before they could do any
real damage.
- But why fight each other?
- Yeah, and why would
any Godspeed
wanna protect the Flash?
- I don't think they
wanted to help me.
- I think they were trying
to kill the other six.
- Speedsters
fighting speedsters?
- Yeah, that ain't no
regular bad guy battle.
- Whatever it is, we're
stuck in the middle of it.
All this time,
we assumed
the Godspeeds were aligned.
But if they're not...
- It's a civil war.
[suspenseful music]
- You know, technically...
we didn't win.
But we are alive.
Something I didn't think
would be the case an hour ago.
That...
is cause for celebration.
Now I guess that you're
done with me,
you're not gonna let me
spend the night, huh?
- [coughs]
Uh...
No one's kicking you out.
Not yet.
- Wow.
One little
near-death experience.
Are we becoming friends?
- You tell me.
- Well, you gotta admit,
we do have explosive chemistry.
It's kinda like sucrose and
potassium chlorate with heat.
- [laughs]
What a nerd.
- [chuckles]
You know, when those two
Godspeeds had us pinned,
I really thought that was it.
But somehow,
I was okay with it.
Can I tell you why?
It was because
you were with me.
And somehow,
knowing that you would be
the last face that I would see
or the last voice
that I'd hear...
just made everything okay.
Everything.
- I didn't think
we were gonna make it, either.
But we did.
What are you
thinking about now, Mark?
- You, Snowflake.
[bang, clatter]
- What the hell was that?
Sucrose and potassium chlorate
my ass.
Mark!
- Barry?
- Mm.
- Stop worrying.
You're gonna be a great dad.
- [chuckles]
- We all know it.
- Thanks, Cecile.
I just...
wish Iris was feeling better
and could be here.
- I know, I know.
But you're gonna call her
as soon as we're done.
- Yeah.
- Okay, what is it?
- Oh, I was just thinking.
I'm...
I hope our child has
Iris's heart.
And her fearlessness.
- Oh, she will.
- It's...it's negative.
I don't...
I...
I mean, my dream.
Nora said everything
was gonna work out.
- It will, honey.
I know it will.
- How?
If...if this isn't
the future for me and Iris...
What is?
[crickets chirping]
- Creyke hasn't shown up
all day.
Maybe he moved on?
- No, he'll be here.
I can feel it.
It's strange,
being so close to almost
closing this case.
- Are you worried about
arresting an old friend?
- After we joined the service,
I went into intelligence.
Adam ended up
in special forces.
Turns out he had a knack
for killing.
- Oh.
- One the army used
to great effect.
Something changed in him, West.
And I didn't see it.
- And since you two grew up
so much alike...
Now you're worried that
whatever broke him
might break you too?
- All our lives,
we had each other's backs.
'Till he stabbed me in mine.
Left me for dead.
What could change a person
enough to do that?
- What the hell is that?
- Get out of the car!