My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
Zoom wants me dead.
The meta-humans that he's
sending from Earth-2,
they don't care how many
innocent people get in the way.
I have to go.
I need you to tell me that it's okay.
- Ah!
- Barry.
Is this the face of your hero, Central City?
- Ah!
Seriously got your ass kicked.
I can't feel my legs.
All right, I got you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
I can't do it right now, all right?
- Oh, yes you can, Barry.
- No, no, no.
We've been making so much progress.
Yep, six whole steps.
Someone get me a Bozo button.
Hey, give yourself some credit.
You just broke your back.
Yeah, a normal person
would've been paralyzed
the rest of his life.
How long until I'm fully healed?
The initial MRI I took a week ago
showed a complete dislocation
at the T12-L1 interspace
of the thoracolumbar junction.
But this is the MRI I took this morning.
It's remarkable, but you're
almost completely healed.
I'm still having trouble breathing.
That's totally normal with a spinal injury.
It should clear up soon.
We're going to get you
back in that suit, Barry.
Real quick, trust me.
What are we gonna do about Zoom?
No sign of him since Cisco
nailed him with that tranq dart.
And I haven't vibed since then.
- Maybe Zoom's not coming back.
- I highly doubt that.
Which is why I'm gonna go do
something about it.
What do you mean, go do something about it?
I need access to your breach
room and your speed cannon.
Why is that?
Because, Barry, it's time to go home.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
So, you show up on our Earth,
you screw everything up,
and now you want to go home?
Sounds very familiar.
Again, that wasn't me.
I need to go take care of Zoom
once and for all
before anyone else gets killed.
How do you plan on doing that?
I'll think of something.
Ramon, if you'll escort me
to the speed cannon.
No, no, you can't go through the breach.
Yeah, he can.
Jay taught us how to send people.
That's not what I mean.
Look, if you can figure out how to stop Zoom
on your Earth, you can
figure out how to do it here.
We need you to stay here until
we defeat Zoom, Dr. Wells.
What I need, Dr. Snow, is to return home.
And I'm going to that with
or without your assistance.
What are you doing?
If Harry wants to go...bye.
Look, like it or not, Cisco,
we need his help.
I'm not sure another plan
from Wells is what we need.
Yeah, I mean, the last bright idea he had
nearly got Barry killed.
I know, but Jay's gone,
and Dr. Wells knows Zoom better than anyone,
so until Barry is back on his feet again,
we need to keep Wells around
in case Zoom returns.
Caitlin, if he doesn't want to be here,
then we're better off without him.
Let him go.
I can't do that. Not yet.
[alarm blares]
Oh, snap, meta-human attack.
Nope, nope, my bad, that is
just an alert for me.
- For what?
- Oh, it's just a reminder.
I have a date in an hour, so...
Oh, with who?
With the lovely Kendra Saunders,
the barista at Jitters.
Oh, she makes a mean latte.
I think we're gonna go out
for dinner and a movie,
and then, I don't know,
maybe some breakfast.
- [laughs]
- Wait, breakfast?
Why breakfast? I don't...
Yeah...
'Cause, you know, you go home...
- Cisco.
- And...
- He's messing with you.
- Go.
Oh.
[phone vibrates]
[sighs] Patty.
- Patty, hey.
- Hey. I hear you're still sick.
Yeah, yeah, it's a... Nasty bug.
Well, I make a mean chicken
noodle soup from scratch.
I could bring some by later if you'd like.
No, that's sweet, I just...
I'd feel terrible
if you caught any of this.
Besides, I love the canned stuff.
Okay, well, try to stay off your feet.
Oh, yeah, believe me, I am.
You sure you're okay?
You sound like something's up.
Yeah, no, no, no, no. I'm fine.
I'm just not myself right now.
Okay, well, I hope to see you soon,
and, uh, feel better.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Bye.
You should stay away from the cheese curds.
They're addicting.
[chuckles]
I'm going to take a wild stab
and guess that you're here
without the consent
of the rest of your fabulous team.
It's been difficult, having you here.
For all of us.
You don't have to worry about that anymore
because I'm leaving.
We can help you save your daughter.
I know that's why you want to go home.
Look, I made a big mistake coming here.
and use that help to stop Zoom,
and my plan failed.
I don't have another plan,
except to go back home
and face Zoom myself.
So let's say you go back to your Earth,
and you fight Zoom.
He will kill you.
And then, how does that help your daughter?
Look, the best way to save Jesse
is for you to stay here,
and work with us as a team.
No.
Now, please leave me alone, while I discover
which one of these breaches
is gonna get me home.
You know, you're lucky
Cisco and Professor Stein
never figured out how to close
all the breaches,
'cause then you'd be stuck here.
Wait.
We close the breaches.
All of them, except one,
so Zoom only has one way
to get to this world.
- The breach at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Exactly.
And then we set a trap.
It's got fencing, fighting,
torture, revenge,
giants, monsters, chases, escapes,
true love, miracles, and,
it's ranked as one of the best
date movies of all time.
Well, let's see if that's true.
Cisco?
Are you okay?
I gotta go.
What? Why?
I am so sorry that
this is happening right now.
I am so, so sorry.
Um, I have to go.
I'll call you, okay?
I'll call you, I swear.
Mm!
Okay, Brian, let that sit overnight,
and then we'll assay in the morning.
Dr. Shore?
You okay?
[gasps]
[screams]
What are you doing?
You can't take that out of here.
Ah!
[heavy breathing]
What happened to me?
- [helicopter rotors]
- [guttural grunting]
What are you?
- [roars]
- Ah!
Foolish Human...
I am Grodd.
Patty.
What'd you find?
Found these weird-looking
hairs all over the street.
I'm gonna run 'em against the database
and see what I can find.
Uh, here, our victim.
His name's Dr. Jeffrey Shore.
He's a biochemistry engineer
here at Vaughan Pharmaceuticals.
This is the second dead
lab tech in two weeks.
That ain't a coincidence.
Yeah, and like the other tech,
he had just stolen a serum
from their storage cooler.
- Really? What kind of serum?
- It's called Cortexin.
It's used to treat encephalopathy,
a blood disease in the brain.
The serum's missing, but
his colleagues found him here
a couple of minutes later, dead.
He didn't get far.
He died from blunt force trauma to the head.
Ugh, and apparently a lot of it.
Yeah, check this out.
- Is that his blood?
- Point of impact.
Okay.
Can you run through what you told me to her
and see if you can get anything else,
and if the cases are linked?
Sure thing.
- Hi.
- Some of the evidence.
I'll be right with you. Uh, Detective?
How's Barry feeling?
Oh, heading to see him right now.
He asked me to bring him
some of my homemade chicken noodle soup.
He hates that canned stuff.
Don't we all.
Faster, Barry!
There you go.
Push yourself!
[groaning]
- [grunts
- Barry!
- Are you okay?
- [groans]
Oh, yeah, you know, I'm not great right now.
What happened?
It's nothing. I'm good, all right?
- Just forget it.
- Barry.
Talk to us. We can help you.
No, you can't help me.
Not this time. I'm sorry.
You just... you wouldn't understand.
[exhales sharply]
- What up, Barry?
- [sighs]
Zoom destroyed me.
He showed everyone in
Central City what he could do,
and that I'm powerless to stop him.
They gave me a key to this city, Joe.
I'm supposed to be their hero.
I'm supposed to be the guy
that can protect them
from something as evil as that, and I failed
in front of all of them.
[groans]
When they think of the Flash,
all they see now
is someone not strong enough
to protect them.
- Hey.
- I'm good.
Oh, hey, I know I keep asking,
but have you read any reports
or anything recently
about a Birdman attacking anywhere?
There's no such thing as a Birdman, Cisco.
Okay, like that's a stretch. In this city?
Look, I know what I vibed.
It was a man with these big, wide wings.
It was crazy.
What if it was an angel?
[laughs]
It was an angel.
Caitlin?
Okay, come on, like that's a crazy idea.
Ah!
What is wrong with you?
Just don't know what to do about Barry.
I mean, all the test results say he's fine,
but it's like there's
something holding him back.
I keep trying to talk to him,
but I can't get through.
Then maybe we should get the person who can.
[phone vibrates]
We can talk about that
when I see you at home.
I gotta take this, okay? Okay.
- Bye, baby.
- Bye.
Patty, what's up?
Turns out our dead scientist
cases are linked.
Okay, hit me.
Well, the other scientist
stole a large quantity
of a racetam drug,
typically used to treat
patients with Vertigo.
Okay, so we got two stolen drugs,
one for blood disorders of the brain,
and the other one for Vertigo.
What's the connection?
Well, they are both nootropic drugs,
used to enhance intelligence.
Hey, did you get results
from the hairs you found?
Yes, I did.
Uh, apparently they were all
over the other crime scene too.
The weird thing is, they're not human hairs.
Uh, they're hairs from a... From a gorilla.
- How... How did you know?
- Patty, I gotta go.
But... Uh...
Did Caitlin come through here?
No.
She just hit me in the face and ran away.
Yo!
- Grodd!
- What?
- Grodd's back.
- Caitlin.
That must be why she was acting like that.
She was being mind-controlled.
[dramatic music]
I'm continually amazed by the similarity
between our two worlds.
You got talking gorillas on your Earth, too?
- Oh, yeah.
- Remind me never to go there.
Ramon, why would this Grodd abduct Dr. Snow?
I don't know. It doesn't make any sense.
She was always so nice to him.
He mind-controlled two lab technicians
to steal chemicals
that enhance intelligence.
He wants her for something.
Well, looks like he left
his bachelor pad in the sewers.
Grodd's a big-ass gorilla.
He can't just waltz through downtown
in the middle of the day
without anybody noticing.
Right, and if there's been sightings,
then we might be able to
approximate his location.
I can call CCPD.
They can access the tip hotline,
send over files of Grodd's recent attacks.
Good.
We gotta get her back.
We will.
Barry.
- Barry!
- Yeah?
You can't blame yourself for this.
There's nothing you could've done.
I still don't have my speed.
How are we supposed to save her from Grodd?
You may not have your legs just yet,
but you still got that brain.
Use it. Help us figure that out.
[sighs]
Where are you?
[eerie music]
Caitlin.
Grodd?
You... Remember me?
[loud footsteps]
[snarling]
Caitlin... always... kind...
Why did you bring me here?
Need help.
I... I don't understand.
How did I become Grodd?
Oh.
That's a long story, Grodd.
Um...
The dark matter
from the particle accelerator explosion?
That's how this happened.
Repeat.
Repeat?
[snarls]
Need to repeat Grodd.
You want me to make more like you?
I don't know how to do that.
Learn.
[heavy breathing]
Keep that chin down, slugger.
Dad.
Yeah.
That was a hell of an idea
you had, bringing Henry here.
Well, he may not have his mother,
but he's got two amazing fathers.
Seemed like he needed both.
Hmm.
- Good girl.
- Mm.
So how did Grodd become sentient?
A few years ago, S.T.A.R. Labs
had this contract
with the military to research and awaken
latent mind-reading capabilities
for interrogation purposes.
And I'm guessing Grodd is
one of the test subjects?
Right, but then Dr. Wells
shut down the program,
and we all thought it was to save Grodd
from all the crazy mind-control experiments,
but it was really so that
Dr. Wells could use
the accelerator explosion to create
a 1,500-pound mind-controlling gorilla
that he could manipulate.
What kind of algorithm is that?
It's an algorithm meant to
extrapolate Grodd's location
from places we know he's already been.
Hello.
There we have it.
No spinal cord edema.
I don't see any subacute hemorrhaging.
Bone fused beautifully.
You're all good, Barry.
I'd give you some physical therapy,
but you don't need it.
I'm really glad you're here, Dad.
Me too.
You know, I tried to call,
but you can't a cell
in Granite Peak National Park, so...
Granite Peak... what are you...
You went camping by yourself?
Yeah, yeah, I got a tent.
I went fishing every day.
I have had my fill of
largemouth bass for a while.
[both chuckle]
Sometimes you just have to slow down
to get back to where you want to be.
- Yeah. Look, Dad...
- Hey, guys.
I think we've found them.
Yeah?
Grodd has to be in one of
these three bell towers.
The only reason we couldn't find him
on any cameras underneath the city before is
'cause he upgraded from a bachelor pad
to a penthouse, like a baller.
Okay, so we know where he is.
We still don't know how to get her.
- We got a plan for you.
- What's the plan?
We use me.
[grunts]
That's Harry! That's the other Wells!
- Barry.
- Let him go.
Let him go.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We found another suit in the Time Vault.
- I thought he was dead.
- He's dead.
This is... this is Harrison Wells
from Earth-2.
- Earth-2?
- I'll explain later.
If we can get Harry to convince Grodd
that he's Wells, that he's his father,
maybe we can convince him to let Caitlin go.
I'm not gonna be able to help
if anything goes wrong.
That's a chance I'm willing to take.
Looks like we're 0 for 2 on
the bell towers, huh?
I like to think of it more as,
now we know exactly where they are.
Okay, let's do this again.
Gimme your best Wells.
I'm not doing the Wells again, Ramon.
- I told you...
- Look.
I just made these
anti-mind-control ear buds.
They could fail, and
if they do, you're toast,
so you're gonna need to nail it
if you want to live.
[sighs] Ramon.
- Cisco.
In many ways, you've shown me
what it's like to have a son.
What?
Okay, let's... Let's just try it again.
This time, up the creep
factor, like, a lot more,
and make it a little more sincere.
Like you really love me,
but you're gonna have to kill me anyway.
Cisco.
In many ways,
you've shown me what
it's like to have a son.
Yup, that's the one. Here you go.
[phone rings]
Yo.
Yeah, we're moving
on to the third location.
Copy that.
Now we wait.
So this is what it's like
every time you go after
one of those meta-humans?
Uh, pretty much.
Only, Cisco and Caitlin are
normally the ones in here
and I'm the one out there.
Well, there's no reason you shouldn't be.
Iris showed me what happened.
With Zoom?
That was hard to watch.
I can only imagine what that
must have been like for you.
He showed everyone in Central City
that their hero wasn't
good enough to stop him.
Well, that's certainly what it looked like.
Was he right?
[scoffs]
Your body's healed, Barry,
and yet here you are,
feeling the shame of losing.
I can't stop him.
I know it. He knows it.
And now everyone in this city knows it too.
They don't believe in me anymore, Dad.
At my trial for your mother's death,
a lot of our family and friends
were in the courtroom.
They heard awful things about
what I had done to your mother.
It didn't matter that it wasn't true.
Every day, I could see it on their faces,
the moment when I lost them,
until everybody had stopped believing in me.
Well, that was my reality.
You know, I was gonna serve a life sentence
for a crime I didn't commit,
but worse than that,
every time I looked at someone in the eye
from that moment forward,
they were gonna believe
that I had killed the woman I loved
in front of our son.
So yeah, I do know what it's like
being destroyed.
How did you get past that?
I embraced it.
Accepting it was the only way
that I could move forward,
but I know that if I could survive that,
and learn to believe in myself again,
then I could survive anything.
You know what lit that belief in me, Barry?
You.
11-year-old you, running around,
believing in me,
gave me that hope.
And now I'm giving it back to you, son.
No more monsters can take that from us.
So, one of the main differences
between ape and human brains
is the white matter and
connectivity in the brain cells.
[grunts]
The chemicals that you were treated with
as an infant were meant
to overcome those differences
and cause an explosive growth of both,
similar to what humans experience
in their first few years of life.
Maybe these chemicals can be used
to duplicate that growth,
and then we won't need
a particle accelerator explosion.
[growls]
- Hey, buddy.
- [growls]
Easy, buddy. It's me.
I'm back.
Father, you died.
No.
No, buddy, I didn't die.
I just went away for a while.
All right, that's great,
Wells, keep talking.
But now that I'm back,
we don't need Caitlin anymore, do we, buddy?
So you can let her go.
[growls]
Come on, buddy.
Let me get her out of here.
Please.
Father never ask. Father take.
Run.
[roars]
Who are you?
Cisco, you gotta get in there, man.
[roars]
Oh, Cisco, thank God.
Okay, you guys gotta get out of there.
Harry's trapped. We can't leave him here.
What do we do?
The drugs. The drugs that Grodd stole.
Wells... an overdose of those
drugs will shock his brain.
Okay, just hit him with as much as you can.
You are not him! You are not Father!
- I am father.
- [growls]
And you hit father.
Grodd.
Look at me.
- Look at me!
- [roars]
I would never leave you here alone.
Grodd, I made you a promise.
I have bigger plans for you. Remember?
One day, this city will be yours.
I promised you.
I intend to honor that promise.
[growls]
[roars]
Go!
[growls]
Come on.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for rescuing me.
Well, we're a team, right?
I'm impressed. I think we all are.
Yeah, well, we need to do
something about Grodd.
- Like what?
- Like get rid of him for good.
You want to kill him?
Considering how many
people he's killed, yeah.
This isn't Grodd's fault.
He's only like this because
Wells made him this way.
Yes, but, Catie, he kidnapped
you and you could have died.
You didn't see what I saw.
Grodd's getting smarter.
He's lonely and sad.
He wan more apes like him.
What are you saying? He wants kids?
'Cause I'm pretty sure
one telepathic Grape Ape
is more than enough for this city.
I know somewhere we could send him.
What are you talking about?
When the singularity exploded
and I discovered the breach
in S.T.A.R. Labs, I ran similar tests
and discovered the same thing,
51 additional breaches.
The difference being
the breaches in Central City
are scattered all throughout the city
whereas counterparts in my world
most definitely are not.
And you know where they lead?
Well, I was in the process
of figuring all that out
when Dr. Snow so gallantly
convinced me to stay,
but if I am correct,
this breach is gonna get Grodd
as close to home as he's ever likely to get.
Okay, even if you're right,
how do we bait Grodd to go through it?
My son'll do it.
Won't you, Flash?
Grodd?
Caitlin.
Flash.
You want Caitlin, Grodd,
you're gonna have to catch me first.
[growls]
So Barry's gonna lure Grodd
in front of the breach?
Yep, and once he gets him to the right spot,
Cisco's gonna blast him into
Earth-2 with his thingamajig.
- [laughs] Speed cannon.
- Exactly.
Well, things have gotten
a lot more complicated
since I got out of prison.
- Mm-hmm.
- Man, you have no idea.
Cisco, almost there. Are you ready?
I'm in position.
Now, once you turn on the speed cannon,
the quark matter will stabilize,
stretching the breach about so big,
so anywhere within this circle will suffice.
Right on time.
Okay, come on.
I don't have eyes on Grodd.
Does anyone see him?
[roars]
That is a big gorilla.
Where is Caitlin?
[chokes] Ah!
[roars]
- Oh, my God.
- Get up, Barry.
- Ah!
- [growls]
Where is Caitlin, Flash?
[grunts]
Right here.
No. No, no, no.
You need to let him go, Grodd.
Flash is my enemy.
Now you, too. No.
He was trying to save me from you.
We didn't understand what you wanted,
but now we do.
I can give you what you want.
I can give you a home.
You just have to trust me.
[gasping and coughing]
All right, here he comes.
[grunts]
Ready to flip the switch.
Now, Barry.
[roars]
- Full power.
- It is.
[roars]
Barry, you can't let Grodd get free.
Conquer your fears, son.
Believe in yourself.
Come on, come on, come on.
[exhales]
[heavy breathing]
[laughter]
Welcome back, Flash.
Thanks, bro.
I can't believe something good
finally came from that suit.
First and the last time.
That thing still gives me the creeps.
We should destroy it.
Let's do that, but see if you can figure out
how to get it back in this ring first.
Might be nice to have something like that
instead of carrying around
a bag all the time.
I can help you with that.
What?
I know a thing or two
about micro-technology.
Yeah, you know a thing or two
about a lot of things.
Well, as long as what he knows keeps my son
and these good people safe,
the more you know, the better.
Pleasure to meet you, Harrison. Again.
Dr. Allen.
Good to see you. Cisco.
- Let's go.
- Take care.
So, Dr. Wells, this place on your Earth
that we've sent Grodd, what is it exactly?
It's a refuge where gorillas
subjected to lab experiments,
like Grodd,
can roam freely.
I know it's for the best,
but I still feel like I betrayed him.
No, don't say that. You didn't betray him.
You gave him a better life.
I still don't understand, though, I...
Why do the breaches on our Earth
lead to different places on yours?
I don't know yet, Ramon,
but I do know we have to close them all,
and I don't know how to do that.
You don't have to do it alone anymore.
Any of it.
Together, we defeated Grodd,
and if we stay that way,
we will figure out
how to close the breaches,
get Zoom, and get you your daughter back.
Thank you.
Oh, this one is definitely a keeper.
[laughs] Oh, yeah.
He could've done your standard
vinegar and baking soda volcano,
but no, Barry wanted to do
a molecular structure
of chocolate and nougat.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's my favorite candy bar.
Who does that in the sixth grade?
Why, a true science nerd.
Like father, like son, I suppose.
All right, Dad, we should get going.
Yeah. Uh, Joe, can I have...
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Iris, thank you so much
for reaching out to me.
I am so glad you did. Me, too.
Joe, there are no words, man.
Thanks.
All right, I'm gonna swing by
my lab before I come home.
Which reminds me... Patty?
She's a smart girl.
She's not buying your
whole sick story, FYI.
- All right.
- Patty?
Would this be a new girlfriend?
Uh, yeah, something like that, yeah.
We'll talk about it on the way
to the bus station.
Come on.
- Bye.
- See ya.
You okay?
[sighs] It's embarrassing.
I... I love Barry
like he's my own son, but
when I'm reminded that he isn't,
I start to wonder what it would've been like
if, you know...
Dad, you would've been just as amazing
with your own son, just like
you were with me and Barry.
I hear you've been spending
a lot of time up here.
[chuckles] Well, you know what they say.
When the CSI's away...
It's good to see you on your feet again.
Must've been all that canned soup you had.
Or maybe the homemade stuff Joe brought you?
It... yeah, I wasn't actually sick, Patty.
Yeah, I figured that out.
Why did you lie to me?
My dad was in town.
I needed to spend some time with him.
And you couldn't just tell me that?
You gotta understand, Patty,
my dad was convicted of murder.
When someone's image has been
tarnished like that,
it's hard for some people to see past it.
And you seriously think
I'm one of those people?
No, I know, I should've
given you more credit.
No, you should've given
yourself more credit.
This isn't about your father, Barry.
This is about you.
I need to know that I can trust
you if we're gonna do this.
- Okay.
- I'm serious.
I can tell.
You cannot always be a smart ass.
["In Your Eyes" by Peter Gabriel]
♪ Love I get so lost ♪
- Hi.
I didn't know if you liked
flowers or chocolate,
so... I got you both.
Well, I'm allergic to chocolate,
and I think that flowers
are a waste of money.
Um... I have lollipops in my car?
- Cisco, I'm joking.
- Oh, God.
[laughs] This is great. Thank you.
Listen, I wanted to come over here
and say I'm sorry for
bailing the other night.
I... I'm a liaison with the CCPD
and there was an emergency,
and I had to be there.
- The CCPD?
- Yeah.
Wow, that's really cool. And very brave.
Thank you.
And this is very, very sweet, Cisco.
Um, what is this?
- Well, see, that right there.
- Mm-hmm?
That's a digital movie projector.
I loaded all of "Princess Bride" on there.
- [laughs]
- Mm-hmm, that's right.
So, all we need is a wall, or, you know,
some place where we can pick up
our date where we left off.
Well, if we're gonna pick up
right where we left it...
Whoa.
Whoa what? What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're just a really amazing kisser.
[laughs] Okay.
- Let's go watch "Princess Bride."
- Let's.
There's a great wall up on the roof.
♪ Oh, I see the light and the heat ♪
[grandiose music]
[roars]