Why is it so complicated
deciding how to have a baby?
The Batsuit isn't exactly baby-proof,
but I can't force Sophie into
nine months of indigestion
and swollen ankles.
Sis, you are spiraling.
Do you remember what I told you
when I was your maid of honor?
No, I was busy getting married,
not taking notes.
I told you to stop thinking so much
and to listen to your heart.
If you want to have a baby,
your heart will figure out the "how."
And then that sweet little girl
is going to grow up
and decide that she hates you.
Jenna has been thinking
the worst insults at me tonight.
Let me tell you something.
Teenagers...
Do not use the bathroom,
it's occupied.
Really occupied.
Thank you.
Allegra!
Hey.
So, how's London?
You calling cookies "biscuits" yet?
Nope. But actually, I might be
moving back to the States.
I got a job offer in Gotham.
Oh, my gosh. Allegra, that's great.
Thanks. Yeah, I haven't decided
if I'm gonna take it or not yet.
So...
If I could have
everyone's attention for a minute.
When you find...
the love of your life,
you're part of something greater, you...
You're part of something wonderful,
magical, beautiful,
and, frankly, surprising,
because you never know
what face
fate will be wearing
when she knocks on your door
to change your life forever.
And my only wish for you
is that when that face shows up
to change your lives,
that that face is as beautiful
as the one standing next to me.
To Iris West.
The love of my life.
What the hell is he doing here?
You got a lot of nerve
showing up here, Allen.
It's been you this whole time.
Despero,
Armageddon, Joe...
Don't you dare say my father's name,
you murderer!
Guys, it's me, Barry.
Iris is my wife.
We've all fought Thawne together.
My God, he actually believes
the things he's saying.
All right, I'll show you it's me.
Thawne, what did you do?
You're not the Flash,
Allen.
I am.
Team Flash,
suit up.
Guys.
Thawne is tricking you.
I came here from 2021.
Save it, Allen.
I'm not falling
for your mind games this time.
Put him down.
It's a paralysis ray.
No speed for a couple seconds, Allen.
- Why are you doing this?
- So I can do this.
That was for Ray and for Nate.
And that was for Sara.
And this...
...is for Cisco.
So sorry, Allegra.
But we did put a tie on the door.
What did we miss?
Get away from me.
Iris, you have to believe me.
Thawne's not the Flash, I am.
He must have changed the timeline.
You're my wife.
This is our home, our loft.
We even have kids.
- Bart and Nora.
- Stop!
Please, you have to remember us.
Iris, you're my lightning rod.
You're psychotic.
Iris West is my lightning rod now,
Reverse-Flash.
What the hell did you do?
Nothing you haven't done before.
You created a Flashpoint.
Wrong. I created a Reverse Flashpoint.
I started by doing a little housekeeping
at S. T.A.R. Labs.
And then, I took care
of the one father you had left.
Why?
Because after our last encounter,
it was clear to me
you're faster than I was.
And that the only way to defeat you...
was to become you.
So, I ran back
to the year 2013 and made sure
that I was the one struck by lightning.
I was the one that Iris West wrote about
as the Streak. I led Team Flash.
I was the one Iris West
fell in love with.
I stole your life!
And because every hero needs a villain,
I created that, too.
You wore my face.
It was you
that attacked the city that day.
That's why they don't trust me.
Made you think you were crazy,
crazy enough to beg,
literally beg Jefferson Pierce
to steal your speed.
What's it at now?
Five percent?
Maybe less.
Thawne, what you've done
destroys the world.
It creates Armageddon.
- No.
- No, it's true. Damn it!
I would not create a perfect world
just to watch it die.
As a matter of fact,
the only thing that is set to expire
is you.
Do you know why?
Because I finally did what I
set out to do all those years ago.
I killed you as a child.
You can do that all night long.
But the fact remains, at the stroke
of midnight, my timeline will solidify,
and you will cease to exist.
And your precious Speed Force
cannot help you now,
because in this timeline,
she chose me and Iris chose me.
I've won!
I finally won. Who's faster now?
Earlier today,
protesters gathered downtown...
...outside the penthouse
of Damien Darhk, demanding justice.
Darhk, who was released from
Iron Heights Prison on a technicality...
...was convicted six months ago
for the murders
of A.R. G. U.S. director, Cisco Ramon,
the heroic team known as the Legends,
as well as tech philanthropist,
Ray Palmer.
Meanwhile, Darhk's accomplice,
the mass-murdering speedster,
the Reverse-Flash, is still at large.
Barry Allen.
I was wondering when my old partner
was going to come back and say hello.
I hope you've been
laying low somewhere relaxing.
I need your help again, Damien.
Yeah, of course you do.
Whoa! Mm.
Huh.
You seem... different.
It seems like you're
running on empty, old friend.
What happened to you?
The Flash happened to me,
now I want payback.
I like where this is going.
Spill your tragic tale.
Well, after you were arrested,
- I fought the Flash and beat him.
- Yes!
But before I could drive a hand
through his heart,
he ran back in time,
changed things, so he had won.
He created an anachronism.
Only it wasn't just one event.
Thawne changed everything.
Trying to stop him cost me my speed.
Now we're living in a timeline
he constructed for his own benefit.
Really?
And that's downright villainous.
Mm.
We need to put him down.
Yeah, we will. We will.
Nobody gets to rig time except me.
But fixing this won't be easy.
If the Flash created
multiple anachronisms,
the only way to reset the timeline is to
turn everything back at the same time,
which is why we need the P.E.D.
- The P.E.D?
- The P.E.D.
The Particle Eradication Distributor.
The thing that erases
any type of matter.
You yanked it out
of Ray Palmer's cold dead hands.
Right.
When you've killed as many people
as I have, you start to lose track.
Huh.
I sometimes forget...
you're even darker than me.
Pun intended.
All right, old partner.
Here's what we're going to do.
If we combine the P.E.D.
and my Time Stone,
any anachronisms on that temporal plane
will be erased.
So this could work.
Oh, it gets so much better.
After my arrest,
they confiscated the P.E.D.
Guess where it ended up?
Frost, Chillblaine, and Batwoman
are searching the city,
- but no sign of Reverse-Flash.
- And I can't feel him anymore.
It's like he magically disappeared.
Then try harder.
Cecile, um, we know that
you're doing your best.
Yes, of course you are.
What's up with him, anyway?
Has he gone crazy?
I mean, the guy actually thought
he was the Flash.
He's a sociopath.
There's no explaining a mind like that.
Runk, where are we with the satellites?
Runk?
- What?
- Satellites?
Right.
Satellites are scanning
for his negative tachyons, sir.
But after analyzing samples
from Robern's,
looks like the Reverse-Flash
is running on limited speed.
Less speed means lower tachyon output.
Making him harder to track.
But not impossible if we sync
the Atom Bracelet's micro-sensors
to the satellite.
That'll isolate the smallest tachyons
that'll give us Allen's location.
Consider it done, Captain Eo.
Horton, use The Thinker's chair
to boost your empathic scan.
Snow, get the med lab ready
in case there's trouble.
Danvers, Garcia, weapons check.
What are you thinking?
Well, I'm thinking you should be at home
resting up for our big day tomorrow.
I will.
What?
It's just that Allen seems off.
Baby, he called me his lightning rod.
Only you call me that.
I know.
But he's smart.
He's attacking our love.
We cannot let him pull us apart.
He won't.
I love you.
What's the deal
with you and Chester?
Nothing.
- Why?
- The stolen glances,
the nervous energy.
You either hooked up, you are
hooking up, or you really need to.
Okay, we did once, but it was
ten years ago and it went nowhere.
What happened?
We'd been flirting for months,
and one night we were playing D&D
and it just happened.
It was a really lusty quest.
Anyway, I thought
something would come of it.
But by the time I woke up
in the morning, Chester was gone.
Hold up, he just left?
Yep.
And by the time we talked about it,
we decided it was better
just to be friends.
Bye-bye.
And you know how much longer
until my new look is ready?
I'm going to look so good
kicking bad guy butt.
Just making some last-minute tweaks.
Okay.
Okay, good to go.
Now we can hunt some tachyons.
It's working.
According to these readings,
there's a pocket
of negative tachyons in this room.
You had to ruin the surprise,
didn't you?
You find the P.E.D.,
I'll take care of these two.
Hello, boys.
Ah-ah-ah.
Of course.
Ooh! Tupac. What an artist!
- I've got it.
- Already?
You and I, what a team!
Hurts, doesn't it?
Well, so will this.
Let's go.
Oh, I've got a better idea.
Imagine how devastating
it would be to the Flash
to lose his friends
on the eve of his wedding.
Nothing destroys a man
like losing the ones he loves the most.
What the hell was that?
We got what we wanted.
Killing them
wouldn't have been efficient.
We can kill them later.
Huh.
The Barry Allen I know wouldn't wait,
which means you're not
the Reverse-Flash.
So, who are you?
Don't make me ask you again.
Who are you?
Thawne's the Reverse-Flash...
Erased me from the timeline
at midnight.
Man, he is good!
I mean, that's like a work of evil art.
The question is now
what do I do with you?
You could still help me.
"Help me?"
Yeah, I'm the bad guy.
I don't help heroes.
But you're also a father.
Which means you know what it feels like
to love someone
with all your heart and soul,
like your daughter, Nora.
My Nora's dead.
I'm done listening to you.
She's supposed to be alive.
And she is, in the timeline
I'm trying to restore.
In my timeline,
a demon was going to take over her soul,
but you switched places with her.
You gave your own life
so she could live.
If you're lying to me,
I'll see you burn.
Nora! Nora!
- Dad, why?
- Because I love you.
And I couldn't watch you
become a monster like me.
It's true.
My Nora Doll's supposed to be alive.
I sacrificed myself to save her.
So honor that sacrifice.
Help me restore the timeline
and bring her back.
Let's go to work.
I guess you guys
haven't found Allen yet, huh?
Nope.
And Batwing called from Gotham.
- Two-Face turned up, which means...
- You have to go.
I will be at the ceremony tomorrow,
I promise.
Until then, take this.
It's a Velocity-Zero gun.
Luke designed it the last time a certain
lady-in-red tried to kill us all.
It will temporarily disrupt
Reverse-Flash's connection
to whatever speed force
he's connected to.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Now, uh...
you want to talk about
your other problem?
I don't know, I've been
working on it since I got home.
Every time I think about my future
with Eobard, my mind just...
It goes blanker than that page.
Any chance it's...
just cold feet?
I don't know.
I love Eobard, I do.
But when I think about what Allen said,
I mean, I just...
I can't...
I can't get it out of my head,
it's like it's haunting me.
Ryan, I've won two Pulitzers.
Why can't I write my own wedding vows?
Iris.
Tonight, you told me to stop thinking
so much and listen to my heart.
Yeah, okay, I get it.
- That's what I'm supposed to do now.
- 'Cause it works.
Look, tonight I saved a kid
living in their van near the waterfront.
Just like I was
before I found the Batsuit.
Some lowlifes were mugging her,
and as I was kicking their asses,
my heart told me what I want.
I wanna save a kid, like Cora saved me.
So after I dropped their sorry asses off
at the nearest precinct,
I called Sophie.
We're gonna adopt.
Ryan...
I'm so happy for you.
Take your own advice.
Trust me,
if Eobard's the one, the vows will come.
And what if he isn't?
Then I will get you
out of here in a hot minute.
My car drives really fast.
That's good work.
- Martini?
- Dude.
Right, you don't drink alcohol.
Hey, Chester.
Why did you ghost Allegra?
- I never...
- Oh, here we go.
Ten years ago,
the morning after you two hooked up,
you snuck out while she was sleeping.
First of all, that's not ghosting,
that's called the French exit.
I never ghosted anyone, okay?
I went to get coffee
and blueberry muffins.
- Wait. What?
- Yeah.
I wanted to have breakfast in bed,
watch the sun come up.
Had the whole day planned.
Because I knew even after one night,
that I wanted to spend
the rest of my life with her.
Dear God!
When I got back,
she was gone, Alex, so...
Allegra ghosted me.
Which is why we always abide
by rule number one:
Never return to the scene of the crime.
Why didn't you ever tell her?
I wanted to,
but we were attacked
by the Legion of Doom.
That week was seriously chaotic.
And when the dust settled,
I tried bringing it up again...
but she cut me off.
Told me that night was a huge mistake
and that we were better off as friends.
I think I'm going to get some air.
Yeah.
Uh...
See, this is what happens
when you try and play Cupid.
What is your problem?
Why don't you love love?
Okay.
Love is just a chemical flood
of dopamine and oxytocin
giving people an addictive dependence
like a bad drug.
Science.
It's taken me years to help Chuck
feel happy without Allegra.
By telling him to hide his heart?
Okay, now you're going to give me
a whole greeting-card-inspired speech
about your perfect wife
and how she's the love of your life.
Okay, all right.
All right, fine.
But one day you're going to
wake up alone, and you're gonna realize
that you missed out
on the best part of being human.
Look, um,
according to these equations,
I'd have to hit Mach 20
in order to open a time portal.
Really?
Yeah.
And is that a problem?
To reach that kind of speed,
I'd need 40,000 miles.
That kind of runway doesn't exist.
Yes, it does.
Is that big enough?
Yes, but the Earth
isn't just a solid rock.
It has a molten core.
The kind of pressure
I'd be exerting on its mantle
would cause cataclysmic damage.
We're talking volcanoes erupting,
ice caps melting, earthquake, tsunami...
It'd be Armageddon.
So in order to save the world
and bring my Nora back...
I'd have to risk destroying it.
Just like Despero predicted.
Look, uh...
I hate to break up your pity party,
but we're running out of time.
Barry, you have to do this.
Trust me. I want my life
and Iris back more than anything.
But I've run the numbers.
I will have two minutes to accelerate
before my destruction
destroys the world.
Well, then you better run fast.
Damien, the odds of me hitting Mach 20
in two minutes is two percent.
It's better than nothing.
Look, you don't understand,
Despero says I cause Armageddon.
This is exactly what he described.
I won't be responsible for killing
every single person on the planet.
And what happens to those people
if you give up?
You're leaving eight billion souls
in a world where Thawne has everything
that he wants and nothing to lose.
- I'm still not fast enough.
- Fast enough?
How dense are you?
Speed isn't the only thing
that guides you through these things,
- it never is.
- What else is there?
Love, you idiot!
You're the paragon of it.
I saw what you did in the Time Stone.
You restarted
an entire universe with love.
This should be peanuts.
That's not gonna work, not this time.
Really?
Well, it's guiding
the both of us right now.
Why do you think I'm helping you?
You think I want to die?
I don't.
But if sacrificing my life means
that Nora gets to live the life
that Thawne stole from her,
then yeah, I'm going to do it because...
my love for her is what keeps me going
every damn day of my life.
Who do you think
I built this whole empire for?
And Iris?
Your family? Your friends?
They are what keep you going.
Iris doesn't remember what we had.
Well...
That doesn't matter.
You do.
You lied to me about Chester.
Chester loves you.
When he went to tell you,
you cut him off.
Why did you do that?
You want to know how every relationship
in my life has ended?
With me getting kicked to the curb.
Everyone I've ever loved has left.
When I woke up the next morning alone,
it was like a trigger.
Suddenly I was 12 years old again
and my mom was telling me
that my dad left us because of me.
Yep, she was a bag of crap, too.
The point is, I was crushed.
So, when I saw Chester walking
up the street with coffees and a bag,
I knew what that meant,
how he felt about me,
and I just freaked out,
and I pushed him away.
You know...
my wife is my rock.
But things were not always perfect.
Trust me,
putting yourself out there, it's scary.
But it's also so worth it.
But what if I lose him?
You'll never know unless you try.
Alex...
the reason why I don't love love...
is because nothing scares me more
than putting my heart out on the line.
So I make fun of romantics.
But this whole Don Juan thing,
it's just an act.
- Really?
- I knew it.
The truth is...
I don't want to wake up alone
for the rest of my life.
Look...
Chester's my boy,
and I know what my boy needs.
He needs you.
Guys,
we got a hit on Reverse-Flash!
Let's go.
I was just thinking about...
I just want to talk, I swear.
You take one more step
and I'm gonna shoot you.
Okay.
What's wrong with you? Are you dying?
Something like that.
I came here because I'm about
to do something impossible.
And even though it might not work,
I couldn't leave this world
without telling you that...
Nice try, Allen.
But she doesn't love you.
She loves me.
Tell him, Iris. Or better yet...
shoot him.
- Iris.
- What are you waiting for? Shoot him!
I need you to know,
no matter what happens,
after everything Thawne's taken from me,
he can't take away my feelings for you.
I love you, Iris.
Enough.
Go... before I change my mind.
- How'd it go with the missus?
- I don't know.
But she let me go.
Has to mean something.
Well...
Let's do this thing.
Now I'll stay here,
your point of origin,
just in case we get some visitors.
But I'll be in touch.
- How?
- Magic.
You'll hear my voice wherever you go.
Now remember,
you've got two minutes to reach Mach 20
and open the temporal portal.
Damien...
thank you.
Get outta here.
We tracked down the P.E.D.
and Reverse-Flash.
He's crossing the Atlantic Ocean.
What the hell is he doing?
He's destroying the city.
It's like the end of days out here.
Holy crap. It's not just the city.
Allen's speed wake is causing the globe
to tear itself apart.
It's an extinction-level event
in progress.
He's right. I'm tracking
at least a hundred earthquakes.
A tsunami just hit Japan.
Allen really has lost his mind.
He realized he can't win,
so he's trying to kill us all.
I have to go.
I gotta go get Jenna.
Guys,
Mark and I could use backup.
Go. I'll stay here.
Okay.
Hey, not to be that guy,
but since this could be the end
of the world as we know it,
if anyone has anything to say,
now would be the time.
Right.
The Reverse-Flash just hit Europe.
Where's Eobard?
I'm right behind him.
Hey, Flash, you've got company.
Guess what, Darhk?
So do you.
Frosty, Chill-Lame.
Yeah, I'm a little bit busy.
But you do realize my abilities
give me the power
to draw and quarter
with a gesture, right?
Oh.
Not for the next 24 hours, you don't.
Our friend, John, gave us
a badass protection spell.
Constantine, I hate that guy.
Yeah, well, too bad.
Looks like we get to kick
this guy's ass all night.
Won't even take that long.
Really?
Let's see how that goes.
If Boss doesn't catch Allen
in the next 90 seconds...
- Chester...
- Eighty-five.
- Chester.
- Eighty-four.
- Chuck!
- What?
I love you!
Yeah, well, I love you, too!
When did this happen?
This is not working!
I'm still not fast enough!
I'm trying to save
my daughter here, Allen.
Focus!
Never dance with the devil.
Yeah. I increased the molecular density
on that little toothpick of yours,
a thousand-fold at the sub-atomic level.
Good luck trying to lift two tons.
I hate science.
Then you are really gonna hate that.
- Thanks for the assist.
- Of course.
- Hey, nice threads.
- Thanks, man!
We're running out of time.
Sixty seconds.
Come on, Flash.
You're too late, Allen.
You're too late!
Iris...
Barry, I love you, too.
I love you, too.
You're no hero.
You are a monster!
I'm going to ask you one last time,
Miss Horton.
And if I don't like your answer, you'll
join your friends in the afterlife.
Now...
the Flash...
Where is he?
I told you, I don't know!
You know what?
I believe you.
What is this?
Flash, what did you do?
I went to the future.
Iris was right.
Someone manipulated the timeline
to drive me insane.
Turns out, in order to fix it,
I had to start Armageddon.
Only this time,
I didn't destroy the world.
How is that possible?
You left 2031 before the world ended.
What you didn't know
was that Eobard Thawne,
the Reverse-Flash, was chasing me.
He wanted to stop me
from restoring the timeline.
The speed wake created by us both.
That is what caused
the destruction you saw.
If that's happened, what stopped you
from tearing this world apart?
Iris.
She helped me reconnect
to the Speed Force.
Now the future's safe.
I can see you believe it to be true.
And as a traveler in time,
my senses confirm this world
has been altered.
But as for the true reason...
well, that remains to be seen.
Maybe you should go to 2031
and see for yourself.
I shall.
But if you're wrong
or if I find any evidence
that this world is still in danger,
I will return,
and you will die.
Yeah.
- Gluten-free? Cecile.
- Gluten-free.
- Here you go.
- Nice.
You have yours, right?
Is there drinks?
Hey, babe!
Uh, I would've got you something,
but I thought you were
working through lunch
at the precinct today.
Don't worry, there's plenty.
Got a burger for you, boss.
I missed you so much.
Not that I don't love
this attention, but...
where's this coming from?
Barry, you okay?
Something happened, didn't it?
What was it?
Later, all right?
I just want to be here with you.
With all of you.
Okay.
Want me to call Dad? Frost?
Dad. Here we go.
Joe...
Can I call him?
Uh, I mean, yeah, it's ringing. So...
Joe?
It's really you.
You're really there.
Nobody uses time against me.
I will live.
I will change what's about to happen.
And you will help me.