Previously on
Crisis on Earth X...
- To Barry and Iris.
- Are you asking me to marry you?
- I am.
- Just forget about it.
- Felicity.
I don't wanna marry you.
I just called off my engagement.
To making things go away.
Does anyone have just cause
why these two should not be married?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Nazis?
Why would Nazis want to
crash my wedding?
There's a 53rd Earth called Earth-X.
Basically, our Earth
with one difference.
The Nazis won the war.
I call it
"Calm after the Firestorm."
No powers for either of us.
The other archer
and flying woman
are Oliver and Kara of Earth-X.
And Thawne is working with them.
The General is dying.
All we need is a new heart
and we found the perfect donor.
I don't think
this is our Earth.
Eyes front!
So, this craphole is Earth-X.
Wells was right.
He usually is.
It's hard to believe a place like this
actually exists. On any Earth.
I wish I shared your sentiment,
but in all my travels to distant times,
one thing sadly remains constant,
is man's ability to feel hatred
for other men.
Keep moving.
Move.
Stars and triangles.
Badges used to identify reported crimes
these people have quote-unquote
committed to land in here.
What's the pink triangle for?
What'd you do?
I loved the wrong person.
We gotta get out of these things.
Transmute us out.
With pleasure.
I can't vibrate through them either.
Power-dampening collars.
Why are we wearing them, then?
Doesn't matter.
There's too many guards here, anyways.
They're going to kill my sister.
Look, we're not gonna
let that happen, Alex, I promise you.
We're gonna get back to our Earth
before them.
How? We don't even know how we got here.
No, we don't. We're gonna figure it out.
Then we're gonna find a way
to get out of this place
and we're gonna get back
to the people we love.
I hope everyone else is okay.
Oh.
Rip Van Ramon awakens.
This doesn't look like a wedding.
You missed quite a bit, Cisco.
All you need to know is that
you're locked in one of your
fabulous anti-meta-human cells
with the rest of us.
And we can't escape.
Of course we can't.
That's what I designed them for, genius.
Good command of the obvious.
- Boys...
- Is that a ball?
Why? Is it bothering you?
Yes.
God!
Hey!
Are they gonna do that
the whole time we're in here?
Probably.
- It hurts. Cut it out.
- Cut what out?
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Feels like old times, doesn't it?
You know, I built this place?
With my own hands,
and called it home for 15 years.
And do you know what?
I hated every minute of it.
- Where are my friends?
- Your friends...
They're on Earth-X.
But I wouldn't worry about
your friends too much
because they're not going to be alive
much longer.
Oh, my.
It's because of the red sunlight.
And trust me, it'll make you
weaker than you can possibly imagine.
You did all this just... Just to get me?
Do you know how many
innocent people you killed?
Their lives to save mine?
Well, they should feel honored.
It's a strange sensation, isn't it?
Feeling vulnerable.
And it's just gonna get worse
because this red sunlight,
it's softening you up,
until pretty soon, I'm gonna
crack you open like a walnut.
Then I'm gonna take your healthy heart.
I'm gonna put it in her.
Which means we should probably
get you going.
Good.
That'll give me time to talk to
myself.
Did you hear that?
Everyone else is on Earth-X.
Kara only has a few hours
before they go full Mengele on her.
- We gotta stop them.
- Got any ideas?
I don't know.
Give me some time to think.
Iris, I'm all for girl power
and everything, but how are you and I
gonna stop the meaner Nazi version of
my whatever he is right now,
and people with superpowers?
We don't have to, we just need
to get to the pipeline and get Cisco.
He could turn off all the power to
the building and breach us out of here.
Do you know how to get to the pipeline
from here?
- I think so.
- Lead the way, McClane.
Move!
I don't like the looks of this.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Keep moving.
What are we doing?
- It's round-up time.
- Round-up for what?
In line. Now!
So, these are...
The heroes.
Yes, Sturmbannführer.
Blond hair, blue eyes.
This is Nordic perfection.
Why would you align yourself
with the unpure?
Because I like men.
And I like women.
You know, I had a daughter
who looked just like you.
With similar compulsions.
And I expunged that filth
from my family line forever.
Bring them all.
And him!
Move! Now! Go!
Not to be an alarmist,
but if we don't have an escape plan,
I suggest we get one immediately.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Up!
Go.
Turn around.
I know you are not him,
but I cannot stomach
the sight regardless.
Ready!
I'm sorry, Kara.
Aim!
I hate fire!
- Snart?
About time!
Kill them all!
Take cover!
Hey? You're cutting it close.
I thought that was great timing.
I really enjoyed the pun.
So, you're Leonard Snart's doppelganger.
No, I'm Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Leo.
That is a fantastic outfit.
Did you make that?
- Leo?
- Right!
Time to make you shine, buddy.
Uh, you...
You might wanna close your eyes.
Why?
I believe he just answered
your question.
Come on, let's go.
- Where we going?
- To our base.
- Your base?
- And... And who are you?
I was thinking exactly the same thing
about you all.
You might have to tell us on the way.
You're looking more human,
scared, helpless, pathetic,
- inferior.
- We're not that different from them.
Oh, please.
We're everything they want to be.
Blonde, white.
- Aryan perfection.
- I'm not like you.
I don't think I'm better
than everyone else.
You should, you are.
You're a god to them.
You could've been living like one.
- Like you?
- Yes, like me.
They want someone to bow to.
To worship. To lead.
What you're doing is not leading.
It's ruling.
Yes, it is.
They're like ants, Kara.
They shouldn't fear us
for what we can do.
They should rely on us
when they need us.
Oh, spare me the Good Samaritan crap.
I'm not going to take advantage
of anyone just because I can.
The world isn't made better
by protecting the weak.
It's made better by getting rid of them.
You really are pathetic.
You know, I saw you at the wedding.
By yourself.
Poor lonely little Kara,
can't even find a date to a wedding.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
It's written all over that
pouty little face of yours.
You spend so much time on your planet
taking care of everyone but yourself.
No wonder you seem so utterly miserable.
It's not going to work.
You're not going to get what you want.
Really?
Why do you care if I take your heart?
You're not using it.
At least I have one.
We're almost ready.
Clear.
I know bad guys have inopportune timing,
but this is, like,
the worst timing ever.
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
Barry and I were
just about to get married.
At least you guys left on good terms.
Last thing I said to Oliver was,
"I don't want to marry you."
And now, he's stuck in Nazi world.
What if we never see them again?
Stop! Hands in the air.
- That was extremely badass.
- Same to you.
Cisco?
Cisco!
Hey!
Guys! We're trapped in here!
We're gonna get you out of here.
- Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
- What?
- I can't open the blast door.
- You mean they're trapped?
I'll send an SOS to the Legends.
How long will it take
for them to get it?
Depends where they are in time.
I can't wait that long.
It's up to us to save Kara.
I guess we're in Earth-X's Star City.
I have to say,
that's one hell of a story.
- You're a speedster. Okay.
- Yeah.
You two turn into the burning man,
and you're the good doppelganger
of the Führer.
"Good" might be an oversimplification.
You still haven't told us
which Earth you're from.
Clearly it's not this one.
We're from Earth-1.
Earth-1. Well,
golly.
Am I missing something here?
I'm from Earth-1, too.
If you're from our Earth, then you know
how we got here, don't you?
Yeah. I have a pretty good idea.
I think you guys
came through this.
A temporal gateway?
Same physics as a breach.
Just more stable, and larger.
Yeah, much larger.
So, we have a way to get back?
So, where is this thing?
- It's actually not too far from here.
- 22.3 kilometers, to be exact.
- Well, we drive it.
- Good. So, take us to it.
Can't do that.
Why?
Because the gateway's in a facility
guarded by a not-so-small army of Nazis.
Yeah, well, we've faced worse, so...
Look, it's our only way home.
We're going through it.
Nobody's going through anything.
Because we're blowing it the hell up.
Winn?
Please, Freedom Fighter, General Schott.
- General Schott?
- Yeah.
- And who are you?
- New friends from Earth-1.
They're on our side.
Except for the part where you guys wanna
blow up our only way home.
We don't exactly want to.
Everyone we care about is on
the other side of that gateway,
imprisoned by Nazis.
The Nazis that want to
cut open my sister.
We have to get back!
Eliminate that facility,
and you eliminate our only chance
of saving our friends from your enemies.
I'm sorry, but we've been waiting
for an opportunity like this for years.
We cannot wait any longer.
This is our only chance to separate
the Führer from his army.
We are trying to turn this war around.
You are gonna leave our Earth
at the mercy of the three psychopaths
who have ravaged yours.
Wait, why does this man look exactly
like the Führer I'm trying to kill?
Look, fingerless gloves,
all we're asking is
for a little bit of time.
Let us get into the facility
and through that gateway.
The gateway's guarded
by 30 Panzer XII's,
50 Sturmtigers,
and 100 Schutzstaffel officers.
- Not the best odds, maybe.
- I'll take them.
No! You will not!
We're blowing up that gateway right now.
Final order!
Sorry, he's a little rough
around the edges,
but he is the General,
and he's issued his commands.
Hey, hey, hey.
You won't change his mind. No one does.
Look, on my Earth,
he and I are like family.
And he would do anything
to help my sister.
Ray! Let her try.
You don't seem to know
how to take an order.
That's because I'm used to giving them.
You can't do this, Winn.
General Schott.
Look, I don't know
where the hell you think you are,
but this planet has been
at war for generations.
We are tired.
There are men dying for the same causes
their grandfathers did.
We're not asking you to surrender.
Hey, just let us get back home
before you destroy that thing.
I'm just asking for a little time.
Time is what I can't give you!
They have a weapon,
a doomsday weapon powerful enough
to affect other worlds.
It has to be eliminated.
Winn.
Please.
The Führer on your Earth,
the people that you hate,
they're going to kill my sister if you
don't let me get back to save her.
On my Earth,
my sister is your closest friend.
She's saved you countless times.
You would do anything to help her.
You'd do anything to help each other.
No matter the risk.
Without question.
So, all I'm asking for is a chance.
Please.
I am sorry about your sister
and about your Earth,
I truly am,
but today, I have the chance
to protect my people, my Earth.
My decision stands.
Winn?
Jefferson?
Uh, Grey, I'm busy, man.
Yes, I can see that,
but I was hoping you might
take a moment away from your
ruminations on dystopian alternative
history to accept my apology.
I may be a learned man,
but I am not always an astute one.
I think I was just so thrilled with
the reality of my imminent departure,
that I neglected
to consider your feelings.
Look, man, I'm not tryin' to take you
away from your family, or nothing.
You are my family.
Long before I unexpectedly found myself
with a daughter,
I found myself unexpectedly with a son.
- Yeah, I know. I...
- You know.
You know, do you?
Look around you. We're standing
in one of the darkest places imaginable.
Yet somehow, I'm optimistic.
- Do you know why?
- 'Cause you're a crazy old man.
Yes. No!
Because I'm standing here with you.
You are a better son
than I could have ever hoped for.
And no length of time or distance
will ever change that.
A'ight. Apology accepted. Come here.
What are you doing?
Looking for a gun.
Or a knife. Anything.
Okay, I don't care how many Sturmtigers
they have out there,
I'm gonna go save Kara
with or without the help
of these people.
No, you're not.
I'm a government agent
certified in over 30 military weapons.
And you're impressive,
I'll give you that,
but you still can't fight your way
through an army of Nazis
alone and scared.
I'm not scared.
No, not for you. For your sister.
I should have done more.
I mean, if I hadn't gotten so
distracted.
Well, sorry to be a distraction.
You don't understand.
I can't lose her.
I understand more than you think.
I lost my sister.
The anger and guilt that I felt
for not being able to save her
took me down a dark path.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
How could you?
I mean, the only thing
we know about each other
is what we look like with clothes off.
Beautiful, by the way.
You also don't know
that I protect my team.
And you, Danvers, you're on my team.
And I promise you,
we're not gonna let what happened
to my sister happen to yours.
I'm sorry. I just want...
I wanna save Kara
and I wanna get back to Maggie.
Maggie is...
- Complicated.
- Yeah.
I had a Maggie, too.
And I think about going back to her
all the time.
Look, Alex,
you seem like
a pretty thoughtful person.
And if you thought it wasn't gonna
work out and had to end it,
I'm sure that reason was valid.
Trust your instincts.
Ray, please, let's talk to him.
Look, you said to let Alex try,
I let her try, she didn't succeed.
So, that's that?
We'll just let these poor,
strangely dressed individuals
lose their one way home?
Look, it's what Winn ordered.
And I'm not in the habit
of defying generals on any Earth.
And what about your family?
Back on Earth-1?
What about them?
You'd be giving up any chance
of ever seeing them again.
Leo,
why are you pushing this?
- Pardon?
- We have fought, and bled,
and sacrificed for this war,
and then these strangers show up,
and you're willing to throw
everything away for them?
The fate of the world is at stake.
So are the lives of their loved ones.
Come on.
Tease me all you want
for being sentimental,
but these heroes would risk everything
for the people they love,
just like I would.
For you.
You know I can't say no
when you look at me like that.
That is why I look at you like that.
We talked to the General,
and after a lot of arguing,
- he agreed.
- We're gonna help you out.
Now, you referenced 100 guards.
I assume most of them
are around the perimeter?
- Correct.
- All right.
We fight through them outside,
we access the main corridor.
What is security like inside the hangar?
I'll do some recon.
So, the entire facility
has meta-human dampeners.
Okay, we can't take that hangar
with no powers, man.
These satellites indicate a control room
off the hangar.
That must be where the dampener is.
Okay, well, we definitely can't take
the main control room with no powers.
It's not like we blend in here.
I think I know how to get in.
I'm allowing this mission
against my better judgment.
You have one hour.
I appreciate it. We all do.
Yeah, I know.
I know what you're thinking.
If you don't make it
through the gateway,
I am not giving you more time.
I will blow that place to kingdom come.
Red light saturation
is complete.
She's cooked.
And you will wake up
stronger than you've ever been.
I love you.
And I love you.
Unfortunately, Miss Danvers,
we need you awake for this procedure.
My cousin,
he'll find you.
Your cousin.
Really?
Fun tidbit.
I fought your cousin once,
in the future.
He is fast.
I'm faster.
- They're starting the surgery.
- I'm working on it. And...
Just have backup power
and it's not enough.
Well, everyone in the building
has been accounted for.
Where might people be hiding?
Take that, you Nazi mother...
Hey, hey, hey.
Come with me if you wanna live.
- Get me to the sun.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- I got her, I got her.
- Okay, okay.
We've gotta go!
I don't believe
Mr. Thawne is done with you yet.
Your papers, Sturmmann.
We don't have papers.
This is a special visit.
Your papers. Now.
Suit yourself,
but I think you better talk to our boss.
As you were.
My God, my apologies, sir.
- Let them through!
Thank you, Mein Führer.
Mein Führer, we were...
We were not expecting you.
Nor was I anticipating
being back so soon.
Thanks to your incompetence.
The Earth-1 doppelgangers,
my doppelganger,
escaped his execution.
Yes. He did.
And?
We are exhausting every possible means
to locate them.
Good.
Would you like us to delay deployment
until we do so?
"Deployment"?
She is inbound and ready.
Doomsday device.
The Wellenreiter
is fully operational
and at the ready, Mein Führer.
Shall we send her through?
As scheduled.
Begin!
The Wellenreiter is on its way.
Hail victory!
Hail victory.
- Report.
- Good news.
The Wellenreiter's
made the transition to this Earth.
Kara is all that matters.
That red sunlight
we're flooding her with,
that's burning off.
And so, pretty soon,
her cells will be so desaturated,
we cannot perform the surgery.
- Fix it.
- I can't.
This is your city.
This is your facility.
So, turn the power back on.
I can't because the system
has been encrypted.
By who?
By Miss Smoak.
Is there anything else
I could help you with?
No, that'll be all.
Very well.
Before I go, I have something for you,
Mein Führer.
A gift
to celebrate your return.
Guard!
Well, I know how much you enjoy
executing rule breakers
and this one has broken many of them.
We discovered that there's a Jewess
handing her rations
to the work camp children.
Strictly against camp rules, of course.
Those children were starving.
Well, this must be hard.
I hear your doppelganger on Earth-1
loved a woman who looks just like this.
Did you really think
I would hand you a loaded weapon
before verifying who you are?
Hey, hey, hey. Are you okay?
No, no, no, you're fine, you're fine.
Just take this and go.
Why are you doing this?
It's the strong's duty
to protect the weak.
Take it and go.
Go!
Clear.
How did it...
Oh.
Barry, we have a problem.
The gateway control's been damaged.
- We can't turn it on?
- We can't turn it on here,
but there should be a manual override
at the platform.
All right, we're gonna have to
fight our way through.
What do you mean "call it back"?
Too late. It's been programmed.
- There's no changing course now.
- You said we'd have an hour!
Yeah, well, I changed my mind.
The team hasn't gone
through the breach yet.
That team has nothing to do with us
or saving our planet!
And everyone who can threaten it is on
the other side of that breach.
They're not coming back through!
- General...
- Leo, enough!
I'm not risking any more time.
We are blowing it up.
Guys, we have a problem.
What kind of problem?
A weapon's heading
to blow up the facility.
A weapon? You mean a missile?
Not exactly.
Felicity Smoak, turn the power back on.
He said...
Felicity!
Turn the power back on.
I'm sorry, Earbard. "Earbard"?
- Eobard.
My God, the future sounds weird.
It's funny.
Sometimes, we think
we're more clever than we are.
Because where I come from,
the history books are filled
with stories of this age of heroes.
Green Arrow.
Black Canary.
The Flash.
And yet, no one,
no one
- has ever heard of "Felicity Smoak."
- Stop!
Stop. Stop.
You came here for me,
so just take me, please.
Please don't hurt anyone else.
Give him the code.
If I do, they'll kill you.
It's fine.
Nobody's gonna die because of me.
Latte, Ada, Jonas,
one-one-nine-zero-zero.
"Latte"? Cute.
Let's go.
In 10 minutes, Red Tornado's gonna
bring down this entire facility
and there's nothing we can do
to stop that robot.
Then we need to reopen the gateway
before that happens.
Barry. Ray.
We know. Stop a flying robot somehow.
Good. The rest of us
will open the breach.
That's the whole plan?
Well, as the Snart we know used to say,
"Make a plan. Execute the plan.
"Expect the plan to go off the rails.
Throw away the plan."
Wow, that is...
That is terrible advice.
I always have a plan,
down to the second,
so nothing ever goes wrong.
No, no, no, the only plan now
is not to leave this Earth without me.
Okay.
Right. Ready for Tornado watch.
Let's do it.
I thought it'd be fun
if we put on our costumes.
Where'd you get the bow and quiver?
The General collects weapons.
Let's go to war.
No one gets to the gateway!
No one!
Here we go!
Okay, we're Nazi-free. Let's go.
Hold on.
That's an automated power cell.
We need to activate it
before using the control console.
I can hot-wire it, no problem.
Then I'll turn on the console.
Oh. You wanna split up? You sure?
It's our most favorable odds.
Let's kick some ass, Jefferson.
Grey, we've got power!
Ray?
A little help here.
Whoa!
- Oh, crap.
Well, that's not very fair.
I'm pinned down!
Grey! No!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::