[light music]
- Who's hungry?
- Hi.
I didn't think you'd be out
of bed already.
- Yeah, there was a car fire
on Route 220.
And I thought I'd bring home
some breakfast,
but this looks a lot better.
Is that blueberry compote?
- Freshly mashed,
and paired with a savory bacon
and baked egg danish.
- The Speed Force.
- Are you okay, Barry?
You're not still feeling
the effects of Psych's attack,
are you?
- Nah, I'm good.
I just...
I had no idea
that you could cook.
- Bobby Flay has got
nothing on Nora.
- You know, it's funny,
cooking is the process of
combining ingredients
with heat to create
molecular change,
but this feels like
so much more.
- Huh.
- Mimosa?
- Sure.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[light music]
Actually, I think I'm good.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- So Chester has
all the satellites
scanning for the new forces.
- There's the Sage Force,
Strength Force,
and now the Still Force.
- Yeah, uh, so far,
no hits on any of
their isotropic signatures.
- Well, it's still good
that you're here with us.
The last time the Forces
attacked you,
you almost died.
- I don't want to burden
anyone.
- No, you're not.
You know, in a weird way,
it's like you've been a part of
this family all along.
[playful music]
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm just, um,
a little worried
about the fact that
my powers are glitching again,
especially since
I just got them back.
- Okay, well,
we can call Caitlin
and have her run
some more tests.
How do you feel now?
- I feel fine, I just...
I don't know what happened.
- Actually, I think
I'm the reason.
Since I'm here now,
I'm increasing your abilities
as best I can.
It may take
some getting used to,
but you'll need it
if the other Forces come back.
[phone buzzes]
- Uh, that's work.
I gotta go.
- I should come with you.
- Oh?
- I'm like your battery now.
If Fuerza and Psych are back...
- Yeah, no, I don't...
having you at a crime scene
might not be a great idea.
- You've already been
hurt once.
I can help boost your speed.
- I know, I know, it just...
it might just be, like,
a traffic accident
or something,
so, um, just let me find out.
- Of course, but don't worry.
If you need me, I'll sense it,
and I'll be there
in a heartbeat.
- Great.
- Okay.
- Um, so I'm gonna go.
- [sighs]
I hope he's okay.
- [clears throat]
[somber music]
- One count
of aggravated assault...
One count
of attempted murder...
Two counts of kidnapping.
It's a good thing you never
lived up to your original name.
- I thought once you started
helping people,
CCPD dropped the investigation.
- Yeah, they did,
they did, but...
the State never officially
dropped its charges,
which means Kristin Kramer
has everything
that she needs to put you
in Iron Heights.
- I'm gonna find Kramer,
and I'm gonna kick her ass.
- No, no, you're not.
Kramer is former
Army Intelligence.
Wherever she goes, heads roll.
Just...
- Look, I'm not some thug
anymore, okay?
I've grown.
- I know that, honey, I do.
Look, I'm one of the people
that you kidnapped.
My advice to you,
as your attorney,
is to lay low.
- Wait, so...
Frost can't do superhero stuff
anymore?
- Nope, not out in the field.
Look, Frost, you're an artist,
okay?
Just take some time off,
chase those canvasses,
create...
just do it all here at S.T.A.R.
Labs, where you're safe.
- I just got a life,
and now you're telling me
I can't live it.
- For a little while, yeah.
Look, Kramer is appointed
by the governor, right?
She doesn't get results,
she's gonna
get reassigned.
- Frost,
I know this isn't fair,
but it's our best option
right now.
- Fine, I'll quarantine here.
[phone buzzing]
- Blazing Bessie Blount,
I just got my first solo
crime scene call.
[excited laughter]
Oh, since Cisco and Kamilla
are away and all,
I'm the only CCPD tech
consultant around.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe it's a 1090.
Maybe it's a 1011.
Oh, snap, it's a 1035.
Frost, I am so sorry but...
- It's fine.
Go have your fun, Peralta.
[tense music]
- Thank you, thank you,
sorry, thank you.
Holy Baby Grogu,
what happened here?
- This delivery van
was full of tech,
and was hit by a perp
in an ice attack.
Apparently some experimental
microchip was stolen.
- Huh, that doesn't
sound so bad.
What's all that?
- The driver.
- [gagging]
- Officers.
[sighs]
Looks like Killer Frost
has been busy.
[suspenseful music]
- I know how this looks.
But there are other criminals
that use ice to commit crimes,
like Leonard Snart.
- Snart was a man with a gun.
Mr. Runk, you're our new
technical consultant
on meta-human affairs,
What's your take on all this?
- Well, um, ma'am, uh...
♪ ♪
Dark matter levels...uh,
Dark matter levels here are...
Oh...
Well, they're...
they're off the charts.
- That doesn't mean it's Frost.
Look, you see the pattern in
these ice crystals here?
They're dendrictic,
like tree branches.
Frost's ice crystals are
usually hexagonal.
- It's Killer Frost,
Officer Allen.
And you seem to know
a lot about her powers.
- Yeah, I've worked
her crime scenes,
and she's never killed anyone.
- Until now, apparently.
- Officer Allen is
our department's
top forensics examiner, ma'am.
If there's any evidence here
that we can use,
he will find it.
- And Killer Frost
is still out there.
Captain, I hate to pull rank,
but Governor Williamson
gave me special authority
in order to address this city's
long-standing
metahuman problems.
We need to keep
public safety in mind.
- Agreed.
- Good.
Because I'm going
to ask the DA's office
to issue a warrant
for Killer Frost's arrest.
I'm gonna need you
and your officers for backup.
- I'll alert
the Meta-human Task Force.
- Thank you.
I need to update
the Governor's office.
Excuse me.
- Joe,
you can't be serious.
We all know Frost
didn't do this.
- What am I supposed
to say, Barry?
"Yes, Frost did spend
the evening with Caitlin."
- You can't give Kramer
her alibi without admitting
that you've talked
to a fugitive.
Dang, that's
a real catch-22.
[mimics echo]
[tense music]
I'm sorry, my timing on that
was terrible.
I'm just gonna go tell Frost
what's going on.
- We can't let Kramer
arrest Frost.
- You don't think I know that?
But we gotta follow orders.
- So what are
we supposed to do?
Frost can't lay low forever.
- The only thing
we can do, Barry:
find the real meta-human
that did this.
- All right.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[whimsical music]
♪ ♪
- Huh.
That looks painful.
- Chuck, said you had something
important to tell Frost?
- Right, okay...
Well...
there's a new ice meta in town
who killed
an Ivo Labs employee,
but Kristin Kramer
thinks that it was you,
so she kind of ordered Joe
to put the Meta Task Force
on alert
while she gets a warrant for
your arrest.
- What?
Why didn't Joe
and Barry stop her?
- Because, technically,
she's their boss.
She's also
a very intimidating person.
But don't worry.
We're doing everything
we can to get this cleared up.
Me and Caitlin
are even trying to fix
one of H.R.'s transmogrifiers
to work for you.
- Thanks, Runk.
- Look,
is there anything else
I can do?
I mean, you know,
if you need to talk
or vent or get the weight
off your shoulders,
Chester P. is all ears, I...
- Go tech-out, Chuck.
We'll be fine.
She's starting cardio anyway.
- Right, right, okay.
[tense music]
- Okay, he's gone.
What's the plan?
- I'm gonna do twelve miles.
- Five years in Iron Heights
over here.
You think I can't tell
when someone's lying?
Plus there's no way
you'd stay put here.
You're going after Kramer.
♪ ♪
No, not that.
You're going after
this new ice-meta yourself?
Yeah,
I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not.
- Wha...so you're gonna
do this alone?
What about the rest
of Team Flash?
- I need to handle this myself.
There are places
that Team Flash can't go.
Hell, I used to work
at some of them.
And you aren't gonna
say a thing.
- I used to be a freakin' car
thief, Frost,
I know how to talk
to criminals.
- I am not looking
for a criminal.
I'm looking for a killer.
You want to help me?
Cover my ass.
If I need backup, I'll call.
Promise.
♪ ♪
- You must see a lot
of strange crime scenes
working in this city.
- Yeah, yeah...
this case is another one.
Usually, I'd find dark matter
dispersed evenly
throughout meta-produced ice.
But from what I can tell,
this ice has dark matter.
It's just...
only on the surface.
- What would cause that?
- I don't know,
but I'm gonna find out.
- I'll let you work.
- Thanks.
[sighs]
[static]
Have you been there
the whole time?
- She admires you.
- [stammering]
Kramer?
Okay, well, look...
she could be back any second,
not to mention
a dozen other officers, so...
But I thought you were gonna
spend the day with Iris?
- Well, I told her I needed
to stretch my legs.
- Okay.
- You know,
it's just like you said,
the ice is different.
The particles inside all this,
I can feel them, they're...
compacted, constrained.
- Like on a molecular level.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- You know what, I...um,
I need to get this back
to my lab, if I could...
no, hey, hey, hey.
If I can figure out why
this ice is different,
it might lead to the real...
♪ ♪
- Right, I'm on my way.
- Allen?
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Um, I'm...I'm, uh,
tracking footprints
from our suspect.
They led me out here, so.
- Where?
- What?
Oh, the...uh, yeah, no,
they're hard to detect
without one of
these little infrared...
♪ ♪
- Cutting edge tech.
- Yeah.
- Impressive.
Keep up the good work.
♪ ♪
[static]
- I like her.
- Yeah, um...
Look, I really appreciate your
help, but I got it from here,
so I'll see you back
at the loft, okay?
- Of course.
I understand.
- [sighs]
[tense music]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- The place was a lot
more lively when I worked here.
- [scoffs]
Here for the ambience?
- Looking for a meta
who likes ice.
- Ah, a missing relative.
- Ha-ha, funny guy.
Look, I used to do your job.
I know a good bar slinger
keeps his ears open
more than any of these losers.
- I might know a few things.
- 'Cause you're a bartender,
who tends bar.
- [chuckles]
- I'm...looking for intel.
Something was taken
from Ivo Labs this morning.
Do you know anything
about that?
- No,
but I do know a bit about...
science.
If you take a hydrometer to
a bottle of Plymouth gin,
you'll find that it has
a specific gravity...
0.94...
which means, a liqueur
like, say,
crème de noyaux here,
will sink right...
to the bottom.
Ergo, the secret to
the smoothest cocktail...
is density.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- That is...
not bad.
- The famous Killer Frost
likes my work.
I'll call "The Citizen."
- It's just Frost now.
- Oh.
♪ ♪
Turn that up.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
- So in light of the violence
at Ivo Labs this morning,
the Central City Police
Department is offering
a $100,000 reward
for information
leading to the arrest
of the meta criminal
known as Killer Frost.
If you have any knowledge
on the whereabouts of
Killer Frost, immediately call
the Meta-Human Task Force
tip line.
- Crap.
- [grunts]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- I had him.
- Great.
I guess I wasted
an IPA then.
[quirky music]
- ♪ Hot in ♪
♪ Hot in ♪
♪ So hot in herre ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
[funky music]
♪ It's getting hot in here ♪
- Take a picture,
why don't you?
- [scoffs]
Whatever.
See you around...sometime.
- ♪ It's getting hot in here ♪
- Hey, Frost.
There's a new meta in town.
He's got a thing
for experimental tech.
Keeps it all at the old
Wieringo complex off Route 119.
If he's the guy,
you're gonna find him there.
- What's that gonna cost me?
- How about a second visit?
Just ask for Mark.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Let it just fall out ♪
♪ I like it when you uh-uh ♪
♪ ♪
- Dude, the 24-hour news cycle
picked up
on Kramer's "John Wick"
parabellum move.
[laughs]
That's a great movie.
"Yeah, I'm thinking I'm back."
- I'm thinking
we need to focus.
Frost is safe at S.T.A.R. Labs
right now,
but Kramer's
not gonna back down,
not until we find proof.
[screen trills]
Here, check this out.
Look at these cryo-membranes.
Speed Force was right.
It's way past compacted.
Now if we could
just figure out why.
- Barry, these computers
are way slower than you are.
I mean, this much data?
It's gonna take all night.
[gasps]
Cool, but scary.
- I can feel
how frustrated you are.
How can I help?
- Look, it's okay,
we've got this.
- Totally, I mean, we are,
like the Power Rangers
of forensic science, basically,
But the Speed...
Nora here...
is omnipotent, omnipresent,
and omniscient.
She's like our Zordon.
Say, can
white hole singularities
actually exist...
without mass?
- Yes.
- I knew it, I knew.
Barry, we don't have
to crunch data all night.
Nora can do it right now.
- It's our job to find answers.
- Of course, but, uh,
y'know, Nora is
a literal force of nature.
- He's right, just let me...
- No.
[clears throat]
No, we need to do this
ourselves.
- Maybe just this once?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[panting]
Anybody else taste pennies?
It tastes like there's 78 cents
in my mouth.
- Barry, what did you do?
We've lost everything.
- What did I do?
I didn't lose the data that was
supposed to clear Frost.
You did...by being here.
- I was only trying to help.
- Okay, I didn't ask for any.
- Guys, maybe we should
take five?
- Barry, you helped me
be reborn,
and now
you're keeping me safe.
of course I want to help you.
- I keep telling you.
I didn't ask for help.
Look, you chose me
to be the hero.
So, let me be the hero.
♪ ♪
Sorry about that.
You know what I meant, right?
[radio static]
[tense music]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Korber,
hey, what's going on?
- Kramer's got a location
on Killer Frost.
They're gonna bring her in.
[line trilling]
- I'm calling Frost.
She's not picking up.
♪ ♪
Hey, Allegra.
Yeah, is Frost with you?
This is an emergency.
- Sorry, Chuck, she's here,
but she's going full Amazon
with her workout.
What's the message?
- Okay, tell her
Kramer's making moves,
so Frost needs to stay put.
- Got it.
♪ ♪
C'mon, pick up, pick up,
pick up.
♪ ♪
[eerie tones]
[electronic trilling]
- Seriously?
[knock at door]
- CCPD, you're surrounded.
Caitlin Snow, I have
a warrant for your arrest.
- What's the charge?
- Kramer to Task Force command,
hold your positions
around the perimeter,
and prepare for
prisoner transfer.
Are you alone, Dr. Snow?
- Yes, but I...
I think there's been
a mistake.
Joe?
What is this?
- Who are you?
- I'm Rene Carpenter.
I'm a clinician
with the M.H.E. team.
- Mental health evaluation?
- Yes, ma'am,
it's standard procedure.
I'm just here to help.
- Joe, what is going on?
- Would you turn around please?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Killer Frost,
you're under arrest
for aggravated assault,
attempted murder,
and two counts of kidnapping.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney...
[knock at door]
- Okay, so I just talked
to the D.A.'s office.
Kramer didn't find
anything incriminating
in your apartment,
so once your blood tests
come back negative
for the meta-gene,
they're gonna be forced
to release you from custody.
- Great,
this is the first time
I'm relieved that Frost and I
are in different bodies.
- Yeah.
- How did she know
to come after me?
- Uh...
[laughs]
it was an anonymous tip,
which means either somebody
got very lucky, or...
- Or...somebody out there
knows that Frost
used to be you.
I'm sorry, Caitlin,
but Kramer wouldn't tell me
where the Task Force
was headed,
and by the time I knew,
it was too late.
- It's okay, Joe.
This is not on you.
- This ain't how law
enforcement's supposed to work.
I'm gonna go talk to Kramer.
Look, I think
the next step is...
[phone buzzes]
Oh, uh...
Frost, where are you?
- Across the street.
You and Caity get away
from the north wall.
- [stammering]
North wall?
Uh-uh, okay, uh...
I think that Frost is about
to try and bust you out.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Put her on speakerphone.
- Okay.
- Frost, what the hell
are you doing?
- Getting you out of there.
- You promised me
you would stay put.
- Yeah, well, I lied.
Now take cover.
- Oh!
- Don't you dare.
- You're in there
because of me.
- I'm here because Kramer
has some sort of grudge
against you, okay?
But you're innocent
and so am I,
so we just need to let this
play out, okay?
I'll be fine, I promise.
- Yes, yes.
Frost, she's right.
Look, I know this system.
Just let me handle this.
They have no case
against Caitlin.
Honey, please.
Stand down.
- This isn't fair.
You shouldn't have
to go through this.
- Neither should you, okay.
When Kramer looks at you,
all she sees
are the mistakes you've made.
She doesn't see how much pain
you've gone through,
or how much you've grown
because of it.
You're a good person, Frost,
and, human or meta-human,
you deserve the chance
to prove it.
- Human.
That's it.
Thanks, Caity.
- Thanks for what?
- I figured out who framed us.
Now I'm gonna go
figure out why.
- No, Frost!
Hey...
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Sergeant Kramer,
we need to talk.
- I'm in a bit of a hurry,
Captain.
Is there a problem?
- Yes, there is.
You mobilized my task force
to harass someone...
who, from all accounts, is
innocent...off of a phone call.
There's no way in hell I would
have authorized that.
- Captain.
- Sergeant.
We're not supposed to work
that way.
- That's your point of view,
and I respect that.
But I also respect
the evidence.
Dr. Snow matches Killer Frost
in 80 nodal points
of facial recognition.
Their known whereabouts
over the last few months
line up perfectly.
And her prints were
all over that delivery van.
What's your conclusion?
- I promise you,
Caitlin Snow and Killer Frost
are not the same person.
And even if they were,
I doubt that
they wouldn't wear gloves
as they went
on a killing spree.
This evidence,
this anonymous phone call?
It's like someone is trying
to frame Frost.
- Okay, then who?
- I don't know,
but Frost helps keep
this city safe.
Hell, she's saved my life...
more than once.
- She's still a criminal.
Captain, you seem like
a good cop,
and I know that Dr. Snow
is a friend of your family.
But if you really want to
honor your badge,
you need to think about what is
truly best for the public good.
If you'll excuse me.
[tense music]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Nora's still holed up
in the guest room.
I know she's a force of nature,
but as crazy as it sounds,
there's a person forming
inside of her, too.
- Iris,
whatever she is,
she's not human.
She's the Speed Force.
She powers my abilities.
You don't know what it's like,
seeing...
someone like that,
eating breakfast at our table.
- That's why you don't want to
call her Nora.
Maybe I shouldn't have invited
her to stay here.
- No, it was...
it was the right thing to do.
She needs us to keep her safe,
and protecting her now
is the least I can do.
[laughs]
What's wrong with me?
- Nothing.
♪ ♪
Nothing, Barry, it's just...
I think for you, she's this
all powerful cosmic entity,
but she's changed.
I don't know how or why,
but...
whatever she was before,
she's even more now.
Do you remember when I...
[sighs]
First came back from college
after freshman year?
- Yeah, I was living
in my own apartment,
and you moved back in with Joe.
- Yeah, it was great,
for a while.
I was waitressing
and, um, making tips,
trying to write
my dissertation,
but, after about a week,
me and Dad
started butting heads
over the stupidest things.
Me coming in late at night,
him watching sports
all day Saturday
when I was trying to study...
I mean, all we did was argue.
- I remember, Joe told me how
bad he felt through all that.
- Yeah.
And do you want to know why?
Because when I left that fall,
I really was his baby girl.
But, when I got back,
we were both adults.
Different habits,
different schedules.
We weren't just...
father and daughter anymore.
[sentimental music]
Finding a new normal,
between the two of you,
is gonna take some time,
and it may get pretty painful
along the way.
That's how relationships grow.
[phone buzzes]
- It's Chester.
He's got a lead
on the new ice meta.
[suspenseful music]
I gotta...
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- What'd you find?
- Okay, so I somehow managed
to salvage some of the ice data
that we lost.
Remember how the dark matter
at the crime scene
had compacted membranes?
- Yeah?
- It's because it wasn't
dark matter at all.
It was a half-life variant.
- Artificial dark matter?
That means the killer
that we're after isn't a meta.
- They're human.
Somebody's been fooling us
this whole time.
- Somebody who's an expert at
science and...
knows that Frost and Caitlin
used to be one person.
We should ask Frost if...
Wait, where is Frost, anyway?
- Fine, I lied, okay?
She went looking for our baddie
by herself.
- Frost went full "Fugitive."
- If this new killer is trying
to frame Frost,
they might come after her next.
- I know, it's my fault.
She made me promise
not to tell anyone,
but I-I should have
said something.
- Nah, it's okay, let's just...
let's focus on finding her
before it's too late.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- That was fast.
- So, Mark...
give me one good reason why
I shouldn't live up to my name.
- [sighs]
Well, because Caitlin
wouldn't like it.
[suspenseful music]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Thirsty?
[scoffs]
♪ ♪
All right, I know
that you're angry,
'cause I know all about you
and you know nothing about me.
So go ahead.
[satisfied sigh]
Ask away.
- How did you know?
- Oh, that you and Caitlin
were related?
I'm an observant guy,
sue me.
In studying you,
I also traced your movements.
Every fight, every battle.
- Stalk much?
- Honestly, finding out that
you and Caitlin seem to
come and go
interchangeably was...
well, let's call it more
of a happy accident.
Did come in handy, though.
- So you could frame us?
That's why you sent me to
that empty warehouse,
which wasn't really empty,
was it?
- Very good.
See, I already had the chip.
I just needed one final thing:
A neurogenic scan of you
to perfectly replicate
your powers.
- Neurogenic?
That's quite a fancy word
for a thief.
- Uh, yeah, maybe
because I'm not a thief.
I simply took back
what was mine.
- The microchip?
You built it.
So you worked at Ivo Labs.
- I'm a cryo-geneticist.
The best.
- Oh, let me guess, your former
employers didn't agree?
- Well, they said that the...
experiments I was conducting
were...
[chuckles]
Inhuman.
So they got a warrant to put me
in a cozy Iron Heights cell
for the rest of my life.
Unlike you, I've been smart
enough to avoid capture.
I'd rather die than end up
in some warm prison.
Have you ever even heard
of hypothermia?
[laughs]
It doesn't matter.
When I was nine,
I went ice skating up
on Central Lake.
It was Christmas,
so the ice...
should have been thick enough,
but I fell through.
♪ ♪
I was submerged, body and soul,
for over 15 minutes.
And at first, the cold
was terrifying,
but then
after 20 seconds or so,
you know,
it got warm...
hot, even.
And then I died.
- And the paramedics saved you,
and now you're obsessed
with refrigerators, I get it.
- No, you don't.
The ice,
it holds the power of
life and death.
A power all too clearly
wasted on you, Killer Frost.
Oh, I've watched you for years,
admiring your abilities,
wondering what I could do
with them.
All I needed was for Ivo
to move my microchip
out of deep freeze, so that
I could steal it back again...
and then combine it with
that pesky scan of you.
And now...
I'm as powerful as you are.
- Bring it on, Mark,
if that even is your real
name.
- Oh, Mark Blaine.
Yeah, that was my name.
But you can call me...
Chillblaine.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
I kind of like this.
[grunts and pants]
♪ ♪
[panting]
- You fight like a boy.
- [grunts]
- What the hell did you do?
- Looks like
somebody's snow blind.
[suspenseful music]
- Guys,
satellites just picked up
one hell of a cryokinetic spike
on the southside of Keystone.
- Frost said she might be going
somewhere she used to work.
- O'Shaughnessy's.
Let's go.
- Wh...you still
want me to come?
After I lied to you?
- Someone's gotta convince
Frost to come home.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- To think,
you have so much strength,
so much power,
but so little imagination.
I guess that just means
I'm a better meta than you.
- Actually, Chillblaine...
- [winces]
♪ ♪
- You're not a meta at all.
- [groans]
- There's one thing
your bracelets can't copy.
- [screams and winces]
- Ice healing.
- [groans]
- Frost, you okay?
- Yeah, I'm...okay,
it's just a scratch.
I could use a little help
with this though.
- Yeah.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Thanks.
They broke you down?
- I tried, honest.
- It's okay,
'cause the only other person
I trusted today
just tried to kill me, so...
arriving with backup...
I'll let it slide.
- So who is he?
- He calls himself
"Chillblaine."
- Wow, I'm glad Cisco's
not around to hear that one.
- Chillblaine
didn't just commit a crime
against good taste.
He also killed
the Ivo Labs driver,
and I've got his confession
on tape.
- That means
you're in the clear.
[sirens wailing]
- Killer Frost,
come out with
your hands raised.
You have two minutes to comply.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[sirens whooping]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Flash, there's a whole squad
of CCPD cars
outside of your location.
- Yeah, we're trying
to handle it, Chester.
- Killer Frost,
there is nowhere to go.
We have you surrounded.
You have one minute.
- So what?
Let 'em try.
- Or we could try calming down.
Chillblaine here
is the real killer.
So I'll go out.
I'll hand him over.
I'll let them know
you're innocent.
- Guys,
I may not have killed
that person today,
but I'm not innocent.
I have to go out there myself.
- What?
- Frost,
Kramer has a warrant
for all the crimes
you committed
before joining Team Flash.
You get arrested,
you're facing hard time,
if there's a conviction.
- Uh-uh, that ain't happening.
We can hide you somewhere
while we figure this out.
- Right, then you're harboring
a fugitive.
I can't let you do that.
Guys, before today,
I never paid for
any of the bad things I did.
- Because you were
out saving the world.
- And I thought
that was enough too.
But, if I'm gonna prove
that I've really changed,
then I have to own up to it,
as...
painful as that might be.
- Frost,
I've been to Iron Heights.
Jails do not
make better people.
They're hell.
You cannot do this.
- I think I have to.
You're not gonna try
and stop me, are you?
- Not unless you want me to.
- I don't.
- Frost, please.
What if you don't come back?
- Don't worry, I will.
- No...
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Time's up, go.
- I'm coming out.
- Guys...
is Frost really doing this?
- It's her choice, Chester.
Something tells me
it's the right one.
♪ ♪
[shackles clinking]
- All right, thanks.
Okay, bye.
That was Cecile.
Caitlin is back home.
Now she's trying
to get Frost out on bail
before the sentencing hearing.
- What about a trial?
- Frost is pleading guilty
to all her old crimes,
so whatever happens to her next
is up to the judge.
- Well, at least Chillblaine
will be in Iron Heights
for a very long time.
- Yeah.
- How does Caitlin
feel about it all?
- I'm not sure.
I think she was
just getting used to
Frost having her own body.
I know how hard it can be,
when a relationship
like that changes in a snap.
[whoosh]
- Speaking of which,
I should get ready for work.
- Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt.
- No, it's...it's fine.
- It's okay,
I could feel you listening.
And I-I'm glad.
I...
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten
so upset at you earlier.
- No, it's okay.
I tried to fit in somewhere
I didn't belong.
Being here, in your home,
with you and Iris?
It's not my place.
- Yes, it is.
Look, I know...
how much things
have changed between us.
You're not the same
as the Speed Force
I'm used to interacting with.
And I...
I can't expect you to be
the way you were.
It's not fair to you.
- To either of us.
- Yeah, you're something...
else now, something new.
And it's something I'd like
to get to know better, Nora.
♪ ♪
And, look, no more glitching.
- I'm almost fully healed.
- So now we can take on
all three forces together.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.