- Happy birthday
- Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
I don't care if we need to see
every fucking young girl
in this fucking town
in the next few weeks.
Look, I'll make it simple.
We need her young.
We need her hot.
We need her now.
How the old bitch has been able
to stick around for this long...
That's the fucking mystery to me.
Oh, Oscar winner, my ass.
When was that back in the 30s?
What, for King Kong?
No, I don't give a
fuck what we promised her.
This is network TV,
not a fucking charity.
Find me somebody new.
Now.
Hey, did you know that a woman's
fertility starts to
decrease about the age of 25?
How old is Jennifer?
You better get busy.
It's like when you see
someone fart on screen.
People just love that.
I mean, that's just the way it is.
So you know what I mean?
People are just people.
And I have to give people what they want.
That's what keeps the shareholders happy.
And people always ask for something new.
Renewal is inevitable.
And at 50, well...
it stops.
What stops?
What?
Um, you know, the um...
The um...
Oh, George!
Oh, oh!
I'm sorry, I gotta run.
Harvey!
George, those ratings are insane!
You're a genius!
Oh, what a mess. You're a genius.
That's why you've been drinking.
Oh, that's hilarious.
Well, it's your lucky day, Miss Sparkle,
because we have
X-rayed you from head to toe,
and you don't have so
much as a cracked molar.
So, you are good to go.
Uh, vaccination, okay.
Not going on a vacation.
By the way, I just want to say:
my wife is a huge fan.
Um...
blood type...
Oh, hey, it's your birthday.
Happy bir—
Oh, uh, that's an emergency, I'm sorry.
I, uh, have to....
Have a... um....
Bye.
One moment.
There's just one last exam to perform.
I thought he said I was good to go.
Is there a problem?
No, it's perfect.
You're a good candidate.
I mean, you're good to go.
I wish you the best.
Lizzie?
Lizzie Sparkle?
Oh my God, I can't believe it.
Fred!
Fred, from 10th grade homeroom!
Oh, Fred, of course.
You haven't changed a bit.
You're still the most beautiful
girl in the whole wide world.
You know, I followed your career.
What a success.
I mean, wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
Hey...
Why don't we go out
maybe for a drink sometime
now that we're,
you know, reconnected?
Um...
Oh, of course, I'm stupid.
You're super busy.
You know what?
Why don't you give me your card?
I mean, you never know.
Um, sure, what I...
This'll do. Oh...
Don't look at my cholesterol levels.
They're a disaster.
Oh, God.
What was that?
There.
Now you've got it.
Have you ever dreamt of a
better version of yourself?
Younger.
More beautiful.
More perfect.
One single injection unlocks your DNA,
starting a new cellular division that
will release another version of yourself.
This is...
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you.
And everything is you.
This is simply a
better version of yourself.
You just have to share.
One week for one
and one week for the other.
A perfect balance of seven days each.
The one and only thing not to forget:
You can't escape from yourself.
Yes.
Hello.
I'd like to order.
Address.
1057 Beverly Canyon.
Write this down.
35 North Byron Alley.
35 North...
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you,
and everything is you.
This is simply...
a better version of yourself.
Hello.
Thanks.
We'll let you know by next week.
Thank you so much.
I'm just dying to get the part.
Great dancer.
Too bad her boobs aren't in the
middle of her face instead of that nose.
Next!
Looks like everything sure is
in the right place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
I'm Sue.
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue,
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue, Sue.
Where is she?
What a gorgeous little angel.
You're hired.
We want a show that's just like you.
Beautiful and happy.
People want to be happy.
We air in two weeks,
so let's get to work.
I'm gonna let you organize
the rest with my assistant, uh...
- Uh...
- Isabella?
Is-is-is...
Who has time to say that?
We're gonna make you Cindy.
It's shorter, it's better.
So, I'm gonna let you
organize everything else with Cindy.
Oh, um, before you go,
I just have to mention a...
small scheduling issue.
I have to be...
out of town every other week...
to take care of my mother...
who's very sick.
I want you for this show.
And we will work around
any mother, brother,
fucking sick puppy
you need to take care of.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Gorgeous, with a pure heart.
People are gonna love that.
Perfect.
So you jump out,
touch your elbows,
head down, contract.
And five, six, seven, eight, elbows.
Oh, there she is!
Where have you been?
We've all been wanting to have a
drink with you for your departure.
Anyway...
We all chipped in...
and we got you just a little
something to keep you busy.
It's French.
My wife, she's very inspired.
Oh, I love my wife.
Oops, I gotta run.
But it's always great to see you.
The antelope and the deer moving about
are hunt through the—
...98 with remote.
I cannot believe the
incredible price for $49.98.
Look at the quality of this thing!
This thing is sturdy.
Beautiful!
You can listen to
your music at home, shoppers.
For $49.98, I'll take one myself.
Put it right there.
Hold that one for
me, that one's mine.
How can you ever—
God dammit!
I mean, come on!
I haven't slept in three nights!
Open up.
God dammit!
When you gonna open the—
I, uh... Sorry.
I thought that Ms. Sparkle...
She moved out.
I'm the new tenant.
Sue.
Oliver.
You wanted to complain about something?
Oliver?
What?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think it's, like, awesome when
there's stuff going on in the building...
you know what I mean?
Um...
I'm actually...
quite handy if you ever need...
need me to be of aid in any way.
I got a sack of tools, and a...
and a big hammer.
You know what I mean.
Anyways, I live right here,
so you know where to find me.
Anytime.
Day or night.
Later.
Hi everybody.
I'm Sue and it's time to pump it up.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Thank you so much everybody.
I'll see you next week.
And in the meantime,
take care of yourself.
Where is she?
There she is!
Wonderful, wonderful.
That's what I'm talking about!
Yes!
I won't be out late, so just wait for me.
Don't eat too fast.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'll be right back.
What did you do?
You seem even more
beautiful than before.
Yes.
Yes, hi.
This is Elizabeth Sparkle.
I'm 503.
Yes.
Yes, hi.
There's been a slight...
misuse of the substance.
A few extra hours
were accidentally used...
causing, um...
an alteration.
So I'm just looking for
the procedure to reverse it.
What has been used on one
side is lost on the other side.
There is no going back.
No, I don't know what she was thinking.
And obviously she was drunk.
Remember there is no she and you.
You are one.
Respect the balance and you
won't have any more inconveniences.
Sue!
Sue?
I just saw you on TV.
Holy moly.
Makes me want to join your class.
Hey, you don't give
private lessons, do you?
Hey, um...
What about a
drink at my place tonight?
Come on, don't be shy.
I see you standing behind
the door there, gorgeous.
All right, take your
time, but it's a date.
♪ You know, pump it up ♪
♪ You got to pump it up ♪
What can I get you?
Mocha Latte.
It's long, isn't it?
Excuse me?
Seven days.
Did you follow me here?
I was just curious...
to find out how
things were going for you.
Each time you feel a little more...
lonely.
Don't you think?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
It gets harder each time...
to remember that you...
still deserve to exist.
That this part of yourself...
is still worth something,
that you...
still matter.
Has she started yet?
Eating away at you?
Fuck!
Watch out!
What?
Hey!
Move!
You're still the most beautiful girl
in the whole wide world.
Hello?
Hi, Fred.
It's Lizzie.
Hello?
Sorry, I mean, I'm in shock.
- Oh.
- Wow.
Wow, wow.
I thought I'd never
hear from you again after...
Oh gosh, no, no, not at all.
I just, I've just...
been really busy lately.
So listen...
I was thinking that...
maybe we could get
together and grab a drink.
Are you still there?
Sorry, I-I'm in shock again.
I could book Luigi's, at eight?
Eight at Luigi's it is.
I will see you tonight.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
And we're back!
Welcome back to Who Knows!
Father Judy, are you ready?
Well now you've seen the scales.
Who Knows is the show
where you keep your eye on—
Hi everybody.
Hi!
Okay, here we go everyone.
Clear the set please.
First positions, thank you.
Roll cameras.
And in three, two, one.
And squat, squat, squat.
Circle those hips.
Contract, contract, contract,
contract, contract, contract.
Head between your legs.
Cut.
I'm sorry, I thought I, uh...
thought I— I—
I just got distracted.
Not a problem, let's
get right back to it.
Back to one please.
Sorry, it's the control room now.
The director said he saw something
bizarre on the monitor.
Bring up the replay on camera two.
Camera two.
Forward.
Can I have my dressing gown?
Sorry, it's in your dressing room.
Well then go and get it.
Let's just take this frame by frame.
I need five minutes.
- Yes.
- This balance is not working.
I barely have any time to enjoy myself
while she wastes seven days
stuffing her face in front of the TV.
Remember there is no she and you.
You are—
Hello, everybody.
What's happening?
Where is everybody?
The taping's been canceled.
What, why?
Sue.
Harvey wants to see you
in his office immediately.
Okay.
I'll go change and—
No, he said now.
I'll get right to the point.
We can't keep you on the morning show.
But why?
I just started.
Ratings are through the roof.
We started at 42.
Now we're up to like...
216.
It's phenomenal.
People love you.
They adore you.
They want more and more and more of you.
That is why we have decided...
that we want you to host...
the New Year's Eve show.
You mean the...
The network's biggest show.
50 million viewers live.
You can't go higher than that.
That's gonna be intense.
We only have a few
months to pull it off, so...
are you in?
If you don't open the
door when opportunity knocks,
you won't get another chance.
You of all people know this.
Just one more day and
then I have a whole week off.
We can switch.
We're doing the cover of Vogue.
Just one more day, okay?
Yes.
She didn't respect the balance.
She's stealing more
and more time from me,
completely without
consideration of the consequences.
She's a selfish bitch.
Would you like to stop?
Stop?
You are the matrix.
If you are not satisfied,
you can put an end to the experience
and go back to being
just you on your own.
Would you like to stop?
Will it go back to the way it was before?
What has been
transferred won't come back,
but you can stop the
experience as of now.
Would you like to stop?
To go back to being just you on your own?
No.
No, no, no.
I can't stop.
She just...
I...
The balance just needs to be respected.
So respect it.
Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it, stop it.
You are the winner!
Well, Bob, congratulations,
you've won $25,000.
Now you have one final chance to
answer a simple question
in our big question
round and play for $250,000.
And you'll have just 45
seconds to come to a conclusion.
Answer correctly
as best you can...
Just a little something to keep you busy.
Fuck.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, she is here.
The superstar of the moment, Sue.
Are you ready?
Let's welcome her, Sue.
You popped up out of nowhere on
our screens like a tornado.
I don't think anybody was
really prepared for this whirlwind .
It all started with the morning show
and rumor has it that you are
up for Tom Grant's next movie.
Wait, just a moment.
I'm being told that you are going to host
the New Year's Eve show.
Can you confirm this?
Yes, that's right.
"Yes, that's right."
Oh my God, that is huge news.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
Where are you from?
How did you get discovered?
I want— We want to know everything.
Well, I mean, there's...
really not very much to tell.
I'm just a girl from a...
very small town in Indiana.
I'm sure that
you've never heard of it.
In fact, it's not even a town.
I'm not sure you could
really even call it a village.
It's a farm, perhaps?
But ever since I can remember,
it has always been my
dream to be on screen.
This is my dream.
As a child, I used to
put on shows for my family.
Mm, your family.
How sweet.
So, everyone is aware...
that you replaced Elizabeth Sparkle.
And no doubt about it, you stepped in,
you turned up the volume,
and you rocked their world.
Were you a fan of her show?
Um...
Well...
Well, I can't, uh...
I can't really say that I
actually watched her show.
You do know that we're not exactly
from the same generation.
And you have to admit, it
was a bit old-fashioned.
Jurassic Fitness, really.
"Jurassic Fitness"?
It needed a change.
I'll fucking show you.
You wanna see
some Jurassic Fitness?
You want it?
Come on, come get your
fucking Jurassic Fitness!
But my mother was a huge fan of hers.
So, every morning...
rain or shine...
Sparkle Your Life was on TV.
So, in a way, I grew up with her.
Whether I liked it or not.
I guess that's why you could say
we have some sort of connection.
"Some sort of connection"?
You wouldn't exist without me.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
It is time, ladies and
gentlemen, for our final question.
The question that we ask each
and every one of our guests.
Okay.
Would you share one of your
little beauty secrets with us?
Just one little trick of yours that
helps you look so incredibly stunning.
I mean, look at you.
- I don't know, uh...
- Say it!
Say it!
- Let me think.
- Say it!
Tell them who your
little beauty secret is!
- I guess...
- Why don't we just show them right here.
Here's your little beauty secret.
I guess I just try to be myself.
To be sincere and
grateful for all that I have.
And to always remember
to lead with my heart.
Oh, I'm here at the sweetheart center.
We'll be back in a minute.
I just, oh, I try to be myself.
Stop it!
Stop it.
You're taking it from me.
That's your little secret.
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
You have to control yourself!
I can't go back to her.
Gross! Old! Fat!
Destructive!
Coming to bed?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Yes.
Hi, hi, this is emergency.
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
Hello?
It's fucking 503.
Yes.
I'm telling you, this is urgent.
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
It means you've reached the end.
What do you mean the end?
You've drained it all out.
If you want more, you must
let the fluid regenerate.
Tell me how to do it.
I need to stabilize myself right now.
You simply have to switch.
Excuse me?
The switch reboots the
fluid secretion process
so you can continue to
enjoy the experience.
No, no, no, no, no.
I can't switch, I can't.
Especially not now.
There is no other option.
Sue?
Babe?
You all right?
Stressed out about tomorrow?
Babe?
Sue? Is something wrong?
You a little cranky
because of your lady business?
Sue, open the door.
Come on, Sue.
It's not funny, I need to take a piss.
Sue, open the door.
Open the door, Sue, come on.
Sue!
Open the door! Come on!
Sue, open the door.
Sue, open the door!
What the fuck?
Get the fuck out!
Who's this? Who the fuck is this?
Leave me alone!
What the fuck?
Yes.
It's 503.
I want to stop.
Are you sure? Once you
stop, you can't go back.
I want to stop!
I want to fucking stop!
We'll deliver.
Sue, I was—
Fuck off!
Are you sure?
Once you stop, you can't go back.
You will simply remain on your own.
Just on your own.
Shut the fuck up!
Oh shit...
I can't...
I can't do this.
I need you.
Because...
I need myself.
We...
You gotta get ready.
It's our big night.
Come on. They're gonna love you so much.
Come on.
You're the only lovable part of me.
You have to come back.
You have to come back!
Come back!
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Oh, don't!
Got an hour and a half for makeup and hair.
Then we gotta get you in the fitting room,
get you your dress.
After that, we'll have one final test
on stage for lighting and sound.
Then we have a bit of downtime
before the show starts.
You got it?
You good?
Okay, let's go.
The dress!
Wonderful!
Perfect!
There you go...
It's good.
Can we get the dance lights?
I'm gonna be right back, sorry.
They need to see you on
stage to set the lights.
Have you ever dreamt
of a better version of yourself?
More beautiful, more perfect.
Sue?
Yes, let me meet you there.
Okay, so I'll wait for you on stage.
Sue?
Let me introduce you to the shareholders.
They have been dying to meet you.
Is everything okay?
So smile.
That's what we want tonight.
Pretty girls should always smile.
Feathers, feathers, feathers!
Hey, you ready for tonight?
I just need a better version of myself.
Please give me a better
version of myself, please.
Please!
Come on!
Looks like everything sure is in the
right place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
Pretty girls should always smile.
At last, we're starting to worry.
Hurry up, you're up in five.
There she is, so beautiful.
We love you.
This is where you belong.
And you'll always belong here.
We can't do it without you.
We could never do without you.
You're irreplaceable!
Girls, come on, let's go.
What are we waiting for?
Alright, come on, everybody,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
You will not be disappointed.
She's my most beautiful creation.
I have shaped her for success.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
I'm so happy to be with you tonight.
I've missed you all so much!
The monster!
Shoot the monster!
It's a freak!
No...
Shoot the monster!
Monster!
Freak!
You freak!
Monster!
- Freak!
- Monster!
Monster!
It's me.
Too bad her boobs aren't in the
middle of her face instead of that nose.
Hmm.
Next!
Pretty girls should always smile.
And at 50, it stops.
So beautiful!
We love you!
You're irreplaceable!