- News Reporter:
The city is in chaos
and hospitals are overwhelmed.
CCPD advises you, stay indoors
as the violent
speedster war escalates...
- Iris!
I need to get back out there.
- Nora: Dad!
Something's wrong.
Our family...
- [chokes]
- The future...
It's all changed.
- [choking]
- Flash has to do something
before it's too late!
- [chokes]
Nora!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What's happening?
[whooshing]
[sirens wailing]
- People are getting attacked
in their offices, their cars,
their own homes!
And seemingly at random.
[monitor beeps]
- So...
Godspeeds are attacking folks
in their homes now?
You mean I could just
be hanging out at home
listening to my Nas-Nasty-Nas,
drinking coffee, and a whole
Godspeed could just...
- Ah, the Godspeeds
are gone again.
- You're hurt. What happened?
- They ambushed me while I was
evacuating City Hall.
I barely made it out
in one piece.
- Okay, let's get you
to the med lab.
Chester, can you call Iris?
- Yeah, sure.
- No, no.
She's still home feeling sick.
Let her rest.
Frost is out there helping.
Chester, how long was it before
they showed up this time?
- About eight hours.
But their movements
are unpredictable
and we still have no idea
where they're going
once they disappear.
- Can we figure out when
they're gonna come back next?
- I could start working
on a predictive algorithm.
Right, okay.
If there's a pattern
to their freaky-deaky moves,
I'll find it.
- Even if we figure out
when they're gonna attack next,
we still have no idea
what these new clones want.
- The original six
want your speed.
- And just as they were
gonna get it,
six more showed up
and saved you.
- Right, but why?
[gasps in pain]
Why?
I mean, how do we stop
a civil war
if we don't even understand
why both sides
are fighting each other?
- Hey.
Has anybody heard from Joe?
He left town with Kramer
hours ago.
I haven't been able to get
ahold of him.
- I think I know why.
This Godspeed war is causing
a buildup of electricity,
shielding Central City
in what's essentially
a faraday cage.
Any electronic signal is being
totally contained inside.
- So no one in the city
can text or call
the outside world right now.
I'm sorry.
- Cecile, if there's one thing
Joe knows how to do,
it's take care of himself.
And right now, anywhere's safer
than Central City.
[foreboding music]
[fire crackling]
♪ ♪
- Ah.
You got out.
♪ ♪
Two against one.
Not fair.
♪ ♪
[phone beeps]
[blaster powers up]
Time to go hunting.
♪ ♪
[both breathing heavily]
- So that was Creyke.
How did you know he had us
in his sights?
- That light.
I'd recognize the signature
of Adam's pulse rifle anywhere.
[sighs]
You okay?
- I'm alive, so I'm good.
We need to get backup, though.
[phone beeps]
Damn it.
I can't get a signal.
- He's jamming cell service
to keep us isolated.
Which means he knows
we didn't die in that blast.
- We need to keep moving.
- [winces in pain]
- Easy.
You still have six broken ribs
and some internal bleeding.
- Another hour
of speed healing, I'll be fine.
Those Godspeeds
will be back soon.
I need to be ready.
- Look...
I've patched you up
enough times to know
that this isn't about
some broken bones
or clones, or...
even Iris being
under the weather.
- I had a dream about Nora.
My Nora, from the future.
It was the second dream,
actually.
This time, she was so afraid.
She told me the future
had changed and...
I needed to do something.
I know it was just a dream,
but...
Caitlin, I'm really worried.
Godspeed was Nora's enemy
from 2049.
If all these other Godspeeds
are here now,
what does that mean
for the future of my family?
What if it somehow means...
- Your Nora
doesn't exist anymore.
You could...go check on her.
Run to the future.
- I want to, but I'd risk
causing another Flashpoint.
Plus, more Godspeeds could
show up at any moment.
- Then you wouldn't be here
to fight them.
I get it. You're right.
- I can't leave.
Not while there's
a civil war in the city.
- Maybe I can help with that.
- John?
- Dig!
- Barry, Caitlin.
I brought you something.
- What is it?
- If we're lucky,
a way to end this war
before someone gets killed.
- It's called an entropy trap.
And hopefully, it's gonna
save your city.
- Chester:
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So you're saying
that John Diggle
is gonna help us end
the Godspeed war?
AKA Spartan,
AKA Oliver Queen's
right-hand man,
AKA the heart and soul
of Team Arrow?
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
[laughter]
And this is something
that Cisco cooked up
after you called him and gave
him the 411 on Central City.
- Dig, when we reached out
for help,
I had no idea
he was gonna send you.
- He didn't.
I volunteered, man.
You're fighting a war, Barry.
I know something about that.
- And with
a battle-tested soldier
like you on our side,
we're gonna win.
- This motion-detection plate
has a response time
of a picosecond.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
And now it's live.
Hey, do you mind
handing me that thing?
- Oh, yeah, absolutely!
I mean, like, absolutely
I don't mind kinda...
[chuckles nervously]
I'm the new guy, by the way.
Chester.
Big fan, man, big fan.
- Thanks.
All right, guys,
you might want to stand back.
♪ ♪
- Whoa, dog!
So the plasmatic wave
eliminates
all entropy from any object
or person.
- Yup.
Freezing it in time.
- Guys...
If we could trap
one of these Godspeeds,
find a way
to communicate with it...
- We can find out
what they want
and why they're fighting.
- And end this thing.
- Once we've caught one,
we'll bring it back here
for questioning.
- John: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You want to invite the enemy
into your house, Barry?
Is that a good idea?
- Look, these new Godspeeds
saved my life last night.
If there's any chance
of finding allies in this war,
it's with them.
- Right.
[winces in pain]
[faint sharp humming]
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[inhales]
Let's go catch a speedster.
- This band is made of the same
metal alloy as your mask,
so your body won't reject it.
It'll maintain
the laryngeal structure.
All right, you're good to go.
No more updates,
no more surgeries.
I'll let you two catch up.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- You going somewhere?
- I have work to do.
- [scoffs]
This is on some old
Black Hole security squad.
Wait...
are you serious?
You're going after the dregs
of Black freakin' Hole
before your anesthesia's
even worn off?
You have a death wish?
- Those who survived
Carver's reign
are digging up
old bank accounts.
Giving money to those
same doctors who hurt me.
[in Spanish]
- I get it.
These are bad dudes.
Like, really bad.
But they can wait,
'cause you have to heal first.
I have a chance
to stop them now.
I may not get another.
- What about your chance
at a new beginning?
Caitlin just saved your voice
and probably your life.
You really wanna risk it
for some Black Hole scum?
Damn it, Esperanza,
You are not strong enough
to fight them.
- So help me!
- So you can get more blood
on your hands?
No!
- Fine.
No killing.
But we will do this together.
As a family.
- I can't.
It has to wait.
There is a war going on, prima.
A whole lot of lives
are in danger.
This city needs me.
Team Flash needs me.
- I need you.
Those doctors will torture
others if I do nothing.
- Just wait.
As soon as this is over,
I promise...
I will help you.
[intense music]
[whooshing]
- The clones are back.
- Seems like they came back
awfully fast this time.
- Flash, we got company.
[car alarms blaring]
- I'm ready, Chester. Do it.
[monitor beeps]
- Signal activated.
[high-pitched tone]
Okay, Flash's suit
is emitting a signal
identical
to the original Godspeeds.
- So the new Godspeeds will
think that he's their rival...
- When he's really bait.
[high-pitched tone]
- We got one!
[monitor beeping]
♪ ♪
[monitor beeps]
- What happened?
Did it work?
- It worked, all right.
[whooshes]
[chuckles]
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
That's something
you don't see every day.
- Okay, so...
why isn't he talking?
- He's a soldier.
He'll talk when he's ready.
And not a moment sooner.
[soft dramatic music]
So...
word at A.R.G.U.S. is
you are leveling up, Cecile.
- Hmm.
Didn't know you guys kept tabs
on us ordinary people.
- I guess that means
you're far from ordinary.
- Speaking of, can you sense
what's going on
inside his mind?
- No, Barry already had me try,
and the only thing
that I could feel
was...hatred.
And determination.
- Why isn't he trying
to make contact
with the rest of his team?
- Oh, he's trying.
But I'm sending out
serious interference.
He can't get through.
- She's our own personal
signal jammer.
- That'd come in handy
in the field.
This whole team is leveling up.
- Guys, it might not
understand me.
- Chester:You think
it might be a...drone?
- Maybe.
Queue up your translator.
- A translation
will not be necessary.
[mysterious music]
- So you can speak.
- Yes.
And we have much to discuss,
Barry Allen.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Now where, oh, where
could you be?
Hmm?
- [sighs]
- You want to tell me
why he's trying to kill us?
- No idea.
Killing's what the army
taught him to do, so...
we need to move.
- Hey, if we head north,
we could hit the main road
in about an hour.
- I'm not letting him go.
- I'm not going
into a suicide mission.
- Look, you do
what you have to do.
The 12 soldiers Adam killed
were my family.
I promised I would do whatever
it takes to get them justice.
Justice is that way.
So while I'm gonna do whatever
it takes to finish this,
I won't ask you to do the same.
- Hey, hey,
I'm not gonna let you
go after him alone.
I got your back, but, Kramer
if he did
everything he could do
to make sure you weren't part
of Operation Griffin,
why would he try
to kill you now?
He doesn't know
who he's hunting.
- If he doesn't know
who he's trying to kill,
I know how we can catch him.
- And I know
what we're gonna need
- Let's go.
- You've been listening
this whole time.
Why talk now?
- I needed to be sure.
In this war,
we fight versions of ourselves.
But when two sides
are evenly matched,
there is no winning.
Only endless suffering.
I know now you are strong.
You are the advantage we need
to achieve our goal.
- Which is?
- To live!
We did not ask to be born,
but we do ask not to die.
The others,
they want your speed
to give to their master,
August Heart.
But upon completion
of their mission,
they will bow down
to his final edict.
Total submission.
- And once they do,
they'll die?
- We do not want that fate.
- I understand the need
to defend yourselves.
But if you're from the future,
why bring your war here?
- We had no choice.
The Prime August Heart is here,
in this time.
- That's what they're
all doing.
That's what they're doing.
They're searching
for August Heart.
- And whoever finds him first...
- Wins the whole damn war.
- We are on the same side,
you and I.
We have the same goal...
stop one man
from gaining a power so great,
it would destroy us all.
So join us, Flash.
And by doing so,
you can end this war.
Save your city,
save your family.
- If I do help...
what happens to August Heart
once we find him?
- We kill him.
Until he is dead,
our freedom
will be compromised.
- I won't kill.
Not even an enemy.
- Then know this...
anyone who stands in our way
will die with him.
[monitor beeping]
- Uh, Godspeed's
biometrics show
he just tapped into his speed!
- Barry, turn on the trap!
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- If you are not an ally,
you are an enemy.
- [groaning]
- Let him go!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- Is everyone okay?
- How did he get out?
- I don't know.
The meta-cell should have
kept him powerless, but...
oh, man.
Godspeeds are fueled
by a velocity formula...
a chemical
Speed Force substitute.
- Which means
he's an artificial meta,
so dampeners
wouldn't do anything.
- So why didn't he just
peace out
as soon as we unfroze him?
- We thought we were
interrogating him.
He was interrogating us.
Chester, you have to fix this.
- Uh, I'm sorry, but...
Cisco built this core with
original Time Trapper tech.
That kind of tech's
one of a kind.
I can't...
- You have to.
It's the only way
to stop one of them.
- Barry, this isn't junk, okay?
Without access to bleeding-edge
temporal components,
there's just...
- Then find another way!
[sighs]
- Chester, Allegra,
give me a second with Barry.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
So you want to tell me
what's really got you so upset
that you're talking
to your teammates like that?
And don't tell me it's about
some broken tech, Barry.
- It's my daughter.
[breathing heavily]
Nora.
Before she came to join us,
she lived in the future.
2049.
The exact time Godspeed's from.
- Okay, and with everything
that's going on,
you think it affects
the future somehow?
- Dig, if...
if August Heart is here,
what does that mean for Nora?
And the future of our family?
Is she okay?
Will Iris and I
still have a family?
Is Nora even alive
in the future anymore?
[breathing heavily]
Now all I want to do
is run to 2049
and make sure Nora's okay.
See with my own eyes
that my daughter's safe.
But I can't do that.
- Why not?
- Dig, you know
better than anyone
what could happen if I did.
Besides, man, with this
civil war destroying the city
staying here to fight
is the right thing to do.
- No, it's not.
Barry, I lived a long life
here on this earth.
I've been a spy, a vigilante,
a soldier...
hell, I've even been
the Green Arrow.
The most important job
I've ever had is as a dad.
And there's not a bullet
I wouldn't take,
there's not a timeline that I
wouldn't risk changing
if it meant
protecting my family.
I know that now.
Lyla...
my kids, they're my heart, man.
My soul. My entire world.
How far would I go for them?
As far as it takes.
Everything else be damned.
Don't be afraid
to do the same.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Godspeeds are gone again.
How you holding up?
- Cecile, as long as these
Godspeeds are here,
I can't shake the feeling
that my family's future's
in trouble
That's why I need to go
and make sure
my daughter's okay.
- Nora? How?
- I'm gonna run to 2049.
- [gasps]
- It's...I know.
It's dangerous, but...
I'd risk anything
to keep this family safe.
- Yeah, well,
you and me both.
Which is why
I've been reading this.
- Nora's journal?
- Yeah.
Iris gave it to me.
Apparently...
she has been
looking for anything
about the original
August Heart.
Yeah, I know, even when
she's under the weather,
your girl is thinking
of ways to help us.
Now, turns out,
Nora mentioned a few places
that seem personal to Heart.
So if he really is here
in 2021,
Iris thinks he's hiding
at one of those.
- But without the entropy trap,
finding Heart first is our
best chance at ending this war.
- Exactly, and with Iris
out of commission,
I'm about to go
follow up for her.
- Cecile, I mean,
going after Heart by yourself
is dangerous.
- Okay.
Then I'll take
John and Allegra with me.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Thanks for coming.
- Happy to help.
Where's Allegra?
We could use
the extra firepower.
- Yeah, no, I called, I texted,
still nothing.
[sharp humming]
- [shouts]
[grunts in pain]
- Hey...
- Do you hear that?
Do you hear that?
- No. John!
John, hey, hey!
Are you all right?
- These headaches.
This one's a lot worse
than the others.
- Okay, okay.
Are you sure that
that's all it is?
[low humming]
- [grunting]
- [shouts]
[gasping]
It's too much!
It's like...
fighting a hurricane!
[yells]
[gasping]
- Okay, John,
buddy, I don't know
what that was,
but that was a hell of a lot
more than a headache.
I...I felt something.
I don't know what it was,
but it felt huge.
No.
More like...
infinite.
John, maybe you should
stay here.
- No.
No, I'm fine, I promise.
If there was something
really wrong,
the doctors in Gotham
would have found it.
- I...
- Really, whatever it is,
I can handle it
when we're done here.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Let's just find Heart
while we still have the chance.
- Comms aren't working in the
Speed Force for some reason,
but you'll have
Mobile Gideon with you.
- Okay.
Chester...
about earlier,
I was out of line.
I'm sorry.
- Thanks for saying that.
And look, I totally get it.
We're all just trying
to keep the city safe.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
[adventurous music]
♪ ♪
- Gideon:Now passing 2022.
2023.
- Warning, Barry Allen.
Temporal passage blocked
by invasive forces.
Warning.
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Deon?
- You okay?
- Yeah, I...
- Good.
'Cause we got a lot
to talk about.
- Deon, what's happening?
I mean, a second ago,
I was in the Speed Force.
Those...those clones,
they attacked me.
- I know, it's kind of
crazy stuff, right?
- What do you...
what were they doing in there
in the first place?
- Feeding on
pure Speed Force energy.
It's pretty tasty
to their artificial cells,
only they can't
hold onto it for long.
That's why they keep
coming back for more.
- Does the Speed Force know?
- Hell yeah.
Man, those wannabes in white?
Infesting the Speed Force
like damn roaches.
Now big sis
has got her hands full
trying to exterminate
their sorry asses.
That's why I stepped in.
- Wait, Deon.
You can control time.
You can take me to 2049.
- No, man, not till she's done.
Look, until then,
it's solo trips only.
All right? It's too dangerous
for anyone else.
Besides...
I kind of don't have
the strength.
I'm pretty busy right now.
- What are you...doing what?
- Keeping me safe.
[soft dramatic music]
- Iris?
W-what are you doing here?
- Turns out I have
more than just a bad cold.
[gasps in pain]
- What's wrong?
- I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Thanks to Deon.
Barry, something is causing me
to move in and out
of our timeline
- How is this possible?
- We don't know, but...
Mom's been phasing
through temporal planes, man.
Look, I don't know why,
but once I sensed it,
I knew I had to step in
and help.
I've been using
all my stillness
just to stabilize her.
Otherwise she'd fracture
through time itself.
I can keep her alive.
Long as she stays here with me.
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I know I should have just
told you what I was gonna do.
There just wasn't time.
- No, it's...it's all right.
Thanks for lookin' out for us.
How long do you have
to stay here?
- I don't know.
But I trust Deon.
- Thanks, but...
look, I'm...
I'm using all my energy
just trying
to keep you here this long.
I gotta put you back inside
a pure temporal strain.
Right now.
- I'm...I'm coming with her.
- Man, you can't!
Man, moving back and forth
through that kind of power
ain't recommended.
Even for a speedster.
Besides, man,
you've got a war to fight.
- Iris, we can't just...
- Barry, we have to.
It's my only chance.
[shouts]
- We gotta go.
- [grunts in pain]
- Deon, you have to find a cure
for whatever this is...
whatever's happening.
- I will.
- Iris, I love...
[siren wailing]
- John: Yo, Casper!
I got something for you.
- [screeches]
- Nanites.
Courtesy of Ray Palmer.
[grunting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
You're gonna be okay now.
Go, get to safety!
Go!
[sharp humming]
- [groans]
[voices whispering]
- Worlds await.
- Leave...me...alone!
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
- Frost: Spartan, look out!
You all right?
- Yeah, I am,
since you had my back.
- It happened again.
I gotta get you out of here.
Caitlin needs to examine you.
- No.
[panting]
Not while Heart
is still out there.
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no!
- Uh...
isn't he supposed to come back
at the exact same time?
- Yeah.
And if he hasn't,
it's because
something's gone wrong.
Barry?
Is Nora...
- Not Nora.
Iris.
- Esperanza!
- [gasping]
Oh...
[gasping]
- [chokes]
[In Spanish]
- I'm sorry.
I never should have let you go.
I should have chosen you...
my real family...
the second you asked.
- But you did not.
[gasping]
I fought alone.
[breathing heavily]
Now I die alone.
But I'm not afraid.
- No.
No, don't leave me.
No...
[crying]
No.
[climactic music]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
- Better make it quick.
You sure
this is the right place?
- Yeah, Iris' notes say
that August Heart
works at this address in 2049.
But in our time, Dayton Labs
hasn't been built yet.
- This was the last place
on your list?
- Yeah.
Did you see that?
Wait.
He's scared. I can feel it.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait,
we're not gonna hurt you.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Hi.
My name is Cecile Horton.
Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- What's your name?
- I...I...
I-I-I don't know.
- Okay.
Okay, well, look, we g...
we gotta get you out of here.
It's not safe.
- No, no, no, I can't...
I can't leave!
It's there.
This place is...
it's important.
It's important.
[breathing heavily]
I can feel it.
[stammers]
- Do you know why
it's so important to you?
- No!
No.
[sighs]
Do you?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[blaster powers up]
- [chuckles]
Well, that was fun!
What?
Nothin'?
Still looking
for a way out of this?
There isn't one.
Oh, you can try.
You could shoot me.
Light me on fire.
I know it's a trap.
But I've died before.
17 times, actually.
So why don't you
give me your best shot.
'Cause I can't be killed.
- Is that why you killed
12 innocent soldiers
from Fort Dakota?
Because you knew
they'd die and you wouldn't?
- Kristen?
[projectile fires]
[grunts]
[chuckles]
- You were like
a brother to me, Adam.
How could you do it?
- I'll tell you.
Right after you tell me
who the hell you are.
'Cause Kristen Kramer
died in that explosion.
And that means you're dead.
- What's he on about, Kramer?
- I don't know.
And I don't care.
All I care about
is why you killed our unit.
Was it money?
If you were in trouble,
I would have helped.
- [laughs]
Trouble?
Listen. I'm immortal.
And once I discovered that,
I realized the world
was meant for me
because I deserved it.
- What you deserve
is life in prison.
- Oh, really?
I gave my life to the army.
And what did it get me, huh?
Nightmares and a kick
in the teeth.
That's when I realized
I could go down broke
or live it up rich.
'Cause there's plenty
of folks out there
willing to pay
for my new talents.
[chuckles]
Look at him.
Trying to figure out what I am.
- I already have.
You're the kind of meta
that gives the others
a bad name.
- You killed innocent people.
- I finished a job.
- You're a mercenary.
Did I ever know you at all?
- You're the only one
who knows me, Kris.
Sure, I'll kill anyone
if the price is right.
But I take half
the money I make
and I give it back to the Rez.
To build something good.
Something we never got.
- Doing something good
doesn't erase something evil.
- Oh, yeah?
You tell that to the kids
that look like you and me.
They got futures now.
Everything I did,
I'd do it again.
[blaster cocks]
- You're not even sorry.
- Kramer, stand down!
Kristen.
It's not worth it.
♪ ♪
Come on.
[blaster powers down]
- [chuckles]
- Chester: Hmm, uh...
if this is
the real August Heart,
shouldn't he be in, like,
I don't know,
triple lockup at A.R.G.U.S.
or something?
- Well, right now,
it's just a feeling.
- Yeah, we need to find
a way to prove it.
One way or the other.
It's what Iris would want.
- Based on everything
you told us,
being with Deon
is the safest place
for Iris to be right now.
- Yeah, I mean, we've all seen
what the Still Force can do.
If anyone can keep her safe,
Deon can.
- All right, right now,
let's stay focused
on keeping the city safe.
- Right, right, okay.
I just finished
running the algorithm
on the Godspeed disappearances.
Turns out, these clones
are coming back
exponentially faster each time.
- How long do we have?
- At first, it was eight hours,
then four.
- And now?
- If we're lucky, 90 minutes.
This war's about to go turbo.
- Cecile, can you sense
anything from this guy?
- Yeah, I tried.
The only thing I'm picking up
is the same fear
that anyone suffering
from memory loss would have.
Whoever this person is,
he seems like somebody
who needs help.
- I ran complete
diagnostics on him.
There's no sign
of speed powers,
organic or artificial.
But take a look at this.
His neurological scans
show severe memory degradation.
But his somatic memory cells
are still intact,
they're just inactive.
- Can we access them?
- I could give him a nano dose
of neurogenic dark matter.
It might reactivate the cells.
But it's risky.
And the effects
would only be temporary.
- I think if there's a chance
that what's inside his head
could save lives,
it's worth trying.
- As long as he agrees.
Let's get the shot ready.
- I'll ask
if he's willing to help.
- Tell Cisco that I have
scanned every element.
And I am on the case.
If there's any way to duplicate
this Time Trapper tech,
we'll find it.
- I know you will.
You got skills, man.
This team is lucky to have you.
- [chuckles]
Thanks, man.
So see you soon?
- Sure.
Take care of yourself.
- Whoa.
- [chuckles]
- You leaving?
- There's something I've been
putting off for far too long,
and today it nearly
got me killed.
And now I have to deal with it.
- I get it, it's...
it's just this war.
We need all the help
we can get.
- Barry, you think
I don't know that?
And as much as everything
inside of me
wants to stay
and help you fight,
in my heart and soul, man,
I know I can't put this off
any longer.
- All right, well,
whatever's going on,
let us know
if you need anything.
- Yeah.
Thanks, man.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
And Barry?
Good luck.
With everything.
- Thanks.
♪ ♪
- Will this hurt?
- No.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
- I need to know who I am.
And if you think
this could really help...
Then...
do it.
[exhales]
- Can you tell me your name?
- My name is...
[gasping]
My name is...
- It's okay.
Take your time.
- [grunts]
August.
♪ ♪
- It's him, August Heart,
the real Godspeed.
Only...that's all
we could get out of him.
His memory loss is too severe.
- So even though we found him,
we're back to square one.
Damn it.
- Barry, you never said
what happened
when you went to 2049.
- I never made it.
Those clones were
blocking my path.
I couldn't get past them.
Now I can't check on Nora,
plus I can't help Iris.
This war keeps getting worse.
Cecile, even with all my speed,
I've never felt so helpless.
- Barry...
It's okay to be scared.
And...angry.
But I just need you to save
a little bit of room
for hope.
'Cause no matter how bad things
might seem right now,
we will get through this.
All right, I am, uh,
gonna check in with Chester.
He's trying
to help me reach Joe.
- All right.
Cecile: Ok.
[sighs]
[whooshes]
- Hey, Dad!
- Nora!
- And, yes,
before you say anything,
I know I'm not
supposed to be here,
but it's really important,
I promise.
- Oh, thank God you're okay.
[exhales]
- Well, like, yeah,
why wouldn't I be?
- Because I...
well, I couldn't
get to the future.
And then with Iris gone...
wait, but if you're here,
that means...
- Oh, right!
Don't worry.
Mom's gonna be okay.
I'm proof that everything
works out all right.
We both are.
- You...
you and Iris?
- Not...not exactly.
Um...
But, uh...hey!
I mean, if you're happy
to see me,
you're gonna be twice as happy
in just a second.
[whooshes]
- Whoo!
Hoo! What did I miss?
- Dad, meet your son, Bart.
- Hey, Dad!
What's good?
Or "Pops."
Can I call you Pops yet?
You like it when I call you
Pops later.
I can't remember
when that is, though.
Yo, this place is crash!
- Greg, move your head.