(PANTING) Okay.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, buddy.
Come on,
come on, we gotta move,
we gotta move.
Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
(SPITS) Uh-oh!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
No, no, no, no, no!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Huh?
(GASPING) Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(GRUNTS) Hey! Hey! Gotcha!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(GRUNTS) Ow!
Ow! Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
I don't like it!
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Whoo! (CHUCKLES)
(SCREAMING)
Ow! Ooh! Ah! Ow! Ow!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow! Oh!
Beak! Wing! Tail!
Ribs!
Giblets!
(GROANS)
Ha!
(SCREAMING)
I'm flying!
Nope, still can't fly.
(SCREAMING)
(BURBLING)
I cannot believe this.
Breathe, breathe. (INHALES)
(GASPS)
(COUGHING)
Bottom feeder.
Up and over!
(PANTING)
Whew! (GASPS)
Ta-da!
(HORN TOOTS)
(SHRIEKING)
No, no, no, no.
Look. It's okay.
I'm just a clown.
Oh, boy.
That's a loud... Loud...
(SOBBING)
You're very scared of me.
Here, come here.
(SHRIEKING)
Nope. Okay. Nope.
Never mind.
Uh, happy hatchday!
Oh! Hi, pal.
You must be so disappointed
in yourself for
being this late.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
I'm not late.
Look at the time.
See,
the order said before noon.
(CACKLING)
Okay, now you're late.
What?
Where have you been?
It's funny you ask.
You see, I was...
You missed the party.
What is that?
Oh, that.
Um, yes, see,
I fell on the box.
(CHITTERS)
Oh, the squirrel?
(GIGGLES)
That's on us.
You know,
I tried to keep my body
between the ground
and the box,
but, you know, I think
I got a little bruise.
See anything back there?
(GROANS)
Hear that, honey?
The clown we paid to
be here an hour ago
fell on our son's
hatchday cake.
That's why our
son's hatchday party
is ruined!
Oh!
And the next time you mess up,
don't tell me a story,
just take responsibility.
Hey, man, it wasn't a story.
"I'm a screwup
that woke up late
"and fell on the
thing you paid for!"
(MIMICKING GIBBERISH)
It wasn't a story.
I almost drowned.
"I'm really bad at my
job and I'm late..."
Why don't we
just settle this out
and say the
cake's on you.
You.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
I'm sorry, it's on me?
Well, who else would it be on?
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Well, you know, I...
I'm not sure you're
gonna like this, um,
but since you asked.
Rather than being on me,
as you suggested,
this cake is on you!
So, you wanna hear a story?
I run my butt off,
literally, mind you,
to get the "gluten-free cake."
What the heck is gluten?
I mean,
does gluten even exist?
(TREMBLING) Who are you?
Get outta here!
Already?
But you're the only one
that's had cake.
What...
Mmm.
Oh, that's good stuff.
Anybody want to eat some cake
off their dad or husband?
Who needs plates when you got
this guy's face, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, oh, mmm!
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
You know, I'm supposed to do
a quick customer
satisfaction survey
before I
(WHISTLES) split, okay?
So, on a scale of
one to three stars,
what would you say
about my performance?
And don't forget,
the squirrel was...
(SQUEAKS)
(DISTORTED) ...free...
(DISTORTED SCREAM)
Sorry about this!
No!
My bad.
(GRUNTS)
Huh!
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(OTHERS GASP)
Mmm!
RED: (MUFFLED)
Congratulations!
Huh?
Oh!
It's a boy!
(PARANOID BY
BLACK SABBATH PLAYING)
Mmm.
(ANGRY GRUNT)
Hmm?
Ooh. Ooh, ooh.
Huh?
Mm. Mm.
(GASPS)
Ooh-hoo-hoo! (GROANS)
FEMALE CLASSMATE:
Hey, Eyebrows.
(LAUGHTER)
(WHISPERING)
Eyebrows!
ALL: Eyebrows!
(ANGRY GRUNTING)
(SNORING)
(POUNDING)
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(RED SIGHS)
Whee!
(GASPING)
(SNEEZES)
Huh?
(SNIFFLES)
(SNEEZING)
(GROANS)
Oh!
Hmm.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(GULPS) Uh-oh.
Hmm?
Oh.
(GRUNTING)
(GIGGLING)
(ANGRY GRUNT)
EVA: Your Honor,
our family has
always practiced
natural childhatch.
The risks of having
a scrambled infant
are too great.
There was going to be music,
the nest was
going to be full of
beautiful, fresh-cut flowers.
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
And the first two faces
he was going to see
were the loving faces
(SOBBING) of his
mother and his father.
(CROWD MURMURING)
(GIGGLES)
We can never get
that moment back.
Ma'am,
I never wanted my face to be
the first face your baby saw.
(CHUCKLES) I mean,
what are we
talking about here?
He probably
doesn't even remember me.
Daddy!
(CROWD GASPS)
No, no, no. No.
Shh. Shut up.
Shut up.
(GROWLING)
Cool it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
am I a passionate bird?
Yes.
(CHUCKLES) Guilty as can be.
It was a quality cake.
Mmm.
Look, I worked very hard
to get it there on time
and he wouldn't even try it!
(CLEARS THROAT)
Mr. Red, we are a happy,
happy bird community.
ALL: Mmm-hmm.
Under the protection
of Mighty Eagle,
we work, we play,
we laugh, we love,
and we live our lives free
from conflict and strife, sir.
We love the sound
of our own voice,
too, evidently.
Perhaps you
never heard the joke,
"Why don't birds fly?"
I'm gonna tell you why.
Because where else
would we ever wanna go?
(LAUGHTER)
It gets me every time, guys!
Wow! Not a good joke.
So now, what am I to make
of the likes of you?
There seems to be
a recurring issue here.
Anger.
(CROWD MURMURS)
(SCOFFS) I don't think
I have an anger issue.
I think you got
an anger issue.
(CROWD GASPS)
Anger is a weed
growing in our garden.
And what do you do
when you find a weed?
I don't know, but I
bet you're gonna tell me.
You pluck it out!
Oh, my God.
Mr. Red,
when you moved your house
outside of our village,
did you notice that
nobody tried to stop you?
(SIGHS)
Birds, they may smile
at you on the street,
but that doesn't
mean they like you.
(EXHALES)
Mmm-hmm. Hey, you know what?
I got a question for you.
Are you aware that that robe
that you're wearing
isn't fooling anybody?
We all see ya
prancing along the street,
Your Honor!
And you're, what, and I'm just
approximating here,
like, an inch tall?
You... What are you doing?
(CROWD GASPS)
Voila!
(SNEEZES)
(SNIFFLES)
Yeesh.
(CROWD GASPS)
What the...
Daddy!
Mr. Red, given
the severity of the crimes,
I have no choice but to impose
the maximum penalty
allowed by the law.
Anger management class.
(CROWD GROANS)
Oh.
Pluck my life.
(GASPS)
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
Fresh worms caught today.
Huh?
Hey, Red. How are ya?
Oh, I'm horrible.
STELLA: Oh, hi, Red.
It's good to see you!
I wish I could say the same.
Get your worms here!
(LAUGHING)
Upsy-daisy!
(GASPS)
Thank you. (GROANS)
(PLAYING LIVELY TUNE)
Ah! Huh?
(PLAYING SQUEAKY NOTES)
Huh?
Let's go.
Oh.
(YOUNG BIRDS GIGGLING)
How are you, Susie?
You good?
No running.
No running. (CHUCKLES)
Ooh!
Come on.
Hey, how's that nap
schedule coming along?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, boy.
You guys ever
thought about bird control?
Oof!
Left, right, left, right.
There ya go.
(HUMMING)
(MOCKING HUM)
Hey, hey.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(GIGGLING)
All right. Oop!
(GROANS)
SHIRLEY: Shirley.
Girly, you got this.
MONICA: We don't
want you to fall, now.
Take your time.
(GROANS)
Here we go. That's it.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, you're doing it!
Seriously?
I'm almost there.
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
Hmm?
Nope.
Hmm.
(BIRDS GASPING HAPPILY)
(ALL GASP)
(SPITTING)
(LAUGHTER)
YOGA INSTRUCTOR: Pigeon pose.
Crane pose.
(PANTING)
Okay, we worked out.
Who's down for a froyo?
Ooh!
Froyo.
Wow.
"Mighty Mighty Eagle,
soaring free.
"Defender of our
homes and liberty!"
Hi, Red.
Is one of those yours?
What?
Yeah, when birds fly.
DAY CARE BIRD:
"Mighty Eagle is a legend."
(STATUE LAUGHING RHYTHMICALLY)
(AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
(GRUMBLES)
(CRACKING)
(ANGRY GRUNTING)
(EXHALES)
Mmm.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS IN PAIN)
(EXHALES)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
You think that's funny?
Ha-ha-ha!
This is funny!
(RHYTHMIC LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Uh-oh.
(GRUNTING)
Oh! Ah! Come on!
(RHYTHMIC LAUGHING DISTORTS)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(RHYTHMIC LAUGHING STOPS)
(PANTING)
(RHYTHMIC LAUGHING)
What?
(GRUNTING)
(STATUE GRUNTS)
Oof!
(GRUNTS)
Whew! (PANTING)
(HELENE GASPS)
Hmm?
Don't look, Bobby.
(CHUCKLES)
The anger might be contagious.
Let's go!
He started it.
HELENE: Move it, move it!
Don't look back!
(GROANS)
There you go.
Uh-huh.
(STATUE GROANS WEAKLY)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, look at this.
This is gonna be awful.
Okay, I guess that's art.
That's garbage.
And that's exotic.
"Free rage" what?
MATILDA: Oh, hi!
(GASPS)
Hi there! Welcome...
Oh, hello.
...to the Infinity
Acceptance group.
I am Matilda.
Okay.
And I'm just super psyched
to be taking this
journey with you!
Ah! You're gonna have a blast.
I'm really fun.
(CHUCKLING)
Everybody says that about me.
Hey, guys.
Say hello to Red, everyone.
Hello!
Hi, Red. (CHUCKLES)
Hello, birds I
won't get to know well.
Hey, apparently
somebody didn't get
the memo that we
like to start on time
because you're about
two minutes late.
Don't let it happen again.
Hi, my name is Chuck.
I'm sorry we got off
on the wrong foot.
I like you a lot. I can tell.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Now, Red, would you like to
share your story with us?
No, not really.
Well, the court mentioned
something about a rage episode
at a child's birthday party.
How long is
this class, anyway?
As long as you make it.
Really? Oh, okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Uh, gentlemen,
very nice to see you,
and to almost meet you.
Probably the nicest part of it
is not getting to meet you,
you know, in some weird way.
(BOTH GROAN)
All right,
so I'm gonna go ahead
and scoot on back out
past those creepy
statues and, uh...
(GRUNTS) Back you go.
Sure. No, I can take a seat.
(HUMMING)
So, in another sense,
you are here until
I notify the court
that your anger issues
have been resolved.
(GIGGLES)
Oh, boy.
Chuck!
Share your story with Red.
Me? I am the last guy
who should be here.
Simple speeding ticket.
Judge tells me I
was going too fast,
so I say, "Your Honor,
to be honest, I was.
"You caught me."
I'm not angry. I'm honest.
So, shouldn't I be in
honesty management class?
'Cause we gotta
manage my honesty.
Mmm-hmm.
My one problem,
that's a different story
than you told last time.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(SIREN WAILING)
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
* Woop-woop!
That's the sound of da police
That's the sound of the beast
Hmm.
* Woop-woop!
That's the sound of da police
That's the sound of the beast
* Woop-woop!
That's the sound of da police
That's the sound of da beast
Drinks on me, guys!
(CHEERING)
* Woop-woop!
That's the sound of da police
That's the sound
of the beast *
Mmm-mmm.
MATILDA: Chuck?
Okay,
maybe it wasn't ice cream.
All right, Chuck, thanks.
We got it.
And this is Terence.
(LOW GROWLING)
Whew! More like terrifying.
Now, it says here,
in your little filey...
(SIREN WAILING)
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
(CRASHING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(LOUD SCREAM)
(CRASHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LOW GROWLING)
Terence, uh, seems to have had
an (CLEARS THROAT) incident.
Now, Bomb started
with us two weeks ago.
Tell us your story, Bomb.
(SIGHS) Okay.
Well,
sometimes when I get upset,
I, uh, have been
known to, uh, blow up.
So, like, uh...
Like, what, like,
you get mad, you mean?
Well, no.
I literally blow up, okay?
I explode like a bomb.
(IMITATES BOMB
WHISTLING THROUGH AIR)
(IMITATES EXPLOSION)
(CHUCK GASPS)
Hence the name.
CROWD: Surprise!
(SQUEAKING)
(PARTY HORN SQUEAKS)
Ah, excuse me.
Party foul.
Ow!
(SQUEALS) Do it!
No can do.
I just went
boom-boom before class.
Hey, look, I don't
want to be here at all,
but this can maybe make it
a little more interesting
to me, so please, explode.
You can't do it, can you?
Yes, I can,
but I'm having
back issues today.
Ugh!
So, I'm gonna have
to take a rain check.
Oh, do it!
Not the time or place,
little amigo.
These guys are all nuts,
huh, big man?
(LOW GROWLING)
Are we speaking
telepathically,
or you're just...
(LOW GROWLING)
Good talk.
Nice chatting with you.
Today we're
gonna be working on
managing our anger
through movement.
CHUCK: Mmm.
The first pose is
the dancer pose.
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(GASPS)
Great form, Terence.
Mmm! Eagle! Heron!
Peacock! Warrior!
Mountain!
Tree! Rabbit! Fish! Locust!
King pigeon!
And of course, downward duck.
(GROANS) Huh?
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
Uh, excuse me,
boring hippie lady.
Uh-huh?
Looks like
the explodey guy's gonna puke.
And have you done this before?
Uh, yes, I have,
but usually not for free.
(GRUNTS)
Didn't think so.
Awesome.
And how are we
doing over here, Bomb?
(STRAINING) Doing wonderful.
Stretching out the core.
(GROANS)
Just remember to breathe
up through your feathers
and from your talons.
(GROANING)
Namaste.
(HISSING)
Bomb?
(CHUCK COUGHING)
CHUCK: Nice!
(COUGHING)
BOMB: I don't know
what happened.
I was doing the poses,
I was feeling all Zen,
Matilda was digging it,
then I lost my grip on it.
Let it slip and it
just squeaked out.
Hey, so, where we going?
I'm sorry. "We"?
Yes, we.
There's a new
happiness exhibit
at the Museum of Happiness
that I'm dying to see.
Uh, you know what?
I... I mean,
I got a... I got a thing.
A thing?
(WHISPERS) Like a disease?
(GASPS) Is it bird flu?
Chicken pox?
(GASPS) Cardinal sin?
No, by "thing,"
I mean, like, um,
desire not to hang out.
With you.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, well...
You know,
may be for the best, you know,
because,
uh, I got something, too.
Ha! How did I forget?
Even if you'd said yes,
I probably couldn't have gone.
I'm busy, too.
I have a, uh, business offer,
uh, deal that is, uh...
No, Bomb, you're not
good at this, buddy.
It's...
It's charming up to a point,
and now it's just sad.
It's a guy I know.
(GROANS)
And he's opening up
a brand-new luxury...
Mmm-mmm.
...class reunion.
Okay.
Good. Good, good, good.
Well, looks like it's just us.
Want to go get a bite?
Oh, but what about
your "class reunion"
where everybody
brings a "business offer"?
Oh! (CHUCKLES) No, no, no.
Chuck, I was lying.
I'm sorry if I fooled you.
(BEHIND BLUE EYES
BY LIMP BIZKIT PLAYING)
(YOUNG BIRDS LAUGHING)
Hmm?
Nuh-uh! No means no.
Hmm.
My sweetheart.
Cheers.
Hey!
Hmm?
Get over here!
Hey, peckerhead!
(CHUCKLING) What's up?
(SIGHS) Hmm.
* To be the sad man
OLIVE: Ooh!
Oh! Oh, I felt a peck!
Oh!
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
* And no one knows
what it's like to be hated
* To be fated
(SIGHS)
* To telling only lies
This is
the legendary Mighty Eagle,
our protector and hero,
but no one has
seen him for years.
Mighty Eagle is missing.
(GRUNTING)
When's Mighty Eagle
gonna come back?
Eyebrows, didn't your
parents ever tell you
Mighty Eagle isn't real?
Shh. He doesn't know that.
He doesn't have parents.
Yeah.
Or even friends. (CHUCKLES)
(CLASSMATES WHISPERING)
* No one knows what it's like
To feel these feelings
* Like I do
* And I blame you
* No one bites back
as hard on their anger
* None of my pain and woe
* Can show through
(LEONARD SNORTS)
LEONARD: Aha! Eureka!
Say bye to Daddy.
ALL: Bye-bye!
Goodbye, hatchlings.
ALL: Bye!
(CHUCKLES)
Have a happy day!
Good morning!
CYRUS: Morning, Your Honor.
Ow!
Here you go.
(SNEEZES)
Bless you.
Mmm! (GULPS)
Mmm!
Yes!
Bye!
Daddy's making dinner!
"If my name were Bobby
Would you ask
about my hobbies?"
Whoa!
"Or if my name were Judas
Would you ask me
what my mood is?"
(GROANS)
"I laugh,
I cry, I love, I hate
"I do so much
more than detonate"
Think about it.
That was beautiful.
Oh, you're gonna make me cry!
Yeah, that was some
real clever symbolism.
Ah! Red,
why don't we hear your poem?
I don't have a poem.
Uh-huh.
Why not?
Because I didn't write one.
Right. Uh-huh.
And is there a reason?
Well, you know,
I was gonna do it,
but then I thought
about it and I realized,
"Oh, this is a huge
waste of my time."
So, I didn't do it.
(INHALES) Deep breath,
deep breath.
(IN DEEP VOICE) Deep breath!
(SIGHS) Ah!
And we're back in the now.
Chuck! You've had your hand up
the whole time.
Mmm-hmm.
My poem is about a hate crime.
(GASPS)
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Lot of sickos out there.
Lot of sickos.
"What,
oh, what did I make you of?
"I made you out of love"
MATILDA: Aw.
"But wait, too late!
"Now I see your fate
"Some very troubled somebody
Destroyed you out of hate"
(GROANS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
"What could have
made him so despise
"Your happy smile,
your laughing eyes?
(WHIMPERS)
"Your soul was pure,
your heart was true"
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm.
"And someone hated that
"But who?"
(GASPS)
(GULPS)
(GRUNTS)
(WHISTLING)
(COUGHING) Terence.
(LOW GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
Yeah, I deserved that.
(GROANS)
Billy has passed...
RED: Oh!
...to a higher
plane of existence.
(CRYING) Everyone, join wings.
Let us all say our goodbyes.
Yeah, let me get in here.
I gotta say goodbye.
Okay.
(LOW GROWLING)
Okay. You know,
I'll just mourn
from back here.
That's fine.
You know, if there's one thing
Billy always hated,
it was goodbyes.
Hey,
what's going on out there?
(GASPS)
Oh! Class dismissed.
(TERENCE GROWLING)
Very moving.
Come on, everybody! Let's go!
(EXCITED CHATTER)
Hey, where's everybody going?
Hurry! Something's coming!
Last one to
the beach is a rotten egg!
Let's go!
Coming through!
Pardon me! Excuse me!
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
(GRUNTS) What?
(LOW GROWLING)
(GROWLING CHUCKLE)
(IMITATES SIREN WAILING)
Ah! Again?
(IMITATES HORN HONKING)
BIRD 1: Let's get down
to the beach!
BIRD 2: Follow the trail!
BIRD 3: Last one
there is a rotten eggy!
What?
(SHIP HORN BLOWING)
Huh!
Didn't mean to photobomb you.
Sorry about that.
(GRUMBLES)
What is that thing?
It looks like a UFO.
An Unidentified
Floating Object.
Daddy!
Stop it.
No, I'm not your daddy!
(GIGGLING)
BIRD 1: What is that?
BIRD 2: Look at
the size of that thing!
SHIRLEY: Where's it going?
BRAD: I don't know,
but it's not stopping.
(ALARM BLARING)
My house, my house.
Slow down!
Stop!
(PANTING)
Aw.
(CREAKING)
Phew!
What the...
(GROANS)
That house took me
five years to build.
Wow!
It's such
a shame when you create
something and
someone just destroys it.
LEONARD ON SPEAKER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a very
special guest for you!
Huh?
He's a green
marine sailing machine.
Careful, now.
And he's keen to let
you know he's not mean!
Put your wings
together for Leonard!
(ALL GASPING)
Thank you so much.
Please hold your applause.
Greetings from my world!
The world of the pigs.
(WHISPERS) What's a pig?
I am a pig.
(SIGHS)
(GEARS CLANK)
Unbelievable.
(BEEPING)
(CHUCKLES)
Oh! Where we going?
Wrong way. (GRUNTS)
Oopsie. Not working.
(SIGHS)
We practiced this 100 times.
ROSS: Oh, man. (SQUEALS)
Give it to me.
Oh.
We're gonna come in again.
I'm so sorry.
(GIGGLING)
My name is Leonard...
(SCREAMING)
...but my friends
call me Chuckles.
Oh-ho-ho-ho! Very generous!
Thank...
We mean no harm.
(GRUNTING)
We saw your
island across the sea,
and we thought,
"Wonder what they're up to."
But there's no other
place besides here.
Yes, there is.
Stop it!
And we are from there.
(GRUNTS) Please stop!
We call it Piggy Island.
(SCREAMS)
Oh, my God.
P-I-double-G-Y Island.
(SCREAMING)
Who else is out there?
My first officer, Ross, and I
have sailed everywhere.
One brave soul
against the sea.
(PANTING)
And Ross.
RED: Uh, excuse me.
Have you come to smash
all of our houses
or just mine?
Oh, man!
(CROWD MURMURS)
LEONARD: Somebody
want a gift basket?
Please, please,
don't be afraid.
(ALL SIGH)
My partner and I request
the honor of your friendship.
Ross, show 'em how we do it.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Don't worry,
he's had all his shots.
(SHRIEKS)
We're all friends now!
(GRUNTS)
Hi, friends.
(LOW GROWLING)
(SNORTS) Oh, not a hugger.
Huh? (SIGHS)
Welcome to Bird Island!
Welcome to our new friends,
the pigs.
Let us have a celebration!
Put 'er there!
(MUFFLED) Welcome!
Whoo! Sorry.
And a hoof to a wing.
STELLA: We would
like to honor the pigs
with a special performance.
(UPBEAT SONG PLAYS)
* Hey, let's explo-o-o-ode!
* Explode!
Oh, watch out.
Shakin' my bacon!
(WHOOPS)
They don't have feathers?
You know, they're just
walking around naked,
just presenting themselves.
I'm looking at all
their business here.
That part about
them I really admire.
Now we would like to welcome
our special guests, the pigs!
(ALL CHEERING)
LEONARD: All right!
Thank you for your
kindness and hospitality.
Our king sends
his warmest regards.
"King"?
You have shared
with us the wonders
of your quaint,
simple little island.
Drop the banner, Ross!
(ROSS GRUNTING)
Whoa! Uh-oh.
Now we would
love to humbly share
some of
the wonders of our world.
(SCOFFS) Yeah.
Humble, my bird butt.
Language.
A hundred years from now,
everyone will ask,
"How did
the friendship between
the pigs and the birds start?"
Who cares?
Oh, no.
(CROWD GROANS)
Well, let them say
we lit up the night!
(CROWD GASPS)
Holy moly!
(LAUGHING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
Hey, look, they
destroyed more of the stuff
we worked hard to build.
But there's more!
CHUCK: More?
Has gravity gone haywire?
No! Even better!
Your friends,
the pigs, proudly give you
the trampoline!
(CROWD GASPING)
Those are my assistants,
Oinky...
Hello.
...and Jon Ham!
(BLOWS KISS)
Hold on a second.
I thought there was
only supposed to be
two of these guys.
LEONARD: Squad goals!
Look at those jiggly pigglies!
ALL: Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
But that's not all.
Throwing things just
got a whole lot easier.
Say hello to
the slingshot!
Ta-da!
I can't see. Wow!
This is crazy!
Tired of carrying things
from place to place?
CROWD: Yeah!
Wish you could
just get it there?
CROWD: Yeah!
Well, now you can!
CROWD: How?
Waiters, do me a favor.
Huh?
Take the rest
of the night off.
Thank you.
Hey, if you got the night off,
why don't you fix my house!
Yeah, it's the same guy.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, the slingshot
does it all in
three easy steps.
Ready, aim, fire!
I got it!
LEONARD: Incredible!
Flown in fresh!
Me! Me! I want fruit!
Guys,
it's the same fruit sitting
on the plates in front of you.
(GRUNTS)
LEONARD: Watch out
for that pineapple.
Somebody, please... (GULPS)
And now for our
last gift to you.
Shut up and fix my house!
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
We don't know him.
I'm going to ask for
a volunteer from the audience.
Pick me!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Who should I pick?
Who, who, who?
BIRD: Pick me, Mr. Pig!
How about the red guy
with the enormous eyebrows?
Aw.
(CHUCKLES)
Me?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, you, sir.
Come on up here.
It's your lucky day!
Are you sure you
don't want to choose
one of the hundreds of birds
that had their wings up?
LEONARD: Get him up here!
Come on, Red!
Have some fun!
ALL: (CHANTING) Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Oh, he's shy.
You hear that?
They're cheering for you.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
LEONARD: Red guy
with the eyebrows!
(CROWD CHANTING)
I would've sat
closer had I known
that I was gonna
be part of the show.
Okay, now what?
Come on, give him a hand.
(ALL CHEERING)
Right this way.
Come on. (SNORTS)
Relax. Be brave.
Ready!
Who, me? Yeah, no, I'm ready.
Aim!
Aim at what?
LEONARD: Everybody
on this one.
ALL: Fire!
(SCREAMING)
(CROWD GASPS)
Who says birds don't fly?
This seems really unnatural!
(GASPS)
I hope he's okay.
(SCREAMS) Ow!
(GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
Hey, don't worry!
I'm fine!
Thanks for the lift!
I wish they
would have done that
10 minutes ago.
Oh.
(WHOOSHING)
You know you want
to search their boat.
What? No, I don't.
Yeah, you're right, I do.
(WHOOSHING)
Bomb's on his way. Mmm. Mmm!
Come on. Let's go. (GRUNTS)
And remember, keep it quiet.
Oh, yeah.
(GRUNTING)
Whoa!
This is an impressive ship!
Shh. No. Inside voice.
Inside voice.
Come on.
Oh.
(WHISPERS) Sorry.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GRUNTS)
Hmm. Piggy fitness.
Hmm?
(MUMBLES)
Mmm-hmm.
(SQUEALS QUIETLY)
Ugh!
Mmm? Mmm-mmm.
Ah!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HORN PLAYING LA CUCARACHA)
Very strange.
Mmm.
Huh? (GASPS)
Huh?
Who are these weirdos?
(BOMB GRUNTS)
Huh?
Whoa!
(BOMB WHOOPING)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
What are you doing?
We're trying to sneak around.
We didn't rent this place out.
BOMB: Wow!
You can rent this place?
(CLICKS TONGUE) Hmm?
Give me that!
Aw.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH GASP)
BOMB: Hey, you guys!
(GRUNTING)
No, all right.
Looks like there's
some more stuff down here.
(PIGS LAUGHING)
(SNORTING)
(LAUGHS) We were hiding.
When I say, "Hey!"
you say, "Ho!"
Hey!
CROWD: Ho!
Ho!
Hey!
There's more of them!
(CHANTING STOPS)
Ho... Oh!
That's right, I'm back.
Uh-huh.
Enjoying the party, everyone?
Because while you
were living it up,
I snuck onto their boat.
CROWD: What? (GASPS)
SHIRLEY: What did he say?
And look at what I found.
(CHUCKLING)
There's more of them
than we thought!
Which is,
um, mysterious and weird,
am I right?
(LAUGHS)
Hi.
How ya doin'?
Oh.
Remember, he said there were
only two pigs on board,
but he was obviously lying.
Hmm.
Oh,
and there are strange devices
on their boat!
So, clearly,
there's, you know,
some messed-up stuff
going on here.
How messed up? I don't know.
What specifically?
I don't know that, either.
Any questions?
(GASPS)
Sweet!
You snuck onto their boat?
Uh, you know,
I don't need a reward.
If you guys are trying
to think of what honor
to bestow upon me,
don't need it.
Boo!
Yeah, boo 'em!
CROWD: Boo!
You're booing them or me?
You!
Oh, it's me.
Perhaps I can explain.
You see,
my cousins are simple folk.
Watch.
* A, B, C...
Nothing. See? Nothing.
(GROANS)
I didn't want to
risk their lives
until I found out that the...
The new world was safe.
We were gonna put on
a cowboy show for you.
(SNORTS) Let 'er go, boys!
Yee-haw!
(UPBEAT COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
* Hey, hey, you and me
Different as
different can be *
(SHUSHING)
* ...and I'll take
the low... *
(MUSIC STOPS)
Ixnay on the ongsay.
That was Pig Latin.
Oh.
Ooh!
But perhaps it
wasn't meant to be.
Oh.
I believe that birds and pigs
are meant to be friends.
But if we crossed boundaries
that were not
meant to be crossed...
Oh!
(CROWD GROANS)
Mr. Red, you've
shamed not only yourself,
but our entire community!
Oh, I think you...
You messed up there.
You said "shamed"
and you meant "saved," right?
I sent you to treatment
to deal with your problems.
Clearly,
more treatment is required.
No!
Do not trouble our
honored guests again!
My friends, we would love
to see your cowboy show.
CROWD: Yeah!
Thank you. (SNIFFLES)
Thank you so much.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
EARL: Come on, everybody!
Put your hands together!
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Whatever. Don't listen to me.
(LAUGHTER)
TINY: Party train
coming through!
Choo-choo!
(PIGS IMITATE TRAIN WHISTLE)
PIGS: * It's crazy that we're
standing side by side
(GRUNTING)
* Fighting just like
two birds of a feather
Ah! I can't see. I can't see.
Whoa!
(WATER SPLASHES)
* Who's gonna tell us
now that we can't fly?
* Just some
roughed-up desperados
* Hanging tough
through thick and thin
(CROWD CHEERING)
* Kicking up dust
wherever we go
Whoa! Ho-ho-ho-ho!
* I can see that you and me
Are gonna be friends...
Piggyback rides?
Yee-haw!
Let's move it, piggies!
Oh, boy.
Group picture! Group picture!
Everybody say, "Cheese"!
Cheese omelet.
Cheese!
(LAUGHS) Cheese omelet.
Classic.
Ooh! Spoiler alert. (LAUGHS)
Step right up!
Jump!
So, I'm thinking
about what kind of nest.
I don't know.
I was in the store,
and I saw this...
* Whoa
* Whoa-oh-oh
Yee-haw!
(CROWD CHEERING)
I am famished... Whoa!
PIG: It's chow time!
(PIGS CHEWING NOISILY)
* Just some
roughed-up desperados
(SNORTING)
Yuck!
* Hanging tough
through thick and thin
* Kicking up dust
wherever we go...
Yeah!
(CHEERING)
Ow!
(GRUNTING) What?
(SNORING)
* To the end
You and me are
gonna be friends... *
(SNORING)
What the heck?
(CHUCKLES)
Who invited you to move in?
Hey! Whoa!
That's my toothbrush!
Get it out!
(RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
Whoo! Yee-haw!
Yee-haw!
(YELLING)
(GASPS)
(LOW GROWLING)
(DEEP CHUCKLING)
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE) Huh?
(MATILDA HUMMING)
All right, class,
thought for the day.
Water is the softest thing,
yet it can penetrate
mountains and earth.
Here's my thought of the day.
When are we done?
Ugh! Red, what
the caterpillar calls the end,
the world calls a butterfly.
Can I just say I
never understand
a single thing
you're talking about?
(MOCKING) Can I just say...
(SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Ah. Mmm-hmm.
Wow, that's very lifelike.
(BOMB LAUGHS)
Whoa! (CHUCKLES) Oh!
So deep.
And, Terence,
let's see your...
(LOW GROWLING)
Oh! My goodness.
I did not know
you felt that way.
Aw...
Uh, class dismissed!
And now we've come to
the prestigious
Palms district.
Hoo-whee!
Where birds of all
feathers flock together
with eight kinds of
fruit and nut trees.
Suck those bellies in.
Insta-ham!
(GIGGLES)
Hmm.
Is that what I think it is?
That's an egg.
That's how our
children are born.
(GASPS)
You guys don't lay eggs?
I wish we did.
*
(CORK POPS)
Enchante.
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
You look delicious, my dear.
(LAUGHING)
* Every time you are near
* Just like me
* They long to be
That's us.
(GULPS)
(LAUGHING)
Hey. Hello.
Excuse me. Buddy?
(RECORD SCRATCHES)
Those are fragile.
Maybe you shouldn't
pick 'em up, all right?
Not yours.
Oh!
My friend from the banquet.
Well,
that's a very good painting.
Very good.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, the assignment
was "Paint Your Pain,"
so I painted your pain.
It's actually
the first in a series.
Here you go.
Uh-huh.
This one is nice.
Oh.
I call this one Catharsis.
And... Oh,
I call this one Bye-Bye.
Huh.
Wonderful likeness.
I thought you said
you stored your
nuts for winter.
(LAUGHTER)
Burn.
All right,
what's going on here?
Are you explorers,
or are you staying?
Because if you're explorers,
then why are there
more of you coming, huh?
(SHIP HORN BLOWING)
Hi, everybody!
Whee!
(LAUGHING)
RED: Not my house again!
That's my home!
PIG: Okay!
And you know what?
If you are staying,
why don't you just say so?
And why'd you leave your home?
How do we know
you're not
fugitives of the law?
You are making our
guests feel unwelcome!
And you're not
asking basic questions.
Oh!
Maybe I wasn't clear enough.
Your opinion is not needed!
Why do we have to agree?
Why does it matter
that we're not the same?
Anger is not
always the answer!
Continue the tour.
Um, surf's up, you guys.
So, get ready to hang loose.
That went well, if you're me.
(PIG SNORTS)
(LAUGHTER)
(SCOFFS) Dummy.
(SIGHS) We could really
use you right about now.
Wait, actually...
Hey, Chuck! It's Red!
Zip on down here!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Oh! Hey, Chuck's mom.
Can your son come out to play?
(WHOOSHING)
(SLURPING)
All of this does not
just happen on its own.
(BOMB VOCALIZING)
(BOMB YELLS)
(EXPLOSION)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Oh, hey. Just taking a shower.
Bomb, buddy, TMI.
(CHUCKLES)
RED: Now, I'm telling you,
something isn't
kosher with these pigs.
Bull's-eye!
And it's up to us
to figure it out.
Figure what out, exactly?
BOMB: I don't know,
maybe they're just
being innovative.
Go ahead.
All aboard!
(LAUGHTER)
BOMB: Does seem
a little odd, though.
(PIGS SCREAMING)
(WHOOPING)
Nailed it!
Flawless.
Come on, does none of this
seem wrong to you guys?
BOTH: (MUMBLING)
I'll tell you this,
if anyone knows
what these pigs are up to...
Hey!
...it's Mighty Eagle.
ANNOUNCER: Mighty Eagle!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, yeah!
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
Ha-ha!
Take that, tree! Hyah!
Eat my foot! Oh-yah!
Tasty! Yum, yum, yum! Mmm!
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(WHIP CRACKS)
Whoa.
ANNOUNCER: Mighty Eagle!
(GASPS)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Peek-a-boo.
Hello, Bird Island!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SPITS)
(CHUCKLES) You're welcome.
(SHRIEKS)
Does Mighty Eagle still live?
Did he ever live?
And if he did live,
where would he live?
By the Lake of Wisdom
in the Ancient Tree.
That's a fairy tale.
I've run all over this island.
Where could that possibly be?
Way up high.
It's a long way
up that mountain,
and if I'm being honest,
well, I mean,
you know, I could
kind of use your help.
What's that?
What are you trying to say?
Nothing. I was just saying
that I, you know,
I could use your help.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I couldn't quite hear you
over your ego.
Could you enunciate
that last word a little bit?
I need your help!
Oh! Why didn't you say so?
Bomb?
Let's do it!
(GRUNTING) Phew!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
If there is
a Mighty Eagle, well,
how come we don't
ever hear his battle cry?
I don't know.
Maybe we have.
What would a Mighty Eagle
battle cry sound like?
You know what?
I think I got an idea.
Maybe something like, uh...
(SCREECHING)
No, I bet it's more like...
Ca-caw! Ca-caw!
That's theoretically what
it's more like,
scientifically.
Oh, I got one.
(SINGING OPERA MUSIC)
Ah.
Not bad.
It's a good impression.
But in my head,
I'm kind of imagining
it's something more like a...
(HIGH-PITCHED SINGING)
* Hey-you-ho!
That sounds about right.
Now I'm thinking maybe
it's a little bit more subtle.
(PANTING)
Like a little bit just
more majestic, like...
(HARSH SCREECHING)
(ULULATING)
* "Hello, world!
* "I am calling for you!"
(SCREECHY SINGING)
Stop making
Mighty Eagle noises!
(SIGHS) It's like
running a nursery.
Absolute child care.
(SING-SONG)
Someone has anger issues.
(RED GRUNTS)
This, uh...
This is the wrong mountain.
(BOMB GRUNTING)
My calves are killing me.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Whew!
Oh, wow!
Whoa.
That is simply unreal.
(GASPS)
The Lake of Wisdom.
(LAUGHING)
CHUCK: What are
you guys waiting for?
(LAUGHING)
Guys, hurry up!
This is what
Mama talked about!
(GASPS) Wow.
(SLURPS)
Ah!
Be honest,
do I sound any wiser?
Oh, way wiser.
You were kind of dumb before.
I can say that now.
BOMB: That water is no joke.
(GRUNTING)
I can literally taste
the intelligence and wisdom
circulating
through my body now.
Guys, nobody's here.
I mean, nobody's used
this place in years.
What are you doing?
*
Get out of there.
(GROANS)
(BOMB GARGLING)
Don't spit in his mouth.
No, don't spit it back!
(CHUCK GARGLING)
Oh, don't swallow it.
(GULPS)
(GROANS) Yuck!
(LAUGHING)
Whoo!
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(DISTANT ROAR)
(GASPS) Whoa!
(PANTS)
(DISTANT RUMBLE)
Get out. Let's go. Come on.
(CHUCKLES)
Shh, shh. Come.
Take your time, will you?
Red, I've found
the meaning of life. It's...
Shut your wormhole.
(DISTANT BOOMING FOOTSTEPS)
(ECHOING ROAR)
(ROAR ECHOING)
(FOOTSTEPS BOOMING)
Oh, wow! It's him.
(MIGHTY EAGLE SIGHS)
(MIGHTY EAGLE YAWNING)
(MIGHTY EAGLE GROANING)
(MIGHTY EAGLE SIGHS)
Oh, man.
(MIGHTY EAGLE HUMMING)
(TRICKLING CONTINUES)
(RETCHING)
(MIGHTY EAGLE HUMMING)
No. No. No.
Ew!
Ugh! Horrible turn
of events. Horrible.
Whew!
(SOBBING LOUDLY)
(RHYTHMIC BRUSHING)
(MIGHTY EAGLE GROANS)
(MIGHTY EAGLE SIGHS)
(SMACKING LIPS)
Well, not so much
the Lake of Wisdom,
it's more like
the Lake of Whiz.
MIGHTY EAGLE: (ECHOING)
Did you just come
here to look at me?
Or did you have
something to say?
I think he saw us.
Oh, you think so?
MIGHTY EAGLE:
You have passed
the first test!
You have found me.
Whoa, whoa!
Look out.
Behold.
Gaze upon
Mighty Eagle!
(PANTING)
CHUCK: Hmm?
I see all and know all.
What are your names?
If you know all,
why don't you know who we are?
Ow!
I know very well who you are.
Uh-huh.
You are lost souls
who have come here
seeking wisdom.
Whoa!
Can we have some?
Wisdom is not
something that is given.
It is something
that is attained.
Okay. Goodbye.
No, no, no, no.
Will I help you
attain wisdom?
Whoa! Ha-ha!
Yes. That I will do.
Right.
So, the reason we've climbed
the mountain is
that we want to know...
Prepare...
Okay.
...to have your minds blown.
Oh, son of a...
This guy is good.
(ECHOING) Welcome to
the Hall of Heroism.
Wow! It's really
amazing to meet you.
You know, I actually
have your poster up...
You might want to
shield your eyes
from the sparkle
of those trophies.
How many? I have no idea.
Countless, I'm sure.
Thirteen.
Wow, this is way nicer
than my Hall of Wimpiness.
Bring it home, mamacita.
Get outta town.
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCK LAUGHS)
What the...
(WILD THI BY
TONE LOC PLAYING)
Oh-oh-oh. Mmm-hmm.
(GRUNTING)
Those are some
old-school moves there.
Yeah.
* Wild thing
Wild thing, wild thing
Ooh! Oh-ho.
What?
(WHISTLES) Wow!
Yes!
Yeah. Cha!
* Hasta la vista, baby
(MIGHTY EAGLE CACKLING)
So,
he's kind of a wackadoodle.
You know, that
doesn't mean he's not wise.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(ROSS LAUGHS)
Hey, are you tired of
filling your balloons
with heavy old air?
Finally, there's a better way.
Helium.
Helium?
It's a gas.
(GRUNTS)
Aw, don't worry
about your balloon.
It'll just land in the ocean.
(YELLING IN PAIN)
The fish love it.
It's good for their tummy.
(GIGGLING)
(SPUTTERING)
Free party, free party.
It's gonna be
the piggest party of the year.
(ROSS SCREAMING)
Party! Get a birdsitter.
PIG: Let's go, piggies.
Well, now,
that is some fine handiwork.
Hey, Judge,
you're under arrest.
What?
For looking too good.
(LAUGHING)
Hello. What about me?
Do... Do I get a plus one?
Oh! Thank you.
Let me see, let me see.
(MUFFLED SNEEZE)
(ROSS SCREAMING)
Oh, that was a wet one.
(ENGINE IDLING)
(GIGGLING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
ALL: Ooh!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Almost there. Don't rush me!
(HORNS HONKING)
Deep breath, deep breath.
(EXHALES) And we're
back in the now.
Who's ready for trust falls?
I gotcha.
PIGS: No, no, no.
(LOW GROWLING)
(MUFFLED SHOUTS)
PIG: Help.
(GUITAR PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
* Mighty, Mighty Eagle
Soaring free
* Defender of our homes
And liberty
* Bravery! Humility!
(SCREAMS)
Whoa!
* And honesty
You must have grown up
singing this song in school.
Um...
Yeah. Yes, we did.
Um, right. Yeah.
* Mighty, Mighty Eagle
* Rescue me
Now, you do the second verse.
Uh... I, uh...
Come on.
Me?
Yes.
Do it. Do it.
Uh...
* Mighty, Mighty Eagle
Flap your wings *
Oh, yeah.
* And fill up your big cave
With all your fancy things
That's it.
* Politeness
Good sportsmanship
That's not me.
* And a long attention span
What?
* Mighty, Mighty Eagle
Yeah!
Take it away, Charles.
* Oh, great heroic
Mighty Eagle
* With finer plumage
Than a seagull
Oh, sing it.
(HIGH-PITCHED) * Oh... Oh...
* Oh, oh...
* Um, ambidexterity
Pottery
* And bankruptcy
Ouch!
* Uh, Mighty, Mighty Eagle
Harmonize. Harmonize.
(HARMONIZING)
* Rescue me
(CHUCK HOLDING HIGH NOTE)
(PITCH WAVERING)
Wow!
You know it better than me.
(MIGHTY EAGLE GRUNTING)
So, anyway, the other day,
these pigs showed up
out of nowhere,
and it caused me
a great deal of suspicion...
(MIGHTY EAGLE HUMMING)
And he's walking
out of the room.
Unbelieve... I don't get this.
This guy sits here on
his butt, all alone,
clearly doesn't
leave the house.
He talks a good game,
but he doesn't care
about anyone but himself.
Sounds a lot like you.
Oh, good. Thank you
for your opinion, Chuck.
(BOMB CHUCKLES)
MIGHTY EAGLE: Hmm.
Well, hello.
Hello? Mighty Eagle?
What?
What are you doing?
Uh...
I'm bird-watching.
What?
(SIGHS) Take a peek.
Ah.
Oh, you're disgusting.
Oh, yeah.
Look, are you gonna
help us or not?
I am helping you.
No, this is you helping.
Looking through binoculars,
spying on old ladies.
Whoa, whoa! What is that?
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, my...
(GASPS) I was right.
I was right. I knew it!
Bomb, Chuck, hurry up!
Get out here!
Uh-oh.
(GULPS)
Mighty Eagle,
hey, fly us down there now.
No.
I'm sorry. What?
I don't do that anymore.
I'm retired.
(SOFTLY) Mostly just tired.
Go handle it yourself.
This is everything
I've prepared you for.
What? "Prepared us for"?
Hold on, did I miss something?
Let me just go through
my notes really quick.
Let's see.
Crazy stuff, bragging,
crazy stuff, karaoke.
No, see, I don't see
anything useful here.
(SLURPS)
The whole world,
everyone we know,
is in danger.
Yes, it is.
So, off you go.
Hey, you know what?
I used to believe in you.
When I was a kid, I believed
nothing really bad
could ever happen
because you were here.
And now I see
the fate of the world
hangs on idiots like me.
And that, sir,
is sort of terrifying.
It's time for you to go.
You know,
it's really upsetting to me
that you're
the only bird that can fly
and you're too
afraid to do it.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(ALL GASPING)
Hey, guys, come on, let's go.
We're done here. He's no hero.
So, um, I'm having
a party next Tuesday.
Could you just do,
like, a little pop in?
Come on.
(GASPS)
Hmm.
Come on, run faster!
(WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTING)
Ow! Ow!
Oh!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(EXPLOSION)
Come on, come on,
come on, let's go.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD WHOOPING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(CHUCKLING)
(HIGH-PITCHED) I sentence
you all to four hours
of hard partying.
(LAUGHING)
PIG: Look out below!
(GASPING)
Ooh!
CHUCK: They're
taking the eggs!
RED: Follow 'em.
(PANICKED SQUEALING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
Oh, man!
(PIGS LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
PIG: Move it!
Right on time. Eggcellent.
(MANIC LAUGHTER)
Chuck,
go shut that party down now!
Me? But I only know
how to get parties started!
Go!
On it.
Bomb, we gotta stop 'em.
Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Gotta get more speed!
(YELLS)
It's Chuck time!
PIG: Get to the ship!
Move 'em out!
(HORN HONKS)
(LAUGHING)
Catch.
(DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES)
Can everybody
please stop partying?
There are eggs being stolen!
(SHRIEKS)
Matilda, we need your help.
The pigs are
stealing our eggs!
What?
I'm airborne!
We have to get
back to the village!
(SHOUTS)
Stop dancing
and start running!
(GASPS) Hors d'oeuvres.
My weakness.
Come on, let's wrap it up.
(LAUGHING)
We gotta get
the eggs off the ship.
BOMB: Yes!
LEONARD: Is everyone on board?
Let's go. Let's go.
Use the trampolines.
(GRUNTING)
Can you get up there?
(GRUNTS)
PIG: We've got intruders!
What the heck are they doing?
RED: Untie the ropes,
drop the eggs in the water.
(SHIP HORN BLOWING)
Get rid of 'em!
Get him off of there!
It's too strong.
I can't break it.
Ah! Bomb, blow up the chain.
LEONARD: Knock 'em down.
(PIGS LAUGHING)
Come on, Bomb,
you can do this.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
RED: Come on, Bomb,
you got this.
Blow up.
You gotta get me mad.
Okay, well,
then what makes you mad?
Try insulting me
on a personal level.
Um... Oh, oh, uh...
Your poetry stinks.
You're just a bad poet.
And you know it.
(SOBBING) I know! I know!
(HISSING)
Hey, who wants a birdie bath?
(GASPS)
Mmm!
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
Oh, I'm sorry, Red.
I couldn't do it.
Don't give up.
This isn't over.
LEONARD: Thanks
for your hospitality.
(ALL LAUGH)
Set sail for Piggy Island.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(BOTH GASP)
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS) Oh, no.
We'll find them.
Oh. (SIGHS)
(SOBBING) Oh!
They're all gone.
(SNIFFLING)
Shh, shh. It's okay.
(BOMB SNIFFLES)
(CHUCK SIGHS)
Mr. Red.
What do we do now?
Wait, hold on,
you're asking me?
You knew.
You tried to tell us.
But we didn't listen.
I didn't listen.
Red, we need a leader.
What are we gonna do?
What do we do now?
Wait a minute.
I'm not a leader.
Okay, pigs stole our kids.
That sucks.
Made all you guys
look like idiots.
You know what we gotta do?
We start replacing those kids.
(CROWD GASPS)
Ladies, get busy!
We're gonna be
laying some eggs tonight.
No, no, stop.
No, no, no, no. No.
We're not gonna
replace those kids.
We're gonna get them back.
How are we gonna do that?
What do you mean how?
The pigs
already showed us how.
That is where they went.
And so,
that is where we're going.
But how do we get
from here to there?
I am not aquatic in the least.
Well, uh, you know, uh...
We're gonna
build our own boat.
CROWD: Huh?
BIRD: What are you
talking about?
They stole your kids...
No.
They stole our kids.
I mean, who does that?
Have you ever stolen
anyone's children, huh?
Have you?
I mean,
you look like you would.
And you know what?
I'm a little bit angry.
Correction. I'm really angry.
(CROWD MURMURING)
And I don't think
I'm the only one.
Come on, we're birds.
We're descended
from dinosaurs.
We're not supposed to be nice.
Right?
(EXCITED CHATTER)
(ROARING)
(SQUEAKS)
Uh, yeah. Point... Point made.
Who else here is angry?
CROWD: I am!
Yeah, you are.
We're getting our kids back.
And I don't need any calm,
detached, happy birds.
Not gonna help us.
Don't need it.
I need some
angry flockin' birds.
(CROWD CHEERING)
You hear me? Now, who's angry?
ALL: Yeah! Yeah!
Let's go!
Bring me
everything that floats.
Yeah, yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah.
(GROWLS MENACINGLY)
(GROWLS APPROVINGLY)
(HOWLING)
RED: With every
single feather of my being,
I am not gonna let
any of these eggs
get taken from their parents.
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMING)
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(GROANS)
Chuck, I need you to
tie those crates together.
You got it.
(CHEERING)
Done and done.
Uh, a little help here?
Let's go. Move it, everybody.
(SHOUTING)
HAL: Push with your
upper body.
BUBBLES: I have no upper body!
(GROWLING)
Darn good for
a bunch of birds.
Whoo!
(ALL CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
All right!
When I say,
"Eat the," you say, "Eggs."
Eat the...
ALL: Eggs.
Wow! What a reception!
All right, snouts up.
(WHOOPING)
(PIGS LAUGHING)
Man, it's a snout staircase.
Who thinks of that?
(CHUCKLES)
(FANFARE)
ANNOUNCER PIG: Welcome home,
King Mudbeard!
(CROWD CHEERING)
My father and my
father's father
and my weird Aunt Chloe
have all searched
for the eggs.
Hey!
But only I, King Mudbeard...
Ah!
My pom-pom.
...have found them.
PIG: We love you, Leonard!
I present to you the eggs!
(CHUCKLING)
(SCREAMING)
EARL: Oh, man!
Say goodbye to Harvey.
A feast!
(CROWD GASPS)
I proclaim a feast
two nights hence.
(ALL CHEERING)
Let's go make some omelets!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, I feel
a little nervous inside,
but that's normal, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
Uh,
anybody else got butterflies
in the stomach?
Yeah.
(SPUTTERS)
RED: Probably because
you ate too many caterpillars.
Hmm... Mmm.
Drop your nuts
and move your butts!
Come on, let's go!
(CLAMORING)
(YELLING)
CHUCK: Oh, no.
(CROWD GASPING)
STELLA: I wasn't
expecting this.
RED: Oh, hold on a second.
That guy's the king?
He's got to have the eggs
with him in the castle.
What the heck's a castle?
And that's where we're going.
Hey, guys, do you remember
everything you
learned in my class?
Yep.
Nope.
What class?
Well,
forget all of it for now.
Now it's time to let loose.
Oh, good, because I never
learned anything anyway.
Oh, me, neither.
I actually just
came to socialize.
I came for the snacks.
You don't happen to
have any now, do you?
Ooh! Deep breath, deep breath,
(IN DEEP VOICE) deep breath!
How are we gonna
get over those walls?
Uh...
I'll tell you how.
We're gonna fly.
Remember,
the goal is the castle.
Get to the castle.
Who wants to go first?
Over here! Me! Me! Me!
I do!
Hey! All right, Matilda.
Aw! Always a bridesmaid.
Step right up,
keep your wings,
legs and feet
inside the slingshot
at all times.
Shoot it!
Okeydoke.
Fire!
(SCREAMING)
(CHUCKLING)
And a one and a... Whoa!
Take that, porkers!
EARL: Incoming!
MATILDA: Boom, baby, boom!
(PIGS SCREAMING)
Well, how about that?
My teacher can shoot fireballs
out of her butt.
You! What's your name? Hal?
I've seen you
do something
strange before, right?
Well, let's see,
I'm really good at...
Doesn't matter. Launch him.
(HAL SCREAMING)
Oh, this guy looks good.
CHUCK: He's gonna make it!
(BABBLING)
This is incredible.
We're witnessing
history right now.
RED: Nope. He's coming back.
He's coming, duck. Get down.
(SCREAMING)
Uh, did we win?
Uh, no, not quite yet, buddy.
We're still tied.
Hey, can we get
an ice pack for Hal?
Medic!
All right, who's up next?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What can you do?
(SNEEZES)
Ugh! (SHUDDERS) Yuck!
BOMB: Uh, need a tissue?
(SCREAMING)
(SQUEAKING)
Who's next? We need fliers,
not standbyers!
Let's go!
You go out there
and you show them
how frightening mimes can be.
Yeah!
Oh, my God!
* We're having a feast
We're eating the eggs
* Gonna have a big feast
(MIME SCREAMING)
* We're gonna
eat all the eggs *
(GASPS) What?
What is that?
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Fire!
That guy again. Ah!
Citizens of Pig Island...
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
...if you spot any birds
destroying your neighborhood,
please, capture them.
What did he say?
LEONARD: There's
been a change of plans.
We will eat
the eggs for lunch.
Did he say, "Eat the eggs"?
(GAGGING)
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
Hmm. Mmm.
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
Okay, I want you to
curl up into a little ball.
All right?
Make yourself aerodynamic.
Like this? (INHALES)
To the left. To the left!
Let me at 'em!
Launch!
(YELLING)
Don't mess with Bubbles!
PIG: Get him!
Piggy pile!
Hog-tie him!
I told you not
to mess with me!
Wow! That blows.
In a good way.
CHUCK: To the left!
Hold on, wait.
My left or your left?
(GROANS) My left is your left.
We are facing
the same direction.
Right. Good call.
Just look where
the last bird went
and adjust from there.
I got this, you guys.
All right.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(PIG SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(DISTORTED SHOUT)
STELLA: Hi-yah!
(PIGS SCREAMING)
(COUGHS)
(PIGS GASPING)
She got far,
but not far enough.
Uh-oh.
Get out of our town!
We have to get closer.
Judge power...
(YELLING)
Oh!
Trial by fire!
No, literally,
he's on fire right now.
Can somebody please help him?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS)
* Gotta make you understand
* Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down
(GRUNTING)
* Never gonna run around
Mighty Eagle!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Terence, I got an idea.
Do you think you can
pull the slingshot back
far enough to hit
that giant boulder?
(TERENCE GRUNTS)
Okay. Launch me right towards
the top of that thing.
(LOW GRUMBLING)
Ready?
Red, I'm not gonna lie to you.
I am
(SOBBING)
really gonna miss you
when you die.
Rest in peace, my friend.
Rest in peace.
Hey, guys,
let's not get cheesy, okay?
Ready? Fire!
(SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
This is gonna hurt.
(GRUNTS)
(RED YELLING)
What was that? Huh?
(SCREAMING)
My roof!
Did he make it?
I hope he's okay.
I'm in!
Yeah. I knew he'd make it!
(ALL CHEERING)
Send everyone else!
Guards! There is
a red bird in these walls.
(GUARDS GRUNTING)
Bring him to me.
Aye, aye, sir.
Roger that, boss.
(GRUNTING)
Not in these walls.
In the castle!
Come on, you guys.
Here, pretty bird.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
Whew!
Transport the eggs!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Trot, trot, trot,
trot, trot...
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Launch me exactly the same way
you did for Red...
I wasn't ready! (SCREAMING)
Faster!
(YELLING)
(GULPS)
(GRUNTING)
(EXHAUSTED SIGH)
Chuck, is that you?
(SOBBING) This is
the house of horrors.
I gotta be honest,
you look a little, um...
Fine. You look fine. Come on.
Bomb's on his way.
(ULULATING)
Ouchie!
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS) Ha!
Call in the Piggy Air Force!
(ALARM BLARING)
LEONARD: My loyal subjects,
the treacherous birds
have repaid our friendship
with an unprovoked
act of aggression.
(SCREAMING)
The attack will fail.
We have glass,
we have wood, we have TNT.
We tried to kill them
with kindness,
and now we're
just gonna have to...
Well, you know.
Bye-bye.
(SCREAMING)
Who's gonna go next?
(LOW GROWLING)
BIRD: Aim for that ramp.
(CHEERING)
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Terence! Terence! Terence!
(SLINGSHOT CREAKING)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
CHUCK: No eggs in here.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Hey! Whoa! I'm on this.
BOTH: Redrum.
Uh, never mind.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
PIG: Backup engines!
(WHOOPING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, hold on a second.
Wait, I know that rear end.
That's Bomb.
Yeah, Chuck,
that's not his rear end,
that's his face, man.
Sorry, Bomb.
No prob.
Easy mistake to make.
Thanks for getting me out.
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
PIGS: (CHANTING) We want eggs!
We want eggs!
(LAUGHING)
He was sick,
but then he got cured.
(ALL LAUGH)
"No eggs in here." (GASPS)
Ooh, these are clever pigs.
Okay, look, I'm gonna
run up and tackle
the pig on the left.
Bomb, you could handle two.
Chuck, I don't know
if you can help.
We gotta figure out
a way to get into that
(DISTORTED) roo...
(CHUCKLES)
...oo...
...oom.
Anyone have
any bright ideas?
(GRUNTING)
Uh... Huh?
You are gonna pay for that.
(SCREAMING)
What the heck just happened?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You were saying?
And here we are?
BOMB: We found 'em! Uh-oh.
Aw, come on!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
BOMB: Red!
Guys, come on!
Quick, follow him.
PIGS: (CHANTING) We want eggs!
Things are
looking sunny side up!
(LAUGHING)
Guys, I'm here.
Everything's gonna be okay.
We're gonna get
you out of here.
Hurry up, Bomb! Come on!
I'm coming!
RED: Don't lose me!
Doesn't this
nightmare ever end?
Oh, boy!
We want eggs!
What is he doing up there?
This is a civilized buffet.
(STRAINING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
Huh? (SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Don't hatch now.
Do not hatch now.
Get that red scab off my eggs.
Hey!
Oh, man.
Bomb, are you okay?
Oh, I've been better.
PIGS: (CHANTING) We want eggs!
Hmm.
I'm gonna get a running start.
(SQUEALING) Chuck time!
(GRUNTS)
LEONARD: Fine. Boil him, too.
Let's pig out!
(BUZZING)
Looks like it's just
you and me, pork belly.
I'll be taking that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(PIG SCREAMING)
(PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BUZZING)
Hey! Oh!
No!
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING) Red, we're coming!
Deep breath. (INHALES)
Ow! I'm in!
(GASPS) Classy joint.
MIGHTY EAGLE: Hello!
Where is everyone?
Mighty Eagle!
Where's he going?
Oh, I can't believe
I'm about to do this.
(SHOUTING BATTLE CRY)
Oh, my battle cry?
Coming in, coming in.
Mighty Eagle!
(GASPING)
(DISTORTED ROARING)
Whoa!
(CLAMORING)
Whoa, whoa! Oh-ho!
(GRUNTING)
(PIGS YELLING)
(CLANGS)
Mighty Eagle.
Mighty Eagle, wake up.
Come on.
Oh, that's bad breath.
I can sleep late, Mom.
It's not a school day.
Throw them in the pot, too.
I'll have the big turkey.
(GRUNTING)
Red!
(GASPS)
Hey!
Whoa! What did I miss?
You gotta fly
those eggs to safety.
I got this. Here we go.
(GRUNTS)
Oh-ho! Whoa, oh!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
(PIGS SHOUTING EXCITEDLY)
My eggs!
Don't forget Chuck and Bomb!
Who?
BOMB: Hey!
RED: Those guys!
MIGHTY EAGLE: Right, right.
(GRUNTING)
Gotcha!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
You're not
getting away that easy.
(ALL GRUNTING IN PAIN)
No!
(GASPS)
(CRACKING)
Save yourselves!
Hold on, Red!
I'm gonna save that egg.
Red, don't be a hero. Red, no!
No!
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Huh?
BIRD: Get out of town,
everybody.
Whoa!
Get down!
There's just so many of them!
We're outnumbered!
What? How many?
Oh, no, not that many.
Just the right amount, really.
No need to look back.
Just keep flying. Faster!
(GASPING)
I'll take that.
No, you won't.
Get him!
Gimme that!
(GRUNTS)
Ow! Ow! Ow!
(PANTING)
You just don't know
when to stop, do you?
Here's a two-word answer...
Uh-uh.
LEONARD: Looks like
your little slingshot game
ends here.
Gimme that!
Not gonna happen!
(CREAKING)
(GASPS)
Oh, no.
(PIGS YELLING)
Get out of my way!
(YELLING)
PIG 1: Every pig
for themselves!
PIG 2: I quit!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
I know what I gotta do.
I gotta blow up that ramp.
And that would be
a good plan if you were
good at blowing up.
I need to stop those planes.
Remember me, Chuck.
Remember me!
Bomb's away!
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(PIG SQUEALING)
Oh, hi there.
PIG: Here, chickie,
chickie, chickie.
This little piggy popped.
This little piggy exploded.
And this little piggy went,
"Wee, wee, wee,
I want my mama!"
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
(CHUCKLES)
Come on, Bomb,
you can do this.
Blow up! Blow up!
Uh-oh.
(CACKLING)
Oh, no.
Think explosive thoughts.
(GRUNTS)
Surprise parties!
Yoga poses!
(CACKLING)
Pigs in airplanes!
(YELLING)
BOMB: I blew up.
On purpose.
(PANTING)
You're wrecking my house.
What's wrong with you?
You wrecked my house.
Your house was ugly.
Well, now we're even.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Aw!
(PIG GRUNTING)
Strike!
(BOTH YELLING)
Run! Run!
Guys, look out!
Everyone, stand back.
(WHIMPERING)
(GROWLS)
Terence?
Put on your seat belts,
everyone. Trust me.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PIGS PANTING)
(GROANS)
Well, this is dynamite.
Hmm. (GASPS)
There you are.
Not by the hair of
my chinny chin chin!
(CACKLES)
Oh!
(GRUNTING)
Delicious bird eggy-weggy.
Ooh!
You can't eat eggs!
What are you gonna do?
I'm a foodie.
(CREAKING)
It's over.
You're finished, Eyebrows.
(CACKLING)
FEMALE CLASSMATE: Eyebrows!
(GRUNTING)
CHUCK: Someone has anger
issues.
JUDGE PECKINPAH: Anger is not
always the answer!
(EXHALES)
Well, you know what?
I guess you win.
What?
That was an awesome plan.
Mindblower.
(IMITATES EXPLOSION)
(CHUCKLES)
Really? Well, thank you.
You know, a lot of hard work
goes into my sinister plans.
It does. (CHUCKLES)
Nah, I mean,
your plan was great.
But you didn't plan for this!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
You have annoyed me
for the last time.
Yup.
Ah!
No!
(GRUNTING)
CHUCK: Faster!
Whoa!
(SCREAMING)
(YELLING)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
Cramp. Cramp. (GRUNTING)
FEMALE BIRD: It's him!
Look at that!
Are you seeing
what I'm seeing?
BIRD 1: Jeez,
is that Mighty Eagle?
BIRD 2: It's him!
Wow, this guy looks
nothing like his statue.
Honey.
(GASPS) Our eggs!
Are you okay?
Chuck, my man.
Did you see what
I did back there?
Yeah.
Oh! This egg is
the spitting image of you.
There. Safe and sound.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Oh!
(SOBBING)
(EXPLOSION IN DISTANCE)
Oh!
(GASPS) Where is he?
Red?
(BIRDS MURMURING)
FEMALE BIRD: Where is he?
(YAWNS)
Oh!
CHUCK: I think
he might be dead.
(SOBBING)
(SNIFFLING)
(CRYING)
(COUGHING)
Daddy!
(GASPING)
He's alive!
(HAPPY SHOUTS)
(BIRDS CHEERING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
What?
(BABY BIRD SQUEAKS)
(SQUEAKING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(LAUGHING) Yeah!
Oh-ho!
Red, you're alive!
I thought you had died!
Or defected
to the pigs' side.
Hey, buddy,
way to not be dead.
Hey.
It's good to see you guys.
Come on.
(ALL CHEERING)
(LAUGHING)
(JUDGE PECKINPAH GRUNTS)
RED: Sir. Ma'am.
(BOTH GASP)
I think these belong to you.
(SQUEAKING)
Oh! (LAUGHS)
(ALL GIGGLE)
(CHUCKLES)
(CRYING) Thank you.
(OLIVE LAUGHS)
Oh, Crimson, Woody, Ash.
Who?
Is he talking to us?
You learned
your lessons well.
Come on, bring it in.
(GRUNTING)
No. I'm not really
the affectionate type.
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
Okay. Does it feel like
this is crossing
the line to anyone else?
Yup.
Nope.
(ALL EXHALE)
You're my prize pupils.
Your prized what?
(LAUGHS) Don't you see?
I had to make you
lose faith in me
so you could learn to
have faith in yourself.
That's really
not how it felt.
Tell them, Rosy.
Yeah, I don't think
that's what happened, man.
Oh, look, he's blushing.
(WRY LAUGH)
I'm not blushing.
I'm just red.
(LAUGHING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
MIGHTY EAGLE:
Okay, who wants
an autograph?
(CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(YOUNG BIRDS LAUGHING)
Oh!
MALE BIRD: Hoist it up.
Nice.
(GIGGLING)
Hmm?
(SADLY) Hmm...
(FEMALE BIRDS SQUEALING)
(LAUGHING)
Grand reopening.
Get your worms.
(GRUMBLES)
JUDGE PECKINPAH:
Well done, indeed.
CHUCK: Wow!
Is that you
right there, Red?
Oh, really? Where?
No. They didn't
have to do...
Oh, yeah.
That's funny, I don't remember
crying on my knees like that.
But, you know, it's nice.
Look at that.
They gave Mighty Eagle
all the credit.
They made him look
so much more
handsome than you.
Mmm-hmm.
You know,
back when I was angry,
that would have
really ticked me off.
Ah, forget
about that.
Ooh!
You know what we
should do? Let's go
to the village.
Let's do it.
No, actually, I'd love to
go hang out with you guys,
but, you know,
I got this thing,
and I have another
thing after that thing,
and there's all these
things in a row, so...
Would you
look at that!
What the...
(SQUEALS)
Mr. Red,
welcome back
to the village.
(ALL CHEERING)
(WHISTLING)
(BOMB SIGHS)
(MATILDA LAUGHS)
Mmm!
Ta-da!
(CROWD CHEERING)
RED: Huh?
ALL: * Mighty, Mighty Red
You rescued me
* Defender of our homes
And liberty
* Bravery
* Humility
* Anger-y
* Mighty, Mighty Red
You
* Rescued me
(VOCALIZING)
(TERENCE VOCALIZING)
(HOLDS NOTE ALONE)
(GRUMBLES)
Oh, my God.
(DEEP CHUCKLING)
Mmm.
Hmm?
How did you guys
find the time
to pull this off?
(CHUCKLES)
This is why we went
to go get pedicures,
isn't it?
Nope. We got
pedicures because
we're worth it.
I got gels.
You guys are
something else.
To be honest with you,
I am gonna miss
the beach view.
But so what?
It's still there.
It's just not right
there when I wake up
and look out my window.
Well, you can still
look out your window
and see me and Bomb.
Right.
So, you know,
pluses and minuses.
Okay. See you later.
Oh!
Well, this just
got awkward.
That's really
insensitive.
Want to go
get a bite?
Forget it.
Let's just go home.
Hmm.
Guys! I'm just
messing with you.
Get in here.
(BOTH GASP)
(CHUCKLING)
BOMB: I knew it!
CHUCK: Let's be roomies.
BOMB: Roommates!
Oh, I can't wait to
make a chores list.
RED: Wait, hold on a second.
CHUCK: I'll move my nest
in the master bedroom.
Bomb, you can stay
in the guest house.
RED: No, no, no.
BOMB: Can we get a bunk nest?
CHUCK:
This is gonna be perfect!
RED: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys! No!
(BOMB LAUGHING)
(WHOOPS)
(MIGHTY EAGLE CHUCKLES)
* And how to get along
Oh, yeah.
* And so you're
back from outer space
Groovin' out.
* I just walked in
to find you here
Watch this.
Coming right at you.
* With that sad
look upon your face
* I should have
changed that stupid lock
made you leave your key
* If I had known
for just one second
* You'd be back to bother me
* Go on, now, go
* Walk out the door
* Just turn around now
* 'Cause you're
not welcome anymore
* Weren't you the one
Who tried to hurt
me with goodbye?
* Did you think I'd crumble?
* Did you think
I'd lay down and die?
* Oh, no, not I
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
* I will survive
Whoo! (LAUGHING)
* As long as I
know how to love
I know I'll stay alive
TERENCE: Mmm.
* I've got all
my life to live
(WHOOPING)
* And I've got
all my love to give
* I will survive
I will survive
Whoa. Whoa. (GRUNTS)
* Go on, now, go
Walk out the door
(LAUGHS)
* Just turn around now
* 'Cause you're
not welcome anymore
(EXCLAIMING)
* Weren't you the one
Who tried to hurt
me with goodbye?
* Did you think I'd crumble?
* Did you think
I'd lay down and die?
* Oh, no, not I
* I will survive
(LAUGHTER)
(WHOOPING)
ROSS: Come on, Leonard.
Leonard can't dance.
He's hatching a new plan.
(DEVIOUS LAUGHTER)
Yeah!
* I will survive
* Yeah, yeah
Okay, maybe I'll
dance for just a sec.
(LAUGHING)
(WHOOPING)
Whoo! Show 'em
what you got, Red.
Ba-boom! Come on,
Red Stuff.
No.
Yeah, yeah.
Nice try.
*
(GASPS)
Hmm?
Uh...
Oh! Okay.
Mmm-hmm.
(SONG CONTINUES)
* Ooh! Whoa!
* I will survive
* Ooh!
* Yeah
OLIVE: There you go.
(FEET SCREECH)
(GRUNTING)
Ooh!
Wait. What are we doing?
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GASP)
Watch out.
(PANTING)
(THUMP)
Ow!
ALL: Whoa!
(CREAKING)
ALL: Mmm!
*
* Whoo!
* There's
a moment in this journey
that I gave up
* My boots just
couldn't walk another mile
* And that cloud above
me had no silver lining
* I couldn't buy
a break with my last dime
* Oh, but when I saw you
standing in the corner
* I'd have never thought
that you would have my back
* But then we rolled in
like the thunder
and the lightning
* Threw some punches,
then we had a laugh
* Just some
roughed-up desperados
* Hanging tough
through thick and thin
* Kicking up
dust wherever we go
* I can see that you and me
are gonna be friends
* Who'd have thought
we'd wind up here together?
* It's crazy that
we're standing side by side
* Fighting just like
two birds of a feather
* Who's gonna tell us
now that we can't fly?
* Just some
roughed-up desperados
* Hanging tough
through thick and thin
* Kicking up
dust wherever we go
* I can see that you and me
are gonna be friends
* To the end, you and
me are gonna be friends
* Yeah!
* Here we go!
* Hey, hey, you and me
Different as different can be
* You like to rock,
I like to roll
* You take the high
and I'll take the low
* Whoa, whoa-oh!
* Just some
roughed-up desperados
* Hanging tough
through thick and thin
* Kicking up
dust wherever we go
* I can see that you and me
are gonna be friends
* To the end, you and
me are gonna be friends
* I can see that you and me
are gonna be friends
* Yeah!