- Previously on "The Flash."
- I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
- I think it's time you
introduced these guys
to your mean roommate.
- Tell Amunet I'm done.
- Nobody walks away from me,
Frost.
- So you think DeVoe and
his wife are super villains?
- Who are you really?
- I was born on the same
evening you were.
[screams]
I know every answer to every
question ever asked.
- Incredible!
Clifford!
Your body's deteriorating
faster than the chair
can handle.
- It will survive long enough.
[Jules Larson's "Honey I'm
Home (For Christmas)]
- ♪ The snow's blowing
my flight's delayed ♪
- What are you doing?
- Tinsel.
- Your tinsel to surface ratio
is terrible.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm not kidding you.
- I've done extensive research
to make sure that this tinsel
is properly proportioned
for the tree.
- It's terrible.
- It's terrible?
I'll tell you what's terrible.
- What?
- Your Scrooge to Grinch ratio
is terrible.
- You're a mean one.
I wouldn't touch you
with a 39 1/2-foot pole.
- Haven't heard
that one before.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Cisco,
where's Gypsy?
- She had to work
the holiday shift.
But I think I got her
the perfect gift.
A Gulag-class mech knife
forged in the unholy
blood fires of Earth-22
by none other than...
[together] West 2.0.
- Of course, Gypsy should have
sent something for me by now.
- Awkward.
I'm sure it's fine.
- Yikes.
Did, uh, Rudolph just
diarrhea all over your tree?
- Cool, cool.
Two humbugs.
It's a Festivus miracle.
- No, don't get me wrong.
Ralphie loves Christmas.
I ring in every holiday season
with my nana.
She never remembers me,
but I am getting
that inheritance.
- You are just incorrect.
- Well, if you don't want
to spend Christmas
conning your grandma,
you're more than welcome
to join your friends
at the West family party.
- Extremely obvious.
I saw that.
And by the way,
that sounds like a snoozefest.
Unless, of course,
you're serving baking soda.
- [together] Baking soda!
- Wha...Uh, sorry,
what's that about?
- Uh, well, it's a...
Bit of an inside joke
actually concerning
Killer Frost.
- Classic Killer Frost.
- Mmm-hmm.
- You guys were hanging out
with Killer Frost?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
- I hope you had a great time.
- Oh, we had the best time.
I mean, you're great,
Snowcone.
But my girl Frostbite,
ai yi yi.
- Ah, ah.
- Come on.
- I'm gonna go get
a cup of coffee.
[together] Caitlin!
- Hey, if you see my girl
K-Frost later,
tell her what I said
about the baking soda!
[together] Dibny!
- Too much?
[whooshing]
- Okay, from Oliver
and Felicity.
We have an espresso machine.
All right.
- Okay.
Not on the registry,
but I guess getting married
during our wedding
wasn't on the registry, either.
So, yeah, sure.
I'm not bitter.
- I'll put this
in the return pile.
- Well, I guess
that's everything.
- No, we got one more.
There's no card.
Um...
Great.
It's another set of knives.
It's not even a full set.
Yeah, it's one knife.
That's just shoddy gifting.
- Let me see.
- I'm gonna clean up.
- So, what, so
no speed cleaning today?
- No, we're not in a rush.
- Barry, you barely used
your powers in Bali, either.
I mean, not even
to put on suntan lotion.
- It was a spray-on bottle.
- What is going on, Bar?
- Nothing.
I mean, I don't know.
I have been thinking recently
that, you know,
when I first got my powers,
I would use any excuse
to use them.
It would just be
me and the road,
and everything around me
would disappear.
It's like the first time
in my life
I really felt like
I was at peace.
I just feel like that
all the time now.
I don't have to run
when I'm with you.
[romantic music]
- Aww.
That's so sweet.
[giggles]
- I love you,
Iris West Allen.
- I love you, too.
♪ ♪
- [strained breathing]
- Let me.
[sighs]
- The atrophy of my fine motor
skills is accelerating.
- I'm so sorry, my love.
- Oh, the pain is but fleeting.
After all, today is the day.
- How fitting.
You'll share a birthday
with the Messiah.
[both laughing]
- The Nazarene wasn't
born until spring.
You can check the constellation
patterns to verify that.
♪ ♪
Oh, you've heard this lecture
before, haven't you?
- Maybe.
But I will never grow tired
of hearing your voice.
♪ ♪
- The words are still mine.
Even if the voice isn't.
♪ ♪
Do you have any doubts?
- No.
Of course not.
♪ ♪
It will just take
some getting used to.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Don't be afraid, my love.
This is the great work.
I swear I will stand
beside you in no time.
♪ ♪
[doo wop music]
[bell ringing]
- Ho-ho-ho!
♪ ♪
- Well, it's the dark roast?
The light roast?
What are you having,
the self pity roast?
- I wish.
- Oh, the Killer Frost.
- Finally got a drink, woo hoo.
I'm thrilled that she helped
everybody fight the Reichsmen,
but now it's like
I can't escape her.
Everybody keeps saying,
"Killer Frost is so funny."
"Killer Frost is so badass."
I spent so long worried
that she was gonna hurt people,
but now,
turns out people would
rather hang out
with my villainous alter ego.
- Look, I...I get it.
I know what it's like
to have the evil doppelganger.
But you're not like me anyway.
No, you're different.
You're...special.
And your friends
would much rather
be with you than with her.
- Thanks, Harry.
- You're welcome.
[glass shattering]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
- Ho, ho, ho.
♪ ♪
- This is, like, a lifetime
supply of store credit.
Why would Rory think that
we needed 40 toasters?
- He said that there was some
kind of fire sale.
- He stole them.
- He definitely stole them.
- Yeah.
[buzzing]
♪ ♪
- Barry!
- Caity!
- That's Amunet.
- Hide, hide, hide!
[screaming]
- [grunts]
- Ooh!
- I blocked your glock.
♪ ♪
- Hello, Iris.
My deepest congratulations
on your wedding.
[electronic whirring]
[booming]
[screaming]
[chiming]
- No, no, dear.
- [grunts]
- Frosty melted away.
I've come for you, Caity.
[giggles]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- I'll be right back.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
[electric buzzing]
- Barry!
- DeVoe.
He attacked us on the street.
He took Barry.
- What?
Are you kidding me?
- What happened to you?
- Amunet Black
abducted Caitlin.
- Two people go missing
at the same time.
That's quite a coinkie-dink.
- Yeah, that's a great
observation, Captain Obvious.
- Can you set the satellite
to look
for Caitlin's
cryokinetic energy
or Barry's Speed Force
signatures?
- No, no, we've gotta look
for both of them.
Cisco, I need you
to vibe Barry.
I need to know that he's alive.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
[shuttering]
- [grunts]
- Holy poltergeist!
- [groans]
- Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm just not gonna
be vibing again for a while.
- What about Allen?
- Wherever he is,
I've never experienced
anything like it.
- [sighs]
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
- Hello?
[electricity crackling]
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[electricity crackling]
- Here we are.
- Really moving up
in the world.
- You know,
a sprinkle of enthusiasm
would not kill you.
- Listen, Amunet,
whatever it is
you have planned,
I guarantee you Killer Frost
wants nothing to do with it.
- So right, darling.
I don't need her.
I need you.
♪ ♪
Meet your patient.
- What have you done?
- Oh, there's no need
to be over dramatic.
He's alive.
And I'm sure he'd be happy
to meet you just as soon as
that tranquilizer wears off.
- Why do you have him?
What is he to you?
- My golden goose.
You see,
Dominic here is a delightful
new meta that I...found.
And I'd intended
on selling him,
but unfortunately he did not
want to go so gently
into the good night.
And, um...
I shot him.
- Uh, he's...
- In desperate need
of medical attention.
I know.
And now you know
why I need you, Caity, M.D.
- You're talking about an
intricate cranial foreign body
retraction at best.
At worst that's an endoscopic...
- I'm gonna stop you there,
'cause I've absolutely
no idea what you're saying.
But you see,
it does not matter,
because I knew that you
would understand
what needed to happen.
[dramatic music]
- Amunet, I won't.
I can't.
This environment
isn't sterilized.
The equipment is ancient.
- [sighs]
I suppose I could just
yank it out myself.
- And risk him bleeding out,
or a dozen other
brain deficits.
- Right.
Good point.
Well, there's only one way
to find out.
- No, no.
♪ ♪
I'll do what I can.
- Excellent.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Oh, I almost forgot.
Should he die,
you die as well.
♪ ♪
This Killer Frost iced mocha
is really delicious.
♪ ♪
[buzzing]
- [grunts]
[heavy breathing]
- Hello, Mr. Allen.
♪ ♪
- Not exactly S.T.A.R. Labs.
- [groans]
Who are you?
- My name is Caitlin Snow,
and you're in
St. Andrew's Hospital.
At least,
I think that's where we are.
This place has been
closed down for a while.
- Please, you have to help me
get outta here.
- Easier said than done.
- That blonde lady?
She took you, too?
God, I don't understand
why this is happening to us.
- Dominic, do you know
what a meta human is?
- Listen, I...I didn't
do anything wrong.
I didn't rob a bank
or something.
- No, I know.
People with abilities...
people like you...
they're a commodity.
Especially...
- Especially to Amunet.
- Yeah.
Listen,
I'm gonna be honest with you.
It would be very difficult
to fix what she did to you,
even under the best
of circumstances
with the right equipment.
- But I feel fine.
My head doesn't even hurt.
- Which is a minor miracle.
But if that shard
were to fracture...
- It could cause permanent
motor skills and parallel
brain deficits.
♪ ♪
- How did you...
You have telepathic abilities.
Can you hear what I'm
thinking right now?
[whooshing]
- When did I get my powers?
A couple months ago.
Uh, I took the bus
to my job at the airport.
TSA.
But when I got there,
it was like everyone was
yelling at me screaming mad.
But their mouths
weren't moving.
It only works when I'm close
enough to see someone.
You don't think we're
getting out of here?
- I'm gonna do everything
I can to fix you,
but I can't get you
away from her.
Not on my own.
- Caitlin.
I'm scared, too.
♪ ♪
- Wow.
What an entrance.
So, where are we?
This is your sanctuary?
- What gave that away?
- DeVoe,
if you wanted to kill me,
you could have just
electrocuted me on the street.
So I'm here for a reason.
- Yes, Mr. Allen.
So that I may teach you.
I am, after all,
first and foremost,
a teacher.
- Oh, God.
[sighs]
All right.
Fine.
Teach me.
But first I wanna make sure
I'm all caught up.
You sent your Samuroid
after me.
You arranged to pull me
out of the Speed Force.
You made sure that we turned
all those people on that bus
into meta humans.
Why?
- You see, the finer points
of my agenda
are not part
of today's syllabus.
- Oh, come on.
We can squeeze it in.
I'm a fast learner.
- Please.
You're about as capable
of seeing the breadth
of my machinations as an infant
mastering multivariable
physics.
- [laughs]
- The lesson I have prepped
for today is much more simple.
Life 101.
There are no happy endings.
[doorbell rings]
- Oh.
We have a guest.
♪ ♪
- DeVoe?
- You should learn to lose
every once in a while, Bar.
A little humility will prepare
you for what lies ahead.
Now, if you will excuse me.
- DeVoe!
If you hurt him...
If you put a hand on him...
DeVoe!
[shocking]
- It's open.
[dramatic music]
Good evening, detective West.
Something tells me you're not
here for more of my wife's
world-famous lemonade.
- Where's my son?
- Mr. Allen,
has he gone missing?
- He's not missing.
He was taken.
By someone I am eager to meet.
- Thinly veiled threats aside,
Mr. West,
I'm afraid I have not a clue
as to Barry Allen's location.
I do know, however, that your
colleague is located
behind my front porch carrying
an ionic sub-repeating
pulse firearm.
[laughs]
The bird bath has
a much better vantage point.
A smart man would have taken up
position there.
- A smarter man would
understand that this gun
has no safety,
and my finger is still
on the trigger.
- [chuckles]
- Is there something
you find funny?
- Well, it has occurred to me
that there is an amusing
irony at play.
You being a detective and all,
yet you fail to acknowledge
the most basic result
in missing children cases.
- And what would that be?
- Well, perhaps your son
just ran away.
- Don't.
- Now, I do have
a restraining order
against your son.
Shall I add you
to the list?
- If something happened
to Barry,
there ain't a restraining
order on Earth
that would keep me
from getting you.
I'm coming back with
a search warrant.
- Completely unnecessary,
Detective.
If you desire
to search my abode,
by all means.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- You're not as smart
as you think.
- Yes, I am.
♪ ♪
[electric shocks]
- Come on!
[grunts]
- You're only hurting yourself.
Running faster than sound,
vibrating through walls,
even throwing lightning.
None of that can destroy
this barrier.
- You know a lot
about my abilities.
Is that why I'm here?
DeVoe wants my powers?
You don't have to do this.
Whatever he has planned,
you don't have to help him.
- A helper?
Is that what you think I am?
A mindless minion carrying out
her master's bidding?
Some sort of evil secretary?
- You tell me.
- No, Mr. Allen.
I am now and forever will be
my husband's partner.
[dramatic music]
- I understand that.
You're not the only one
who promised
to stand by your loved one
for better or for worse.
In sickness
and in health.
If you go down this path
with DeVoe,
can't you see that you risk
sacrificing everything
that you have together?
Your entire marriage?
- You're missing the point.
I am willing to sacrifice
everything for my marriage.
I'd ask if you could
do the same,
but there's no need.
My husband already knows.
His body may be human,
but his brain is
smarter than yours.
♪ ♪
[electric shocks]
- Sark me!
- What happened?
- Well, the satellite's
trying to search
for Barry's Speed Force energy
and Caitlin's cryokinetic
signature,
so the bandwidth limiters
are overheating.
- Well, that's what you get
when you rely on machines
rather than
a master private eye.
I've had a ton of missing
person cases.
There was this wife once.
Turns out she faked
her own death.
She was just living in Arizona.
- Are you saying Barry
faked his own death
and moved to Arizona?
- Well...no.
- Well, then shut up.
- Oh, boy.
Tell me you got something.
- Got nothing.
Searched the DeVoe
house thoroughly.
It's clean.
Your father's gone
to check the scene from
where Barry was taken.
- You know, there was
this other case once.
Woman couldn't find
her husband.
Turns out she just had amnesia.
He was home.
She just didn't recognize him.
And I still got paid.
Twice.
- Ralph.
Please.
Shut.
Up.
- You got something you wanna
say to me, Ramon?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I got something to say
to you, Ralphie boy.
Caitlin's been kidnapped.
Of course, she wouldn't
have been at Jitters
in the first place
if you hadn't acted
like such a jackass today,
but of course,
in true Ralph Dibny fashion,
you drove her away
with your fat mouth!
- Maybe I should have
turned my hand into a fat fist.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Oh, yeah?
- Guys, cool it.
- Listen, the people we love
are in danger,
and you can't get it together?
Really?
[uplifting music]
- Whatever.
I'll be in my lab.
♪ ♪
- And I will be in whatever
room is farthest from that.
- Speed lab.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
What is wrong with those two?
- You.
♪ ♪
- Excuse me?
- You know what's wrong.
You're the team leader.
Team leader's supposed
to make the tough call.
I made a call.
I said we would look
for both of them.
- No.
Looking for both of them
is not a choice.
We're overtaxing our resources,
our people,
because you won't face
the hard truth.
And the hard truth is,
we can't look for both.
We can only look for one.
- [sighs]
Harry,
I just made a vow
to love and protect Barry.
To stand by him through
thick and thin.
And now you're asking
me to choose
between my husband's life
and my friend's?
I can't.
I...I can't do that.
- You have to.
Or we risk losing them both.
♪ ♪
You have to choose.
- Damn it.
[rumbling]
- Who's Killer Frost?
Sorry, she's just
on your mind a lot.
With a lot of cursing.
- She is my meta power.
Whenever I get scared or angry,
she takes over.
She is violent and dangerous
and unpredictable,
but she's a whole lot more
useful than I am.
- No, thanks.
I'm already scared to death
of one psychotic woman.
I'll take my chances with you.
♪ ♪
- Dominic, I'm sorry.
It's too risky to perform
this surgery here.
And I don't have any powers
to save us.
But you do.
♪ ♪
[rumbling]
- Take a right.
Caitlin, get back.
♪ ♪
[buzzing]
- Somebody's made
my naughty list.
- Gentlemen, can you please
take Dominic in?
I need to have a word with
Caity in private.
[dramatic music]
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Why can't you just appreciate
how nice I've been to you?
- I don't think you understand
the meaning of the word nice.
- Now, now.
It's not about words.
It's about actions.
And I have not stabbed you
or punched you or shot a deadly
piece of metal at you once.
Today.
So why did you run
away from me?
- Tried.
Tried and failed.
Killer Frost would have
been able to do it.
♪ ♪
- Ah.
I see.
Caity, do you know what I was
doing before I became
the successful entrepreneur
you see before you today?
- Mean British nanny?
- Hmm.
No.
I was a stewardess.
You see, unlike you,
I did not have fancy
scientists for parents.
I did not collect scholarships
or attend fine institutions.
My career options were...
Limited.
So I spent my days
in a quaint little skirt
in there serving coffee
to handsy pilots,
powerless to stop them.
But then the particle
accelerator exploded.
And I was powerless no more.
♪ ♪
[giggles]
I showed those pilots
the error of their ways.
♪ ♪
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because.
Obtaining my powers was quite
literally what made me me.
But the same cannot
be said about you.
There are any number of doctors
I could have come to
for this procedure.
I did not.
I came to you.
Because you,
Caitlin Snow,
are and have always been
remarkable.
You are bright.
Resourceful.
Resilient.
And I am more than certain
you can do this.
♪ ♪
So, with that said,
unless you want to spend
the rest of your medical career
in the morgue,
I suggest you buck up, darling.
You know, pull on your big girl
pants and do the bloody thing.
♪ ♪
- Find Caitlin and Barry.
Come on, you bum!
Do it!
- Are you yelling
at my satellite?
- No, I was just
encouraging it.
Although Sally here clearly
doesn't wanna be encouraged.
- Okay.
One, her name isn't Sally.
Two...
I'm sorry.
Barry and Caitlin.
We've lost them both before,
and it just feels like
we just got them back.
So, sorry I was a dick.
- You weren't a dick.
I'm the dick.
Private and public.
You were just being honest.
If it wasn't for me,
Caitlin would be right here
with you, me, and Sally.
- Not Sally.
- The truth is,
I...haven't had friends
in a while.
I'm sure you find that
hard to believe,
given my good looks
and winning personality.
- Mmm-hmm.
- But I'm out of practice.
I suck at being a friend.
Now Christmas is ruined.
Everyone is kidnapped.
And it's all my fault.
- You're here.
And you're helping.
♪ ♪
- Caitlin's in a vulnerable
state right now.
And Barry can take care
of himself.
♪ ♪
So let's turn off
the Speed Force satellite.
We're going after Caitlin.
- We're on it.
- Let's go get our girl.
♪ ♪
- I used some equipment
that I found in the basement
to jerry-rig and MRI machine
so that I don't hit an artery.
- Now that's ingenuity.
You know, I knew you were
the right doctor to kidnap.
- This is a very
delicate procedure.
Do you mind giving
me some space?
- Right, sorry.
I'll just, um...
I'm gonna leave this
right here.
You know, medical insurance
and all.
- Great.
[beeping]
Ready?
- I trust you.
♪ ♪
- Now I need you
to hold still.
♪ ♪
You might feel some pressure.
Extracting the foreign object.
[squishing]
♪ ♪
Foreign object extracted.
Applying some surgical glue.
[rapid beeping]
He's going into shock.
- So unshock him!
- I don't know if I can.
- [grunting]
- That is not the rhythmic tune
of a steady heartbeat!
I need to hear
a "beep, beep, beep," dearie,
or Dominic won't be the only
flatliner in the room.
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
- Oh.
♪ ♪
- Oh, you're good.
- We're clear.
♪ ♪
- They're all out?
- 40 PSI of inhalation
anesthetic?
That'll keep them out,
but not for long.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
- The satellite's pinging
Caitlin's latent
cryokinetic signature.
- Where is she?
♪ ♪
- East wing of
St. Alexander Hospital.
That place has been
closed for years.
- We'll breach over.
You got your suit?
- Never leave home without it.
♪ ♪
- Caitlin!
[whooshing]
- Damn it!
I was aiming for your head.
♪ ♪
[buzzing]
- [grunts]
So pointy!
That is not very nice, lady.
- [grunts]
- Are you a time traveler?
'Cause those white girl dreads
came straight from the '90s.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Yeah, what he said.
Although, if you wanna give me
your phone number,
we could Netflix and chill,
or...
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Impossible.
- Well, that's the thing.
I am the impossible.
[whooshing]
- We built that cell so
you couldn't run your way out.
- I didn't run.
Just stood still.
Really fast.
- You vibrated faster
than the eye can process.
- Like your wife said,
your brain may be
smarter than mine,
but your body is still human.
It's over, DeVoe.
- Far from it, Mr. Allen.
- [grunts]
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
[car honking]
[tires squealing]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[buzzing]
♪ ♪
[explosion]
[shouting]
[air whistling]
- Flotation mode activated.
♪ ♪
[splashing]
- Life raft was a good call,
Cisco.
[sighs]
[uplifting music]
[whooshing]
- [gasps]
Barry!
- There's no sign of DeVoe.
- The house is empty.
Facial recognition's not
picking up him or his wife.
- So, what?
He just drowned?
- Or went back to wherever
he was holding Barry.
- Why do you think he took you?
- I'm not sure.
But I think that he's
interested in my powers.
- Great.
We got evil Mary Poppins
collecting metas, too.
- Yeah, and Amunet
won't back down.
- Nothing like a lingering
threat to put us all
in the Christmas spirit.
- Speaking of which,
with all this DeVoe stuff and
Cecile being out of town,
I didn't have a chance
to decorate the house.
If you guys still
wanna do Christmas.
- Yeah, of course.
We have a lot to celebrate.
- Do you mind if
I invite Dominic,
that meta we just saved?
- The more the merrier.
- Let's get some nog.
[uplifting music]
- So everything worked out,
huh?
- Yeah, but what if it didn't?
What if he killed you because
of a decision that I made?
Honestly, Barry, I don't know
if I can keep doing this.
- Wells told me about the tough
call you had to make yesterday.
You're gonna have to make
a lot more in the future.
But you made the right call.
I'm proud of you for making it.
♪ ♪
- So, what now?
- Now we have ourselves
a merry little Christmas.
- [laughs]
- Let's go.
["Christmas Is
That Time Of Year"]
- ♪ Christmas is
that time of year ♪
- [laughs]
- What the...
- Wow.
- Ho, ho, ho.
Oh, wait.
[stretching]
Like a bowl full of jelly.
- Ralph, what is all this?
- Well, Joe said he didn't have
any time to decorate,
and I wanted to do something
nice for my friends.
I realize that I don't usually
say or do the right thing.
So I just wanted
to say I'm sorry.
- Well, you...you really went
all out, Ralph.
Thanks.
- Yeah, it looks great, man.
Thank you.
- Well, I'm glad you like it.
- Oh, wow.
- Uh, Caitlin.
Uh, it was wrong of me
to say that Killer Frost
is better than you.
Because the truth is...
No one is better than you.
- Thank you.
And, I know.
I'm the one who saved
the day this time.
- You know, Cisco,
a gift came for you through
one of those death holes
that you call a breach.
- Oh, well.
Looks like Gypsy came through,
I guess.
- Um...
- Wait.
This is a break up cube.
- I thought things
were going so well
with you and Gypsy.
- That makes two of us.
- Ramon,
that's not a break up cube.
You should open that
when you're alone.
- No, no, no, if she's gonna
break up with me,
I wanna hear why.
- No, Ramon, I wouldn't...
Okay.
- Cisco, somebody told me
you've been a very naughty
boy this year.
Why don't you come over
and jingle my bells, huh?
- Sweet baby Jesus.
- Wanna jingle my bells?
- Told you,
not a break up cube.
- And I promise...
- Use the same button to...
- It's not gonna be
a silent night.
- Joe, do you mind if I...
- Take that to your house.
- Yeah.
- No Wally?
- He couldn't make it.
- He still in Blue Valley?
- Cambodia.
[knocking at door]
♪ ♪
- Dominic,
I'm so glad you came.
Come on in.
This is Joe.
- Uh, thank you.
- This house is...
- Bitchin'?
- Festive.
- Thanks for the compliment,
but, uh,
who the hell are you again?
- He's the guy you
just helped save.
- Yeah, a meta who
can read your mind.
- Oh, good.
Then he knows that I'm thinking
that there's only room for one
new guy in this group,
and that's me.
- I'm not here to fight crime
or get a code name.
Just to brainstorm ideas
about my powers.
- I hereby christen thee
"Brainstorm."
- Oh, come on, man!
I've been here for months,
and I don't have a name yet.
[cell phone vibrating]
- Uh-oh.
- What, what is it?
- Security at the loft.
Um, it's probably just more
gifts being delivered.
I'll be right back.
[whooshing]
[beeping]
[cell phone vibrating]
- Hello?
- Hello, Mr. Allen.
- Dominic?
- You really have
an acute sense of detection.
And wit.
But like I said, Mr. Allen.
You are incapable of seeing
the breadth of my machinations.
[suspenseful music]
- DeVoe?
- You really should have
listened to your teacher.
- How is this possible?
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- I told you I have
a very important buyer, Dom.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- As promised.
- Always a pleasure
doing business with
another savvy woman.
♪ ♪
- Please, don't do this to me.
- I won't be doing
anything to you.
[whirring]
- Pleased to meet you,
Dominic Lance.
Or should I say
Subject Six?
♪ ♪
[grinding]
Oh, I have created
many meta humans,
but only your unique abilities
allow me to do...
♪ ♪
This.
[electricity buzzing]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[whirring slowing]
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
You see, Mr. Allen,
three months ago you emerged
from the Speed Force
a new man.
And in order for you and the
world to experience my plan,
I, too, needed to be reborn.
- If you hurt my family...
♪ ♪
- I have no interest
in your family.
Besides, you're gonna need
someone to miss you
when you're gone.
- What did you do?
- I merely left something
for you.
It's a re-gift, as it were.
I don't have need
for it anymore.
♪ ♪
[knocking at door]
- Allen?
CCPD.
Open up.
[knocking]
- Open up in there.
- Breach, breach, breach.
[banging]
♪ ♪
- Don't run.
[banging]
- Move, move, move, move, move!
- Keep your hands where I can
see them, Barry.
♪ ♪
- Clear!
- Clear.
♪ ♪
- Barry Allen, you're under
arrest for the murder
of Clifford DeVoe.
[handcuffs clicking]
♪ ♪
- Excuse me.
I have to go.
But thank you so much.
- Of course.
Thank you for coming.
- Merry Christmas to you all.
- Merry Christmas.
♪ ♪
- I told you
I'd stand beside you.
♪ ♪
- Always.
- Now let's bring about
the enlightenment.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head!