- Breakfast is ready.
- Coming.
Have you finished your homework?
Yes.
Here.
Why are you always so forgetful?
- You'll be late.
- Okay, Mom.
- You need to get up earlier.
- Next time.
[Grocery store]
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By
The Devotion of Suspect X Team @ Viki
Thank you. Thank you.
Have some mercy on me! Have some mercy on me!
- Okay.
- One beef dish.
Thank you.
A signature dish, please.
One signature dish!
One signature dish coming up.
Packed already.
A beef dish, please.
CP...
Find the answer for T.
Chen Xiaoxin.
[Music spreads the wings of dreams]
Please sign it, Madam.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Who's that?
Xiaoxin, is it you?
[The Devotion of Suspect X]
[Jiangbei Criminal Police College]
The information revolution and the Progress of Science
[Tang Chuan, Sr. Consultant, Provincial Dept. of Public Security]
are changing people's lives and behaviors
and are also increasing more and more the levels of concealment and camouflage crimes.
So... does the perfect crime exist?
This murder was disguised as a car accident.
The murderer was a doctor in Physics.
When the murder happened, he didn't touch the victim.
How did he do it?
This device is called a "directional acoustic generator."
[Criminal tool: directional acoustic generator]
It emanates a violent acoustic wave
that can travel in straight lines in the direction given.
So, no one present can realize
that the glass is broken by sound resonance.
The killer used this method to distract the driver with a loud noise,
making him lose control and hit the guardrail.
In order to defeat these sorts of high-IQ offenders,
we have to solve problems using their ways of reasoning
and have the courage to challenge conventional thinking,
even if you are the only one raising objections.
In the game among intellects,
he who thinks wins.
Tell your captain to invite me to dinner next time.
Coming to me for such an easy case?
Come on, give me some time to research.
- Able men are always busy. You are a recognized genius.
- What genius?
The clues are obvious. You just didn't review them seriously.
Tell your captain that your doubt in the case of the falling floor, last time, was correct.
The dead did commit suicide.
1. Based on the distance from the body to the building,
if the deceased fell from the balcony and had an initial velocity,
we can conclude she jumped after running.
2. The broken bones pierced the muscles and arteries
and the blood showed a splash shape, which means that her heart was still beating when she fell to the ground.
- And 3...
- We got a new case.
- Have this.
- Hey!
- And 3. If it's not hard enough, don't come and bother you. Right?
- You...
I've lived here for over 20 years.
I'm familiar with everything in the area.
I haven't seen any stranger today.
- Captain.
- What's going on here?
We found the body of a man on the scene.
The body is severely damaged.
Those are half-burned clothes.
There are coats, pants, and shoes.
The size fits the dead man.
We guess the killer intended to destroy the evidence.
Understood.
That old man reported it.
He found it here when he was doing physical exercises in the morning.
Captain,
the lower jaw and the teeth were smashed.
The murderer prepared tools like a hammer beforehand.
The deceased's fingers were burned.
The fingerprints have been completely destroyed.
Where is the mortal wound?
Here.
The marks of strangulation are deep.
- Have you found the rope?
- Not yet.
Extend the range of the search, including the river.
Yes, Sir.
- Luo Miao.
- Yeah.
What do you think of it?
The murderer's M.O. is extremely brutal and he is good at counter-detection.
It's not a normal homicide.
I guess this case will catch the attention of the media soon.
We have to solve it as soon as possible in order to avoid panic.
Yes, Sir.
Not far away from the crime scene,
we found a rented bike with a punctured tire.
The ID information on the rental card shows that the registrant's name is Fu Jian.
He rented the bike at 11:00 a.m. on April 12.
After screening the recently reported records, we located a motel with a missing guest.
Why have these people become so shameless?
He disappeared without paying the room fees.
All the information of this missing person points to the victim.
[Fu Jian: Male]
The DNA picked up in the room matches the DNA on the burned clothes.
The fingerprints on the rented bike all match those on the glass.
The identity of the victim has been confirmed.
Fu Jian, male, 42 years old.
Time of death: April 12, between 6:00 and 10:00 p.m.
Death occurred between 6:00 and 10:00 p.m. on April 12.
Cause of death is asphyxia from pressure to the neck.
According to our investigation, the victim was single, unemployed,
grew up in an orphanage,
no family, no permanent home, and no criminal record.
We've come up with three suspects.
Two have debt disputes with Fu Jian.
The third one is Fu Jian's ex-wife, Chen Jing.
Chen Jing lives in an old building downtown with her 14-year-old daughter.
Not many residents are there. However, her daughter has no blood relation with Fu Jian.
Police.
What can I do for you?
We found a body by the levee a few days ago.
It's your ex-husband, Fu Jian.
How could this happen?
- Have you seen your ex-husband recently?
- No, I haven't.
When was the last time you saw him?
Last year? Or the year before last?
I don't remember. We haven't kept in touch since I moved here.
Could you tell us why you divorced?
He had a gambling addiction. He would have been a bad influence on my child.
Is there someone else at home?
My daughter.
Ms. Chen, we need to know, where were you on April 12th?
On April 12th...
As usual, I went to work before 7:00 a.m.
But that day, I saw a movie with my daughter after work.
Do you have any proof? For instance, ticket stubs?
I should have thrown them randomly.
Did you go back home directly after that?
No, we went to a noodle restaurant for dinner.
And then we went to a clothing store.
We arrived home at about 11:00 o'clock.
Do you remember the names and the locations of the two shops?
Both of them are near the cinema.
I can't remember the names.
I've found this.
Thanks for your time.
Excuse me, I'd like to ask you about something.
Just one minute.
Have you ever seen this guy?
Nope.
- Are you familiar with your neighbor, Chen Jing?
- Not really.
Were you at home at night on April 12?
I got home at almost 7:00 p.m.
Did you hear anything from your neighbor?
I don't remember anything.
Morning, Professor Tang.
You'd better not touch it.
If it's dangerous for it to be touched, you wouldn't have left it like that.
But the precondition is that the one who touches it has some knowledge in physics.
What brings you here today?
I just passed by and dropped in.
If you want some coffee, wash yourself a cup first.
When your assistant isn't here, you don't even wash mugs.
If scientists liked to wash mugs, then penicillin wouldn't have been found.
Have you solved the case that happened by the levee?
How did you know that I'm on this case?
You were called away in the morning and the news came out in the evening.
Captain said that in the 30 years that he's been here,
he'd never seen such a brutal homicide.
- Any progress?
- We have narrowed it down to three suspects.
I feel there is something wrong with the ex-wife of the victim.
The murder happened on a workday and she brought her daughter out until 11:00 p.m.
That doesn't make sense.
She has an alibi, doesn't she?
When you were speaking of the ex-wife, your arms were crossed against your chest.
In behavioral science, that's a physical sign of being under great pressure.
The result of the investigation must be different from your expectations.
It's pretty exhausting chatting with you.
The ex-wife said she went to a movie on the night of the crime, which can be proved by the movie stubs.
And after the movie, she went to the clothing store.
Movie stubs? Where did she get that?
I know what you're thinking about.
If she kept it on purpose, it could be suspected.
She said she just threw it away, but she found it in a brochure in a while.
If she really was the murderer and put the stubs into the brochure for the police to accidentally find them,
this woman is remarkable.
I met someone who had the same letter yesterday.
This is from the international association of mathematical physics.
It's a small circle. What's their name?
Shi Hong. And he's living next door to the ex-wife.
Don't move!
What class is this?
Shi Hong? Where is he?
You!
Are you muddleheaded?
Is this the exam for geography or art?
You shall take all the responsibility.
Has anyone ever told you that you aren't normal?
How could you solve a math problem in the geography exam?
You know what I was doing?
It's a four-color problem.
If you use different colors for adjacent areas,
any map can be filled with just four colors.
- The teacher doesn't understand it, but I'm not a fool.
- You've done it before, too?
The four-color problem has been proved right. No need to waste my time anymore.
That proof was completed by the computer.
It can't be considered true mathematics.
I want to find out the simplest and the most elegant mathematical way to prove it.
Let me see!
- Let me clean up first.
- Sure.
What shall we have for dinner?
- Let's dine out.
- Let's eat at home.
How long has it been since we last met?
Sixteen years?
Counting from the day we graduated,
it should be 15 years 9 months and 14 days.
You haven't changed a bit.
- Judging from your desk, I guess you are teaching junior high.
- Yes.
It's a waste of your talent.
What about you?
I'm staying at a university and taking charge of a lab.
- You're a professor!
- Associate professor.
And no way to get a promotion.
I'm not good at sucking up to anyone.
We should hang out more often.
Do you still play badminton?
Not really! But I will go climbing the mountain sometimes.
Mountain climbing is quite like studying math.
There's only one summit
with a lot of paths leading to it.
Finding out the most elegant path
is the dream for every mathematician.
Actually, after graduation, I thought about finding you several times, but I never reached you.
I moved several times and lost contact with many of our classmates.
How did you find me?
A friend met you here the other day.
A friend?
His surname is Luo; a police officer.
A man was killed.
He was the ex-husband of your neighbor.
I came to you
because of this.
You didn't forget about our competition, did you?
Every time I go into a room,
I can tell who the smartest person is within 10 seconds.
You mean yourself, right?
I'm not so sure now.
Shall we have a competition?
Let's challenge each other in turn
and the one with more right answers is the smarter one.
You go first. I'll let you.
Use four continuous lines to link up the 9 dots.
You think too little of me!
It's just a warm-up.
Your turn.
[Disproof of Riemann Hypothesis]
Disproof of Riemann Hypothesis?
Does it work?
I just want you to try it.
It was given by a math professor.
I wonder whether your ability is falling behind.
Will it be too hard for you?
Thank you for coming! See you next time!
Don't even mention him to me! He kept harassing Chen Jing after they divorced.
He beat her when he didn't get money from her.
He even dared to come here to ask where Chen Jing had gone to.
Why would I tell him? Such a bastard!
Besides Fu Jian, who else kept in close contact with Chen Jing?
There was one who was a regular guest.
That's an interesting algorithm, but it's still wrong.
I didn't expect you to solve it over one night.
You've got a way for it.
The next-door neighbor got up so early.
She went out before 7:00 a.m.
Are you familiar with her?
We have very little contact.
But I often go to the snack bar owned by her.
I heard that she is a suspect.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Four, two, three, four,...
Such an interesting path!
Yes. But the scene stays the same every day.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Give me some money, please. Have some mercy on me.
- Thank you.
- Four, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
They are like meaningless gears in a clock,
repeating meaningless life every day.
This is the snack bar that belongs to my neighbor.
I'll buy some food in it.
All right. You win this time.
And next time, it will be your turn to challenge me.
Bye.
Thanks.
Signature dish.
On April 12, Chen Jing went to a movie with her daughter after work,
which can be proved by the movie stubs.
The movie ended at 9:30 p.m.
The time of death of Fu Jian is between 6 and 10 p.m.
It would take at least 40 minutes for her to get to the levee from the cinema.
So theoretically, Chen Jing didn't have the time to commit the crime.
The stubs cannot prove anything.
What's more, five days earlier,
Fu Jian went to the nightclub where Chen Jing worked to ask about her whereabouts.
I think she is still quite a suspect.
But judging from the M.O., the killer should be physically stronger than the victim.
Chen Jing is just a woman. It doesn't make sense.
- Luo Miao, check this out.
- Yes, Sir.
- And what about the angle of money and debt?
- On April 15, we found the suspect, Wu Daqing.
And he doesn't have an alibi at present.
Wu Daqing!
That night, we found Hu Gang in an underground casino.
- Stand still!
- Don't move!
He escaped and was listed as an escaped suspect.
A witness said that three days before the murder, Hu Gang had a quarrel with Fu Jian in the casino.
I think Hu Gang is the top suspect as of now.
Okay then.
Go back to your room.
We need to have further confirmation.
On the night of April 12, which two stores did you go to with your daughter?
Please think it over and mark them on the map.
We had noodles around here.
And we went here to look at some clothes.
Welcome! Come in, please.
Police. Did you see this person
on April 12?
I can't recall it.
At noon on the 12th, Chen Xiaoxin told her classmates that she would go to the cinema after school.
The chef at the snack bar also gave witness that Chen Jing left around 7:00 p.m.
At this point, we have no way to confirm, definitely, Chen Jing's movements during the time at the cinema.
The best we can do is ascertain where she was between 9:30 and 10:00 p.m.
Chen Jing. 9:50 p.m.
Now the suspicions on Chen Jing are fewer and fewer.
Let him do it. You can go now.
Then, I'll record the previous result into the database.
Goodbye, Sir.
Your friend, Shi Hong, what kind of person is he?
Why are you asking about him?
I saw you talking to him that day
when I was keeping watch at Chen Jing's work place.
Were you watching her or me?
It is hard right now to continue the investigation against Chen Jing.
Besides, judging from the M.O., the murderer should be more like a male.
So your suspicion is that Shi Hong helped her?
Your friend goes to Chen Jing's snack bar almost every day.
Doesn't that mean anything?
Daily routine is his style.
There's nothing strange about it.
Are you so sure your friend has nothing fishy?
Math means everything to Shi Hong, while money and love are not important at all.
Therefore, it's impossible that he might have killed someone.
You still look so young.
I really envy you.
I'm getting old, too.
And I'm not as intelligent as before.
Your watch is fogging. I'll fix it for you.
Professor, do you need me to do the sample analysis for you?
No need. You can go.
Luo Miao, bring me all the files about the levee case.
I want to see them.
[Criminal Investigation Folder]
[Jiangbei Police Department]
[Criminal Investigation File No. 072]
[D. unable to learn from experience - E. behavior affected by accidental factors F. social maladjustment G. highly aggressive]
[...extremely indifferent to things besides self]
[...antisocial personality disorder]
Why are you still here?
I'd like to know what made you suddenly so interested in this case.
Today, Shi Hong said some words
that shouldn't have come out of his mouth.
He said
that I still look so young that
he envies me.
What does it mean?
Do you recall that you asked me before, what kind of person Shi Hong is?
The Shi Hong I knew based all his values on Mathematics.
He's never cared about appearances.
That something could make him say something like that...
unless...
Unless he has fallen in love.
From what I know about him,
no matter the situation, he would never use murder,
such a foolish method, to solve matters.
If he is involved, the only possibility
is that when he intervened, the victim was already dead.
What could he do at that time?
All he could do was to propose any countermeasure
to help Chen Jing avoid the investigation.
If you also think Shi Hong is suspicious, I have confidence now.
He is just a math teacher. Committing a crime, he must have left clues.
You're wrong!
If Shi Hong is really involved,
if he's really helping Chen Jing avoid the investigation,
you'll have a big problem!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The Devotion of Suspect X Team @ Viki
Nice apartment!
You've moved four times. Each time it gets better.
If you don't leave, I'll call the police.
What's wrong with me checking on my wife?
Go ahead! I can give you my phone.
The police don't care about your lousy matters.
It's also a chance to let them know what you did for a living before.
I'm begging you, leave us alone!
How much money do you owe to gamblers this time?
If you want money, I have none.
Xiaoxin! You're getting taller.
Go away! Get inside.
Why don't you call me? Say "Daddy!"
- Xiaoxin is well-shaped now.
- Go away!
She can be a prostitute in a few years.
Xiaoxin! Open the door!
Open the door!
Open the door! It's your dad!
I'm coming in!
- Go away!
- Get lost!
Open the door! It's your dad!
You want money? Take it! Take it and leave!
Fuck it! Now you have money?
Didn't you just say you had none?
Fucking bitch!
Liar! Bitch!
Chen Jing, it's too tough for you to bring up the child alone.
You should live with me.
Xiaoxin...
It's all right.
You fight?
Fucking brat. I'll beat you to death. I'll beat you to death.
Take this, you brat!
Don't hit her!
Get off!
I'll beat you to death! Fucking brat!
You hit me?
I have to give you a lesson! Take this! Hit me?
How dare you!
It's all his fault!
What about now?
Go inside! Don't come out!
Go inside!
Who's there?
I'm your neighbor, Shi Hong.
I heard something.
Is there something wrong?
Nothing.
We had a cockroach.
Dead?
Is the cockroach dead?
It's fine now.
I'm sorry that we have disturbed you.
I'm going to turn myself in.
You can't! Mom, you'll go to prison.
You did nothing wrong. I don't want you to go to prison.
- Murder is murder.
- I'm guilty, too. I committed murder, too.
If you go to prison, we'll go together!
Give me that.
Have you decided?
If you call the police, I have nothing to say.
If you haven't decided,
maybe I can help.
May I come in?
Just the two of you,
you can't get rid of the body.
How did you know?
I've been living here for so many years,
but I have never seen a cockroach.
I did it alone. It has nothing to do with her.
No, it was me who hit him first.
Stop talking! It has nothing to do with you.
You can't hide it.
He got the bite mark on his hand from Xiaoxin, right?
No, it was me.
It's impossible for one person to strangle him from his back
and seize his left hand at the same time.
The police will find out.
My mom did nothing wrong. She wanted to save me.
Otherwise, he'd have beaten us both to death.
What can we do?
We need to take his clothes off.
If we don't do it right now, the body will get stiff.
Tell me everything about him.
Tidy up the whole place carefully.
I'll give you a new phone number, and try to reach you later.
You both need an alibi.
That's the key point.
But we don't have any.
That's why we need to create one.
- It's me.
- The police came again.
They asked where we went after the movie.
We answered honestly.
Good.
Did they look for Xiaoxin?
Yeah.
They asked if somebody could prove that she'd gone to the movies.
- How did she answer?
- Just as you told us before.
She mentioned a friend.
Good.
That cop seems to have seen through it.
He knows it was me.
I'm really scared.
Every single day, I think I should just turn myself in.
If they can't find any new evidence,
they will turn to new suspects.
Trust me!
Okay.
The shared bike was found there.
Here we found Fu Jian's footprints.
Try to reconstruct the crime now.
On the morning of April 12, Fu Jian rented a bike.
In the evening, he rode here and met the killer.
The killer and Fu Jian knew each other.
He took advantage when Fu Jian wasn't expecting it and strangled him to death with a rope,
then smashed his face with the hammer he carried,
burned out his fingerprints, and also burned his clothes.
Why are you so sure that he got here by bike?
Fu Jian's fingerprints are on the bike.
Why did the killer take off Fu Jian's clothes and burn them up?
To cover his identity.
The same reason why he burned his face and fingerprints.
But why didn't he burn all the clothes?
Maybe he slipped in the hurry.
It only takes a few minutes to burn some clothes.
The killer had so much time to get rid of the body,
but he didn't have a few minutes to burn the clothes?
And as for what you mentioned before,
the killer was so careful in the crime,
but he just forgot to wipe the fingerprints on the bike?
Moreover,
if this murder was premeditated,
why did the killer choose to dump the body here?
He hoped the body would be found soon.
So it seems that this could all be a deliberate set-up by the killer.
Until we have checked out these clues,
I won't be sure.
[RT-Mart]
Don't worry! It's just a neighbor.
With oranges, you have to pick the ones that bounce back when you pinch them.
There's a sunken circle in the back.
This kind would taste sweet.
You can buy this one.
Why do you help us?
Is there a discount here?
Yeah.
You dress almost the same every day.
No one ever told me that.
Signature dish?
Thank you.
[Eat at a regular time. Take care of yourself. Thank you for everything you've done for us.]
Uncle.
I often have nightmares these days.
I keep dreaming about that night.
I'm so scared.
Don't be!
It's all in the past.
My mom and I will be fine, right?
You will.
By the way,
if I disturb you when I play the oboe,
you can knock on the wall to remind me.
Do you know Morse code?
I can look it up on the internet.
Brother Kun.
[Table of Morse code]
I remember you like eating shrimp.
Here.
Thank you, Brother Kun. Let me get it myself.
You haven't changed a bit.
How is Xiaoxin?
She's already in the second year of junior high.
(T/N: the equivalent of 8th grade)
How time flies!
Kids grow so fast.
How are you doing?
My wife died of cancer two years ago.
I'm sorry,
I didn't know.
That woman was so fussy and naggy,
so annoying.
Now there is no one around nagging me.
Turns out, I find it uncomfortable.
I heard about what happened to Fu Jian.
Have they found the killer?
Enough. Don't think about it.
Life is like having a cup of tea.
A bitter taste may last for a while,
but not for a lifetime.
Feel free to find me when you need help.
I will.
Thank you.
Here.
Eat some more.
You really don't need to drive me home.
You're so big. Don't get cold in the rain.
- The rain is too heavy, take the umbrella! I'm going back.
- No need, Brother Kun.
Take it! I'm not a stranger. I'll check on you later.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The Devotion of Suspect X Team @ Viki
It's for your husband?
For a friend.
Then your friend will certainly be very happy.
I don't know what to have for dinner tonight.
It occurred to me that the restaurant you always go to seemed fine.
Did you come here especially for this?
It's not an inconvenience, is it?
This is my friend.
Everything looks good.
No wonder my friend always comes here.
What do you usually order?
The signature dish.
The signature dish has been sold out today.
Then... an assorted double dish, please.
Take away.
Me, too.
Two assorted double dishes.
Hello?
How is business today?
Not bad.
When you are available, I'll take you out for dinner.
It's a little busy today. I need to settle the account tonight.
The two assorted double dishes are ready.
Two assorted double dishes.
You know what, I'll have my supper here.
After all, there is no one else at home.
This restaurant is doing very well.
Let's go to my place to eat.
I'll take you to see where I work.
- Is it far?
- Right down the road.
The Criminal Police College.
On that case of the doctor in Physics,
you must have been a great help to the police.
Even you pay attention to something other than math?
It was such a big piece of news that it was hard not to notice.
Want some?
No, thank you.
Today, you went to the restaurant.
Was that to help the police with the case, too?
I wanted to see the suspect personally.
But she didn't look like a killer to me.
She didn't?
You can't judge a person by their appearance.
The body was found by the levee.
The victim should have been killed at night.
The clues found until now are very limited.
Have you been to the levee lately?
I go there for a run sometimes.
I see.
I took apart your watch
and checked the chemical components of the water fog.
Can I have my watch back?
I'm afraid you have to wait until I fix it.
It is such a coincidence that on that day,
I was helping the police analyze the soil water by the levee.
Two days before the homicide, the chemical plant poured some wastewater into the river.
So, I found some residual components in the soil water.
The components in the soil water are identical to the components
of the water fog in your watch.
I did fall down in that area last time.
Where did you fall? Was it serious?
I'm fine now.
Don't go to the levee these days.
The murderer hasn't been caught yet.
You need to be careful.
I will be.
Right, one more question came to my mind.
To design a problem that nobody else can solve,
or to solve the problem,
which one is more difficult?
Very interesting.
I'll think about it carefully.
In this exam, there was a blind-point question.
Nobody solved it.
Answer me! What's a blind-point question?
I don't know.
For instance:
it seems to be a geometric problem,
actually, it's a function problem.
- Remember?
- Yes.
On the evening of April 12, you said you got home at 7:00 p.m. and then stayed at home all night.
- Do you have a witness?
- I don't.
Both on April 12 and 13 you asked for a half-day leave in the morning. What was the reason?
I got a cold. I took a rest at home.
Then in the afternoon, you came to class. You didn't go to the hospital?
It wasn't that serious. I bought some medicine for the cold.
Do you remember at what time you bought the medicine and the name of the pharmacy?
Please write them down.
Do you know this man?
- I don't.
- His name is Teng Kun.
He was a regular client in the nightclub where Chen Jing used to work.
They've been meeting frequently in the last period.
You live next door to Chen Jing, have you seen him?
I don't pay attention to other people's business.
The information you provided is very precious.
Thank you!
- Brother Miao, Teng Kun is also a suspect?
- No.
Yet you took Teng Kun's picture to provoke Shi Hong on purpose.
- Was it Professor Tang's idea?
- No. It was my idea.
Professor Tang said that Shi Hong would never be moved by emotion.
But I think it's the opposite.
Emotion will be his only weakness.
I hope Shi Hong will start making mistakes.
Have I been bothering you with these dates?
No, I just want to stay at home with Xiaoxin more.
It's so hard for you to raise Xiaoxin alone.
Xiaoxin needs a complete family.
I do, too.
What is your relationship with this man?
You're not considering what I've done for you, either.
Break up with him immediately.
Otherwise, I can make him disappear, too.
You should understand my words.
Brother Kun, shall we still go to the south side?
In the parking lot behind the Times Tower on Jianshe Road, somebody got hurt. Need an ambulance.
I'll send someone there immediately.
Please leave your name and phone number.
Catch him!
Drop the weapon!
Who's behind you? Tell the truth.
I really don't know who he is.
He contacted me online.
He just said he would pay the rest after I gave that guy a lesson.
Never seen him before?
Teng Kun received a blackmail letter.
These photos were in it.
Is there anybody stalking or harassing you?
Don't be afraid!
Please believe the police will ensure you and your daughter's safety.
No one.
If it's just for revenge,
why would he call the police before murdering?
This should only be a warning.
He must have planned it all. We can't find a flaw.
Sir! The voice print was tampered with.
It can't be recognized.
[Shi Hong: Climb the mountain together tomorrow?]
I thought we were just going out for one day.
There are a lot of variable factors in the mountains.
It doesn't hurt to bring something more and be prepared.
When I meet problems that I can't solve, I come here and take a walk.
It feels like this mountain is a part of me.
All worn out?
Not too bad.
Chop the wood!
These trees seem very old.
No matter how long they live,
in the end, the result will always be this.
I thought I knew you well.
Little by little, I realized
you seem to be hiding many things that I don't know.
I remember you once said
that studying math is the same as climbing a mountain.
There was a time before
when you understood that feeling?
There's a mountain in front of you.
You have been climbing for a long time,
but you can only wander back and forth in the mountain forest.
You can't reach the peak.
You can't find the way out, either.
Unexpectedly, you're caged.
The harder I struggled,
the deeper I was trapped.
I completely felt like a meaningless gear.
I couldn't tolerate myself like that.
I can imagine that despair.
But I also believe
that you can find a good way out.
For me, the best way out
isn't going out,
but going down.
Have some soup.
I hadn't taken fresh air like this in a long time.
When I finish this case,
I'll take a long vacation.
Cases will never be finished.
Resting a while is best for you.
I can't rest.
Nowadays, murderers are harder and harder to deal with.
Like that doctor in Physics.
His M.O. was practically flawless.
We only arrested him after much effort.
Guess what he said in the interrogation room?
He said,
even if he hadn't been caught by us, he would have chosen to turn himself in,
because he couldn't bear the feeling of guilt in his heart.
Thank you for telling me this.
Thank you for bringing me here.
Don't forget to come back in winter and have a look.
It will be another view.
Mom, today I have to compete in a music contest.
Mom!
Come back home right after school, okay?
Okay.
Dig in! Don't be a picky eater.
- Prosperity Eatery.
- Go fetch your mail in your mailbox.
This is the last time I will contact you.
You ruined all I had, so I'll take what's yours.
Officer Luo, please save my daughter!
Save my daughter!
Chen Xiaoxin is not at school.
She went on a trip to attend a competition with the school band. They departed a while ago.
- Hello?
- Shi Hong stole the directional acoustic generator.
Damn it! Chen Jing just called me and said Shi Hong threatened to hurt her daughter.
- Call the school now!
- Chen Xiaoxin is not at school.
She and her school band are on the way to a competition out of town. There are more than twenty students on the bus.
If Shi Hong attacks the driver, the bus will be out of control. That will put all the students in danger.
- I'm driving there.
- I'll go right away.
When the difficulty comes,
please raise your right hand
I got the teacher's number.
It represents hope
It won't worry about the frustration
The teacher isn't picking up!
Look!
It's them!
Mom, I'm fine!
- Sit down, for now.
- Please, students, sit down and be quiet.
Luckily, we got ahead of Shi Hong.
It's too simple. Too simple.
It can't be this simple.
It seems to be a geometric problem,
actually, it's a function problem.
What if Shi Hong's target is not Xiaoxin?
- Professor Tang is in danger!
- What do you mean?
Without him, nobody can prove Shi Hong is the murderer.
What?
[Luo Miao]
Pick up!
Come on, pick up!
- Hello?
-Where are you? Shi Hong's real target is you!
Tang Chuan!
Tang Chuan! Tang Chuan!
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The Devotion of Suspect X Team @ Viki
Luckily you didn't die.
You still owe me a bunch of sandwiches.
I just sprained my neck.
Let me out as soon as possible.
Captain said to do as you wish.
He'll let you rest for a few more days.
The case is closed?
Shi Hong has pleaded guilty.
He confessed he murdered Fu Jian by the levee
because he was obsessed with Chen Jing. He didn't want her to be entangled with her ex-husband.
He took us to his home.
In the cabinet we found the electric wires, the hammer,
and the airbrush he used for the murder.
We also found an audio monitor on the wall.
He confessed he had been listening in to Chen Jing for a long time
and knew her every movement.
When the murder happened, Chen Jing wasn't aware of it.
And then, Shi Hong kept stalking her and harassing her.
He also sent her a blackmailing letter. All of this checked out.
I really never thought he was that kind of person.
Shi Hong also confessed that he was the one who had Teng Kun beaten.
And he's the one who made that call to the police, too.
The evidence we hold now completely matches his confession.
The case will be closed right away.
A few days ago, suspect Shi was transferred to the department of justice.
What awaits him is the most severe penalty.
That's the full report on the 413 Levee homicide.
Thank you for watching.
Mom, why did they say that in the news?
He is the same as that man. He's not good.
Our neighbor is a good man. He is innocent!
It's not him!
You have solved such a big case. You will get a promotion.
Why are you so downcast?
I'm not in the mood.
Two days ago Chen Xiaoxin fainted at school.
How could a child go through that?
All the people involved in this case will need a while to get over it.
I feel something wrong in this case.
That day, how did you guess that Shi Hong's real target was me?
It suddenly occurred to me that he mentioned the blind-point question.
"It seems to be a geometric problem, actually it's a function problem."
Sounds like his style.
Back in the day, the first question he ever challenged me with was a blind-spot question.
Try to link up the nine dots with four lines.
The key to solving this question is to avoid habitual thinking.
You fell into the trap set by the designer;
hence, you failed to solve it.
If she kept it on purpose, it could be suspected.
I did fall down in that area last time.
He was on leave for two consecutive mornings when the crime happened.
I completely felt like a meaningless gear.
I couldn't tolerate myself like that.
It can't be.
The answer is too simple.
How could I have not seen even this?
What's wrong?
Maybe we were all wrong.
The truth is not at all as we think.
What do you mean? Isn't the case very clear now?
If uncovering the truth only brings more pain,
then all along...
what on earth have we been after?
And what is the meaning of truth?
I suppose you still remember who I am.
Today, I'm not here to see you as a policeman.
What I am going to say is only my personal guess.
You need not reply.
Your alibi is real.
On the night of April 12, you did see a movie with your daughter;
hence, no matter how the police questioned,
you and your daughter could always answer honestly.
Because you didn't lie.
But you must consider it strange.
Why did you not need to lie?
Why did the police only ask about the matters of April 12?
Because it was on the day before, April 11,
that you killed Fu Jian.
In fact, you aren't willing to believe that Shi Hong is a psychopathic stalker either. Right?
In your mind, he shouldn't be that kind of man. Right?
You know nothing about the truth.
You can't even imagine what he actually did
to protect you two.
Shi Hong, someone is here for you.
Give me a few minutes. Turn off the surveillance.
Are you still well?
This place is very fitting to research mathematical problems.
You didn't mean to kill me at all.
The car windows were not shattered, which shows that you'd turned the power of the sonic waves to the lowest setting.
Otherwise, I would have long been dead.
You pretended to be a psychopathic stalker
just to protect her.
The first step in solving a problem
is to understand what the real problem is.
My detective friends thought that, in order to solve the case,
they should first invalidate the alibi.
That's how they fell into your trap.
What do you want to say?
That body...
is not Fu Jian's at all.
Fu Jian died on the day before the levee homicide,
which was April 11th.
When you intervened,
Fu Jian had already died.
You decided to create an alibi.
On Fu Jian's body you probably found a motel key
and his bike-rental card.
On the second day, you went to Fu Jian's motel room first,
erased every trace he left.
Then you found a vagrant with the same shape and size as Fu Jian,
you made him wear Fu Jian's clothes and stay in that room.
So, what was left in that room
was only the vagrant's hair and fingerprints.
You also used Fu Jian's bike-rental card to rent a public bike.
At the set time, the vagrant left the room
to go meet you at the given place.
After you met him, you made him use the public bike you rented.
On the bike, too, the fingerprints left belonged to the vagrant.
You two rode bikes to the levee,
then...
you strangled him.
You smashed his face and made the body unidentifiable.
Then you deliberately burned his fingerprints,
but left other clues of his fingerprints.
The aim was to lead the police into thinking that that corpse was Fu Jian's.
You were on leave for 2 consecutive days.
You used the time to dispose of Fu Jian's corpse.
All of this had been part of your sophisticated calculations,
but you didn't expect that I would appear.
You realized that the truth would be found out sooner or later,
hence, you changed the plan.
You hired someone to attack Teng Kun.
You wrote the letter to intimidate Chen Jing threatening her daughter.
While you were sure I would survive, you also attacked me.
You let everyone believe that you were a psychopathic stalker and deserved the punishment.
Because this was the only way that Chen Jing wouldn't turn herself in.
Fu Jian's murder in truth happened on April 11.
Shi Hong,
in order to cover all of this,
you killed an innocent person with your hands.
You can draw your own conclusion.
You're free to do so.
I don't understand.
On April 12,
a vagrant who lived under the bridge went missing.
His whereabouts are still unknown.
If we can just find his family members,
we can do a DNA test.
Then the identity of the victim of the levee homicide
will emerge.
Even if your assumptions are correct,
finding your so-called vagrant's family members
would be like dredging for a needle in the sea.
The case is almost settled.
No matter what verdict the judge gives, I will not appeal.
Fu Jian's homicide ends here.
What a pity!
Such a bright mind as yours,
in fact, was used for this.
Shi Hong, what on Earth has she done for you to deserve your...
She... once saved my life.
Sorry to disturb you, I'm your new neighbor from next door.
My name is Chen Jing. This is my daughter, Xiaoxin.
Hello, Uncle!
Excuse me, do you have spare books in the house?
I'm sorry, it's a task assigned by her teacher.
It doesn't matter if you don't.
Will this do?
[Basics of partial differential equation]
Hurry, say thank you to the uncle.
Thank you, Uncle. This is for you.
Oh right. Xiaoxin has been studying a musical instrument recently.
If she disturbs you, please do tell us.
Goodbye, Uncle.
[Thank you for your kindness!]
Xiaoxin, come take a look for me.
On this table of coordinates that is the world...
Look. Does it look nice hanging here?
-...having the two dots representing them...
- Here?
...to me is just like a miracle.
- Signature dish.
- Signature dish!
I'd never hoped to walk into their lives.
And they aren't people whom someone like me can make happy.
Here, one signature dish.
Sometimes,
if a person simply lives well,
it is just enough to save another.
Without them,
there wouldn't be the man I am now.
All of this was not about finding the culprit,
it was repaying their kindness.
That man seems reliable.
Being with him
their chance of being happy should be quite high.
Chen Jing,
please forget me completely.
If you two know nothing about the truth,
it will be best.
If you don't live happily,
all I did will then be in vain.
Goodbye, Tang Chuan.
I'm the winner.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
For us, you...
A woman like me
does not deserve it.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm the one who killed him.
Everything started because of me. It's all my fault!
If anyone, they should have caught me.
I should be punished as well.
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
- This is all I can do.
I'm sorry.
This is all I can do.
Take them away!
Come!
[Three months later]
All supplementary documents have been handed over.
I'll be back in a bit.
Are you waiting to appear in court?
Yes, as a witness.
The coloring problem can be written in such a thick book?
Some problems seem very simple,
but they are hard to explain.
Sometimes, even a lifetime is not enough.
I visited Chen Jing yesterday. She cheered up a bit.
She was trying to write letters to her daughter and Shi Hong.
Aren't you going to visit Shi Hong?
[The mathematical proof of the four colors problem]
Is this problem difficult?
Yes,
too difficult.
Timing and Subtitles Brought To You By The Devotion of Suspect X Team @ Viki
Who is your difficult problem?
Easy to solve, hard to figure
Foolish people!
A lifetime of poverty makes them smart
Can you plead innocent?
Whose answer are you?
Open the door, come out
The torbid crowd
turning up and down
No one can keep out of it
Who's your unexpected accident?
Constant doubt, how to let go?
Who owed, whose debt? (Who understood?)
If you can bear it, then you can give up (Who's innocent?)
Blank mind, innocent heart
Owed love, returned love, not missing love
Who never owed, whose debt? (Who understood?)
You can bear it, you can put it down (Who's innocent?)
Two empty hands, full innocence
Didn't take those clouds away, of course, are there
As soon as you confess you understand
empty hand, innocent heart