My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
"I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me."
But I became lost in time.
"It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back."
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
This is where
I came out of the Speed Force.
And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
DeVoe orchestrated everything to get
the people he wanted on the bus.
But why does he need their powers?
I can't figure out his end game.
We got a planner. Just like Thawne.
I hereby deem Barry Allen's appeal
- denie...
- Wait!
- DeVoe?
- Not DeVoe. It's Ralph.
Barry Allen
is hereby ordered released immediately.
Some people don't think
you should be back on the force.
When do you think I can come back?
When everyone believes DeVoe
is really alive and well.
I call this my "thinking cap."
He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers.
- All of them.
- We know a bus meta?
There's three more people out there
who need our help,
and we need to find them
before DeVoe does.
What if...
What if I just, like,
breach all three of the bus metas
to, like, Earth-2?
How about this?
We alter each bus meta's DNA
by performing inter-cellular surgery?
And what, and turn them into chickens?
Yeah.
We're not Frankenstein-ing
innocent people.
Listen, Ramon.
DeVoe wants these bodies.
Maybe we change the bodies,
we keep these people safe.
I'm sorry. Don't you have like six PhDs?
- Seven.
- Yeah, which one of them
is in mad science?
Mad science is just an area of study.
It's not a degree. Okay? And by the way,
I don't see you coming up
with any other ideas.
You know why? 'Cause it's
bedtime over here on Earth-1.
Do you know what bedtime is?
Do they have that on Earth-2?
- Bedtime...
- It's this thing where we just
shut down to recharge our batteries.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I highly recommend it.
- Harry.
- You're still here? What?
No matter what you think,
DeVoe has already thought of it.
So why don't you just go home,
recharge, start again in the morning,
all right?
I'm gonna keep going.
Good night.
Maybe you have thought of everything.
Just like Thawne.
What is all this?
This is gonna give us the edge
we finally need
to be smarter than DeVoe.
Or for me to be smarter
than DeVoe, actually.
Take a look at this.
What is that?
This is an intelligence booster.
You put this thing on Dibny here,
and even he will be able
to understand Poinsot's Construction.
You put it on a real genius,
I'll finally be able to out-think
the Thinker.
You know what?
I'm not sure this "thinking cap"
is the best idea you've ever had.
It's an intelligence booster.
Looks like a thinking cap.
You don't like it, blame yourself.
- You gave me the idea.
- What?
You're the one that said
DeVoe planned all this,
just like Thawne,
in order to stop Barry,
and you said
that DeVoe became the Thinker
the same night you became the Flash
and so I hacked into the security
footage of that night
to see how he did it.
This is why he is so smart.
DeVoe boosted his intelligence
with neurochemical engineering
powered by the dark energy from
the Particle Accelerator explosion,
and if we build our own,
we can do the exact same.
Wait. You want to blast your brain
with ten billion joules of dark energy?
I've harnessed energy from the
Particle Accelerator explosion before,
and I can do it again.
Yeah, but, Harry, re-engineering
your brain's neurochemistry, that's...
DeVoe did it.
So can I.
How many more metas have to die
before we finally stop DeVoe?
Uh... not... not me. I mean...
I say we go for it, right? Right, guys?
What do you think?
I say we explore it.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Ramon?
No, this is way too risky.
Of course, it's risky,
but if we succeed,
we will save the lives
of the four remaining bus metas,
including a member of our team.
You're talking about
intense amounts of dark energy
going right into your brain,
right into that cap,
that turned
a mac-and-cheese-loving pacifist
into a homicidal maniac.
You put that cap on,
what's it gonna do to you?
I ran the numbers dozens of times.
The math and the chemistry
check out. I can do this.
- I don't think you can.
- I can with your help.
Not this time.
All right, let's keep coming up
with more ways to solve this.
Just so I'm clear on this,
someone finally came up
with a way to stop
this La-Z-Boy-riding lunatic,
and we just might not do it?
That's really cool, guys.
- I got this one.
- Yeah, thanks.
It's the only way.
I'm gonna do it
with or without his help.
Hey, Ralph.
Look, don't worry, okay?
We're gonna figure this out.
Yeah, everybody keeps saying that,
and each time we almost get DeVoe,
he gets away.
Every time he gets away,
he's one step closer to getting me.
Hey! That is not going to happen.
Well, I can't
take that chance anymore, Iris.
So, if anyone needs me,
I will be downstairs
in my tiny guest quarters
until this is over.
There are still three bus metas
out there.
And we're gonna need your help
to find them and protect them.
Iris, the only person I need to protect
from now on
is good ol' Ralphy boy.
You are part of this team.
Yeah, and I'm the only one with a body
that DeVoe is trying to snatch.
You don't have any concept
of how dangerous it is for me out there.
Yes, I do.
- How could you?
- Because I am the leader of this team.
Yeah, that's right. You are.
But you're always back there, hiding,
safe and sound.
While the rest of us
are out in the field,
putting our lives on the line.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Some drama in the Cortex.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- It's all good.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm, you know...
Cecile's in her third trimester,
so it's definitely getting serious.
You guys have any names picked out yet?
Uh, yeah, a few.
Come on, I'm not gonna tell anybody.
No, you're not,
because you're not gonna know
until Cecile tells you.
- All right.
- Anyway,
I talked to Singh
about getting you back in the lab.
Yeah, and?
It's gonna be awhile.
Why? I thought
Judge Hankerson and Singh
had everything they needed.
We thought so, too,
but the mayor wants to sit down
with the DeVoes herself.
Seriously?
Look, we can't find Marlize,
so the only chance we got
is to get Ralph to use his
nauseating powers
to impersonate DeVoe again.
I'll ask him, but right now
he'll barely leave S.T.A.R. Labs.
What happened to that whole
buddy system thing you had going on?
It's not enough for him, I guess.
Then I don't know, Barr.
I should be out there, helping people.
Putting bad guys away.
Right now, we should be trying
to stop DeVoe
and finding those last few bus metas
'cause I got a bad feeling
one of them is gonna show up soon.
Next time, it'll be your hand.
Now,
everybody on the floor.
Dude, you got a death wish?
Do what he says.
Stealing is a sin.
You shouldn't be using the powers
you've been given this way.
I'll use them any way I see fit,
including frying you to a crisp
if you move any closer.
I don't think you will.
You don't want to hurt me
or anyone in this bank.
You can still walk away from this.
But the moment you touch that money,
your life changes forever.
Now, you don't really want that, do you?
Maybe you're right.
Or maybe you've got a death wish.
What the hell?
My powers, they're gone.
No, no, no!
Hey, buddy, you're a real...
hero.
- Cisco.
- Hmm?
What have you got?
Oh, you know, the usual.
Just loads and loads of dark matter.
Makes sense. Eyewitnesses said
this guy melted this vault door
with fire from his hands.
Hmm, figures. And not just any fire.
This fire melted through ten inches
of reinforced steel.
I mean, that would take over
6,000 degrees Fahrenheit,
ten times the thermal output
of Rory's heat gun.
Well, here's where it gets weirder.
Apparently, shortly after,
his powers stopped working.
"Stopped working"?
Yeah, so if he was one of our bus metas,
I guess we have one less to worry about.
How would his powers stop working?
Erik Frye.
Six months ago, were you on the 405 bus?
Please.
Do I look like someone
who takes public transit?
All right, then, Mr. Frye,
how long have you had your powers?
A few years.
You're an OG meta.
And you just started using them now?
Here, yeah.
Once Flash showed up,
I took this act on the road.
Doesn't matter anymore, though.
Right, you don't
have your powers anymore.
'Cause they just disappeared,
vanished into thin air? Huh?
All right, Cisco.
He's clear.
You have any idea how this happened?
One minute, I had powers.
The next, nothing.
Can you get him out of here?
That's right. Get him out of here.
No rights?
Yeah, get him out of here.
I can't believe his powers
disappeared like that.
How does someone lose their powers?
So, I can think
of a couple of ways
this might have happened.
If this Erik Frye metastasizes
solar radiation to create heat,
we could put him in the dark
to de-power him.
But it was still broad daylight.
Okay, maybe his internal
biochemistry has been altered
to create its own internal
thermal combustion,
and he just ran out of fuel.
Okay, so if this guy
is not one of the bus metas,
then that means that
there's still three more out there
before DeVoe gets to me,
so I'm safe... Safer. I'm safer.
Those are innocent people, Ralph.
I'm innocent.
I'm still gonna get terminated.
God.
I'm Sarah Connor.
No. I'm gonna go back to my room,
get some comfort food.
Ralph.
The way I see it,
Frye walks into the bank
with his fire powers,
meets this other guy,
and then his powers are gone.
Coincidence, I think not.
So you think this guy
did something to Frye?
I think we can ask him some questions.
I interviewed every eyewitness
in that bank.
Nobody knew who he was.
Cisco, why don't you cross-check
the deposits from today
with Dad's witness list?
Way ahead of you.
Everyone on the list checks out,
except Matthew Kim,
an EMT out of Central City General.
Barr, let's go ask some questions.
Oh, I'll go.
Barry, you can stay here.
Um, okay, I...
Well, you know, I never go out
into the field,
so I thought, you know...
Yeah, I mean, you're the boss.
Okay, Caitlin, why don't you see
how this power-stealing thing works,
and, Cisco, why don't you use
the satellite's tracking parameters
to scan the city for dark matter?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I'll just come running, if you need me.
Okay. Thanks.
Can I hang out in here?
Can you...
Do you mind...
Can you save the eating till later?
We're actually trying
to save lives here.
This is really good though.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
You put this together pretty quick, huh?
Yes, I did, for a test run.
Oh.
I can feel my neurons firing.
Firing at a rate
20 times their normal rate.
And that's without
the addition of dark matter.
I can feel my brain's
processing systems evolving.
There's a 67% chance
you're gonna spill
that mustard on the floor. Oh!
Okay, how did you do that?
Well, I simply
analyzed your eating habits
and extrapolated them into
a predictive behavior model,
all within four seconds.
The cap is working.
Eh, cool, but not quite convinced.
No? Really, you're not convinced?
All right, then.
The answer is none.
And have a little more respect
for your body, will you?
It's a veggie dog, man.
I'm not talking
about the veggie dog, man.
I'm talking about the wiping the mustard
on the pants,
causes the pant movement,
which indicates
a lack of clothing-to-bodily friction,
which can mean only one thing.
Right.
What kind of underwear am I wearing?
And the answer
is none.
You got all that
from your fancy metal cap?
- Yes, I did.
- It's impressive, Harry.
Except for one very small thing.
Which is?
Your head is on fire.
It's not...
When I mentioned
spending more time together,
I meant family barbecues,
not questioning people of interest.
I know. I just want people to know
that I'm not afraid
to go out in the field
every once in a while.
Who says you are?
- Ralph.
- Ralph?
He should talk.
He won't even leave the building.
I know, but he made me wonder, you know,
what kind of leader constantly
puts everyone else's life on the line
except their own?
Baby.
We all know you're fearless.
Whenever you've been needed
on the field, you've gone.
So don't let Ralph get in your head.
Excuse me.
CCPD. We're looking for an EMT
named Matthew Kim.
- Yes, he's right through there.
- There?
Thank you.
Matthew Kim.
Detective Joe West, CCPD.
We'd like to ask you some questions
about the attack
at Central City Bank this morning.
I wouldn't know anything about that.
Really? 'Cause I have
a dozen witnesses that saw you
stand up to the man
that melted the vault.
He was going to hurt people.
It was my duty to help them.
Any reason you left
without making a statement?
I need to finish restocking my inventory
before another call comes in.
- I can't help you.
- Look, Matthew,
we know you had something to do
with the guy at the bank
losing his powers.
We need to know, what did you do to him?
Why? So you can steal mine?
No. No.
- Let her go.
- Put the gun down.
I said, put it down.
He didn't deserve
those powers.
He was hurting people.
Flash.
You're not the only one
that's been blessed with powers.
I'm helping people, too.
Not like this.
You did this, not me.
I got him.
I lost my speed.
What do you mean, you lost your speed?
Uh, guys, I think I found it.
This is amazing.
Yeah, it is.
Well, I've run every test
I can think of.
EKG, cellular regression synthesis,
brain chemistry,
and dark matter confirms it.
Iris is a speedster.
So what about Barry?
Um...
Everything that was a part of you,
your speed, connection to
the Speed Force, the dark matter,
it's all a part of Iris now.
- Can you...
- Reverse it?
I don't know. I can try.
So Matthew Kim isn't just removing DNA.
He's transferring it
to anybody he touches.
He's not getting rid of metas.
He's creating new ones.
Well, that's not the only thing.
Guess who's got an apartment
just a block away
from the 405 bus line
and rides it every day to get to work.
So, Matthew is our bus meta,
not Frye, which means that
DeVoe is gonna come after him
sooner or later.
And if DeVoe gets Matthew's abilities,
he could take away all our powers.
Unless we get him on our side first.
Then he can remove
the meta DNA from DeVoe.
- Would that work?
- I mean, yeah.
It could. As best I can tell,
Matthew's abilities
work by melting down
the highly concentrated bonds
between DNA.
That makes them totally pliable,
so he can extract them
and infuse somebody else
with the exact same meta DNA.
"Melting highly concentrated bonds."
Melting Point.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I gotta write that down.
Okay, great, so you guys figure out
how to get this Mr. Melting Point
in the same room as DeVoe
and not get his brains sucked out.
I'm gonna go get a couple of bear claws
and go back to my room.
It's not Mr. Melting Point.
Look, it... it's just Melting Point.
You know, somebody out there
has Frye's fire powers right now.
We need to find them as much as
we need to find Matthew.
I'm on it.
And I'll see if there's a way
to reverse this.
Well, until then, what do we do?
We train.
Okay.
Ramon! Where...
There you are.
What are you doing?
I'm updating some software.
Oh, good, so nothing.
Great. I need your help.
Try Ralph.
Ralph's useless, all he does is eat.
What do you want?
Do you have a micro-filament
compression wrench
with a cobalt-retrieving clamp?
Yeah.
Yeah, where is it?
Why? So you can work
on your death cap?
- Not a death cap.
- It's a death cap.
No, it isn't.
I hear there's plenty of tools
on Earth-2.
- Well, I'm on Earth-1.
- You need a lift?
- I'll breach you there right now!
- "I'll breach you there right now!"
- That's not what I sound like!
- "That's not what I sound like!"
Fine.
Cisco, why can't you just help him?
Why am I the only one who thinks
putting a rageaholic
and dark matter together is a bad idea?
He's trying to stop DeVoe.
That's not a bad idea.
He's trying to match his intellect
with a madman whose innovations
are warping his brain.
Have you not seen Spider-Man 2?
- No.
- How can you live with yourself?
It might be dangerous,
but it also might work.
And we're kind of running out of ideas.
Besides, Harry is gonna do this
whether you help him or not.
So maybe there's some way
to make this thinking cap
and to keep him safe.
She can move.
Hey, Iris.
- You might just want to...
- I can't slow down.
That's okay. All right,
just gradually ramp your speed down.
Otherwise, you're going to...
Do that?
Whoa.
Hey, you okay?
- Come here. Are you good?
- Yep. I'm straight.
Thank God for speed healing, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, I know this isn't easy on you.
Hey, I'm fine.
Barry.
I am. I...
I lost my speed.
I lost my job at the CCPD.
Just feels like DeVoe
is slowly taking everything away
from me.
He hasn't taken everything away.
What if I never get it back?
Hey.
Caitlin is gonna find something. Okay?
Hmm.
Until then, you just have
to watch me like I've watched you
these last three years.
Yeah, I guess so.
Wow, that's super annoying.
What's happening?
Baldwin Tower's on fire.
CCFD is responding,
but there's people on the top
floor they can't reach.
Okay, Caitlin,
Killer Frost is on fire duty,
Ralph, Cisco, suit up.
- Yeah.
- Not a chance.
This could just be a trap
for DeVoe to get us out in the open.
I think we got a bigger problem.
We don't have a Flash anymore.
Yeah, we do.
I don't think she's ready
for all that. I mean, she...
You just got your powers.
Um... no, I wanna do this.
Okay, okay, all right,
we'll monitor from here, then.
Okay, well, you can't
go out there wearing that.
Oh, right.
Sorry, Caitlin.
Mask.
Right.
Thank you, Jesse Quick.
Nice.
Please be careful.
Guess you're on comms.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. How do I...
- Other monitor.
- Wrong monitor.
I'm here.
Oh, boy.
Okay, Iris, there are five people
trapped on the 14th floor.
Just get them out of there
as fast as you can.
I did it.
Great work. Okay, now you've got to
get back in there
to put out the fire.
Right.
Guys, I'm here. What do I do?
You know what to do. Use your arms.
Create a wind funnel,
suck all the oxygen out of the room.
And the fire'll go out.
Just like he's done 1,000 times.
You got this, girl.
It's making it worse.
She is rotating her arms
the wrong way, or?
Go the opposite direction, okay?
Iris, what was that?
Iris?
My leg is pinned. I can't move.
- Okay, you have to phase through it.
- What? I don't know how.
You have to vibrate
your whole body. Okay?
You just... You have to feel it.
I can't. I can't move. I can't do it.
We're running out of time, Barry.
The integrity of the room is failing.
The ceiling is gonna collapse.
Barry, the whole place is going up.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
There's still a little-bit
of irritation in your lungs
from all the smoke
you inhaled last night,
but you should be good to go soon.
Your leg is already healed.
We shouldn't have let her go out there.
You weren't ready.
I saved a lot of people
last night, Ralph.
Yeah, and Cisco had to save you.
Look, we just need to make sure
this doesn't happen again.
We have to find Matthew Kim
and whoever he transferred
Eric Frye's powers to.
How close are you to reversing this?
- I don't know that I can.
- What?
I was up all night trying
every conceivable solution.
Dark matter splicing,
pattern DNA cloning,
even regrowing meta-enhanced
stem material
on a cellular level.
Nothing will work.
I cannot replicate
Melting Point's powers.
So unless we find him and get him
to reverse what he's done...
Iris is Team Speedster
on a permanent basis.
Great, that's, uh... That's great.
I'm gonna go work on my will.
Ralph...
Harry.
Harry, I know you hear me.
Another team member hurt
by one of DeVoe's meta.
- I know.
- And we can fix it, but no!
- You know what else?
Snow wasn't the only one
who was up all night working.
I was up all night working.
I'm almost done. I'm almost finished.
- But you won't help me finish.
- I'm gonna help you finish.
- Finish...
- The thinking cap.
I'm gonna help you
finish the thinking cap.
It's an intelligence booster.
Actually, it's called
an intelligence booster.
Two conditions.
What are your conditions?
One, we stimulate your synapses
without using dark matter.
Fine, no dark matter.
And two?
The minute you start acting like
Locutus of Borg
and start assimilating everybody
with your Borg chair...
You can vibe me back to my Earth. Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Take it easy.
It's just day two.
Oh, man.
You're right about running.
It's so peaceful.
So calming.
Actually makes it easy to think.
Look, you just got your speed.
You know that, right?
I don't think
anyone'll hold it against you
if you took a minute.
Maybe just let
Cisco and Caitlin handle this.
Just run point. Like always.
Just stay here like I always do?
No, I... you know I didn't mean that.
No, I know you didn't. I did.
Iris...
You think that...
What, that you need
to prove to the team
that you're not afraid?
No, not to all of you. To me.
Barry, when I was a reporter,
I was always in the field
putting myself in danger for a story.
And after last year,
for some reason, that just stopped.
Maybe it was because of Savitar,
maybe because...
you were gone into the Speed Force.
I don't know, but...
I quit my job,
I joined this team,
and now, for the most part,
I just stay here
while all of you are out there
putting your lives on the line.
- Because of our powers.
- No, it's not just that, Barry.
And it took me getting these powers
to realize it.
But now that I'm the one that has it,
it's my turn to do
what all of you have been doing.
To prove to myself that
that fearlessness that I had
is still in me.
Guys, I think we found
Frye's missing powers.
Then go get 'em.
Satellite's tracking temperature
at the same intensity
- as the bank robbery. So...
- That's him.
- Yeah.
- So who's that?
Matthew Kim.
Kim's going to try and steal his powers.
All right, let's go.
No!
You guys run point.
I can do this.
You sure about this?
I have to, Barry.
All right,
but remember, he can't touch you,
- or he'll take your powers away, too.
- Right.
Also, I'm not sure my clothes
are gonna work this time.
I have a fix for that.
It's the best I could do
on such short notice, though.
Thanks, Cisco.
I got hangers.
All right, here we go.
Don't make us shoot you. Stand down.
Oh, I don't think so, copper.
Not until I get my money.
- This is a mistake.
- Down, now! Take him down!
Hold your fire.
You need to stop this.
Oh, I just got going, pal.
Wait.
You're that hero from the bank,
aren't you?
I am.
And I need you to stop this.
So you can take my powers
like you did his?
I don't think so.
You just gave them to me.
What are you talking about?
You didn't know that?
When you took powers from him,
you gave them to me.
And now I'm gonna get
what he couldn't. Money!
I think you've done
enough saving for today.
I'll take it from here.
How about we just end this right now?
That sounds fun.
'Cause I was just warming up.
What's wrong?
Can't stand the heat?
All right, Iris,
we need you to run around him,
create a vortex.
The lack of oxygen should
- extinguish the flame.
- Can't get close to him.
Temperature is at 800 degrees.
Like, how hot is that?
It's hot as lava.
Guys, we need a plan.
I got a plan, lady!
It's called, "Give me my money
before I unleash hell"!
Yeah!
What the hell is that?
That is a thermal cyclone.
That fire is gonna get too close
to those apartments.
And thousands of people will die.
What do we do?
We turn this thing on.
- Harry, no. Don't.
- Iris needs answers.
- We haven't tested...
- She needs answers.
Come on, guys, what do I do?
Do it.
Barry, come on,
I need an answer!
Hang on, Iris. Hang on.
There are 4,827 ways this could go,
and all those ways will fail except one.
If Iris uses her speed
to draw enough water
from Central City Bay into her wake,
she could extinguish that blaze.
You want her to create a tidal wave?
It's our only hope.
Iris, I need you to run
as fast as you can.
- On the water.
- On the water? What?
Make sure, when you run,
you dig your heels in,
you move back and forth
in a tight formation.
Why?
So you drag as much water
ashore as possible,
put out the cyclone.
You want me to make
a 100-foot tidal wave? Are you crazy?
- I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
You told me
that you used to be fearless.
I know that you still are.
You're the bravest person
that I know. You can do this.
I know you can. We all do.
Now, run, Iris. Run.
That's it.
That's it. Now...
And then, tight formations, okay?
Tight formations.
That's it, Iris. Keep going.
Keep going.
Everybody, back!
Move, now!
Long live rock 'n' roll.
Yes!
Nice work.
She did it.
Nice work, Flash.
I'm so sorry I did this to you.
I thought I was cleaning up the city,
but I was just making it worse.
We stopped him.
He's in Iron Heights,
and that's all that matters now.
You sure you both want to do this?
It's your call.
I have to say,
running on water is really fun.
But... if you guys will have me back,
I would love to get back behind
the console again.
- Of course.
- Please, and thank you.
You're ready?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Let's see.
- Okay.
- All right, here?
Okay.
That's it?
You okay, baby girl?
I think so.
How about you, Flash?
I feel great.
My boy's back.
Well, that's the last time
I'm using this power.
This city was almost destroyed
because of me.
But you had no idea that would happen.
Yeah, don't be so hard on yourself, pal.
I thought I was chosen
for a higher purpose.
This can't be the plan for me.
Maybe you were chosen for a bigger one.
What do you mean?
The guy we mentioned, Clifford DeVoe.
He isn't gonna stop until
he gets all the bus metas,
which means we have to stop him.
We could use all the help we could get.
Are you sure I can make a difference?
Absolutely.
DeVoe's shown weakness
against other bus metas in the past.
With your help,
we might actually have a chance.
How do we start?
I'll give you the tour.
All right.
No offense, I like my powers.
So, Barr,
you never made
your own tidal wave before.
No, I haven't.
You go, girl.
So what do you say? You want to teach
an old dog a new trick?
All right. Training, 6:00 a.m.?
Ooh, don't be late.
- You got it, boss.
- Welcome back.
Hey, Ralph.
Hey.
You know, Matthew
is gonna need a buddy, too.
Well, that's assuming he stays.
After he finds out that DeVoe has gotten
everyone he's come after,
he'll be terrified.
Just like I am.
Look, Ralph.
I know what you're going through.
No, Iris, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Last year, when I thought
that Savitar was going to kill me,
I was scared out of my mind.
How did you deal with it?
It was really hard.
But then I realized
that if I hid from him,
if I hid from the world,
then Savitar had already won.
So I made the decision
to not give in to the fear.
I chose to keep living.
Look,
what I said before about
you never putting your life on the line,
I was wrong.
You make
one hell of a Flash
in or out of the costume.
Thanks.
- You going up?
- Yeah.
I think maybe it's time
that Clifford DeVoe
paid the Mayor another visit.
Hmm.
I thought you were
never leaving S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well... I think maybe it's time
I started living again, too.
Plus, we're definitely out
of veggie dogs.
Hey, thanks, Iris.
Fresh from this little place in Keystone
that Cecile recommended.
Wow.
Those cravings of hers
are getting really intense, huh?
Yeah, tell me about it.
It's a good thing I'm a speedster again.
You know you didn't have
to give up your speed, right?
I mean, I would have never asked you to.
I know.
Why did you do it?
You know what makes a great speedster?
It isn't their speed.
It's being the light that everyone needs
when the world goes dark.
It's the kind of person they are.
The kind of person
that always wants to help.
That's why being the Flash
is your destiny.
It's your way of helping others.
But it isn't mine.
This is.
I'll leave you to it.
All right, take it off.
Take it off, Harry. That's enough.
We're already 20 percent over
your suggested safety limits.
You've got to give it
a little more time.
No, that's it. I'm shutting it down.
No, we're almost there.
We're almost there!
You're not breaking bad, Locutus!
All right?
I'm disengaging the photon flow.
All right.
I don't need it anymore.
You got the names?
The last two remaining bus metas.
Janet Petty and Edwin Gauss.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::