My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats
and I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
Twelve markers, twelve metas.
Why would anyone want to create metas?
What's happened to me?
Clearly, this guy is a bus meta.
You can stretch these cells...
- Like Silly Putty.
- ...like Silly Putty.
I'm Silly Putty?
Let my team and I train you.
What made you look into Mayor Bellows?
It was a client. Last name, DeVoe.
You do what Amunet says,
for as long as she tells you.
Tell Amunet I'm done.
Joe, I'm pregnant.
Hey, you guys wanna see
something really cool?
Um... Sure, go for it.
Stretch, Ralph.
Stretch.
- That is pretty cool.
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay, look, are you sure
we can't find this DeVoe guy?
I mean, we were warned.
We had a heads-up
that someday someone named DeVoe
would be one of my greatest foes.
The other thing to think about is,
do you know how many people there are,
- in this state alone, with the name DeVoe?
- No.
Thousands. And we still don't
have an age.
Unless one of your
greatest foes is
the three-month-old William DeVoe
who lives four blocks from here.
I don't think
one of my greatest enemies is a baby.
- Evil killer baby.
- It could happen.
You're right.
Hey.
- Felicity.
- Hey.
- How did you get in here?
- I literally walked in here.
You have no security, you have no
alarms, you have nothing on your door.
You guys might wanna consider something.
Anything, at all.
- You came prepared.
- Team Arrow to Team Bride.
You know, I'm very excited
for that bachelorette party.
Getting inebriated with same genders
to celebrate an archaic institution?
Priceless.
I mean, you only get married once, so...
Well, actually, pretty much
everyone gets divorced these days.
Fifty-five percent to be exact.
I mean, that's just statistics.
But not... Not you and Iris.
That would just...
That would never happen to you guys.
Whose feet are those?
That's Ralph Dibny.
I'm gonna go meet up with the ladies.
That...
Well, here you are. Okay.
Are you ready for the ladies' night
to end all ladies' nights?
And by that she means a quiet, low-key
dinner at a very classy restaurant.
Yeah. That's exactly what I mean.
Super low-key, super quiet.
Do you want a pink or
a blue feather boa?
Actually, Iris, if it's okay,
I don't think I'm gonna make it tonight.
I'm just not feeling up to it.
What? Are you feeling okay?
No, I'm fine. I just...
Sometimes life catches up
with you, you know?
That's 'cause you're not
wearing a tiara.
Put on the tiara,
everything'll change... Oh!
- Wearing a tiara. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Caitlin, please. Come on,
we work together every day.
We never get to do a dinner,
just us girls. You have to come.
She's right. Just one dinner. Please.
Wouldn't miss it.
This is so insane. I can't believe
you're gonna be a mom again.
I know. Well, you've always
wanted a sibling.
And seven Dr. Who's later,
you totally came through.
- You're a Dr. Who fan, Joanie?
- Well, ever since he became a lady, I am.
Hashtag feminism.
Bachelor party! Girls, get out.
Oh, that's our cue.
Hey, Barry, congrats on getting hitched.
Thank you.
I didn't realize you were in town.
Well, I just stopped by for the weekend.
- Awesome. Good to see you.
- You too.
Have a great time. Don't get too crazy.
No drinking.
Mmm-mmm.
No, Iris promised me a totally chill night
that even my pregnant booty can handle.
You should come with us, sweetie.
You know, I'm sure Iris wouldn't mind.
Uh, no, it's okay. I actually have plans.
But I will drop you off.
- Okay. Have fun. Later, guys.
- Bye.
Okay. I'll get the lights.
Harry'll get the brandy.
Hey, Harry, before you pour the brandy,
make sure you warm the glasses.
- What?
- For real?
It's cool.
Okay.
Barry Allen,
are you ready to have your mind blown?
Meet Barry Allen.
Before he met Iris West,
before he became an inter-dimensional
time-traveling speedster,
he was an adorable baby
boy with Ewok-level chub.
Oh, those cheeks!
Cisco, this is great,
but where did you get these videos?
Hey, man, I'm a ninja. Watch this part.
Ah, I forgot that you two got married!
You two were so young.
Damn, I was so young.
Mmm-hmm.
Gentlemen, I have arrived.
- Ralph.
- Dibny.
Wasn't expecting you.
You said, "See you later."
I assumed this was a superhero hangout
and this was a test for my
highly-attuned detective abilities
which, for the record, nailed it.
- Okay, or...
- You weren't invited.
- Wow, this house is...
- Bitching?
No. Small. It looks much bigger
from the street.
- What's all this crap?
- This is my bachelor party.
Oh, dear God. You're serious.
This weiner fest is your bachelor party.
This weiner fest is about to indulge
in some very fine cigars
and a very nice steak dinner at The Oak.
Okay! Stop. You're going to pay
$50 for a steak dinner?
I know a place where you get
all-you-can-eat steak
and chicken for $4.99.
And they even throw in napkins.
- Come on, ladies.
- No, really, Ralph.
- We're gonna stay here. We're gonna...
- No, Slim Jim.
I insist. You can thank me later.
- Hey, that was meant to be enjoyed!
- I enjoyed it.
Cisco, don't worry. Where we're going,
the drinks flow freely and the view is...
Oh! Spectacular.
- So fancy.
- Yeah, a toast,
to the future Mrs. Allen.
- West-Allen.
Although your life with Barry
may be fast-paced,
I hope you guys take the time
to enjoy the special moments.
Thank you, guys, for coming.
It really means a lot.
- Cheers.
- Yeah.
Well, all right. Who wants my champagne?
Craziest thing I get to do tonight
is order two desserts.
- I'll take it.
- That's right.
Iris told me you're pregnant.
How's that going?
Yeah. It's good.
I mean, it wasn't exactly part of my plan.
But, I just could not be happier.
I know exactly what you mean.
Oh, yeah. How is everything
with Oliver and William?
It's an adjustment...
Do I hear wedding bells ringing
in your future?
Oh, no, the last time we did anything
that resembled a wedding,
Oliver got shot with an arrow. So...
- Uh, did you girls order a stripper?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I would've brought all my singles.
- No, I...
Girl, you into some freaky stuff.
Amunet wants you.
Uh... Caitlin, do you know him?
- You need to come with me.
- I'm not going anywhere with you.
Please tell me that
this is just part of his act?
Yeah, if it is, it's taking too long.
Take it off.
Gross! I meant take off your pants,
not your eye.
Oh, my God!
Stay back, baby mama, we got this.
Holy...
Please don't do this.
It didn't have to be this way.
What?
I was hoping to see you again.
Really? So I could give you another scar?
Ugh! I hate pink.
Doesn't it just take your breath away?
Ladies and gentlemen,
that is Jade.
Gentleman, I welcome you
to The Golden Booty.
There ain't nothing golden
about any of this.
I came through for you, right man?
What do you think?
I think I should have
brought some hand sanitizers.
I always come prepared.
Yes!
Ralph, this isn't really my speed.
Speed jokes?
You're better than that, Allen.
- I wasn't...
- Hey, Ralphy.
Uh, Disney, you're a regular
in this joint?
So much more than that.
The girls might not be bottomless,
but for yours truly,
the french fries always are.
Golden Booty policy,
you know, out of respect for the ladies,
no touching, no pictures, no video,
- and no cell phones.
- What?
Next, on the main stage...
I need a drink.
God, I wish I could have a drink.
Bro, you really think
I'd let you down like that?
Your special concoction.
Guaranteed to give you
that gentle pleasant buzz,
all night long.
What if we need the Flash?
I volunteer to be designated superhero.
Go for it, Barry, you deserve it.
Oh!
- To Barry and Iris.
- They're not picking up.
- What the hell just happened?
Who was that Medusa man?
You know that is not
a Cisco-approved name.
Don't worry about who that was.
Caitlin's taste in clothes is matched
only by her taste in men.
Both terrible.
Wait. How are you, you?
I thought Caitlin was cured.
Caitlin shouldn't be
keeping secrets from her friend.
You are friends, right?
Yeah. Of course we are.
Your "friend"
was going out-of-town tonight.
What? Why?
Because she got herself into
something she couldn't handle.
Where are you going?
To find Norvock's boss. And to kill her.
And you need a change of clothes
for that, because...
Whoa! Whoa! Okay, apparently someone
doesn't have boundary issues.
Okay girls,
can I talk to you in the Cortex?
Can we take it back for a minute?
Since when did her superpowers
make her a super villain?
She's not a villain, okay?
I remember being kidnapped
by her last year.
- What?
- Okay, yes, but that,
is because she was being manipulated
by Savitar.
And in the end, we wouldn't have been
able to stop him without her.
Look, I know that
there is some good in there.
I get it. Technically, Caitlin is
underneath all of that somewhere
but she is still dangerous.
And she is also our friend, okay?
I'm not just gonna abandon our teammate.
Fine. I'm coming with you.
No, Cecile, you're pregnant.
And your father will kill me if you get
killed at your own bachelorette party.
That is some crazy logic
and that means I'm in, too.
- Oh, great, happy bachelorette.
- What are you all talking about?
Oh, nothing. You know, just talking
about how cool it is to kill people.
And such. No pun intended.
It's been real, ladies.
I'm gonna use the S.T.A.R. Labs
satellite to track her cold signature.
Great, I'm going to try
and call for back-up again.
And I'll remember that it's Caitlin
under there.
- You gotta stop doing that.
- I'm just getting change for a five.
What? Did you think I was stealing?
It's not about your sticky fingers, Ralph,
it's about your stretchy arm
outwardly displayed.
Oh, so I should be more like
Captain Discreet over there?
I'm the Flash!
I may have slightly miscalculated
his bachelor elixir.
I got this one.
That's good stuff.
- Hey buddy, how are you feeling?
- Hey. I feel good.
Oh, you're gonna need to walk this off.
Or run it off! Because I'm the Flash!
Let's get you back to the table.
Barry, what did you just do?
I just went and got peanuts from the bar.
- You didn't even move.
- Or did I?
- Drink up. So I was talking to...
- I'm good.
It's cranberry juice, buttercup.
So I was talking to Charity,
not her real name,
she tells me that the dancers here
make more in a month than an average...
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Less talky, more dancy!
...dancer, it's Jasmine.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, hell no.
Hey, she looks like Cecile's daughter!
Oh!
I'm sorry. I thought touching without
permission is what you wanted.
I'd let me pass, unless you want to know
what it feels like when
the liquid in your eyeballs crystallizes.
Darling, you're here! Let her in.
Let her in. Let her in.
Amunet, next time
you want to talk, come yourself.
Don't send that eye-hole to attack me.
Did you start a fight?
Honestly, Norvock, it's why
you're my third favorite henchman.
I mean, what do I always say?
"Never start a fight you can't finish."
Hmm?
And that, my dear,
is why you're my favorite.
- You listen.
- Well, apparently you don't.
- I'm out, Amunet.
- "Out"?
Out of what?
Out of options? Out of your mind?
Out of the closet? There's just so many
outs for the lady in blue.
You're asking me to dance?
You should know by now
I don't "ask" for anything.
I tell and I take.
Now, come along.
I want to show you something
that could make us both very rich.
Do you think they're gonna able
to tell that we don't exactly fit in here?
Well, it was your idea to wear boas, so...
- Have we heard from the guys yet?
- No.
Look, ladies, okay?
We're on our own. Okay?
- How about a little love?
- No, no, no. No, no love.
Engaged. Okay, bye.
Is it just me, or does it seem like
everybody here already bought
what that guy is selling?
Uh... Ladies, stay here, okay?
I think I know where Frost is.
You got a pet. Congratulations.
I call him the Weeper.
I love naming metas.
I know someone else like that.
Three weeks ago,
this young man became a meta-human.
And I acquired my new favorite product
to sell in my network.
Did you notice?
Love,
is, quite literally, in the air.
Do you know why?
Oh.
Pure.
His tears are a drug?
His tears, my dear,
are a gold mine.
One taste and Central City
will be hooked.
Then why do you need me?
Really? Well, if I'm going to be selling
something quite valuable,
I'm going to need protection.
That's what you've got
good old snake-eye for.
A deal like this
requires a lady's touch.
In your case, strength.
And I'll cut you in for 10%.
Fifteen percent, and I throw in
not killing you right now
for your misguided rebellion.
And that's only because
I've got forgiveness in my kidneys. Right?
I think you meant your "heart."
No. There's no
beat-beat in this chest, sister.
As much fun as it is to play
"I'm the bigger badass," I'm bored.
And like I said, I'm done.
Do you know what everyone's mistake
in business is?
Hmm?
Not realizing who has
the power in the room.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey, hey!
Ladies, let's put the meta abilities down.
I'm sorry, who is this chick?
Oh, this chick is trying
to stop a meta-fight
from destroying your very enchanting club.
Let's go.
Frost, let's go.
- Should I stop her?
- No.
Let her think she can walk away.
You're lucky she didn't kill you, West.
- Who was that?
- That, was Amunet Black.
Of the underground market?
I'm guessing
this chick has a criminal record?
Yeah. She's been linked to the meta-human
black market selling stolen technology,
but we've never been
able to nail her down.
- And how do you know her?
- Through Caitlin.
Six months ago, Caitlin thought
she had everything under control.
You can't keep a good bad side down
for long, am I right?
She felt me becoming much stronger.
She found out that Amunet had some tech
that would let her stay in charge.
She got desperate,
so she decided to use it.
- But it came with a price tag.
- Which was?
Being her muscle.
Did you kill anyone?
Some people lost their fingers
and their toes, but...
No. No one died.
How are you here, now?
While Caitlin sleeps, I'm awake.
Oh, my God.
You're like the Incredible Hulk!
That's...
I said that with too much chutzpah.
Dialing it back.
Look what are Amunet's plans
for the Weeper?
Not my problem.
Look, he was on that bus.
We helped create him. We need to save him.
No. I need to leave and escape Amunet.
And you're just going to run away?
Listen, there's a reason
the CCPD has not caught her,
and that you idiots just realized
there is a major crime lord
living under your noses
for the past three years.
She's too powerful. We can't stop her.
Guys, we have a responsibility
to the Weeper and to this city.
What do you suggest we do?
We need to rescue him before Amunet
does whatever she's planning, okay?
Cecile, you need to
gather information on Amunet,
and Felicity, you need to
pull up the blueprint to the club.
We got this.
We're strong women.
Yeah.
Hashtag feminism.
This isn't what you think, Joe.
Good, because I thought I saw you dancing
on that stage in a gold-sequined bikini.
No. I'm writing a book
on the female experience.
I'd buy that book.
Why does your female experience
include you dancing at The Golden Booty?
Because we live in a society
that's dictated by the male gaze.
I want to control
the narrative of feminism. Okay?
I wanna show the world
that a powerful, strong woman,
she can wear anything.
Be it a bikini or a pantsuit.
Or nothing! Feminism!
That's not how feminism works.
Will you cut it out?
Joanie's practically his daughter.
Hey. Sad Flash,
why the face?
Nothing, I just...
I just love chicken wings so much.
Where are you gonna go?
I know a guy who can breach me
to another Earth.
Start over, escape Amunet,
be who I wanna be.
And that's Killer Frost, right?
Don't be cute, West. You can't stop me.
I wasn't planning on it.
Look, I know you could kill me.
Just like you could have
killed Amunet tonight,
or Cisco six months ago.
But you didn't.
There is a part of you that is good
and decent.
You just don't know how to accept it.
You think you know me now?
No, but I do know what Caitlin looks like
when she's scared.
And you have that same
look in your eyes right now.
You're just as afraid of being Caitlin
as Caitlin is of being Killer Frost.
If you still wanna have a hand
for Barry to put a ring on,
I suggest you move it.
There's a strong, powerful woman
that we both love and fear,
and her name is your mother.
- Does she know you work here?
- Of course not.
She would just jump to all
the same conclusions that you are.
Joanie, your mother and I
just want you to be happy.
But I think you need to ask yourself
why you're keeping this a secret from her.
Joe?
Why didn't Rose make room for Jack
on the door?
There was plenty of room for both of them.
Uh, Cisco, when does this gift of yours
stop giving?
Man, I don't know.
I thought we'd be watching
home movies right now.
Again, you are welcome.
You steal $20 from me, Ralphy?
When? I mean, no.
Yeah, he did. I saw it.
I've been waiting a long time
for this Dibs.
Oh!
You monster!
Everybody, stop! I'm a cop!
I'm the Flash!
You're late.
I'm right on time.
What, were you expecting a different meta?
Nobody walks away from me, Frost.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Did you really think
I was going to let you
just breach into the sunset?
You owe me your life.
And I always take what I'm owed.
Hands over your head, ma'am.
Is there any part
of the way that I'm dressed
that leads you to believe
I want to be called "ma'am"?
Hmm?
Ugh.
Blood.
Kill you later, Caity.
Let me help you.
Please.
Okay.
It's already knotted.
You just have to pull it tight.
Thanks.
Yeah.
What happened?
You don't remember?
When she's in control,
I don't remember much of what happens.
Did she...
I hurt anyone?
Just that snake-eyed scumbag.
Didn't kill him though.
So, the cure, it...
Didn't work.
Not all the way.
Which is why you wanted to leave tonight?
And why it took you
six months to come back?
When Cisco said he was gonna get Barry
back from the Speed Force,
I thought that
maybe I could come back and make up
for some of the pain that I caused.
But she's getting stronger.
I never should have come back.
That's not true, Caitlin.
You can always come back to your friends.
Why didn't you tell any of us?
I didn't know who to talk to.
You could have talked to me.
I'm your friend, Caitlin.
Work friend.
I mean, it's not like you and I have
become besties over the last few years.
Yeah, I guess we haven't.
Hey. Jerry, buddy.
We gonna get that phone call or what?
Hey, come on, man.
I know you can hear me.
I'm right here. Hello.
Okay. Great.
You just know everybody, don't you?
Yeah, I've been here a few times.
You know, I could wiggle through
these bars and get us out of here.
I may make my finger into a key.
That'd be pretty sweet.
Lot of pressure put on
the index finger though.
Iron versus flesh.
- What do you think?
- I think you should stop talking,
immediately.
I don't ever have to drink again.
Words uttered by everybody
who's ever had too many. Here.
This was a bust, huh?
It's a bachelor party.
Happens.
What's up with you?
All night, you've seemed preoccupied.
I'm worried.
About what?
Being a dad again. I'm almost 50, Barr.
Mmm-hmm.
I saw that video Cisco made of
you and Iris when you were kids and it...
Hit me like a ton of bricks.
I was...
I was young the first time I did this.
And then seeing Joanie.
It's hard raising humans, Barr.
You'll be fine.
I barely get enough sleep as it is,
worrying about you three.
Especially with Wally being gone.
Add to that a crazy baby schedule.
Feeding, crying...
I'm honestly scared to death.
Joe, when you raised Iris, you were alone.
When you took me in, you were alone.
And you know,
when Wally showed up, you were alone.
You did all that, by yourself.
Single parent.
No one could have done a better job.
No one.
Now you've got a partner.
You've got family.
You've always been there for us
when we've needed you,
and now it's just our turn
to do that for you.
And we will.
I know you will.
I'll take those three.
Four.
These tears are more than just water.
When ingested, the dark matter inside it
alters the brain function
like that of a psychoactive drug.
So it's like what, an opioid?
It's like a love drug.
- From tears?
- If this spreads,
Central City's gonna have a massive
drug problem on its hands.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay, well, we need to stop
Amunet and save the Weeper
before that happens.
How do we find her?
I don't know. She's smart.
Off the grid.
Always on the move, never leaves a trail.
Okay, what about her powers?
The metal that she controls.
Do you know what it is?
It's some kind of alnico alloy.
Do you think you could
use our satellites to track it?
You mean run a geological scan of the city
for small-scale signatures
of aluminum, nickel and cobalt?
Girl, please.
There. She's headed to Lawrence Hills.
That's all industrial out there.
That's steel mills, docks, warehouses.
- Okay, we need to stop her.
- Okay.
Guys, I can't go with you.
If I lose control,
I could become a liability.
I'm sorry, Iris, I can't go.
You don't have to.
We got this.
Okay.
Ladies, what's your status?
We're in position.
I think you'll be pleased.
- This is him?
- Hmm.
Good boy.
Sample.
I'll take him.
- On my count, we move.
- Okay.
One, two...
Three.
I remember you.
You are the chick from the bar, hmm?
Oh, no.
Hey, Amunet.
This is between you and me.
Let my friends go,
and I'll come back and work for you.
It's too late for that, Caity.
Do you know why no one has ever
testified against me over the years?
Well, it's because they're not alive to.
Sorry.
Take care of them.
No!
Well, hello, Chilly.
We got to get out of here.
And I thought I wasn't going to be
able to kill anyone today.
Kill them!
I don't think this is gonna
hold much longer.
Well, this is a steel factory,
and you move steel plates with...
Magnets.
Really, really big magnets.
Cecile, turn the crane on.
What? How?
It should be in the schematics.
Just highlight it and turn it on.
Okay, I'm...
You and I could have been gods.
I used to work with a god.
Over it.
Cecile, now!
Not so scary without your bling, now,
are you, sister?
Stop!
Caitlin, stop.
I'm not Caitlin.
And I'll never be free unless she dies.
No, it's the opposite.
You are free right now.
But if you do this,
you will always be a killer.
Killer Frost, Caitlin,
you don't have to be one or the other.
You get to decide who you are.
Get out of here.
You've ruined this for me today.
And one day soon, I promise you,
I will ruin something for you.
Hold on.
It's okay, okay? We're gonna help you.
- Get away from me.
- Wait...
The police are on their way.
We did it, guys. We really did it.
Actually, it's "girls."
I'm gonna have a headache now
until my wedding day.
Worth it.
Agree to never speak about what
happened tonight?
- Agreed.
- If I have to.
What?
Hey, I saw you called 17 times.
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything is fine.
How was your night?
Good.
- Quiet.
- Uneventful.
- Yours?
- Yeah. Not much happened.
You know what,
we actually had a few scrapes.
Honestly, so did we.
Tears were involved.
Yeah. Us, too.
More crying, then puking.
Lost access to the happiest
place on Earth.
Pretty sure nothing could have
made tonight any worse.
I'm so tired.
Can we just do this tomorrow, please?
Oh, Chicks with white hair. Hot!
Why is Killer Frost here?
Guys...
She has something
that she wants to tell you.
And you all should listen.
Aww... It's just Caitlin.
I can explain everything.
Hey, Joe.
Hey.
When you got arrested, I figured
you'd be okay, 'cause you're a cop,
but still...
Yeah, we're all fine.
How was the rest of your night?
It was fine.
Joe, I'm gonna do what I want.
I know, you're an adult.
I was not trying to tell you what to do.
But if I'm being honest,
I know that I took it too far tonight.
Then, what about your feminist research?
I still believe everything I was saying.
But after we talked, I realized
that's not why I'm working there.
So I'm gonna quit.
Are you gonna tell Mom?
That's not my secret to tell.
But your mom loves you.
And she'll always listen,
if you let her.
Just got my first craving.
Hi, you two.
How was your night?
It was fine. Nothing happened.
- You?
- Oh...
Same. Super chill.
I'm gonna head to bed. But do you wanna
do breakfast in the morning and just talk?
- Yeah, sweetie, I'd like that. Okay.
- Okay.
- Good night, guys.
- Good night.
- I gotta tell you something.
- Mmm?
This kid of ours,
definitely not a vegetarian.
"This kid of ours."
Cecile, I gotta tell you,
I never thought I'd even have
a second chance at love, and here you are.
You're my everything.
To top that miracle,
we're having this baby.
It's exciting.
Is it okay to say that
I'm scared?
I'm so glad that you told me that.
'Cause I am terrified.
- Really?
- Yes. Really.
I thought that I'd finally
hit this groove in my life,
in my career, and with you, and now,
this changes everything.
The last thing I thought at our age
we'd be having a baby.
I know!
It's scary. But I figure
pretty much all we gotta do is love this
baby as much as we love each other.
- That's a lot of love.
- Yeah.
So much for quiet and classy, right?
Not exactly the bachelorette party
you had in mind.
Well, saving the city wasn't a bad way
to spend the night.
But the best part of the night was
spending it with the ladies of Team Flash.
It was. When we weren't
almost getting killed.
- Yeah, we should do it more often.
- We should.
The "hanging out" part, not
the "almost getting killed" part.
I'd like that.
Actually, I wanted to ask you a favor
about the wedding.
Oh. You want a custom ice sculpture?
No.
Um...
I wanted to know if you wanted to
be my maid of honor.
- Me?
- Yeah.
We're more than work friends,
and we've been through a lot together.
Weddings are all about
new beginnings, right?
So, what do you say?
You wanna stand up for me?
I do.
I guess that's your line though, right?
Thank you.
- I'm so excited!
- I know. I'm excited, too.
- Do I have a bridesmaid's dress?
- Of course.
I went through
a lot of trouble
creating you.
I can't have you running away.
Not until you've completed the task
for which you were born.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::