My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
Last night, on my way
to the morgue, I saw something.
Taxi! Oh, come on, I'm gonna be late.
Simon Stagg, remember him?
Hasn't been seen in like six months.
You're saying Wells knows where Stagg is?
No, Wells killed him. I have evidence in a
secure digital file that will explain everything.
There is a tsunami heading for the city.
You need to get as far away as possible.
I have not been able
to stop thinking about you.
Go.
Taxi, taxi!
Oh, come on, I'm going to be late!
Oh, boy.
Hey, what's going on?
- Dude!
- Yeah.
Cisco, I'm here.
What happened? Why'd you stop?
I just got a little disoriented.
You need to make up some time, man.
You'd better hurry up.
- Hurry? What are...?
- Hurry, as in, get to the morgue.
The morgue?
But I was there yesterday.
What are you talking about?
Come on, you gotta go.
Hey, Barr, what's with all the water?
Did the sprinkler system go off
or something?
What? No, I checked the sprinklers.
They're all intact.
But the water has ice in it.
And the bruises on the coroner aren't just
on his face. Check. Look at his torso.
Whoa.
- How the hell did you know that?
- He was killed by hail.
- We have to listen to the recording.
- Recording?
Joe, we got something.
The coroner's office just installed an
automated dictation system. Listen to this.
- Please, no more.
- I'll stop when you tell me.
- Stop.
- Who killed him?
That's Mark Mardon. He wants revenge.
- And I really don't want to go.
- He's your brother.
- Not by choice.
- Okay, well, how bad can a birthday party be?
Um, my folks think
Dante's stink don't stink.
Doesn't matter how much he screws up
or how many times he gets in trouble...
in their eyes, he can do no wrong.
And yet they never fail to remind me
that I can do no right.
What if I came with you?
What? Seriously?
Absolutely. You've done so much for me.
Let me be there for you for a change.
And I can look at old
family photo albums...
and see what little Cisco looks like
without long hair.
I'm rescinding your invite.
Clyde Mardon has a brother?
So both Mardon brothers
survive the plane crash...
and the dark matter released
by the particle accelerator explosion...
- affects them in the same way.
- Virtually the same way.
That's right.
Only Mark's not like Clyde at all. He can
do things that you couldn't even imagine.
- You mean he's sort of like a weather wizard?
- Weather wizard?
Yeah.
- Trigeminal headache?
Mister Allen.
A word, please.
Yeah.
You ruptured the time continuum,
didn't you?
You're experiencing temporal reversion.
- Yeah.
- How long?
A day and some change.
It's like I'm living it all over again.
Good. That means there's not too much
you could've messed up yet.
How did this happen?
I don't know. I mean I was running
faster than I've ever ran.
The first time I lived this day,
some horrible things happened.
- There was a tidal wave and...
- No. Do not tell me.
I do not wanna know anything
about the future you experienced. Nothing.
- Okay, but, Doctor Wells...
- Barry, time is an extremely fragile construct.
Any deviation, no matter how small...
could result in a cataclysm.
Here's what you're going to do.
Everything you did before, every word
you uttered, every step you took...
you're going to do again. And you're not
going to tell anyone this happened.
Good day, Dr. Wells.
Time will tell, Gideon.
- Show me the future.
- As you wish.
The future remains intact, Dr. Wells.
If anything changes, alert me immediately.
Of course, doctor.
Hey.
What is going on with you? How'd you
figure all that stuff out at the morgue?
Lucky guesses, I guess.
Look, I'm telling you, I'm gonna get Mardon
if it kills me.
Joe. Um...
I gotta run an errand.
I'll see you later, all right?
I didn't know there was
anyone else like me.
I'm gonna break out
and I'm gonna create a tidal wave...
that destroys your entire city.
So I still don't understand.
How did you find him?
Uh, I just had a hunch.
That's gotta be some kind of record.
Heh. Yeah.
Well, there goes my excuse
for bailing on my brother's birthday.
Do you have any idea
what you've just done?
Yeah, I do.
- I just saved a lot of lives.
- I warned you not to mess with the timeline.
If you would let me tell you what was going
to happen, you'd understand why I did this.
Whatever tragedy
you think you've just averted...
time will find a way to replace it
and trust me, Barry...
the next one could be much worse.
- Don Santini, they're here.
- Move it.
Oh. Love the paneling. Mahogany?
So glad your house is made out of wood.
It's gonna be a pleasure watching it burn.
Refreshing.
What are you doing back in Central City,
Snart?
- This is my city.
- Our city.
I told you if I ever saw you again,
I'd put the hurt on you.
You stir up trouble.
Trouble is bad for business.
It's time for you and your family to pack
up, leave town, retire to warmer climates.
And if we don't?
You will all freeze.
Or burn.
I heard about your guns.
Also heard that you lost them.
So tell me, Snart...
what the hell are you and your pyro
friend gonna do without your fancy weapons?
This.
Now, that was fun. Fun, fun, fun.
Go.
Tell the rest of the Santini family
there's a new godfather.
And his name is Cold.
Wow. Your parents really went all out
with the cake.
Oh, well, it is Dante's birthday,
the most important day of the year.
Mijo was invited to play Carnegie Hall
when he was just 13 years old.
They invited the entire band, Mama.
That doesn't make it any less worthwhile.
- Hey, what's up, man?
- Hey.
- Glad you could make it.
- Of course.
Hi, I'm Dante.
- This is my friend, Caitlin.
- Hi, Caitlin.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Here, I got you this.
- I think you'll really like it, it's...
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
I don't get it.
I've been running just as fast as I was when
it happened and nothing. I'm still here.
Anything could've triggered the wormhole
that allowed you to repeat your day.
Your emotions, circumstances,
cortisol levels, all of the above.
I mean, my adrenaline was super high
since Iris and the entire city...
No, no, no, no details, I told you.
I'm sorry, but Mark Mardon's
already locked in the pipeline...
and nothing bad has happened.
Yet.
- Detective.
- Hey. What are you doing here?
So when were you planning on telling me
you took down Mardon?
I just haven't had a chance yet.
- You got sidetracked.
- You can't be mad.
I'm not mad. But I am curious.
I mean, you were acting so weird
at the crime scene.
- I always act weird.
- Okay, weirder.
Look, Joe, there are just some things
that I can't tell you...
and you're gonna have to trust me.
Hey, Linda.
Yeah, I know, I'm so sorry, I lost track.
I'm gonna head that way now.
All right, bye.
I have a lunch date with Linda.
I gotta run.
And I don't suppose
you're gonna fill me in either?
- No.
- Mm.
Here is one who was touched by God.
I was a little rusty.
I haven't played in a while.
Well, if that was what you sounded like
rusty...
I can't imagine what you sound like
when you've practiced.
For you, I'd practice morning, noon
and night.
That means you'd actually have to get up
in the morning.
So Mom tells me you're still working
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah. Why?
No reason, man.
Guess it was just hard to find another job.
I wasn't looking.
I like working at S.T.A.R. Labs.
And we couldn't do what we do
without Cisco.
He's loyal. Just like a dog.
Come on, why are you so serious, mija?
Happy birthday.
Hey, I am here. So sorry again.
Well, you get a pass
considering you're never late.
Hey, what's going on with you lately?
Nothing.
Come on, give me a little credit here.
I've just been dealing
with a lot of things lately.
I like you, Linda, and we really get along.
Relationships should be more
than just getting along.
Your heart should ache for me.
Does it?
You're not upset with me?
No one did anything wrong.
I really do feel a lot for you, Linda.
It's just...
Just not as much as you feel
for someone else.
Go get her.
"The Flash. Speeding his way
into our lives."
That's a little bit on the nose,
don't you think?
I have something to show you.
Simon Stagg. Remember him?
Hasn't been heard from in nearly a year...
Hey, Iris. Mr. Bridge, hi.
Do I know you?
Oh. No. We haven't met. Yet. Fully.
- Iris, can I talk to you for a second?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
- We'll catch up later.
- Yeah.
Nice meeting you, strange young man.
Is everything okay with you and Linda?
Uh...
No, that's done.
Oh, I am so sorry.
No, no, no, it's okay,
we're gonna be friends.
Yeah, no, it's gonna be awesome.
Uh, anyway, are you...?
Are you free tomorrow?
Do you wanna get some coffee?
And we can just talk
and just tell each other stuff.
I don't know, stuff we got rolling around
in there. You know, I don't know.
Okay, yeah, sure, sounds great.
Okay, great. Great.
All right, I'll see you.
I know you think Harrison Wells
had something...
to do with Simon Stagg's
disappearance.
But you're wrong.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, man.
Thanks for meeting me here.
Even though, um, you can't get drunk.
- No worries.
- So how was your day?
Great. But Linda and I did break up.
That's the first time I've heard anyone
use the word "great" to describe a breakup.
I have a feeling that I'm about to move
forward with someone really special.
Okay, go ahead, Barry.
Hi. I don't normally do this,
but I was watching you and...
can I buy you a drink?
Uh...
- Wow. I'm really flattered, but I...
- Actually, I was talking to him.
Um...
I'm sorry, you said you were talking to me?
Yeah, I just told my friends over there
that I thought you were cute...
and they dared me to come over here
and talk to you.
So please talk to me.
Yeah, yeah, I suppose I can talk to you
for a little bit.
- Dude, get out.
- Yeah, I was just leaving.
Make me proud.
- I'm Lisa, by the way.
- Hi, Cisco.
I'm just in town for the symposium
at Mercury Labs.
- Really? What do you do?
- I'm a structural engineer.
Why do you look so surprised?
Can't a girl be an engineer?
No, of course. That's...
You just don't look like an engineer.
I can't help how I look.
I mean, it's good. It's a good look.
It's a great look.
You don't look so bad yourself.
Am I being pranked right now?
What do you think?
I can't believe this.
The day started out pretty terrible...
but it's turning out pretty damn good.
- I'll say.
- Wow.
Look at this, these are nice digs.
Oh, we're just squatting.
- We?
- Yeah.
Me and my brother.
Hello, Cisco.
What exactly are your intentions
with my sister?
Oh, come on.
I should've known better.
I am not that lucky.
Please don't kill me
for kissing your sister.
You kissed him?
- You're not Dad, Lenny.
- I know, Dad's in jail.
Sterling role model.
What do you want, Snart?
Guns.
Heat and cold, to be precise.
There's no way I'm making weapons for you.
- Never again.
- Mick.
I know I would do everything in my power
to protect my family.
The question is, will you?
Dante, Dante, just keep cool, okay?
Let me do my thing.
Really? And you're gonna save us
with your "mechanical engineering" skills?
Right now my skills are the only things
keeping us alive, so shut up.
- You shut up.
- Ah.
There she is.
I missed this baby.
Here it is. All finished.
You gonna let us go now?
You know, I took the first gun you made me
apart dozens of times.
Learned how it ticked. What went where.
Thought you could tamper with
the firing pin without me noticing?
Nice try, kid.
Yes.
Lenny, where's my gun?
Girl's gotta defend herself.
Besides, why should you two
have all the fun?
My sister needs a weapon.
Something that suits her personality.
Make me something pretty and toxic.
Like me.
How about something with gold?
Gold. Heh.
Hey. One incredibly heavy cronut
and one Americano with an extra shot.
- Just the way I like it.
- Just the way you like it. Yeah, I know.
I know you, Iris. Ahem.
So, um, what is going on with you?
You're acting like Christmas came early.
Heh. Uh...
Yeah, no, I guess it did, kind of.
Iris, I still think about you all the time,
and I know you've been thinking about me too.
- So let's just stop thinking and start doing.
- Barry.
I know. I know that we both have
awful timing, but we were meant to be...
Barry, what are you talking about?
You and me.
We like each other.
Barry, we've been over this.
Okay? Nothing has changed for me.
No, but it has.
How do you know that?
I just...
I just know some stuff. Somehow.
I don't know, maybe it's like ESP
or something...
Barry, I love Eddie, okay?
I'm sorry, but nothing has changed for me
since Christmas.
And you can't keep springing this on me,
okay?
It's not fair that you keep making me
the bad guy who keeps telling you no.
What? No whoosh in?
- I needed the walk.
- What happened?
Nothing. Uh...
Linda.
Iris.
I don't wanna talk about it actually.
Okay.
Have you talked to Cisco?
I've been trying, but he's not answering.
I'm kind of worried about him.
He had a rough night.
Trust me. It got better.
- Hey, Joe, what's up?
- Yeah, Snart's back.
Wait, Cold is back?
Yeah, he was spotted
at the Santini crime family casino.
If he's hitting the Santinis, we could be
looking at a mob war.
Well, this day just keeps getting better,
doesn't it?
You killed my brother.
You shouldn't have messed with my family.
That's funny, I was gonna say
the same thing about ours.
All that glitters.
This is sick.
You wanted us to spend more time together.
How many times
are we gonna go through this?
Until the best man wins.
Drop the gun.
We both know you're not
going to do anything to her.
Oh, by the way, meet my baby sister.
Lisa, Flash. Flash, Lisa.
Cisco has been very, very busy.
Unless you want me to mail small,
frozen pieces of him back to his family...
I'd take your hands off her.
Let him go, Snart.
I'll think about it.
God.
Barr.
Witnesses reported seeing the Flash.
They said you had Snart dead to rights,
but you let him go. Why?
Cisco.
- Snart and his sister have him.
- Oh, man.
Okay. Get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'll get there when I can.
All right.
- Allen.
- Eddie, I...
Whoa!
- Stay away from Iris.
- What is going on here?
- Hey, if you two have a beef, take it outside.
- You know what the worst part is, Barry?
I thought you and I were friends.
So there's Cisco getting into a car
with Snart's sister.
The license plate is iced over.
All right, Dr. Wells, you were right.
I screwed with time,
now time is screwing with me.
Cold is back, he kidnapped Cisco,
and Iris...
Stop before you cause
another disruption to the timeline.
Please, Dr. Wells.
Please, I have to talk to someone.
Go ahead.
In the previous version of today...
Captain Singh is seriously injured...
Joe is in danger,
and Iris said she had feelings for me.
And now Cisco's life is on the line and Iris
has no idea she confessed those feelings.
But she still has them, right?
The unconscious mind, Barry,
is a powerful thing.
It sounds like...
it took this apparent
disaster to jar those feelings loose.
And without that disaster,
those feelings remain deeper down.
Un-accessed.
I don't understand.
I thought that I was helping people
by stopping Mardon.
Yes, but this new ability of yours,
Barry, is a dangerous thing.
You only traveled back in time one day.
What if you traveled back decades?
Centuries?
Imagine the havoc you could wreak.
But I will have the opportunity...
to travel back in time in the
near future and save my mom.
Are...? You're saying I shouldn't?
I'm saying how many more
people could die...
if your mother lives?
Did you guys find Cisco?
Most people think the hottest part
of the flame is the white part.
They're wrong.
You gonna admire those or drink them?
Both.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
I told her you wanted to become a priest.
Broke her heart.
Why'd you do that?
Because I was jealous of you, man.
Even then,
I knew exactly where my life was headed.
- Nowhere.
- Dante...
that's not true.
I live at home
and I work a crap job for no pay.
Yeah, but you still manage to be
Mom and Dad's favorite.
I don't even know why.
It's because they still think of me
as their son, the concert pianist.
But you, man,
they never understood your talents.
Never understood that you pursued
your passion no matter what.
And me, I was just too scared to even try.
Dan... Dante.
No.
Mick?
Mick, calm down.
Mick. We need them.
Mick.
Baby, it sounds like you're hungry.
How about you and I grab some dinner?
I like you, kid.
You're smart, you pulled yourself up
from humble beginnings.
You seem like a good brother.
Yeah. You too.
Debatable.
You answer one question for me,
I'll let you and your brother walk.
- What's the question?
- The Flash, who is he?
I swear, he always wears a mask.
No! No, stop.
This is first-degree frostbite.
Your brother could recover
with proper treatment.
If not, all his tendons, blood vessels
and nerves will freeze.
His fingers will need to be amputated.
No more concertos
for the Ramon family holidays.
Now tell me, who is the Flash?
There's nothing
on the satellite thermography.
You were right. This is my fault.
- How is this your fault?
- Brave heart, Barry. We'll get Cisco back.
I'm back.
My God, are you okay?
We were so worried.
- What happened?
- How did you escape?
I didn't.
Snart just let you go. Why?
He tortured my brother.
And he said he was gonna kill him
if I didn't...
If I didn't tell him...
Tell him what?
Who the Flash really is.
I... Honestly, man,
they could've killed me...
but they were gonna kill my brother.
I couldn't let them do that.
Hey.
- I'm sorry, Barry. I'm so sorry.
- No.
I put you in that position.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Where you going?
I don't deserve to be here.
I won't be the one
to put you in jeopardy, not again.
Never again.
Hey.
What? What a surprise.
As big a surprise as Eddie punching Barry
at a crime scene this evening.
Oh, my God. Is Barry okay?
Yeah, he heals fast.
Look, Iris, this got complicated.
I know. I'm sorry.
Barry was too late. I'm with Eddie.
Let me ask you something.
Who do you love?
I mean, I love Eddie.
Okay. You need to make them believe that...
because I'm not sure
either of them does.
Okay?
Did I ever tell you
how wise and amazing you are?
Not enough.
See you later.
- Bad time?
- Yes, actually.
Don't worry, I'll be out of here soon.
Well, before you shuffle off forever...
may I show you something?
I get it.
- I failed.
- No, no, no.
Now, you're an incredibly
clever guy, Cisco.
So why don't you tell me...
why would I bring you down here?
Because we all failed that night,
but we kept going.
We kept trying to protect each other
and Barry, despite the setbacks.
Making a choice between
two people you love...
that is the hardest dilemma
you will ever face.
Well, you won't have to worry about me
making the wrong decision again.
All you proved today, Mr. Ramon...
Is that you're human.
All you proved today
is that you love your brother.
And the reason that
we all want you to stay...
is that we love you too.
Now, I am not a parent...
but in many ways, you have shown me
what it's like to have a son.
Guys, you should get up here.
Shall we?
The casino wasn't the target.
Then why did he do it?
Casinos keep tons of cash on hand
to cover their markers.
But if they're under attack, protocol is
to relocate the money outside the casino.
So that was Snart's plan all along,
to trigger the move.
Okay, where is it now?
Get ready. We got company.
Good to see you, Barry.
We have to talk.
I know Cisco told you who I am.
Can't really blame the
kid for giving you up.
You or his brother? Come on.
I put him in a tight spot.
Same kind I got you in right now.
Can't really stop me,
now that I know who you are.
I could speed you to my private prison
where you'll never see the light of day.
But then I won't be around
to stop my own private uplink...
that'll broadcast your identity to the
world. So the million-dollar question:
What to do with me now, Barry Allen?
I won't let you keep stealing whatever
you want, whenever you feel like it.
- It needs to end.
- Can't do that.
- It's what I do.
- Find a new line of work.
- Don't want to.
- Why's that?
The same reason
you keep running after guys like me.
The adrenaline. The thrill of the chase.
I love this game. And I'm very good at it.
Then go play it somewhere else.
- Leave Central City.
- Can't do that either.
I love it here.
This city is my home.
You've seen what I can do.
You know that I can stop you.
You wanna keep
pushing your luck, go for it.
But from here on out, no one else dies.
If you're as good as you say...
you don't have to kill anyone
to get what you want.
That's true.
And if you or anyone
in your rogues gallery...
goes near
any of my friends or family again...
I don't care who
you tell my identity to.
I'm putting you away.
I guess your secret's safe, Flash.
For now.
Oh, I don't suppose you'd give me
a ride back to town, would you?
The Rogues.
Cute.
I am so sorry, pal.
It's not like me to hit anyone.
I don't know what came over me.
Uh, thanks, Eddie. It's okay.
You poor thing. I had no idea.
Is that right? Um...
But what exactly
did you have no idea about?
I was just explaining to Iris and
Eddie about your Lightning Psychosis.
- My what now?
- Your Lightning Psychosis.
How your recent odd behavior is a
side effect of being struck by lightning.
Mood swings, sudden outbursts of affection,
and other lapses in judgment.
He has had all of those things.
He told me that he had ESP.
It's a very uncommon
neurological phenomenon.
We're really only just now starting
to research in kerauno-medicine.
That's why Barry's been
spending time at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I just wish you would've told me.
It hardly feels real sometimes.
- We're just glad you're getting help.
- Yeah.
- So we're good?
- Yeah, we're good.
- Coffee?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
Oh, come on. Hey.
Harrison Wells.
What do you know about him?
What do you know?
Everything I know is in that drive.
I swear.
Everything?
Everything. Just take it.
You really were
on to the story of the century.
Well, this century anyway.
Do you think I made a mistake?
Letting Snart go?
You did what you felt
was right in the moment.
And really, Barry,
that's the best any of us can hope for.
For now, let's be thankful
the timeline remains intact.
Oh, I keep forgetting, I've been meaning
to ask you. It's about Simon.
You were saying, Mr. Allen?
Uh...
Nothing. Sorry.
- 'Night, Dr. Wells.
- Goodnight, Barry.
Barr, what's up?
Why'd you wanna meet up here so late?
I think that maybe
you were right about Dr. Wells.
Which part?
All of it.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::