Previously on "The Flash"...
- Caitlin!
- Dad.
I'll always love you.
You took our daughter
back to the future?
I can't trust her.
Thawne is manipulating her.
Follow my instructions
and we will defeat Cicada,
destroy his dagger,
and save your father.
- You created your own Speed Force?
- Yes, I did.
And I can access it to go back in time.
- How could he leave me?
- Nora...
How could he stop loving me?
- She's gone.
- Gone where?
I don't know where.
I only know when: 2019.
Gideon, scan servers for blueprints
from McCulloch Technologies.
Gotcha.
Gideon, infiltration analysis.
Yes, Nora West-Allen.
The odds of accessing
this location on your own
are 1 in 3 million.
Shall I send a request to Barry Allen?
No, Gideon.
I need people who can actually help me.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Tachyon scanners set up
at every half-mile
interval across the city.
And the seismometer is
searching for sonic booms
in the hundred-megahertz range.
As for the satellites,
I've got Carrie, Charlotte,
Miranda, and Samantha scanning
for her yellow-purple
lightning signatures.
I am clearly the Samantha
of this group, right?
- Yeah, okay, Miranda.
- Ugh.
So, technically, if Nora
uses the Speed Force...
We'll find her.
Kinda thought she'd pop right up.
If she's even here.
How can you guys be so sure
that she even came back from
the future in the first place?
Because Thawne sent her.
He showed her a new way to time-travel,
something that can't be detected.
But as soon as she starts running again,
we're gonna be able to bring her home.
Well, Team Flash,
Nora West-Allen is not the
only time traveler who's absent.
We've been running down
abandoned buildings,
- foreclosed condos...
- Anywhere that Grace Gibbons
may have hidden her younger self, but...
We got bupkis.
And we have no idea why
she stole the Cryo-Atomizer,
except that it was
worth killing my dad for.
Hey, if you need more time...
Yeah, we're more than capable of chasing
a wild goose or two on our own.
Thank you, I'm fine.
I'd rather be working.
On that note, I'm happy to help you
follow that lead on the atomizer.
Really?
- What about... Sherluck?
- Sherloque.
Do you think any of you will
get this right at any point
at any time in your life? Sherloque.
No, I'm going to continue
the quest for Nora West-Allen.
I... feel somewhat responsible.
Hmm.
Hey, it's CCPD... There was a break-in
at an architecture firm
on 34th and Williamson.
Meta-suspect.
Citizens reporting an explosion there.
Sounds like you guys might
need an extra set of hands.
I'll grab my gear.
Oh.
There's an alert at my
dad's old lab in the Arctic.
We should check it out.
Yeah, better wash my long johns.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
You gonna get that or...
Yeah, I'm going to get it,
but I know already it's Renée Aldler...
- Adler.
With these emoticon pictogram
things that she send me.
Oh, master detective like
you can't decode a few emojis?
I can decode these
emojis no problem, huh?
Heart, she like me. Kissy
face, want to kiss me.
Peach, eggplant, she
like fruit and vegetable.
At this point with the
other Renée Aldlers,
we are not keeping
secrets from one another.
Well, I did it.
Every exercise, every intention,
and now that Kamilla
and I are hunky-dory...
You have completed the Book of Ralph.
- I sure did.
- Thank you for your service,
old friend, but your job isn't done yet.
Shirley, I think you could use this.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What, do you think I
need help with a breakup?
Oh, come on. Look, Addendum C...
Appendix four.
A guide to taking your
relationship to the next level.
It worked for Cisco.
Barely worked for young Ralph Macchio.
No, no, no. This guy,
he's chicken, right?
Even in his current relationship,
he's too afraid to tell this girl
that he's actually Vibe, right?
I'm actually not afraid.
I'm gonna tell her when I'm ready.
It's just hard to navigate
the meta-life, personal-life balance.
More like chicken-life balance, hmm?
Man, you're a chicken
personal-life balance.
I can tell her whenever I want.
Well, then tell her
right now, why don't you?
You want me to tell her right now?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell her right now.
I just got... well, you know.
I have spotty reception in the elevator.
Come on out and do it.
Well, you know, I gotta get to work.
- Come on out and do it.
- I gotta get to work.
I just talked to one
of the architects here,
and G. Simone & Associates used to do
all of this high-profile design work...
Casinos, banks, military bases...
But apparently, last
year, they had been working
with an anonymous client.
So because our thief covered his tracks,
we have no idea who
that client might be.
Hey.
Look at this.
Look at these hard drives.
Fried from the inside, like
in a massive power surge.
A server like this would
have a surge protector, right?
A typical metal-oxide varistor
protects against a thousand joules.
How many joules does
a lightning bolt have?
A billion.
What, you think this was Nora?
No, this couldn't have been.
I mean, our scanners
would've picked her up.
Yeah, about that... I
just picked up a frak-ton
of background particle radiation.
Particles? Tachyons?
Negative tachyons.
That's a thing?
I mean, negative tachyons
can't generate lightning, right?
Unless negative tachyons
don't just offset positive
ones like we thought.
Maybe they actually
siphon positive tachyons.
Stealing speed from the
Speed Force like a parasite?
That's what Thawne taught her how to do.
She's using negative tachyons
to run and avoid our scanners.
Yeah, but why would Nora
be trying to avoid us?
I don't know, but if
she's stealing blueprints,
this ain't gonna be her last stop.
Pretty paint job.
Predators know these
colors get you stung.
Yeah, it's always a great idea
for a thief to draw
attention to herself.
At least I don't fly around
in a fuzzy green sweater.
Didn't think I'd recognize
Weather Wizard's kid?
It's Weather Witch. I have a name, okay?
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
Don't call me that. That's their name.
I heard you took your
robot bee act to Star City.
Something about curing a spinal tumor?
Well, I heard you and your
other half were in Bolivia.
Or did Silver Ghost ditch you?
Van Zandt talked a big game.
She tried to recruit me too.
What did she want to call us?
Young...
Rag Doll, right?
You blew up the Seaver Building.
Bee-utiful.
And whom do I thank for
my mysterious invitation?
Wait, I got an anonymous offer too.
This wasn't your job?
I thought this was your job.
Actually, I invited you.
You want us to work for you?
Not for me. With me.
One big score split four ways.
What's the catch, goody two shoes?
No catches, no tricks.
Just one condition.
No killing.
Well, this has been
really fun, guys, I'm out.
If anybody dies, the
cops will be all over us.
Yeah, you would love that, huh?
I was surprised that the
Flash isn't already here.
I'm not working with him anymore.
Look, you can put on your leather
and you can act like a
bad girl all you want,
but you will never be one of us.
What about the ice patch?
If you don't trust me,
why did you stop that test car
from running me over?
Is she for real?
It was cold.
Water freezes.
Not like that, it doesn't.
Look, these past few months,
I have been through a lot.
I'm not the same person I was.
Okay. Prove it.
What's the job?
McCulloch Technologies.
It's the largest manufacturer
of military-grade
weapons in the country.
So why does a speedster need our help
to pull off a smash-and-grab?
McCulloch builds and tests
all of their weapons here.
The Forge.
And it's protected by
a meta-human dampener
that makes A.R.G.U.S.'s
look like a bug zapper.
So, you need us for our tech,
because it won't be affected.
McCulloch's hosting an expo tonight.
That'll give us cover
to get on the property,
but breaking into the Forge
is where things get tricky.
There's no way this
score is worth the risk.
Look. See these weapons?
There's a hundred
more like these inside.
Each will go for a million
on the black market, easy.
We just need to make
one quick pit stop first.
We need to rob the Flash.
Okay, pretty safe
bet She-Cada was here.
Better check it out.
See if we can figure out what she took.
Yeah, that is if I can get my
fingers to start moving again.
Whew.
You think there's any chance
Frost could help us out
with some sealant up there?
I don't think she's coming out today.
She still having a tough
time with your dad's death?
I mean, Frost protected me for so long
that I don't think she's ever
felt pain of her own before,
not like this.
Well, I-I think I could help with that.
Here.
"Ralph's 27 Steps to a Better Mourning"?
I don't think Frost would respond
very well to a pamphlet.
Oh, come on. Look.
Uh, number 10: go see
your dentist because
you should be doing that
at least twice a year
and you've been slacking,
and it'll give you something to do
other than dwell on the pain.
There. Now will you shut up?
Told you I'd get her to come out.
Guess what?
G. Simone & Associates
has spent the last year
working for McCulloch Technologies.
The weapons manufacturer?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
They just built a factory in Keystone.
Missing blueprints. Top-secret facility.
I think we might have
a heist on our hands.
You think Nora's going
after these weapons?
No, maybe she's just trying
to get them off the market.
You know, like the time
that Barry and Ralph
were gonna buy the Toastmasters.
She's on a mission for Thawne.
He doesn't think that small.
Hey, Barry is scanning
for negative tachyons.
Why don't you and I dig
into what kind of weapons
McCulloch is making?
I know this whistleblower
down at the DOD.
Maybe she could offer some insight.
Uh...
Iris, are you sure
there isn't anything else
you'd like to talk about?
Look... when I saw Nora in 2049,
she was so upset and so angry,
but she knew that I
wanted to bring her back.
Then she comes back to this time
and... and she doesn't even come home?
I mean, even if she's mad at Barry
or she wanted some
kind of sci-fi weapon...
Then why didn't she just come
to the rest of us for help?
There's gotta be a good reason.
I know it.
Come on, Nora.
She's avoiding us. She's
stealing blueprints.
I mean, she could really
get into trouble out there.
But you think she'll
return if you do find her?
After all, she has good reason
to be angry at all of us.
Uh, what? Don't lump me in with you two.
I was pissed. She was pissed.
But we've both had
time to... get over it,
and she's still Nora.
If I tell her she can come home again,
I'm sure she'll stop
working with Thawne.
Is that Nora?
It has to be.
She's in the Starchives.
Nora.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, where you going?
Nora is my responsibility as well.
I must speak with her.
Hey, hold that!
One of our motion sensors
just got tripped in the sewage system.
Sewage system?
Mais non. Nobody could fit down there.
Is that Spencer Young's phone?
What are you doing?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Nora...
I shouldn't have left
things the way that I did.
All right?
I want you to come home.
We all do.
You just have to stop
working with Thawne.
Target acquired.
Copy that.
Are you talking to someone?
What do you think,
I'm talking to Thawne?
He's in the future, Dad. I
can't exactly call him up.
I didn't say that.
Yeah, but you did say
that I couldn't come home
if I was still working with him.
- You still don't trust me.
- Nora, trust takes time.
Then what's to stop
you from sending me back
the next time you get pissed at me?
Nothing.
Because you've given up on me again.
Given up on me like you do every time!
Nora, what are you doing?
You know, I came back here to meet you.
And the second I got here,
you started pushing me away.
And then you left me in the future.
You just dumped me in
the middle of the street
and walked away!
You have to stop.
And you didn't come with
Mom to bring me back.
Because you don't want me
here. You don't want me at all!
- Nora, please!
- I hate you!
Nora broke into the Starchives.
I'm sorry, what happened?
I thought I could stop
her, but I couldn't.
She stole Spencer Young's phone.
Spencer Young's hypnotizing phone?
- Yes.
- Barry, it's okay.
Did you at least find
out what she's doing?
No, no. I tried.
I-I thought I could
convince her to come home.
But...
her face started vibrating, and...
and then her eyes...
her lightning...
it was red.
Just like his.
I thought we had time to reach her,
but he got to her.
Thawne really got to her.
Uh, guys,
there's a blinky red light
thing on the computer.
Another alarm went off at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Guys, this was only five minutes ago.
Joss Jackam and Peter Merkel?
How would they get into S.T.A.R. Labs?
Nora had someone in her ear.
It was a coordinated assault.
But that would mean
that she's working...
with them.
Barium.
We're in Keystone City.
Well, we got a Rag Doll,
a Weather Witch, and, uh...
hold up, is that crazy bee girl?
Hey, girl! What's going on?
What a throwback.
What the hell is he doing here?
What the hell are you doing here?
Oh, no.
She's with them.
I said I wanted Ramon. No one else.
Yeah, well, they were together,
and you said no killing,
so here they are.
Killing?
This phone was synced
to Spencer Young's DNA.
We need you to hack past the
coding so we're able to use it.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry, I don't mean to blow up
your spot, fangirl, you
see, it's just, um...
I've done this exact same thing before.
We need to hack a weapon.
Let's kidnap Cisco.
I mean, what, did you join a
Rogues cover band or something?
How's this for a cover band?
Oldie but a goodie.
Look, XS, I owe you an apology, hmm?
Never should've exposed
your secret the way I did.
I put my pride in front of
the family that took me in...
Your family... And
your family loves you.
I'm sure you heard.
Your father told you
as much today, right?
You saw your father?
You said you were robbing the Flash.
No. No, don't you get it?
Her old man is the Flash.
Look, you don't have to
worry about the Flash, okay?
Just get Ramon started on that phone.
Hey.
Boot scuff marks.
I'm thinking she hit this thing.
Yeah.
Intravenous electrolytes.
I mean, those can be used
to treat coma patients.
So maybe she grabbed
them for Grace Junior.
Hell, yeah.
I knew your "Grey's Anatomy"
thing would come in handy.
Ralph, why did you really bring me here?
Was it to help Killer Frost and me?
The same way you helped
Cisco get over Gypsy
and Sherloque with Renée?
What are you talking
about? I mean, we're a team.
It's what we do. We help each other.
Yeah, but the minute you
got the Book of Ralph back
from Cisco, you tried
to give it away again.
Don't you want to use it?
Try and find someone
special for yourself?
Caitlin...
look...
Book of Ralph...
works great for other people, but...
never actually worked for me.
I know I'm not...
built for love.
And that's okay.
Ralph Dibny, you are kind,
intelligent, and compassionate.
And most of all,
you put the needs of
others before yourself.
So that means you are built for love,
and you deserve someone
who loves you back.
Caitlin...
I'm sorry, I just don't
feel that way about you.
Ugh. Gross!
Oh, come on, you idiot.
Sorry, I got my... I
got my wires crossed.
Jeez.
Hey...
I think this might be the fridge
that Cisco was telling me about,
the one that he rewired as an incubator.
And now the top shelf is empty.
Okay, what was on the top shelf?
Cisco's prototypes for
the meta-human cure.
I think I know what Cicada is planning.
Last time a group of women
had me tied up like this...
They were your ex-wives?
No, their attorneys, actually.
Am I gonna end up like you?
Married to the job?
Keeping secrets from everyone I know?
Well, actually, in my current romance,
I'm not the one keeping secrets.
No, no, I meet Renée Aldler...
- Adler...
- And then I discover...
she's a meta-human.
And she hasn't told you yet?
No, monsieur. Can you believe that?
So if you know the truth,
and you're bottling it in,
doesn't that mean you're
kind of being dishonest?
Chicken recognize chicken.
Hmm.
And yet, are you really a chicken...
Monsieur Bawk?
Or are you not sharing your
secret identity with Kamala...
- Kamilla.
- Because...
you're not super-satisfied
with your secret identity?
Are you saying I don't want to be Vibe?
Well, let's examine
the evidence, shall we?
You spent this past year sans
powers for the first part,
and the second part curing powers.
Perhaps being honest with Kamala...
Kamilla.
Begins with being honest with yourself.
Think about that.
So what we know is that
Nora put together a team
to break into here,
McCulloch Technologies,
a weapons manufacturer.
But not just any weapons.
The city has contracted
these guys to clean up
the shrapnel from the
S.T.A.R. Labs satellite.
Let me guess: none of that crap
ended up in the dump.
They used it to make meta-tech
like Spencer Young's phone.
My source says that
McCulloch is debuting
a new line of products tonight.
That's a perfect cover-up for a break-in.
We have any theory on Nora's motive?
Actually, Cicada's dagger
dampens the abilities
of meta-humans nearby,
but it wouldn't have
any effect on meta-tech.
So maybe Nora wants to catch Cicada?
Or do something worse.
Barry, there's no way.
This is exactly what
I was afraid of, Iris.
Thawne's been manipulating her.
Now she's acting like
him, talking like him.
That doesn't mean that she's
capable of killing Cicada.
She's working with Rogues.
She kidnapped Cisco and Sherloque.
We don't know what she's capable of.
So what do you want to do, Barr?
We bring her in.
We use Cisco's force fields,
Ray's nanites... We're bringing her in,
before she steps anywhere
near that building.
Hey, Barry. Hold on.
Hey.
We can't keep treating Nora
like she's some kind
of super-villain, okay?
We're just gonna push her away.
What are we supposed to do?
Just let her keep
taking advantage of us?
No. We see where she's coming from.
We try to figure out
why she's doing this.
It doesn't matter why, Iris!
This is Thawne.
It's his plan.
Well, maybe his plan isn't so bad.
What?
Maybe...
I thought...
I thought we were past this, it's...
It's not okay for her
to work with Thawne.
You saw him. You said
he's manipulating her.
And I said that he cares about her.
He's worried about her safety...
No, he needs her, Iris. He needs her.
Or... he's changed.
Barry, Thawne is the one that
convinced me to come back home
and try and patch things up with you.
Thawne.
Thawne gave you advice?
Look, I know it sounds insane,
and I know this must
be hard for you to hear,
but, Barry, ever since I got back home,
the same question keeps
running through my mind.
What if Nora is right?
What if Thawne really is
trying to redeem himself
and that he does want to stop Cicada
and the only reason that
Nora hasn't come back home
is because she knows
that you don't trust her?
Look...
Barry, having Nora in our lives
has made us better people.
Isn't it possible
that she did the same thing to Thawne?
Jenni Ognats?
I thought the idea was
to not draw attention.
Oh, what, so now that you
know my dad's the Flash,
you don't trust me?
Hey, you're the one
who doesn't trust us.
Isn't that right...
Nora?
Yeah, your secret identity,
it's really not worth much.
Feels like nothing about
me is worth much lately.
My dad left me,
after everything that I've
done to try and help him.
You know what the most
embarrassing part is?
There's this tiny,
little, weak part of me
that still wants him to
walk through that door
and take me home.
My dad left my mom
at the maternity ward.
She couldn't look at
me without seeing him.
She made sure I knew it too.
So the day I turned 13, I ran.
I didn't leave town at first.
I stayed under the overpass
with all the other runaways.
And I thought for sure,
one night, I'd look up
and I'd see my mom.
She never showed.
- Sorry.
- I'm not.
When people tell you that
family is always gonna be there for you,
they're full of it.
Mentors will always
let you down eventually.
Parents will break you.
Yeah.
That's why we have to stick together.
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's done.
Come on. Nerd's done with the phone.
One reprogrammed meta-tech phone,
now with visual and auditory
hypnosis capabilities.
Plus unlimited data.
You gonna let us go now?
What, so you can run
right back to the Flash?
How stupid do you think I am?
Any bugs in there?
- It's clean.
- Good.
Now make sure they
can't try anything else.
Come on.
This score's not gonna steal itself.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Hey.
I'm not gonna get away with it?
Cisco's old speedster trap.
You think that's gonna work for Nora?
I don't know.
I'm not sure I'm ready
to find out, though.
Hey, look, I'm sorry about, um...
how I was acting earlier, I just...
seeing Nora looking so much like him...
No, I get it, Barr.
That guy's always gonna be in your head.
Mine too.
And you were right.
Nora broke the law.
And there should be
repercussions for that.
But whenever you guys
step out of bounds,
I always have to remind myself,
the detective side says there's the law.
But the father side says
there's also what's right.
And... I'm always gonna
choose to be your father first.
Maybe that's my problem.
What?
I was ready to give up on her.
You know, I mean, If
I'm ready to do that,
it makes me feel like...
even after everything
we've been through,
I'm not a good parent.
You know, I mean, maybe I never will be.
Come on, Barry. You
know that's not true.
You're going to be an amazing father.
I wanted her to leave.
The second that she
got here, I did, I...
I've held back from her.
It still doesn't feel
right when she calls me Dad.
Well, you didn't call me Dad till...
It was here, in this room,
right after you got your powers.
But you know why that was.
You already had a dad. Henry.
And when the whole world thought that
that man was a criminal, Barr, you...
You thought he was perfect.
Do you think Iris is right?
Nora's plan, Thawne's plan...
could be a good thing?
I don't trust that man.
I never have and I never will.
But I do...
trust my granddaughter.
And if we're gonna
bring Nora home, Barr...
you're gonna have to trust her too.
Oh, thank Crom.
I might've given you unlimited data,
but I also gave you spotty reception.
Nice work.
All right. The bees are in drone mode.
So if we move very, very slowly...
Man, what in the world?
What?
I was trained in the art of escape
by Thaddeus Brown from Earth-51.
Yeah, well, help me escape!
That's a good plan.
So, um...
- Count backwards from ten.
- Ten...
Ow!
How did you do that?
- Trade secret.
- Okay.
So...
You're not fireproof,
are you, Monsieur Ramon?
Am I fire... Oh, God.
Oh.
Ah.
No, no.
Hey!
That's all of them?
- I think so.
- Good.
Because Nora West-Allen
is in grave danger.
Thank you for your patience,
ladies and gentlemen.
With the kind of technology
we're displaying tonight,
security is our highest priority.
Visitor IDs, please.
You bet.
Okay, here we go.
Right this way, ladies.
The last ten months have been
very exciting here at McCulloch.
Buyers from the Army and Navy
are already waiting for us
in our state-of-the-art demo room.
Uh, what's behind that door?
Ah.
That's what our engineers
have dubbed the Forge.
It's where we develop
and test our new weapons.
Unfortunately, it's only
accessible to employees
with the highest security clearance.
Remember.
No killing.
That's a Montgomery
4000, 30-ton vault door.
It'll only open from the inside,
so the only way into the
Forge is through there.
Mm, cozy.
Ready, clown?
Are you sure you can
fit through that thing?
This shall be my aria.
Remember, once you
get to the other side,
the dampener will take away your powers,
so get out quick.
Yeah, I'm gonna vomit.
Mm, mm, mm...
Open, sesame.
Stay with the hostages.
We'll grab you on the way out.
See you soon.
That's one serious meta-dampener.
Whoa.
Last part of the plan.
Load up.
Sorry, XS.
Change of plans.
Good evening, Central City.
We've prepared a special show for you.
Tonight's festivities
will feature several
expendable worker bees...
The employees of McCulloch Technologies.
Unless the Flash comes down
here in the next 30 seconds
and reveals his identity to the world.
Gucci?
You don't want the money?
Oh, no. We want the money.
We just wanted to make a
name for ourselves first.
So, what, outing my dad
makes you legitimate Rogues?
I trusted you.
Oh, God.
You sound just like Silver Ghost...
when I left her in Bolivia.
At least you'll die fast.
I'd say it's been
about 30 seconds, right?
- Yeah.
- Right?
Okay.
Wait!
I am here.
All right, Speedy.
Show us your true identity. Mask off.
Dad, please. You do not have to do this.
I have to.
I am a man sitting alone
at the dinner table.
Is he drunk?
See, when you're in position
to feed the world,
it can make it hard to be a father.
You have to constantly ask yourself,
is what's right for the world
what's right for your child?
Hey, can we get on with it?
Yes, um... yeah, uh...
- No.
- What?
Did you seriously think I
was gonna fall for this again?
Ha!
I phase right through your blast.
Ha! You can't stop the Flash!
No, I think the jig is up.
Confused?
Don't be.
Holy shrap.
How the hell is this even possible?
We bypassed security
while you were busy with General Cloud.
And then you walked us
worker bees right inside.
You're outnumbered,
ladies. Drop your weapons.
Don't let them hit that dampener.
Get the hostages out of here.
We'll handle the Rogues.
Okay, this way.
- We gotta get back in there.
- Yeah.
What the hell is that?
You don't want to know.
Cisco, we need our powers back.
Can you do something about these bees?
Hold tight.
Iris!
All right, we're not gonna
last here much longer.
I'm gonna create a diversion.
Get ready to shoot the dampener.
No, no. Dad, it's too dangerous!
Dad!
He's lucky I don't
throw his ass off a roof.
Nobody out-techs me.
Damn it. Ramon's in my phone.
She's not getting out of this one alive.
Nora, wait!
Dad! You've been hit.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm not the only one.
You were here with me.
The whole time.
I abandoned you once.
I'm never gonna do it again.
So we should probably...
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
The Young Rogues.
Not the nicest friends
you made there, kiddo.
Yeah, I... thought I could control them,
steal the weapons back
after we lifted them,
but I got in over my head.
Even if it was for a good reason.
Nora, killing Cicada
is not a good reason.
No, I-I wasn't trying to kill Cicada.
I needed this.
It's a weapon built from
the solar reflector panels
from the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
capable of destroying any
object down to its atoms,
and it's the only thing that
can destroy Cicada's dagger.
Nora, why didn't you just tell us this?
Because I wouldn't have believed her.
'Cause it's Thawne's plan.
I knew how angry Dad was.
And then you came to
the future without him.
I just thought he'd never believe me.
Plus, I had to stay in a
seriously unschway headspace
to use the negative Speed Force.
But I know now.
I don't ever want to
leave you guys again.
And if that means not following
through with Thawne's plan,
I'm okay with that.
I think we should use it.
- You what?
- Barr, are you sure?
We have to stop Cicada.
I'm never gonna like
where this plan comes from.
But if this thing works...
sounds like our best shot.
You really believe him?
I believe in you, Nora.
And I'm sorry that I
made you feel otherwise.
Dad...
that stuff I said earlier...
I deserved it.
I-I...
I shouldn't have left you in the future.
I shouldn't have put
conditions on you coming home.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
We both do.
We're never gonna leave you again, Nora.
I promise.
So what's the verdict?
Nora's story checks out.
This thing has got a prismatic battery
supercharging its reflector panels.
So if anything's gonna
destroy that dagger,
it's this mirror gun.
That may be easier said than done.
Why's that?
We figured out what Cicada
took from my dad's lab.
It's your cure prototypes.
Why would she need those?
They're just prototypes.
No, they're not just prototypes.
They're failed, broken
versions of the cure.
If a meta-human takes that
without the proper treatment...
They would die.
Cicada has a lethal virus on her hands.
That's why she stole the atomizer.
So she can spread the virus.
She has weaponized the cure.
This is it.
This is the nightmare.
Cicada's gonna kill every
meta-human in the city.
A rare, old bird is the pelican,
whose beak can hold
more than his belly can.
He can hold in his beak...
enough food for a week.
- But I'm...
- Darned...
if I know...
how the hell he can.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --