All right, prepare to die,
Klamulon scum.
The USS Engager is about
to crash the mode on your asses.
How do I turn this on?
Oh, cool. Okay.
All right. Here we go.
Oh, come on. Why do I have to be
the Squid Clam Warriors?
'Cause you're the enemy
and I'm the hero. Okay?
That's how this works.
Now, raise your shields,
because I'm ranked top ten
on the global leaderboards
and you're about to get
your butt kicked.
Hey, that's my ship.
That's my global ranking.
No, no, no, no. Go somewhere.
- You hate this game.
- Not anymore.
Oh, crap. Uh...
- Hi, Bart.
- Oh, Mom. It's crazy you called.
I was pulling an all-nighter
studying for this midterm.
- Yeah. No, you weren't.
- Yeah. No, I wasn't.
Never try to fool someone
who's won two Pulitzers.
Look, Nora, I'm glad I have you.
Your last story did so well
that I would like you
to write a follow-up piece.
Yeah, sure. When's the deadline?
Uh, if you could get something
to me by...
Mom? Mom?
Yeah, that looked like
more than just bad service.
Bart? Nora, is that really you?
Uh, sis...
is it just me
or does Mom look really young?
Oh, shrap.
Mom, what's the last thing you remember?
I was in my office with Taylor,
then I got lost in the time stream.
Guys, I need to talk to your dad
about what happened.
- Uh, Dad's off-world with Uncle Jay.
- But past-Dad is still looking for Mom.
I know he's gonna figure this out.
We should really get you back to 2022.
What was that?
Why can't you run back in time?
I've seen those particles before.
Mom, I think the Still Force
is keeping you here.
Why would Deon do that?
Mom.
- No, it's gone. I'm okay.
- No, you're not.
Sis, what are we supposed to do?
We don't even know what
this time sickness stuff is,
let alone how to cure it.
Or how Mom got infected
in the first place.
- I know this is a big step.
- Yeah, I'll say.
Now, that... That's a superhero.
Are you sure I, like, need to wear this?
Maybe we're moving too fast.
These suits monitor our vitals and
allow us to communicate with each other.
That keeps us safe,
just in case something happens.
Like my connection
to the Negative Speed Force.
I know you can handle this,
and I will be there with you
every step of the way.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Let's get back to training.
You're at Mach 1.7.
1.78.
Wow, that's double
her last recorded speed.
Meena, your heart rate's in the red.
You need to slow down.
- No. I can get to Mach Two.
- You're pushing yourself too hard.
I told you, I got this.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- I just got the wind knocked out of me.
- What were you thinking?
Speed-healing
doesn't make you invincible.
Don't you think I know that?
I'm sorry.
And you're right, okay?
I'm a disaster.
I'll talk to her.
Get it together, Meena. Get it together.
- Oh, God. You got this.
- Pull it together. Okay.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
I'm sorry, Flash. I appreciate
everything you've done for me...
but I'm not ready for this.
Meena, why are you
pushing yourself so hard?
You can lap the planet in seconds.
I can barely stay on a treadmill.
Flash, how am I supposed to be a hero?
- You already are.
- No, I'm not.
Flash, I don't have what it takes.
- I think you do.
- Why?
Because, honestly, when I first
built that machine, I wanted...
I wanted...
nothing.
Look.
I'll never be the person you are.
Holy crap.
- You're...
- Officer Barry Allen, CSI.
So the fastest man alive
is a badge with a day job?
- That's so...
- Ordinary.
Yeah, that's my point.
You'd be surprised
at people's capacity to rise up
and help others during a crisis.
They just need
to be given the opportunity.
That suit, that's your opportunity.
I think you're gonna
be surprised at how well it fits.
But you have to give yourself a chance.
- Damn, that's good.
- I have my moments.
Fine. I'll give it a shot.
Besides, I already have my own suit.
Guess all I need is
my own superhero name.
No, you already have that, too.
Fast Track.
So you're here to fulfill my destiny.
Well... you can start
by getting me out of this prison.
And then...
giving me my speed back.
Oh, you'll get everything
that you deserve, Thawne.
Is that right?
And just what is that going to cost me?
Just one thing.
- Your life.
- No. Wait. No!
What is it?
There was just a major
energy surge in Lian Yu.
- What kind of energy?
- The temporal isotopic kind.
Deon.
Let us know what you find
when you get there.
After last time, I reached out to Cisco.
S.T.A.R. Labs now has
a secure comm link to the island.
Find anything, boss?
It's Thawne. He's dead.
It's like his body was aged
a hundred years in an instant.
Which the Still Force could easily do.
Why would Deon kill Thawne now?
Doesn't make any sense.
Deon hasn't been himself
since we went to search for Iris.
Sorry, Barr. Gotta bounce.
It's exactly what I was afraid of.
Her time sickness has infected his mind.
Chester, can our isotopic sensor
find him?
No. It worked last time because Deon
exited the Still Force for a moment.
But now that he's disappeared,
we're flying blind.
With the power to travel across
the past, present and future...
he could turn up at any moment.
So you were out patrolling last night?
You told me you were working late.
I was. Kinda.
Look, babe,
you don't have to worry about me.
Guess what. I don't just throw emotions
in and out of people now.
I can induce vertigo, too.
- You mean like Rosa Dillon?
- Yeah.
Babe, that's not a good thing.
It's not like
I'm some kind of super villain.
Joe, I would think
that you would be happy for me.
I am. But I just wish
I knew how all this happened.
Oh, speak of the devil.
We are about to have a visitor.
Wait for it.
- Come on in, Rosa.
- Hold up, hold up.
Ain't nobody invite
your criminal behind in here.
Really? 'Cause I think she did
when she stole all my powers.
Uh...
Wait. You what?
Cecile, is that why you leveled up?
Okay, time out. I think...
I think that I can explain...
You think? I want my powers back.
- Why do you think I was tailing you?
- Oh, you what?
I was tailing her.
Right after all my powers went missing,
I got a mental image of her in my mind.
So, yeah, I thought I'd swing by
to see if I could get to
the bottom of all this.
Now, that makes sense. But how did
Cecile end up with your meta-powers?
I, uh... Hear me out.
You know how I can throw emotions
into somebody else? I can take them...
- Yeah, I taught you that.
- Right.
It seems like now somehow I can actually
tap into the powers
of any psychic that's nearby.
Okay, you live off of Third Street,
right?
- Yes.
- Yes. Last night I was out patrolling.
There was somebody who needed protection
from a mugger, and I thought to myself,
"I wonder if I could use
Rosa's vertigo powers,"
and I tried it, and I did it,
and it worked.
That can't be a coincidence.
Congratulations. You cracked the case.
But I still don't have my powers back.
You got an explanation for that, too?
- No, she doesn't.
- No, I don't.
- Then what am I supposed to do?
- I don't know.
What? My theory is just that.
It's a theory.
Then you need to test it.
Hey, David. Sorry to bother you, man.
I need a favor from the chief of police.
I need two visitor passes
to the meta-wing in Iron Heights ASAP.
Thank you so much.
So that's what's causing my life
to be a nightmare.
I'm afraid so.
It's a negative tachyon,
and your body is flooded with them.
They're the cause of your time sickness.
- So how'd they get there?
- I don't know.
But the negative tachyons inside you
are increasing exponentially.
And that's putting an incredible strain
on your physiology.
Your body can't withstand this forever.
- Mom.
- It's okay.
I saw the Forces. Bashir, Deon, Alexa.
But something happened.
They were different.
Why would I see something like that?
All I can theorize is that
somehow your sickness
must also be triggering
some kind of temporal visions.
- It's the only way.
- Agreed.
But someone needs to stay here
to keep Mom safe.
You were with Dad in the Speed Force.
I'll stay here.
I'll go to 2022 and get help.
- Are you sure that's a good idea?
- No.
But if anybody can help save Mom...
it's Dad.
You're gonna burn yourself out.
You've been training
all morning with the Flash,
and now, instead of resting,
you're pushing yourself even harder.
- Eobard, you're worrying too much.
- Meena, you need to ease up.
Not yet. I need to keep training.
Why? So you can kill yourself?
What's gotten into you?
Eobard, what's the point
of having these powers...
We've been looking for you, Eobard.
Who are you people?
Who we are isn't important.
At least not to a dead man.
Whoever or whatever you are,
you need to get the hell out
of my building.
Oh.
Before I make you.
Oh, I like her.
Well, don't get too attached.
Play time's almost over.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You'll find out soon enough.
- I'm not kidding. Back off.
- Or what?
You have no idea
who you're up against, do you?
- Then enlighten me.
- We're the true Forces of the universe.
Ones written in darkness.
And we're here to kill you, Thawne.
So you can fulfill your purpose.
Don't look so negative.
I promise I'll make it fast.
- I won't let you hurt him.
- I was hoping you'd say that.
I can taste her fear.
- Ooh, amuse-bouche.
- Hold on.
Too easy.
Looks like you're the last Thawne left.
Hope you enjoyed
your time, man. 'Cause you're all out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What is it?
- He's coming.
Not fast enough, Flash.
Besides, this ain't your kind of party.
- I'm gonna crush you...
- ...like a grape.
What the...
Who are they?
Whoa, whoa.
It's my speed. Something's wrong.
Well, it probably had something to do
with that light show you just put on.
No, it's like when Meena
attacked me at the dam.
- Only much stronger.
- They tried to kill Eobard.
- Just like at Lian Yu.
- And that's just the beginning.
You see, there's only room for
one set of Forces in the universe.
The negative ones.
And we're tired of sharing our turf.
Speed Force Nora and the others,
what did you do to them?
Oh, he just gave them
a case of the Mondays.
It'll be a while
before you see them again.
Why are you doing this,
and what does it have to do with me?
You're not the Avatar.
You just being here makes us weak.
So sacrifices got to be made, Flash.
And you've got to pay for what you did.
I don't care who they are.
I won't let them hurt Eobard.
Whoa, whoa.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey.
All right, we need to get him some help.
Come on.
I think itjust arrived.
Uh, Chester?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So sorry about the hacking comms thing,
but once I saw the Flash's vitals,
I had to track him down.
Do you think you can bring
the Flash to S.T.A.R. Labs?
Yeah. Be there in under a minute.
- Good. 'Cause he's got company.
- The best kind.
Caitlin, why are you helping me?
I thought you gave up on Frost.
I had.
But after I saw your designs,
I realized I'll never stop
trying to bring her back.
I can't.
Okay, if all goes according to plan,
the pod's cerebral circuitry
should stimulate
and then reactivate Frost's residual
subconscious left inside your mind.
- And then I'll get her voice back.
- Yeah. Then when she's with us again...
We can pick up where we left off
and build her a new body.
Hey, what if Barry
discovers what we're doing?
You know, he pulls you out,
destroys the CRC?
Then we'll find another way.
It was like slamming into
a brick wall.
It didn't matter how fast I was.
The negative tachyons in Mom's body
won't let her travel through time.
I still can't believe we have to fight
Negative Forces or that they even exist.
True that. And what did they mean
by Thawne's not the Avatar?
Dad, you said that it was just
Negative Deon, Alexa and Bashir.
But there was no Negative Speed Force
Nora. Where was she?
This other Deon
said I had to pay for what I did.
And I took away Thawne's speed
by severing his connection
to the Negative Speed Force.
Which might have erased Negative Nora.
That must be why they're weaker now
and why they blame you.
Maybe they think that killing Thawne
will somehow bring back
the Negative Speed Force Avatar.
Hold on.
If they're tired of sharing their turf,
they'd wanna level the playing field.
By weakening the forces we know.
Iris' time sickness.
It was never about her.
They knew Deon would try to help.
And Mom's sickness
would spread to the Positive Forces.
Taking them out of the picture.
Wait. Hold on.
What happens if the bad Forces
end up being the only ones left?
Then every speedster we know
could cease to exist.
Leaving the entire planet unprotected
from the Negative Forces.
Nora, you need to run back to 2049.
You and Bart have to watch over Iris
while we face the Forces here.
But you're still too weak
to fight again. Dad, if they come back...
They will.
But nobody's gonna die tonight.
We're gonna find a way to save
your mom and end this. I promise.
Barr, these Forces?
They're literally gods,
and there's three of them.
How are we supposed to fight that?
It's all three isotopic energy masses.
Electrochemical, temporal
and geothermic.
They're gathering strength
on their own planes of existence.
That's what's bleeding through.
Look, guys, I know this feels different.
That's because it is.
This is personal to them, which means
it's not gonna be an ordinary fight.
We need to be ready for anything.
Have you heard back from Cecile yet?
Yeah. Joe said she was at Iron Heights
and that it's important.
She thinks she might know
how her powers are leveling up.
- But she'll be here as soon as she can.
- Good.
'Cause we're going to need
all the meta-power we can get.
Mona, I don't have much time,
so here's how it's gonna go.
I'm gonna take those off,
you're gonna read my mind.
Tell me what I'm thinking.
- If you can.
- With pleasure.
Don't get any ideas, Mona.
She's taking the cuffs off,
but this is a meta interrogation cell.
The walls are meta-dampened,
so you won't be able
to read anything except us.
Like I wanna read
that empty mind of yours.
- Watch it.
- Or what?
You're gonna put me back in prison?
Can we save it for the playground,
ladies? And, Mona, no tricks.
Now, let's have some fun.
Oh!
What'd you do to me?
My telepathy is gone.
Oh!
Excuse me.
Somebody has a potty mouth.
And no, Rosa, you are not
the good cop in this situation.
'Cause you stole her powers, too.
What is it?
I can hear them.
All of them. Everyone. I can hear
the entire city, all of their thoughts.
This is personal to them,
which means it's not gonna be
an ordinary fight.
Barry.
We need to be ready
for anything.
- Barry. We have to go.
- What the hell, Horton?
No. No way. She said
these walls were meta-dampened.
How can you read
every single mind in town all at once?
Even I couldn't do that.
I don't know.
I don't understand it either.
I think I do.
Look, I don't know how,
but, Horton, you're becoming
one of the most powerful metas
this city has ever seen.
- The planet, for that matter.
- What?
What's happening to me?
You're telling me this is just some
sick play by the Negative Forces?
Damn.
The negative tachyons replicating
inside Iris' body keep increasing.
I don't know if she'll survive
another temporal attack.
- There's got to be something we can do.
- There is.
Pray that Barry can find the strength
to defeat the Negative Forces.
Because it's the only way
to cure Iris and save her life.
Hang on.
There's no time
to stop and talk.
I need to keep training
for our next fight.
Hey.
I know you.
And that adorable
brow furrow thing you're doing,
that only happens
when something's really bothering you.
So you want to tell me what's wrong now?
I mean, aside from cosmic forces
trying to kill me.
Because you have been pushing yourself
beyond your limits all day,
and you still haven't told me why.
And with the way things are now,
I get it. Look, I'm scared too. Okay?
But whatever happens,
let's face it together.
I told Barry this morning
that I could never be a hero like him.
I don't have what it takes.
So he convinced you otherwise,
and that's why you're training so hard.
- You're afraid of letting him down.
- No.
I'm afraid of letting you down.
Eobard, this... this was always
supposed to be you.
And it should be. This is your dream.
- You're keeping it alive.
- That's what makes it worse.
I never wanted to be a speedster.
I... I still don't.
Eobard, I wanted to share
meta-powers with the world
so people could heal their bodies
and live fuller lives.
That was my dream.
Now I'm afraid of losing it.
You're not.
Because what you're doing now,
risking your life
to fight side by side with the Flash
to make me safer,
to make the city safer...
Meena, it's the same dream.
And you may not be able
to share your speed,
but you're doing something far greater.
You're sharing yourself with all of us.
And I couldn't be prouder.
How did I get so lucky?
Blame it on a resume.
God, I wish the B.L.O.C.
wasn't only programmed to just me.
If only there was a way for me
to share this gift with you.
You can.
I'm sorry. I just came down
to check on your training.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Meena, I've been trying all day to find
a way to give us a fighting chance
against the threats
we're facing with no luck,
but... you just found the answer.
Which is?
I'm gonna teach Meena
how to share her powers.
And turn you into a speedster.
Okay, people,
according to S.T.A.R. Labs satellites,
those isotopic energies,
they're on the move.
Let me guess.
They're headed straight for us?
The Negative Forces want a fight,
let's give it to them.
You guys know the plan.
Just keep them occupied
long enough for us to do this.
Okay. Now what?
Take Eobard's hand,
listen to my voice and concentrate.
All right. Let's do this thing.
You're gonna need this first.
Flash, what happened to me
at Keystone Dam,
what if it happens to Eobard?
It won't. For the same reason
you were able to become yourself again.
The love you have for each other
balances you both.
What is this, the B-team?
You got to be kidding me.
- Clearly y'all have a death wish.
- I'm a little disappointed.
Get used to that feeling.
Nothing's happening.
Transferring speed
isn't just about energy,
it's about how you feel.
You're sharing more than your powers.
You're sharing yourself.
Imagine giving
the most important part of yourself
to another by letting them in.
No way. You're not this strong.
Allegra, now.
Okay, that's really bad.
Ooh, Allegra, time to play.
I'll make this fast.
Do your worst, lady.
That's an inverse energy trap.
Good luck fighting yourself.
I feel alive.
But there's so much hate.
It burns.
The Negative Speed Force
is trying to influence you.
You have to fight it. You have to
help each other find a balance.
I'm over here.
Boo.
So close.
Psst.
Ooh!
You're bad at this.
Poor orphan Allegra.
The power of light in your hands
but born into a life of darkness.
What is that,
some kind of evil poetry diss?
'Cause you're gonna need
a lot more than that to scare me.
Why would I scare you...
when I can kill you?
I can't hold him much longer.
The field's breaking down.
She's too strong.
Don't give up. Don't give up. We've
gotta buy them as much time as we can.
It's too late. You're all out.
Meena, remember what I told you.
This is your chance.
Your moment. You can do this.
You can be a hero. And you're not alone.
Looks like y'all gotta bounce.
Permanently.
Back off. All of you.
That's your only warning.
Seriously?
- That's all you got?
- It's three against one, Flash.
You don't stand a chance.
Good thing I brought backup.
- It's time for some payback.
- You sure we can do this?
As long as we work together.
- Where'd he go?
- I'm guessing not far.
Mom.
Mom, you have to stay with us this time.
The Forces he's fighting...
Barry... It's a new moment in time.
- What does she mean?
- It's another vision.
I think she's seeing something
from 2022.
This can't be happening.
Time is changing.
Whatever's happening in the past
is connected to her time sickness,
and now it's literally
changing the future.
Which means we have no idea
how this will turn out.
- I can't.
- No. No, Mom, stop.
Wait. We're not losing you.
No. Wait. No.
Sacrifices got to be made, Flash.
What is it?
The visions.
They're not random.
You can't win, Flash.
We're weak, but so are you.
Which means we can handle
anything you dish out.
This might be our only window
to win this fight.
But to do it, I need you two
to hold them here while I get ready.
I have to give in.
- No, Mom, you can't.
- I have to.
It's the only way to see
what's really happening.
Iris, wait.
You're not the Avatar.
You just being here makes us weak.
And you've got to pay for what you did.
What are you doing?
We needed that to find Iris.
Sacrifices got to be made.
No. The sacrifice isn't Thawne.
It never was.
The real sacrifice is...
Iris? Iris? Iris?
No, no, no.
I told you, Flash.
We're tired of taking the back seat
to those sorry-ass opposites of yours.
Sacrifices had to happen.
And that ain't the only one.
What?
- Eobard? Eobard? Hey.
- Get back.
Something's wrong.
What's happening to him?
Thanks for the resurrection...
Flash.