CLAY: People think of tar now as
mainly a roofing product.
Fun fact, it's also been used as
medicine and flavoring for
candy and liquor.
I bet what you're thinking right now
isn't "yummy," is it?
-What I hope you're thinking is,
-(MUFFLED BREATHS)
"Wow. Clay is serious about wanting
to know where I put that money.
"I think I'll give him
that account number now
"so he doesn't drop me
into this vat of boiling tar."
(MUFFLED GROANING)
Hmm. I'm sorry, what?
Central City Bank, account
five-four-six-three-seven-two-eight.
(CHUCKLES)
Please. Please, pull me up now.
I'm so sorry...
(SCREAMING)
I thought you said
you weren't gonna kill him.
I say a lot of things.
MAN: Where's Joey?
Wishing he were somewhere else. Let's go.
(CRACKLING)
Get in the car, let's go!
-Drive! Drive, man!
-(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
BARRY: There's this song lyric I like,
"All the broken hearts
in the world still beat."
Mine's beating, but bruised.
Hopefully, not for long.
The one thing I do know is
time changes everything.
-(LAUGHING)
-I didn't think about
how many crazy things police see.
And can't unsee.
-You always wanna be a cop?
-Yeah.
My dad was one, he was my hero, so...
I never thought of being anything else.
-What about you?
-No, uh...
I wanted to be an astronaut.
(CHUCKLES)
-Wait, that's what Barry wanted to be.
-Mmm.
Really? Well, probably not
for the same reasons.
Going to space is like the fastest
a human being can go.
So it was either an astronaut or, like...
-Have you heard of scramjets?
-Mmm-mmm.
Okay. They're like supersonic
on oxygen, dude.
It's nuts.
You're right.
Not the same reason as Barry.
You are really all about the speed, huh?
Yeah, I mean, it's what I love.
Is that why you're still drag racing?
You are, aren't you?
Isn't that a little dangerous?
Yeah.
For the people that race against me.
Sure is.
Look, thanks for the hang, but I gotta go.
It's early. Don't leave yet.
No, I got some stuff to do.
I'll see you later.
(DOOR OPENS)
Why'd you do that?
"Thanks for the hang"?
Is he your son
or your age-inappropriate buddy?
Look, I know the dynamic is weird.
I'm just trying to figure it out.
From my perspective, it seems like
you're ignoring something that could...
Oh, I don't know, get Wally killed.
The fact that Wally even wants to
get to know me is the big win here.
So, in the future, could you try
not chasing him out of the house?
Look, Dad, I'll play along
if that's what you want.
But which "you," exactly,
are you trying to let him get to know?
Because the person that I saw tonight?
I don't recognize that dad.
Journal entry one-fourteen.
Turtle's brain.
So...
What I learned from
Turtle's brain matter and
the Reverse-Flash, as it turns out,
has allowed me to complete a device that,
when installed inside the Flash's suit,
will let me harness his speed,
so that the next time
he taps into the Speed Force,
(SIGHS)
I can begin the collection.
I wish there were another way,
but there's not.
-BARRY: Oh, Hey.
-Hey.
You're here late.
As are you. Shouldn't you be out...
Doing whatever it is
that twenty-six-year-olds do
on a Thursday night?
-Um, I am recently single.
-Ah.
So I thought I would tackle
the breach problem,
and see if I could figure out
how to close them.
-Looks like you had the same idea.
-Oh. Right.
I work better alone.
No. Haven't you heard the expression,
"Two heads are better than one"?
-No.
-Must be an Earth-1 thing.
You understand, for me,
that my earth is Earth-1.
-Yeah.
-Your earth has yet to create
CFL Quark Matter, and so it would
take you too long
to catch up on the science.
So I'll do it by myself.
-This science?
-Yes, that science.
Watch this.
That's annoying.
Wow. All right, I'm all caught up.
For the next, like, 30 minutes,
give or take.
Looks like I missed one, though.
All right. You can assist.
But I'm in charge.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, you're in charge.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(REVVING)
(MAN WHISTLING)
MAN: Check that out!
Uh...
What the hell are you doing here?
Aside from trying to send me to therapy?
I told you I did some research.
I thought it would be a good idea
for a story for the paper.
Plus, I thought this would be a great way
for us to really get to know each other.
I mean, I want to know what's so great
about this that you can't let go, bro.
No one here is eager to get their picture
in the paper, you got me?
In which part of the paper?
The part where they put the mug shots
or in the back, in the obituary section?
Yo, why don't you just take
a page out of your dad's book,
let me do what I'm gonna do, okay?
I don't need a big sister.
I know, you're gonna need an undertaker.
Last race of the night, people.
Our reigning champ, Tail Lights!
-(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
-(HORNS BLARING)
Oh...
What? No "good luck"?
(ENGINES POWER ON)
(SHUTTER CLICKS)
(ENGINES REVVING)
TV NEWSCASTER: We'll have
the latest on Oliver Queen's
mayoral campaign coming up.
In local news, Roofing Tar Industries,
which was devastated by the S.T.A.R. Labs
Particle Accelerator explosion
two years ago,
is finally set to reopen.
(SIGHS)
Guys! Clean up before you leave!
Two years!
Two years I was trapped in the ground.
In that blackness.
I couldn't see.
I couldn't feel.
But I could still hate.
Joey?
Did you ever wonder what it felt like
when you dropped me
in that vat of boiling tar?
Since I went in head-first,
I actually felt my ears and nose burn off.
The pain of my eyeballs searing
was unimaginable.
But it was the way
that it burned down my throat
as I tried to breathe
that I thought was really special.
Please.
Why don't I just show you?
(YELLING)
-Excuse me. Barr, you good?
-Hey.
Yeah. Yeah, no, it's just...
-You know, it's weird Patty's not here.
-(SIGHS)
Just not for the same reasons,
but I miss Patty, too.
What have we got?
Uh, victim's name is Daniel Burge.
Not exactly a boy scout,
but managed to
buy this garage two years ago.
It looks like he was dipped in a volcano.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, the depth and uniformity
of the burn pattern
is something you would see if the body was
covered in something like lava
but with a lower burn temp.
And an added chemical characteristic.
The fire investigator didn't find
a secondary accelerant.
Yeah, he probably wouldn't, with a meta.
All right, I'm gonna take
a sample back to S.T.A.R. Labs,
have Cisco run some tests.
Good. I'm gonna go meet Iris for lunch.
She wants to talk to me about Wally.
Yeah, how's that going? You and him?
Great! Well, good.
I don't know,
(SCOFFS) baby steps.
I'm trying to give him space.
I mean, he just lost his mom,
just met me and his sister.
He's got a lot on his plate.
Yeah, he just found the best dad
he could've wished for.
Oh, you say that now,
but you didn't always think that.
(LAUGHS) Well, you were pretty strict,
that's for sure.
-(CHUCKLES)
-But strict isn't always a bad thing,
especially when you know
it's coming from love.
-I'll talk to you later.
-Yeah.
Ugh. It's disgusting.
(SIGHS)
(BEEPING)
CISCO: Okay. Now, click here.
Bam! That's my app. See?
The app just went live.
So, you can sync up all social media
postings about meta-human activity.
Somebody sees something cray
in Central City?
-I get an alert about it.
-Yo, man.
You have too much time on your hands.
Oh, I thought you were
going to say it was cool.
(CHUCKLES)
CISCO:
I'm just saying, you can't judge me.
Didn't your girlfriend just
break up with you?
-Yeah?
-Pretty sure she just did.
Hey, Harry.
Wait, so if that app gives you
eyes and ears all over the city,
then why don't you use it
to find the next Ms. Right?
-Did I just make the meta-human Tinder?
-Mmm-hmm.
Nope. Not starting that fetish.
Stop checking your profile.
This is not a place for that.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
-Looks like you're working hard.
-I am.
I'm researching a story.
One that you'll find
-interesting, actually.
-Mmm.
This is Curran Roberts.
After his head went through
the windshield of his hot-rod,
he was in a coma for six months.
This kid, he died.
He wrapped his car around a tree
at a 110 miles per hour.
They were all street racers, Dad,
and Wally could be the next one.
What do you want me to do, Iris,
lock him up?
Or stop the races.
Look, I learned a long time ago,
you can't stop your kids
from being who they are.
Really?
Why won't you be his parent, Dad?
What are you so afraid of?
All right, you're right.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid he'll reject me. Us.
Look, the last time
I confronted him about the races,
it didn't go so well, remember?
And I need it to go well with Wally.
I mean, after all these years lost,
I want him in our lives.
Look, let me get him to trust me.
Then I can do something about it.
Okay.
Oh...
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
(SIGHS) What's the matter?
Um...
No... I jus... I can't remember,
is the helicity of a particle left-handed
if its spin and motion is
the same or opposite?
-It's...
-No, hold on! I got it, hold on,
I'll find the answer to that.
(EXHALES)
Opposite. I knew that.
You know that's really annoying.
It's... You know, just gotta,
(CLICKS TONGUE)
recharge the old short-term
every once in a while.
(EXHALES)
-You know, this feels like old times.
-Okay.
Yeah, I mean, I know, obviously,
this is our first time working together,
but I am learning a lot from you.
-The last Wells was a real mentor.
-(SCOFFS)
He believed that I could do anything,
made me believe it.
-(SIGHS) Okay.
-He opened up whole new worlds to me.
Guess he really was
like another father, almost.
-(GRUNTS) Stop it, all right?
-What?
I did not ask for your help, okay?
I certainly did not ask to be your mentor!
Okay, relax. I was just talking about...
You know what, I have a kid already,
I don't need another one.
So, scram. Let me finish this by myself.
(SIGHS)
All right.
Hey, I ran your crime scene sample
six ways from Sunday...
-What's wrong with you?
-I just...
Nothing. What's up?
CISCO: Two things, very strange.
One, definitely meta-human cells
in the oil.
And two, he didn't die from his burns.
It was suffocation.
Suffocation?
That makes sense, actually.
The burns indicated that the body
was covered in something.
Cross-referencing O2 levels
in the organic matter,
I found a direct match to animals trapped
and preserved in an asphalt seep.
The guy was fossilized.
Whoa.
So, whoever killed him
is like a walking tar...
Tar pit. Mmm, too slow. It's okay.
So, he's basically drowning them in tar.
God, that's a horror show.
Why did he target Daniel Burge?
(RINGTONE PLAYS)
Oh, it's my meta-human social media app.
That's right.
There's an attack in progress,
Sixth and Bell, downtown.
(CRACKLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Remember me, Clay?
We killed you.
I bet right now
you're not thinking... "Yummy."
Oh, you guys seeing this?
Oh, Yeah. We see it.
(GRUNTS)
All right. Any ideas?
The viscosity of asphalt lowers
as its temperature lowers...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And it hardens.
Hey! Find a way to cool him down!
Hey, Barbecue! Hit me with your best shot!
(GRUNTS)
(CRACKLING)
(LAUGHING) Oh, yeah! Team Flash!
Hey, buddy.
I've got some questions for you. Let's go.
You're coming home, Jesse.
You're coming home.
All right, so Tar Pit...
"Tar Pit," that's what we're calling him?
-That's right.
-Tar Pit, uh, was after one Clay Stanley.
Stanley, as it turns out,
is a suspected hitman
that the C.C.P.D.
has been trying to track for a while.
But they haven't been able to
make anything stick.
-(GIGGLES)
-No pun intended.
Do we know why he was attacked?
(SIGHS) Stanley wouldn't answer any of my
questions. He was pretty scared.
When a hitman is scared,
you know something's wrong.
Hey, did you get an ID on our meta-human?
Yeah, I'm running it through
five different facial-recognition systems
right now.
So, it should take a minute.
And there it is. Who's the best hacker
in the world, people?
-Felicity Smoak.
What is wrong with you two?
That's not friendship.
Our meta-human's name
is Joseph Monteleone.
Oh, he looks friendly.
Monteleone was reported missing...
Surprise, surprise, the night of the
particle accelerator explosion.
And what's the connection between
Monteleone and the two victims?
I'll call Joe, have him run
background checks on all three guys.
Okay, I'm gonna run some tests
on the tar sample,
see if I can find his weakness.
(GASPS)
Hey. You feeling okay?
Yeah. Why?
You're going slower than normal.
You clocked in at 1415 miles an hour.
I'm sorry. How fast do I usually run?
1500. Are you getting enough to eat?
Yes! Yeah, dude. I'm fine. Seriously.
The difference seems negligible.
Fast is fast, right?
-See ya.
-Yeah.
(INDISTINCT COMMENTARY)
Just overtake him, you idiot.
Clark Bronwen?
Who's asking?
Oh...
(GROANS)
You're that chick
who was hanging around Tail Lights.
I'm a reporter for CCPN.
I want you to stop holding the races.
(CHUCKLES) Sweetheart, unless you can find
me another way to make five grand a night,
it ain't gonna happen.
Here's a preview of the expose
that I am writing.
You are the star of the piece.
I had a little chat with
some of your previous associates
and dug up some revealing details
about you.
Like the gambling rings you run
or the thefts you've been involved with.
I'm sure the C.C.P.D.
will be interested in this one.
You're forgetting something in here.
Aggravated assault.
You think you're the only one
that can play this game?
I can find out where you live,
what you eat, when you sleep...
Every little detail about your life.
Hmm?
Publish that trash,
we'll see what happens to you.
Mmm.
This entire conversation is being recorded
and sent to CCPN.
If you or any one of your people
lay a hand on me,
my colleagues will send this
to the cops immediately.
Get out of my office.
You got a death wish?
You are not the first person to
accuse me of that, so maybe.
Going down there? Threatening them?
These people, Iris, they live in the dark.
They're cockroaches.
Except they don't scatter
when someone turns on the lights.
They're looking to bite.
If they are so dangerous, Wally,
then why are you in so deep with them?
I'm not.
I can stop when I want.
So why don't you?
You said that you were only street racing
to earn money
for Francine's medical bills.
Well, there are no medical bills anymore.
So why are you still doing it?
Look, I am not gonna pretend
that Francine meant to me
what she did to you.
But in the short time
that I got to spend with her,
I saw what kind of person she had become.
She was smart and kind and loving.
So I can't even imagine
how much you miss her.
You don't know what I'm feeling.
Well, let me tell you how I feel.
I know that you are trying really hard to
convince everyone that you are a badass,
but I know that you're a good kid, Wally.
And you didn't get that way
raising yourself.
You had a single mother who cared for you.
So my dad and I care
whether you wrap yourself around a tree
or get shot by one of these gangsters.
Having someone care about your well-being
cannot be a new sensation for you.
Show up there again
and I won't be able to protect you.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
I'm just going over some research.
Ten-year-old determination.
What?
When my daughter was ten, she...
Science teacher had her do a project.
You know, this...
Project... I spent
every waking hour tinkering,
perfecting her solar-powered oven.
Mmm.
Anyway, ten-year-old determination.
You remind me of her.
(SIGHS)
Did you scold her as well?
-Yes.
-Mmm.
Look, I know that this has been
hard for you.
But you're not in it alone.
Yes, I am, Allen. Yes, I am. I...
As much as you all want me
to be part of your team,
that's never going to happen.
I'm always going to be a father first.
And one day,
Zoom is gonna make me choose
between you and my daughter,
and every time,
unblinkingly, unflinchingly,
I would choose my daughter.
I will betray you.
That's binary thinking.
It doesn't have to be either-or.
Life is either-or.
Yes-no. Black-white. Love...
Hate.
From the dawn of time,
till this moment right now.
I guess I just have more faith in you
than you have in yourself.
And by the way,
I came up with an idea, or...
A notion, rather, on how we could
close the breaches for good.
This is...
-This... Who wrote this?
-You did.
Yeah, the other you.
Evil, not stupid.
I think the answer might be in the
electromagnetic insulator
of the quark matter.
Like I said, we are a team.
I'm gonna take a look at this.
I'm gonna stick around,
run some computer sims on the formula.
See you tonight.
BARRY: Yeah, see you later.
Drink up.
(SIGHS)
Had enough?
Not even close.
Give me back my daughter
and I'll get you the rest.
You're not in a position to negotiate.
You won't kill me.
And you won't kill my daughter.
Because if you do,
then you won't get what you want.
I don't need to kill your daughter...
(GROANS)
I can torture her,
bring her right up to the edge of death,
so I can do it again
the next day and the next...
Bring me the rest of Flash's speed.
(GROANS)
Hey.
I ran background checks on everyone
involved in this Tar Pit mess,
came up empty.
I mean, they all have records,
but they're sealed, so... Can't read them.
Well, that's 'cause you're bound
by ethics, Detective West.
How many felonies are we committing
breaking into sealed court records?
Three or four. No, five.
Well, they were sealed because
the records are all juvenile offenses.
They weren't arrested together.
No, but look at this.
They served in the same
juvenile detention facility.
Actually, Monteleone and victim one
were bunkmates.
Who do we have shacked up with vic two?
CISCO: Bronwen, comma, Clark.
Well, good luck finding him,
he has a ton of addresses,
and I can't seem to find anything current.
I'll run his picture through
facial recognition.
That won't be necessary.
In this case, I am facial recognition.
I know exactly where we can find that guy.
And, Dad, you are not gonna like how.
Okay, you can tell me about it on the way.
What is that?
Breach implosion reactor.
Sorry I asked.
-You ready?
-Yeah, let's do it.
Have fun fixing the universe, you two.
Hey, Harry. What's going on?
You seem like you're in pain.
No, no. I have a headache.
-If our calculations are correct...
-And they are.
And they are. When this device detonates,
it'll collapse the event horizon
on this side of the breach,
thereby shutting off any connection
to Earth-2 permanently.
(YAWNS)
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just a little tired.
I don't feel like myself.
I'm good, though.
Yeah.
-It's gonna work, Harry.
-Yeah. Yeah. Okay, you ready?
Yeah, give it to me.
Come on!
We did it! (LAUGHING)
You just rewrote the laws of physics.
Don't smile or anything.
I guess that was pretty cool.
Yeah, I'd say so.
One down, 51 to go.
Yeah.
Allen...
Yeah?
Thank you.
It's just the first step in
getting your daughter back.
Come on!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
Welcome to the wrong side
of the wrong side of the tracks.
So where's Clark?
-That's him.
-Oh.
Come on, man!
There's Wally.
-Now, if our fly flag girl can step up,
-(ENGINE STARTS)
-we're ready to begin!
-(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CLATTERS)
What the...
(TIRES SCREECH)
-Call Barry!
-(GASPS) Okay.
You good? You've been a little quiet
ever since we closed the breach.
-Listen, Allen, I ha...
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Hey, sorry. It's... Real quick.
Hey, let me call you back, Iris, I...
I gotta go.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(CROWD SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
Iris!
Get her to the hospital!
(MOANS)
-Hey, baby.
-Hi.
You all right?
What happened?
Piece of glass from that car
-pierced your shoulder.
-Mmm.
But you're gonna be all right.
I hate hospitals.
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
-(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Wally, hi.
Hey. Can I come in?
Uh...
I got you some flowers.
I don't know what kind or anything...
I just...
Or maybe you're allergic.
Is she allergic to flowers?
No, I'm not, Wally. Thank you.
(SIGHS) Cool. Uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'll just leave them here.
It's okay, Wally.
Um, feel better.
I'll be back.
Hey. Hey, hold up a minute.
I got somewhere to be.
Yeah, you do.
At your sister's bedside.
Iris came to that race last night
because she cares about you.
Look man, this ain't on me.
I didn't tell her to go to that race.
Look, I know you didn't.
This ain't a blame thing.
Just hear me out, okay?
(SIGHS)
Look, I know you've just lost your mother,
you've just found us,
it's been like a whirlwind.
Now I can't tell you
how to live your life,
but I can tell you this, you're not alone.
You have people that sit up at night
worried sick about you.
And they're not gonna stop
worrying about you.
That's what a family does.
They put up with each other.
And they put each other first,
before ourselves.
So you're not mad at me?
For being reckless with your life? Yeah.
Hell, yeah, I'm mad at you.
But I'm more mad at myself
for being something I'm not.
I'm not your friend, Wally.
I'm your father.
And I ain't letting you go.
Okay.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
It's Barry.
Go. I'll stay with her.
You sure?
She's my sister, right?
That's my boy.
Don't worry. We're gonna get him.
I'm sorry, dude. What?
Tar Pit.
You shouldn't worry.
We're gonna get him. With these.
With these nitrous grenades.
Each of these has 10 times the
concentration of a hot-rod's nitrous tank,
and is triggered by extreme heat.
We're talking 650 degrees,
that's the boiling point of asphalt.
So, one of these puppies makes contact?
You got a Tar Pit popsicle for dessert.
All right. That's great. Um...
Hey, look.
I think that maybe you were right.
I felt slower tonight.
You know, not by much, but enough.
Do you think there's something wrong
with the suit, maybe?
It's unlikely.
The readings from the suit are normal.
You know I take care of that thing.
Yeah, what? Am I sick?
I don't know. Do you feel any different?
No. Not really. I mean,
I know that I'm slower in the moment,
but I can't tell by how much.
CAITLIN: Two percent.
Tests on the components in your blood
show the Speed Force
at a 100% for the last 60 days.
Until today. It dropped to 98.
Zoom stole Jay's speed.
Do you think maybe
during your fight with Zoom,
yours might have diminished?
But that was weeks ago.
Why would I just be feeling
those effects now?
-Doctor Wells.
-Yeah?
You've studied the Speed Force
more than anyone.
What do you think could have happened?
It could be any number of things.
Yeah, all right...
It's just... Look, I mean,
Iris could've died tonight.
She's gonna be okay, Barry.
You know, this time. But the fact is,
she is hurt right now because of me.
I wasn't fast enough to protect Iris
just from some meta-human tonight.
When Zoom attacks again,
I need all of my speed, and then some.
I can't lose anyone else.
You won't.
-I did it.
-What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What is that?
I stole your speed.
I gave it to Zoom.
No. This isn't...
What, are... You're working with Zoom?
No. Not at first.
We trusted you. I trusted you!
Joe, stop!
Why'd you put him in there?
Because if I didn't,
I would've killed him.
Now, let's go find this tar freak.
-Yo! What the hell, man!
-Shut up.
-I thought I was being transferred.
-(CHUCKLES)
You're not being transferred.
You're the bait.
What?
This is for two years ago, Clay!
(GRUNTS)
Stay.
You know, it's ironic.
I was just saying how much you remind me
of the old Wells.
And now, here we are,
just like I did with him,
standing on either side of this glass
with me asking you why.
I'm doing what I have to do
to save my daughter.
Yeah, at any cost, right?
At the cost of Joe's daughter?
I told you I would betray you.
I told you I would have to choose.
You chose wrong.
Really, Detective?
Because I just sacrificed my daughter.
Because I just sentenced my daughter
to death to save your son.
You want a pat on the back?
I want you to send me home.
Send me back to Earth-2.
Think about it.
Zoom wants you to get faster,
he wants you to have more Speed Force
in you for when he finally takes it.
Send me back, use the Implosion Reactor
to shut down the breach.
Shut down all the breaches.
Close them all.
And Zoom will never be
able to cross over, ever again.
And that'll be the end of it.
What about your daughter?
Jesse's my battle to fight. Not yours.
(GROANS)
Hey. How are you feeling?
Mmm, like I could
use some pizza right now.
(BOTH LAUGH)
But they're letting you out tomorrow,
so I can get you any kind you want.
-From anywhere you want.
-Deal.
You know, um,
growing up, we didn't have a lot of money
to go to the movies or buy toys.
Instead, she would just take me in the car
and we'd go for these long drives.
Just her and I and her music.
I remember being on the road with her
and just...
Watching the scenery flash by
and feeling so happy.
Now, when I race,
feeling that rush of speed, it's like...
It's like I get to go back to those days.
I didn't want to stop, because if I do...
(SIGHS)
See? That wasn't so hard.
-Actually, it was pretty hard.
-(BOTH LAUGH)
This is a sample of Barry's cells
after whatever Harry did to them.
As you can see,
not only is it drained of the Speed Force
but it's also presenting itself
as chromosomal damage.
If Harry kept doing what he was doing,
he could have taken
your powers permanently.
Even Evil Wells couldn't figure out
how to do that one.
Well, look.
Somebody better send his ass back
to where he came from
or I'm gonna shoot him.
-Amen.
-No.
What do you mean, "no"?
What would we have done,
if we were in his position?
I mean, what would you do
if it was Iris, Joe?
Cisco, when Snart kidnapped you,
threatened to kill your brother
unless you helped, you did.
And none of us judged you for that.
We still don't.
Because when it comes to family,
when it comes to the people
that we all love,
we're all vulnerable. None of us are
above making a wrong decision.
He could have done it,
he could've stolen my speed,
gotten away with it.
None of us would've even known.
But he didn't.
And now his daughter's gonna die
and we're okay with that?
I can't just give up on her.
I can't give up on a world.
This is a world full of people
who are facing death.
I don't know, I mean, I may not be
fast enough to beat Zoom yet, but...
I'm not gonna just close the breaches
and forget about it.
We have to help Wells.
Look, guys, I...
I was the one that trusted him first.
I own that.
I let him stay when literally all of you
told me not to.
So everything that's happened up
until this point, it's on me.
But this has to be a group decision.
Come on.
Well...
I guess this is good-bye.
No. It's not.
I told you we're a team.
Now you're a part of it.
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
We're not sending you through alone.
We're going to Earth-2.