No!
(GASPING)
-Dad.
-(GROANS)
Dad. Hey, hey, hey, look at me.
Look at me. Dad, don't leave.
Not again, not again.
Dad! Come on, come on, come on.
Hey, it's all right.
No. (VOICE BREAKING) Dad...
(GASPS)
(CRYING) No. Dad.
I told you family was a weakness.
(SOBS)
You feel the anger, don't you, Flash?
But now, the two of us are the same.
No! (GRUNTING)
There you go, Flash!
Use your anger!
-Just like I did.
-(GASPING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I got you, Zolomon.
-I got...
-Barry, embrace your anger!
End me!
(SCREAMING)
Let me do it for you.
(PANTING)
So close, Barry.
Another Time Remnant.
See, Barry, there could be two of you.
You just have to be willing
to kill yourself.
Yeah. You're almost ready.
(GRUNTS)
PASTOR: "...and comfort us today
with the word of your promise
"as we return our brother to the earth,
"and leave us with the hope that one day,
we'll meet again."
Uh...
My father's...
I can't do this right now.
It's okay, Barry.
JOE: Henry Allen.
Henry suffered
two great losses in his life.
He lost his wife, Nora, and he lost Barry.
He suffered guilt,
embarrassment, ridicule, shame,
and everything that comes with
being blamed for a crime he didn't commit.
Henry Allen was proof
that love can get you through
the darkest of days.
And that love will keep him alive
in all of our hearts.
I'm gonna find him, Dad.
I promise you, I'm gonna take from him
what he took from you.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hey.
-Hey.
-I thought maybe you should eat something.
-I'm not hungry, thank you, though.
-Here.
Barry, um...
I had no idea that you were The Flash.
What you did for me,
all the things that you've done
for everyone,
this whole city...
And now this with your dad and Zoom.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks, Wally.
If there's anything you need,
you just say the word.
All right.
Guys, Zoom's still out there.
We need to come up with a plan.
The man can crack open
breaches to Earth-2.
I mean, if he can do that,
what else can he do
that we don't know about?
Right after he killed his Time Remnant,
he told me I was "almost ready."
-"Almost ready" for what?
-I don't know.
Yep, classic psychopath.
Why can't they ever just say
what they want to do?
We also have to figure out
why I keep vibing
Earth-2 being ripped to shreds.
Seriously.
It's like I'm watching Transformers,
in 4D,
but, like, 10 times more realistic.
And with much better acting.
Look, if you can vibe the future,
we need to stop Zoom before that happens.
I'm gonna get some air, all right?
I got it.
When I was in the Speed Force,
I felt like I'd finally come to grips
with her death.
With not saving her when I went back.
And then, the moment
where I'm finally at the place
I could move on,
my father's taken from me.
How am I ever supposed to
find peace with that?
I don't know, Barry.
But you're gonna have to
find a way to do that
or it's gonna tear you apart.
I just miss him so much already.
Zoom.
Barry, no!
(EXHALES)
Bad time, Flash?
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Thought I'd give you some time to mourn.
-This ends now.
-Not yet.
There's always more to take, Barry.
You're gonna stay away from them.
-That's completely up to you.
-What?
When we first met,
I told you that
Zoom needed to be the best.
You just didn't realize
I was talking about myself.
Is that what this is about?
A race, Barry, between you and me,
to see who's the fastest.
You win, this is over,
and you get to be the hero.
I'm not racing you.
Then your father
won't be the only person you love
that I'll take from you.
Think about it, Flash,
all I want to know is
who's the fastest man alive,
on either world.
I'll be waiting.
IRIS: So, Zoom wants to race you?
He's obsessed with being the best.
Why would we trust him?
He just wants to race.
You know, it actually makes sense
in a completely off-your-rocker
sort of way.
That can't be everything he wants.
It isn't.
This Magnetar that's being developed
by Mercury Labs,
turns out it can act as a pulsar.
Whoa.
What is a pulsar?
HARRISON: It's a power amplifier
with a highly magnetized,
dense rotating core
that could be easily weaponized.
Nah, that's not dangerous at all.
That's what happens to Earth-2.
What happens in my vibes
is because of this machine.
That thing is powerful enough
to destroy a planet?
Well, more than just a planet
if it has the right power source.
-JESSE: Like what?
-Like me.
That's why he wants to race.
He wants to siphon the energy
I create when I run.
off both of you.
CAITLIN: When Jay captured me,
he said that
he used to measure his success
by counting the number of victims he had.
But now, he was gonna measure it
by counting the number of Earths
he conquered instead.
He doesn't want to just destroy Earth-2,
he wants to take out
every other planet in the multi-verse.
-How many are there?
-Infinite.
Well, can he do that?
If he can create a breach to Earth-2
all on his own...
He can get to all of 'em.
One pulse to destroy them all.
I guess I don't have a choice.
I have to race him.
I have to win.
Barr.
Don't race him.
-It's not that easy.
-Yes, it is, you just say "no."
We find another way to stop him, together,
like we always do.
And do what, Joe?
Just sit around,
and wait for him to kill somebody else?
Wally? Iris? You?
-No. No way.
-He needs you, Barr.
He needs your speed again,
to get what he wants.
We have the advantage here.
All I have to do is beat him, Joe.
That saves the multi-verse.
This whole city, all of you.
I won't let another person I love die
when I can prevent it.
This isn't just about racing Zoom, is it?
You want to kill this guy.
Of course, I wanna kill him, Joe!
I wanna do a hell of a lot more
than just kill him,
I want him to suffer
for everything that he's done.
-And he's going to.
-Come on, Barr.
Think about what you're saying.
I have to be willing
to do whatever it takes.
I'm sorry, but I'm racing him,
whether you want me to or not.
And I can't talk you out of it?
Not this time.
Then I'm sorry, too.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
(THUDS)
(EXHALES)
What?
What are you doing?
(SIGHS)
(BARRY EXHALES)
Why did you put me in here?
Because you're too angry right now.
You can't race him like that.
Without a plan you... You'll lose.
Keeping me in here
is gonna get everyone killed.
I'm the only one that can stop him,
you know that.
You race Zoom on his terms,
you'll lose.
This is not your decision to make!
(THUMPS GLASS)
It is, this time.
-(EXHALES)
-We all made it together.
BARRY: What?
All of you?
Bro, I went back and forth.
I was, like, a good 60-40 at first...
Ramon...
Yeah, yeah, we all made the decision.
Come on.
Allen.
Allen. This is for your own good.
BARRY: Don't do this.
Guys, come on. Iris?
Cisco, come on, man.
You have to let me...
You have to let me stop him!
-You have to let me...
-(DOOR CLOSES)
Did we make the right call here?
Yeah, we did.
You okay, Joe?
Yeah, that was just a little harder
than I anticipated.
Yeah, and locking up Barry,
that was the easy part.
Using our plan
to take down Zoom without Barry,
that's gonna be the hard part.
But it's gonna be a lot easier
once we know where he is, Ramon.
Chill man, I'm working on it.
Work harder.
Got it.
He's at the industrial park on Leawood.
-Give me that. Mmm.
-Yep.
That is some serious
nerd love right there.
Snow, look,
everybody here would understand
if you don't wanna go through with this.
Jay may be a monster but there's a human
inside of him somewhere.
I've gotten to that part of him before,
I know I can do it again.
I want to stop him, Harry. For good.
HARRISON: Ramon.
So, let's go over the plan again.
Okay. Caitlin will distract Jay
so that you and Harry
can hit him with the boot.
Cisco's gonna open the breach
and we're gonna put him through it.
I'll disarm the Magnetar.
Destroy the Magnetar,
-save the multi-verse.
-HARRISON: Save the multi-verse.
JOE: One more thing, we need to agree.
We all made this decision together,
so, if anything goes wrong,
we stick with it.
Let's load up.
(CLEARS THROAT)
-Hey.
What's the matter?
You know, I've just been thinking.
You know, what's next?
What's next? We stop Zoom.
Right. Right, I guess...
-I don't know, I mean after that.
-I don't know.
(CHUCKLES) I haven't really given it
much thought.
Yeah, I know, no, I know you haven't.
Guess I just,
I've been thinking about it a lot lately.
You know, I see the way you are
with everyone here.
Caitlin and Cisco, Iris and Joe.
Barry.
Especially Barry.
You care about these people. A lot.
You know, but my friends,
they're all back home on our Earth.
I guess what I'm trying to say is,
you know, when this is all over,
I'm gonna go back home to live my life.
But if you need to stay here,
so that you can live yours again,
I get that.
-I understand, it's okay because...
-I...
No, Dad, seeing you happy...
That is all I've ever wanted for you.
HARRISON: (VIA COMMS) Okay. In position.
Copy that. We got you.
Okay, Snow, you ready?
As ready as I can be.
Cisco? Cisco, you good?
Define "good."
Ramon, you're gonna be great.
-Snow, when you're ready.
-Okay.
You got this.
Here we go.
(CREAKING)
CAITLIN: Jay?
Caitlin.
Jay!
How did you find me?
Doctor McGee said
the Magnetar was stolen from her labs.
I knew that it had to be you,
so, I tracked you here.
I tracked you here, Jay,
no one else knows.
I told you, if you left me...
That if I betrayed you,
you'd show me no mercy. I know.
But I just wanna explain why I did that.
Please, Jay.
Talk.
Good job, girl.
Now draw him towards you.
I made a mistake.
I am so sorry that I abandoned you.
But you have to understand,
what you said to me,
that there was
a dark side of me, that I was...
I was more like Killer Frost than I knew.
I didn't wanna accept that.
I tried to lock the darkness inside of me.
But you knew that
that was already a part of me now.
And you're the only one who did.
And now,
I'm ready to accept who I really am.
Cisco, get ready.
I am so sorry that I hurt you.
But now I want to be the one
that only you know.
Please, Jay, let me try.
One more step.
I knew you'd eventually
come around, Caitlin.
(EXHALES)
But it's too late.
(BEEPING)
Now! Ramon!
Damn it!
Tranq him! Tranq him!
Gun is jammed!
It's working.
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
Ah!
Dad! (GASPS)
(EXHALING)
(GROANS)
Did you see my dad?
No, the vibe keeps changing.
It's like my brain is
channel surfing or something.
They must be on the move,
that's why the vibe's in flux.
Keep trying?
Hey, did you turn off the Magnetar?
No, there's no messing with that thing.
Whatever he did to it,
we try and touch it, we try and move it,
this planet's done for.
WALLY: Iris.
What's wrong?
Zoom took Dad.
What? How?
We tried to stop Zoom
by pushing him through the breach,
but he took Joe with him.
Well, where's Barry? Did he go after him?
He's not with us.
-He's in a cell in the intake...
-(CLEARS THROAT)
Wait, you... You tried to stop Zoom alone?
Long story.
Well, we have to get him back.
Wally, before Zoom took Dad,
we all agreed
that if we got him off this Earth,
we would close the breaches for good
and we would never open them again,
under any circumstances.
Why would you do that?
No. No way, that's not gonna happen.
He made us all agree to it.
-Well, guess what? I didn't agree to that!
-Wally.
Iris, I already lost my mom.
If Dad... (VOICE BREAKING)
I...
(GROANING)
I will say, if anything, Barry sure has
an ample number of fathers to kill.
If you're gonna kill me, kill me.
It doesn't matter,
you're not racing anybody.
Come on, Joe, you know Barry
better than that, you raised him.
He'll say yes
if he thinks he can save you.
Not this time.
I made sure of it.
Who is that?
It would just confuse you.
Try me.
I got my speed the same way Barry did.
When I got struck
by the dark matter and electricity,
I became Zoom, the fastest man alive.
It wasn't long
before I had this Earth on its knees.
But it wasn't enough.
I wanted more.
I wanted to be faster.
So I created a speed drug.
Velocity Nine.
It made me faster
than I ever thought possible.
Fast enough
to break the dimensional barrier,
fast enough to run to other universes,
other Earths.
And then one day,
on one of those other Earths,
I discovered him.
He's another speedster?
Yeah, you could say that.
That was right about the time
I discovered something else, too.
All that V-Nine
I'd been injecting into my system
had a little side effect.
It was killing you.
I searched for a cure. I tried everything.
I even tried
to manipulate the Speed Force.
But let me tell you, the Speed Force...
The Speed Force does not like
its rules being broken.
Now it's been sending
its enforcers after me ever since.
So, you brought him here
to steal his speed.
I tried, but it wouldn't take.
But then the skies parted and I saw Barry.
And then I stole his speed.
-I won.
-(SCREAMS)
I beat the rules of the Speed Force.
Then why keep him here?
A trophy.
And a little idea I had for fun.
You see,
I got so tired of being the villain.
So, I decided to be the hero, too.
I even borrowed his name.
Jay Garrick.
(TAPPING)
You know what's gonna be great, Detective?
After I beat Barry in the race
and prove that
I'm the fastest man alive on any Earth,
he's gonna rot in a cage
just like the one Jay's in now.
And then I'll have a Flash from two worlds
to keep me company.
(DOOR BEEPING, OPENING)
Look, everyone's gonna freak
when they find out I did this,
but I don't care.
We need your help, Barry.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Uh... Hey, guys, Barry's not...
-In his cell anymore.
-Wally!
Well, I wasn't just gonna stand here
and let this happen.
You let him take Joe?
What the hell were you thinking?
Allen, Allen,
there was nothing we could do.
You could have let me race him!
Allen, you're not racing Zoom!
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna tranq me again?
Don't tempt me.
Look, I know you guys made a pact
to keep Zoom on Earth-2,
but you did that without me and Wally.
All right? You don't get to do that!
Barry, look at yourself right now.
You're not okay.
Cisco, my dad was just killed
in front of me!
Do you have any idea how that feels?
Watching someone you love die? Yes, I do.
-Cait...
-Look, Barry,
I know how cold and angry
and distant that can make you.
But when this happened to me,
you were the one who kept me in check.
You told me to stop and take a breath.
And that's all
we're telling you to do now.
I'm telling you, I'm good.
HARRISON: Really? You're good?
Because it seems to me
you wanna do more than stop Zoom.
It seems to me you want revenge.
If that's why you're doing this, Allen,
you will lose.
Look, you guys, I...
You may not think I can do this.
You may think I'm too angry,
but we're running out of time.
I have to beat him, and I'm going to,
whether I have your help or not.
So, which one is it?
BARRY: So, how does this work?
It's the same way we took Iris
into the Speed Force.
Harry does his best Frankenstein,
you hold my hand, and I vibe you there.
All right, let's do it.
I'll do it.
Say when and where, I'll be there.
Cisco's learned
how to bring people into his vibes.
There's one condition. You bring Joe back.
But if he's harmed in any way, it's off.
I'll bring him.
But I won't release him
until after we race.
Deal?
Deal.
I tell you, Jay might be crazy pants,
but he can pick a venue.
Brought the whole crew with you, huh?
Can't say I blame you.
-Dad!
-IRIS: Wally.
JAY: It's gonna be one hell of a show.
Let him go.
After we race.
Cut the crap.
We know you plan to power up the Magnetar
so you can destroy the multi-verse.
Bravo, you've figured it out.
Almost.
I don't want to destroy all of it.
This Earth is at the center
of the multi-verse.
It's the access point
to every other Earth in existence.
One trans-dimensional shockwave and...
Poof.
Leaving just our Earth.
How generous of you.
Need to have some place to hang my cowl.
You might wanna say your goodbyes.
Don't worry, I'm gonna save your dad.
No, you're gonna save our dad.
Get back to S.T.A.R. Labs, it's safer.
CISCO: We're not going anywhere.
You got eyes and ears right here.
Either he goes, or we all die together.
We believe in you.
Wait.
Barry,
kick his ass.
What are the rules?
One lap around the inside of this loop
will produce about one gigawatt of energy.
And I need 500-plus to
power the Magnetar enough to do the job.
Once it's full, I win.
Because there is no stopping it.
So, all I have to do to beat you
is stop you before that happens.
Yep, it's that simple.
But if at any point you decide
you don't want to race anymore,
dear old Dad number two is a dead man.
As well as your little fan club.
They're not my fan club,
they're the reason that I'm running.
Why I'm gonna beat you.
(SCOFFS)
Let's see what you're made of, "Flash."
Just say when, Zoom.
Run, Barry. Run!
He's powering up the Magnetar.
Come on, Barry, catch up.
JESSE: Which one's Barry?
HARRISON: Both of them.
-He made a Time Remnant.
-Time Remnant!
-Go, all right? Go!
-How are you...
I'll explain later, go!
ZOOM: A Remnant.
Stole my trick, Flash.
But you're too late.
Bye-bye multi-verse.
(GRUNTS)
What's the Time Remnant doing?
He's creating his own pulse.
Why would he do that?
Because if that's out of phase,
it'll counteract that one.
Wait, his body can't handle that!
Then what's gonna happen?
He'll die.
(SCREAMING)
No!
(ZOOM SCREAMING)
Do it.
You're a hero, Barry.
You couldn't kill me before.
You won't kill me now.
(PANTING)
(TIME WRAITHS SCREECHING)
I don't have to.
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(ZOOM SCREAMING)
(TIME WRAITHS SCREECHING)
Okay, so you ran back in time
and made a copy of yourself?
Well, uh... Basically, yeah.
It's called a Time Remnant.
It's not something
that I can do every day,
but I needed a way to draw
the Time Wraiths out of the Speed Force,
hoping they'd be more upset
at what Zoom had done
than they'd be at me.
Is that what I look like
when they start talking about science?
Pretty much.
Don't worry, Wally,
it'll get easier to understand.
Well, how does that even work?
Same way Zoom did it.
I ran back in time moments before I left.
It's the only way
I can be in two places at once.
Okay, so, the Time Remnant,
it's still you.
-Yeah.
-But he died.
I...
He was willing
to sacrifice himself for all of us.
That's how much he loved us.
You know what, we'll just...
We'll forget about it.
Uh, Barry, I'm glad you're okay.
(CHUCKLES)
You know what? In battle...
-CISCO: Here.
-...choose your weapon wisely.
All right, some people choose a gun,
I choose a Phillips head.
-Screwdriver.
-Oh, I'm sorry, you're so particular...
Ramon, can you just, please!
Have you ever worked with a tool before?
-I'm working with one now.
-Are you ready?
One, two, and...
(CLICKS)
(MAN GROANS)
MAN: I don't know what's more annoying,
being in that thing
or listening to you two arguing about it.
BARRY: Um...
You're...
I'm Jay Garrick.
The real Jay Garrick.
What?
I'm sorry, I... I'm sorry.
(SOBS QUIETLY)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Barr.
He looks just like him.
He looks just like my dad, Joe.
I can't believe this. My dad told me...
He told me this, he said his,
his mom's maiden name was Garrick!
I just never thought that that meant...
-I never thought that meant...
-Hey, Barr. Barr.
He doesn't know that.
He doesn't know that
he's your dad's doppelgänger, okay?
Do you want me to tell him
that you had to leave?
No. No.
Sure?
Yeah, I just need a minute.
I'll be all right.
HARRISON: That's why he wouldn't.
CISCO: Yeah.
-It's so smart because of...
-Yeah, there it is.
So, the reason you didn't have your powers
is because there was a dampener
in the mask. You see?
I don't wanna see this thing ever again.
(CLATTERS)
So, your powers are back.
I see, Jay, excuse me, Hunter,
stole your color scheme, too.
He took a lot of things that were mine.
Except for that. That's, um...
That's all him.
He said it was his father's, from the war.
Ironically, on my... On our Earth,
this helmet stood for hope.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Maybe I can continue that sentiment.
Take something from him for a change,
make it my own.
It suits you.
Thank you, all of you,
for saving me from Zoom.
Especially you, Flash.
You're welcome, Flash.
Now all I have to do is find my way home.
And where's that?
I think you would call it Earth-3.
Uh-huh. Well, I can get you to Earth-2.
My daughter and I
can help you with the rest.
We can?
Yes, we can.
We're going home.
(CHUCKLES)
HARRISON: Okay.
Snow, you're a tremendous scientist,
but you're an even better person.
(VOICE BREAKING) Don't make me cry, Harry.
I've done enough of that already.
-Detective Joe West.
-Harry.
You have great kids,
you take care of them.
Same to you.
You take care of that beautiful girl.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm a better man
than I was when I got here,
and it's 'cause of you.
I'm not the same, either.
Hey, uh, don't be surprised
if I project myself over to Earth-2
every once in a while, you know, just to
throw your stuff across the office.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
I'll miss you, too, Cisco.
So, I guess I can't text you
from another Earth, huh?
Yeah, I guess not.
It's too bad.
Thank you, guys, seriously,
-for saving our home.
-Mmm-hmm.
Ready?
Yeah.
(BEEPING)
(EXHALES)
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Can't stop thinking
about my dad's doppelgänger,
seeing him, knowing that he's out there,
that should've made it easier.
Doesn't.
Just made me miss him even more.
I can't even imagine
how hard that must've been.
We just won. We just beat Zoom.
Why does it feel like I just lost?
Because you've lost a lot in your life,
Barry, more than most.
But...
Maybe you and me,
seeing where this thing goes,
maybe that can give you something
for a change.
That's all I ever wanted to hear you say.
And I wish that I was in a place
where I could try that with you,
but I feel so hollowed out inside
right now.
I feel more broken
than I've ever felt in my life.
If I'm ever gonna be
worth anything to you,
I need to fix what's wrong with me.
I need to find some... Some peace.
Barry, listen to me,
you waited for me for years.
You let me get to a place
where this was possible.
So, I am telling you,
I am gonna do the same thing for you.
Wherever you need to go,
whatever you need to do, do it.
And when you get back, I'll be here.
Okay.
I love you, Barry.
I love you, too.
And I always will.
(DOOR CLOSES)
That's why I'm so sorry.
But I have to do this.
No! Mom!
Run!
Barry! No! (SOBS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
You're not gonna kill her this time.
You're not gonna kill her ever again.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
(SOBS) No.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
-(WHIMPERING)
-I'm not gonna hurt you. Okay?
I'm not gonna hurt you. You're safe.
(INHALES SHAKILY)
You're safe now.