Sunshine keeping quiet?
Our source confirms she hasn't
said a word since her arrest yesterday.
But Captain West
won't stop making noise.
He is obsessed with connecting you
to Sunshine, Ultraviolet and Dr. Light.
That won't matter much longer.
When will our guest arrive?
Thanks for coming on short notice.
This is your target.
Kill him, please.
And... go!
I can't wait. Oh.
- Like, a map of some kind?
- No.
- That's a flux capacitor.
- Hold... No.
No, that's speed-drawing. Yeah.
They are not gonna get this.
- Oh, this is...
- Okay. Hold on. All right.
It was gonna be the Eiffel Tower.
Oh, yeah, it looks just like
the Eiffel Tower.
Maybe, like, a radio tower?
It actually does look like that.
I've gotta take this. Hey, David.
Joe, I know you think we can tie
this assassin Sunshine to Carver,
but she is just not talking.
Okay, so, let me take a crack at it.
Actually, I need you to take
a step back from this case.
You're too close to it.
Besides, you're the captain now.
David, it's because I'm close,
that I can rattle her.
Come on.
There's nobody else that can do this.
- Okay.
- Is that the Carver case?
- Yeah.
- How can I help?
- You just conserve your energy.
I'll call you if I need anything.
I gotta go, guys.
- Take care.
- Okay.
Bye.
I think I found a way out of here.
- What? How?
- I started focusing on the monitors.
At first, when I tried,
I couldn't read them.
- I would get all these headaches.
- Yeah.
But today,
it started to come into focus.
Perfectly clear.
- You're adapting to this place.
- I read your theory
that says that someone could pass
through the mirror
if their molecular structure
was destabilized.
- Yes.
- If I could
just contact my husband,
I think he might be able to help us.
Eva, my husband, Barry Allen,
is the Flash.
What?
And with his speed,
I think he could phase us out of here.
If his instantaneous velocity
correlates with the limit
of the fractal surface...
then he'll become intangible.
- So... it could work.
- Yes.
I just... I need to recharge.
I've been controlling the mirror
all morning, and I'm exhausted.
Yeah. Take all the time you need.
I will, um...
keep trying to decipher more.
Yeah, you do that.
You're on the right path.
She just did exactly what
I knew she would do.
She even told me the truth
about her husband.
Eva, Joe West is still looking
into your husband's activities.
He knows about Black Hole.
Then it's only a matter of time
before Barry Allen helps him.
You have a new mission.
The Flash is losing his speed.
Drain him of the rest.
- Why do you care about the Flash?
- I don't. I care about my husband.
The Flash is not gonna
take that away from me.
Success is assured.
I got your text. What's up?
Okay, Carrie Mathison. Red string much?
I've been tracking Sue
since she disappeared.
She's hit five banks in five locations.
Every single one of them was doing
some schmoozy cocktail party
when she did it.
And while everybody was sipping
champagne and eating an overpriced meal,
bam, server rooms get hacked.
Oh.
I know that look.
You found her next target.
Of course I found her next target.
First National CC Bank is holding
an investors brunch
for their biggest clients.
Fits Sue's MO to a T.
Now, here's where
you come in, my friend.
I need a hacker who can set up
a net to help catch her.
Somebody who can monitor
the security feeds.
Somebody who speaks bandwidth
and knows binary.
Mmm, I'm not sure you know
how hacking works.
Please. I've seen You've Got Mail
several times.
But I know you've been working on
the artificial Speed Force, so...
I have,
but I'm running simulations all day.
Simulations I don't need
to be there for.
Look, here's the deal. I know
how hard this case has been on you.
I should've been there to help you
from the beginning.
So...
So, you're in?
Will there be waffles?
There better be waffles.
No!
Okay? Thank you.
It was crazy. It was like
it was accelerating by itself.
I know you won't believe this,
but it was like somebody
cut the brakes while I was driving.
Is that even possible?
- I don't know. I'll find out.
- Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
It's Carver that needs to worry.
You think Carver's the one behind this?
He knows
I took down one of his assassins,
Millie Rawlins, AKA Sunshine,
and he knows I'm the lead on the
RICO case we're building against him.
If that's true, we have to
get you in Witness Protection.
- You're just not safe out here, Joe.
- David, I'm not going anywhere.
Look, if Carver is coming after me,
that means he is scared.
What do scared people do?
They make mistakes.
We need to take advantage of that.
Fine. You have my complete support, Joe,
as always.
But if anything happens,
I'll never forgive myself.
I need to go talk to Rawlins.
Okay. The investors brunch
is in full swing.
Now, you go get us eyes
on that server room. I gotta tinkle.
- Yeah, I heard what I said.
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay. The doctor is in.
Say "aah."
What? You call this
an encryption scheme?
I could do this with one hand
tied behind my back.
Prove it.
Uh, Good morning. Don't mind me.
I'm just doing
a routine software update.
Can I have my hand back, please?
You dress well... for tech support.
I have a good work ethic.
Funny. It looked like you were tampering
with the facility's security system...
not repairing it.
Tampering?
Oh!
- You mean all this?
- Yes, all of that.
No, I'm...
It's... This is a procedure we follow
to make sure that your money's secure.
That is, if the safety of your money
is important to you, Miss...
Ms. January Galore.
And the safety of my money
is very important to me.
I'm sure it is.
So, what do those
little green lights do?
The green lights,
they, um...
they are not important.
I'm actually all done here. Um...
- Enjoy the waffles.
- Oh, I will.
I think they only have
apple fritters here.
- Are we live?
- Yeah, we're live.
We got eyes.
We almost didn't get 'em, though.
I ran into one of the donors,
some rich British lady.
What was her name? June? April?
April Gabor.
- Wait. January Galore?
- That's the one.
That's not good.
She's an arms dealer
that Barry and I met in Midway City.
I don't know.
She seemed kind of charming to me.
Very forward, but charming nonetheless.
Uh-oh.
We're in trouble.
The security feeds are dead.
Servers are
on the fifth floor. Let's go.
Ew! Ew, ew, ew!
What is that?
- A perfect disguise.
- A disg...
I think I just lost my appetite.
Hi, slick. You miss me?
Almost as much as I miss Fredrico,
my tapeworm.
Hello, Sue. Or is it January?
What can I say?
Collateralized loan obligations
are deliciously robust.
Although... not half as delicious
as you in a tux.
Still up to your old tricks,
swiping diamonds and pearls?
You like Prince?
Me, too.
Yes! Me three.
I'm Cisco, by the way. We met
back when you were January Galore.
That was an excellent accent,
by the way. Do you have any training?
Oh, thank you.
I did my senior year abroad.
- London, no doubt.
- Italy, actually.
It... She fancy. You fancy.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Okay. Sue, you're trapped.
- And you're going down.
- Actually, I'm going up.
Ah!
- Did you see that?
- What are you...
Damn it!
Uh-oh.
Dibs.
If this is what she used, she has access
to all the bank's financial holdings.
Oh, well, it's only several...
billion... dollars.
Millie Rawlins.
This man, he worked for Joseph Carver.
This is what happens
to those who fail Carver.
Incentive for the rest of us to succeed.
But you didn't succeed.
So, that probably means you're next.
Now, look. I can offer you protection,
but this is a one-time deal.
Are you interested?
No, thanks.
The only way
somebody could accelerate the car
and simultaneously cut the brakes
is from inside the car's engine,
which is... I mean, obviously,
no person could fit inside there.
Ray Palmer could. Only he's not
a murderous sabotaging type.
How about a meta-human
who could squeeze into tight places?
Likes to watch
his victims suffering up close.
Rag Doll.
Now...
what would...
First Lieutenant Millie Rawlins...
a soldier who rescued 14 friendlies
from an insurgent labor camp...
think of what you've become now?
You were honorable.
Legion of Merit. Medal of Valor.
Millie, restore that honor.
Help me stop Joseph Carver
before it's too late.
Get down!
What the hell?
Joe? Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine. I'm all bandaged up.
All right, Joe, that's twice now.
And that's twice
I've gotten a clean bill of health.
- All right.
- Wait. Hold on. Where are you going?
Barry, I am still the lead
on this investigation
and I was this close to getting a deal
with Rawlins. If it wasn't for...
He's a dangerous psycho
and he's got your number.
All right, look.
I hate to say it, but I don't know,
it feels like maybe Singh was right
and you should let this go for a while.
So, you're gonna
take me off the case now?
No, I just...
I'm trying to keep you safe, all right?
I'm not fast enough to do that anymore.
I mean, look at your arm.
Barry, you know I'm not gonna stop
if I'm this close.
Look, I get it, but will you please
just stay here at S.T.A.R. Labs?
At least until I've stopped Rag Doll?
- Fine.
- Joe...
- Hey, you okay?
- I'm good.
- What happened?
- There was gunfire.
And... I wasn't fast enough
to stop all the bullets.
He's fine,
but it's my fault that he got hurt.
- Barry, your speed.
- Yeah.
- It's getting worse.
- I know.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna use
facial recognition algorithms
and meta-human trackers.
I'm gonna find Rag Doll and stop him
if I have to use every last resource
in S.T.A.R. Labs to do it.
Except the one that counts.
Barry, you promised me
that you would keep him safe.
- I know.
- I can't lose my dad.
You won't. I swear. I...
Come in!
When my private security said
I had a guest,
the last person I expected to see
was Captain Joe West.
I suppose you're here
on urgent police business.
Personal.
You made it that way
when you tried to kill me. Twice.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Peter Merkel. Rag Doll.
The last he was seen was
breaking into McCulloch Technologies.
- That was about a year ago.
- Yes.
We have had a number
of security issues lately,
as I'm sure you're aware.
You know, the strange thing is,
the C.C.P.D. never apprehended him.
He just vanished.
Until today.
Do you know anything about that?
Sounds like you've crafted some
very interesting narratives
about me, Captain West.
Mmm.
It even sounds like you're saying
I hired someone
to pop out of a box to assassinate you.
I didn't say that Rag Doll
popped out of a box.
Damn.
And I was doing so well.
You've been a pain in the ass, Captain.
And you've taken up
far too much of my time.
So, I'm gonna make you
a one-time-only offer.
I will call off Merkel,
and all you have to do is walk out
that door and leave me alone forever.
I'll make you a counteroffer.
You spend 80 years in Iron Heights
for attempting to assassinate
a precinct captain.
Technology is a fickle mistress.
A localized EMP pulse.
One of the advantages of owning
the most advanced
technological institution in the world.
Whatever you think I've done...
it's a million times worse.
I can eliminate anyone, anywhere.
And that includes you.
Your lovely companion, Ms. Horton.
Even that precious little baby of yours.
You took your badge off,
just walked right in there,
knowing what could happen.
What the hell were you thinking?
Do you think I went over to
Carver's house for some macho BS?
You know I'm not proud like that.
I'm just terrified
I can't protect my family.
But you're the one
who needs protecting right now.
I'm not worried about me, Barry.
I can't lose Cecile and Jenna.
And we can't lose you.
Listen. Carver has
unlimited resources, right?
First, it was Dr. Light,
then it was Sunshine.
Today, it's Rag Doll.
And tomorrow, it's... Who knows?
And now, if I can't protect you...
What do you want me to do?
Think about Witness Protection.
Joe, you need to stay alive.
Committing to a five-year investment
will guarantee you
a 5% return, Miss Genoa.
As for security,
our server room is reinforced
with military-grade steel alloys.
Hmm, sounds wonderfully
impenetrable.
Yeah,
but nothing is impenetrable.
Isn't that right, Ms. Dearbon?
Dearbon? You said your name was Genoa,
like the salami.
Yeah, she lied
about that. It's kind of her thing.
She is stupid rich, though.
Oh...
In that case... how do you two
know each other? Are you married?
- Gross.
Uh...
Do you mind excusing us for a moment?
I would love to speak to my friend
about possibly investing here as well.
By all means. Take your time.
So, slick, you here to make
a super-citizen's arrest?
- I know what you're up to.
- Really? I'm all ears.
The files on this
are your parents' bank accounts.
They've been wiring money every week
like clockwork to a coded account.
Your parents are being extorted.
What? No snarky comeback?
Oh! Means I'm right.
Are you going somewhere with this?
My guess is, that your parents
are being blackmailed
by the same person
who owns every single banking system
that you've hacked into
since we last met.
- Joseph Carver.
- Careful, slick.
You weren't stealing anything
in Paris, Shanghai or Central City.
You were investigating Carver.
He must have found out
their ugly little secret.
What? Did they lie on their tax returns?
They bribe their way
into that yacht club?
Enough. Assume
whatever you want about me,
but don't do it about my parents.
They're good people.
Then let me help you.
I barely know you.
You know everything that matters.
For the record...
I didn't enjoy tricking you.
Okay, I enjoyed it.
But honestly,
I felt pretty crappy afterwards.
Why is that?
'Cause you are a good person...
just like your parents.
You just have some...
issues.
You're so decent. It's nauseating.
Oh, boy, you should have seen me
about two years ago. I was a...
I was a real crapbag.
Actually, you probably
would have liked that, though.
I don't know.
This whole good guy thing
you got going on?
It's... tolerable.
Tolerable.
Which is why...
I'm giving you this.
Look into that.
You might find something interesting.
I did.
I just talked to Iris. She said
someone tried to kill Captain West.
Yeah. Joseph Carver.
So, what do we do?
Uh, I sent Jenna to stay
with her sister Joanie,
so, we know she's safe and, uh...
I don't know.
Cecile, if you're helping Joe,
and Carver finds out...
What? Do you think
he's gonna come after me, too?
If he does, he'll have to go through me.
Come here.
Me, too.
Sorry. I couldn't help but overhear,
but I'm here to...
help keep everyone safe. You feel safe?
We're safe. You, not so much.
Allegra. Hey, Allegra. Come on.
Hey, what can I do to fix this?
I feel terrible.
What about how I feel?
I've been lied to before. A lot.
By pretty much anyone
who has ever said they cared about me.
And now, you expect me to smile and
say it's all okay because you feel bad?
No. I...
What am I supposed to do?
Walk away.
Great.
Allegra!
Argh!
Ahhh!
It's too much pain.
You will bring
so much suffering.
Barr. Rag Doll took Cecile.
He sent this.
So much delicious suffering.
See you soon, Captain.
All right. I can track Cecile's phone,
but, Joe, he wants you to find her,
just like he used me to lure Iris.
It's a trap.
If something happens to her, it's on me.
No, we're gonna bring her home.
- But what about your speed?
- Don't worry about my speed.
I'll do whatever I can, all right?
I won't hold back until she's safe.
Let's go.
- You okay?
- I'm okay. I'm good.
Joe, find Cecile. I'll hold him off.
Run, Captain. Run.
Cecile!
Babe!
Babe, I'm coming.
Okay.
Careful. Don't touch me.
It's a pressure bomb.
If it's not weighted down,
it'll explode.
How do you know that?
He told me to tell you.
Okay.
I see you.
Missed me.
Almost. Getting closer.
Suffer. Nice and slow.
Ow.
Captain West, Rag Doll was here.
Yeah, I know. He took Cecile.
I'm here with her now.
Listen, I need your help
defusing an explosive.
What kind of device is it, Captain?
It is a Michael 112
composition Charlie four,
block demolition charge.
C-4. Block demolition charge.
Yeah, got it.
Okay. So, easy. Open the outer panel.
You're gonna see four wires.
Pull the green one.
There are more than four wires
and they're all green.
- I got this.
- But how? Captain...
Okay.
Babe, do you remember dancing
at your cousin's wedding?
When you were stepping
on my toes until we finally got in sync?
- Yeah, we're gonna do that now.
- What? No.
Shh! We do not have time.
- I can't let you do that.
- Follow me.
- On three, move. Okay?
- Okay.
One, two, three!
We lost a minute.
You're not gonna make anyone
suffer anymore, Merkel.
No matter how much
Black Hole's paying you.
Pay? Don't care about money.
If you're not trying to kill Joe
for money, why are you doing this?
For release.
Mother's dead. Heart attack.
No one left to suffer now,
except myself.
Thank you, Flash, for helping me suffer.
Any second now,
release comes with kaboom.
Joe, what did you do?
What I had to do.
Please, get Cecile out of here now.
No. I don't wanna leave you.
Cecile, please.
Make sure that Jenna is safe.
- Joe, I'm not...
- Barry, go. Now.
Okay. All right. Come on. Let's go.
- Barry!
- I have to try.
I should go into WITSEC.
Federal agents will be here any minute.
They'll be the only ones
who know where you're going.
They'll keep you safe, Joe.
At least till we get
this Carver mess sorted out.
Thank you, David. For everything, man.
Iris isn't answering her phone.
She needs to know this is happening.
They're here.
I can maybe...
Just tell Iris I love her, okay?
Okay, I don't think I can do this.
- Yes, you can.
- No, I can't.
Yes. Listen. I have to go. It's the
only way to keep our family safe.
You just tell little baby Jenna
that her daddy's gonna come home
as soon as he possibly can, okay?
- I love you, Cecile Horton.
- I love you.
I love you.
Listen. Iris and I, we're gonna
take down Carver and Black Hole,
and then we're gonna bring you home.
I promise.
- Keep Iris safe.
- I will.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Joe West is out of the way,
as requested.
Success is assured.
Good. If anyone's gonna make my husband
pay for what he did, it's gonna be me.
Looks like Captain Joe West
will no longer be a problem.
Someone else must
have heard the good news, too,
because they sent you a gift.
I had it delivered.
Hello, Joseph.
You're a hard man to get a hold of.
That's on purpose.
Wait. I just have one little thing
I need from you.
An apology.
Seriously?
- That's what this is about?
- I wanted to help the world.
Now, you're destroying it.
I am keeping it safe.
You let me rot in here,
while you took everything I created.
- I had a vision for humankind!
- So did I!
And now, I'm making it a reality.
This is your last chance, Joseph.
Threats are for real people, Eva.
Not phantoms.
Because that's what you are.
And me?
Darling... I'm untouchable.
Literally.
I just talked to David.
- Is my dad really gone?
- I tried calling you.
That's your excuse?
My dad is in Witness Protection, Barry.
- You should have come to get me.
- Yeah. Iris, there wasn't enough time.
You're the Flash, Barry.
You can make a second last an hour.
Where is he?
- I honestly don't know.
- When is he coming back?
The second that we catch Carver.
Carver's pockets are lined
with politicians and lawmakers, Barry.
Not to mention assassins.
It could be years before we catch him.
Iris, I'm so sorry, but Cecile
was almost killed, and then Joe.
He had to leave right away,
or else Carver may come after
Jenna or you next.
- Carver already came after me.
- And I wasn't here to protect you.
Look, I'm trying to keep
this family safe.
I want you to take me to him right now.
I told you.
I don't know where he's going.
You don't need to, Barry.
They left, what, like, 30 minutes ago?
They're probably still within
a 50-mile radius.
With your speed, you could search
the entire area in seconds.
- You know I can't. Not anymore.
- Can't or won't?
- It's not that simple.
- Yes, it is, Barry!
No, it isn't!
Look, Iris, I'm barely hanging on.
I can't catch my breath.
I'm getting dizzy, my feet are numb,
my fingers tingle.
It feels like with every step I take,
I'm getting ripped in two.
All I can think about is if I'll be fast
enough tomorrow to save another life.
- I trusted you, Barry.
- Iris, I...
Now, we have something else in common.
We both lost our parents.
I hope that was worth it.
Where are you going? Iris?
I want you to leave.
- You can't be serious.
- Barry, you always do this.
You always make all of these decisions,
and then the rest of us
have to deal with the fallout.
Flashpoint, going into the Speed Force,
taking Nora into the future,
and now, this? I am done, Barry.
- Iris...
- I want you to get out.
Please. Okay, look,
we can work through this.
- You're my home.
- Not anymore.
Leave.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::