BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
JOE: Previously on The Flash...
DR. WELLS: I stabbed your mother
in the heart. And I was free.
CISCO: Eddie's his ancestor.
If Eddie dies, he'll never be born.
He's being erased from existence!
- EOBARD: Gideon.
- Yes, Professor Thawne?
Where the hell am I?
I was accepted into the forensic science
program at Midway City University.
I'm leaving Central City.
BARRY: Joe, you have a son.
Hi, I'm Wally. I'm Francine's son.
These races, that's the only way that
I can pay for my mom's hospital bills.
Jesse's my daughter and Zoom has her.
Daddy! Please help me.
Don't let him take me back.
DR. WELLS:
I would do anything to get you back.
BARRY: There are many reasons why we run.
But, usually, it's to avoid
what's right in front of us,
a decision to be made,
or a dilemma we have to face.
Lately, for me, it feels like
running is all I've been doing.
What you got for me, Cisco?
You've been playing Good Samaritan
all morning. Take a break.
Are you sure you don't wanna
get to CCPD, give Patty your attention?
No, I can see her later.
'Cause we cannot afford
to waste any more time.
What, 'cause we just been
sipping Mai Tais since you got here?
I don't know what you've been sipping
since I got here,
but Barry needs to get
better, stronger, faster.
We need to train to prepare for Zoom.
Oh, I see.
You haven't had your coffee this morning.
I had my coffee this morning.
Don't slurp.
Don't. Don't. Don't.
(COMPUTER TRILLING)
Runaway chemical transport truck
heading south on Kester.
On it.
(SIRENS BLARING)
Hey, uh... I can't stop the truck!
Somebody rigged it.
Sorry!
You can't let that truck crash. If you do,
you'll take out a whole city block.
Great. Thank you. Thank you for that.
(HONKING)
(WHISPERING)
That was close. That was close.
Oh, and the plot thickens.
CISCO: Dead end dump ahead.
You gotta get out of there.
Oh, come on.
Yes!
That one was a little close.
Nice.
Now can you please, please take a break?
- How's that for training?
- Great.
Look, we're gonna catch Zoom.
We got Turtle locked up in the pipeline.
All we got to do is use him to figure
out how to steal Zoom's speed
And then we'll get your daughter back.
That might take longer than we thought.
Why is that?
Because Turtle's dead.
Barry, we need you back here. Stat.
All right. I'm on my way.
Gideon.
Was the trip a success, Professor Thawne?
I believe it was.
I've finally figured out
what time period The Flash is from.
Now let's figure out a way to get home.
CISCO: He better not be pulling a Juliet.
Yeah, that's right. I see plays.
He's dead, Cisco.
How'd this happen?
Preliminary brain scan shows
an acute brain aneurysm.
The night we captured him.
How's that for timing?
What does that mean?
You think I did this, Garrick?
This man is the key to us stopping Zoom.
The key to me saving my daughter.
Why would I want that?
Never understood why you
do anything, Harrison.
That's fine with me, Garrick.
Guys, look.
We need to figure out how to stop Zoom.
Everything we've tried so far has failed.
We need to start thinking outside the box.
I mean, we haven't even figured out
how to close the breaches yet.
Maybe that's where we should start.
That's a good idea.
I'll get on that.
- L'll help.
- (PHONE BUZZES)
I've gotta get to the CCPD.
I'll check in with you guys later.
Okay.
Every time
you think that Wells is on your team,
something happens that makes you doubt it.
Hey. I just wanted to see
if you could run this trace for me.
Someone messed with
an ethanol transport truck this morning.
They cut the brake line
and tampered with the gear shafts.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay. Wow. You're backed up, huh?
Iam, yeah.
Yeah. I guess I'll find out
what that's like once I finish CSI School.
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah. You will. I guess.
- Yeah.
Look, Barry, I know that you're upset,
but I was hoping it wouldn't
be like this between us.
(BARRY swans)
What did you think it was gonna be like?
(CHUCKLES) I just thought we could
at least talk before I left.
You're moving.
I don't know. I mean, it just
doesn't feel like
there's much to talk about now, right?
I guess not.
PATTY: Hey.
- Hey.
I sort of overheard some of that.
Mmm-hmm. Um...
Patty's going to CSI school,
in Midway City.
She is moving in two days.
I mean, you don't have to let her leave.
She's wanted to be a CSI her whole life.
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Just went to see Francine and, uh...
She doesn't have much time.
I already said my goodbyes,
if you want to do the same.
CISCO: It's not gonna work.
They're closing the breaches,
that's like solving Einstein's riddle.
Yeah.
I solved Einstein's riddle when I was 10.
Yeah, well, maybe Earth-2 Einstein
wasn't as clever as ours.
You realize this earth
is my Earth-2, right?
Listen to this.
What if we can figure out
how to control my powers?
We could find Zoom, get the jump on him.
That's a good idea.
You should get on that.
I need your help, Harry.
What you need, Ramon, is to
figure out what triggers your vibes.
Exactly.
And I don't know what triggers them,
It's completely inconsistent.
Sometimes it's when I touch
something that belongs to a breacher,
Sometimes it just happens.
There's always a cause. Cause, effect.
Doesn't take Einstein to figure that out.
Okay, so what is the cause?
You saw when I tried to vibe Dr. Light,
when I tried to vibe you.
It took a while to work.
Yes. Yes, it did.
Meet me in the Time Vault.
For what?
Hello?
Harry?
Of course.
Now he's gonna make me wait
in this freaky-ass Braille room.
- DR. WELLS: Hi, Cisco.
- (SHRIEKING)
(STUTTERS) Stop! Don't do that!
(GROANS)
I figured out your trigger.
The rush of adrenaline.
Dopamine floods the brain.
And the quickest way
to achieve that result...
Fear!
Do not move!
You can't be.
What did you see?
Reverse-Flash.
He's here.
Oh, my God!
Christina McGee.
Who are you?
You're coming with me.
Flash!
Eobard Thawne.
You know who I am?
You died!
Good to know.
And guess what, Flash?
I know what time period you're from.
So that means, very soon, you will die.
(GRUNTING)
No.
You okay, Barr?
I'm good. Yeah, it's just a lot.
Eddie Thawne died,
so Eobard Thawne should've
been erased out of existence, right?
Not necessarily.
It is possible
Eobard was in the Speed Force,
protecting him like a bomb shelter,
keeping him alive and his time line intact.
It's what's known as a "timeline remnant."
A... A what now?
Here, let me... show you.
This, this is now.
Here. Today.
This is the time Thawne comes from.
This is the moment
you all erased him from existence,
but since Thawne is from the future,
this is where his timeline begins.
That's why he's still alive.
This Thawne has not yet traveled
back in time to kill Barry's mother,
he's here, now,
in this time period, for the first time,
timeline remnant.
Explains why nothing's changed.
Yeah, it also explains why
he didn't know my name
Or that we have met before.
To him, you hadn't. Not until the future.
If Thawne dies
before he can time travel again,
will that save Barry's mother?
No. That's not how it works.
In her timeline,
Barry's mother's already dead,
and her death is a fixed point.
Nothing can change that.
All right, well, I'm gonna end this.
Him. In this time, once and for all.
Let's find Dr. McGee, then we'll
figure out what to do about Thawne.
Okay?
I gotta go check on Iris.
Ramon.
Caitlin, I know you're worried
about Dr. McGee,
but we're gonna get her back.
It's not that. It's Jay.
- What about Jay?
- He's sick.
And it's getting worse.
When Zoom stole his speed,
it affected him on a cellular level.
We need to do something about it.
All right. Like what?
I think we should replace
his dying cells with healthy ones,
indistinguishable from his.
How do we do that?
We find his Earth-1 doppelganger.
There.
Tachyons?
A man in a yellow suit tried to
steal another tachyon prototype last year.
(CHUCKLES)
I must have gotten stuck here once before
and not been able to access
enough of the Speed Force.
Tachyons should do it.
I want you to isolate and accelerate
their energetic properties for me.
I don't know if I can do that.
If you want to stay alive, learn.
Franny...
Hey. (EXHALES)
How you feeling today?
Better now.
I'm gonna let you two talk, okay?
Okay.
(SOFTLY) Hey.
Can I get you anything?
Oh, just that brother of yours,
so all of us
can be together for the first time.
Yeah, he should be here.
Well, his mother's leaving him.
Can't blame him
for being angry about that.
I just wish he'd get all that anger out
while I'm here to help.
Same thing goes for you, Iris.
One thing you learn when you're dying
is not to hold anything back.
You want to say something to me,
you need to say it while you can.
I have so many great memories
from when I grew up.
Now, when I think about those memories,
I can only wonder
what it would've been like
if you and Wally would've been there.
I'm not angry at you anymore
for what happened.
I just wish
you would've come back to us a lot sooner,
because I would have forgiven you then,
just like I'm forgiving you now.
Mmm...
Thank you.
(CRYING)
I don't know why this is so hard.
I barely even know her.
The facial recognition software
at S.T.A.R. Labs
didn't find anything either.
No, but there's still
more databases to check.
We'll find his doppelganger.
- Thanks, Barry.
- Yeah.
PATTY: Hey.
Hi, Caitlin.
Hi.
Uh, can we talk?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, for sure.
Um, I'll let you know what I find.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What's up?
I didn't know you were
working with S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah... Um, yeah, Joe and I
help out every once in a while.
Really?
Yeah, I probably shouldn't tell you this,
but there's a lot of weird stuff
that happens over there. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
Is that what you came to tell me?
Um...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) You're just rolling
with the whole me-leaving thing.
Yeah, I mean...
I don't know what to tell you, Patty.
Everyone in my life that I love
leaves at some point.
Kind of getting used to it.
You never told me you love me.
Yeah. I guess I don't get that chance now.
I don't understand. What is it?
What's going on with you?
Why are you being like this?
My life... It's complicated.
And I don't want you to have regrets.
I don't want you to miss out on something
that you've always wanted to do, and...
I wish that things were different
for both of us.
You know, but they're not. Sorry.
Me, too.
So, what did you do to my goggles?
I added a wavelength trigger to stimulate
the fear receptors in your brain.
And then, I took what you already had
to induce slow-wave sleep,
upgraded it to get you
to stage four sleep.
Now, this is good,
this will give us more control.
- Okay.
- Now, I'll be able
to dictate how
long you vibe for.
Put 'em on.
What am I gonna see?
I don't know. Never done this before.
You'll have to tell me
so I can steer you where you need to be.
Ramon, if you want to find Reverse-Flash,
put on the goggles.
Okay.
Atta boy.
(SIGHS)
Go ahead.
(LAUGHS) Oh, yeah, man.
I'm in full-on vibe mode right now.
What do you see?
It's hard to explain.
It's different events.
Different events in time.
Concentrate on the Reverse-Flash.
Okay.
I see him.
Move toward him.
Okay. Now what?
Try to picture him with Christina McGee.
Where the hell am I?
It's charged. You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
Yes, I did, didn't I?
No!
(PANTING)
Well, what is it?
She's dead.
Dr. McGee is dead?
Harry and I were trying to hone my powers
to find Zoom.
And then we ended up
using them finding the Reverse-Flash,
and that's when I saw him kill her.
And then he left.
He left? What do you mean, he left?
McGee built him
some kind of speed machine,
and he ran into it
and got flung back to the future.
(SIGHS)
You'd need superluminal energy
to send someone through time.
- You mean like tachyons?
- Tachyons.
Wait, we can track their location
once they've been activated.
- Anything?
- Nothing.
Cisco, you're sure that's what you saw?
- I'm positive.
- All right.
What else did you see?
There was all sorts of weird
tech everywhere. There was a clock.
What time did the clock say?
9:52, I think. How is that relevant?
It's 6:00 now.
Are you telling me I can see the future?
That's exactly what I'm telling you.
Those goggles are getting
named immediately.
But that means Dr. McGee's alive.
That's right.
Okay, we have 3 hours,
52 minutes to find her
and stop Reverse-Flash.
Let's do it.
JOE: Spivot.
Hey.
Can't get away from
those case files, huh?
Ah, just following up on a hunch.
You're gonna miss the action, right?
Maybe. A little.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
It's nice to know someone will.
Wait, we talking about Barry? 'Cause it
sounds like we're talking about Barry.
He kept telling me there was stuff
he couldn't share with me,
and I've been going a little crazy
trying to figure out what that stuff is.
Yeah. Barry's not great at sharing.
Neither are you.
What do you mean?
Barry just told me that, you know,
sometimes he helps you out
with S.T.A.R. Labs stuff.
Yeah, he does,
when he has a few extra minutes.
I didn't know that. I mean,
the whole time I've been working here,
you never mentioned it to me.
But then I realized why.
I went through some of Barry's old cases.
All of them involved The Flash
saving the day,
with details that Barry
couldn't have possibly even known.
That's weird.
Yeah, it... It is weird.
The only thing that does make sense
is that Barry is The Flash.
Have you ever seen Barry run?
He waddles. Like a slow-ass duck.
There's no way he's The Flash, Patty.
You know, when I started this job,
you told me I had to learn
how to lie to do it.
You're a terrible liar, Joe.
See you.
Nice nitrous kit.
You're gonna get caught one of
these days. You know that, right?
Get thrown in jail?
I'll stop racing
when these hospital bills stop coming in.
I saw Mom today.
She says you haven't been by in a while.
Yeah. She knows why.
She thinks it's because
you're angry with her.
I have every right to be angry.
Nothing for 20 years.
Then out of nowhere, she tells me
I have a sister. I have a father.
Yeah, the same thing
happened to me, too, remember?
But that shouldn't keep you
from seeing her before you can't anymore.
No, look, that's not what it is.
Then what is it, Wally?
I gotta go.
Last year, my fiancé died.
Unexpectedly.
One moment he was here, the next, gone.
I didn't get a chance
to say goodbye to him,
to tell him everything
that he meant to me,
that he was my world,
that he was loved.
But today, I got to say goodbye
to your mom. My mom.
And it helped us both find peace
with what happened to our family.
Wally, don't make a mistake
you're gonna regret the rest of your life.
Go, see your mom, while you still can.
No sign of tachyon activity.
We're running out of time.
We've gotta find them.
It'll take a few minutes for the device
to reach full power once it's activated,
but when we find it,
you're gonna have to get there fast.
- Hey, Barry.
- (SCOFFS) Yeah.
Have you found out anything else
about Jay's doppelganger?
There's no Jay Garrick on this earth.
It's so weird.
Everyone has a doppelganger.
Maybe just ask Jay. He's a good guy.
Just ask him. I'm sure he'll tell you.
Okay.
Hey.
Hold on. What's up?
We got a problem.
Patty knows you're The Flash.
- What?
- She caught me off guard,
I mean, I played it off, but
come on, she's a smart girl.
And, she was going through some case
files, and you were acting all squirrelly.
- This is my fault now?
- No, it's nobody's fault.
Oh, my God.
Maybe you should tell her.
- No.
- Patty's trustworthy.
It's not even about that, Joe. I...
I don't want another person that Zoom,
or Reverse-Flash,
or any of these meta-humans,
can use against me. I don't want it.
Patty can't get hurt over this.
(COMPUTER TRILLING)
CISCO: Tachyons! 87th and Avenue J.
Must be one of Mercury Labs'
off-site facilities.
- Hack into their security...
- I've hacked into the security feed.
- You're one step ahead...
- I'm one step ahead of you.
Uh-oh.
Barry, hurry up!
It's charged. You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
Yes, I did, didn't I?
He's gonna kill her.
(GROANING)
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, get out of here,
all right? Go! Go!
(GRUNTING)
That was my way home!
You're not going anywhere.
You haven't won here, Flash.
I'll find another way back.
You're gonna have to get through me first.
You really think
you're fast enough to stop me?
Well, let's find out.
Catch me if you can.
Oh, it's on.
Get him, Barr.
Not fast enough, Thawne.
I will never lose to you again!
This war between us, it ends now!
(GROANING)
Barr, you gotta stop!
Barr! Don't kill him! Just bring him in!
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
Get the cell ready.
Hey, he can't...
Phase his way out?
No, he can't do that.
It's the same cell
we used to hold Dr. Wells last year.
- Barr, where are you going?
- I'm going down there.
No, you're not.
The more he learns about you,
the more you will alter the timeline.
He killed my mom!
He's from the future,
he hasn't done that yet.
He doesn't even know you're The Flash,
and you need to keep it that way.
You already said that his mother's
gonna die no matter what we do.
Ramifications,
any time anybody messes with the timeline.
And it's impossible to predict
what those ramifications are gonna be.
Barry, you caught him, and you
stopped him from killing Dr. McGee.
In my book, that's a win.
This doesn't feel like a win.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
I gotta go.
So, what'd you want to talk to me about?
My dad had Multiple Sclerosis.
Every day, for years,
I watched this amazingly strong man
fight for his life, and lose.
So I can't sit by and watch another man
I care about fight for his life
and not do something about it.
I tried to find your doppelganger.
Same DNA, same cellular structure.
I could replace your dying cells
with his living ones.
But you don't have
a doppelganger on this earth.
Caitlin, there is a good explanation.
Meet me at Hofherr Park tomorrow,
and I'll show you.
Why can't you just tell me?
Because you need to see for yourself.
(SIGHS)
How'd you get your suit in your ring?
Who are you?
My name is Cisco Ramon.
And we know each other well, don't we?
We have a history together.
You could say that.
And that's all you want to know?
How I got my suit in my ring?
I want you to know that I'm the one
who figured out you were back.
I helped stop you. Me.
And how'd you do that?
I have powers.
And I helped track you down
and I put you in here.
That's quite the ability
you've been given.
And here's what's so ironic about it.
You gave me these powers.
Have fun thinking about that
while you rot away in this cell
that you helped me build.
Bye, Felicia.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Got your text.
I wasn't sure that you would see me,
considering
you've been avoiding me lately.
Patty, I haven't been avoiding you.
No. Just, busy, you know,
speeding around Central City.
I know you're The Flash, Barry.
Patty, come on.
Please don't make me feel any
more stupid than I already do.
Look, I'm a detective and
I should have known.
I was so smitten with you.
Okay, look,
what you're saying, it's insane.
Look, you don't have to
lie to me anymore, okay?
I understand, I understand why you didn't
want to tell me.
I understand why you've been distant.
Look, I understand everything.
But just tell me the truth now.
Just be honest with me. Just...
Admit to me you're The Flash,
and I'll stay.
I can't do that. I'm not him.
That's too bad.
It would've been nice to stay.
Fight crime during the day,
and be with you at night,
but I was wrong. Take care, Barry.
Is that you, Flash?
Why do you hate me so much?
I didn't always.
I was obsessed with you.
For so long, I wanted to be The Flash.
I spent years figuring out
how you came to be,
duplicated the reaction, and it worked.
(LAUGHS)
I became like you.
All right, so what happened?
This ability to travel through time
revealed the truth.
My fate was to become your greatest enemy.
I was never going to be The Flash.
So I became the reverse
of everything that you were.
The more people you saved,
the more you were loved,
the more I had to take from you.
That is why you killed my mother?
That's why you ruined my life?
Because you couldn't be me?
I became better than you!
(SCOFFS)
I am the one thing you
cannot stop, Flash!
No. No, no. Not anymore.
Our race is over.
And you lost.
I've learned what time period
you're from, Flash.
And one day soon, I'll learn your name.
CAITLYN: We need you in the cortex now!
(GROANING)
What's happening?
He's experiencing an uncontrollable
amount of electrical energy in his brain,
Putting him in a prolonged state
of clonic seizing.
What? (STUTTERS) Can you stop it?
I don't know.
Hold him down!
We're trying!
- Sedate him, Snow, now!
- Come on! Come on!
Benzodiazepine. This should do it.
(SIGHS)
Finally.
(ALL GASP)
- What the...
- What was that?
What's going on? Where the hell am I?
Cisco!
- It's the time line.
- What? What are you talking about?
When you, when you captured Reverse-Flash,
we ruptured the timeline.
That's what this... All the blood,
and the seizures, and it all.
Cisco is being affected to...
By the changes to the timeline.
The changes to the past,
and the changes to the present.
This is what this is.
We need to do something.
- We need to do it fast.
- Like what?
We need to restore the time line.
Barry, you need to get Reverse-Flash
and send him back to the future
As quickly as possible.
I just caught him!
You want me to let him go?
Keeping him here is killing Cisco!
Barry, if this is the only way
we can save him, you gotta do it.
You gotta let go of Thawne!
Okay, all right, look.
(STUTTERS) I destroyed the tachyon drive
in the speed machine.
There's no way it'll reach the speed
necessary to send him back home.
- You can.
- What?
Your speed coupled with Thawne's speed,
that'll be enough to catapult him
through the time continuum. You can do it.
All right.
All right, let's do it. Let's do it.
Time to send you home.
The time paradox. Yeah.
You've all messed with something
you don't understand.
Can you do me a favor
and just shut up?
(LAUGHING)
And how exactly
are you going to send me home?
Don't worry about it.
You fixed Dr. McGee's tachyon device?
No. I came up with a different method.
Is that so?
Uh-huh.
Who are you?
No one of consequence.
No. I doubt that.
I win again, Flash.
All you have to do is provide him
with enough momentum
to get him past the space-time barrier.
All right.
Hey, listen to me.
Thawne knows about you.
Right here, right now.
This is where he learns about you,
all of you.
It's how he knows about S.T.A.R. Labs,
how he knows about me,
the Harrison Wells from this earth.
And there's nothing I can do about it.
There's nothing you can do about it.
This is his origin story.
And it's going to happen
no matter what you do.
But right here, right now,
you can send him back to his time.
You can save your friend,
you can save Cisco.
And then move on with your life.
This could be a good thing.
You can finally let go of him.
I could throw him three centuries
from now, he'll always be a part of me.
Time to send you back where you belong.
We'll meet again soon, Flash.
I know. And every time,
I'll be ready for you.
Hurry!
He did it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
He's gonna be okay.
CAITLYN:
I don't understand what we're doing here.
Just like you, I thought that if I could
find my doppelganger on this earth,
I could replace my damaged cells
with some of his healthy ones.
Believe me, I was just as shocked as you
when I couldn't find
a Jay Garrick anywhere on this planet.
Took me a while to figure it out.
But eventually, I found him.
His name is Hunter Zolomon.
Hunter Zolomon?
Why doesn't he have the same name as you?
From what I could gather,
his mother died during childbirth.
He bounced around from family to family
but eventually was adopted
and raised by the Zolomons.
Why does that mean he can't help you?
My DNA was mutated
when I became a speedster.
There's only one way to reverse
what's happening to me.
If we can catch Zoom,
I can get my speed back.
Then let's finally figure out
the best way to do that.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- Wally, hi.
- Hey.
Um, do you wanna come in?
(STUTTERING) No, I can't stay. I Just...
I wanted to tell you that I'm gonna
take your advice, go see my mom.
Okay.
Iris, I was...
I was wondering if you would come with me?
Yeah, yeah, I would love that.
- Yeah?
- Okay. Um...
(IRIS WEST SIGHS)
(GROANING)
My head feels like it's in a vise.
What happened?
I think you vibed one too many dimensions.
Maybe I should stop doing that.
(JOE LAUGHS)
Yeah, he's gonna be fine.
How did you, um, get the vibing to stop?
We sent Thawne back to his time.
You let him go?
I couldn't let him take another person
I cared about.
Thank you.
Of course.
Okay. I think I need a Big Belly burger.
Anyone?
- I'm good, thank you.
- Yeah, no pickles.
Two triple-triples. Please.
You got money?
Mmm-mmm...
Rest up, all right? I'll be out here.
So, Patty,
she's on a train to Midway City right now?
Mmm-hmm, I had to let her go, too.
Mmm, I was thinking about what you said,
about part of being The Flash is that you
have the ability to do amazing things
that nobody else can do.
And we see now that a hundred years
from now, you'll still be doing them.
But the other part is,
you're gonna be loaded with sacrifices,
and you're gonna have
hard choices to make,
And there's gonna be a lot of things
where, eventually,
you'll have to let them go.
You gotta be ready for that.
I am. I'm ready.
That's my boy.
(CHUCKLES)
(PHONE BUZZING)
That's weird.
Hey.
Barry, I'm on the train.
There's a... there's a man with a gun.
All right, hold on. I'll get you help.
Is everyone okay?
PATTY: Everyone's fine.
It was a false alarm.
But thanks for coming so fast, Flash.
I just want to make sure
everything's okay before I go.
Don't worry. Everything's good.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Goodbye, Barry.