My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one fast enough
to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
I didn't kill Clifford DeVoe.
Tricked ya.
Barry, they took a hostage.
- Who did he take?
- Your dad.
I'm ready for my super-suit.
This "tarp" is your super-suit.
What is this? A puppy's raincoat?
Nice job, rookie.
I won't be a fugitive.
If I'm convicted, I'm not gonna run.
We find the defendant guilty.
We're losing control!
Deploy smoke grenades!
We need backup!
They're back in! Lock it down!
Let's move. Move out.
Fine. Just tell us what you want.
I want you to back off
or I will detonate this thing!
Okay, calm down.
Nobody needs to get hurt today.
You just follow instructions
and everybody here gets to live to
see the sunshine tomorrow, all right?
And I better not
see the Flash either.
All right!
First, I want a car!
Something eco-friendly.
Like a... Like a Prius.
- Okay, we can do that.
- Good.
Right.
Now, second...
I want a plane, okay?
A private plane.
Okay?
And a salad, all right?
- I'm counting calories.
- Okay.
It's gonna take us
an hour to arrange that.
You better hurry up,
'cause these hostages
don't have much time.
Should've gone with a steak, pal.
'Cause it's the last
decent meal you're getting
for the next five to 10 years.
Who the hell are you?
Your friendly
neighborhood superhero.
You can call me...
Mr...
One second.
Guys, this is a huge moment for me.
What's my name?
I was wondering where
you were going with that.
Hey, hey, where are my hostages?
Ah... Bathroom break.
They just couldn't hold it anymore.
Don't worry, though.
They're totally safe.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Get back, freak!
"Freak"?
Oh, sticks and stones
may break my bones, buddy.
Well, they used to. Not anymore.
I'll blow this whole city block.
Ah... You do realize
you're a part of that block, right?
Come on, man, it's a weekday.
People just wanna get off work,
go home, watch the boob tube.
So why don't you
take off that vest and...
Don't touch me!
Ralph, are you okay?
Yeah, just wicked heartburn.
Let this be a lesson to all of you
would-be criminals out there.
Catching you won't be
too much of a stretch.
And so, our streets are safe again,
thanks to Central City's
funniest new hero, the Stretchy Man.
Okay.
Embarrassing.
Cisco, next time
you're going with him.
Iris, a chicken needs to
leave its roost sooner or later,
especially when that chicken insists
on doing his own solo mission.
- This is bad.
- This is really bad.
"Stretchy Man."
That's a terrible name.
Also, now that
I'm gonna be on TV all the time,
this gray suit gotta go.
Hey. Easy, chickadee.
No, Ralph, I meant you, okay?
That bomb could've
torn you to shreds.
Or Joe, or any of the police outside.
Relax, ladies,
my cells are completely polygamized.
- Polymerized?
- Yeah, that.
Which means they can stretch
and take a bomb blast.
- Oh, my God.
- Dibny is in-dib-structible.
Okay, Ralph,
you are missing the point.
You need to be more cautious.
No, no, no.
You are missing the point.
What I really need, guys,
is a new superhero name.
Ramon, you've had all this time.
You can't come up with anything?
Patience, okay? I'm getting to you.
I've just been a little preoccupied,
what with Barry being in prison
and all!
You find anything that might prove
DeVoe framed Barry yet?
My dad and Cecile are meeting
with Judge Hankerson tomorrow
to go over his appeal.
We've been poring through the
evidence piece-by-piece, but...
Don't worry, Iris,
we're gonna get him out.
Hey, has Barry joined a gang yet?
I got some friends on the inside,
I can make some calls.
Shut up, Ralph.
Okay.
I will stop helping now.
You can watch the clock all you want,
but it won't go any faster.
You're Barry Allen, right?
Henry Allen's kid?
- I'm...
- Axel Walker.
You and your dad
kidnapped my dad once.
Yeah. Right.
Pudding?
Lunch lady gave me extra.
I think she has a crush on me.
Hey, word on the block is
you carved up some professor.
He give you a bad grade or something?
I didn't kill anybody.
Yeah, sure.
Everyone's innocent in here.
Especially that guy.
Yeah, Big Sir.
He's really innocent.
This is grosser than usual.
Does pudding go bad?
Axel, what do you want from me?
To be murder buds.
You know,
we could share trade secrets.
I'd love to hear how you
carved up that college quack.
I don't need any friends in here.
Man, I do not feel good.
Get him up.
You got mud on my bright whites.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
"Sorry" is right.
First week in Iron Heights
is often the hardest, Mr. Allen.
You've already seen what happens
when a few inmates try to revolt.
Acclimating to your new life
will take time.
Always does.
In the meantime,
do your best to stay clean in here.
Oh, and Mr. Allen?
Your 1:30 is waiting for you.
Hey.
- I'm so glad to see you.
- Me, too.
How's it going?
It's not as bad as
I thought it would be.
And, hey, you're talking to
the newest member
of the Iron Heights janitorial staff.
I'm the fastest mop alive.
Well, we've been
surveilling the DeVoes 24/7.
I mean, they must have
made a mistake somewhere, right?
And I've been poring over
all of the evidence with Dad.
We are gonna get you
out of there, Barry.
I know you will.
How's the rest of the team?
I saw Ralph on TV.
Ralph is...
Getting a little cocky.
Yeah. I was when I started, too.
It happens.
Yeah.
Iris, it's okay.
I just can't believe
this is our new normal, Barry.
I don't want this to be our lives.
You're gonna find something.
I know it.
Closing time!
Wrap 'em up!
I just wish
I could touch your hand again.
You will.
I promise.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Every tomorrow.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Walker here
spewed all over his cellmate.
Says he's got cramps.
Who are you? Where's Nurse Hill?
Out sick.
Looks like he ate the pudding.
Yeah. How do you know that?
Because I'm the one who sent it.
Come on, Axel. Let's go.
Mom?
Walker and the nurse
used tranquilizers
on two more guards on their way out.
And nothing tipped you off
that this nurse might be a criminal?
Her background check was clean.
She said her name
was Lindsay Fineheart.
She was sent over
by our staffing company.
I'm gonna need the hard drive
of the surveillance footage
from the security cameras
in the infirmary.
Well, unfortunately,
we're still analog here in gen pop.
It'll take a while to dub the tapes.
In the meantime,
I'm having Fineheart's file
brought down for you.
How's Barry doing?
He's a model inmate.
Just like his dad.
- Do you mind if I...
- No.
Let me check on that file.
Barr.
Joe. Hey!
What are you doing here?
Axel Walker escaped.
Some new nurse helped him get out.
He was in here
because of the pudding.
- How do you know that?
- He was complaining about the taste.
Hey, let me help with this,
all right?
- Barry.
- No...
Is Cisco having any luck figuring out
how to bypass the system?
Once he does that I can phase out
of here. I can help you track him.
Barry, you need to stay put for now.
Trickster is just
a messed-up kid.
We can handle him.
No, I know, of course. I just...
I'm already tired of feeling useless,
you know?
The only thing you should focus on
in here is watching your back.
Pretty sure
cops can't touch inmates, so...
Otherwise, I'd give you a hug.
Stay strong, Barr.
Mmm-hmm.
- Detective.
- Sir.
Well, this is her.
This woman's name
isn't Lindsay Fineheart.
Her name is Zoey Clark.
James Jesse had a girlfriend?
Yeah. She called herself "Prank."
Back in the day,
she was Bonnie to Jesse's Clyde.
No matter what,
whether it was attempted murder,
arson, robbery,
she was always by his side.
Man! What were people wearing
back then?
Zoey Clark was the beneficiary
to Clarx Toys' empire.
Not much of an empire.
All those stores closed 20 years ago.
Looks like she has Bachelor's degrees
in Arts and Applied Sciences
as well as a Masters in Chemistry.
"Trickster and Prank were responsible
for a series of terrorist attacks
"across Central City,
including the destruction of...
"The Gadzooka Bubblegum Company."
I always wondered why my favorite gum
suddenly disappeared in the '90s.
I have it on my Earth.
- You do not.
- I just said we did.
- We do.
Anyway, after Jesse was arrested,
she disappeared.
She's been a fugitive ever since.
Looks like Axel was born nine months
after Zoey was last seen.
I bet she left town
to take care of her son.
And she came back
to bust him out of prison
and pick up where she left off.
Well, I'm digging into C.C.P.D. files
to see if she had
any other known associates.
I'll set the satellite
to do a search grid. Ramon.
Hey, how about you hook me up
with some of that gum?
- Why don't you breach yourself?
- Sounds like an insult.
Kind of was.
Hey, Ralph,
do you wanna go to your usual spots,
see if any of your contacts
have seen her?
Sure. Need a chaperone.
Caitlin, you're up.
It's happy hour. You're buying.
Come on.
Use Killer Frost's credit card.
- No way, Jose.
- You think Ralphy's made of money?
Where are you two hiding?
Wow!
What is this place?
- It's all that remains of Clarx Toys.
- Oh!
It's cold in here.
Oh, awesome!
I made the news!
Not "awesome."
Now the police are looking for you.
As soon as night falls,
we're out of Central City.
And then
we'll go meet up with Dad, right?
That's why you broke me out.
Because Dad wanted to see me, right?
Not exactly.
Axel, I wanted you back in my life.
Right, but what about Dad?
Well, he broke out a year ago,
and he hasn't come looking for you...
He doesn't care.
Of course he does.
Axel, your dad's a deadbeat.
He doesn't want to be a part
of this family and he never did.
Don't talk about him like that.
Honey, I'm sorry, it's just that...
You just don't know him like I do.
Do you know what it was like for me
when you were growing up?
While you were idolizing your dad,
I was the one making your dinner.
While you were watching him
terrorize the city on TV,
I was the one driving you to school.
I was the one making sure
you got your homework done.
I was the one packing
the lunches in the morning.
- I was there for you.
- I know. I know, Mom!
Okay? Now we can get him back.
I don't want him back.
I want us to go be free together.
I never wanted you
to end up like your father.
Well, it's too late for that, Mom.
I just need to get Dad's attention.
I'll show him that someone in
this family still has a funny bone,
Mom.
...everyone walks away safe.
And so, Central City has a new,
sexier model of superhero.
Me, kids.
And I know just how I'm gonna do it.
I'm the sexy model.
Anyone want an autograph?
Autograph, anyone?
No, Axel. Axel!
Axel!
Heard you had a little one-on-one
time with a badge this morning.
Oh, God.
First, you dirty up my shoes.
Now, you're snitching to the cops?
You've had quite the first week,
haven't you?
I don't want any trouble.
Too late.
This isn't over!
Thanks.
Hey, how's the search coming?
Harry and I
already set all the parameters.
Just got 300 square miles
to comb through. So...
Yeah.
- That's not good.
- Hello, Central City!
It's been far, far too long since my
beautiful face graced your screens.
This kid's got a face for radio.
Trickster's hijacking
the city's broadcasting signals.
Today, we're going to play
a little game I like to call,
"What does this do?"
Looks like a regular old bouncy ball.
But what does this do?
- Cisco.
- Tracing.
Let's find out!
If and when
you throw it hard enough...
Kaboom!
He's downtown.
Corner of Demeo and Bilson.
Bring me the Stretchy Man.
Or else you're gonna go "boom-boom."
My first supervillain
Thunderdome challenge.
This is awesome!
Ralph, you do not know this guy.
He's dangerous.
He's throwing bouncy balls
and wearing a bedazzled peacoat.
I got this.
Still haven't taken that off, huh?
I sleep in this.
You mind breaching me there?
It's a lot faster.
Where are you, Stretchy Man?
I've got plenty more
where that came from.
Nice suit, Fall Out Boy.
Yuck.
Yours could use some work.
Oh, look at that cutting wit.
You wanted me, here I am.
Great. Do want to play, uh, catch?
You're really blowing this
supervillain fight.
Well, it's my Central City
return party.
And your death will make me a star.
Child's play.
Okay. All right.
This is what I call
the "Hurty-Squirty Gun."
Tricked ya!
It's acid,
with a little ingredient X.
I call it "axid."
He's panicking.
His heart rate is off the charts.
Ralph, are you okay?
Help!
Burn, Stretchy Man. Burn!
Not today, Satan.
What the hell did he do to me?
What the hell was that stuff?
Looks like Axel
created some sort of super acid.
Yeah, it's got a pH level
in the negative 50s,
and all it did
was burn through your skin?
If it were anybody else, it would
melt right through them
like Xenomorph blood.
- Like in... Aliens.
- Aliens.
But you said my cells
were polymerized.
- No.
- You said nothing could hurt them.
Dibny, I didn't say that.
I said your cells were bonded unlike
anything I've ever seen.
I've never seen acid like this,
and so,
cannot be responsible for things
I have never seen.
- It definitely hurts.
- Mmm-hmm. Of course.
Well, now we know
what your Kryptonite is.
What the hell is Kryptonite?
- What?
- Aw, come on.
Think I'm gonna heal?
- Eventually.
- Probably.
"Probably"?
Well, you know...
I thought I was indestructible.
So did we.
- Get out.
- All right.
Okay, well, Caitlin, you can treat
the wound and manage the pain. Right?
- As needed.
- Okay. Well,
the most important thing is
that you're safe.
Ralph... Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
Um... Axel's still out there.
We should track him down.
Oh, my God.
This might sting a little.
Excuse me. My wife was supposed
to be here a half-hour ago.
Could you see if...
Cool.
Hey.
I was just wondering
why you helped me.
Because your dad helped me.
- Oh, are you okay?
- No, Mom. I'm not.
Stretchy Man's still alive.
All Dad's gonna see is that I failed.
He won't want to see me.
Who am I kidding?
I'll never be like him.
I think you can be
even better than him.
You don't see it, but I do.
You're the real Trickster, Boo-Boo.
What's gotten into you?
Okay, I didn't take my meds.
Mom!
You did that for me?
I would do anything for you, Boo-Boo.
Would you kill with me?
It's like riding a tricycle.
You never forget.
Let's paint the town red.
I know whose blood we should use.
We just need a new trick
to strong-arm Stretch Armstrong.
- No.
- No?
What we need is something better.
Because if there is one thing
I've realized,
it's behind every great trick
is an even better Prank.
Hey, guys.
Any luck finding Trickster?
Joe, geo-tracking is an art form.
It takes precision, it takes finesse,
it takes grace.
It requires none of those things.
Simply the fact that
he's not a meta-human.
Regular humans are harder to track.
Is there anything
you can't suck the fun out of?
Leaf peeping.
Trickster.
Hello again, Central City.
It's time for
the exciting new game show,
"Wheel of Misfortune."
With prizes so amazing,
you'll think you died.
And if you play your cards right,
you just might.
Here's your host,
the murderous matriarch,
Prank.
What do we have in store for tonight?
Well, we have chills, thrills
and plenty of kills.
These guys are
absolutely nuts.
So, why don't
we meet our first contestants?
Ta-da!
Ha-la!
They've got hostages.
Shocking prizes are in store.
But, Prank,
what about the grand prize?
Well, I'm so glad you asked.
Because we have an axid shower.
Oh, no.
Sorry, Mr. Beebo.
Oh...
Beebo loves getting clean.
Beebo has an owie...
- Cisco.
- Triangulating their signal.
We need a special VIP to come down
for our special show.
So, if you're watching,
Stretchy Man,
why don't you come on down
and spin the wheel?
You have one hour
or these nice people die.
There you are.
They're at the old Clarx Toys factory
in Lawrence Hills.
Tick tock, Stretchy Man.
Time's a-wasting.
So let's
spin that wheel!
I'm gonna have
C.C.P.D. create a perimeter
a few blocks away,
so they can't escape.
Harry, how are you coming with
the solvent for Trickster's axid?
Well, slowly. Very difficult
to neutralize a solvent
that hasn't existed until today.
- You got 59 minutes.
- All I need is 58.
Ralph, suit up.
Well, you wanted a new suit,
didn't you?
I even made it pocket-sized.
Is it axid-proof?
I can't do it, guys.
These people need our help.
Yeah. Sorry, but me getting melted,
that is a deal-breaker.
Were you only doing this
because you thought
you couldn't get hurt?
Yeah. Why the hell else
would I do this?
Ralph, last year, I thought
I was gonna die too.
But that didn't stop me.
Okay. Well, that's
the difference between us, then.
I'm not that strong
in the face of danger.
I'm out.
Psst, Barry.
Ralph, what are you doing here?
I'm breaking you out.
I mean, come on. You're a hero.
Slap on some tights, go be heroic.
Ralph, there are
cameras everywhere. Okay?
They would know within minutes
that I'd vanished.
So? A minute to us
is like hours to you.
Just vibrate through the walls,
go slap Trickster around
and you'll be back before
whatever passes
for dinner in this place.
- Trickster attacked again?
- Yeah.
He and his mommy want
to tussle with me,
but I have a rule
against fighting terrorists
with an Oedipus complex.
So, this looks like a job
for the F-L-A-S-H.
Sorry, why is this different?
You've done a good job
handling bad guys so far.
I got hurt.
Axel created some kind of acid that,
we're guessing,
can probably kill me.
I'm not ready to die.
Look, this job,
it has a way
of making you feel invincible.
But, every once in a while,
a little mortality check shows up.
I've been trying so hard
to ignore this feeling, but...
I'm not fearless like you are.
Ralph, I'm not fearless.
I mean, I wake up every day
in this cell
and feel like there's nothing
I can do to help anyone.
And, I mean, that terrifies me.
I used to be somebody who saved
and now I'm just Barry Allen,
inmate number 3562.
- So let me spring you.
- That's not my point.
Having the ability to help someone
but do nothing,
that is a far worse death
than anything
that Trickster has for you.
But rising above that fear
and saving those lives,
that's a greater life.
All right? So rise up.
I don't think it's a stretch for you.
- You really believe I can do that?
- Yes.
You just need to believe it yourself.
Hey, you know your way
out of here, right?
Yeah.
You got one hour.
Scans are reading some kind of
container on the roof. It looks new.
Galvanized steel. That's where
they're keeping the axid.
All right, I will neutralize it,
and you two guys,
you get the hostages out.
Oh...
We're gonna need the ice queen.
That's not how it works.
I can't just...
- Lexi LaRoche!
It's her childhood bully.
There's a lot of repressed anger
in there.
Let's go!
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
Thank you. Big Sir.
My dad saved your life in here,
didn't he?
That's why you helped me out.
How?
I had stomach pains for days.
Your dad found me,
figured my appendix
was about to burst.
Prison doctors are gone
for the night.
There's no way
they could've made it back in time.
But Doc Henry convinced Warden Wolfe
to do the surgery.
He operated and saved my life.
That's why you owed him.
Now we're even.
Big Sir.
Okay.
Remember, anything in here
that looks fun is probably lethal.
- Just like me.
- Nice. Okay.
Let's deliver these delivery people
to safety.
Or we could just leave them
and kill Trickster and Prank.
Remember that talk
about murdering your way
out of problems?
- Yeah, we don't do that.
- Yet.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Beebo hungry.
Beebo likes to play.
Beebo.
Tricked ya.
I'm guessing the plan didn't work.
Help!
Harry, it's a trap.
They've got Caitlin and Cisco.
- I'm on my way.
- No, you're not.
I am.
Then you're gonna need this.
Groovy.
Hey!
Leave him alone.
I told you you'd be sorry.
You won't get lucky twice.
Like father, like son, eh?
Harry,
are you on the roof yet?
Yes. And so is the axid.
All right.
You need to neutralize the axid.
We're running out of time.
Yeah. Thank you. I'm aware of that.
Oh-oh!
Well, we asked for one hero.
But now, we've got two.
It's time
for our showcase showdown.
So let's spin that wheel
and see what fun prize
awaits our new friends.
Harry?
Tell me you got it.
Don't got it.
Hurry up.
I haven't killed anyone in years.
A tie?
Hmm, I guess they die together.
Nice outfit.
Thanks. I've got a great tailor.
Now let everyone go, pranksters,
and no one gets hurt.
We thought you chickened out,
Stretchy Man.
Actually, I did.
See, I thought
I was pretty much invincible
until you
and your oversized water pistol
- put the fear of God in me.
- You're welcome.
And I was ready
to throw in the towel.
But then I visited a friend of mine.
And he helped me remember
that no one is fearless.
But real heroes,
they find a way
to rise above that fear
and make a difference anyway,
even if it kills them in the process.
So, this is me,
rising up,
hopefully without the dying part.
Now, let my friends go.
First of all, great speech.
So inspired. It melted my heart.
Thank you.
I worked on it on the way over.
Now let's melt yours.
Shoot him.
Oh! Boo-Boo!
I'd give up if I were you.
How about I melt
your friends instead?
Harry, now.
I don't got it.
Harry?
No!
Say goodbye to your little friends.
Harry!
It doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt!
I'm not dying.
Why am I not dying?
Because I got it.
Yes! Nice work, guys.
I'm gonna live! Whoo!
Don't even think about running.
- Anytime.
- Oh, yeah.
You got scissors anywhere?
You know what they say, Detective?
The family that slays together,
stays together.
- Yeah. In prison.
- Hey, come on.
You can't keep a Trickster
behind bars for long.
We'll see about that.
You were amazing.
Can we do it again in 10 to 15 years?
Boo-Boo, I'm gonna break us
out of here in two.
Get in the damn car.
Is it true that you took down
Trickster and Prank single-handedly?
How long
have you been a superhero?
Are you single?
Yes. About an hour. Oh, hell, yes.
Do you like shrimp?
No. But I'm sure the people
of Central City would love
to thank you, Stretchy Man.
That's not my name.
Then what should we call you?
I mean, you do stretch.
No, I don't stretch. I...
I contort.
I elasticize. I...
I elongate, man.
"The Elongated Man"?
It was just an expression.
It has a certain, je ne sais quoi to it.
I don't know.
- I like it, too.
- Well, I hate it.
Oh, maybe you should've let me
do the naming.
Exactly.
Don't worry. You'll get your chance.
There's no way this is gonna stick.
Probably gonna stick.
The Elongated Man?
Please. It's so literal.
You think Prince would have settled
for "Shorty Guitar Man"?
- Hey.
- No way. And like the Purple One,
I too need something that hints
at the true depth of my sexy nature.
- Like "The Flash"?
- Exactly.
He's a fast operator.
Gets the job done in seconds.
Or "Killer Frost."
What can I say?
When you got it, you got it.
You got it.
Hey, Joe.
Hmm?
What should I do?
Man, do whatever it takes
to keep this city safe.
Just like the rest of us.
I can live with that.
Guess I'll be looking out for you
a bit longer.
I didn't get involved
because I wanted a favor.
I just wanted to help.
Piece of advice. You want
to survive in here, find a friend.
Your father would be
very proud of you.
Thanks.
Did my dad call you Big Sir?
No.
He called me Dave.
Allen, you've got a visitor.
Well, whatever you said
to Ralph must've landed.
He risked his life to save Caitlin
and Cisco, thanks to you.
I just brought out
what was already inside him.
You seem to have that effect
on a lot of people.
What?
Just turns out being in here
isn't so different
from being out there.
Except we're not together.
And I can't touch you anymore.
Coffee? That's all I get
for being a hero?
What do you want, a cookie?
Don't mind if I do.
Come on, man.
The thing about wearing a mask is
no one even knows you're a good guy.
Them's the breaks, kid.
Aha! Yes. There's the delicious nectar.
Hey, thanks for getting this coffee,
by the way.
Who, me? I'm broke.
I didn't even bring my wallet
with me.
I don't even own a wallet.
- Are you serious?
- Allen always pays.
Oh, my God.
No worries.
The... Always pay it forward.
That's my motto, you know?
'Cause at any given moment, one of us
could need a helping hand.
Like now. You two total strangers,
you know, were short on cash
and then someone
just steps out of the blue
and helps out
in a totally random way. Am I right?
Uh-huh.
And, you know,
it's more than just karma.
It's the principle
of infinite consequence at work
in our lives.
And it's always expanding.
Creating positive sums
on an infinite basis.
Isn't that amazing?
Yes?
You know what's amazing?
- That shirt's pretty amazing.
- Yeah.
Thanks. Yeah. It's a classic.
Oregon Trail. I love this game.
Have a great day.
Okay.
A nice, beautiful girl
and Ralph Dibny doesn't offer her
a delicious crustacean buffet?
Mmm, I think she's too smart for me.
Self-awareness from Ralph Dibny?
I think there's hope for you yet.
That's a stretch.
Is that
where we freeze-frame?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::