Last season, on "The Flash."
Melt.
- Killer Frost...
- Is gone.
It says there's still another
cryogenic anomaly in my DNA.
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
Hang on.
See, right there.
Killer Frost, she was part of you.
Even then.
How is that possible?
To the newest member of Team Flash.
- Hi.
- Hey.
We need to talk.
- Who are you?
- I'm your daughter, Nora.
Sally's in a decaying orbit.
Okay, how do we stop something
that's going to send us
back into the Stone Age?
Barry, you've got to
destroy that satellite.
That satellite...
It wasn't just me who took it down.
There was another speedster.
Okay, let's back up.
My name is Nora West-Allen,
the fastest woman alive.
When I'm from, 30 years from now,
I'm the guardian of Central City.
I'm a speedster, just like my dad.
People call me XS.
Every day, I hope to live up
to the legacy of The Flash...
But I've still got a long way to go.
You're saying you're our daughter?
From the future?
Named Nora?
After your mother.
Anybody need a refill?
No? Just me?
Mm.
Cisco Ramon,
always cutting the tension with a joke.
You know our names?
Of course. I know all of you.
You're Caitlin Snow, Ralph Dibny,
Papa Joe, Mama Cecile.
Little Auntie Jenna.
She's so cute.
And Uncle Wally.
Uh, and your nickname is XS?
Clearly not my doing.
No, uh, it's a nickname
that you gave me when I was a kid, Mom.
"Mom"?
You said I did everything in excess.
Guess I've always been like that.
Overdoing things, getting
in way over my head.
Like, uh, recently.
This mistake that you made?
Big mistake.
Which was...
Helping you save the city
by destroying the STAR
Labs satellite last night.
You were the other speedster?
I just couldn't stop myself
from getting involved.
But something happened
when I did, because now,
I can't seem to go fast enough
to open up the Speed Force.
Par... pardon me.
Are we talking about
actual time travel here?
Do you just like, not pay any attention
when we have our briefings?
Y'all didn't teach
him about the Legends?
Look, nobody said
bubkes about time travel.
Shh, shh, shh. Oh!
Come on, Ralph. You're scaring the baby.
Yeah, you're scaring the baby.
No, no, she's not scared.
She just said she's hungry.
She said that she's... Joe!
I heard her!
I read her mind!
I might not be losing my powers!
Awesome.
I'm sorry.
I know how bizarre this must seem,
meeting your daughter from
the future as an adult.
But really, this wasn't my plan at all,
but I'm kind of stuck here now,
and you're the only
people who can help me.
So... anybody know what to do?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
This is so, so weird.
Yeah, I mean, I can't believe
that's our daughter up there.
- We have been lied to before.
- Barry.
Yellow lightning like yours,
purple lightning like mine?
I mean, it's... It's got to be her.
We're meeting our daughter
for the first time, Barry.
Yeah, well, look. If it is true, Nora
could say the wrong thing or
step on the wrong butterfly
and screw up the whole timeline.
I mean, she could Marty McFly
herself out of existence.
Mm, "Terminator 2," yeah.
No, that's "Back to
the"... It doesn't matter.
Look, we just need to be
responsible, all right?
I mean, I think we need to find
a way to send her home, fast.
Barry, don't you think
future us taught our daughter
how not to screw with the timeline?
Wow, this Speed Lab
sure is archaic, huh?
La-la-la-la-la, you don't know...
You know what, um...
Sorry, just... no future
talk, all right, please?
Right, I don't want
to wreck the timeline.
- Right.
- All right, Nora.
This is gonna link us
up with your biometrics.
Ow!
And this little scrunchy doohicky
is gonna analyze your
connection to the, um, uh...
- The Speed Force.
- The Speed Force. Thank you.
Great.
I'll be back in a... flash.
And what does it say?
A quick analysis of her DNA shows
patterns that are
similar to both of yours.
I knew it. She's our daughter.
What about her being stuck here?
Everything's normal.
She definitely has Speed
Force in her system.
She's just not going... fast enough
to, uh, open up a time portal, so.
How much champagne did you
have at Joe and Cecile's?
This is the first opportunity I have
to process my breakup with Gypsy, okay?
How was I supposed to know
that your future daughter
was gonna come show up
and crash my pity party?
How was I supposed to "ancipitate" that?
Crap, I was supposed to meet Singh
- at CCPD an hour ago.
- Okay.
Hey, Wally, can you do me a favor?
Can you take the sample to the Legends
to see if they have any insight?
And maybe, worst comes to worst,
we can take her home on the Waverider?
- Yeah, I got it.
- All right.
Okay, just... I'll hurry back.
Keep an eye on her.
New ID, keys to the lab.
You are officially reinstated
as our CSI tech, Allen.
Thanks, Captain.
Oh, one more thing.
We didn't fill your
position while you were away,
so there are a few cases
waiting for you in your lab.
Get to them fast as you can.
Welcome back, Allen.
"A few"?
- Ahh!
- What you working on?
- I don't...
- You are crazy behind.
Hey, so I thought you were
gonna stay at STAR Labs,
with, um... with your...
Iris... mom.
Your mom.
You know I'm a forensic scientist too?
CCU grad, just like you. 5.6 GPA.
I could help you get through this.
Oh, I don't know. I mean, it's...
So the fire marshal at this site says
crazing in the melted glass
suggests a liquid accelerant.
Mm, any petroleum-based
household product
could cause crazing.
Well, like floor wax, or
shag rugs, even balloons.
Yeah, the glass melts under the surface,
like ice cream in the
cracks of a waffle cone.
Oh, like when you get two scoops
of cookie dough ice
cream with extra sprinkles
at the Mason Family Ice Cream Shop in...
Happy Harbor, Rhode Island.
My parents used to take
me there when I was a kid.
It's my favorite dessert.
Mine too.
Hey, look, I'm sorry,
um, you're obviously
good at forensics, but
you shouldn't interfere.
I mean, people like us,
we need to be responsible.
Right! Uh, timeline.
The timeline, yeah.
All available units,
M-0-3 in progress, 10th and Neely.
M-0-3, that's a meta attack.
Yeah, my suit's all torn up.
I don't have anything to...
Direct from Cisco's back closet.
One first-edition red
emblem OG super suit.
Total fan favorite.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Uh, I'm... I'm gonna handle this.
You just... no, no, no.
Uh, you... stay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Seriously, please.
Now I'm gonna...
Going old-school today, Flash?
Yeah, it's a little tighter
than I remember, though.
Hey, uh, you might want to do something.
Now it's my turn, Flash.
Gridlock? Schway!
- What are you doing?
- No, no.
I just... I just wanted...
Nice.
Oh, grife. You're mad at me.
No, Nora, we're not. We're just...
Please don't say "disappointed."
That's so much worse.
I mean, I just didn't
think it was a big deal.
It was only Gridlock.
Oh, Gridlock, huh?
Boy, the future's got some great names.
This lighting!
How did you know who he is?
Flash Museum.
Did you say...
- "Flash Museum"?
- Yeah.
It has all the villains and
battles in chronological order.
I've studied everything.
So you know this guy's real name?
Mr. Myles, the curator,
he scrubbed all the
names for legal reasons.
But it really shouldn't matter.
I mean, Gridlock was a one-and-done.
You guys beat him in one try,
or at least... you were supposed to.
Ugh, now, because of
me, he's on the run,
and the timeline's all
messed up again, and I...
Nora, hey, look, look.
I've made way bigger mistakes
than this time traveling.
We'll get this guy... you don't
need to worry about that...
But the longer you stay here,
the more things might change.
We need to get you home.
But I can't go fast enough to get home.
What about the tachyon
absorption enhancer?
The one that Thawne used
to increase his speed?
Ooh, and if we charge it up,
we could uh, boost the
Speed Force in her cells,
like some kind of, um...
thing that boosts Speed Force in cells.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a good idea.
Let's... okay, finding Gridlock
and getting Nora home
need to be our priorities.
No, no, no. Stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait. Loud!
Okay, so... but this
needs to be our priority.
Now, I realize that
you're all way ahead of me
in this time-travel business, but guys,
I think I just discovered something.
So if... if Nora can time travel,
that means she can create
new timelines, right?
New timelines means that
parallel timelines can exist.
So, guys, I think that a whole
other universe could exist.
I know, I know, I know.
It sounds crazy, but think about it.
There could be an Earth
where we're all bad guys,
or another Earth where
there's no world hunger,
or... or another Earth where...
Where they never made that
last "Indiana Jones" movie.
Think of the possibilities.
It's like some kind of a manyverse.
And everybody knows about the manyverse.
Multiverse, and so do you, Ralph.
Breacher? Gypsy? Harry?
What did you think we meant when we said
Harry was from Earth-2?
That he is from Earth "also."
Oh, my God.
You guys really need to make,
like, a welcome pamphlet,
or at least a Powerpoint or something.
Hey, Ralph, buddy?
Can we get off time
travel, maybe, please?
Let's focus on finding
Gridlock, all right?
Thank you.
I'm gonna go to CCPD,
see what I can dig up.
Okay, I'll stay with Nora.
- Let's just make sure...
- I know.
Protect the timeline.
You thirsty?
Okay, latte for me, and
a decaf Flash for you.
Wow.
Dad's lightning bolt is way
cooler than Lightning Lad's.
And do you think he's
gonna be back soon?
Well, you know your dad.
Whenever there's a problem,
he's gotta run off and fix it.
But, you know,
this gives us a chance to connect.
You're not worried about
messing things up, like he is?
I... well, I just, I...
want to get to know you a little.
How about this?
I will ask you questions
about your life, and if I'm right,
you just blink twice.
I mean, blinking never
broke the timeline, right?
Okay, yeah, I mean,
if you really want to.
Yeah, I think it'll be really fun.
Okay, um, so let's see.
You are a reporter for a newspaper
that you can only read on Instagram.
Um, okay, you... you are a cop.
You're a... a CSI?
You're a CSI.
Just like your dad.
Okay, well, what about you and I?
Do we... do we, like,
have dinner every Sunday?
Do we talk on the phone?
Do we still get coffee at Jitters?
- Uh...
- Was that a blink?
Uh, no, I just... I
have something in my eye.
You know, a coffee in my
time at Jitters is $43 a cup.
- Wow.
- That's one thing
I really like about now.
2018 is way schway.
- "Schway"?
- Oh.
Yeah, I guess it's a future thing.
Oh... oh, no. Oh, "schway."
No, I know, I'm hip. I
know what schway means.
Like, I'm schway, you're schway.
We're... we're schway, baby.
Stupid.
Do you think maybe Caitlin
and Cisco need any help?
I can't believe I'm wearing
the same tachyon enhancer
my dad used to meet
Supergirl for the first time.
All set.
Wait, what happened
to the second version?
The smaller one that
was inside the emblem
of my dad's second suit?
Um, if he wore that one,
he could harness tachyons
and share them with me.
Hey, fangirl, relax.
We know.
Did all these suits shrink?
And why does it smell so bad?
Because it's the one you used
when you swam against King Shark.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Flash!
Zoom wants you dead!
Yeah, yeah.
I know King Shark is
technically a bad guy,
but you should see... Just wait.
- When he fights Grodd, it's...
- Um!
Spoiler alert.
We should get going, actually, let's...
Right.
Then this is goodbye.
From your guys' perspectives, at least.
I'll see you again in
a minute and 27 seconds,
but when you see me
again, I'll be a baby.
Get home safe, Nora.
I'm sorry
we didn't get to spend
more time together.
Oh, it's fine, Mom.
We spend our whole lives together.
All right.
Did they already leave?
Yeah, why? What's up?
We have to stop them.
I'm sorry I was too late.
It took me a while to find
where the Legends were.
Well, when they were.
But we got their Gideon
to scan Nora's blood sample.
- What'd she find?
- Negative tachyons.
Negative tachyons?
So, what, instead of speeding
you up, they slow you down?
Yeah.
Oh, damn, I was just joking.
That's a real thing?
Yeah, Ava and her
team at the Time Bureau
have encountered them
before, but no one knows
where they come from or
how they're generated.
Like dark matter for
the space time continuum.
Exactly, and they're
saturating Nora's body
and keeping her from
entering the Speed Force.
What about the Waverider?
Can the Legends take her back?
If negative tachyons come anywhere near
the Rider's time drives,
uh, the reaction will vaporize the ship.
Well, there's got to be a
way to get rid of them, right?
I mean, I don't know
about getting rid of them,
but maybe we can offset
the tachyon absorption enhancer
to negate the reaction somehow.
- A new meta was last seen...
- Hey, guys.
Jumping off a building in order to
evade capture after stealing...
How did we miss this?
I guess this is a
parting gift from DeVoe.
Without our STAR Labs
satellite, we've lost
our eyes, our ears,
our dark matter scanner,
our facial recognition...
I mean, we're always
gonna be one step
behind these metas now.
I'll work on this.
Why don't you guys go help Ralph
with the Gridlock crime scene, okay?
Uh, I can come help.
Please, no, just... we just
can't let this get any worse, all right?
Just relax, okay?
How's your investigation going?
Uh, it just doesn't really add up.
I mean, if Eddie wanted to
erase Thawne from existence,
why didn't he just have a vasectomy?
Right, uh, nobody's talking.
Probably because they're afraid
Gridlock will attack them.
Right, but maybe if I had
Killer Frost at my side,
people would be a little more willing
to tell us what they know.
Ralph, Killer Frost has been gone
since the night that
DeVoe took over your body.
Jeez Louise, no one tells me anything.
- Is she gone for good?
- I hope not.
But I've tried everything I can think of
to get her to reappear.
You don't have any other leads?
Cisco vibed me back to when
Killer Frost and I were younger.
You've been a meta since you were a kid?
- I guess so.
- How?
- I have no idea.
- Did you see anything else?
- Just that my dad was there.
- Well, that's something.
Except my dad's been dead for years.
But none of this matters right now.
We have much more pressing
things to deal with.
Hey, come look at this.
I present Gridlock.
A mystery in three acts.
Please note the dark matter levels.
Act One, Gridlock attacks the
cops before Barry shows up.
Okay, but these dark matter levels
are perfectly normal
for a man of his size.
Until Act Two.
He gets lightning punched by Barry.
His dark matter levels increased.
Which brings us to our
third and final act...
Gridlock hits back.
Even higher.
How... how is that possible?
It isn't, unless every
time Gridlock got hit,
his cells absorbed the kinetic energy.
That would increase his
dark matter quotient,
thereby increasing his powers.
If this is true, then whatever
movement he's exposed to...
The stronger he's gonna get.
So, if Gridlock keeps moving,
he becomes unstoppable.
So, figure it out yet?
Whatever these negative tachyons are,
it feels a lot more like science fiction
than actual science.
I wasn't asking about the science.
I was asking about the scientist.
You and Nora, you guys have
such a strong connection.
I mean, it's... it's effortless.
So why are you so intent
on sending her back?
I mean, what do you mean?
First of all, she can't stop
talking about the future.
But... I mean, you know the
danger that her being here
poses to the timeline.
Yeah, I do, but I also know you, Barry.
Look.
You're the guy that went back in time
- to borrow Snart before he died.
- I know.
You're also the same guy
that travelled to 2020
to figure out who Savitar was,
and 2015 to train with Wells.
You changed fate to save my life.
So, now that our daughter
is here in front of us,
asking for our help,
you expect me to believe
that you're worried about the timeline?
Nora shouldn't be here.
Look, I'm...
- I've always wanted a family.
- I know.
You know, and when we got married,
I knew that one day, we'd
decide to have a baby.
We would try, and you'd get pregnant.
I'd be there for the sonogram,
I'd hear her first heartbeat,
and then she'd come.
And we'd take her home,
see her first smile,
her first tooth, the
first time I read to her.
Her first steps. The first time she ran.
But her being here
now, don't you feel like
we missed all those firsts?
That we skipped all the good stuff?
Baby, we will still
have all of those firsts.
Just not in that order.
But my whole life's been out of order.
These powers, time travel...
That's the reason my mom was killed,
why I grew up with my dad in prison.
They missed so many firsts.
They missed our wedding.
I know.
I don't know, I just thought
that when it was our turn
to have a kid, that life would let us
have this one little
thing the normal way.
Just once.
But we lost that chance.
No, we're not losing anything
by having her here now.
We're only gaining
something extra, Barry.
And look, if we figure this out,
I mean, by the time we do have a baby,
we are gonna be the best parents ever.
- Maybe you're right.
- I know I'm right.
You're gonna be there to put
that quarter under her pillow,
and you're gonna be there
to drive her to her first day of school,
to cheer on her first run.
And we are gonna have
all of those firsts.
I promise.
And think about it.
We have a kid who defied
the laws of physics
to hang out with her parents.
I mean, that's pretty...
That's pretty schway.
Yeah, as eager as she is,
you'd think that she's the one
that grew up with a parent in...
What's wrong?
Nothing. Um, nothing.
I'm... I'm gonna be right back.
Nora.
Um...
What happens to me in the future?
You said that you spend your
whole life with your mom,
but you didn't say the same for me.
My poker face is that bad, huh?
I need to know.
_
How long?
You never come back.
How old were you when it happened?
I was born, um, a few
years before you vanished,
but I don't have any memories of you.
So the wedding was...
Was pretty much the
first time I met you.
I'd imagined so many
different things to say to you.
Still can't believe I went
with "Remember to say 'I do.'"
I guess things don't always
go the way you plan them.
You're not stuck here, are you?
I found it in the museum archive.
Negative tachyons, harnessed on demand.
Really should work on
that poker face, I guess.
This didn't have to be a secret.
Why did you keep this from us?
Because if you knew I
could have gone home,
you would have sent me back
the second I walked
into Grandpa's house.
I mean, it's like you said, Dad.
Speedsters have to be responsible.
But... but I'm not responsible, am I?
I'm... just selfish
and really, really bad
at being a speedster.
Nora, you're not bad.
I mean, I can do some
cool things, you know?
Sometimes, I run so fast,
I reverse time a bit,
but I can't do the things you can.
I don't even know how to phase yet.
Guess there's only so much
you can learn from a museum.
What about your mom?
Yeah, I... she's around, you know?
It's just, uh... Just me and her.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I know.
I shouldn't have lied.
I just wanted to see you so badly
and spend a day with you.
Go for a run for the
first time together.
I missed all your firsts.
I was so worried about
screwing up your childhood
and screwing up our family, but...
I'm not even there.
Barry, we need you in the Cortex.
It's about Gridlock.
- I...
- I'm fine. Um...
you need to go fix my mess,
and then I can go home.
I scanned the crime scene
photos and got a match.
This is not Lang's first rodeo.
CCPD put out a warrant
for him for carjacking.
He killed the whole crew inside.
And now he absorbs kinetic energy?
He only gets stronger if you punch him,
you shoot him, you
throw him into traffic.
Which could only make the traffic worse.
God, I'd hate to be
stuck in that gridlock.
Gridlock... Gridlock...
I came up with the name.
I am fortune's fool.
So how do we find this guy
without Sally the satellite?
We don't need a satellite
to hack a cell phone.
And if we want to find his
cell phone, we'll find it...
By the airport?
Got it, 'cause he's on a
plane that just took off.
Central City Air, flight number 5201.
Why would he get on a plane?
Because he's gonna crash it.
We are currently cruising at 34,000 feet.
We anticipate a smooth landing,
so sit back and enjoy...
Excuse me, sir.
If you could please fasten your seatbelt
until we reach cruising altitude
and the captain turns
off the seatbelt sign.
Are you gonna buckle that thing in too?
Well, it must be something priceless
to get its own seat.
Jewels, maybe.
The plane just lost an engine.
It's headed for downtown.
If Gridlock takes out the other engine,
the pilot won't be able
to avoid the buildings.
Thousands of people will die.
Not if you phase the plane
through the buildings.
I read about you doing the same thing
to a plane in the future when
you were fighting Mob Rule.
Can you two do that?
A plane?
No... I mean, no, I don't think so.
I mean, I think it's too big.
The three of us.
I mean, the three of us
might be able to do it.
Well, I can't phase anything.
I can't even phase myself,
let alone at G-Force.
Wait, G-For... G-Force, that's it.
The plane is still ascending.
Once he blows up the other engine,
it's gonna slow down and point downwards
before it starts its descent.
That'll give us about ten seconds
- of zero Gs on the plane.
- Yeah.
And zero Gs means no kinetic energy,
means Gridlock has no powers.
Can you breach them onto the plane?
A plane goes way too fast.
I'd need to see it in person.
- Then go.
- But I don't have a suit.
I actually have a backup.
I got more than just a list
of metas from that museum.
Damn, Gina. I made that?
Uh, Ryan Choi, actually.
Oh, this is a supersuit.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Guys, he just took out the other engine.
You can do this.
Uh, don't drink and vibe.
I feel like I'm gonna hurl.
It's slowing.
Guys, you've got ten seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Okay, everybody stay calm, all right?
Just stay calm.
All right, come on.
Hey, take a wall, all right?
We got this.
Barry, hurry.
- It's not working.
- What?
I can't do this.
All right, yes... Listen
to me, just breathe.
Feel the floor beneath your feet.
Feel the rumble of the plane.
Feel the air.
Feel that wind on your face,
- and the lightning.
- And the lightning.
Feel its electricity
pumping through your veins,
traveling to every nerve in your body
like a shock you never want to end.
- You are no longer you now.
- You're no longer you.
You're part of something greater.
Part of the Speed Force.
That's right.
All right, it's ours.
Now, let's do it.
Everybody hold on!
Hold on!
Are you okay?
Nice.
You phased.
For the first time!
Well, Gridlock's off to
Iron Heights' meta wing.
Where he won't be moving
from for a very long time.
Thanks to your help.
I'm glad we got to team up.
Me too.
Ladies and gentleman,
say hello to the tachyon
absorption enhancer 2.5,
now complete with
completely recalibrated
Time Bureau technology.
We haven't tested it yet,
but it should counterbalance
the negative tachyons in Nora's cells.
Here you go, Billy Pilgrim.
Consider yourself unstuck in time.
So I can run home now?
Or...
maybe we hit pause on this thing.
You want Nora to stay?
Um, yeah, I thought
getting her home was our priority.
No, it is, I just...
Now, I'm thinking that
maybe we should make sure
her powers are working correctly
before we send her home.
And what about the timeline?
It's risky, but I don't know.
I mean, Wally and I
were talking about it.
Yeah, the Legends have a theory.
Uh, there are some historical
events that are soft.
Basically, you change those,
it's not going to affect much else,
like catching Gridlock late.
And then, there are
those that are fixed.
You mess with them, and
all sorts of craziness
starts to happen.
Like the night my mom died.
Changing that created Flashpoint.
It looks like Nora is
gonna need a place to stay.
Uh, yes, and I'll stay in the lounge.
What lounge?
This lounge.
Ah.
- Damn.
- Dad.
- You found my spot.
- You knew about this?
I've been napping in here since day one.
Uh, well, Nora was gonna stay here,
if that's all right with you.
Okay, well, now I can get
to know my granddaughter.
Mm.
I'm sorry, you met Elvis?
Met him?
Uncle Wally fought the
ghost of his twin brother.
I, uh... I went to a monastery,
and I was trying to find myself,
but I was really close.
Then, the Legends came,
they swooped me up,
and life got even more crazy.
You want to go back, don't you?
I can't. I mean, I just got here.
I don't want to leave the
team. I don't want to leave you.
Wally, everybody in this
room loves you, especially me.
But you didn't finish
what you set out to do,
and nobody's gonna get in your way.
So promise me, when you
find what you're looking for,
come back, or you're gonna have
a very angry-looking
dad in your zen garden.
Will you take care of him, XS?
You got it, Kid Flash.
Hmm.
You okay?
Yeah.
I thought I missed out on my
chance to connect with Nora,
but now that she's
staying, I get another shot.
If you could have
seen her on that plane,
you'd know that you guys
are already connected.
Really?
She was fearless, just like you.
- We have a daughter together.
- Yeah.
We make a person.
In the end, everything works out.
We get our happy ending.
Hey.
If Barry can go back in time,
why didn't he stop the
Thinker from killing me?
Kidding, I'm kidding.
Guys, I'm kidding.
I realize that could have upset
the delicate balance of the universe.
Besides, if he did that, who knows?
He might have created a timeline where
I died in that particle
accelerator explosion.
Wishful thinking.
Kidding. I'm glad you're here,
and I'm glad that we don't
have to hold your hand
through the time travel
thing, you're figuring it out.
Yeah, well, time travel's
not the only mystery I solved.
While you guys were fighting Gridlock,
I was, uh, running this down.
- What's this?
- An answer.
And a lot more questions.
It's my father's death certificate.
A friend at county
helped me out with that.
The ME who signed off
on it, Cameron Mahkent?
He doesn't exist.
So then, this death certificate...
Is a fake.
You should get some rest.
You've had a long day.
Ooh, I'll try.
I'm just so excited. Like, literally.
Phasing excited all of the
electron clouds in my body.
Well, if you're not tired,
two scoops of cookie dough
ice cream sound good right now.
From Happy Harbor?
If that's okay with you.
It is, yeah.
Just, uh, bring me back some mint chip.
My name is Nora West Allen,
and I'm the fastest woman alive.
When I was a child,
my father disappeared
in something impossible.
Then I grew up and
became the impossible.
Now I'm trying to live up
to the legacy he created
so that one day, I'll stop
him from ever disappearing.
I'm XS.
How schway is that?
CCPD! Stay where you are.
Freeze, don't move.
Who the hell are you?
Wh... what do you want?
For all of you to die.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --