My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Barry, what you're seeing
is the Speed Force.
Your past, your present, your future.
- Say, Iris, you look amazing.
- Thanks, Tony.
His skin changed. lt turned to metal.
Tony might have been a bully,
but he didn't deserve to die.
Barry, you've always had
someone to come home to.
I can't help but wonder, maybe,
we were meant to be together.
- You lost your powers?
- I gave them up to save Wally.
I can recreate the circumstances
to get you your speed back.
Let's set off the Particle Accelerator.
Barry, he's gone.
This wasn't...
I didn't...
I'm so sorry.
We lost him.
No, no, no.
He could've gotten knocked somewhere,
or maybe even run there.
Nothing on the GPS.
There were strikes all over the building.
Jesse, come down here please.
Jesse? Wally?
Oh, God! Wally! No.
No!
- Wally, wake up! Can you hear me?
- No!
- Wally!
- Jesse, Jesse. Jesse!
- Jesse!
Stop yelling, please.
Her heart's stopped. Her heart stopped.
- Jesse...
- Are you okay?
Jesse!
It's beating, her heart's beating.
Henry's a doctor. He should see her.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Hey, what's with him?
It's Barry.
Barry's gone.
Are you good, Wally?
Okay, we should get you home,
get some rest. Okay?
- Wait, I don't understand...
- No, it's okay, let's go.
Jesse.
Henry, Wells' daughter is upstairs.
The energy hit her, too.
Her heart stopped beating. Henry!
All right.
I saw him. I saw Barry.
He's alive.
Joe?
Good to see you, Barry.
But I'm not Joe.
- You're not?
- No.
And all of this.
It's not real?
How do you feel, being back here?
I feel awful.
We thought you'd be more comfortable
talking to someone who looked familiar,
and in a place you knew.
We?
Who is we exactly?
That's a little hard to explain.
Sit, Barry.
Sit.
How much do you know
about the Speed Force?
It's the source of my power.
- It's what makes me a speedster.
- Yes.
And no.
When the first sub-atomic particle
sprang forth from the Big Bang
to form reality as you know it,
we were there.
When the last proton decays,
stops vibrating and
plunges the universe into heat death,
we'll be there, too.
I'm talking to the Speed Force?
Isn't that like saying I'm having a
conversation with gravity, or light, or...
You need a minute?
It's okay if you do,
it's a, a lot to take in.
So, you're saying, I'm talking
to the source of my power,
which just so happens to look like...
My adoptive dad?
That's trippy.
We pretty much invented trippy here.
Look, I'm not sure why you
brought me here,
but you need to send me back.
My friends are in danger from Zoom.
Did you see that?
You're not going back.
Not until...
Until what?
Until you catch that.
Cisco says Barry is still alive.
Where is he?
- I don't know.
- Harry, I vibed him.
In the center of a storm.
He was in, like, a vortex or something.
He's in...
- He's in the Speed Force.
- Get him out, damn it.
- You can get him out, can't you?
- I don't know if I can.
Henry, come here.
Listen, you are the only one
that can help Jesse.
Let me sit on Wells until he figures out
what the hell he did to Barry
- and we can get him back.
- Joe, I know you love Barry.
Okay? But you have Iris
and you have Wally.
Barry's all I have left.
I promise, we'll find him.
Thank God, you're here.
Caitlin's usually the one
doing this, but...
Heart rate's normal,
reflexes and breathing are fine.
She should be waking up.
She's just not.
It was the same with Barry.
Um...
After the first accident, he was in a coma
that no one could explain.
What did you do with him?
So they brought him here.
Well, Wells brought him here.
The other Wells.
Right, the Wells who was actually Thawne.
- Eobard, not Eddie.
- Right.
It's, it's complicated.
Anyway, we took care of Barry
while Wells, Thawne treated him.
Are there any records of that treatment?
We might find clues how to help Jesse.
Uh, yeah, they'd be downstairs
in the storage room, in the morgue.
Ew! You guys have a morgue?
Well, it's not like a "morgue" morgue.
It's not like...
It's like a poor man's
morgue, really. Morgue-ish.
Would both of you go get them? Please.
Okay. Well, I'm not going alone.
Thank you.
Okay, so it's a morgue-morgue.
But, you know, we had to keep the
dead meta-humans somewhere.
Yeah, looks like you did a lot more
than just store them.
Fake Wells might've done a few
dissections for study purposes.
And this didn't tip any of you off
that he might be secretly evil?
It was a crazy time, okay?
We had a lot going on.
I'll tell you what, it's a good thing
Thawne was so organized.
Would you stop knocking stuff over?
Would you stop,
I didn't touch anything.
Okay, whatever you say.
Okay, this is it. This is Barry's X-files.
A zombie? For real?
- Tony?
- Nope, not Tony, not anymore.
- Get behind me.
- You get behind me.
Tony.
- Didn't see that one coming.
- Zombie Girder. This...
Iris.
We're glad you made it, Barry.
Not Iris.
It's just you again.
Sit, Barry. Sit.
You're always on your feet.
You remember this place?
Where we first kissed?
Yeah, of course, except that wasn't you.
We thought you'd find this place
and our appearance less upsetting.
Yet, you seem upset.
My friends, my city,
my whole world is in danger.
Zoom is on a rampage with the power
that he stole from me
and you are keeping me here.
You were given a rare and precious gift
and you rejected it.
No, I did not reject it.
I gave up my powers to save
someone's life, to be a hero.
I nearly killed myself
trying to get them back
when you brought me here.
Wherever here is.
- That's not what we meant.
- Okay.
If you would rather have given
these powers to somebody else,
why did you give them to me?
Because you're The Flash, Barry.
We got a new problem.
Our accelerator experiment seems to have
reanimated one of the dead metas
in our morgue.
Reanimated? Like, brought back to life?
Life-ish. You ever seen The Walking Dead?
It's The Walking Dead
but without higher brain function
and with major rage issues.
Still unsure if our brains
are on the menu, though.
- Which one?
- Tony Woodward.
The bully from school
who turned into the metal man?
That's not good, Cisco.
"History repeats itself, first as tragedy,
and then as farce."
Wells, as a parent, believe me,
I have nothing but sympathy
for what you're going through.
Listen to me closely when I say to you,
we got a lot of fires
burning at the same time,
and if we all work together
we just might be able to put them out.
Let Henry take care of your daughter.
Me and Iris will handle
this Girder situation.
But you and Cisco are the scientists.
You're the only one
who can bring Barry back
from wherever the hell he is right now.
Ramon.
Give those medical records to Henry
and meet me in the Breach Room
in five minutes.
We've got work to do.
Now we just need to find Tony.
Yeah, hopefully, before he kills someone.
Come on.
Big Belly Burger in Starling City
is way better.
This place sucks.
- Oh, my God! ls that your car?
- Oh, yeah.
That's my mom's car!
So how do we know
that this is safe?
Well, define safe.
Safe. As in, my brain's not gonna melt.
No, it's a simple feedback loop, Ramon...
All right? When you vibe on Barry,
your brainwaves send me the necessary data
to pinpoint whatever dimensional pocket
or corner of the universe
that Barry is stuck in.
And then we electrically stimulate
your prefrontal cortex
while opening a breach
which gives you physical access to Barry
and let you be the beacon
to guide him home. Simple feedback loop.
I'm sorry, did you say,
"Electrically stimulate"?
Ramon, do you want to
bring Barry back or not?
Okay-
And we have a lock.
I don't understand.
If I'm The Flash, then why are you
doing this to me?
Why do I have to catch this thing
before you let me go back?
Please, look, I will do whatever you want,
just let me go back right now
so I can help my friends.
Barry!
Barry, turn around!
What is that?
Those are your friends.
They want you to come back.
Can I?
Of course.
But if you do,
it'll be without your powers.
Take my hand!
Do it, take my hand!
The choice is yours, Barry.
Barry!
What is going on in here?
Just hang on a little longer,
Ramon, a little longer.
Hey, you're killing him.
Cisco.
Hey, Cisco, can you hear me?
Yeah. lsaw him.
Barry, he turned to me...
I'm sorry. I lost him.
No.
Whoa, Cisco's meta-human
alert app is going crazy.
Oh, Tonyjust trashed
the hell out of Jitters.
Now, that is strange.
He knocks over a hydrant
on Fourth and Stevenson,
doesn't go in the building.
Then smashes a Humvee
in front of the Big Belly Burger
but doesn't go in the building.
Gets to CC Jitters, he actually goes in.
Yeah, it's like Jitters was his target.
But why?
When I was in Iron Heights awaiting trial,
I had a cellmate who always swore
he was gonna break out.
At a pre-trial hearing
he stole a deputy's gun
and escaped in a police cruiser.
- There's a point to this, Joe, I promise.
- Mmm-hmm.
Now, the poor, dumb bastard
could have gone anywhere, right?
But he was apprehended two hours later.
Do you know why?
'Cause he went to his
old girlfriend's house looking for her.
So you think that's what Tony's doing?
Even in the state he's in now?
Ithink people
are creatures of habit.
Sometimes at a level stronger
than conscious thought.
No, ldon'tthinkthat
Tony had a girlfriend.
I mean, not the way that he was
hitting on me when he...
He came in to Jitters.
- Huh.
- He's after me. Again.
So, when he was after you
the first time,
where'd you see him next? After Jitters.
Home.
He came to our house when he took you.
Wally's there now.
No, no, Dad. This is good.
We know where he is
and we know what he wants.
That means we know how to beat him.
How do you propose we do that?
We use me as bait to lure him
back to S.T.A.R. Labs
where Cisco and Wells can kill him.
Again.
Mmm-mmm. Mmm-mmm.
Who're you pretending to be now?
I don't have time for this.
Yes, you do, Barry.
You have all the time in the universe.
- Literally.
- No, I don't.
And how can you stand there in judgment
and accuse me of rejecting my gift?
D0 you have any idea how much I've done
since I was first struck by lightning?
How many people I've helped
with the power that you gave me?
What I've sacrificed?
Of course, we do.
You've saved countless lives.
And now you are the only thing
standing in between
your world and unspeakable evil.
And yet, for all of that,
you've never been here.
I can't believe he's coming here.
- Oh, Wally, thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Wait.
I've been meaning to ask you, uh...
How are you feeling?
Uh, tired, but fine, I guess.
So, you don't notice anything different?
Uh, no.
I mean, I want you to know that you can
come talk to me if you're scared,
or you have questions about
how your body is changing...
Oh...
I think you're a little late
forthe puberty talk, Dad.
I've seen the Internet.
Looks like I'm going to have to do this
the old fashioned way.
Are you okay?
Wally, go upstairs.
Please, go upstairs now.
Dad, do you really think
that he's a meta-human?
Well, he got zapped by the
Particle Accelerator
and he was unconscious.
It was worth a shot.
I gave you that mug.
He's coming.
- You sure about this?
- You know what?
Two minutes ago I would've said,
"Yes, absolutely."
But now? What the hell.
Tony! Hey!
Come on, over here.
- You getting towards S.T.A.R. Labs?
- On my way.
I'll meet you there.
Wally, stay here, I'll be right back!
Why did you bring me here?
Your mother's death
happened to you, Barry.
It made you who you are
but have you accepted it?
Really accepted losing her?
Maybe that's why you couldn't come here.
Because that would make it real.
I know it's real.
Every day I know it.
I had a chance to save her.
You saw what I chose.
And you're at peace with that decision?
At peace.
How could someone ever be at peace
with letting his mother die?
With deciding that his life
was more valuable than hers?
Do you really think your mother
would have wanted you to die for her?
Anol all the people The Flash saved
as a result of that decision.
What about them?
Do their lives have value, too?
I don't have to listen to this.
I have to get home.
- Cisco.
- Is iZombie still behind you?
Good news is...
- We lured Tony back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Yeah.
Bad news is we lured Tony back
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
No, no, no, this is good.
Okay, uh, side note,
you both might wanna be
on this side of the room,
especially if you're wearing any jewelry
or you have any metal plates in your body?
- Huh?
- Excuse me?
The stray energy from the Accelerator
reactivated Girder's brain,
well, parts of it, anyway.
So, I disassembled our MRI machine
to set up these electromagnets.
So, when Girder walks through that door,
and gets caught in the field
that they generate,
it should disrupt the energy wave
that turned him Abby Normal.
- Like wiping a hard drive.
- Rah-kah-tah!
Okay, now I can only maintain full power
for a few seconds,
so I can't actually turn this on
until he's in the room.
There he is. Hi.
Why don't it look like it's working?
Because it's not.
Uh, let's get out of here?
This is the safest place for her, for now.
- Well, not safe enough.
- Plans A through G did not work.
Do we have anything in here
that can stop him?
Barry could stop him,
ifwe could bring him back.
- We tried that already, Dr. Allen.
- We need to try it again.
Somebody needs to try something,
that door's not gonna hold.
Mom?
Hi, Barry.
You're not my mother.
Why are you doing this to me?
We're not doing anything
to you, sweetheart.
You're just so tired.
Sit, Barry. Sit.
You were right all along,
I haven't accepted it.
Not for a second.
I don't think I ever will.
My beautiful boy.
You have to find a way.
- How?
- I don't know.
But I know this.
What you've become?
It's wonderful...
A miracle, even.
But it won't make bad things
stop happening to you.
Even The Flash can't outrun the tragedies
the universe is gonna keep
sending your way.
You have to accept that.
And then you can truly run free.
I know.
I just miss her.
I miss you so much.
What if I told you that
she's proud of you...
And of the man that you've become?
Who's telling me that?
The Speed Force or my mother?
Both.
Is there any other way out of here?
No, the Breach Room
was designed to be sealed off.
All right, look, if it's me that he wants,
- I'll just lead him away.
- No, you won't.
You'll never even make it past that door.
If he came back from the dead
and still wants you,
what makes you think
he's gonna let you go now?
Wait.
I saw Barry, he had this look.
What if we couldn't get him
out of the Speed Force
because he didn't wanna come back?
Do you remember this book?
It was always your favorite.
"Once, there was a little dinosaur
called a Maiasaur
"who lived with his mother.
"One day he told his mother,
"'l wish I were special
like the other dinosaurs.
"'If I were a T-Rex, I could chomp
with my ferocious teeth."'
"'But if you were a T-Rex, '
said his mother,"
"'How would you hug me
with your tiny little arms?'"
"'I wish I were an Apatosaurus, '
said the little dinosaur,
"'so with my long neck
I could see high above the treetops."'
"'But if you were an Apatosaurus, '
said his mother,"
"'How would you hear me in the treetops
when I told you I love you?"
"'What makes you so special,
little Maiasaur?' said his mother,
"'Is it your ferocious teeth,
"'or long neck, or pointy beak."
"'What makes you special"
"'is out of all of the different dinosaurs
in the big wide world,"
"'you have the mother
who is just right for you."
- "'And who will always love you."'
- "'Love you."'
You're ready.
Turn it on.
We got to try again.
- Any of you got a better idea?
- When you look into the Speed Force,
can someone else see into it, too?
Well, as long as you're in
physical contact with Ramon
while he's vibing, then, yes.
Let me do that.
I can get Barry to come back.
No.
Let me do it. Please?
Iris...
Barry.
Barry, come home to me.
Run, Barry, run.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Barry.
I am so glad you're back
'cause we're about to die.
Wait, what?
So...
- Girder...
- Girder came back to life
and he's all Young Frankenstein now
and he only recognizes Iris
and she lured him to my workshop
so we could demagnetize him
but the machine shorted out
so he's about to come through that door
and smoosh us all into chunky salsa
and possibly eat our brains.
- I don't know, thejury's still 0ut...
- All right, I got it. Uh...
I will lure him to your workshop
and we figure out a way
to turn the power back on, okay?
Plan H.
Hey, Tony!
- He's taking him the long way.
- Come on.
I hope you're ready, he's almost here.
- Nope, not ready.
- No.
Power needs of these two electromagnets,
too much for this wiring to handle.
We're gonna need a really big
extension cord.
All right, I'll see what I can do.
Barry!
Tony.
Tony, look,
you were never my favorite person...
But let's end this,
so you can finally rest.
- He's using spin to charge the magnets.
- Like an electric turbine.
Sorry, I got lost.
It's okay. We found you.
Barry.
You should rest,
you don't need to be here.
No, that's just it. I think I do.
Hey.
How did I get here?
How did you do that?
Are you, like, magic now?
Did you know that was gonna happen?
Maybe. It's hard to explain. It's...
It's the Speed Force.
It's been quite a day, huh?
Not so much "one damn thing after another"
as "every damn thing all at once."
It all worked out okay in the end.
No, you worked it out okay in the end.
It's funny,
I never really understood
where you were coming from
with your whole fate
and "everything happens for a reason"
point of view.
But now...
I think that maybe I was wrong.
Everything that's happened to us,
good and bad, it made us who we are.
And I don't think that I would change it,
even if I could.
- Does that make any sense?
- Perfect sense.
And since we're on the subject
of changing our minds
about important things...
You know that part where I told you
I was gonna leave Central City
so that you could be The Flash without
being concerned about me all the time?
Well, forget all that.
You're stuck with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
Joe offered to take me, so many times.
I always found an excuse to say no.
My mom and I read this when I was little.
- Do you know it?
- Yeah.
I never really liked that book.
Why?
Because it was about a mother
who was always there for her child,
no matter what.
And that wasn't my mom.
Or yours.
We never had anyone who was
just right for us.
Didn't we?
I'm seeing things a lot differently now.
I wasted so much time
Being angry about what I had lost
when I had so much.
My dad,
Joe,
and you.
The truth is, Iris, that I don't know
what this is between us.
Or where we go from here.
All I know is
you're everything to me
and you always have been.
And the sound of your voice
will always bring me home.
- Cait, please.
- I asked you not to call me that.
Caitlin.
We've been through this again and again,
and we've gotten nowhere.
Now I need to know,
are you with me or are you against me?
Don't answer that yet.
I'm gonna go out there,
spend a moment speaking to my friends,
and when I come back
you'll give me your answer.
If you're still here,
I'll know you've chosen to stay with me.
But if you're not here,
I'll know you've chosen
your friends instead.
And I will show you exactly as much mercy
as I will show them
when we next see each other.
So, there you have it.
I need to go.
My brothers and sisters.
My friends.
I've brought us to this new world,
which lay before us defenseless,
ours for the taking.
The humans think
that this planet belongs to them.
- Whose world is this?
- Our world!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::