My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multi-verse,
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't
as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on
The Flash...
I got hit with the dark matter.
That must've affected me somehow.
We're going home.
I went back in time
and created an alternate timeline.
Wally?
Wally? Can you hear me?
My name is Edward Clariss.
Rivals should know each other's names.
When I came back,
things weren't the same.
I don't trust you.
And I don't like things
that I don't trust.
You'll always be Barry.
And I'll always be Iris.
And we always find each other.
- Who are you?
- I am Alchemy.
- Alchemy?
- You failed, Clariss.
Remember that feeling you got as a kid
when you were so excited about something
that you couldn't focus on anything else?
That's me right now.
Thinking about,
well, what I always think about.
Allen! Enough with the knee.
- Uh, where are you going?
- I'm going on a date.
Well, not yet you're not.
You know,
you're not actually my boss, Julian.
Well, I am the senior lab tech.
And the last time I checked,
the hours were 10:00 a.m. till 7:00 p.m.
Not 6:58, not 6:59, but...
Remember that other feeling you got
when that thing you were excited about
seemed to take forever to arrive?
Imagine being a speedster.
Days seem like weeks.
Hours seem like days.
And seconds seem like...
You get the point.
7:00.
I'll see you tomorrow.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
It's too much? Yeah, it's too much.
It's the heart, right?
It's too cheesy. All right, hold on.
Is that better? That's... It's worse?
We'll go back to the heart.
No, Barr, wait. Wait, wait.
It is so beautiful. And you are so sweet.
But tonight, I wanna be with you.
Barry Allen, not the Flash.
- So...
- So no Flash talk, no speed.
No problem. All right.
Starting now,
the Flash is officially off-limits.
So... Wow.
Um...
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
Are you planning on donating
a kidney sometime in the near future or...
"A kidney?"
This place is...
Don't look at the prices.
Just get whatever you want.
So...
Um, yeah, so...
How was work?
Um, yeah, super busy.
How about you?
Uh, well, Julian had me write up
a carbon dating report,
then a DNA sequencing report.
A couple of chemical compound reports,
so he pretty much just gives me
all the work he doesn't wanna do, so...
- Yeah, I know. It's really boring.
- No, no. I'm so sorry, Barry.
I'm just... It's been a really long day.
Yeah, I know. Me, too.
Uh, what's going on?
Apparently, a robbery's in progress
across the street. Excuse me.
Go. Go, go.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. Yeah. Use your speed. Go.
Okay.
Um, where were we?
Um...
It's Cisco.
We should go.
Yeah.
- What's going on?
- That.
- Yeah, Why'd you open a breach?
- I didn't.
- What?
- That's why we called you.
Well, can you close it?
Once again,
wouldn't have called if I could.
All right. Somebody's coming through.
Get back.
Allen.
Wells.
I need your help.
With what?
- With that.
- Hey, guys.
Jesse. You're a speedster.
Yeah. It's pretty cool, right?
I mean, yeah. I would say so.
When did this happen?
A few days ago.
So when I got Allen his speed back,
Wally and Jesse were hit
with the dark matter.
Turns out she was affected.
She was totally affected.
But I didn't get speed,
so could it have been from something else?
No. I mean, I doubt it.
Dark matter affects different people
in different ways at different times.
Sometimes not at all.
So be thankful, but she was affected,
and I wanna run some tests
and find out just how much.
Well, then you've come to the right place.
Let's go to the Speed Lab.
- "Speed Lab?"
This is insane.
Something tells me
you've never been in this room before.
Nope.
Wait, you've, you... Allen.
I suppose that means
you traveled back in time again.
Yeah, but I...
How many times did I tell you
not to do that?
Oh, you figured that out
pretty quickly, Harry.
Yes, Miss West, it was easy
because we've never been here either.
Nope.
Right. Other Earth, other timeline.
Yes. Exactly. So when did you do it?
After we returned to Earth-2?
Look, Harry, I...
Only a couple of things are different.
Oh, I'm sure. Not.
Really? You guys are doing "not"
on Earth-2 now?
Uh, no. That's all him.
Okay. Let's just get Jesse
on the track and see what she can do.
Yeah. Let's do it.
All right, check this out.
Damn. She really can move.
Yeah, she can.
Um, I gotta go.
Wally... Oh, man.
I'll talk to him.
Hey, Joe.
Um...
Look it's just,
it is better if he doesn't have speed.
Oh, you don't have to convince me of that.
Last thing I want is
two of my kids zipping around the city,
running into danger.
'Cause he looked pretty disappointed.
This is about
that other timeline, isn't it?
No, I just...
I think you should keep an eye on him.
Honey, I'm home.
Hi, Charlie, how was your day?
Oh, it's so wonderful to see you.
- Where's dinner?
- It's almost ready, John.
- What're we having tonight?
- Pot-roast it's your favorite!
I work hard every day
to provide for this family
and this is what greets me now,
an empty table?
- Just five more minutes.
- I'm hungry now!
And you speak when you're
spoken to, girl, you understand me?
I saved you from the orphanage
and I provide for you every day.
So keep your mouth shut, Frankie,
you got it?
Sorry, John. Frankie's gone.
Hey-
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
I was trying to get some information
about the man who was attacked
by a lamp post last night.
Hey, um, just come here for a second.
So, uh, last night, I know our first date
didn't shatter any records...
- I mean it wasn't that bad.
- It was...
Okay, yeah it wasn't that great either.
- It was just kind of...
- Boring?
Boring, yeah.
Which feels like my fault.
Maybe I'm boring without my powers.
No, Barry, you are perfect
without your powers.
Thanks, but I mean,
what do you think it is then?
You don't think it's a sign
that we shouldn't...
No!
- I...
- Okay. Good, I mean, 'cause I do.
I wanna try this again
as soon as possible.
But just with everything that's going on,
- this new case and...
- Yeah.
- Wells and Jesse showing up and I...
No, Barr, I totally get it.
I get it, I should probably concentrate
on making my deadlines anyway. So...
Cool.
- Okay. Okay, yeah. Yeah, work.
- All right. Well, I'm gonna work now.
Cool.
- Yeah, all right. I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
- No, I was... Yeah. Okay.
- Yeah, of course. Yeah, all right.
So this says you were in the room
when your father...
Foster father, John.
Right. Foster father.
You were in the room when he was struck
by the street lamp post
that flew into the apartment?
Yeah.
But I don't remember any of that.
Um...
He came home and yelled at Karen,
my foster mom, to get him dinner.
Mmm.
Is that when you blacked out?
Yeah, I think so.
Has that happened before?
You blacking out?
Is John gonna be okay?
He's in Central City Hospital. I...
He's pretty banged up.
Frankie, can you excuse me for a second?
- Yeah, of course.
- Thank you.
- Barr.
- Yeah.
What'd you find out?
Okay, get this. So, the outer layer
of the lamp post is a half an inch thick.
But to bend even a quarter inch of steel
requires 177 tons
of tensile strength. So...
So, we're looking for a meta
with super-strength?
Well, I'm not sure yet.
But that's as much as I could find.
What? Why?
- Because I showed up.
- Yeah.
Yes. The only problem
with Barry's little theory
is there were no fingerprints
found on the post.
Again, Julian, not my theory.
And the meta could have been
wearing gloves.
Yes, perhaps.
But the curvature on the post suggests
that equal amounts of pressure
were applied to the whole thing
at the same time.
So, unless our strong man
has a wingspan of over 20 feet...
Something else caused it.
Yes.
Who's that, sir?
That's Frankie Kane,
the victim's foster kid.
That poor girl's been
in and out of homes for years.
Listen, she said that
she blacked out during the incident.
- "Blacked out?"
- Yeah.
Repressing memories is a coping mechanism
for lots of foster kids.
- Hmm? Is it?
- It is.
Could be something else.
What are you...
- Hello, there.
- Hi.
You okay?
Yeah.
Can I get you some more water?
Yes, thank you.
Sure.
Gonna need another glass, detective.
- Follow him.
- Mmm-hmm.
- See what you can get.
- What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna finish this up
and convince my son that
he's not meant to be a superhero.
Good idea.
So, how'd I do?
Blood pressure, heart rate,
metabolic rate, all excellent,
- and you've got some serious speed, girl.
- Mmm-hmm.
I think you're good to go.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I just still want to run a few more tests.
- Like what?
- Like more tests.
- Uh, hey so, is Wally here?
- No, not yet.
Right. Mmm.
Okay, I'm gonna go grab some food.
I'm starving.
Yeah. There's some power-bars
in the workshop. Help yourself.
Cool.
- Harry?
- Mmm-hmm.
- What are you doing?
- Being thorough.
Yeah? 'Cause it seems like
you're stalling.
Okay, fine. I'm stalling, I'm stalling.
So what?
So what, so why?
"So why?" Why?
Why, I gotta explain myself to you two?
Oh, I guess I do
'cause you're not parents.
That's my daughter, okay?
And she spent months on this very Earth,
watching Barry Allen defeat meta
after meta after meta, and Zoom.
Then all of a sudden, bam!
She's got speed and now
she wants to be a hero just like him.
And I think that's a great idea...
Not.
Harry, we can help her.
We can train her just like we did
- with Barry.
- I don't want you to train her.
Okay? I brought her here
for you to talk her out of it.
Not talk her into it.
All right, Ramon?
You should talk to her. You're a meta.
Yeah. Which makes me the last person
she should talk to about
not using her powers.
Okay, Snow, Caitlin...
You and her, you've always had
such a special relationship.
You talk to her.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah.
And I don't know anything
about having powers,
so I'm the last person you should talk to
so don't ask me.
But...
Dad.
What's going on? Why'd you want to see me?
Oh, hey.
Uh, have a seat.
Look, I know
it's been really hard for you.
Seeing Jesse with speed and...
I just keep thinking of what Harry said.
How sometimes it takes a while
for powers to manifest.
Yeah. Harry also said
that they may never manifest.
Yes. But I got hit by that
dark matter, too, just like Jesse.
It could still happen for me somehow.
Look, you weren't here when
the first particle accelerator exploded.
That dark matter went
throughout the whole city.
Everybody got hit.
Me, your sister, this whole precinct.
Do you know how many metas
there have been so far?
I know you want this more than anything.
But you have to face the fact
that it might not happen.
So you think just let it go?
Give up on wanting to help people?
You don't need powers to do that.
Look, Barry was coming to the rescue
as a CSI long before he was the Flash.
He wanted to help people then
just like you want to help people now.
So he studied,
he honed that brilliant mind of his.
And you have the same
brilliant mind, Wall.
- Dad...
- No, I mean it, son.
Look, a lot of people dream about
making the world a better place.
With that mind of yours
and that engineering talent,
you literally could build a better world.
So what? I gotta stay in school?
Yeah, you gotta stay in school.
Just a couple more years.
What are you doing?
I assumed you'd taken
a DNA sample before.
Okay. Yes, I know what you're doing.
I mean, why are you doing it?
What, you're looking
to steal another sample?
I've isolated an element consistent
in all five of the husks that we've found.
Including Edward Clariss'.
You mean the Rival?
Mmm-hmm, that's what the papers
are calling him, yes.
What's the element?
I don't know.
But it's not one
that I've found in any other
meta-human samples that I've studied.
So you think that Frankie,
the girl downstairs,
has the same element in her DNA?
Well, I wouldn't be comparing samples
if it wasn't a possibility,
would I, Allen?
It's a good thing for both of us I did.
- What?
- Come on.
What?
- Calm down, okay?
- Where is she?
- Julian...
- You, you girl, stop!
- Hey, ease up, Julian.
- Stop!
- You did it, didn't you?
- Me? What?
The lamp post. You did it, didn't you?
What? No, no, no, stop!
- You're a liar.
- Julian!
- You're a meta-human.
- Stop, no. Stop!
You put your foster father
in the hospital, didn't you?
- No, no. No.
- Didn't you?
Didn't you?
Oh, I wanted to do more than hurt him.
And, now, I'm gonna do the same to you.
Frankie! Frankie, stop!
You okay?
Frankie!
No. Frankie's gone.
My name is Magenta.
You're like this because of Alchemy.
He changed you, didn't he?
This isn't you.
Just come with me.
Tell me what happened.
I can help you.
I don't need any more help, Flash.
I just don't want anyone to get hurt.
It's too late for that.
Frankie, don't!
It's me or him!
Come on.
Her name's Frankie Kane.
But she's calling herself Magenta.
- Meh.
- And Magenta is a whole different person
than the scared, kind girl
I was interviewing.
- She's dissociative.
- You mean split-personality.
According to her medical records,
it's a condition she's been dealing with
her entire life.
I'm sure all the yelling at C.C.P.D.
is what triggered it.
So Frankie is Jekyll, Magenta is Hyde.
Classic, good versus evil.
- Or she's pulling a Primal Fear.
- She's faking it.
No, she's not faking it.
I saw the struggle going on inside of her.
Magenta's trying to take over completely.
You said she was raised
in the foster care system?
Yep. All her life.
She went from home to home.
Yeah, and maybe not good ones.
Her current foster father, John,
the one who was hurt in the attack?
Yeah, he's got a few disorderly conducts.
He might have some information we can use.
I can follow up with him.
Mmm-hmm. There is something else.
She got her powers from Alchemy.
When I said his name, she knew who he was.
So Magenta must have existed
in the other timeline, too.
Who's Alchemy?
Well, uh, Doctor Alchemy
is a magic man in a cloak
who can somehow restore the powers
that people had in Flashpoint.
Okay, and what's Flashpoint?
That's what we're calling the alternate
timeline that Barry created
when he went back in time
and saved his mom.
Oh, so Magenta is another
side effect from your time trip.
Genius... Not.
Um, I don't need to be reminded.
Thank you.
Look, anybody with those powers
and as angry as her
needs to be tracked down, fast.
Well, great. I mean, fast I can do.
Let me just go carb-load.
He didn't... That's... You don't...
Snow.
Please.
Okay, Harry. I'll talk to her.
But I don't know what I'm gonna say.
Hey, Joe, did you talk to Wally?
He still seems a little bummed.
It's not gonna fix itself overnight,
but it's all good. He gets it.
- Okay.
- And I gotta be honest,
it was one of my better
"Dad-Cop" speeches.
What's "Dad-Cop?"
There's good cop, bad cop, and "Dad-Cop."
Firm but reassuring. Cuts to the point.
I don't think I know that one.
Yeah, I didn't use it on you.
Wally's different than you, Barry.
You're like a second daughter.
You overshare your feelings.
Him I gotta be a little bit more nuanced.
Huh? Cool.
I'm messing with you.
I'll talk at you if I get
any leads on Frankie, all right?
All right.
Second daughter, what is he talking about?
Hey, hey.
Hey, sorry, um...
You guys were not kidding when you
said speedsters were hungry all the time.
Yeah.
Listen, Jesse,
before you speed off to find Frankie,
I just wanna make sure
that you feel like you're ready?
Why? I mean, is something wrong?
I mean,
did the test results say something?
No, not at all. All the test results
have come back fine so far.
It's just, maybe you should take it slow?
Right. This is because I'm a girl.
What? No, not at all. Why?
Well, I mean,
Barry didn't have to take things slow.
You know, he was stopping criminals
the second he got his powers.
Why can't I do the same thing?
Well, I mean, I'm sure you think
that it's a great thing to have powers,
but sometimes it's not so great, trust me.
I'm just saying that if I had powers,
I would probably take it slow.
My dad put you up to this, didn't he?
Yeah, I mean, of course he did.
Jesse, uh...
Hey, you don't want me
to have this speed, do you?
I mean, that's why we're here, right?
Not so you could test me,
but so you could get everyone
to talk me out of using my powers.
- I just want you to be...
- To be safe. Yeah.
Yeah, I know,
I've heard it my entire life.
This is different. This is way different.
Yeah, no, it is.
- Because I'm not Barry, right?
- Right.
You're not Barry.
Let me talk to her this time.
She's still here.
I can feel Frankie trying
to stay in control.
You said I could beat her.
What I said was,
"I'd return to you the power you had
to inflict your pain upon others."
But I need Frankie gone to do that.
Do you remember why you came to me?
I came to you,
because you showed me a way
to stop him from hurting me.
Show him Magenta is in control.
And once you've done that,
Frankie will know it as well.
Here you are.
Hey.
Hey, so, where did you go yesterday?
Well, I didn't want to
interrupt your training.
Right, yeah, well, looks like
there won't be much of that anymore
now that my dad is getting everyone
to talk me out of using my powers.
Wait, that...
That's not why you're here, right?
No, no. This is all me.
You all right?
Uh, you know, when this whole thing
happened to me, you were...
You were actually the first person
I wanted to call.
I was sort of hoping
it happened to you, too.
Uh, I dreamt about it. Believe me.
How did this all happen?
I mean, it was... It was crazy.
So like, one day,
I was walking home from a friend's house,
and this car, it ran a red light,
and, you know,
it was speeding right at me.
And I just stood there, frozen.
You know, basically waiting to be hit.
And then I looked around,
and everything around me was frozen, too.
And it was peaceful and quiet,
but I felt this, like,
electricity running in me.
And, so, I ran out of the way.
Like, I kept running and running
and I mean, now I don't ever want to stop.
So you basically
just jumpstarted your powers.
I mean, I guess so, yeah, why?
It's good to know.
Wally!
What are you doing?
Getting my speed! Why would you do that?
To save your life?
- It could've worked, Jesse...
- No! Okay, look,
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
Seriously, what the hell
were you thinking?
You can't just go
stepping into the street like that!
I mean, you gotta use your head.
Nothing happened, Barry. Chill out.
- Didn't you talk to Joe about this?
- Yeah, so?
So, it clearly didn't help.
I mean, what would you have done
if Jesse wasn't there, huh?
I don't know, man.
Because there's nothing
you could have done.
Because you don't have powers.
Only room in our family
for one speedster, Barry?
Please just stop trying,
before you get yourself killed.
You done?
- Do you have anything to say?
- No, you pretty much covered it.
- This has got to stop!
- Stop yelling at me, okay?
I saved his life,
what did you want me to do?
That's not the point,
that is not the point.
I know the point.
You don't want me to use my powers.
- Right, yeah.
- Fine!
Fine, but I don't need to stay here
and listen to this anymore.
No, Jesse, Jesse! Don't...
What did you say to her?
Me?
Yeah, you.
Don't blame me for this. I tried to help.
Help her? Or help me?
Listen, Harry,
maybe the reason she's shutting you out
is because you're not trying to
understand what she's going through.
- But I don't need to...
- Maybe if you helped her
navigate her powers rather than
just assuming they'll destroy her,
she'd turn to you
rather than push you away.
Can't even bring myself to
take a lap around this thing.
- Why is that?
- I don't know, I mean, you said it.
Everything's different here.
There's a guy creating meta-humans,
innocent people,
because I changed the timeline.
It's on me.
Yeah, well, I think I know a thing or two
about what that feels like.
Yeah, I keep making mistakes.
I make mistakes and then
I want to make up for my mistakes,
then I just make more mistakes.
The next thing I know, I have a daughter
that won't even speak to me.
How do we keep from messing things up,
when all we want to do is help?
I don't know.
But you did once tell me that,
"You have to trust that in the long run,"
"the decisions you make
are the right ones."
Yeah.
I was always too good
at forgiving myself, Allen.
You were never good enough.
John James?
Who's asking?
Hi, I'm Iris West.
I'm a reporter for
Central City Picture News.
I wanted to ask you a couple questions
about Frankie Kane.
They find her yet?
I don't believe so, no.
What the hell's taking so long?
That damn meta-human freak
nearly killed me.
I know. I'm sorry.
That's what I get for taking
Frankie in, huh? This?
God help me if I ever see her again.
What does that mean?
It means that
she's gonna be the one in the hospital.
Tough love, John?
Yeah, you're damn right.
She was getting back at you
for hurting her.
And she's gonna try it again.
Nurse!
We need to get this man
to a safe location.
Why?
What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
- Where are you taking me?
- Frankie is coming for you.
And as much as it pains me
to help an abusive dick like you,
I can't let you die.
What kind of alarm is that?
That's Iris' panic button.
- Her what?
- Her panic button.
We installed them on everyone's phones?
'Cause we kept getting kidnapped?
Well, at least something's an
improvement in this timeline.
- That's the hospital.
- Frankie's foster father's there.
Yeah, and Iris went to see him.
Looks like she's not the only one.
- Is that a tanker?
- That's a tanker, yeah.
She is gonna kill him
and everyone else in there.
- I gotta go.
- What are you gonna do?
You don't have super strength.
Start thinking.
Guys...
There's not enough time to get everybody
out of the hospital.
This thing's coming down.
Barry, Iris is still in there.
What if... What if I create a wind funnel?
You won't be creating enough updraft
to keep that tanker up.
No, no, not, not with my arms. If I run.
- That could...
- Propeller.
That could work.
Barry, run in a figure-eight fashion.
It'll act like a propeller.
The wind will build upon itself,
it'll create the supersonic resistance
we need.
- Could work.
- All right.
Bye-bye, Daddy.
Flash!
Okay, well that worked. But now what?
He can't stop her if he's up there.
Cisco's right.
Go help him.
- Dad...
- You need to get out there, now.
Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
I know you can do it.
You're more than fast enough.
Now run, Jesse.
Run.
Hey, thought you could use a little help.
I got this, you go take care of her.
Magenta.
I got a little help.
So I could help you.
Okay, killing your foster father
and everyone else inside that hospital
isn't gonna give you what you need.
You have no idea what I need!
It's not just John
that I want to get rid of.
I want them both gone.
Barry, you got to stop her now,
that tanker's coming down.
I know you're still in there, Frankie.
Don't let John destroy the good
that's still inside you.
He said I was weak, that I was pathetic.
He said I was a horrible person.
He's just blaming you for all the
bad things he's caused in his life.
It's not your fault.
This isn't because of you.
I just want him to stop hurting me.
This isn't the way.
Your foster father never forgave himself
for his mistakes.
That's why he took them out on you.
He couldn't face who he really is,
he couldn't move forward.
But you can.
They did it.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
It's okay, it's gonna be okay.
So no one else got hurt?
Luckily, no.
You don't have to worry about that.
What about John?
The DA is prosecuting him
for what he did to you.
So I think he's gonna be serving time,
and he's not gonna ever be
anybody's foster father again.
It's just so strange being responsible
for all of this
and not remember any of it.
What do you remember?
About how you got your powers?
How this all began?
Um...
I started having dreams
at night of Magenta.
Dreams?
Well, they were more than dreams.
I don't know, it was like
I was living another life or something.
And then I started getting them
all the time, during the day...
And the more it happened,
the more painful they became.
Then I started hearing a voice.
What voice?
It was a man named Alchemy.
He said he could give me what I wanted
and make me powerful again.
But I didn't understand,
I thought I was going crazy.
Trust me, Magenta is not here
because of anything that you did.
There may be a darkness inside of you,
but if you face it,
it'll make it easier
for the good side of you to win.
You're letting me go?
None of this is your fault, Frankie.
Caitlin found you a good home in Keystone.
People that will never hurt you.
But what if Magenta tries to come back?
Fight her.
And if you need help, we'll be there.
We have faith in you, Frankie.
Thank you.
Thank you, all.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I, um,
I just feel bad for her. You know?
You sure?
Yeah.
No "Dad-Cop" required.
- You heard about that, huh?
- Yeah, I heard about that.
Hey-
There she is.
You were tremendous out there.
You really were.
I guess that's your first victory
as a superhero.
My daughter.
Jesse Quick.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I mean, I was only able to
do it 'cause you believed in me. So...
Uh-uh.
I should have been that way
a long, long time ago.
But I...
You know, one day, you'll understand.
I don't expect you to now, but...
I'm always gonna worry.
I'm always going to be cautious.
I'm always going to love you.
Dad, I know. I mean, of course I know.
And I will always love you.
Even when you drive me absolutely insane.
So...
Are we going home or...
I think we'll stay here a few more days,
run a few more tests,
and also to see if this fits you.
Cisco did the insignia,
and Snow thought
this would help you, and I agree.
- You do?
- I do.
My...
My fear,
my guilt has kept both of us back
for far too long.
You know, you've always been my hero.
But now,
it's time for me to let you
be one for everyone else.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey, just made it?
Yeah, I had to make sure Frankie was okay.
So, you're ready to try this again?
Um, actually, I had a thought about
why our last date was so boring.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, um...
Here you go.
Um, so, I know that you think
that I shouldn't use my powers.
And it's not that
I'm nothing without them,
but they are a part of me now, you know?
They're a part of you.
This is our life and I think last date,
we were ignoring that part of us.
We were trying to be the people
that we were before I was the Flash.
And that's why it wasn't working.
Okay, so, what are you saying?
I'm saying we have to stop denying
who we really are.
Uh, well, yeah, I mean,
when you put it that way.
I agree.
We can't pretend like
none of this has happened.
- I thought you'd see it that way.
- Mmm.
Sorry.
It's Joe. He needs me at the station.
It's fine, go.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah. This has already been
a really amazing date, Flash.
- Hey, what's goin' on?
- There you are.
Listen, Singh wanted me
to show you guys this.
This happened a few days ago
at Iron Heights.
They tried to keep it under wraps,
'cause they didn't want anybody to think
there was a security issue,
but check it out.
- That's Clariss.
- Alchemy?
It was Clariss.
No, no!
Dead before he hit the ground.
Alchemy.
You ever heard that name before, Alchemy?
No, I haven't.
Maybe there's an invisible meta?
Maybe it's a ghost.
Do you believe in ghosts, Allen?
No?
Hey, do you think this thing is part
of the Flashpoint timeline, too?
I have a feeling a lot of things are
these days.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::