My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man who killed
my mother, but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Iris' mom is alive.
And you thought you could pay me
to walk away from my own daughter?
Last time you walked away for free.
When you created the Singularity,
you also created a breach.
A portal, connecting our two Earths.
You really think he's just
bringing these guys here to kill me?
Zoom was obsessed with destroying me.
Now he wants to destroy you?
I'm starting to perceive things.
Horrible things.
We have to merge
the inner and outer event horizons,
by separating in the eye of it.
No!
Ronnie died saving me and I...
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no. Get back! Come here!
Professor Stein, can you hear me?
Everyone secretly thinks
they've figured out
what their life is gonna be like.
But what no one ever considers is
that life has its own plans for you,
whether you like them or not.
And so you're left with a choice.
You can either embrace the change
and move forward.
Or fight it,
and be left behind.
Dude!
I knew you could do it!
That was some touchdown, man.
You won us the game.
Hey, nah, man.
We won us the game.
Hey, that's not what
the cheerleaders were saying.
Yeah? For real? All right.
Jefferson.
Great game.
Hey, thanks, coach.
I'm not the only one that noticed.
A lot of scouts in the stands tonight.
And after that touchdown,
they all pulled out their cell phones.
You're gonna get your pick
of colleges, son.
You really think so?
I know so.
You get home and celebrate with your mom.
Everybody, run!
Hey! Hey, come on, man. I got you!
We got to get inside the tunnel!
Hold him steady!
He's dropping out.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Cisco, we're losing him!
Got it!
Dios mio. Thank God.
He's getting worse.
Look, I did what I could
to re-engineer Dr. Wells' original
stabilizer to quell the reaction,
but I don't know what
he used as a power source.
Best I could find
was the one from his wheelchair.
And how long will that last?
Well, that's the problem is we had
already used up most of its energy
trying to dampen the metas' powers
during our little rogue air trip
with Weather Wizard and company.
I think we got a few days, tops.
And he's stuck in bed?
Yeah. When he wakes up,
I'm gonna transfer the stabilizer to this.
Give him a power cane.
Get him moving.
We got to figure out a way to save him.
I think I might know how to do that.
When the Particle Accelerator exploded,
the dark matter that collided
with Professor Stein
fused with the Firestorm matrix
and altered the normal molecular processes
that occurs within his body.
Those highly-reactive molecules
needed something to bond
with in order to stabilize.
And that's where Ronnie came in.
Yes, and now that Ronnie is no longer
a part of Professor Stein...
Those molecules don't have anything
to bond to.
And the longer he goes without merging,
the more unstable he becomes.
Oh.
All right, so what do we do?
Find another participant.
Okay, cool. So how do we do that?
Are we just gonna make a Tinder app
for potential meta-humans?
'Cause I'm pretty sure merging with Stein
and randomly bursting into flames
sounds like the biggest
swipe-left of all time.
Even if we could find someone willing,
Stein can't just merge
with whoever he wants.
No, he can't.
But I have done some research,
and I found two potential candidates
that might be compatible with him.
They both were affected
by the dark matter.
And they were both admitted
to the hospital
showing symptoms of gene
rearrangement mutation.
And they both share the same blood type
as Professor Stein and Ronnie.
All right.
This is more than organ donation.
We'll need more than tissue typing
to see if their bodies are compatible.
If I can isolate the genetic locus
of the two candidates
and cross-reference it
with the mutations in Professor Stein,
I might be able to find a match,
and save his life.
What do you need to do that?
All right. Blood samples
from both potential candidates.
Damn! That was fast even for you.
I may have skipped
the asking-for-permission part.
Let's see if we can't find a match.
You were two in that picture.
You just got some shots.
You were so mad at the nurse.
Kept saying, "She pinched me."
So we took you to the park
afterwards to cheer you up.
Gave you your first ice cream cone,
which was a mistake,
because all we heard the next month was
"Mimp-choplat chip, mimp-choplat chip."
Oh. That's where the obsession started.
Baby, you don't have to do this.
If you don't want to meet
your mother tomorrow,
I get it.
No, it's okay.
I want to meet her.
I need to meet her.
It's gonna be fine.
My brave, baby girl.
Take after you.
Love you!
Love you more.
Barry?
Hey! I was just looking for you.
I would've called
but I don't have your number yet, so...
- Oh, yeah. You...
- No, no, no.
Uh, I just wanted to show you this.
These werejust found in an alley
off of Eastwood Avenue.
What are these? Teeth?
Shark teeth.
And I have an eyewitness
that says he saw a shark,
walking on land. A...
A man-shark.
- Man-shark?
- Yeah.
Sounds like a bad sci-fi movie.
Or awesome sci-fi movie.
Totally.
Um... What, are you for real?
You think there's actually, like, a...
Yeah, I mean, I...
I know it sounds really wack-o,
but, I mean, nothing seems impossible
now that we have meta-humans, right?
And lthought it would be fun, you know,
for us to work together again. On a case.
Yeah, I know. I mean, I really...
I'd love to work on anything with you.
It's just, you know,
meta-humans aren't really my thing.
Oh. Okay, yeah. That's fine.
I can handle it.
No... You... Look, um,
how about I Just... I'll run a test.
See where the teeth came from.
- That would be amazing.
- All right.
- Cool. Yeah. For sure.
- Thanks.
Detective Spivot.
Detective.
- How's your man-shark case coming?
- Lt's good.
I was just gonna go and canvass the area,
see what else I can dig up.
And Barry, here, agreed to run
some tests for me.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
So, progress. Thanks again.
Mmm-hmm.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were flirting with my partner.
What? Patty? No, I'm...
No, what are you
talking about? I'm not.
What is it with you, and Iris,
and my partners?
Hey, how is Iris, by the way?
She's pretty nervous about seeing
her mother after all these years.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what? I got to go.
It's Cisco. It's about Professor Stein.
Okay, go. I'll cover you with Singh.
All right. Thanks.
Well, I must admit,
I never imagined
a Sphinx's riddle about a man requiring
three legs would ever apply to me,
but if this device keeps me mobile,
then I will gratefully oblige.
Well, hopefully you won't need it
for much longer.
There was no agglutination
in the blood samples,
and cross-matching was negative for both.
And it appears that the dark matter
from the Particle Accelerator explosion
mutated their genes
in a very similar way it did to yours.
- I think they're both potential matches.
- So, who do we go with?
Well, my first choice is Henry Hewitt.
He graduated summa cum laude
from Hudson University,
with a double major
in Applied Physics and Bioengineering.
A Hudson boy. I like him already.
Now, what about this other guy?
Jefferson Jackson?
High School quarterback. 4.0 student.
He's got the physical attributes.
And it looks like more of his alleles
match than Hewitt's.
Doesn't that mean
that he's more compatible?
On paper, perhaps.
But Hewitt is a scientist.
Clearly, he's trying
to make something of his life.
I think he'd be open
to something like this.
I think we should meet with both of them
before we make a decision.
- That's an excellent idea.
- I'll see if I can get Hewitt here.
All right. In the meantime,
we'll go meet with Jefferson Jackson.
And I will try to find something else
to help keep you stable.
Are you sure this is the right place?
Yeah. Jefferson's a mechanic.
Could indicate a strong
technical aptitude.
That's a positive.
Oh. Prone to allergies.
That's definitely a negative.
Not to mention his taste in music.
Would you prefer Celine Dion instead?
I got the Titanic soundtrack
in the back there.
- No, thank you.
- Jefferson Jackson, right?
- People call me Jax.
- Ooh. Catchy.
I... Well, my name is Barry Allen,
and this is Martin Stein.
We're with the Department of Safety.
It's a small, newly formed agency.
Very new. We probably
don't even have a website yet. Do we?
You need to see our licenses?
I mean, we're all up to code here.
No. No, nothing like that.
We are compiling data on people
who were affected by the Particle
Accelerator explosion two years ago.
Look, man, I lost enough time in my life
'cause of that stupid thing going wrong.
Now, you don't got a car I can fix,
I can't help you.
If you would consider coming back
to S.T.A.R. Labs with us,
I believe we can help you.
Help me, how?
Well, we know what
the Particle Accelerator did.
Look, I already told you,
I don't talk about that night.
Why is that?
Because that's when everything changed.
Look, lgot hit hard.
When I woke up, I was in the hospital.
Busted up leg, torn ACL.
The look on my mom's face.
I knew any dreams I had
of playing pro-ball were over.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah.
Well...
Look, I got to get back to work.
Yeah. Um...
Here, it's just...
It's our number.
Just think about it, okay?
Thank you for putting
this together, Joseph.
Iris' idea. Not mine.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi, Dad.
Iris.
This is Francine.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello, Iris.
Can I get you a coffee or something?
Um, no, thanks.
Let's just sit.
I can't get over what a beautiful,
young woman you've become.
And a journalist?
I'm so proud of you.
Why are you here?
Why now?
After two decades.
I want to make this right with you.
How about you start
by apologizing for walking out on us?
I am sorry.
So very, very sorry.
There's so much you don't know.
I'm sure that you've been through
a great deal.
And I can appreciate you feeling like
this is suddenly the right time
for you to want me in your life.
But that doesn't mean
that it's the right time for me.
- Iris?
- No, Dad, it's okay.
I've thought about this a lot.
And it wasn't fair
for me to make you the bad guy.
So, I want you to hear this from me.
I don't hate you, Francine.
I do wish you well.
But we have lived separate lives
for over 20 years.
Let's keep it that way.
I've always thought
my destiny was for greater things.
And people, of course.
Well, when it's all said and done,
flying will be the least impressive
of your new abilities.
Man finally achieves the promise
of the atomic age.
Caitlin? What's going on?
Hi, I'm glad you're back.
This is Dr. Henry Hewitt.
This is Barry Allen
and Professor Martin Stein.
- How do you do?
- The illustrious Martin Stein.
I've read all your papers back at Hudson,
especially on transmutation.
Fascinating.
You're a legend.
Oh, please. You're over estimating
my contribution to the field. I...
Isn't he great?
Yeah. He's got an ego the size of Texas,
but, yeah, he's all right.
So, where's Jefferson Jackson?
- We just need more time.
- We don't have more time.
I couldn't find another power source
for the cane.
And that thing's running out.
Okay. Then let's do the merge.
Hewitt's in.
What do you mean? You told him the details
of the Firestorm Matrix?
Absolutely. Becoming Firestorm
is a huge life change.
He needs to know
what he's getting himself into.
If I remember correctly,
vector, variance, hypotenuse...
- Proton, neutron, Go HU!
- Yes!
Look at that, that's so cute. We'll have
two Professor Steins if this works.
- It's gonna work.
- Yeah?
Okay.
When I put this splicer on your chest,
you're gonna feel a rush.
That's a molecular primer
being released into your body.
Then, you can make physical contact
with Professor Stein,
and Firestorm Matrix will take over.
Easy enough.
- Ready?
- No time like the present.
- Thank you, my dear.
- Okay.
Try again.
This is unexpected.
Something's supposed to be happening,
right?
- Why isn't it working?
- I don't know.
Well, looks like you two
aren't compatible after all.
I'm just gonna...
So, all this was for nothing.
Believe me.
No one is more disappointed than I am.
Yeah, don't be so sure about that.
Next time,
try to get your act together
before you get someone's hopes up.
Move the show-and-tell
to next Tuesday.
Remind me to call Richard tomorrow
about the shareholders meeting.
And where are we with the replacement
for Dr. Snow?
We...
Applied sciences?
Stop! Don't move!
Harrison?
Detective West.
Thank you for coming.
Dr. McGee, this is my new partner,
Detective Spivot.
It's nice to meet you.
I was saddened
by Detective Thawne's passing.
Please extend my condolences
to your daughter.
Thank you.
On the phone you mentioned
this was a sensitive matter.
It is. And I called you directly
because I've always appreciated
your discretion in the past.
Of course.
Can you tell me what was stolen?
It's not so much what was stolen,
but who stole it.
The person who broke into
my facility last night
was Harrison Wells.
Harrison Wells is dead.
I seem to recall the circumstances
around his passing
were a bit inconclusive.
Is there any possibility
he could be alive?
Zero possibility.
I knew the man for over 20 years.
I know who I saw.
The only thing distinctively different was
he's walking again.
Like I said, I trust your discretion.
You have full access to the facility.
Thank you again, Detective.
First a shark-man, now a dead man walking.
We need to call Barry,
get him in here first.
Barry can't hear about any of this.
What? Why?
Because he's got a lot on his plate.
He's got a friend who's sick,
who needs his help.
And Harrison Wells is the man
who murdered his mother.
Once he hears that...
- Is he okay?
- He's fine,
but not a word to him, or anyone. Okay?
Okay.
Yeah, it's just...
I'm not really good at lying.
Well, you better learn. Quick.
Yeah, definitely.
- Spivot, go on ahead.
- Sure.
This is the last time you ever
show up here. Do you understand?
I needed to talk to you again.
How much clearer do we need to be?
Iris and I do not want you in our lives.
Leave. Please.
Go home, live your life.
Joe, there's something else.
I wanted to tell you
when I first saw you, but...
What is it?
A few months ago,
I started getting weak.
The doctors ran a bunch of tests,
they couldn't figure it out.
But finally, they did.
Said I have something called MacGregor's.
Supposedly, it's pretty common
among ex-addicts.
Told me I had till the end of the year,
if I'm lucky.
Is... Is that why you came back?
I just want my daughter to know me.
This me.
I'm really glad
you decided to come.
I thought S.T.A.R. Labs had to shut down.
It's under new management.
Whoa, what kind of treadmill is that?
Cosmic.
Cool.
So, let's get started.
You got some kind of Billion-Dollar-Man
technology that's gonna fix my knee?
Actually, Jax,
this isn't about fixing your knee.
What are you talking about?
When the Particle Accelerator exploded,
the energy wave that collided with you
is known as dark matter.
And, it didn't just hurt your knee.
It changed the molecular structure
of your body.
Whoa, hold on, Grey.
So, you're saying I'm like
one of those meta-humans
I keep hearing about on the news?
Yes, I am. Please, call me Professor.
We think you have potential capabilities.
What kind of capabilities?
The same as Professor Stein.
The ability for your body
to process fission and fusion.
And you can harness excess energy
and turn it into these
massive nuclear blasts.
And you can fly. There's also that.
So you're saying you can do all this?
Only during times of convergence
with a willing partner.
Convergence? You and me?
Yes.
No. This is crazy.
Jax, this is your chance to right
the wrong that was done to you.
Yeah. Sorry, you got the wrong guy.
I don't want nothing to do with this.
Wait a second. We are giving you
the chance to be a superhero,
and you're going to say no that quickly?
Yeah. Not my kind of thing.
If the man isn't willing to participate...
Look, I saw your test scores, Jax.
Your grades were good enough
to get into college, but you didn't go.
Why?
Is this the type of guy you are?
One setback and you fold?
Well then, maybe you're not
the guy for us anyway.
Well, maybe I'm not.
Jack...
Maybe, this just wasn't meant to be.
Caitlin, what do you... I mean,
Jax could be our last chance
at saving Professor Stein.
He said "no" to being a superhero.
Who does that?
I mean, you didn't say no
when you had the chance.
- Cisco, would you?
- Chance to have superpowers?
Sign me up.
Look, we're asking Jax
to change his entire life.
To sacrifice what he does have.
I mean, that's not a decision
that can be made lightly.
It took me a long time
to figure out this whole hero thing.
Exactly. Which is why we need someone
who wants to do this.
- Where are you going?
- To get Hewitt back.
We have to try again.
Human DNA?
Yep. Definitely not a man-shark.
Not even a land shark, ma'am.
Well, thanks for testing it for me.
Yeah. What are you gonna do now?
I don't know. Probably file it
under never-gonna-happen.
- I have another case, anyway.
- Oh.
Anything I can help you with?
No. No, no, no.
Detective said definitely not.
- Is everything all good?
- Sure. Why?
I don't know.
You're just acting kind of different.
No!
No, I'm the same old P. Spivot.
You know?
What... Actually, I have to go.
But thank you so much for testing this.
And I'll see you.
Okay. I...
Yo, Joe.
Hey.
You good? Everything all right?
Yeah. I don't know.
- I just had a hell of a day.
- Yeah?
Iris' mother.
She told me she was dying.
Yeah. And I know Francine.
She's telling the truth about this.
Okay.
Does Iris know?
Not yet.
Did... Did you need something?
Uh, no. Nah, I Just...
Patty said that you don't want me on
some case that she's on with you.
No.
I was checking out a lead.
I'll let you know.
All right. Cool.
What is up with you and my partner anyway?
- Come on. I...
- Barr,
you can't take your eyes off that girl.
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
I mean, she's great, you know.
She's adorable and funny,
and we have a lot in common. But...
But, um...
I don't know. She's not Iris, I guess.
Right.
You've known Iris since you were 10,
you've been in love with her
since forever.
I mean, you two are friends now,
but she was your first love.
You're never gonna feel the same
about anybody else.
But you can't let that stop you
from exploring something new.
Yeah.
And in happier news,
remember Flash Day,
the downtown celebration to honor
Central City's one and only superhero?
Well, just weeks...
Hewitt. You have those nucleosome results?
- Tomorrow.
- I told you I needed them tonight.
And I'm telling you,
you'll have them tomorrow!
You know, I... I know you think
you're smarter than everyone here, Hewitt,
but I'm sick of you not doing your job,
your not showing up.
If I have any more trouble from you,
you're done here.
What? You're going to take the test away
and give it to another lab rat of yours?
You gonna report me to the board?
Or maybe you're thinking of firing me?
I'd like to see you try!
Now, get the hell out of my lab!
What's being described
as a "spontaneous energy malfunction"
erupted last night
at Eikmeier Technologies.
Wanted for questioning is scientist,
Henry Hewitt.
Hewitt's dormant abilities must have been
triggered when we attempted the merger.
This could be catastrophic.
If his powers are anything like mine,
he requires a grounding mechanism
to stabilize his volatility. Otherwise...
Yeah. He's gonna pop his top.
And he's got a long history of violence,
according to his police record.
Police record?
- I didn't find a police record.
- Yeah, of course not.
It was sealed. But guess what?
Your boy hacked in and...
Hold on. Wait for it.
One count battery,
two counts aggravated assault,
court ordered anger management therapy.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
He even knew your Hudson nerd song!
You okay?
It appears Mr. Hewitt's stability
isn't the only one in question.
I think I need to lie down.
- Yeah, I'll come with you.
- Thank you.
Professor Stein is getting worse.
And Hewitt's like this because of me.
And now, Jefferson Jackson will never
come back because of what I said.
I just didn't believe
that he has what it takes.
This isn't because
you didn't believe in him.
Sometimes, great possibilities
are right in front of us,
and we don't see them
because we choose not to.
I think that we need to be open
to exploring something new.
She's dying?
A few months left.
I just don't think I can see her, Dad.
And that's fine.
But
you and me need to be
crystal clear about this, Iris.
If you want to have a relationship
with Francine, it's okay with me.
You don't have to protect me.
I'm a grown man, and I've dealt
with these feelings a long time ago.
So, you... You just believe her?
She's done some bad things in her life,
but she wouldn't lie about this.
Dad, she shows up out of nowhere,
and she only says that she's dying
after I told her to stay away?
Look, she didn't come to Central City
to see me.
She came because of you.
I just wanted you to know everything
so you can make
the best decision for yourself.
I mean, she is still your mother.
Either way, whatever you decide, just know
I got your back.
I know.
Let me guess.
You don't got car troubles.
I came to apologize.
I'm sorry for what I said.
It's fine. Apology accepted.
Look, we could really use your help
to save Professor Stein.
- That desperate, huh?
- Yes.
My husband, Ronnie,
he used to be
Professor Stein's other half.
He actually helped to build
the Particle Accelerator,
and when it exploded,
he was affected by it, too.
Ironically, that's how he got the chance
to show the world
what he was truly capable of.
And he died saving this city.
Wait. He was the guy
that flew into the black hole?
That was him?
He was a hero.
You can be one, too.
I never wanted to be a hero.
What I wanted was to go to college,
and we couldn't afford it.
Football was my way in
until that got taken from me.
I know.
Look, I know the Particle Accelerator took
something from you,
but it also gave you something in return.
Something even more spectacular.
The opportunity to be part
of something bigger,
to be part of a team
that's working to protect
people from losing what you lost.
I believe you were meant to be a hero.
Whoa, hold on.
- I've been looking for you, Dr. Snow.
- Hey, look man, we're...
You did this to me!
But it's not what you promised!
Is it?
Come on!
- Where to?
- S.T.A.R. Labs.
Caitlin.
- What's wrong?
- Come here.
Good, you're here.
This thing, it ran out,
like, 30 minutes ago.
His temperature is 142 degrees
and rising fast.
He's going into rapid oxidation.
We need to find a coolant.
Yeah, I think it's too late for that.
I'll do it.
I'll merge with him.
You said this is a chance for me to be
a part of something bigger than myself,
to help people.
- That's what I want.
- You're sure?
Once you merge,
there's no going back on this.
And you said I could fly, right?
- Damn right.
- Okay.
So what do I do?
Okay. Well, here's the abridged version.
Professor Stein.
- What?
- Professor Stein.
Clarissa, five more minutes.
No. Professor, you have to get up.
Jax is here.
- What?
- Jax is here.
Here, grab onto me.
- Jax...
- Yeah.
This is it.
You came back, Jefferson. Thank you.
Well, like my coach always said,
"Out of yourself and into the team."
So, how's this work?
Okay. All you're gonna do is touch him.
- And then what happens?
- You become Firestorm.
Okay.
Jax?
Is Professor Stein...
How will I know?
Hello, Jefferson. Now, you know.
Oh, so I get Grey as my co-pilot.
Did no one ever inform you
of that fringe benefit?
So when do we get to take this
for a test spin?
Uh, how about now?
It looks like Hewitt's recharging
at Central City High School's
football stadium.
Wait. That was where I got hurt.
Cisco!
Cut the power to the field,
so he can't draw any more energy.
I'm on it. Stand by.
Booyaka!
Hewitt!
You need to stop!
This is not who you are!
Stein?
You chose him over me?
That's who I'm supposed to be!
I deserve the Firestorm Matrix!
Now!
Calm down, Jefferson.
Focus.
Use your natural athleticism
to gain control.
Hey, you okay?
I was a quarterback.
I know how to take a hit.
Hey, guys, cutting the power didn't work.
It's like the more we anger him,
the stronger he gets!
That's it. It's like one of those, uh,
controlled fusion devices.
- A tokamak?
- Yes, exactly!
And the more powerful they become,
the more unstable they become.
Barry, make him angry
and he'll blow his fuse.
You up for a little game
of "catch me if you can"?
Let's go for it.
Hey, Hewitt! Over here.
Paging Dr. Hewitt.
Boo!
Man, you are not good at this.
You need a hug, Doctor?
Come on, Hewitt!
Give me your best shot!
Now!
Is that all you got, Hewitt?
Man, no wonder you didn't make the cut
if that's how you fight.
Not bad for your first go at this.
Well, I had a great coach
to help me through it.
Isn't that right, Grey?
Despite my initial reservations,
we make a pretty fantastic team.
Welcome aboard, Firestorm.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
You have no idea what this means to me.
My dad told me you were sick.
You know, I wasn't sure
that I could believe you,
so I did some checking.
Turns out you're telling the truth.
I would never lie to you
about something so big.
Really?
'Cause I was actually thinking
that I could give you another chance
after hearing that news.
But you are still lying.
Still keeping secrets.
I am an investigative reporter, Francine.
I uncover things
that people want to keep hidden.
Like having a son.
Iris...
He was born eight months
after you left Central City.
- Let me explain.
- Who's the father, Francine?
Is it my dad?
Do I have a brother?
Wait, you know what, I don't...
I don't even want to know.
I mean, I wouldn't be able to tell
if you were telling the truth
or if it was another one
of your lies, anyway.
I want you to leave.
You stay away from me,
and you stay away from my father.
If he finds out that he might have a son
that grew up without knowing him,
It would crush him.
Just...
Leave us alone.
Iris. Iris.
And how is Mr. Hewitt?
Seems like that last burst of energy
has burnt him out.
Our tokamak's gone dark.
Hey, we'rejust gonna keep him
safe and sound in the pipeline
till he decides to keep quiet
about all this.
So you're gonna meet up with Clarissa?
We're meeting in Pittsburgh in three days.
Why Pittsburgh?
A colleague of mine was monumental
in helping train Ronald and me.
She's graciously offered
to help the two of us as well.
Well, how is she going to help us?
Well, there were many aspects
of our abilities
that we never quite achieved.
Hopefully now,
we can fully realize that potential.
My dearest Dr. Snow.
Ronald may be lost to us,
but he will never be forgotten.
Speaking of,
This was Ronnie's.
He always used it
to find his way back home.
I want you to have it.
Thank you.
You know, this whole thing is strange.
Being 50% of someone.
Yeah, but you're 100% a hero.
I went ahead
and re-calibrated the splicer,
so the merging should be
even smoother now.
Thank you.
If I may offer you a bit
of parting advice.
Cisco, I know you're scared,
but this ability you have is a gift.
Not a curse. It's natural to be
apprehensive about the unknown.
But look, look at Jefferson.
He took a leap,
and it changed his life for the better.
The very thing that makes you different
is what makes you special.
Tell your friends.
And now, I believe it's time to
take this show on the road,
or to the sky, if I'm to be literal.
Are you ready, Jefferson?
- All right. Yeah.
- See you later.
That was one hell of a leap of faith
that kid took,
merging with Professor Stein.
Yeah, it was.
There is a lesson in there
somewhere for you.
Things aren't always
what they seem.
Our fears can play tricks on us.
Making us afraid to change course,
afraid to move on.
But usually, hidden behind our fears
are second chances waiting to be seized.
Second chances at life.
- Whoo!
- At glory.
Whoo!
At family.
At love.
And these opportunities
don't come around every day.
So when they do, we have to be brave.
Take a chance,
and grab them while we can.
Zoom wants you dead.
Oh, my God, it's real!
Hey! Put him down!
Put your hands-Your fins in the air!
Who the hell are you?