Surprise, babe.
Yeah, wow.
This is not a banana.
I know Valentine's Day isn't
for a couple of days,
but I thought, why not?
Let me surprise my hubby before
some crazy meta-of-the-week strikes.
Here, I got it. How's your arm?
Oh, um, I mean, it stings,
but it's a bit better.
Yeah?
You know,
if you really want a banana,
- I could always go in the kitchen...
- No. No.
No, I don't want a banana.
This all looks awesome.
I mean, the pancakes
are really... round.
- Hmm.
- I'm just excited to taste them
with my mouth.
Oh, my God. When did you learn to...
I mean, these are really good.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Is this fresh-squeezed?
Mmm-hmm. Oh, um...
We may or may not now
own a very expensive juicer.
I got to say, you're full
of surprises this morning.
Well, the day is young.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm?
Wait, how did you have time
to get a spread like this together?
I mean, it sounded
like yesterday was insane.
Yeah, it was.
Which is why Team Citizen
is regrouping
before we go after Carver again.
And as for all this,
thank God for 24-hour grocery stores.
Amen.
This is your reminder.
You have a reservation at Giovanni's
February 14th at 7:00 p.m.
You know what? If we also made
a reservation for tonight,
we could up our chances
of having an emergency-free
Valentine's Day dinner.
Well, I don't care when we have dinner,
as long as we're together.
Alexa, set a reminder
to call Giovanni's today at noon.
Okay, I'll remind you.
Great. You finish eating.
I will.
- I'm gonna go take a shower.
- Okay.
You're amazing.
Son of a motherless goat,
you do not want to test me.
Oh, thank God, it's just you.
You're out of tape.
Uh, did you just let yourself in?
Relax. I'm not some
whack job meta-killer
with crazy-good aim
and ulterior motives... anymore.
Another house call
from Dr. Light would suck,
but I was actually
talking about Nash.
He's a total stage-one clinger.
Didn't you get shot yesterday?
Shouldn't you be soaking
in a tub of frozen peas or something?
And miss out
on my first Valentine's Day? No way.
I hate Valentine's Day.
And I have a lot of work to do, so...
You know, it's my understanding
that there are two kinds of people
who hate Valentine's Day.
One, those who think
it's a made-up holiday by Big Candy,
or two, those with a broken heart.
I think you're the second one.
No, I'm not.
Really? Uh, I think, actually, you are.
And I think Mr. Emerson Fairweather
is the emo dope who's responsible.
We met after a gig his band played.
Mmm-hmm.
Anyway, it didn't work out.
"Another Valentine's Day
waiting for love.
Let the drinking begin!
#CoffeeNotCocktails."
Ugh. Look, you're perfect
for each other.
You have something in common.
You're both miserable.
Thanks for the reminder.
You know, maybe
you and Mr. Fall Out Boy
could go off and be mopey together,
and then you wouldn't hate
Valentine's Day.
I'm sorry. Have we met?
Look, it says here, he's gonna be
back at Jitters tomorrow.
And you know what? So are we.
'Cause I'm gonna get
the two of you back together
for some V-Day love. Cupid demands it.
What?
I'm glad we decided
to do dinner tonight.
It's awesome.
Celebrating Valentine's together,
even if it's early.
Yeah.
No Crisis,
no dark future looming over us.
Feels nice.
It really does.
Buona sera.
I'm so sorry. We don't speak Italian.
And, uh, can we just
get another minute?
Grazie.
Uh...
What?
What? Do you speak Italian?
Oh, uh, well...
You know that story I was writing
a few months ago on Little Italy?
Well, I picked up a phrase or two.
Like, um...
It's a curse word. But it literally
means "pig misery."
Yeah, weird, right?
Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
Step forward, Saul Frankel...
or I'll kill all of you.
Oh.
And they say chivalry is dead.
Hand over the case, love.
You know what'll happen
if you take this?
I know what will happen to you...
if I don't.
Ah.
Darlings!
Long time no see.
Did I interrupt date night?
C.C.P.D.
Amunet Black,
I'm placing you under arrest
for robbery and aggravated assault.
So very official, Mr. Allen.
But aren't you just a CSI?
I'm still a cop who can arrest you.
Oh, okay.
Well, by all means,
let me help you with the first bit.
I have the right to remain silent,
which will come in handy
if you don't want me
letting that
little secret-identity-cat
out of its flashy red bag.
So, why don't we just
call this a warning?
I'll be on my way. No harm...
no cowl.
I'm supposed to just let you leave?
Bloody right.
Don't think of coming after me.
'Cause if I see you in your onesie
or any one of your frigid
or bendy superhero friends,
I will hold it against all of you
and tell the world your real identities.
Savvy?
That's right.
Because behind every great man
is a woman rolling her eyes.
Ta-ta, sweethearts.
So much for date night.
Pig misery.
There's no trace of Amunet?
It's like she vanished.
Yeah, she does that.
Were there any rumblings
that she was back in town?
None. But Captain West
has all officers
searching on high alert.
Great. Thanks, Korber.
Barry, Amunet has been off the grid
for so long
that, if she's back,
it must be for something big and bad.
And I'm pretty sure it involves
that device that she stole.
I know.
Hey, don't worry.
We're gonna find her.
Still can't believe I just
stood there and let her walk out.
Barry, it's not your fault.
We knew that her knowing your identity
would come back to bite us.
Yeah, time to find her
the old-fashioned way.
I'm gonna run
some sweeps of the city.
Whoa, whoa. She said no onesies.
Please don't call it that.
What I'm trying to say is,
we can't risk her
putting Team Flash on blast.
Okay. I mean,
we also can't do nothing.
We won't.
If you wanna figure out
a criminal's plan,
visit their playground.
This is a bad idea.
Challenging an entire drug cartel
to a knife fight, that's a bad idea.
Fun, though.
This? This is nothing.
Just go over there and talk to him.
He really does look miserable.
Yeah, I'm sure
he's over there working
on some sad-sack song
to perform tomorrow night.
Trust your awesome life coach,
and just get over there.
What do I even say?
I don't know. You said
you could be yourself around him,
so go do that.
You're right.
Don't worry.
I'm sure they're just good friends.
A really good friend.
- Allegra...
- I knew this was a bad idea.
Next time
you wanna play life coach, don't.
Uh...
I still think
it's better if I go.
Babe, this is a known spot
that Amunet used to recruit her crew.
Besides, a cop can't
just waltz in there.
Okay, but it's mostly criminals
in there. It's really dangerous.
Barry, it's my job
to get information out of people.
Amunet's not gonna be there,
but if someone knows
where she's headed next,
I can get them to talk.
It's what I do.
Besides, if things get dicey,
we have our code word.
"Banana."
You hear that, you come fathwooming.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay, fine. Just be safe, please.
Scout's honor.
Whiskey, rocks.
You look familiar.
He must read The Citizen. Get out.
Get out.
Get out of there, Iris.
Maybe I have one of those faces.
I'm looking for Amunet Black.
You don't seem like her type.
Got a problem, Lars?
Banana. Banana! Banana!
Banana!
Banana! Banana!
Banana, Iris!
Now, do I seem like her type?
Seems like I need a new bouncer.
You interested?
I'll keep it in mind.
Now, for the last time,
where is Amunet?
Last I heard,
she was heisting
some specialized tech...
from this spot.
Thanks for the drink.
Hey, what happened?
I heard glass breaking.
Nothing. I broke a bottle
over some loser's head.
You what?
Barry, don't worry.
Everything's fine.
I was playing a role
to get information.
Okay, well, I...
That was maybe crossing a line.
I'm sure they have some sort of
mob doctor in there somewhere.
Okay, but, I mean, it was reckless
and it could have backfired.
But it didn't
because I knew what I was doing.
And we got this.
Is this Amunet's next target?
Let's go get her.
Oh, I do love loud noises.
Yeah!
For the lady who has everything.
Well, your source at the bar was right.
She's here.
Yeah, but what is she doing?
- You have any idea what that tech is?
- No.
But I'm betting it's connected
to the first device she stole.
We have to figure out how to stop her
before things get...
Worse.
Just what I was looking for.
Goldface is working with Amunet?
Well, they did used to date.
You're too late, Keith.
Oh, Leslie.
You know
I can't let you leave with that.
I don't think
they're working together.
No.
This is a gang war.
I suppose you're here
to steal what's mine.
Typical.
What's yours?
Baby, that device belongs to me.
Oh, here we go again
with the possessive man routine.
The vinyl records were mine, Keith.
Since when did you like Radiohead?
I had OK Computer on 180-gram vinyl
with a triple-gatefold sleeve!
Overrated.
You skipped out with my
Straight Outta Compton soundtrack.
Oh, please! Like you even knew
who N.W.A. were before you met me.
Security! Freeze!
Don't anybody move.
Took some doing,
setting up that deal.
And you just stroll out of Giovanni's
with my score?
Sorry, not sorry.
- Baby...
- I said, freeze.
You know I'm not letting it
go down like that.
Oh, come on.
Looks like
somebody's lost their touch.
I said, put your hands in the air!
Really?
Looks to me like somebody's lost
their gym membership.
- Barry.
- What?
It'll be bad if Amunet knows
the Flash is here.
Okay, but that guard might be
really hurt. I have to do something.
But...
Yeah, well,
no amount of gym time
could help me lift all your baggage!
Still strong enough
to lift this, though.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Bye, Felicia.
How did you lift that?
Uh, adrenaline.
Stay here, okay? You'll be okay.
Where are they?
- Gone.
- What?
Well, let's go after them.
We have to get the case.
Who needs the case...
when you've got what's inside?
Oh, my gosh.
- Hey. Did you find anything?
- Uh-uh.
- Why are you so tired?
- I don't know.
I mean, to keep Amunet
and Goldface from seeing me,
I had to run so fast,
I was practically invisible.
But it's getting bad out there.
I mean, their gangs
who are just trading attacks.
It's like both sides think that
the other has the second device.
Yeah, I called my dad.
He said that Amunet and Goldface
are sticking to criminal targets,
like each other's
stash houses, but...
I don't know. I think
they're trying to hurt each other,
not just their businesses.
Okay. All right, well,
until we know what they're after,
I guess I'll just keep patrolling
at super speed.
I'm just worried some innocent people
are gonna get
caught in their crossfire,
while we wait
for this thing to blow over.
I don't think it will, Barry.
When Amunet and Goldface
were arguing at Ivo,
they used each other's real names.
They argued
about an old record collection.
That's personal.
Personal doesn't just blow over.
I mean, but what's personal
about stealing tech?
Okay, so I called Ryan Choi.
The first item that Amunet stole,
a specialized UV projector.
The second item was
a biome-simulated storage unit.
If you combine the two,
it can be used to transport
delicate, plant-based life.
They're after a plant? Why?
I don't know.
But if those two are after it,
it's probably dangerous.
Yeah.
So, a botanist source I used
from an old story is looking into it.
But I think there's a faster way
to figure this out.
Hmm.
We give Amunet what she wants.
What?
Yeah, we use the leverage we have.
We get close to Amunet,
and we solve this thing
from the inside.
No, I mean, that's... way too dangerous.
I mean, Amunet knows both of us.
- So?
- So...
So, we stay put.
You mean I stay put while you patrol.
Well, I mean...
You're the Flash.
You know best, right?
What? Iris, come on.
Look at the facts.
Screw facts, Barry.
I trust my intuition.
My intuition, by the way,
that saved my life from an assassin,
while you were on some island.
What?
Okay, what's going on?
It feels like ever since
you came back home the other night,
you've been acting kind of different.
I mean, the pancakes.
And the bottle-smashing...
Do you hear yourself right now, Barry?
Seriously?
My New Year's resolution?
Learn how to make pancakes.
And I told you
that I was playing a role.
Come on, Barry.
You know what?
Actually, I didn't forget my files
at the office last night.
I was following up on a lead.
So there.
You were following a lead
in the middle of the night?
I mean, something could
have happened to you.
That, Barry. That right there,
that's why I didn't tell you.
I don't need you to save me.
I can handle myself.
I even have my own team now,
Team Citizen.
I know.
And you know what? While you were
preoccupied with Crisis,
I was planning
to start a life without you.
And it was the hardest thing
that I ever had to do,
but I did it
because you asked me to, Barry.
I would do anything for you
and you know that.
But I can't be
your damsel in distress anymore.
And I cannot be the voice
inside your cowl, cheering you on.
I'm a reporter, Barry.
And I'm a damn good one.
And risky or not,
I deserve to be in that field
just as much as you do.
I know that.
I...
It just feels like...
I mean, I don't know. It doesn't feel
like we're connecting lately.
I've grown, Barry.
And I'm really proud
of the person that I am today.
I just wish
that you felt the same way, too.
Come on... Iris.
Ah.
It's just you.
Yeah, I thought, you know,
maybe it might be the...
You know, the girl, the, um...
What's her name? Abbondanza...
Allegra?
Yeah, Allegra, that's... That's her.
Why are you looking for her?
She's, uh... She's...
This nano-dimensional bucket auger,
it's hers.
And she wondered if
I was bucket-augering,
but now she wants
to bucket-auger, so I was like...
Anyway, what are you doing,
sitting here, drinking by yourself?
Yes, Valentine's Day drinking
to celebrate what a screw-up I am.
What is that?
Naltorian mead left to us
by one of the previous Wellses.
You know, back when there were
other Wellses in the multi-verse.
Sorry. Nash, I didn't...
It's fine. It's fine.
See what I mean?
Everything I touch turns out sucking.
I mean, how do I explain to Ralph
that he's wasted the last five months
trying to teach me
how to be a better person?
'Cause it doesn't matter
how much litter I pick up,
how many sick kids I read to,
I still don't get people.
I really thought I could help Allegra
fall back in love with her ex,
but, instead,
I just made a mess of everything.
You know, you got lost.
Now, you just
get back on the highway.
Find new inroads with this Allegra.
Easy-peasy.
You know, I don't know her very well,
but perhaps she's one of those people
that just sees things
in absolutes, right?
Black and white.
Missions fail or succeed, right?
Do you know what you need to do?
You need to get
back in there with her.
Open her up and show her that things
aren't just black and white.
Black and white,
that's just for death and taxes.
Everything else...
Everything else happens in the grays.
Wow.
Someone's not a fan.
Mrs. Flash.
However did you find your way here?
Well, there is
a very charming bartender
that is giving out tips
rather than collecting them. So...
Lars. I'll have to kill him.
- Hmm. Ladies first.
- Uh, wait.
Um, I know what you're after.
And I want in.
Hmm?
So, let me get this straight.
Iris West-Allen,
a sky-rocketing news media force,
daughter of the police captain,
devoted spouse of
the Scarlet Speedster, all of that,
but I'm supposed to believe
you're willing to give me
an invaluable piece of stolen tech.
Why, exactly?
Rappaccini's Daughter,
a rare orchid recently shipped
for study at CC Arboretum.
And why, on this
great big blue marble
do you think
that I would be interested in that?
Well, because what makes it rare
isn't that it blooms every 25 years.
Hmm?
It's the flower's pollen.
When adequately heated,
it could be synthesized
into a telepathic narcotic.
If you can read minds,
it would be much easier
to gain access to PIN numbers
to big, fat bank accounts.
Bravo. Well done.
But you didn't answer
the most important question.
Why the bloody hell
should I believe you?
Because I want to use the pollen.
For what?
Well, as you know,
I am married to the Flash,
and he's a man
who has a lot on his mind.
Mmm-hmm.
And lately, that hasn't been me.
And to tell you the truth, I'm afraid
that all this superheroing is...
ruining my marriage.
But if I could use the pollen,
then I could read his mind.
Why didn't you just say so?
That, I can believe.
Girl, I am no stranger
to roguish means for love.
You mean you and Goldface.
Men, they're all idiots.
Who needs them?
This could be the start
of a beautiful friendship.
Come along.
We're going flower shopping.
Goldface's gang is...
throwing Molotov cocktails
at one of Amunet's warehouses.
They are retaliating by sinking
their latest delivery boat.
I mean, I know it's criminal-on-criminal
attacks right now,
but if we don't stop it, I mean,
it could be
a Valentine's Day massacre
where civilians get hurt.
Yeah, I'll keep doing sweeps.
I'll help wherever I can.
Mmm.
Well, I might have to roll out
a special meta task force.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Can you pull together Team Flash?
No, I can't. I mean,
she knows them all.
I have to protect their identities, too.
You know what, Joe? There's something
not right about this
Amunet-Goldface thing. It...
Iris thinks there's
something personal going on.
Well, I mean,
I do wish they were still a couple.
I mean, things were
a lot quieter out there and safer.
Some Valentine's Day, huh?
Mmm-hmm.
Barr...
You been looking down a lot.
My floor is not that interesting.
So, what's up?
It's Iris, actually.
I mean, she...
I don't know.
There's just something
that's suddenly off between us,
or at least it feels sudden to me.
What did she say about that?
She's grown...
and I haven't accepted it.
Mmm. I don't know
about that second part.
But that first part, she has grown.
She took down a Black Hole assassin.
And she led the charge
to find Ryan Choi during Crisis.
And she was the only one
who knew that Rosso
hadn't completely taken you over.
I mean,
who does that sound like to you?
I know, I mean, she has grown, and...
I guess she was right.
I mean, I didn't notice
because I was consumed with Crisis.
Now we're just not clicking
like usual, though.
Do you think maybe she's grown apart?
Barry, no, no.
Neither one of you
are ever going to stop growing.
I mean, marriage is like a tree.
Bear with me. Look...
The branches,
they grow from the center.
They grow farther and farther away
from the center.
But what you have
to remember is, underneath,
the roots,
they're mirroring the branches.
They're growing just as much.
So, you're growing your foundation.
Now, of course,
you gotta tend to the soil,
communicate with each other,
take care of each other,
look out for each other.
But as the branches grow,
so does your foundation.
So you grow together.
Art therapy. Been there.
Look, I'm sorry about Jitters.
- I know you meant well.
- No, I'm sorry.
Look, my life coach
made my life better.
I was just trying to pay it forward.
I probably should have gotten
the whole story about your breakup
before trying to intervene.
I guess I haven't exactly been
an open book.
Why don't you start from page one?
After I got out of Iron Heights,
I wanted to take a shot
at living a normal non-meta life.
That's when I met Emerson.
And we became friends.
Then we went on a few dates,
had some laughs...
but it ran its course,
so I dropped it.
You ghosted him.
Kind of.
Why?
You didn't want him
to find out you're a meta.
Back then, I could barely
deal with my powers.
How could I expect someone else to?
Anyway, it was never
gonna work between us.
You don't know that.
I mean, you never gave him a chance
to find out who you really are.
It doesn't matter now. He probably
hates me for ghosting him.
Are you sure? Because maybe he's been
looking for you every day since.
Or maybe he forgot you existed.
Whatever it is, you don't know
because you've been filling in
the blanks without the facts.
Coming clean to Emerson might
actually make you feel a lot better.
And who knows?
Maybe you'll get a friend out of it.
But you can't assume
that life happens in black and white,
because life happens in the gray.
And you need to get out there
and live in it.
Keith and I were like fireworks
when we were together.
We shared the same ambitions,
and it ignited us both.
We inspired each other.
Rappaccini's Daughter was meant to be
our greatest score ever.
Even though
it only blooms every 25 years?
What can I say? We were optimists,
making plans for the future.
We knew that it was set
to bloom this year,
and once we had our hands
on its mind-reading powers,
no one would be able to stop us.
We would run this town together.
I felt like I could be myself
when I was with him.
He's the only one
who ever saw beyond all this.
He saw me for me.
So, what went wrong?
Hmm. As business boomed,
our relationship didn't.
Our passion wilted...
and died.
Well... I don't know, Amunet.
The way you two were trying
to kill each other?
Hmm. It's a fine line
between love and hate, my dear.
Thank you.
Why don't you just tell him
how you feel, talk to him?
No.
I'm better off without him.
And when I get my hands
on that flower...
I'll run this town myself.
Come, my lovelies.
Hello, lover.
That case,
it looks like a larger version
of the tech that you stole.
This orchid is a lot like love.
It can only survive
in a carefully tended environment.
That glass device you gave me
is a miniature biome simulator.
The UV projector provides
a nurturing light.
Together...
Flowers?
You shouldn't have.
Seeing that you got the means
to transport the flower,
I figured I'd take them both
from you at once.
Consider it a Valentine's gift.
And here, I thought we weren't
exchanging gifts this year.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Barry, what are you doing?
Amunet can't see the Flash here.
I'm done playing her game.
And I would risk anything to save you.
After putting together
the leads that they dug up,
it wasn't hard to figure out that
they were after Rappaccini's Daughter.
They're gonna destroy each other.
Not if they both accept that
they still have feelings for each other.
Joe did say things were better
when they were together.
My life got better without you.
You're dead weight.
You were the biggest mistake
I ever made.
You always had this one
really bad habit.
Breathing!
You're nothing
but a cheap, bald Mr. T.
I'm gonna stop their crossfire.
I'd rather date Norvock than you!
Makes two of us.
Your American accent sucks!
So does yours!
I'm from Connecticut. I went to Yale!
Okay, stop! Just stop this!
You guys were happy together once,
right? Why'd you break up?
I thought I said...
She stopped listening to me.
I needed her support
when things went bad,
not her cold shoulder.
I got tired of him
always celebrating with his posse,
and only coming to me to whine
about his failures! It got old!
Okay. See, I mean,
you guys are talking now.
This is great, right?
I said, no onesie.
Okay. Why does everybody
keep calling it that?
Whatever you call it,
there's an awful lot of gold
in there, Flash.
Whoa.
Oh, God.
Now, where were we?
I was just about to tell you,
when I told you I liked your dog,
I lied! I'm a cat person!
The mud mask you use at night
smells rank. Real mud smells better.
Ow.
That didn't feel great.
Okay, it's no use.
There's no fixing them.
I have an idea,
but it might be reckless.
Okay, what's the plan?
Burn the flower.
Here you go again,
twirling your shiny spaghetti!
I'd hold you forever,
but it still wouldn't be
enough time together.
The sight of your eyes
fills my heart with gold.
Did it work?
The stars at night
can only dream
they'd ever shine as bright as you.
I was always so proud
of the work you did at Yale.
Your natural
mud mask works wonders.
You complete me.
What's happening?
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
We are strong
No one can tell us we're wrong
Searching our hearts for so long
Oh, I'm sorry.
I should take off my gauntlet.
Leave it on, girl.
- Daddy likes the metal.
- Ooh.
I can't unsee this.
Well, at least, it's less violent
than a gang war.
- Barely. Yeah.
- Yeah.
More links than I remember.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Love is a battlefield
- How'd it go?
- Better than I thought.
I said sorry for ghosting him.
Told him why.
He accepted my apology.
So, he's fine with you being a meta.
Yeah. Turns out his new drummer
is bioluminescent.
Emerson and I are gonna
be friends again.
And you know what?
I think that's what I was
really missing this whole time.
Him, too. He actually wants me
to go take a look at his new lyrics
before he goes on stage.
Look at you. Back to being a muse.
Yeah.
So, thanks...
for your help
with all the gray life stuff.
It's exactly what I needed to hear.
You're welcome.
Although I can't take all the credit,
a friend of mine did give me
some advice.
Well, tell them thanks, too.
They may not know me,
but they get me.
Frost, I mean...
you.
Got your message.
What's so important?
I thought you'd wanna know
that Allegra was here,
so you could give her
your tool thingy.
The... Are you kidding, really?
You bring me to a crappy Valentine's Day
open mic night for that?
Well...
Also, so I could tell you
that I owe you one.
The advice you gave,
it really helped me
get through to Allegra.
It was very insightful.
Almost parental.
You going somewhere with that?
I'm just saying,
if you ever wanna talk...
Like I said, I owe you one.
And, uh, I'm a very good listener.
Hell of a Valentine's Day, huh?
Next year, we lock ourselves
in the time vault
and don't come out till morning.
Listen...
I'm really sorry that
I made you feel like I wasn't seeing
all your success in a larger way.
- Babe, it's fine.
- No, it's not.
You've made a name for yourself,
and this city looks to you
and The Citizen
for the truth about what's going on,
and I am so proud of who you are
and all of your accomplishments.
I just...
For a moment today, I felt like...
maybe we were growing apart.
That will never happen.
I get that now.
And, babe, just remember
that no matter what changes,
you're always gonna be
my lightning rod, too.
- Iris West-Allen...
- Hmm.
will you be my Valentine?
You read my mind.
Get away from him!
Barry!
That's not me!
She's not me!
Barry!