Previously on The Flash...
Council of Wells.
Some of the brightest minds
in all the multi-verse.
There's still another cryogenic
anomaly in my DNA.
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
The more I try to use my brain,
the sooner I'm going to lose it.
I know what DeVoe's doing.
Separate satellites working together
for a single purpose?
DeVoe wants to remove the
intelligence of everyone on Earth?
Just like mine.
Iris?
Sorry, babe.
Go back to sleep.
Iris.
All right. Just...
Just one second. Let me just...
Let me just get this
last sentence done, okay?
Why are you still awake?
What is all this?
This is every file, every report,
every footnote
that I could find on DeVoe.
I dug it all up when I woke up
in the middle of the night.
I just... I couldn't stop thinking
about DeVoe and his machine,
and now that he has
all of the satellites,
I mean, he could turn on the machine
at any point.
And not knowing is maddening,
but at least I know
what he's planned, right?
But everyone else in the city,
they are oblivious.
Which is why I decided that
I need to write a piece about it.
- An article?
- Exposing every single detail
- of his maniacal plan.
- Um...
I think that if people in this city
knew what he was up to,
then maybe they could
protect themselves.
Barry, I really think
this is exactly what we need
to change the tide against DeVoe.
So, I'm gonna go upstairs,
I'm gonna take a shower,
and when I come back, I need you
to tell me everything you know
about that flying chair
and how he uses it to body hop and...
So, last night, Harry,
Cisco and I were up all night
running all the different algorithms
we could think of
involving the satellite tech
that DeVoe stole.
We think DeVoe plans to position
each of his five satellites
at specifically calculated points
around the globe.
And when the quantum computers
in each satellite link up...
He'll use that network to basically
emit a series of dark matter bursts.
That will reboot the prefrontal cortex
of every man, woman and child
on this Earth.
Well, we need
to nip this in the bud.
We can't let him launch
those satellites.
Yeah, but I mean, how are we
supposed to find him?
I mean, we haven't been able to register
DeVoe's pocket dimension energy
for days.
And with Null's gravitational powers
he can launch these satellites
from any place at any time.
Yeah, he can.
What are you thinking, Barr?
I think we shoot 'em down.
- Whoa.
- There is one small problem.
DeVoe has Kilg%re's powers.
Yeah, he can manipulate
any tech-based weapon we fire at him.
So, we don't use tech.
We use some kind of
organic matter weapon.
Right. Like a...
Like a...
You know what, let's split up,
see what we can find.
Ramon.
DeVoe's not acting.
Why is he not acting?
I don't know, but it doesn't matter.
But it does matter.
Oh, and if I had my intelligence,
I could figure that out.
But I don't. I gotta get it back.
No, no, no.
What you need to do is be patient.
We're consulting with, like,
literally every scientist we know.
Will you consult with me?
- Harry...
- No, not... not dumb me.
The other mes.
The Council?
So, I must admit
I found your transmission
intriguing to say the least.
But first,
I have a question for you, Harry Wells.
Tell me, Harry, how did your
"hypothetical" thinking cap
account for the resonant inductive
coupling of the dark matter transfer?
- Well...
- The inductive coupling...
Am I speaking to you? I cannot remember.
Oh, wait. I'm not.
Little guy they must call "Cisco,"
put you in a box,
put the box in the pocket.
Talking to Harry. Simple question.
How does it account
for the resonant coupling?
It, uh...
Ah!
I knew it. He doesn't know.
He doesn't know.
Oh! Simple Harry
is truly Simple Harry now.
No, that's not what's happening.
Ja. Remember I put you in a box,
put the box in the pocket.
Crushed the box in the pocket.
This is very simple, what has happened,
your "hypothetical" thinking cap
has malfunctioned
and left a Wells, a once formidable
intellect, a dumdum.
- That's not what happened.
- Yeah, that's what happened.
That's what happened.
Poor Harry.
- Herr Wells.
- Ja.
Are you gonna help us or not?
- Not.
- Why not?
The Council of Wells is a council
of superior intellects
there to accept the challenge
of others with superior intellects.
It's called the "Council of Wells,"
and not the "Council of Dumdums!"
- Look at this man.
- I see him.
Is he not one of your own?
Are you telling me that you're gonna
betray one of your own
because he doesn't meet some
arbitrary intellectual standard?
So you do understand.
Ja, unlike your simple friend,
here's what you now must consider.
Auf wiedersehen.
He's right.
I am a dumdum.
Hey, you are not a dumdum.
Ramon, come on. Let's face facts.
I've lost most of my science,
lost most of my math.
Language will be next,
and there's nothing we can do about it.
On the contrary, mon frere.
We're the ones who created that
council of dingdongs
in the first place,
so if they're not gonna help us,
that leaves us with one other option.
A new council. A smarter council.
A better council.
Hey, Caitlin.
Do you have any ibuprofen?
Reading up on all this organic matter
is giving me an organic migraine.
Thanks.
You have a little...
Oh, acupuncture.
Ever since I found out I still have
a cryogenic anomaly in my DNA,
I've been doing every medical avenue
I can think of
to get Killer Frost to emerge.
Mmm. You really do miss her, don't you?
Yeah. Killer Frost was a part of me,
and just as I was starting
to accept her,
she was taken away.
I'm running out of ideas.
Hmm. Well, I know
it's not exactly the same,
but I've had my fair share
of missing persons cases.
And what do you do
when you've hit a wall?
I try to attack it from
a different direction.
If that helps.
Anyway, thanks.
We've been attacking this
from the wrong direction.
We know we need a tech-free projectile
to stop DeVoe's satellites.
We've been looking for an object
when what we really need is a person.
Amunet.
- Amunet Black?
- I know she's not the ideal choice,
but Amunet's psychic-powered
alnico shards
are not only deadly powerful,
they're completely immune
to DeVoe's Kilg%re powers.
Not ideal? I mean, she kidnapped you.
She tried to sell me into meta slavery.
And she ruined my bachelorette party.
- I mean...
- That's not...
I mean, you're right.
It's admittedly not as big of a deal,
but you know what I'm saying.
Yeah, we can't partner up with Amunet.
She's a criminal.
Snart's a criminal, so is Killer Frost.
We worked with them.
All right, look...
Look, even if we forgave Amunet
for everything she's done...
Which is a lot.
What makes you say
she'd be willing to help us?
I've seen a different side of her.
She's helped me before,
and I believe she'll do it again.
This isn't what I expected
Amunet's hideout to look like.
I might have made a few changes.
- What...
- Really, boys?
You're trying to get us killed?
That's the Flash, you morons.
And Caitlin may look like a librarian,
but she's a coldhearted beast.
Where's Amunet?
Really?
No "Hello, Norvok, how you been?"
You're not even gonna introduce me
to your new boss?
I'm not her boss, I'm just a friend.
Well, isn't that sweet.
Norvok, where is Amunet?
No one's heard a peep from her
in months.
For all I know,
the witch is dead.
So, Amunet's gone?
Well, apparently, after her deal with
Warden Wolfe took a nosedive,
she's been out of
the meta trafficking business.
Caitlin, you know any personal details
that can help us track her down?
Ooh, I don't know.
Amunet's always been a private person,
sort of unpredictable and rash.
Kind of fly by the seat of your pants.
You know, when she kidnapped me
at Christmas,
she said she used to be
a flight attendant.
I think she was on an airplane
the night
the particle accelerator exploded.
Okay, that we can work with. Let's see.
Yeah, looks like there were
35 flights in the air in Central City
the night of
the particle accelerator explosion.
Cisco, can you access
the flight manifests?
Yes, I can,
and I can take the crew's credentials...
Cross reference them
in the facial recognition?
Can you not read my mind?
I didn't, um...
- Ah.
- Her real name is Leslie Jocoy?
Maybe she's operating under
her real name, not her pseudonym.
Well, she didn't have a criminal record
until the particle accelerator,
so it's not a bad plan.
C.C.P.D.'s database has several prior
work addresses for Leslie Jocoy.
All right, let's pay them all a visit.
Okay. Dad, why don't you and Caitlin
go and check out
the most recent address?
- I'll check out the rest.
- Sounds like a plan.
And I should get back to the loft.
I need to pick up the DeVoe file
- for my article...
- Hey, actually, um,
can I, um,
just talk to you really quick?
Uh, yeah, okay.
Just about your article.
I just think maybe
telling everybody about
a meta-human uber-genius
who plans on rebooting
people's brains...
Yeah, but if we don't tell them,
they might find out when it's too late.
Sure, but I don't... I mean,
the team's always liked to keep
what we're working on low-key.
Okay, well, I'll run the idea by them.
No. I don't mean no, I just mean...
Maybe hold off until
you finish writing it.
Okay, yeah, I'll hold off.
- You will?
- Yeah.
No, I mean, I get it.
We've never openly shared this kind
of information with the city before...
- Right.
- And the team will be
more likely to agree with me
if I have a full article ready
for them to read, so...
I'm gonna hurry up and finish it.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Harry, I give to you
the emotionally astute
Council of Harrisons.
- Hey.
- There you are.
H. Wells, what are you doing here?
Those other stiffs,
well, they got tired of my connections.
Making me tardy to their party, so...
They gave me the boot.
Give you the...
Wait, so I'm not the only one?
Nuh-uh. All of us have been kicked out.
All of you have been...
You got me a council of rejects.
Oh, they're brilliant rejects.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Who you calling rejects?
Hey, look at this guy.
What are you? Stunad?
Allow myself to introduce myself.
- Sunny Wells, Earth-24...
- At your service.
They call me "Sunny" on account
of my sunny disposition.
You know what,
I think that name kind of works for him.
The guy who must be Cisco. Hey.
My motto, personally?
For me, my motto,
"Be kind.
"Rewind."
"Be kind. Rewind"?
They're still on VHS.
What?
Hello, yes. Bonjour.
So, I am Harrison H.P. Wells
of the Earth-vingt cinq.
So, I must say that it warms me
to see us all bonded by our faces
and our hearts.
See his scarf? I like that scarf.
I'm gonna get myself one of them
classy scarfs like this guy.
That's a $10 scarf right there.
So, anyway, without further ado,
it's time for me
to commence this meeting
with one of my poems, so, allez.
"I never knew you.
"I never taste you."
Taste...
"I never smell you.
"Until I do.
"And now, I am hookted."
Mmm. Saucy.
And, uh, what is this poem about?
- Bread.
- Ah, deep connection.
Food can...
feed the soul.
You know, I once had this experience
with a hot apple pie...
Okay, you know what,
that's enough, uh, sharing
from this side of the table.
How about we let somebody else share?
Harry, you have the floor.
- No chance.
- Harry.
- No way.
- Come on.
- Do the intro.
Why? No.
- I'm not gonna... What?
- Harry.
You have to do the sharing
if you want the helping. Okay?
Allez, Harry.
Hey.
- I'm Harry.
- How you doing, Harry?
- Bonjour, Harry.
- Howdy, Harry.
We know his name.
So, uh...
Here's the thing.
I'm losing my intelligence.
- Whoa!
- Oh, no.
And as Wellses, you know how
very important our intelligence is,
and so I'm asking for your help
to get my intelligence back,
so I can kick some...
So I can help my team.
- Will you help me do that?
- Non.
Non, mais... Of course, Harry.
Of course, we will help him.
We will help you. Open your heart.
We'll open your mind.
Come on, let's do this.
- Okay.
- Lovely.
Hey, Barr, we're at the market.
We'll let you know if we find her.
- Copy that.
- Amunet used to work here?
What did she do? Bag groceries?
At least it's not human trafficking.
Let's look around.
Hey, look, when I told you
to look in a different direction
to find your alter ego,
I didn't mean team up with a criminal.
I know how that probably looks.
Yeah, it looks like you want us
to work with Amunet Black
so she can help you with
your Killer Frost problem.
I mean, why weren't you up front
with the team about that?
Because I thought they'd say no
if I had my own reasons.
And besides, I actually really do think
Amunet can help us
and help me with
my Killer Frost problem.
Well, how exactly can she help you?
Last year when I was having trouble
getting a handle on Killer Frost,
I went to her.
She used a black market
piece of tech on me, a splicer,
helped me split Killer Frost.
So you're hoping
she still has this tech.
It worked before, it can work again.
Well, Caitlin, you gotta tell the team.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Damn.
- Somebody saw Molly's Game.
- Mm-hmm.
Hang on a second.
C.C.P.D.! This is an illegal operation.
Everybody out of the room.
Leslie.
Caity.
Leave it to your crafty little brain
to figure out my dark secret.
What are you doing here?
Calling your bluff.
I knew you were still alive.
No one could kill me.
What's with the accent?
It's part of my disguise.
Had to blend in.
Now I'm just your average American
blonde making an honest living.
Well,
a more honest living, yeah?
Besides, you know what they say,
"A zebra never changes it's stripes."
Flash.
Oh! Flash.
You really do stop all the crime
in the city, don't you?
But not today.
I'm not here to fight.
We need your help.
Oh, look, a little hidey-hole
for your outfit.
Hi, excuse me.
You don't seem too concerned
that DeVoe is about to launch
a bunch of satellites into space
that are going to reset
all of our brains.
Oh, no, my dear.
I find it very troubling.
The professor turning everyone
in the world into a dimwit
is tragic.
It's brilliant, but tragic.
So, will you work with us?
Help us stop DeVoe?
Just...
That thing...
Why do you still have it on?
My...
It helps me protect my identity.
No, it's doing
a terrible job.
What?
Yeah, you see that stoic jaw line,
patrician profile.
You're so obviously the speedster
I tried to procure
from the Warden.
May he RIP.
Come on.
Yeah, I'm doing it.
- Hello, handsome.
- Hello.
To think I had the Flash in my grasp.
What a pretty penny I could have
gotten for that sale.
- Amunet.
- Yes?
Focus.
Okay, so...
On the one hand,
I am more dictator than team player.
But on the other,
Professor DeVoe stupefying the planet
would be bad for business.
So, I'll do it.
Unfortunately, there is a but.
There usually is one.
You see, in life I have found
that bigger isn't always better.
But in this case...
You need more shards to take out
something the size of a satellite.
So where'd you get those?
From the plane I was on the night
the particle accelerator exploded.
They were in the cargo bay
en route to a military facility.
Which conveniently never made it
to its final destination.
You see, normally I would just
pop down to my storage locker
to grab my big job stash.
But last week, a naughty boy
or girl
or non-binary gendered individual
snuck in and robbed the place.
Well, we should check out
your storage unit.
There might still be some clues.
I think I have an old CSI kit
back at the apartment.
Great. You guys are so good.
Um, sorry, excuse me, um,
where, where are you going?
Um, to the kitchen for a spot of tea.
Why don't I take you?
Mm... Boy.
Oh! You prepare food in here?
It's not very sanitary.
I wanted to talk to you alone.
I didn't just bring you here
to help us stop DeVoe.
An ulterior motive.
How furtive and apropos.
After all, why go through
all the hassle of procuring me
when Killer Frost could quite easily
just ice blast those satellites down.
Killer Frost is gone.
I haven't been able to get her to appear
ever since DeVoe used
one of his powers on her.
Remember last year when I came to you
because Killer Frost was taking over?
You fixed me.
My trans-modular genetic splicer.
I need to use that splicer again.
Caity.
One of the reasons why I was so
willing to help you and your friends
with your professor situation
is because, well, quite literally,
it also benefits me.
But giving you my splicer,
not as beneficial.
What if I make you a deal?
You give me the splicer,
Killer Frost and I
will do you one favor.
Oh, that is a tempting offer.
But unfortunately,
my splicer was stashed
right alongside my additional shards.
In your ransacked storage unit.
Okay, wherever we find your shards,
we should also find the splicer.
- Ding, ding, ding.
- So, do we have a deal?
You'll give me the splicer
as soon as we recover it?
I'll even tie a little bow on it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
hang on to your wigs and keys.
Here we go. Harry, turn to him,
the guy who must be Cisco,
express yourself.
Yes, it's best you commence with
"I feel" statements.
Like, "I feel a yearning."
Or "I feel aroused."
Okay...
How is this gonna make me
smarter than DeVoe?
Hey! Again with DeVoe.
Why are you so hung up on this mamaluke?
I think that DeVoe for you,
this is a guy that has,
well, he is like a leech upon you.
Sucking and sucking and sucking
and sucking and sucking.
And all you are left with is doubt.
I like that.
Nature, red in tooth and claw.
You know, they say to understand
a man's actions,
you gotta understand his heart.
Okay, question.
How do you understand the heart
of a deranged maniac?
The guy who must be Cisco
makes a good point here.
Let's all close our eyes
and take a moment
to imagine we are all sociopaths
trying to conquer the world.
Ah, yes.
What is...
Oh, mais, Harry.
Go on, allez,
put yourself in DeVoe's shoes.
Close your eyes, Harry.
Now, what do you see?
What do you smell?
How'd he feel?
Dumb. Dumb.
This is not making me any smarter.
But aren't you smarter, Harry?
You must channel your aggression
into love.
I feel like you're mocking me.
Oh, an "I feel" statement.
Winner. Winner.
All right. All right.
Progress, on that note...
Wait, wait. We're not done here, are we?
- Yeah. Yeah. We're done.
- Yeah, we're done.
Oui. C'est fini.
No. No. No. Nothing's fini.
Now, Harry.
You know what they say about
all work and no play.
Leaves no time for making whoopee.
And there he goes.
Look, H.P., come on. We're not...
We haven't done anything.
Non, non, mon frere. Desole, huh?
Parting, such sweet sorrow,
but I must bid you adieu.
Harry, from Earth-2, adieu.
Harry, everything you need,
you got it right in there.
Remember, you're unbelievable.
Ramon, remind me again.
What... what's another word for "huge"?
Colossal.
Colossal. Great. Thank you.
This was a colossal waste of time!
Here we are.
This is where you kept
your stash?
Well, I got something.
Some kind of substance on the lock pin.
Looks like they applied it
to break the door open.
Young man, David Caruso's
got nothing on you.
Nice.
What is it?
Acid? Cyanide?
Oh, oh! Is it anthrax?
Hematoxic venom.
That grotty, mangy, plug-ugly brat
dare betray me?
I take it she knows who did this.
Yup, and so do you.
Norvok.
And I guarantee that snake for brains
will suffer.
If Norvok thinks he can steal from me
and get away with it,
he's got another thing coming.
I can't believe this is happening.
Satellite's not picking up
any of your alnico metal
anywhere in the city.
Norvok may be a moron,
but he's not stupid enough
to keep the stash out in the open.
Hey, did you find anything?
Nope. Norvok and the boxers weren't
there at the ring anymore.
Of course not.
Because you and your gang of heroes
tipped him off that something was up.
Have you expanded the satellites
beyond Central City?
Yeah.
What about trying facial recognition?
Yes, of course.
And what about a geological scan
of the metal signature like last time
or having Cisco run another algorithm
to check the electromagnetic fields
in the city?
Yes, Caitlin. I've done all that.
I've run all the tests.
Bit testy with that, Frost, just...
We're doing everything we can,
all right?
We're gonna find Norvok and the shards.
Caitlin.
Is this about her stolen shards
or her tech?
What? What tech?
Amunet has splicer technology
that she used to split
Killer Frost last year.
I was hoping to use it again
to get Killer Frost to come out,
but it was hidden with her metal
shards in the storage container.
Why wouldn't
you tell us that?
Because I made Amunet a deal.
If she helped me, Killer Frost would
do another job for her.
Well, that splicer tech
isn't your only hope.
Yes, it is, Joe.
I have tried everything that
I can think of
to get Killer Frost to appear,
and that was my last shot.
So, now she's gone for good.
Those weirdos
with their feelings.
I'm done talking about my feelings.
What's your problem?
No. It just looked like
you were gonna...
What is this?
What are you doing?
I am cleaning up my workstation
'cause I'm not gonna need it anymore
since I'm not getting
my intelligence back.
You don't know that.
I don't know that?
Oh, I don't know that?
Ramon, what's done is done.
You spent all this time bringing
this council together
when your time should have been used
helping the team.
I wasted your valuable time,
and for that I apologize.
What are you... What?
Did I spill some soup on me?
No, no, no. It's just... That was...
That was very real.
It's like a very, very genuine apology.
Well, I meant it.
I can tell. There's no snark,
you're not throwing anything.
Right. I'm not. Hmm.
The Council might not have
helped your intelligence,
but I think they might have shown you
a little empathy.
You know, DA Cecile Horton said
there's other ways to be intelligent.
"Open your hearts.
- "Open your mind".
It's been so long since I've been
concerned for other people's feelings
that you know...
You know what?
Maybe it is time I considered
someone else's feelings.
- Well, I feel...
- DeVoe.
- Right?
Maybe the Council had a point.
And the best way for me
to understand DeVoe,
put myself in his shoes.
- Yeah.
- Is that what you were going to say?
No, I was going to say DeVoe.
- Okay.
- That, that makes sense.
- It does.
- Yeah.
Hey, anything on Norvok?
No, but I do have an update on DeVoe.
It's my finished article.
Barry, look, I'm just as anxious
as you are about DeVoe,
but I really think that we need to
arm the citizens with information,
not shield them from it.
Iris, I mean, I... I'm just...
I'm trying to do what's best
for the city and the team.
And look,
I think that telling the truth
is what's best.
I mean, if we give them
all the facts to consider
they will do the right thing.
How can you be sure about that?
Look, Barry.
I can't deny that you've had
a tough year with DeVoe,
but his entire goal is to take
information away from people.
If we don't publish this article,
we are no better than he is.
All right. I just... This is...
I think it's too risky.
I know that's how you feel.
And I really want us to be
on the same page.
So, it's your decision.
- Iris...
- I just want you to remember
that the Flash is a beacon of hope
that the people have
always put their faith in.
And now it's time for the Flash
to put his faith in the people.
Ah, there you are.
I couldn't help but notice
your anger and hostility.
Thought your color was blue, not red.
Yes, I'm angry. I've been angry
for weeks and still no Killer Frost.
And now, Norvok's ruined everything.
Oh, Caity.
I hate to see you so torn up like this.
So, I'm going to tell you something
that will cheer you up.
That splicer did not cure you.
- What?
- Well...
You'd come to me so broken,
so needy,
and so I put that piece of tech
on your head and...
Poof, nothing.
It did not work on you.
So you decided to lie to me
rather than tell me that?
Mmm.
But just because the splicer
didn't technically work
doesn't mean that the results
were not the same.
How? That doesn't make any sense.
You're the doctor, you tell me.
It's a placebo.
You see,
it's been inside you the entire time.
Caity, your power is unlike anything
I have ever seen before,
and no science kit or placebo
is going to explain why you...
Hmm.
A placebo.
A fake.
What are you talking about?
I know exactly where Norvok is.
We were surprised to get the call.
Shouldn't be. I'm running things now.
Amunet's gone.
But she did leave behind
something very valuable.
Thirty times stronger than steel.
You can assemble them
in any shape you like
and, best of all,
they're loaded with enough
potential energy to flatten a city.
We know where Norvok is.
Just when I though I'd considered
every option
for where Norvok might be skulking,
I remembered.
Whenever the fuzz used to be
on to one of our deals,
I would plant a rumor that it was
going down at a false location.
A fakeout to keep the "fuzz"
off your tracks.
Mmm.
So, that's where we think
that Norvok is.
In the abandoned Randall sub-station.
Underground. That's why the shards
weren't registering on the satellite.
Why don't the three of us
go get your shards.
Then we'll be armed and ready
to take out DeVoe's satellites.
I'm coming, too. I'll get the cold gun.
Oh, goody, a group foray.
Dibs on cashing in Norvok's chips.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- No killing.
- That was not a stipulation
when I agreed to join this crew.
Okay, Amunet, look.
I... I know how you usually work,
but I can handle this fast
and without any casualties.
Okay.
It is a bit time-consuming to remove
blood from metal.
This deal's off.
Those shards belong to Amunet.
Well, if that decrepit hag
didn't want them stolen,
she shouldn't have told me
where she hid them.
Decrepit?
That's a big word for such a small man.
Amunet, I've got this.
There are some things that a woman
just cannot delegate.
We agreed no killing.
That'll make this next part easy.
Joe, the shards are in there.
We can't let them get away.
Barry, what's going on? Your vitals
are going through the roof.
Venom.
I think the venom in Amunet's locker.
I'm on it.
You are just as vile
as that thing in your head.
Took a while to get this made.
Now you can't use those things
against me anymore.
You always underestimated me.
Caitlin, get back. Go, go, go.
Over here.
Iris?
Barry, there is no antidote for
meta-human venom that potent.
You're gonna have to phase through it
now before it gets to your heart.
Mmm.
I'm running out of ammo.
I think they'll hit me
before I hit them with this.
We're looking at this
from the wrong direction.
What? What are you doing?
Nice.
I've never understood your superpower.
Are you a man with a snake
or a snake with a man?
Amunet, don't kill him.
He's more than earned it.
It's not about him, it's about you.
Caitlin.
Amunet, there is a good part of you.
I truly believe that.
But the snake has got to go.
Like Norvok, I must be on my way.
Amunet, no. Hey.
You leave, there's no way
we can stop DeVoe's satellite.
She was never gonna help us.
She just wanted her metal.
Oh, truthfully, I did consider it.
I did, but a good player knows
when to fold.
And the professor certainly has
a better hand, so...
Don't try to stop me.
After all, I am packing.
There is nowhere you can go that
DeVoe's satellites won't reach you.
If you leave now, you'll be
mind melted just like the rest of us.
Good point.
Just for the record,
this is not me helping.
It is entirely self-preservation.
Filled with shrapnel and bound with
my meta-human je ne sais quoi.
Pull a shard, throw it,
it will deliver
one savage concussive blow.
But you only get one shot.
I know you won't waste it.
Go save the world, my darling.
And she's gone.
At least she didn't
leave us empty-handed.
Eye snakes.
Why did it have to be eye snakes?
Trust me, man.
It wasn't as cool as it sounds.
Guys, I'm sorry I got so worked up
with Amunet around.
It's okay.
Yeah, and Amunet did give us
the alnico metal projectile bomb.
I still think it's our best bet
at stopping DeVoe.
We just need to figure out
how to fire it.
- Yeah.
- Cisco, can you breach that thing?
Me? No way. My energy field
can't even reach outer space.
Okay, well we need to find
another solution
and we need to find it before
DeVoe launches those satellites.
Well, actually, thanks to Ramon
and the Council of Harrisons,
we may have an idea
about why DeVoe has not yet
launched his satellites.
He put himself in DeVoe's shoes.
Yeah, I thought,
"Well, if I was this ultra genius
"moving around in a floating chair,
how would I feel?"
You'd feel nothing.
You'd be sociopathic.
Right, but to me,
I wouldn't consider myself sociopathic.
Right now all my actions would be
driven by the one thing
that I care the most about. Right? And...
- So, if you're not acting...
- If I'm not acting,
then I don't have the one thing
that I care the most about.
My wife.
You guys need me
to walk you through this?
No, we... We get it, Harry.
It's kind of complicated but,
okay, I'll take your word.
Actually that took a lot out of me.
I'm gonna go have a nap.
Well, we can work with that idea.
Yeah, I will fire up the satellites,
see if I can find Marlize.
And I'll start figuring out
how to launch this
psychic dark matter-infused
metal shrapnel bomb.
No big deal.
Joe, do you want to get
a cup of coffee with me
before you go back to C.C.P.D.?
I could use some caffeine after today.
I know you don't get tired
of hearing it, but...
You were right.
Well, not about Amunet.
She still betrayed us.
But she knew the truth about DeVoe
and she ultimately made
a selfless decision to help us
by giving us the projectile.
And I do have faith
in Central City, Iris.
Because I know that at the core
of every citizen in this city
is something good.
And I know they'll feel the same way
when they read your article.
Let's tell the team.
Are you sure you wanna do this? You...
You want me to publish my article?
Without a doubt.
We're always stronger, better together.
Kiss me.
Thank you.
Uh-uh. This one's on me. I insist.
Nice. What did I do to deserve that?
That's for giving me the advice I needed
even when I didn't want to hear it.
Well, when you raise kids,
you get used to giving advice.
So...
I was convinced that
that splicer technology
was the key
to getting Killer Frost back.
But I was wrong.
The splicer was just a placebo,
and it tricked me into manifesting
those somatic results that I wanted.
You learned that from Amunet?
Mmm-hmm. I thought the answer
was in science,
but it was never gonna be there.
So what now?
I'm gonna take your advice.
I'm gonna look in
a completely different direction.
The key to finding Killer Frost
is not out there.
It's in here.
Iris, what's happening?
- Barry, it's the city.
- What?
I posted my article
and they're responding.
What do you mean? They believed you?
More than that. They wanna help. Look.
This guy says that he saw DeVoe
at Fifth and Knoll two days ago.
Yeah, and another guy
on Crescent and Tenth.
This is great.
Iris,
this means DeVoe can't
hide from us anymore.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::