BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
CISCO: We got Turtle locked up
in the pipeline.
All we got to do is use him to figure out
how to steal Zoom's speed.
That might take longer than we thought.
HARRISON: Why's that?
CAITLIN: Because Turtle's dead.
HARRISON: You need to figure out
what triggers your vibes.
CISCO: Sometimes it's when I touch
something that belongs to a breacher,
sometimes itjust happens.
There's always a cause.
BARRY: We're going to help you save Jesse.
What? You want me to leave everything
I have here? I mean, my life?
You don't have a life here anymore.
Zoom is too powerful.
Close it! Close it now!
(GRUNTS)
No!
Jay's death was not in vain.
We will meet Zoom again.
And the next time, I will beat him.
Whoever that monster is.
Whoo-hoo!
Uh... It didn't look this deep on the map.
That's 'cause maps are flat.
This is like 1,000 feet deep.
Well, you wanna get faster,
maybe plummeting to your death
is the motivation you need.
So, to reach escape velocity,
you're gonna have to go...
(EXHALES FORCEFU LLY)
That fast.
Well, that fast is impossible.
I can promise you that.
Uh-uh! Uh-uh!
"Nothing in life is promised
except death."
- Edgar Allen Poe?
- Kanye West.
If it makes you feel any better,
Evel Knievel cleared a line of cars
that was twice this long,
and he didn't even have super powers.
Ah, unless you count that sweet-ass ride.
- Do you hear yourself?
- Well, look,
you're gonna be fine. I'm 80% sure of it.
- Okay.
- 76.
Like, a strong 72. I can't stop.
Caitlin, help.
If you don't feel ready,
you probably shouldn't do it.
- Not helpful.
- Look, Zoom's still out there.
And once I find a way back to Earth-2,
I have to be faster than him.
And I mean, right now,
I wasn't even fast enough to save Jay.
I have to try.
(EXHALES)
He's going to make it.
- No.
- Oh, damn.
"Why'd you have to bring those drones
along, Cisco?"
"Oh, I don't know."
You're welcome, everyone.
(PANTING)
ANNOUNCER: Time projects include
releases of solo albums.
Pop music would never be the same
after Beyoncé left Destiny's Child.
Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
D0 they mean Senator Knowles?
- Scooch.
- What?
Oh, how'd it go?
Well, he's not a red splat
on the side of a mountain.
- That's our new definition of success?
- Lt's one of them.
- So, you didn't make the canyon jump?
- Nah-uh.
What else can we try?
A bigger canyon?
Okay, fine, no more canyons.
BARRY: I know I can crack this,
I've just been going about it wrong.
I need to find my leg up.
Have we factored in drag?
- Wells, can we re-run the simulation?
- Let it go for now.
Zoom's still out there.
He's terrorizing a whole world
full of people. Yourworld.
I'm not doing this for fun.
Barry, we've been working on this
all week.
You're tired. We're tired.
Yeah. What we need is some downtime.
Downtime leads to increased productivity,
ergo we have to have fun.
And the best way to have fun
is for us to go out to the club.
Am I right? Team Flash. Let's get turnt.
(BARRY CHUCKLES)
No, but seriously. We need a break.
CAITLIN: You know, I think Cisco's right.
And if I'm saying we need a break,
then you know it's serious.
All right then. Let's go out tonight.
Oh, yeah. Can I go?
Over my dead body.
Look, just 'cause you're stuck in this lab
all day doesn't mean I should be, too.
Over my rotting corpse.
Look, what happened to trying new things,
meeting new people?
You said
I should start a life here, right?
And Zoom's over there and we're over here.
So, there's nothing to worry about.
(SCOFFS) There's always
something to worry about.
Okay. Well, you said Barry and them are
good people and I should get to know them.
(SIGHS)
- I did.
- Yeah.
And you know they'll keep me safe,
no matter what.
Look, I have a life to live, Dad,
and a whole world to explore. Please?
Please?
- Fine.
- Yes.
But if you're gonna go,
you should take protection.
Oh, uh...
Dad, I don't need...
I don't know what you thought
I was gonna be doing, but I...
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Oh, right.
I mean, is it necessary?
It's kind of, you know...
Or I can always build you
an inescapable daughter cube.
Funny.
You know I'd get out, though, right?
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
All right, fine.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
(HEAVY BASS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Oh, God, sorry. It keeps doing that.
My dad made me wear it.
Don't worry about it. It's all good.
I'm really glad you came, Jesse.
Even though this place is less than ideal.
Hey. Toast?
To Jay.
I wonder what Jay would say
if he was here right now.
"What's a Kamikaze?" And then you'd spend
10 minutes explaining it.
And he'd say, "Just kidding,
we have those on Earth-2."
Yeah, well, we don't have those, so...
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, uh-uh! I'm sorry, Miss Underage.
None of us plan on getting murdered
by your father tonight.
- Oh, whatever, he's all talk.
- BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
- Yo, guys, what's up?
- Hey.
Glad you could make it.
- What's up, Wally?
- Hey.
Interesting choice of venue.
- The tic-tac-toe theme is cool.
- Barry picked it.
CISCO: For real?
Yeah, I picked it. I don't go out much.
It had four stars on Yelp, so...
- Okay, fair enough.
- So, who's this?
This is Wally. He's my...
Foster...
Step, adopted...
This is Wall... He's my new friend.
This is Jesse.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
So, Jesse, are you new in town?
Uh, yeah. You could say that.
Yeah. Me, too. Are you from far away?
Like you wouldn't believe.
- (ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
- Oh, uh...
You know what? Would you just excuse me?
Uh, I Just need to go powder my watch.
(clsco CHUCKLES)
Hey, so I know
I'm practically your brother
and I'm, like, half Jay's size, but uh...
- You wanna dance?
- Sure.
Come on. Let's go.
(JESSE GROANING)
Stupid watch.
All right, buddy,
you have beeped your last beep.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
HARRISON: (THROUGH WATCH)
Something else rising also.
Some dark instinct
about what I would do to the person
who had taken you.
The things I would do...
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
So, how's Wally doing?
Yeah, he's good.
He's just diving into his schoolwork.
- Good. I'm glad.
- Yeah.
Oh, God.
(BARRY CHUCKLES)
Promise me, if we ever do get married,
you will not do that dance at our wedding.
- Oh, I can promise you that.
- (CHUCKLES)
Not the wedding, the dancing.
What?
I don't know. I Just think it's weird
that we're married in the future
and on Earth-2.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
I wonder what our married doppelgangers
are doing tonight?
Probably Earth-2's equivalent
of Netflix and chill.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Sounds nice. I mean, for them.
(WHIZZING)
- Who was it?
- It was the Flash.
My wallet's gone.
Someone took my purse.
(ELECTRICITY SPARKI NG)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
And who the hell are you?
JOE: Okay, I got it. Thanks, man.
- Hey. Excuse me.
- BARRY: Hey.
What happened last night?
I know you didn't rob these people.
No, I was bored.
Just thought I'd have some fun.
Well, look, whoever did this,
they got everyone within a 10-block radius
in under six minutes.
You couldn't catch him?
No, this speedster's faster than me,
I guess.
Unbelievable. Hey, babe.
Hey, so I spoke to that girl over there.
She snapped a photo of the red blur.
- Look familiar?
- This is not good.
I know. It looks exactly like the photo
I took of you last year.
Don't worry, we'll figure it out.
We always do.
- (CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- Hey.
Oh, it's work. I gotta go.
Keep me posted, okay?
Yeah.
Joe, I don't want people thinking
the Flash is a petty thief.
Well, we need to get to work
squashing those rumors before they spread.
Here it is, people.
Evidence that the Flash has gone rogue.
Couldn't it be
the speedster in the helmet?
The photo speaks for itself,
no helmet glare,
confirming that
this is the Scarlet Speedster.
We're going to expose him as a fraud.
McKay, lwant you
at the police department,
getting any interview you can.
- Okay, on it.
- Williams,
eye-witness encounters.
The people of this city
need to know what it feels like
to be robbed by a hero.
West. I want you to do a piece on it.
From your perspective. You were there
last night, and you've seen him in action.
Okay, but why would the Flash need to
make off with a couple of hundred bucks
when he's saved so many lives?
I mean, he is, actually, a hero.
Iris, you're a smart woman.
You can't be that naive.
We live in a city full of meta-humans
who continually do whatever they want.
The Flash included.
Write it up.
His journey from streak to freak.
Due on my desk tomorrow.
So, fun night?
Before all the chaos broke loose?
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
HARRISON: (THROUGH WATCH)
That I would do anything to get you back.
Including killing a man.
Tell me I'm not hearing this right.
No, that's true.
Zoom had you.
Zoom needed the Flash's speed.
And it was him or you.
And I was not going to lose you.
You know, you were my hero.
My dad, the brilliant scientist,
who could accomplish anything
he put his mind to.
Who taught me I could never dream too big.
But now?
Now you're a killer.
- And I barely recognize you at all.
- Jesse...
No, no, no, don't.
Don't worry, I'm not going far.
BARRY: And where did this speedster
even come from?
I don't know, man.
All I know is, that blur made
60 smackaroos off of me.
Ridiculous.
Maybe it's another one of
Zoom's henchmen somehow?
The breaches are closed.
The only other way to become a speedster's
from a particle accelerator explosion.
Okay, but then why only
make yourself known now?
You see what I'm saying? We would've
had to seen them in action before.
I'm not saying it makes sense.
I'm just saying,
that's the only other way
to become a speedster.
Actually, there's another way.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
It's called Velocity-Nine.
Ooh, it's a sexy-ass name. What is it?
It's a speed drug.
Jay took it when you were on Earth-2
to save the city from a meta-human.
What?
- How could you not tell me this?
- I promised Jay I wouldn't.
Jay? What do you... Why?
Because Jay knew
how dangerous this drug is.
I should know, Barry.
Snow and I worked on it together.
Guys, I've been busting my butt out there,
pushing myself to the limit,
trying to get better, trying to be faster,
and you're telling me
That there's been something
this whole time that could've helped me?
This could've helped me take down Zoom.
It could've helped me save Earth-2 Joe.
- Save Jay.
- Jay was sick.
The drug he took to regain his speed
was also causing cellular degeneration.
It was killing him.
I tried to help. I tried to find a cure.
But in all my experiments,
the effects were just temporary.
The V-Nine is deadly.
Why not tell me this?
Why keep me in the dark?
Caitlin...
(WHIRRING)
Where am I?
(GASPS)
- Are you okay?
- Did you vibe?
CISCO: Uh...
(ALARM RINGING)
Meta-human.
Yeah. Social media app for the win.
Bad Flash is back.
Bad Flash.
Ugh, what? No. Losing my touch over here.
He's coming up on Fifth and Everett.
You can use the alley to cut him off.
(GRUNTING)
(SCOFFS) A lady speedster.
It only took us two years,
but we finally got one.
A lady speedster.
Hey, here's a question for you.
Purely scientific. Was she good looking?
(JOE CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I was a little busy
getting my ass handed to me,
- so I didn't really notice.
- Right, right, right.
But you know, next time, for science?
Okay, yeah.
Next time she punches me in the face,
- I'll be sure to get her number.
- There you go.
But the question remains, who is she?
(GRUNTS) I have no idea.
We could run her
through the facial recognition.
- She had a mask on.
- What was her suit like?
- Hey.
- Hey, it's a valid question.
It is, actually.
How was her suit constructed?
I, uh... lt was good. lt was very good.
It was like mine. It was made by somebody
who understands the needs of a speedster.
So, that would be someone
with access to tech and a lab.
Oh, no, I'm having a very bad thought.
(TYPING)
When I designed V-Nine,
I was having trouble
reformatting the extracellular matrix.
So, I called a colleague of mine
at Mercury Labs for some assistance.
Eliza Harmon.
She knows how to make this speed drug?
No. I followed the protocols
of information compartmentalization.
I only gave her
three of the eight components
necessary for V-Nine's structure.
Okay, so she didn't have the full recipe?
Unless she reverse engineered
her own V-Nine.
Eliza's a genius.
But that's way out of character for her.
- Well, it's worth taking a look.
- I'll go see her.
Hey, I'm coming, too.
Great. I'm gonna go train.
(LIQUID BUBBLING)
Knock, knock.
Am I hallucinating or is that disgraced
ex-Mercury's employee, Caitlin Snow?
Eliza Harmon, burning the midnight oil.
Don't you ever take a break?
Well, you know what they say, these
thiocyanate ions won't bond themselves.
- Hi.
Who is your handsome friend?
Detective Joe West, ma'am.
Detective, what brings you around
these parts?
Well, it's a funny story.
You know how there's a speedster
that's been wreaking havoc on the city?
Yeah. I heard the Flash went nuts.
Fame will do it to you.
I guess some people
just can't handle the limelight, right?
Well, we happen to know
it was someone else.
That's why we're here looking into this.
Wow! How very Law & Order of you, Caitlin.
Do you remember that formula that you were
helping me with a few months ago?
- Uh, yeah, vaguely.
- We think that it was somehow involved.
How? What did you have me working on?
It's classified, but let's just say
it was some kind of enhancement.
And we're afraid
that my research was stolen.
Not from this lab?
Okay, uh, between you and me,
the place is pretty vulnerable.
Ever since that break-in a few months ago,
some of us think McGee
hasn't sufficiently stepped up security.
But I kept my research on lock
and destroyed the originals
when it was given back to you.
But, hey, you're free
to look around my lab if you want.
Uh, I don't think that'll be necessary.
I'm sorry. lwish I could be more help.
It's okay. It's actually kind of a relief.
Will you call me
if you hear anything, though?
Of course. That's what friends are for.
Thank you.
- So, what do you think?
- For now? We take her at her word.
West. How's your article coming?
Um, great.
I have a source who knows for a fact
that this speedster is not the Flash,
but an imposter.
Ah. Who's your source?
I am not at liberty to say.
Well, if you can't tell me your source,
I'm running the original story.
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
You're right. What's one unnamed source
compared to dozens of eye-witnesses.
Honestly, I'm having a hard time
wrapping my head
around your vision for this story.
Something isn't adding up.
How about we, um, talk about it some more?
Uh, grab some coffee, what do you say?
Coffee? Right now?
Yeah, yeah. I mean, a little caffeine
never hurt anybody, right?
Sure.
ELIZA: I'm so tired.
TRAJECTORY: (ECHOING) Well, you've been
pushing yourself too hard.
No, not hard enough.
I'm sick of always being passed over
for the grant, for the promotion.
I'm underpaid and understaffed
and six months behind on my research.
That's why I started all of this.
Your problem is
you're too much of a perfectionist.
You don't have to be.
There's beauty in chaos.
Okay, I don't have time for chaos.
This was supposed to fix things,
and it ended up making it worse.
Oh, silly girl.
You know it makes you feel better
to blow off some steam. (CHUCKLES)
You will say anything for a fix.
It's your fault we're hooked.
It's Caitlin 's fault.
If she didn't want us to find out
what she was working on,
she shouldn 't have made it so damn easy.
There's not enough for both of us.
We need to save it for an emergency.
You take it now.
Worry about getting more later.
You'll thank me.
(BREATH ES H EAVILY)
I know what's best for us
and where to get more.
Whatcha doing?
- Training.
Allen, don't be stupid.
I know you took the V-Nine, Allen.
- No, I haven't.
- Oh, no?
No. I took it. Butl haven't taken it yet.
- Good.
- Tell me why I shouldn't.
(SCOFFS) Figure it out.
If the game is already rigged,
why can't I level the playing field?
I mean, if everybody else is cheating,
how can...
I want to be fast enough to stop Zoom
and any speedster
that tries to hurt my friends.
Shouldn't I use everything in my power
to do that?
You wanna take a shortcut?
Is that right? You wanna take a shortcut?
Remember this, you lose
a chunk of your humanity every time
you compromise your values.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry.
That's really good coming from you.
So, don't be like me.
Be better.
Be like Jay.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah. I'm fine.
Hey, any luck locating our speedster,
since Eliza checked out?
Um, I'm still working on it, but...
(ELECTRICITY SPARKLI NG)
Hey!
(LAUGHS) Time to have some fun.
Hey! Cisco!
Hey, Joe!
Hey, she's got me in the pipeline!
(sum COCKING)
- What do you want?
- Where's the V-Nine, Caity? I need a fix.
Eliza, is that you?
Eliza's not here right now.
My name is Trajectory.
Oh, why do the crazy ones
always name themselves?
Look, Eliza, Velocity-Nine
is very dangerous, okay?
It made a friend of mine very sick.
And he already had the Speed Force in him.
- Look, your cellular...
- Enough.
You are boring me to death.
Hand over the V.
I'm a physician. I took an oath.
I can't give you anything
that will hurt you.
Right. So, either hand over the V
or the cat guy gets it.
No!
(GASPS)
Hey, move, now.
Look, all the flasks are gone.
There's nothing left.
(SIGHS)
Hey, I was really hoping
you wouldn't make me do one of those
"I have to kill you each, one by one,
until you give me what I want."
Oh, well.
- (JESSE WHIMPERS)
- Wait.
Wait.
You want V-Nine,
- we'll make it for you.
- Dad, you can't.
We have all the ingredients.
I'm not a patient person,
so better move fast.
Aw!
Ah, latte for me. And a Flash for you.
Wow, this guy even gets a drink
named after him.
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY) Yes, he does.
He saved a lot of people's lives.
They just want to show their appreciation.
A little too much if you ask me.
Why can't you see what everyone else sees?
(SCOFFS) A few years back,
I won the
Dornfeld Award for Investigative Reporting
for my story
on corruption in the mayor's office.
I investigated a man that everyone loved.
The mayor was young, telegenic,
a former war hero.
(STUTTERS) He was voted in with
overwhelming popular support. It was...
But I knew that his campaign was
bought and paid for by the mob.
Okay, but not everyone is a corrupt mayor.
But I saw him for what everyone else
was too blind to see.
Everyone wants a hero.
Yeah, but in this case the Flash
actually is one.
Iris, Iris, it's our job to...
To ensure that people, even heroes,
are held accountable for their actions.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
So, I'm guessing,
on your list of dating pros and cons,
being anti-Flash is a major deal breaker.
Um, dating pros and...
Did you think that this...
Oh, what? No, no. No.
Forget what I said. I get it. You just...
Uh, wanted to talk about the...
Story some more... (SIGHS)
To stall.
Right? Because you're trying to get out of
writing this article altogether.
Scott, wait, please don't leave.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that this was...
Why would you? Excuse me.
This is what you wanted.
Now let her go.
How do I know the two of you didn't lace
this with a sedative to put me on my ass?
Wouldn't do that.
Hmm. Can never be too safe, right?
- No. (CRIES)
- No!
(SCOFFS) Thanks for the fix, Snow.
Get Barry. Are you okay?
(ALARM RINGING)
- Well, good job on the cell, Cisco.
- CAITLIN: Jesse.
- (GAGGING)
- BARRY: What happened?
- Turn her on her side.
- Eliza shot her up with V-Nine.
- She's going into shock. It's too pure.
- Stay with me, Jesse. Stay with me.
- What do we do?
- We got to get the V-Nine
- out of her system.
- CAITLIN: She needs a blood transfusion.
The new blood will flush
the drug out of her system.
- What blood type is she?
- P-Zee negative.
Yeah, that's not a thing
on this Earth, man.
I'm a match.
Jesse.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey.
What happened?
We... You're fine. Your... (CLEARS THROAT)
You're going to be fine.
We got the drug out of your system.
Oh...
Looks like you saved the day again.
Look, honey,
I know that this isn't enough.
I promise you, though, I am...
I'm going to spend the rest of my life
making it up to you for the...
For that terrible thing that I did.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
And how many more terrible things
are you going to do to protect me?
What does that mean?
I mean, everything that you do
and everything that you have done for me,
it's so dark, and you don't even see it.
I mean,
you didn't even hesitate out there.
(STAMMERS) Of course not,
I'm not going to lose you, Jesse.
Okay, but you just gave that
crazy speedster everything she wanted,
without even blinking.
Without even thinking
what other lives could be at stake.
It's myjob to keep you safe,
to protect you.
That's myjob. That's all that matters.
Well, maybe it shouldn't be. (SIGHS)
Caitlin, I know she was your friend
and all,
but, uh, home-girl has gone cuckoo bird.
And now she's out there with more V-Nine.
What she doesn't know
is I put a micro-tracker in the drug.
Mmm, that's a brilliant idea.
You can run, but you can't hide.
I'm the one to blame for all of this,
so I need to help fix it.
(SIGHS) There's plenty of blame to
go around, Snow. What's her location?
- CISCO: Central City bridge.
- Why is she running back and forth?
Villains gonna vill.
- She's creating friction.
- At that vibration and speed...
- What?
- Complete chaos.
She could destroy that whole bridge.
And everyone on it.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(RUMBLING)
Guys, this bridge is coming down.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
Barry, there's about 200 people
on that bridge right now.
Okay.
(GRUNTS) You're ruining all my fun.
No.
Trajectory is too far away. You won't get
to her running across the river.
I will if I jump.
Barry, to make that jump,
you'll need to go...
Mach 3.3. But only for a second.
Okay.
Yeah, buddy.
(TRAJ ECTO RY G ROAN S)
(BOTH GROAN I NG)
It's over, Eliza.
It is never over.
Wait, hey.
Stop doing this to yourself.
You don't actually want to hurt anyone.
You don't know anything about me.
No, I know you're not a bad person.
This is the V-Nine in your system.
(OVER SPEAKERS) I also know what it feels
like to want to be the best.
Makes you feel like there's not enough
time to accomplish things the right way,
but it's a cop-out.
And this is killing you.
Look at yourself, Eliza, you're not well.
(GASPS)
Let us help you, please.
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
That is all the help I need.
How does it feel to know
that I am faster than you will ever be?
- See you around.
- Her lightning...
It's turning blue.
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Your article was well written.
Thank you.
You know, it's a lot easier to write
when it's the truth.
Not every hero is a fraud.
It's okay to believe in them.
So I've been told.
And sometimes, even greatjournalists,
smart and brilliantjournalists,
can misread situations.
And sometimes,
they can be caught off guard.
Look, about the other night,
itjust surprised me,
but once the surprise went away...
Not a deal breaker.
(CHUCKLES)
Noted.
- Hey, have you seen Jesse?
- No.
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
JESSE: (THROUGH WATCH) Hey, Dad.
It's me.
Listen.
Your job over the years
has been to shield me from harm.
But now, it's my turn to go out
into this new world on my own,
no shield,
and discover what this Earth can offer.
You know,
you are the best teacher I've ever had,
but I don't know
what more you can teach me.
Ilove you.
Please don't come looking for me.
So, Eliza just evaporated?
From running too fast?
It looks like cellular degeneration.
The same as Jay's.
Jay warned us V-Nine was dangerous.
At least now, we know why.
- You find Jesse?
- She went out.
IRIS: Barry, what is it?
Just right before Eliza
disappeared, her lightning,
it turned blue.
Right.
But what if it's a side effect
of the V-Nine?
Yeah, but Jay took Velocity-Nine
and his lightning didn't turn blue.
But how fast was he running?
Not as fast as Eliza.
All right, so what if V-Nine
is what turns your lightning blue?
I mean, that would explain why
Zoom is so much faster than me.
If that's true,
then that means he's sick, right?
He's dying.
That's why he wants your speed.
He's dying and he needs a cure.
Same as Jay.
No.
Jay? No.
He died right in front of us.
Zoom killed him right in front of us.
Yeah, Cisco, we've seen a speedster
be in two places at once before.
I guess there's one way to find out.
I guess now would be a good time to
tell you all, I've been vibing Zoom.
What?
For how long?
It started when we closed the last breach.
And every time it's happened,
I've been near that thing.
(SIGHS)
We need to know.
No.
No, no.
Cisco? What did you see?
I saw Jay.
He's Zoom.
Barry!
(SCREAMS)