BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
DR. WELLS: Previously on The Flash...
You're just letting us go?
Just remember who it was made sure
you didn't get thrown on that plane.
I call it the "Wizard's Wand."
Captain Singh mentioned there
may be positions available
on your anti-meta-human
task force.
- Why do you want to do this?
- Mark Mardon killed my dad.
James Jesse, Your Honor,
AKA... the Trickster.
(CROWD GASPS)
You're going to prison
either way, James.
You stay away from me and
you stay away from my father.
If he finds out that he might have a son
that grew up without knowing him,
It would crush him.
Jesse's my daughter
and Zoom has her.
(CRACKLING)
(DISTORTED) You're next.
(GRUNTS)
Go ahead, kill me.
But my daughter is innocent.
Please.
Let Jesse live.
Go on!
Say something!
Merry Christmas.
- Fathwoom!
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
I had to fight
some old lady for the last one.
They didn't have
any Green Arrow dolls.
Don't know why you'd want a toy of that crazy
man. I can't figure out what to get Barry.
I was thinking you could give him this.
Oh, that's nice.
But I kind of want to get him
something more meaningful.
I mean, it's been a strange,
emotional 12 months.
Yeah. You don't have to tell me.
I know, babe. I miss Eddie, too.
How about you get Barry
uh, a really nice watch?
Like Grandpa Ben gave to you.
That ain't a bad idea.
You know, my dad only gave me
this watch because I was always late.
- You? (CHUCKLES)
- Yeah.
He always gave a gift
with a not-so-hidden message,
like this watch,
or the time he bought me free weights
because he said
I was too skinny.
I told him, "When I have a son,
I'm only giving him fun presents."
And this thing barely works.
Don't know why I still wear it.
Because it's from family.
You sure you're all right?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, yeah, I promise.
(KISSING)
You know, we should really be
more professional.
- You do realize you initiated that.
- (CHUCKLES)
Yes, and I'm fully prepared
to reprimand myself then.
I'm just saying, you know, anyone
could walk in like, Joe, or Captain...
- Yo.
- (CHUCKLES)
- But I... I have, like, a 4:00 to 12:00.
- Yep.
- But I'll call... I'll see you later.
- All right.
- I'll see you at Christmas.
- Yeah. Okay, bye.
I'm so happy for you.
Truly.
Thank you. I...
It means a lot to me that you like her.
(SIGHS) I don't know, it's...
Wells, um...
He left me that message where he said
that I'd never really be happy.
And for a while I really started
to believe him, but now...
I don't know. Maybe there is a way that...
Are you okay? What's wrong?
(WEEPING) I'm so sorry.
I can't keep this in anymore, Barry.
What?
I know I was so mad at you and Dad
for not telling me that you were The Flash,
But when I found out about this,
I didn't know what to do.
What? What's going on? What's...
When Francine came back,
my Dad told me not to trust her
and he was right.
I didn't know how much.
When my mother left us, she was pregnant.
She had a son.
Joe's son. My brother.
What's his name?
Wally.
Wally West.
When I found out, I told her to leave
and then never come back,
and to never tell my dad.
But Barry, I feel... I feel like
this is hollowing me out.
Every time I look at Dad, I feel like
I'm hurting him. I don't know what to do.
I think you know what you have to do.
I can't. It's gonna kill him.
No, it won't.
You don't have to do this alone.
We can tell him together.
Thank you. (SIGHS)
Yeah.
Hey, look. Snow.
Maybe it'll be a white Christmas.
That'd be nice.
I was just thinking that if we could
inject an unstable neutrino burst
into the individual breaches,
it might cause them
to seal on their own.
And stop Zoom from travelling back
and forth between our worlds.
At least then,
we wouldn't have to worry about him
sending any more meta-humans
over for Barry to fight.
- It means a lot.
- What does?
You looking after Barry. He's been
through a lot the last few weeks.
Barry's not the only person here
I want to keep safe.
Oh, dear Lord.
Just kiss already. Oh, the thirst is real.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I keep checking, but all
is quiet on the meta-human front.
Hey, you think Zoom
decided to take Christmas off?
What's Christmas?
Oh, well, it's this holiday we have
where we cut down trees and sing songs
To celebrate the birth of a baby
2,000 years ago,
and then the Romans killed him,
so we give each other gifts.
That's your explanation?
- I know what Christmas is.
- Oh, right. Of course.
Um, you know, Joe and Barry and Iris
are having people over for Christmas Eve.
And they said we could
invite whoever we want.
Who, who do you want?
You.
I want to invite you, I mean.
This is so painful.
Have you guys seen Harry?
Uh, no, I have not.
I told him to rest.
He's just as stubborn as all the rest
of my male patients in this place.
I'm gonna leave you two alone, okay?
I'm gonna go find Harry.
Holy Hannah. Hi.
Hi.
- Everything okay?
- Sure.
Why wouldn't it be?
(CHUCKLES) Why wouldn't it be?
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(RATTLING)
Man, it's really coming down.
The news didn't say anything about snow.
Maybe it's a Christmas miracle.
(GRUNTS)
Let it snow.
We are... (GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Knock, knock.
So, early parole.
You interested?
Don't mean to be a noodge,
but the exit is upstairs.
Just need one more thing.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
It's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas.
(LAUGHING)
Please tell me this is not happening.
It's official, Santa hates us.
This sudden blizzard took out
cameras and the security system.
I mean, thank God nobody was killed
but there's no trace
of Mardon, Jesse, or Snart.
Uh, speaking of which,
with Mardon back on the scene...
- Yeah?
- Patty might not be thinking so clearly.
What do you mean?
What does Mardon have to do with Patty?
We should have expected this.
The unexpected drop in barometric pressure
had to mean Mardon's back in town.
- Patty...
- Jesse was on full communication lockdown
but that doesn't mean Mardon
and Snart weren't in contact.
Patty, Joe told me about Mardon.
(CHUCKLES)
I can't talk to you about this.
Hey, Patty, it's okay.
I got it.
Look, Barry, you're a really sweet guy,
but you have no idea what's
really going on in this city.
I mean, you don't even
know that Harrison Wells...
I'm sorry, I don't have time
to bring you up to speed.
That's ironic. Patty, Patty,
look, I care about you a lot.
I don't want to see
you do anything reckless.
I'm a cop. Going after
criminals is in my job description.
It's not reckless.
And powers or not, Mardon's
gonna answer for what he's done.
Patty...
Deck the halls with body parts
from a girl named Holly
(VOCALIZING)
I don't remember those being the lyrics.
Oh, I am tremendously creative.
That, I can tell you.
You better be. I didn't break you out,
I didn't break either of you out because,
I was looking to make new friends.
That is not the holiday spirit,
Marky-Mark.
Christmas is a time for togetherness.
And what says togetherness
more than mass graves?
- Hmm?
- So why did you break us out?
Well, I owed you one.
And this guy, he's just crazy.
That's a compliment.
And we all want the same thing.
Fashion advice?
To see The Flash dead.
Well, that was more of a
New Years resolution,
but, hey, I'm flexible.
That hasn't gone so well
for anyone in this room.
What makes you think
you can stop him this time?
Three against one. Plus,
the one isn't quite what he was.
See, another speedster,
dressed all in black,
nearly took him out a few weeks ago.
He's vulnerable. He's weak.
It's a mistake
to underestimate him.
No. With my power, his flair,
and your smarts,
we can put him in the ground for good.
- Tell me your plan.
- Tell me you're in.
I'm thinking about it.
What's the matter?
A few months in the clink
make you soft, did it, Snart?
- You wanna dance?
- Boys, boys, boys, play nice.
Mellow out, Mardon.
Don't have a snit, Snart.
Here's an idea.
We all go out, have a few drinks,
kill some carolers. We'll all feel better.
All right.
So what's it gonna be, Snart?
(CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah. Weather Wizard,
Captain Cold, and the Trickster.
There's three of them and one of you.
I do not like those odds.
And I'm gonna be no help
without my speed, so...
Oh, Oh, light bulb, up here.
I have an idea.
Most weather phenomena are marked,
no pun intended,
by a change in electric charge
and pressure in the atmosphere.
We could just map out
those fluctuations to...
To pinpoint his location.
Right, it would just be a matter
of removing all the electricity...
From his immediate surroundings.
Attracting it to one spot.
The same way
a lightning rod does.
Only instead of a lightning rod,
we could use...
A wand?
Have we already had this conversation?
- Kind of.
- What does that mean?
Uh...
All right.
So the last time Mardon attacked,
he, um, generated a tidal wave
that destroyed all of Central City.
So, why are you
not all sleeping with the fishes?
Earth-2 has "The Godfather"?
Every Earth has
"The Godfather," Vito.
So, I ran back through time.
One day into the past,
and I got a do over, and I stopped Mardon
before he could hurt anyone.
You shouldn't have
messed with the timeline.
That's what
the other Wells said.
So the good news is,
in that timeline,
you created The Wand
and it worked.
- For the first time.
- Yeah. No pressure.
I can give you a hand.
- Best of both worlds?
- I like that.
(BARRY CHUCKLES)
You good, Harry?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
Holiday blues? It can't be easy knowing
Zoom still has his daughter.
Yeah. All right, look, I'll be right back.
I have something I have to deal with.
Hey.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Okay, the last time the two of
you were looking at me like that,
Was when you both took
my convertible on a joy ride
and wrapped it around that
big oak tree on Fairmont Drive.
Dad... (CLEARS THROAT)
All right, Joe, we have something
that we need to tell you...
No, um...
I have something that I need to tell you.
It's about Francine.
(SNIFFLING)
(CLEARS THROAT) When she left us,
she was pregnant.
(SIGHS)
Did she have the baby?
Yes.
His name is Wally.
Wally West.
It's short for Wallace.
That's what we were gonna name you
if you were a boy.
I only found out
a couple of weeks ago, Dad.
Dad, I am so sorry
that I didn't tell you sooner.
That's why she reached out to us
after all of these years.
She wanted us to know before...
- She...
- Before she died.
And I thought Francine
was running out of surprises.
I gotta get to work.
Dad, listen... Dad.
I'm sorry.
Just let me sit with it.
Do you think that he's gonna be okay?
I do, yeah, I think...
It's just a lot to take in.
He just needs a little time
to process it.
Ho-ho-ho.
Hmm.
Cocoa isn't cocoa without
the mini marshmallows.
And you're out. I checked.
Are you out of your mind,
breaking into my home?
Careful. Made an upgrade to the cold gun.
If I release my grip from the handle,
the core goes critical.
You might make it. She won't.
Read your article
on the disappearing middle class.
Strong point of view.
Nice prose style.
Yeah, well, who needs a Pulitzer
when you have a homicidal
maniac's seal of approval.
Didn't Barry tell you?
I had a rough childhood.
Everyone in this room had
a rough childhood. Get over it.
Why are you here, Snart?
I got the Noel spirit,
wanted to give you a gift.
Mardon broke Jesse and me out to kill you.
Jesse's on board, of course.
He's shaking with excitement.
Me, I'm gonna pass.
Why? You grow a conscience?
Mardon wants revenge.
Jesse wants chaos.
I'm just not invested like they are.
You mean there's no money
in it for you?
I was never much
for non-profit work.
If you're not in with them,
then tell me where they are.
Nah, consider me more
of a secret Santa.
Besides, you and your friends
love to solve a good mystery.
(CHUCKLES)
You are full of it, Snart.
I think my friends
and I saved your sister's life,
and you just can't stand
owing me a marker.
I hate to break it to you, but that...
that right there is called honor.
Go on. Make your pitch.
I can see you're dying to.
Help me stop them.
Sorry. I'm not interested in being a hero.
(SCOFFS)
Well, you're doing a pretty lousy job
of being a villain this week.
Merry Christmas, Barry.
Hey.
I was just thinking about a big drug bust
that me and Singh made about 10 years ago.
Afterward, we went for a steak lunch,
to treat ourselves for a job well done.
And while we were ordering,
I got this feeling in my chest.
Like my heart was being squeezed.
And I knew something wasn't right.
So I called your school
and the nurse said to me that
she was just about to call me.
Iris was on her way to the hospital.
When her appendix burst.
And I knew it.
I could feel it, right here.
I knew my kid needed me.
So, if I have that feeling as a parent,
why didn't I feel it for my son?
Joe, it's not your fault that
you didn't know about him.
Yeah, it was.
When Francine left rehab that last time,
I should've looked for her.
I'm a cop. I could've found her.
Brought her back here.
Tried again. Tried harder.
You were protecting Iris.
I've been telling
myself that for 20 years.
A 20-year lie. But I wasn't
protecting her. I was protecting myself.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
I couldn't...
I hated not being able to help Francine.
So it was easier
for her to be dead.
Out of my life. Out of our lives.
But it wasn't for Iris.
I was being selfish.
And that poor boy
paid the price.
Joe.
He never had a father
to read to him at night,
to show him how to throw a football,
to make him feel safe.
And loved.
Who taught him how to be a man, Barry?
"Him," I can't even say his name.
What have I done?
Joe, look,
you have been there for me
every day since I met you.
You have.
And...
You would've done the exact same thing
for him if you could've. I know it.
I'm sorry.
Where's your partner, Spivot?
I don't know,
I'm not his babysitter.
I'm sorry, sir. I'm not sure where Joe is.
Flashy the red-nosed Speedster
Had a very shiny suit
And if you ever saw him
You might even want to puke
(GRUNTS)
Merry Christmas, kiddywinks! I'm back.
Get TARU down here now.
I wanna know how he's doing this.
Citizens,
you know, the holidays can be a time
for gentle reflection on the year past,
our ups and downs,
our triumphs and heartaches,
but don't forget, they can also be a time
for disemboweling our enemies.
We don't have a Trickster on Earth-2.
He's one of a kind.
No, my stocking won't be
completely stuffed
until it's filled to the brim
with bloody Flash parts.
So what do you say, speed freak?
You want to roast chestnuts?
I want all tactical units on high alert.
Get in touch with other precincts.
I want watch commanders
coordinating deployment.
Spivot, I need you to... Spivot!
Are there any clues
as to where he is based on the video?
None that I can see.
Guys, there's a reflection
of something in his cornea. See?
What is that?
Not sure.
That's Mr. Jiggle Wiggle.
- Come again?
- It's a doll.
A stuffed children's toy. I gave one to
my daughter when she was six.
Mr. Jiggle Wiggle
was manufactured by Okamura Toys.
Yahtzee! Okamura once had
a shipping facility in Central City
That shut down four years ago.
It's been abandoned ever since.
What if Weather Wizard's there?
The wand's not finished.
Well, the Trickster is.
THE FLASH: What are you doing here?
Same thing as you.
Trying to catch a murderer.
JAMES: We can't let Christmas
hog all the holiday fun.
Happy Hanukkah!
Dreidel, dreidel, dreidel
I made you out of C-4!
(LAUGHING)
Put that in your pipe and smoke it.
I'm afraid we are definitely looking
at closed casket funerals. (CHUCKLES)
There's nowhere for me to run us to!
So what should we do?
Hold me.
I'm seeing someone.
Me too. Don't let go.
- Detective!
- It was all just a trap for you.
Mardon and Jesse aren't even here.
They're still on the loose.
How did you know to come here?
Because there was a reflection in
Jesse's eye of Mr. Jiggle Wiggle.
And that's the thing that my dad...
It doesn't even matter.
That's why you came here alone
without any backup?
Because of your father?
You don't know anything about me.
I know that
you're being reckless.
And I'm sure the people in you
life care enough about you
To not want to see you get hurt.
Except Mardon
didn't kill my father.
I did.
See, he had a little shoe shop,
and we didn't have any money,
so I worked there after school.
Except, one day,
I decided not to show up because...
because I was being stupid
and silly with my friends.
I didn't even call
to tell him that I was ditching.
So he brought
the deposits to the bank, not me.
He was shot and killed by Mardon, not me.
That's why you became a cop.
Joined the meta-human task force.
It'll be legal when I kill Mardon.
I have made my whole life about
getting justice for my father,
even if it meant I didn't have a life.
And now, I met a really great guy,
and that doesn't even feel real to me.
And I'm scared
he's gonna find out how angry I am.
I don't even know
why I'm telling you this.
Sometimes it's just easier to say
things to someone with no face.
Thank you for saving me.
You know, even if you get
this guy that wronged you,
It doesn't always make things better.
It has to be better than this.
(ENGINE STARTS)
BARRY: Patty, it's me again, uh...
I'd really love to talk.
I'm worried about you.
Anyway, just give me a call
when you get a chance, all right?
Thank you. Bye.
- Barry.
- Yeah?
How's it look?
- Eerily familiar.
- (CHUCKLES)
How's Patty?
She is, um,
hiding a lot of pain behind her smile.
They say couples start to resemble
each other after a little while.
The thing is, I mean,
she only opened up to Flash, not me.
So even if I could got her on the phone,
I don't know what to say.
Well,
it's been my experience that just
being around you can be a big help.
Thank you.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
lwant an iPhone, an iPad, and an iTouch.
(LAUGHING) Dial it back, Mr. Greedy.
Those are a little out
of Santa's price range.
How about this?
Now remember,
don't open it until tomorrow.
It's a surprise.
(LAUGHING)
Have you decided?
I need more time.
Don't we all. Decide.
Maybe if I go up there and kill
a few of your new friends...
No.
One more day.
I'll tell your daughter you said hello.
(BEEPING)
What's that? Is that Mardon?
That's definitely him.
Atmospheric pressure
just dropped 200 hectopascals.
- Where?
- Central City Square.
The tree lighting ceremony.
There's thousands
of people there.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Oh, glad to see you.
Maybe you can help me.
Help get back into a jail cell?
That'll be my pleasure, Mardon.
No. No. See, I'm trying to decide
if I should kill everybody down
there with a deadly hail storm or,
a little trickier, with acid rain.
What do you think?
Uh, let me think. How about neither?
You see this wand here? Guess what?
Um, guys? He's flying.
He can fly?
Since when can he fly?
Well, he's using his
powers to alter the air pressure
To create pockets of updraft that can...
No, he can fly.
Barry, get him!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
You didn't really think I'd let you hurt
all these people, did you?
No, of course not.
But I bet you're gonna let me hurt you.
(SCRAPING)
Feliz Navidad!
Time for a real war on Christmas.
(LAUGHING)
- What is this?
- That is a box with a bomb in it.
Yep. (SIGHS) I've handed out
about 100 of them today.
Oh, it feels so good to give.
You see, right now,
there are 100 random children.
They've each taken home a box,
just like that one,
and are shoving it
under their Christmas tree.
There's no way for you
to get to all of them,
even if you knew where to look.
No, no. Please don't do this.
What, me? Kill 100 families? No.
(CHUCKLES)
That's up to you.
I'm happy just to take your life.
So, this is how it's gonna be.
You are gonna stand there
and let me end you.
Very publicly, and very painfully.
- (LAUGHING)
- And I'll let everybody live.
But,
if I see even a little flicker
of electricity on you...
the casket makers in this town
are gonna have a very merry Christmas.
So, Flash,
what's it gonna be?
Huh?
There you go.
(JAMES LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
They're gonna kill Barry!
Unless we find those bombs.
- Jay, there's no way.
- There is a way.
To find 100
randomly-placed bombs?
We don't have to find 100.
We just have to find one,
and then we get rid of them all.
- How?
- A breach.
That's right. We sent Grodd away.
We can do the same to these bombs,
all of them.
Do you have a drone in your workshop?
- Yeah.
- Does it fly?
Good. I'm taking it.
You're not getting it back.
I'll warm up the van.
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
CISCO: I'm cross-referencing
credit card statements
with toll road usage and families
with children under ten.
- (BEEPS)
- Hold up. Make a U-turn. Two streets back.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CH RISTMAS SONG PLAYING)
Your toys, give them to me.
Mom!
(GROANS)
Oh, Flash, you all right?
You don't look so good.
I know. I'll give you a jolt.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
- Oh!
- (LAUGHING)
(BEEPING)
CISCO: Harry, what is the plan?
One of the 52 breaches opened
by the singularity
is a quarter mile directly above the city.
And we are gonna use your drone
to put this bomb into that breach.
Okay, how does that work?
One down, 99 to blow.
Basic physics, Ramon. Magnetism.
Magnetism. Magnets of opposite poles
attract one another. Help me out, Garrick.
If we can change
the dimensional frequency of this bomb
and get it through that breach...
it'll drag all the rest of the bombs
right along with it. I'll drive.
Okay, hold on.
Ah! I'm done. He's all yours.
Oh! God!
(JAMES LAUGHING)
To think this city worships you!
(LAUGHING)
But when I kill The Flash,
they'll realize
I'm the man who saved Central City!
(WHIRRING)
(GLASS BREAKING)
(LAUGHING)
It's working!
- (EXPLOSION)
- Was that you?
No! Gut him!
All right, I'm gutting already.
Barry, the bombs are gone!
(CRACKLING)
Uh-oh.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
How you like the magnets, bitch?
(SIRENS WAILING)
Detective, it's taken care of.
They can't hurt anyone else.
(GRUNTS)
What are you doing?
This is for my father.
No, no, no, Detective!
Detective, no! You can't do this!
He killed my father
for a couple hundred dollars.
What was so important
that my father had to lose his life?
Mardon will get what he deserves.
- He deserves to die!
- Not like this!
You don't have it in you, pretty lady.
I've been asking myself that for
the last four years, and now I know
No. Patty!
You pull that trigger,
your life ends too.
You will go to prison.
Everything and everyone
that you could have had in your life
will be taken from you. Again.
Mardon can't take anything else from you
unless you let him.
I didn't know your father,
but I know he wouldn't want this.
Not over him.
Please. Please.
Mark Mardon, you're under arrest.
(SIGHS)
That was beautiful.
(WEEPING)
- Barr, hey.
- Hey.
Everyone's heading over to our
place for Christmas. You okay?
Yeah. No. Nothing a little meta-human
regenerative healing
capabilities won't cure.
- (LAUGHING)
- How did it go with Francine?
It was good.
It was really good, actually.
I mean, I spent so long
lying about her being dead
that I started to believe it myself.
But the truth is, those feelings
were always there.
That anger, that regret,
the guilt...
(SIGHS) I just didn't realize
how much I needed to forgive her.
And now, there's room for another West.
Did you meet him?
No. He still doesn't know.
- That'll come.
- Wow.
- You have a son.
- I know, right?
It's crazy.
Speaking of which, take this.
What?
No, no, no, no,
I can't take that.
I've always said
that one day, I would give this to my son.
And now I have.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. Thank you.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- See you at the house.
- Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I know that you're not him,
but he's not here
and I have to say this, for me.
In that video message,
You said that,
that I would never really be happy.
And I've been trying.
I've been trying really hard.
(SIGHS)
After what Joe said,
helping Patty.
I realize that you are still in my heart.
How much I hate you
for what you've done. (SNIFFLES)
I don't want to hate you anymore. I can't.
I can't hate you anymore.
I forgive you.
(BEEPING)
You need me for something?
No, no, I'm good.
You know, you should, uh,
come over for Christmas tonight.
You shouldn't be alone.
It's a nice offer.
I can't celebrate without my daughter.
All right.
(CHUCKLES)
- Strong enough?
- We'll see.
Huh. (LAUGHS)
- Yeah.
- I'll be right back.
Hey.
What do you have there?
Mistletoe.
What's mistletoe?
Oh, uh, it's a hemi-parasitic plant
from the genus Santalaceae family,
in North America, I think.
Caitlin, I'm kidding.
We have mistletoe on Earth-2.
Right. Of course. (CHUCKLES)
Urn, we also have
this tradition over there.
We have that tradition here, too.
- JOE: Aw!
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Finally.
- Oh, let me get that.
- Eggnog, please?
- Yeah.
Hi, I'm so glad
you could make it.
Aw, thank you for having me.
Merry Christmas.
This is for you.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I've been really worried
about you. I've been calling.
I know... and I'm really sorry.
I just have been dealing
with something by myself,
But I want to tell you about it.
I think that I'm ready to.
Someone reminded me of what's important,
so if you want to hear, I
would like to share it with you.
That would be the best gift I could get.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
This is a really sweet sweater.
(LAUGHING)
I hope it's as sweet as this one.
It's matching.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Detective Spivot.
- Hi!
What brings you here?
Merry Christmas.
Well, uh, I'm...
Barry's girlfriend.
- About time.
- Cheers.
(KNOCKING)
- Are we expecting anybody else?
- Not that I know of.
Maybe Harry changed his mind.
Hi. I'm Wally. I'm Francine's son.
(STAMMERING) I'm Joe.
This is Iris.
- Hi.
I just wanted to...
I don't know.
I guess now's a bad time.
You've got company, so...
No. No, no, no. Come in.
Time's up, Wells. What's it going to be?
DR. WELLS: I know what you're doing.
I know why you keep sending villain
after villain from our Earth to this one.
You want Barry to get faster.
You want him to get stronger.
You want him to become more powerful,
more full of Speed Force.
You're fattening him up
like a Christmas goose.
The more power he has,
the more I can take.
And you're going to help me.
Let me see her first.
(GASP) Daddy?
(CRYING)
Are you okay? Did he hurt you?
Please help me.
Don't let him take me back there.
I won't.
ZOOM: Now decide.
In return
for your daughter's life...
I'll do it.
I will help you steal The Flash's speed.