She's dead.
You killed Alexa.
Barry and I did it together.
That was the only way.
She was the strongest.
I needed every ounce of power,
including your
strength, to kill her.
I'm supposed to protect
lives, not destroy them!
I'm helping you clean
up your mess, Barry.
This is your fault.
The night you brought me
back, you created these monsters.
You and your lightning rod.
When you regained your speed,
I wasn't the only thing you
two willed into existence.
- That's impossible.
- Really?
Alexa was afraid to come
here, but she trusted you.
Why?
Because deep down, she
could feel a connection with you.
The same connection
that you feel with me now.
But, these new forces?
The way they've merged with
the people they chose as avatars?
It's corrupted them
because it's unnatural.
But once the other two are gone
I won't help you kill again.
My beautiful boy.
You have no choice.
Because if you don't,
those things will kill everyone
you've sworn to keep safe.
Is that what you want?
Then, please, Barry
help me.
No.
You have to help me, damn it!
Nora, stop.
I will destroy those
other forces, Barry,
with or without your help.
Then you'll see that I'm right.
What a day.
First, Frost is sent
to Iron Heights for life,
and now Alexa's dead.
I can't let this happen again.
I'll get to work. I
need to figure out
how Nora was able to...
Kill a god?
She could because she had help.
Barry, she tricked you.
No, she manipulated me,
just like she's been
doing the whole time.
Honey, I know how you feel, but
not everything she
did and said was a lie.
I mean, there were
moments that felt real too.
That must mean
Iris, we can't
trust her anymore.
What about what Nora said
about you two creating
the other forces?
I mean, there's no proof.
Well, what if we find out
if Nora's telling the truth?
If she is, then that
means the other forces
would have been born
the same day she was.
I'll pull satellite scans
from the night we
fought Mirror Monarch.
Please, and thank you.
Okay, you see that cluster
of kinetic energy readings?
Pretty sure that's
the Speed Force
being reborn in the Speed Lab.
Whoa. There they are.
Three brand-spanking-new
isotopic signatures.
Nora was right.
We created the forces.
Fuerza's dead.
Nora killed her.
She killed the Strength Force?
And now she wants to
kill the other two forces.
Maybe I should go
to San Francisco.
What?
My series of photos
on Eva's attacks
got accepted at a gallery there.
Babe, congrats!
Well, I was thinking of going
to help them
install the exhibition.
I'd ask you to come, but I
know you have your perfect job
at S.T.A.R. Labs and
your amazing friends.
I mean... you're an OG
member of Team Flash.
You okay?
Yeah...
Yeah, I'm fine.
This is an isotopic
scanning lens.
It can detect the
signatures of all four forces,
even kinetic signatures
from Speed Force Nora.
And if one's nearby...
It lights up like an
overexposed landscape.
In which case, you
run the other way.
Okay? I'm serious.
I just want you to be safe.
Are you sure you're okay?
It's Barry.
I gotta get backthey
could have found Nora,
or worse, she's come
back on her own.
How bad is it?
Okaydid Nora kill somebody else?
No, and I have a way to
make sure she never does.
Okay, how?
I'm here.
What's going on?
I spent all night
coming up with a
way to fix all this.
Okay, what's the solve?
We need to wipe the new
forces out of existence.
Barry, what are you saying?
I want to go back in
time... and uncreate them.
Barry, you're talking about
creating another Flashpoint.
You know we can't do that.
Not if I can figure
out a way to go back
that doesn't
affect the time line.
- Which would be impossible.
- Barry, look.
I know that you're
devastated about Alexa.
But uncreating forces?
That crosses a line.
I convinced Alexa to come here.
Her death is my fault.
If we don't get these new
forces out of Psych and Deon,
Nora will kill them, too,
so it's on us to fix this.
- By killing Deon and Psych?
- No, I'm not killing them.
I'm saving them from the
forces that took over their lives.
Whoever they were
before this, they can
go back to being those
same people again.
And what about the other
force that was born that night?
- Nora. If you uncreate her...
- We're only gonna target
the new forces, not
Nora. That's the plan.
But if something goes wrong,
Barry, you might
lose your speed.
Then I lose my speed. All right?
It’s it’s worth the risk
to keep everyone safe.
And what about the risk to Nora?
Does her life not
matter at all any...
Nora's not a person, Iris.
She never was.
Look, if we uncreate
these forces,
we can put everything
back to normal.
Hopefully that'll fix her too.
Hopefully?
Barry, do you hear
yourself right now?
Iris, I'm trying to save people.
How how do you not see
this is the right thing to do?
The right thing to do
would be trying to
get through to Nora.
Just like how we beat Eva,
just like how we talked
down Abra Kadabra.
- That is what we do.
- We tried talking to her.
All Nora did was double down.
There's no reaching her.
Obviously we disagree on this.
Yes, we do.
I have to do it.
Then you'll be
doing it without me.
Wait... you want to go
after a force of nature?
Yeah, if I can convince Nora
not to kill Deon and Psych,
then... Barry will see that
she can be reasoned with.
But, how do we find her?
I mean, she's the
freakin' Speed Force.
Well, if she finds us first,
at least we'll
know she's coming.
Holy crap... you
guys gotta see this.
You see that bright
spot at the center of you?
I think that's kinetic energy.
Guys, this is gonna
sound really wild, but...
Yeah, 'cause a ghost-hunting
lens isn't weird enough...
But, if Barry and I
created these forces,
what if there's a little bit of
each of them inside of us?
Like you're all connected?
Wait, Iris... when
you're over by the door,
your glow was brighter.
Like there's something
in that direction
that was intensifying it.
- What if...
- That something is Nora?
Guys, we can use me as a
divining rod to track her down.
Yup, that's weirder.
Elemental Force Particles?
They're the particles that
created the new forces.
The lightning bolt that
re birthed the Speed Force
- was full of them.
- Now if we can extract
a sample of these
force particles
from the lightning,
then we can send out
an electromagnetic pulse
that'll seek out
those same particles,
wherever they may be
along the temporal spectrum.
And you can erase the
new forces from existence.
That's not bad.
Small detail, though.
How in the world
are you supposed to
extract these particles
from a giant bolt of lightning?
A few weeks ago when
Barry was Spock-Flash,
he modified the Tachyon
Enhancer to siphon.
Mirror Monarch's
dark matter photons.
So all we have to do
is tweak the Enhancer
to siphon Force Particles
instead of photons.
Tweaking the Tachyon Enhancer,
and then send out an
EMP to eighty-six the forces.
That's genius. I mean
it's foolproof, even.
But it still doesn't answer
how we're supposed to do this
and protect the time line.
I'll figure out.
Somehow, I will.
I'll figure it out.
Man, I wish Nash Wells was here.
I mean, he came up with
most of these equations
for the A.S.F. Machine.
I feel like he'd crack
this easy peasy.
Modify the Particle
Harness Collector.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Roger that, but
where are you going?
To get the one person
that can help us pull this off.
No... Tess.
President Bartlett
just mixed up his meds.
That's not gonna be
good, but... great TV.
Whoa!
Allen. Allen.
I'm guessing this
isn't a social call?
Not exactly. We need your help.
How bad is it?
- That depends.
- On...
Whether or not you can
help us do the impossible.
Well, well, well.
Honey, I'm home.
Holy deus ex machina...
Timeless Wells.
- Perfect timing.
- Always.
So, apparently, there's
danger in Central City.
- Apparently.
- Well, let's get busy.
Well, you really think
we can do this without
affecting the time line?
I know we can.
As long as we use
me as your guide.
Harrison was there when
the forces were created.
So if we used the other
"him" from that night
as a beacon to lock onto...
Hopefully I can go back
to that exact moment,
also bring Allen
along for the ride,
and he'll collect the particles.
Oof, wait, so you can travel
through time with a plus one?
It should work...
When Allen and I go
back to that exact moment
that those dangerous forces
were created 17 days ago,
I willl will create a
protective-time bubble
from that moment until now,
preserving those
days in this time line,
and preventing
anything from changing.
Which would also allow us
to wipe out the new forces
without altering
any of the events
that have happened since then...
Yo! That is that is trippy.
Cisco, this will work.
What about Iris?
When she sees everyone
safe, she'll come around.
She has to.
You're not convinced.
I wasn't either,
when Allen told me about
this, I thought of Tess.
I thought of my wife, and
how my future with Tess was
ripped from me.
Until this gift
which has allowed me to
relive every single day with Tess,
but only
because I took a chance.
All right.
I'm in.
It's brighter. We
must be getting close.
She should be here.
Maybe it was a false positive.
Maybe since Nora
is the Speed Force,
her isotopic signature is
all over the city by now.
- So what do we do?
- I don't know.
But we are running out of time.
Well, Cisco always says
you can't solve a problem
till you're asking
the right question.
Isn't "Where's Nora's
kinetic energy leading us"
the right question?
No.
The right question
is "Where's Nora?"
We've been trying to
find the Speed Force
when we should be
looking for... the person.
So where would the
real Nora Allen go?
Home.
Come on.
Harness modifications complete.
Let's get some time particles.
Actually, you know what? Um...
Let me run just
one more diagnostic
on the collection disc.
I just need one
more, just one more...
Frak.
Yo, yo, Deon.
What’s what’s...
- What's good, man?
- You tell me.
Something drew me here.
Was it you?
I’m don't think it was...
Who's this? I'm
sorry, who are you?
Who am I? Who are you?
Who is he?
Look, guys, all's
good in the hood.
All right, look.
Barry, this is Deon.
Still Force.
Andand Deon, this is Barry,
who's actually...
Owner of this,
fine establishment.
So you're the landlord.
What's that got to
do with anything?
Deon
it's good to meet you.
Actually, you remember me?
I was with him, you
called us one of the Urkels.
Yeah... the cornballs.
Cornball. He's so funny.
Who's the egghead?
Harrison Wells.
I'm a fellow...
Visitor to Barry's place.
You know, y'all are being
real friendly right now.
But I think
I think y'all are
acting like that
because you're afraid of me.
- Now why is that?
- No, we're just
we're just making awe're
just doing an experiment...
Shut up!
Now
why do I get the feeling
you're reason I'm this way?
Because that's true.
And I'm sorry.
I never meant
for this to happen.
- So please let me fix it.
- Fix it?
Fix it? So I'm a mistake?
- I didn't say that...
- You didn't have to.
I can feel it.
- You want to destroy me.
- No, I want to save you.
Deon... Deon.
There are three other
forces... people like you.
One of them? She
wants to kill you.
Now, she's already killed
one of the other forces...
The Strength Force,
and she didn't care
when the person
containing that force died too.
So I need to make it so the
Still Force never found you.
It's the only way
to keep you safe.
Nah.
I like being me.
I get it.
- I get it.
- Yeah?
No, I get it. I get it.
This is what you're
gonna use to do it?
This is what you're gonna use
to make it like I never existed?
Not you, just
the force inside...
Man, I am that force!
Do you have any
idea what it's like
to be told that you
shouldn't be here?
I never asked to be born.
Deon, listen to me.
Look at what you're doing.
Okay, you you don't
understand what you are.
Yeah, I do.
I'm a god.
Maybe it's time
you understood that.
Deon, wait...
Time to bounce.
Right?
What the hell just happened?
I think your friend
Deon just stopped time.
Yeah, he does that.
Why'd he leave?
Because I couldn't stop him.
Deon just aged the
harness a thousand years.
- How bad is it?
- Pretty bad.
But not hopeless.
See I figured if we
can find some way to...
Somehow create some sort of.
I was working on the collection
disc when Deon showed up.
I figured I better
hide it just in case.
Chester.
You're a lifesaver.
As for the vest,
I'm used to working with junk.
I'll just need a bunch
of replacement parts
from my garage and she'll
be up and running in no time.
- With a little help, that is.
- I'm with you.
What's up?
I think Deon's right.
We can't just
uncreate these forces like that.
So what, we we
we should just give up?
On this? Yeah, we give up.
Doesn't that feel like
the right thing to do?
Cisco, Nora will kill him
if I don't do
something to prevent it.
Just like she killed Alexa.
'Cause she's not gonna
stop until all the forces...
And the people
connected to the mare dead.
Why can't you see?
I'm trying to save him.
He doesn't want
to be saved by you!
He just wants to be given
the chance to be himself.
And Iris understood that.
Look, every second
that we leave these forces
inside Deon and Psych,
people are in danger.
It's only a matter of
time before someone dies
in one of Psych's nightmares
or gets killed by some
kind of Deon time anomaly.
Not to mention
Nora declared war.
She doesn't care how
many people she kills
as long as the forces die.
You're right. Yes,
you're absolutely right.
And something needs
to be done about that.
And I don't have
all the answers.
All I know is
this can't be it.
You guys understand, right?
II have to uncreate
these forces.
Like I said, I aml'm
Team Flash all the way.
But
Cisco has a point, man.
Harrison?
If uncreating these forces is
what you feel in
your heart is right,
I'll take that voyage with you.
But all I ask is that
you think truly think
about the choice you're making.
Please fix the harness.
Good luck.
Iris, you were right.
These isotopic
readings are off the chart.
Where are we?
The old Allen house.
This is where Barry's
mom was killed.
He also said this is where the
Speed Force went when she died.
Whoa. That old
car is hella vintage.
Almost looks brand new.
Must be a collector
or something.
We can ask him when we're done.
Assuming we survive.
Caitlin called me about Alexa.
So it turns out,
when Iris and I brought
back the Speed Force,
we also created
three new forces.
It's our fault that they're out
in the world hurting people.
Killing them.
So I feel like
I have to be the
one to take them out.
These forces.
You think they're
above saving, too?
I think it would be safer for
everybody if they didn't exist.
You remember when
Wally first showed up?
Man, it wasn't just that
I'd found out I have a son.
I found out
I have a son who kept
getting his butt in trouble.
Boy, he was mad at the world.
There was one point
he said to me that he wished
he had never been born.
So I tried to get close.
And he pushed me away.
I tried to give him space,
then he felt abandoned.
No parent is perfect.
But one thing I
never stopped doing
was trying.
And look at the man
he grew up to be.
Strong. Kind. Good.
Yeah I get it, II do, but
I mean, these forces?
- They're not my children.
- You sure?
You said it yourself.
You brought them
into this world.
Look, I know they've
all done terrible things.
But what if they could change?
You never judge your
kids for who they are now.
You help them become
who they know they can
be when they grow up.
So lead with love.
After that, it is up to them.
This is Barry's old room.
Nora?
Psych.
Hi, Mom.
Esperanza, don't kill me!
- They're everywhere.
- We need to keep them out.
Psych, stop. You're
hurting them please.
They're hurting themselves.
Sure, I pull back the curtain.
But what they see is up to them.
Now, before I show
you your worst fear,
why were you looking for me?
I wasn't.
No...
You're looking for
the Speed Force?
Nora. Why?
Why are you so
desperate to find her?
Is it to hurt her?
I want to talk to her
so I can help her.
Are you sure? Because I am
feeling the pain that she
has inflicted upon you.
How deeply she's torn
apart your relationships.
Your whole life.
Actually, the suffering
she's caused is
- quite beautiful.
- That wasn't Nora.
She's lost control.
Just like you have.
But if you let me, I
can help you both.
I don't need your help.
Besides, I can feel
what you fear the most.
It's the person you seek.
Well, your wish is my command.
Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
You'll never measure up.
Okay. It's working.
Now, when you're close
enough to cycle particles,
the disc will light up.
Guys, I appreciate
you helping me.
Make sure the proton
collection housing's
double-fused.
We did.
And it's good to see you.
What changed your mind?
Look, this is dangerous.
And it doesn't feel right.
But I'm always
gonna have your back.
No matter what.
Chester. Let's get it going.
Okay, so. Barry.
All you need to do is
get close enough to the.
Speed Force lightning to
collect a sample of each force.
The PHC and Timeless Wells'
time bubble should do the rest.
Theoretically.
Ready?
Nothing's happening.
- You gonna...
- Wait for it.
Wait for it.
Incredible.
We're at 100% organic speed.
We need you
I need you.
I remember this moment.
This is where it all started.
We should get to the roof.
You think you can
be a good wife?
Good mother?
But you never will.
Everything you do pales
in comparison to me.
Besides... how could
you be a good mother
- if you never even had one?
- I'm not listening to you.
You don't have to.
You already know it's the truth.
No. You're not real.
There's no escaping
your own fear.
I know you're still here, Psych.
Very good.
It is not every day that
somebody can sense my
presence in their nightmare.
- I'm not just someone.
- We have a connection.
I know you can feel that too.
Perhaps. It's not going
to help you, though.
Escape one nightmare
and I'll just serve up another.
Because there's always
more terror to unlock.
But before you had those powers,
before you became a
force. You were a person.
I'm talking to that
person right now.
I have friends. I have a team.
They can help you fight this
monster that's inside of you.
We can help you regain
control of your body.
What makes you
think I'm not in control?
- I know you didn't...
- choose to have these powers.
And you shouldn't have
to go through this alone.
I know that we're
not flesh and blood.
But in a way
I'ml'm like a parent.
So please let me help you.
Well, then there's something
I should tell you, Mother.
I hated my parents.
The isotopic energy
readings are going down.
The forces are dying.
These fools gonna learn.
You mess with Deon.
You get dealt with.
Another 20 seconds,
and they'll be gone forever.
Barry did it.
Okay.
Wait... wait.
What is that?
I think that is an
act of creation.
I have the particles.
Shouldn't the forces be dying?
Perhaps they are. Somewhere.
In time, but right
here? Right now?
They're being born.
What are you doing to me?
I wasn't able to
get through to him.
- And now it's too late.
- Boss, we can't stay here.
Allen.
You okay?
Never judge your kids
for who they are now.
You help them become
who they know they can be.
They're almost gone.
5%.
3%
2%...
What's happening?
Everything just stopped.
The numbers are going back up.
It's as if the forces
are still here.
Iris was right.
You all were.
I
I couldn't do it.
Iris
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Barry, Ium
I went looking for Nora.
I thought that if I
could just talk to her,
that I could fix everything.
But, um.
I ended up finding Psychinstead.
You were right.
I couldn't get through to him.
And it probably would have
been the same with Nora.
I should have listened to you.
No, I'm the one who
should have listened.
Harrison told me about
the birth of the forces.
Sounds incredible.
It was.
Can't believe how close
I came to erasing them.
- What changed your mind?
- You.
Joe. Everyone.
Even the forces themselves.
I could
I could feel how they
would affect the future.
All the speedsters' and
heroes' lives they'd shape.
Some of them were family, Iris.
Our family.
Barry, we both know how
dangerous these forces can be.
I mean, if you
couldn't uncreate them,
and I couldn't get
through toPsych...
- What are we supposed to do?
- Try again.
Together this time.
Joe helped me realize
that we can't judge.
Psych and Deon
for who they are now.
We have to help them become
who they can grow up to be.
'Cause that's what parents do.
Alexa.
- What happened?
- There was a tremor.
And Alexa sat up
and looked at me.
Alexa's alive?
She was for a second,
but she's not anymore.
Which doesn't make any
sense, medically speaking.
What if us being back in sync
is what woke her
up for the moment?
And then she reconnected
with the Strength Force.
Is it crazy to think
that we did this?
No.
'Cause we're all connected.
And if we woke her up once.
Then we could bring
her back permanently?
Why is everyone looking at me?
Listen. I'd ask you to say, but
I already know the answer.
A man's gotta be
where his heart lies.
He's just gotta
learn to listen to it.
One more thing before I go.
Whether it's me,
or any of the many
Wells predecessors,
I want you to know
that you taught us
every inch as much
as we taught you.
Maybe more.
Yeah, I'm never
gonna get used to that.
You okay?
Yeah.
For the first time
in a long while.
Yeah, I feel okay.
Good.
Um...'cause I've been
thinking about something.
And after tonight, I
know I have to do it.
Okay, that's just weird.
I was literally about to say
the exact same thing to you.
I have to leave Central City.
Thank God.
Are you kidding me?
My God.
Babe, what are you
gonna tell Team Citizen?
What are you gonna
tell Team Flash?
You're the one who's after me?
You don't look so tough.
What are you?
A reckoning.
Greg, move your head.