- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
Is my dad even really...
- Caitlin, your father is dead.
- Dad?
- You found me.
I want to make it up
to you, Caity.
I really should've
been there for you.
- Icicle wouldn't have gone
to all this trouble
to kill my dad if there wasn't
a piece of him still left.
- We got Dwyer,
we gave him the cure,
but another Cicada showed up.
- She wants to tell you
her secret.
Someone instructed you
to do it.
Eobard Thawne.
- [panting]
Dad, please don't do this!
- Nora, if you try to run back
in time again,
I will feel it in
the Speed Force.
Good-bye, Nora.
[zap]
- You took our daughter
back to the future?
- I didn't have
any other choice.
- I? It's we, Barry.
We. She's our daughter,
not just yours.
- I know that.
- But you left her there
anyway?
- I can't trust her, Iris!
That puts all of us in danger!
- That's how you feel, Barry.
- [sighs]
- What about asking how I feel?
- I didn't think I had to!
- [scoffs]
Of course you didn't.
Of course you didn't, Barry!
You always see one way
through a problem
and damn what I think.
- Wait, wait, what the hell
does that mean?
- You know, we have been
through so much crap,
we have been through
so much therapy
and you are still...
still making decisions based on
your emotions!
- 'Cause I'm right this time!
[solemn music]
[scoffs]
- Flashpoint?
Going to the Speed Force
and leaving me?
Were you right those times too?
- You think I wanted
to do this?
That this was easy?
Seeing Nora looking at me,
asking for forgiveness
knowing it might be
the last time I ever see her?
- What about the last time
that I get to see her, Barry?
I didn't even get a chance
to say good-bye!
- Damn it, Iris,
she lied to us for months!
- And she explained why!
- That she was working
with Thawne?
- [sobs]
♪ ♪
That doesn't bother you.
- No, it doesn't.
- Maybe if he killed
your mother in front of you,
you'd feel differently.
- [sighs]
Maybe you feeling
differently, Barry,
is why we should have made
this decision together.
She just wanted to meet you,
Barry.
The father that she never knew
and there was one person who
could teach her how to do that.
Is it really so hard
to understand
why she would go to him?
- Doesn't matter
if I understand it.
- [sighs]
- Thawne is manipulating her.
- He's on death row, Barry.
How is he manipulating her?
- You know, if this were
anybody else, you'd back me.
But because it's Nora,
because it's our daughter,
the person who finally
stopped hating you,
you refuse to see
how dangerous this is.
I mean, you talk about making
decisions based on emotion.
Look in the mirror.
♪ ♪
- All those years without
my father
and you gave me
a second chance.
And now I've lost him
all over again.
- I failed you,
Little Runner.
- No, this is my fault.
I should've never lied to them
about working with you.
- Well, perhaps not.
- [sobs]
I screwed everything up.
And now I can't even help them
catch Cicada
because my dad will know
if I run into the Speed Force.
- Mm-hmm.
He most certainly will.
- Wait...
Wait.
You've run into the Speed Force
hundreds of times.
And my father,
other speedsters,
they never felt you coming.
How did you do that?
Thawne, tell me
how you did it.
- Nora.
- Tell me. Thawne!
- It's not for you.
- I need to see my father.
Please, if there is a way
I can go back in time
to see him undetected,
you have to tell me how.
- I used to idolize
your father.
I wanted to be just like him.
But that was not my fate.
I was to be the reverse.
Opposite of him...
in every way.
So instead of tapping
into the Speed Force
to access my powers...
I created my own.
- You created
your own Speed Force?
- Yes, I did.
- And I can access it
to go back in time?
- That and more.
- Can you teach me
how to use it?
♪ ♪
- Well, I...I have to warn you,
Nora.
It's a little bit negative.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, where is Cecile
and Cisco?
- Cecile's relieving
the nanny.
- And Cisco went
to talk to Breacher
about how to track Cicada II.
- Okay.
- Where's Iris?
- [sighs]
Uh, I honestly don't know.
We're not really seeing
eye to eye right now.
- Because?
- Because I took Nora home
for good.
- Nora's gone?
- Just like that?
- Well, only thing to do,
really,
because Nora can't be trusted.
I can deduce from your faces
that you're upset,
but you understand the truth
need to be exposed.
- Yes, we understand that.
What you don't understand is
that this is a family.
You didn't include anyone
in this.
- Oh, look. Baby Giraffe...
- Sherloque,
you've done enough.
All right?
- Oh, I have not done enough.
We still have another Cicada
to catch.
- Man, he says
you've done enough.
- Well, perhaps I have.
[cell phone vibrating]
- I got to take this. Yeah?
- Look since Cisco
didn't take me with him,
I'm gonna round up
the Cicada II files.
Cecile and I are going
to go over them tomorrow,
see if anything makes
my nose wiggle.
[suspenseful music]
- [sighs]
- Are you gonna be okay?
- I honestly don't know.
- Guys, this is CCPD.
We've got a big problem.
- [sighs]
- The nurses heard a crash
in the middle of the night
but nobody saw anything.
By the time they got here,
Grace was gone.
- Judging by the thermal
warping in this glass,
an energy blast with a lot
of heat took out the window.
But I don't really think
we need any clues
to know who took her.
- Future Grace steals
past Grace.
I don't even know if there's
a police code
for kidnapping yourself.
Hey, what's it say?
- Grace's coma is stable.
As long as future Grace is
looking after younger Grace,
her life's not in any danger.
- We still have no way
to find either of them.
Could things get any worse?
[whirring]
[click]
- Working late,
Dr. Tannhauser?
- Or working early,
depending how you see it.
- Well, I stopped by
to say good night.
So I guess I'll say
good morning.
- Good morning, J.P.
[keys clacking]
[glass freezes, shatters]
- [Man] Get back!
Hold it right there!
[gunshot]
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[freezing, cracking]
[whirs]
- [smooch]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
Thomas?
- I don't suppose Icicle
left any frozen fingerprints
behind?
- No, but this docking station
is lined with a carbon-filled
Kapton polymide.
NASA uses it to build probes
meant for the coldest reaches
of space.
- There's a lot
of fresh puddles in here.
You think he stole whatever
kept this place cold?
- Try way beyond cold.
- Why would he want it?
- You're going to have
to ask Carla
when she's done filing
the theft report
or Caitlin when she gets here.
I'm not sure about much lately.
- Hey, Barr.
Have you talked to Iris
since she left?
- I'm just giving her
some space.
- All right, just make sure
you don't give her too much.
- [Caitlin] The right choice?
What the hell
are you talking about?
You lied to me for 20 years
and told me my father was dead.
How the hell is that
the right choice?
- Your father is trapped
inside an ice monster, Caitlin.
What was I supposed to do?
Split custody with him
on the weekends?
- I don't know. You could try
telling me the truth.
But why tell your daughter
anything?
- Funny, I don't recall you
telling me
that you let the monster
out of the prison.
- Because you never told me
he was in a prison!
And now all these years
that I could've been working on
a cure for dad are gone!
We may never get him back.
Well, at least you have
someone to blame.
Moms are always here for that.
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- I will be as soon as
we find Icicle.
My mom told me what he stole.
It's a prototype Cryo-Atomizer.
- And what can he do with that?
- Nothing good.
- My contacts upstate
got nothing.
I even tried Kritschgau
at the DOD. Nada.
Nobody can spare the manpower
to help find Cicada 2.0.
- Hey, what about The Citizen?
Any fresh leads on Cicada?
Iris?
Hello? Um, Earth to Iris?
- [pulsating]
Ralph, wait!
- "Barry, I don't know if I can
ever forgive you for this."
I think you missed
a comma there.
- Can you stay out of it
for once?
- She's not kidding.
Super mad.
- No. Look, um, Iris,
I know how Barry can be.
But you guys are like
the Meghan and Harry
of superhero royalty.
Your love is eternal.
You two will talk and...and...
- We did talk.
I want Nora to stay here,
he doesn't.
How do we solve that?
- Okay, Iris, honey.
I haven't always been in the
near-perfect relationship
that I'm in now.
So take it from someone
with experience,
the only way you two solve
this problem is together.
And you're not going
to find your answers here.
[soft music]
- Yeah, you're right.
♪ ♪
- [pulsating]
You need to go after her.
- Oh, come on.
Give me a break.
Have you seen her right hook?
- Ralph, she's hurt,
I know.
But there's something more.
I feel it.
She's determined.
- Reprogramming complete.
The Time Sphere's
navigation core is now locked
onto Nora West-Allen's
temporal signature.
- And you disabled the
tracker that Cisco installed
into the Sphere?
- Yes.
However, there are still
alarms in S.T.A.R. Labs.
If you wish to use
the Sphere undetected,
you must activate it off-site.
- Planning a trip?
- How did you get in here?
- Followed you then stretched
under the door.
By the way,
was anybody ever gonna
tell me about this secret room?
What else do we got in here?
A bowling alley or something?
- Ralph, I don't have time
for this.
- Actually, it looks like you
have all the time in the world.
- You're not gonna stop me.
- Who said anything
about stopping you?
- [Nora]I'm in position.
Thawne, I said I'm ready.
- We shall see if you're ready.
[Thawne]Now run.
Now listen to me, Nora.
Breathe. Breathe.
You're reaching out
and nobody's there.
The loneliness is pain.
Pain racing through your mind.
Crushing you, wrecking you,
shattering your soul into
a million little pieces.
And suddenly,
you are no longer you.
♪ ♪
You're part of something
different now.
Part of a negative force.
- [panting]
It didn't work.
Thawne, why didn't it work?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Are you ready?
- All set to hit
88 miles an hour!
- Here we go.
[click, whirring]
Open the time breach!
[whirring]
Ralph, hurry up!
- So the Cryo-Atomizer
has the ability
to disperse particles
into the atmosphere.
Particles that slow down atoms
to a grinding halt.
And the slower they get...
- The colder they get.
- How cold are we talking?
- Absolute zero.
And if we combine them
with Icicle's meta-powers...
- He could plunge Central City
into a new Ice Age.
- There is some good news.
I think we can track
the nano-cryoparticles
inside the atomizer.
We just have to reprogram an
oscillating inversion scanner.
Do you mind running to the
downstairs storage area
and grabbing it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Wait. You should use
a modified field array.
There's one in
the upstairs archives.
- No, no, actually
the inversion scanner
would work best.
Thank you.
- No, no. Not since we upgraded
our field arrays last year.
You know you would know that
if you visited more,
not just when
you needed something.
- Apparently, only when
I need the wrong thing.
The inversion scanner.
- The field array.
[playfully tense music]
♪ ♪
- I'll get both.
Might take my time.
- You need help?
- No.
[wind howling]
Is it me or is it getting
really cold in here?
Run!
- [voice echoing] Two for one.
[sighs] So who wants
a family reunion?
Hm? [chuckles]
[solemn music]
- [sighs]
Adieu, Team Flash.
[alarm blaring]
[suspenseful music]
- Barry. Barry, come on!
[whirring]
- Come on, Barr!
I can barely feel his pulse.
- He has hypothermia.
His heart rate's dropping.
We only have seconds
to save him.
- What are you doing?
- Well, this...[grunts]
this machine has
a large power source
I need to access
to save Monsieur Allen.
- Watch out.
[door clanging]
- That'll work.
Stand back.
[grunts] All right.
This current should heat up
the copper wiring
of his suit's circuitry and
we need to heat it up enough
so that his speed healing
kicks in.
- Is this safe?
- Safer than dying.
Come on, Monsieur Allen.
- Barry?
- Come on!
- Barr!
- [gasps]
Icicle. He has them.
- No, no, no, no, Monsieur.
- No, no, wait. No, wait.
- In time. In time.
First, you rest.
Then we bring them home
together.
- [panting]
- [groans]
Where are we?
- In another decommissioned
Tannhauser site.
This site is a little more
off-the-grid than usual.
It's where we kept our
most classified projects.
- Great. I guess we are
Icicle's next project.
We need to get out of here.
- Well, there's a circuit panel
over here.
I think we can hack it
and open the door.
- Neither one of us knows
about electrical engineering.
Our best bet is to break me out
of these meta-cuffs
and let Killer Frost
do the rest.
- Don't be foolish.
You'll never break those.
- Well, it's no more foolish
than you electrocuting
yourself, but if you want to,
knock yourself out.
- You'd like that,
wouldn't you?
- [groans]
How did we get here?
I mean, you're my mother
and I'm your daughter.
But it has never felt
like that.
You've always
been cold, distant.
You never wanted to be
a part of my life.
Not then and certainly not now.
Why?
I mean, what did I ever do
to get treated like this?
- What?
- Why did you leave me?
- You left me first.
You went to school across the
country to get away from me.
You took a job in Central City
instead of working in
the same zip code as my lab.
Caitlin, you were married
to a man I never even met.
I got the hint,
but don't you dare
mistake things.
I didn't leave first.
[door clicks open]
- What are we doing here?
What do you want with us?
- I want what you could be.
- Stop it!
- Just a small blood sample.
See you soon, Snow Pack.
[door slams shut]
- What?
- Snow Pack.
That was your father's nickname
for our family.
- I remember,
and why is that scaring you?
- He said he wanted
what we could be
and then he took a sample
of your blood.
- Theoretically, he could use
the Cryo-Atomizer
to recreate the process
that created Killer Frost.
So if he did that to you...
- I would gain an ice persona.
- And now with
a sample of my blood...
- He can create a serum
that will permanently suppress
our human sides.
- He wants an ice family
and he's willing
to erase us to get it.
[dramatic music]
- Hold my suit.
- Oh, my God, Ralph.
Do you ever wash this thing?
- Focus, okay?
You sure you're ready to talk
to "he who shall not be named"?
- Well, whether I am or not,
Gideon said
that these were
Nora's last known coordinates.
[whimsical band music]
You're up.
♪ ♪
- [sighs] Hey, bro.
Uh, what a day.
Am I right?
You mind if I get a quick word
there with Hannibal Speedster?
It's just going to take,
like, a second.
- Is that right?
Well, unless you got a signed
Shift Change Order,
nobody goes in there
but me, bro.
- Only you, huh?
[chuckles]
Okay, if you insist.
[stretching]
Hm.
- Oh, shrap.
- [grunts]
Oh. Ooh.
[mutters]
You need to hurry.
This guy's such a dick,
I got to think
super douchey thoughts
just to keep this face on.
Douchey, douchey, douchey.
- I did everything exactly
like you told me.
How come I can't do this?
- Listen, not harboring
enough rage to fuel your trip
is not something
to be ashamed of.
You're just like your father.
Your light is
your greatest strength.
[door opens]
[dramatic music]
- Nora.
- Mom?
- Step away from him, please.
- Mom, it's okay.
Eobard is helping me.
He has a way for me
to get back home.
- Nora, step away from him now.
- Nora, listen to your mother.
- Where's Dad?
- It's just me.
It's probably for the best.
Come on, we have to hurry.
- What do you mean
it's probably for the best?
- Nora, the last thing
your father needs
is to see you
here with him.
- She's right about that.
- No.
No, she's not,
and neither is my dad.
- Nora, your dad was wrong,
but he still cares about you.
- Why are you here
and he isn't?
- Look, I understand
how you feel...
- Do you?
Do you know what it's like
to want something more
than anything else
in your whole life?
[thunderous zapping]
To know your father?
To do your best to follow
in his footsteps?
To make him proud?
[crackling]
How could he leave me?
- Wait, wait! That's enough!
- Nora.
- How could he stop loving me?
[pulsating]
[zapping]
♪ ♪
[screaming] No!
[screaming]
It's always
the same condescending
"I know better than you"
crap.
and you never change!
- She's trying to kill me.
[grunting, punching]
- Who else knows?
- Everyone.
- It's time for you
to go home.
Good-bye, Nora.
[echoing] Goodbye, Nora.
Goodbye, Nora.
[screams]
- She's gone.
- What the hell do
you mean she's gone?
Gone where?
- I don't know where.
I only know when. 2019.
- When Nora said you
showed her a way back...
she meant your way.
- Yes.
And I made a mistake.
She wanted to go home,
I tried to help her.
But listen, Iris,
you have to find her.
She needs her family.
- And that family
does not include you.
- But it does include Barry.
She needs you both united.
- I'm only going
to say this once.
You don't get
to comment on us.
You stay the hell out
of our business
or you won't even make it
to the end of that timer.
- I like your anger,
but don't let it drive
Barry away.
The only way for you
to help Nora
is by doing it as a family.
Otherwise, you're simply
leaving Barry
the exact same way
he left Nora.
[door opens]
- Iris, we got to bail.
They found Officer Jackass.
- Think about it.
- Iris, please.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[door closes]
- What's it like having
another person in your head?
- Pretty crazy.
I mean, when she first
showed up,
I couldn't wait
to get rid of her,
but when she disappeared,
I tried even harder
to get her back.
- What finally brought
her back?
- Family.
She protected us.
- Well, I'm glad you had
someone there for you.
- Hey, Mom, that was pretty
clever what you did.
Figuring out Icicle's plan.
- [chuckles] Well, I recall you
helped with that too.
- [chuckles]
It's amazing what we can do
when we're not trying to rip
each other's heads off.
[door opens]
- Stay away from her.
- I'll come back
for her later.
First, we have
some catching up to do.
- What? [screams]
- No!
- Caitlin!
[ice cracking]
[beeping]
- [sighs]
There's no leads.
There's no hits
on Icicle's cryosignature,
no reads on facial recognition,
nothing.
- Barr, we'll find him.
We always do.
- How, Joe?
How are we gonna find them?
Caitlin's kidnapped.
We need Caitlin
to find Caitlin.
Cisco's on another Earth
and Iris won't even answer
my calls!
I...
I don't know how to fix
any of this.
- If I might?
It occurs to me that hiding
a needle
in a haystack is good.
Hiding a needle in
a stack of needles?
[click, beep]
That's better.
[dramatic music]
- These are all the cold spots
in the area.
You think Icicle is masking
his cryo-signature
with someplace
that's already cold?
- Giving him the perfect cover.
So we just refocus
our search,
look for temperature anomalies
in already existing cold spots,
et voila.
- This is great. I'll start
retasking the satellites.
- Hey, thanks for your help.
- The least I can do.
- I've got a cold spike.
- That's quite a stack
of needles.
♪ ♪
[banging]
- Thomas, are you in there?
Thomas, please.
- Now it's time to meet
your better half.
[whirring]
[ice cracking]
[suspenseful music]
- [sighs]
Perfection.
- Boo.
- [groans, scoffs]
How did you get out?
- Me? I just raised my hands.
You were the one
who froze my cuffs
so they shattered like glass.
- Clever, Caitlin.
I'm almost gonna miss her
when she's dead.
[whirring]
No turning back now.
Time to make a choice.
You either save her...
Or fight me.
[ice crackling]
- Save her.
I'm gonna go get him.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [yelps, groaning]
- Okay, explain again
why I'm here doing this
and not anybody else?
- It appears we're a bit
short staffed at the moment.
- All right, if it's just us,
it's just us.
Let's do this.
- Let's do this thing.
- What's happening?
- Oh, great timing.
- Oh, yeah, good timing.
Oh, you do this.
- Okay, Icicle has Caitlin
and her mom in some caves
north of the Badlands.
- Well, the Flash is already
on the scene.
So for all we know,
the problem is already solved.
- [Barry]Guys, I have a
problem. - Or not.
- I need to phase Carla
out of a cryo-chamber
but it's too cold.
I can't even touch it.
- All right,
we need heat fast.
- What if he generates
a lightning bolt?
- He can't throw a bolt.
That would kill her.
- Then why doesn't
he just, uh, hold onto it?
- That could kill him!
- No, no. He's right.
The lightning cannot hurt you
if you are in phase.
- If half my molecules
are in phase,
the electricity would hop
from stable molecule
to stable molecule.
- Creating an electronic bridge
that will generate the heat
that you need, et viola.
- Without electrocuting him,
he can phase in,
grab her,
and then phase out.
- All in 3/10s of a second.
- Uh-huh.
♪ ♪
[pulsating]
[pulsating voice] I got
you. [normal voice] I got
you.
- [Barry]I'm going to
warm her up, all right?
- [groaning]
- What a waste.
- I wanted to make you perfect.
Now I must end you.
[pulsating]
Impossible.
[groaning]
[yelling, ice breaking]
[thud]
Caity?
- Dad?
- Are you okay?
- Is it you?
Is it really you?
- [chuckles] It's me.
It's really me.
- Oh. Oh, my God.
[emotional music]
♪ ♪
- You're going to be okay.
You just need to take it slow.
- Thomas?
My God!
- Are you...
- I'm okay.
I took a beating
but Killer Frost
ice healing kicked in.
I'm going to be fine
thanks to Dad.
- Well, how...how is
this possible?
- Well, I saw Icicle
about to kill Caitlin,
and I found the strength
to break through.
- Just like Killer Frost,
Dad saved me.
- Well, you saved me too,
Caity.
I mean, thanks to you, I think
I may have finally
banished this monster.
♪ ♪
- That's good.
That just leaves one more
monster for me to kill.
- [grunts]
Run!
[groaning]
- Get out of here.
I'll take care of this.
[ice crackling]
Cool knife. I've got two.
[both grunting]
- [moaning]
[cracking]
[groaning]
- Caitlin, run!
[knife plunges]
[whirring, clang]
- [groans]
- Dad? Dad. Please.
- [weakly] Caitlin.
- Dad, I told you to go.
- I already left once before.
- [sobs]
- Left both of you.
Worst mistake I've ever made
in my entire life.
I wasn't going
to make that again.
Family shouldn't leave family.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I'll always love you.
[angelic music]
♪ ♪
- How's Caitlin and her mom?
- Caitlin's still running
some tests,
but she thinks Carla's
gonna be okay.
I mean, as okay as she can be
given the circumstances.
- Why was Cicada II even there
tonight?
I mean, why attack Icicle
and Caitlin?
- Perhaps the ice meta were
not the primary target.
- What could Cicada II want
with the Cryo-Atomizer?
- Well, we're not gonna figure
it out tonight.
So let's rest tonight.
Are you coming back
to the house?
- Um...
No, I'm gonna stay
at the loft tonight.
- You are?
- Yeah.
We should talk.
- Awkward a bit.
- So you went to the future?
- Yeah. John Stamos
still handsome.
- He'll never not age.
- No, never.
Man, he looks good.
- So this endothermic
litmus test
would've created
a stoichiometric reaction.
If there was any residual
meta DNA in your system, it...
- Would've turned white.
I know.
- And it's still green,
so you're clean.
You're not a meta.
Those were all the clues
that I used to find dad.
Including some files
that I may have stolen
from your file room.
- Aww, Caitlin and Thomas'
infamous Periodic Table.
Nerdonium.
- [chuckles]
- You know,
he stole that one from me.
- Really? I thought
he came up with that
while he was fixing
the kitchen sink.
- No, I thought of that.
Come to think of it,
I also fixed the kitchen sink.
Well, I...I better be going.
Good night, Caity.
- Mom?
Um...
Do you want to maybe
go get a drink?
You can tell me more about
elements you invented.
- [chuckles]
- Now or whenever.
- No, actually,
now would be perfect.
- There's a little wine bar
around the corner.
- Mm-hmm.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Heading home?
- Well, it's like
Barry said...and Joe...
I've done enough.
- They did say that.
But you hung around anyway.
- Oui , I did.
- You were there for Barry
when he needed you.
Oui , I was.
- And you helped saved
Caitlin's mom.
- Yes, that's right.
I did all those things.
I should not have done
those things?
- I'm just saying
maybe you have more to do...
For your family.
- [chuckles]
- I just wanted
my family back together.
Even if that meant doing
something drastic
like time travel.
- Yeah, I get that.
More than anyone.
- You were right about Thawne.
I think he's manipulating
Nora,
but I also believe him.
Nora is back here in our time.
- [sighs]
I was...
Wrong.
I shouldn't have left Nora
or made that decision
without you.
Whatever it is that
we have to figure out,
we should've done it together.
Family doesn't leave family.
- Well, I mean you weren't the
only one to make that mistake.
I shouldn't have gone to
the future without you.
I shouldn't have left you
like that.
I mean, that was the same thing
that I got so mad at you for.
But I know now that we can't
solve this
if we don't stick together.
- I can barely
solve things with you,
so without you...
- Are we making jokes already?
Really?
- Let's bring our kid home.
- There's something else
that I wanted to tell you.
Barry, the way that Thawne
looks when he talks about Nora.
I've only ever seen that
in one other person.
You.
- What are you saying?
- I think Thawne might
actually care about Nora.
[mailbox rattles]
[dark music]
[squeaking]
[rattling]
[electricity surges]
♪ ♪
- Soon, Grace.
Soon.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.