Mother is better now, Mayor.
And thanks again. I know family
emergencies are never convenient.
But after some personal reflection,
I realized I have to be with her.
Everything I am started with her.
- You sure you weren't followed?
- Yes.
Good.
- You've changed your appearance.
- The suit is necessary.
The properties inside of it help me
continue my acclimation process
when I'm outside
the reflection modulation chamber.
Now... it's time to get rid
of my husband.
We begin by dismantling
everything that protects him.
- You know where to start.
- Success is assured.
Guys, shouldn't it be all hands on deck
with Iris, Kamilla and Singh
stuck in the Mirrorverse?
Hey, you're just as important.
Found this. Caitlin or Frost?
They're going to the Arctic,
not OzzFest.
How are you so bad at everything?
Caity keeps her heavy coats
in the back closet.
- I'll check on it.
- Right. That makes more sense.
You're so good at this kind of stuff.
- Still mad at me?
- Little bit.
Nash, Allegra will come
around eventually.
You just have to be there when she does.
Trust the process.
- Pretty wise for a Popsicle.
- Thanks.
Got a Dib-ploma to prove it.
Ba-dum-pum.
- Uh... Cool. Can I borrow this?
- Sure.
- I'm really gonna miss you.
- Me, too.
Hm?
I mean, all... We all are.
- Aw. There's hope for you yet.
- Enough. Okay.
Hey, you stay frosty.
- I'm fine.
- No, you're not, and, honey, it's okay.
I promise you, you can handle anything.
You just got to remember,
she's your mom, too.
Of course I am.
Hi, Killer Frost.
Uh...
It's just Frost now.
Hi.
Okay, uh...
We're gonna leave you two alone.
Give us a call
when you get settled in the north.
Mm.
Give 'em hell.
So...
I think I should run a few tests
before we leave.
Check your baseline
for any ribonucleic anomalies.
Great.
Eva's been missing for over 24 hours.
- Where are we with facial recognition?
- Satellites have turned up zilch.
The artificial Speed Force
isn't finished yet,
so I still can't do
my usual sweeps of the city.
- Right. Why are we meeting here?
- I have a backlog of cases.
I can't lose my CSI job
along with everything else.
A job.
Eva said that she had
unfinished business.
Is there any way
that she meant that literally?
If she wants to get McCulloch back,
she does have to deal with Black Hole.
- So, find Black Hole, find Eva.
- Mm-hm.
- Any idea where to start?
- Actually, no.
Maybe.
- Ralph?
- Ralph.
- Where did you get that?
- Sue gave it to me.
- She gave you that?
- She gave that to you?
- She gave that to me.
And it turns out that Black Hole's logo
is embedded inside.
Dude, there is serious UV energy
coming off that thing. Can I?
Oh, yeah.
This is a Triangulation Cartograph.
It's a treasure map.
Allegra, aim it over this.
The center's at 42nd and Darby.
Hang on.
42nd and Darby.
- Holy heck.
- What?
Well, it turns out
that is a ginormous warehouse
with five subterranean levels.
Ralph and I will check it out.
You two, take comms.
Just... excuse me.
Could be a long night.
- I made us a couple of coffees.
- I hate coffee.
No coffee.
- Guys, we're in.
- All right, be careful.
Place like that
could have a guard or two.
More like five.
They were all stabbed.
By a mirror-bayonet, I'm guessing.
That is a lot of bad guy stuff.
It's Black Hole's depository.
Sue said that Carver
was blackmailing her parents.
This is bank statements,
investment records.
This must be everything
that Carver has on them.
- I'm taking this.
- All right.
Smells like gasoline in here.
- Singh?
- I don't want to hurt anyone else.
- Tell that to those guards you killed.
- They left me no choice.
I have to assure Eva's success.
Just put down the flare gun.
Help us bring Carver to justice.
Mother's not interested
in your brand of justice.
Singh. Singh!
- This isn't you.
- You still don't get it, do you?
Carver was there that night.
He let the mirror keep her.
He never tried to rescue her.
Instead, he sold her tech
to the highest bidder...
for weapons, blackmail or worse.
And that is why Carver... is a dead man.
It's not working.
Guys...
Allen, Dibny, are you guys there?
Barely.
- What do we do now?
- The only thing we can.
Protect Carver.
And our guy
knows to destroy anything
that could tie me to the warehouse?
Yes, but there's nothing
left to destroy.
Everything we had was incinerated.
Replace the items, quickly and quietly.
Don't use The Three.
They can't know they're off-leash.
If someone is coming after me,
I'll need their protection.
Hello, Officer Allen.
Please.
You're not here to slap me, are you?
Captain West went for the left side.
How is he, by the way?
Look, there's no easy way
to say this, so...
Your wife wants to kill you,
but C.C.P.D. can keep you safe.
My wife is dead.
Eva's been trapped in another dimension
for the last six years.
A place called the Mirrorverse.
But you already knew that.
If Eva did escape that wretched place,
I'd know.
This is about your wife, isn't it?
I came across this footage from
my wife's office a couple of weeks ago.
Ooh.
- You knew Iris was abducted?
- Your wife was a problem.
Her disappearance was fortuitous.
- What happened to my wife?
- The same thing that happened to my Eva.
- She's gone. They both are.
- No.
- There has to be a way to get her back.
- I used to think that, too.
But if Iris is still alive in there,
there's probably
nothing left of her to save.
I had the most brilliant minds
in the world study that...
Mirrorverse.
You know what they found?
It's incompatible with the human brain.
That place warps the mind until
the person is no longer recognizable.
Your Iris is long gone.
I suggest you accept that and move on.
Oh, one more thing.
How do you know Eva's coming after me?
Who else would've burnt down
your warehouse?
- 42nd and Darby, right?
- I'd never buy on that side of town.
And I don't need protecting.
Give Captain West my best.
Without the satellites,
finding Chief Singh feels impossible.
I know.
We'll have to go find him ourselves.
Every time I interact with this place,
the neural dissonance gets worse.
And what if Eva comes back?
Then what?
Look, things in this place
may be backwards,
but everything works.
We just have to figure out how.
Did you see the map of the city?
You just said looking at those
was too dangerous.
No, I didn't mean to.
But I was thinking about finding David,
and the map came into view.
There was thermal energy
coming from a specific place.
I'm not sure where,
but that has to be David.
There was like a radius,
almost like a beacon.
I feel like if I could just focus,
I can find his location.
No, Iris, come on. Look at you.
No, I'm acclimating
to this place, Kamilla,
that's why I can see the map,
and you can't.
I can find David.
- Mrs. Dearbon.
- Hi.
Mr. Dearbon, so great to see you again.
I have fantastic news.
- So, it turns out that...
- Oh.
So you are the person
my parents employed to find me.
It's so good to meet you.
And please forgive me.
I never meant to cause a stir.
I read Eat Pray Love,
and I took the "pray" part
just a little bit too seriously.
Our Susie joined
a mindfulness retreat in India.
I meant to stay for a month,
and then lost track
of the weeks, months...
Well, it happens, right?
Mr. Dibny, while we're delighted
to have our Susie back,
we realize how much trouble you went to.
Do you have a pen?
Uh...
Oh, heck, wouldn't you know.
I'm fresh out.
Let me just check that hallway closet.
Ms. Dearbon,
- could you help me look for a pen?
- Oh, of course.
We'll be right back.
Do you need a legal pad or anything?
Why would you call my parents?
So, that diamond that you gave me,
it turns out it has a map
for Black Hole's stash house.
I did some recon...
Oh!
I thought breaking and entering
was a line Elongated Man didn't cross.
Would you...
- Inside voices, please.
- I'm sorry.
Look, Carver had files with
your parents' names on them.
Those files contain the evidence
he was using to extort them.
- What do you mean, "had"?
- Well, things got toasty,
and Carver's blackmail arsenal
got cooked.
- You torched the place?
- No. I... No.
Okay. How do I say this?
There's a Mirrorverse dimension.
There's these pod people running around.
They're claiming innocent lives.
It's very Invasion of the Body...
You know what? Why don't
we just forget about that part?
The point is, your parents are safe.
Yeah. Already knew that.
You're welcome. It was really no...
- Wait, what?
- Yeah, Carver called last week.
Said he had a change of heart.
Guys like Carver
don't have hearts to change.
Agreed.
But my parents are safe,
and I can finally go home.
- I don't understand. If we agree...
- Enough, Slick.
You really wanna help me?
Leave us in peace.
Did he say who wants
his head on a pike now?
Who's there?
Hello, Kimiyo.
Shall we do this the easy way...
or the hard way?
Sunshine?
Hoshi?
Ultraviolet?
I'm glad Carver turned you down.
After what he did
to my cousin, Joe, Iris,
he deserves what he gets.
He doesn't deserve to die.
But what if he's telling the truth about
the Mirrorverse affecting minds?
Or he's lying.
He's not exactly the Paragon of Truth.
I don't think he's lying.
I think it could be neural dissonance.
I came across this Earth on my travels
where any visitor to that Earth
immediately suffers
a traumatic psychological state,
neural dissonance.
This could be that.
I'm glad someone believes me.
I need your help after all, Allen.
Federal protection.
The full Joe West treatment.
What happened to your killer minions?
- Eva got to them first, didn't she?
- You gonna help me or not?
Look, get me into protection,
and Joe can get out of it.
One call from me, and he's sleeping
in his own bed tonight.
You're a real piece of work,
you know that?
That sounded like a "yes" to me.
Huh. That's interesting.
The stoichiometric ratio is manifesting
in a way that's abnormal.
It'd be so much easier
if Caitlin were here to help analyze.
I can help.
Oh, I'm sorry. I just meant that
I could use an expert in meta-DNA.
- I forgot.
- I figured.
Probably because every time
you look at me, you just see Thomas...
and the monster he became.
You're not a monster.
You protected Caitlin from her father
and then some, which is a hell
of a lot more than I ever did.
You know, to be honest,
I always kind of
felt like a third wheel.
I'm sorry you felt that way.
No. No.
That must have been horrible.
Then again, I've made
so many mistakes in my life.
Maybe I'm the one who needs fixing.
You're a brilliant scientist who runs
the most successful lab on the planet.
I don't think you need fixing.
'Cause from where I'm standing,
you're a pretty awesome human being.
One I'd like to get to know
a lot better.
I'd like that, too.
What is taking so long?
Federal agents
will be here any minute
to take you into custody.
Officer.
Mr. Carver.
When your paperwork came across my desk,
I thought a VIP such as yourself
shouldn't have to ride
in a two-bit government van.
So I'm here to escort you personally
into custody.
Allen. A word?
Let me walk out of here with Carver,
and Mother will give you Iris.
Eva is not interested in a fight
with you or with your friends.
You knew we were in that warehouse
when you set it on fire.
- That feels like a fight to me.
- Let me have him, Barry.
He's a bad man.
Bring Iris home.
Get your life back.
Are we doing this, or what?
- On my six!
- What the hell?
Will someone please tell me
what the hell is going on?
I saved you. That's what's going on.
- Nash.
- What?
The Barry Allen I know would never,
never have considered that deal.
I knew Eva was ambitious, but...
mirror duplicates?
Eva's more powerful than you thought.
I don't get it.
Why doesn't she just
come after you herself?
Well, Eva's still technically missing,
so she can't be seen in public.
That's why she took Singh.
The Chief of Police
could get close to you.
Fortunately, Mr. Wells
teleported us to safety.
You're welcome.
What is that device?
And how much do you want for it?
- It's not for sale, dirtbag.
- Oh, please.
Everyone has a price.
Hey, listen. We just saved your kiester,
so why don't you put a sock in it
until we can figure out
what to do with you.
So, guess we're stuck
with our new guest for a while.
It's only a matter of time
before Eva shows up here.
Right.
Any mirrored surface
inside S.T.A.R. Labs
is a door for her to walk through.
McCulloch's security system
can protect us.
I have a panic room
Eva doesn't know about.
No offense,
but extra guards and a lockdown
aren't going to help us out here.
I have a biogenic ionization field
that can be activated
around the entire facility.
Anything breaking in
would be atomized in a second.
We just have to get there.
We could take the sewage system,
pop out right underneath R&D.
I break into things.
Hmm.
No time like the present.
Allen.
I wanna ask you a question.
You knew that Carver
was in mortal danger, right,
soon as Mirror Singh
stepped off that elevator?
Why didn't you get him out of there?
I couldn't exactly run him out of there
as Barry Allen.
Or he offered you a deal.
That's the other thing.
I have all these Wellses in my head,
and they all...
They're all screaming the same thing,
that the Barry Allen they knew
would never have hesitated.
You did.
You were considering...
the deal.
You were considering trading
Carver's life to save Iris.
It's more complicated than that.
It's more complicated?
Is it complicated like in the way
you almost killed Eobard Thawne,
and me along with it?
- That was different.
- How is that different?
Iris is my wife. I have to save her.
How do you not understand that?
I do.
But what do you think Iris will say...
when you tell her you traded
another person's life to save hers?
A.R.G.U.S. will be here in an hour
to take you into custody.
Wait, this isn't safe.
Relax, after I saw what happened
to your wife,
I had it coated with protective nanites.
I thought Palmer Tech
and McCulloch were rivals.
Let's just say, what Palmer Tech
doesn't know won't hurt them.
And this is my panic room.
Concrete walls
and not a mirror in sight.
Even if my outer field fails,
Eva can't get in here.
Once the building's clear,
you can engage your ion field.
Then tell your people
to speed up the evacuation.
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Allegra, here.
Take this, just in case.
All right? Any trouble, you should
blast it with one of your UV rays.
All right?
Provide a welcome distraction.
When are you gonna stop trying?
Never.
What the hell?
I knew you were lying.
You really can't take a hint.
You're not here to rob the place.
And Carver didn't have a change of heart
on your parents. You...
You offered to take their place
in Black Hole.
Carver agrees.
I'm more valuable than my parents.
Sue, you...
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I have been trying to collect
leverage on Carver for over a year.
He's untouchable.
Untouchable unless you have one of those
handy-dandy Black Hole pins.
You joined Black Hole
to get close to Carver.
Because you're going to kill him.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
Carver's never going to
let my parents go.
Sue... damn it.
It's the only way it ends.
You gotta listen to me.
There is always another way.
Do you understand what happens
if you kill Carver?
Every time you look in the mirror,
you won't recognize
the person looking back.
- You'll lose yourself.
- Why do you care?
Because I believe in you.
And I know there's still good in you.
I can see it.
I'm sorry about this, Slick.
Oh, come on.
All clear down here.
Ready for the force field when you are.
The ion field's up and running.
Now all that's left to do
is sit and wait.
Cheers.
That's not good.
Guys, the force field
isn't working anymore.
Can we find out what happened
to the power source?
We know what happened.
Carver's Angels invited themselves
to the party.
Something Carver never did.
We're no longer under his thumb.
Neither is Eva.
Whatever she is paying you,
I will double it.
This isn't about a paycheck.
It's about payback.
Eva's coming for you, Carver.
And we're gonna make sure
no one gets in her way.
Nice family reunion.
Eva's going to be here any minute.
We have to get your ion field back up.
- Is there an alternate power source?
- The sub-basement.
There's remote access
to a secondary generator.
Guys, hold them off as long as you can,
I'm going to get the power back on.
You do that.
I know how to handle traitors.
Drop your weapons.
Singh.
You don't want to do this.
This isn't your will.
Eva's will is my will.
Success is assured.
I thought Sunshine was solar powered?
So how the frak is she
frying people at night?
Those bracelets aren't fashion,
they're fuel.
They're solar energy battery packs.
Well, how do we get them off?
Just got to increase the internal
temperature, overload the cells.
- Allegra, if you...
- Already on it.
- She's good.
- What are you gonna do?
I don't know. I'm making it up as I go.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Fine, do it.
You think you're the only one
that feels that way?
The only one that feels alone?
Well, get in line!
Okay, remember when I told you,
if things go sideways, zap the stone?
- Yeah.
- I'd zap the stone.
You came back.
Couldn't let you have all the fun.
Fun must mean something
entirely different when you're rich.
Honey, I'm home.
Guess somebody forgot
to spike the punch.
Let's talk about this.
About what?
How you weaponized my technology?
Extorted charitable donors?
Kidnapped and blackmailed
innocent meta-humans
like Kimiyo, Esperanza and Millie?
This is me talking.
I did what I had to do.
Then I'll do what I have to do.
Goodbye, Joseph.
No, Eva! Wait!
No!
What don't you understand?
He's not worth saving!
Maybe,
but it's not your decision.
Oh, yes, it is.
My husband...
let me rot in that world for years.
He does not get to live in this one.
You're not my wife.
My wife died
in the particle accelerator explosion.
Well...
I've never felt more alive.
You're not even... human.
No. Oh, no.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
God.
What are you doing here?
I'm making this up as I go.
Right.
Flash...
Barry, you and I are not enemies.
We never have been.
You just killed him in cold blood.
Your wife set out to catch a bad man.
She couldn't.
But together, we could.
- We're on the same side.
- No.
Just remember that.
All right, on three,
everybody go crazy.
Got it.
That seems like bad advice.
Song title. No, I like it.
It'll be good. All right.
One, two...
Stand down.
Joseph is dead.
Well, I didn't see that coming.
You're going to let us go?
Of course.
I've achieved my goal for today.
We'll never stop coming after you.
You'll fail.
This building, this company...
is all mine.
And you and your little friends
are trespassing, so...
run along, little Barry.
Before I have to call the police.
Mrs. McCulloch,
where have you been all this time?
Well, over the past six years,
I have been held hostage
by an international crime syndicate.
Forced to watch
as they stole my technology
and used it to create deadly weapons.
How did you escape?
My husband, Joseph...
he worked tirelessly to try to find me.
And he succeeded.
Only to be murdered
moments after we were reunited.
Words cannot express my sorrow.
But know that I am working
with the C.C.P.D.
to try to find my husband's murderer.
And as for McCulloch Technologies,
I will be resuming my position as CEO,
effective immediately.
It's what Joseph would've wanted.
Thank you.
Going somewhere?
Carver's dead.
Which means my parents are finally free.
So am I.
I'm going home.
Sue, I'm not sure you can.
Eva framed you.
For Carver's murder.
Barry, we've been through
stuff like this before, don't worry.
You're going to find a way
to stop Eva and get Iris back.
I can't even be frustrated without...
losing more of it.
Maybe instead of focusing
on what you've lost,
you should try remembering
what you'll never lose.
The reason you beat
Zoom, Godspeed, Thawne...
is because speed isn't what drives you.
It's love.
That's your true force.
And there is nothing artificial
about that.
So as long as you stay true to yourself,
you will always find a way
to beat the bad guys.
And gals.
I'm going to miss you.
I'll be back before you know it.
All set? The car's downstairs.
I promise I'll get these two back to you
and your team as soon as possible.
Thanks.
Yeah, okay.
Hey...
Frost can hear me too, right?
As long as she's awake.
I'm awake, really.
Go ahead.
Just...
Get better.
And hurry back. We still have
a white water rafting trip to take.
I'm holding you to that.
She says she can't wait.
Tell the team I miss 'em already.
I will.
Well, well.
This is a little quieter.
Yeah.
Hey, look, I know that...
I'm not your favorite person, but...
if ever you need anything,
if ever you need my coffee...
What happened to "I don't like coffee"?
Uh...
Okay.
- Thanks.
- For what?
For this.
Of course.
What did it do to her? My cousin?
It made her relive her worst memory.
You know what?
You hang on to it.
Just in case you need it again.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
- Iris and the others,
they're still Eva's prisoners.
We're going to get them back.
And remember, we still have one thing
that Eva doesn't...
hope.
We also have reinforcements.
- Oh.
- Joe.
How are you here?
Well, it turns out that
when the guy that's trying to kill you
kicks the bucket,
they lift the protection detail.
- That makes sense.
- Nash.
Hey, man. Yeah.
- Hey.
- You're just in time.
Team needs you now more than ever.
Well, let's go save some people we love.
You have been at this for hours.
Barry wouldn't give up.
And the woman
that he married wouldn't either.
I found him.
David's at Central City Hospital.
I can't believe I just did that.
Holy frak!
Iris, you can control this place.
Iris.
Iris, stay with me.
Iris!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::