Previously on The Flash...
So, this is where
you've been hiding.
I think you're afraid
to use your powers,
because you think you'll become
like someone you hate.
I know you're doing it for all of us.
That's what it means to be a hero.
I knew I picked the right guy.
- He's gonna die.
- Frost, how do we save him?
I don't know! I can't fix this!
Accepting Ramsey's blood would save
your body, but not your soul.
You would lose the best of you.
The part of you that Iris loves.
That's not Barry.
Barry?
The entire world will embrace...
Bloodwork!
- Are you guys okay?
- Yeah.
I don't understand. That wasn't Barry.
Yeah, it was.
Ramsey turned him
into one of his Blood Brothers.
Babel Protocols initiated.
What's "Babel Protocols"?
I thought that was just some defense
stuff that you added to Barry's suit.
That was version one.
Version 2.0 puts up a forcefield
around S.T.A.R. Labs.
Nothing gets in, nothing goes out.
Not even our comms.
I built them just in case...
Just in case the Flash ever went dark.
Barry said that Ramsey
gave him a choice. Why...
Why would he choose this?
Maybe he decided eternal life
was better than dying in Crisis.
Ramsey's using Barry.
And whatever he's having him do,
he's got a plan.
You have a police scanner?
I'm hoping that since this thing
transmits in analog,
we can figure out what's going on
outside S.T.A.R. Labs.
I don't get it.
Why didn't Ramsey just have
Barry kill us as soon as he woke up?
I don't know,
but don't count us out yet.
You know that tech I've been working on?
- Meet the photon emitter.
- So, what, you built a ray gun?
It's not a ray gun. It's a weapon
that can deliver mega doses
of photon radiation,
the same kind of radiation
typically administered
to cancer patients.
What exactly does it do?
My theory is that these photons
could be strong enough
to destroy Ramsey's sentient infection.
If I get close enough to blast him,
he should revert back to his human form.
He'd still have HLH,
but at least he wouldn't be
a gooey zombie overlord anymore.
What about everyone else that was
infected? Would they be cured?
Yes. They'd lose the goo,
they'd go back to normal.
But since Ramsey's the only one
who can create more Blood Brothers,
I say we hit him first, then Dark Flash.
And you've tested this?
Well, I haven't even finished
building it,
so no... No, I haven't tested it.
So, let me get this straight.
You wanna shoot radiation at my husband
out of some crazy powerful device
that you've never tested?
Iris, this is the only plan we have.
This could kill Barry, Cisco.
Is anyone there? Please, help me!
The city's being overrun!
I'm using a police officer's radio.
He's turning into
some kind of a monster.
His eyes are black.
Ramsey's spreading his infection.
That's why he took down
communications citywide.
Caitlin once said,
Ramsey's infection samples indicate
he needs his victims to be afraid
before he attacks them.
Hey, is your Internet working?
- What's with the lights?
- I don't know.
Who's that?
Get inside. Get inside.
He looks like he has rabies
or something.
Mitch Romero. You remember the mobster
that Ramsey turned into a Blood Brother?
Well, Joe said that he looked
just like that.
Come here.
What... What do we do?
We gotta get out of this building.
Run!
Freeze!
Remember, these people are innocent!
Nonlethal force only!
Your efforts
are in vain, Captain.
I'm going to transform this city
by dawn, and you can't stop me.
Stand down, Dr. Rosso.
Rosso is my human name,
and he had human plans.
My name is Bloodwork now,
and I am not alone.
Flash, this isn't you.
Whatever happened to you,
we will fix it.
It's humanity that needs fixing.
Why would he let that happen?
'Cause this isn't Barry anymore.
Ramsey, whatever the hell your plan is,
we will stop you.
I've already done it.
I've cured death. But not for you.
Continue our mission.
Kill them.
I'm coming for you.
You seek the truth.
Novu.
If you wish to know all,
show your allegiance,
and all will be revealed.
Yeah, that sounds great. Oh, wait, no.
I don't barter with false gods!
Bow down to me...
And all you desire
shall be yours.
Let me in.
Let me in!
Bow down to me!
Planet after planet, Earth after Earth,
I've tracked you, Novu,
and you think some paltry mind games
and a little rock wall is gonna stop me?
You've got another thing coming.
I'm coming for you,
and you can't stop me!
Hmm.
What's this now?
Punishment from an angry god...
or simply faulty wiring.
I say, let there be light.
Still nothing.
Hey, girl, we got this.
We just need to get to the end
of the hallway, to the stairwell.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, I can't.
- I can't even move.
- What's wrong?
Fear.
There's so much fear, and I can feel it.
And I think there must be
other people in the building.
Place is empty.
No one else is working this late.
It's everywhere! And I can't...
I can't stop it,
and I can't keep it out of my head!
Okay, okay, okay.
I believe you. I believe you.
Cisco told me that Ramsey needs
his victims to be scared
for the infection to take.
Something about
a fear-related amino acid.
What if you're feeling
what those zombies are feeling?
The fear inside them.
Whatever it is, just make it stop.
Cecile, don't you get it?
You're a fricking zombie detector.
You're our way out of here.
We've got another 207 downtown.
All available units respond!
207 is an abduction.
There's been ten of those
in the last five minutes.
Iris,
I know you're listening.
I need to see you.
Meet me where our life together began.
Where you said yes.
Iris, that's not him.
That might sound like Barry,
it might even look like him,
but that is Dark Flash.
You don't know that.
What if Barry is still alive in there?
What if it's a trap, all right?
We don't even have comms.
It's too risky.
Listen to me.
I just need to look him in his eyes.
If the emitter doesn't work on Ramsey,
I get to come back
and try something else.
But if you go out there,
and that's not Barry,
you could get infected, or worse!
Please.
In sickness and in health.
Iris. Iris!
Barry?
Yes, Iris?
It's me.
And so much more.
Ramsey.
Neat little trick, huh?
Don't you see now, Iris?
Come on.
My control over
my Blood Brothers
and Sisters is absolute.
As more cured souls accept my lifeblood,
they become extensions
of one collective body.
Mine.
You asked me here. Why?
To offer you a chance.
Barry would want you to follow him
down this path he chose.
- No.
- The path of life.
You aren't saving lives, Ramsey.
You're destroying
what makes one beautiful.
Barry, I know you can hear me.
And you can hear
when I tell you that I love you.
And after everything
that we've been through together...
I know that this is not
how our story ends.
Come home to me.
Why would Barry come home to you?
You accepted his death in Crisis
as inevitable.
What kind of wife is willing
to bury her husband?
Iris, get out of there.
In good time.
This is not over.
Trust me, Iris.
Are you okay?
No.
I piggybacked the audio
off the extrapolator.
I'm sorry.
I have to try again.
Iris.
He almost killed you.
- We can't just give up, Cisco.
- We're not.
But if we're gonna take down
Bloodwork and Dark Flash,
we need to do it with a photon emitter.
- You haven't even tested that thing.
- We have no time.
Maybe you don't remember,
but we actually have been preparing
for this for weeks.
No, we've been preparing for the Flash
to die trying to save this world,
not helping to destroy it.
It doesn't matter!
We were gonna lose him anyway!
This is the moment he prepared us for.
We still have four hours.
That is 240 minutes,
and I am not letting Ramsey take
a single one of those from me.
I am not giving up on Barry.
He's my husband.
He was.
And he was my best friend.
And no one's giving up on anybody,
because there is nothing left
to give up on.
Iris, he's gone.
He was always gonna leave us.
And whether or not the emitter works,
it's not gonna change that.
The emitter's almost ready.
And when it is,
I'm gonna use it on Bloodwork,
and I'm gonna use it on Dark Flash.
Joe!
Just lie still.
- Get the hell away from her.
- Allegra.
Frost, is Captain West okay?
No. We need to get the hell out of here.
Let's go.
Get away. Get away from there.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
Come on.
Wait!
Come on! Come on!
Oh, God. Help me!
That's not gonna hold for very long.
S.T.A.R. Labs is still ten blocks away.
Ten blocks. Ten blocks.
We can do it. Let's go.
Rise, my Blood Brother and Blood Sister.
You are cured.
Now you will never die.
Feel the burn, Bloodwork!
Is that all you've got, Mr. Ramon?
- Too bad.
- Cisco!
My lifeblood is a gift.
Are you ready to receive it?
No.
You have another purpose to serve.
The reckoning is near.
My army is almost ready
to march on S.T.A.R. Labs.
What the hell do you want
with S.T.A.R. Labs?
The particle accelerator.
The very tech you helped to create
will be the vessel
carrying my glorious cure.
Soon, all of Central City
will be granted eternal life.
And I choose you, Mr. Ramon,
to be my messenger.
Go.
Tell your team, the great
S.T.A.R. Labs particle accelerator
is ready to fulfil its true purpose.
- Salvation is nigh.
- An ass-whupping is nigh, pal.
And you're gonna lose, Ramsey.
You're gonna lose.
Plucky right up until the end.
I knew I picked the right guy.
Iris! If you're listening,
I'm coming home!
Look at this.
Ramsey wasn't lying.
Barry hacked the particle accelerator.
He was getting it ready for Bloodwork.
That's why he was pretending
to be Barry.
But why?
If Ramsey drops even just a tiny
amount of his blood into the core,
and it explodes,
the infectious cells will aerosolize,
and it would infect
all of Central City in seconds.
All you'd have to do is take a breath.
Dad!
Do something, Frost.
I can't. I can't handle this.
There's a lot of blood loss.
Looks like a nicked spleen.
Frost, I don't have the equipment I need
to close up this complicated of a wound,
but you can with your ice powers.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
- Frost, come on.
- After Ralph and Barry...
Frost, take control.
- How?
- Let yourself feel the fear,
count to three, and do it anyway.
Because that's what heroes do.
One, two...
Three.
You like that?
For the record,
both our plans failed.
Yeah.
I just went in one direction,
while you went in the other,
instead of figuring out a plan together.
Yeah.
I should have made that happen.
I should have led the team.
Well, it's not too late.
I mean, Barry chose you for a reason.
Don't doubt yourself, Cisco.
What?
Something Ramsey said.
"I knew I picked the right guy."
Barry said those words.
Barry said those exact words to me
when he made me team leader.
Ramsey could have infected me.
He could have killed me.
But he didn't. Instead, he just did
a complete 180 for no reason.
There's something else.
Ramsey said, "I'm coming home."
I begged Barry to come home
the last time I saw him,
but I didn't think that
I was getting through.
Iris, what if that was Barry?
What if you were right,
and he's still alive inside Dark Flash?
Then he could be trying
to tell us what to do.
Like how to take down Bloodwork.
Someone's at the barrier.
I have arrived
to fulfil my destiny.
And yes, my army is coming.
Iris, Cisco...
let the light in.
I think I just figured out Barry's plan.
He just told us the next step.
We need to lower the defenses.
Let them in.
It's time to put an end to death
once and for all.
Find the humans who've rejected
my lifeblood and kill them.
You want me to do what?
Barry's plan is to let the light in.
It isn't for Ramsey to spread
his infection to the city,
it's for you to spread the antidote...
With one hell of a UV blast.
But I can't do that.
Don't worry.
I've done all the calculations.
We'll walk you through the whole thing.
Just get to the Pipeline, now.
Good evening, Team Flash.
I have tried repeatedly
to bestow upon you eternal life,
and yet you've refused.
So now, instead of continuing
to offer you the gift of life,
I've ordered my Blood Brothers
to take it from you.
Now, as you run
for your worthless lives,
do keep in mind that your leader,
Flash, belongs to me now.
I have his access codes,
his handprint, his knowledge.
My objective will be achieved.
Bring me Iris and Cisco.
Barry. Barry...
I want you to know
the scope of your failure.
My lifeblood is circling
the accelerator.
And when it gathers enough speed,
it'll collide with the energy inside,
and the resulting collision
will cure this city.
And you.
Barry.
Barry, I trust you.
What are you doing? Kill her!
Barry.
We are one, you and I.
It's pointless to fight it.
I know you want to execute my will.
I can feel it inside you, Flash.
Much better.
Get ready to run.
- What are you gonna do?
- What I do.
Barry?
We only have about
five rotations left before collision.
How long is each rotation?
A few seconds, if we're lucky.
- Allegra, where the hell are you?
- Right here.
When I open this door,
you need to hit these particles
with all the UV rays you've got.
You got this. Don't hold back.
One rotation left!
Now!
Hey.
Barry.
It's me.
Hey, uh, where's the scary guy
who tried to kill us all?
He won't get far.
I won't be denied.
Okay. Just stay here.
You can't control me anymore.
And I'm not gonna let you
hurt anybody else.
For the last time,
I am trying to save everyone!
Don't you understand?
You're not the hero here. I am!
- Cisco, are you with me?
- Always.
Babel's been lifted, comms are up.
We are back.
What do we have that can hold Ramsey?
After Mitch Romero,
we know a Pipeline cell won't work.
The MAC. It contained
Chester's black-hole energy.
So, Ramsey should be a walk in the park.
Flash, you okay?
Stay down!
Any last words before your death?
I just wanna enjoy the time I have left.
I felt the same way.
My beautiful boy.
Ramsey...
what have you done?
My son...
I've missed you so much.
Mom?
- How is this even possible?
- I brought her.
You entered my mind to bring out
that doubt that was hidden inside.
I let you infect me, so I could
return the favor and bring out yours.
Impossible. I have no doubt.
Only conviction.
Ramsey, I would give anything to have
just one more day with my mom.
You have that chance right now.
Listen to her.
He's right.
You were born to heal.
But you've become
an angel of destruction.
No. This isn't happening.
This isn't real.
My dear son...
you wanted so desperately to save me.
Now let me save you from yourself.
I just wanted to help them all.
No!
No. She was wrong.
I was born to save the world!
And I still can.
Can you hear me, Flash?
I was chosen to save the world.
And when I escape these chains,
I will complete my destiny,
and you will all accept my cure.
Containment protocols holding.
It worked.
We did it. We beat him.
Now it's time for our next fight.
Lyla says Ramsey is officially
in A.R.G.U.S. custody.
And I called the local hospitals.
Ramsey's infection doesn't seem
to have any long-lasting effects.
So, everyone's gonna be okay?
Everyone except Ramsey.
Frost ran some tests,
and it looks like
his condition is, um...
pretty permanent.
Joe's resting in the lounge,
and I think I'm gonna go check on him.
What was it like being Dark Flash?
I knew what was happening,
but I couldn't stop it.
Honestly, it took everything I had
just to keep from hurting you guys.
But as the night went on,
I could tell I was getting to him.
I could feel him doubting himself
more and more.
Thank you for what you did.
You saved the city.
Right back at you.
But you should really thank Frost.
She got me there.
- She's badass.
- Yeah, she is.
Speaking of, where is the ice queen?
Caity, I know the last couple of days
have been a roller coaster,
but I just wanted to say thanks.
For believing in me,
even when I didn't believe in myself.
No thanks needed.
And for what it's worth,
I'm really proud of how you've grown
these past few months.
I can't wait to see where you go next.
Me too.
But, for tonight,
I think you should take over.
It's only right
that you're with the team
for whatever Crisis is about to bring.
Guys...
sitting in silence really isn't
how I want to spend
the next few minutes.
Joe...
When you gave me your watch,
it meant... It meant the world to me.
I wanna give you mine.
So I know, wherever I go...
a part of me is with you.
I love you for that.
But you're not going anywhere yet...
so you hold on to it.
All right.
H.R. Wells told me once...
"Barry Allen's superpower isn't speed.
It's hope.
It's hope. And that kid has
an endless reservoir of it."
I didn't know how right he was until
I really got to know you, Barry.
Whatever is about to happen,
this world's a better place
for having you in it.
You know,
when you first came into my life,
I had lost faith
in just about everything.
You saved my life, Barry.
God, I remember the old days.
No doppelgangers,
no Flashpoint, no time travel.
It was just us against the bad guys.
I miss that.
I don't know.
I kind of like time travel.
When you were stuck in the Speed Force,
I would have Cisco vibe me
to the waterfront
so I could watch our first kiss.
You know, the one that you had
to erase from the timeline
to save the world.
Why'd you do that?
I don't know.
I guess when you're filled with sadness,
happy thoughts are what
get you through the day.
And what's happier than...
getting to have your first kiss
with the love of your life,
other than getting to do it twice?
Our love story never ends, Barry.
Not even with Crisis.
Iris, it's inevitable.
Maybe.
But whether you vanish...
or worse, I am gonna be there with you.
I'll be right there with you
to the very end, okay?
Because the only thing
more inevitable than Crisis is us.
Iris is right.
Whatever's in store for us,
it can't change
what we mean to each other.
It can't erase what's in our hearts.
As long as we hold on to that...
we've beaten Crisis
before it even begins.
For so many years,
I've traveled across worlds...
...across the multi-verse,
to do one thing.
To kill you.
And now, here...
you saved my life.
Submit and begin your life anew.
Show me.
The knowledge is within you.