Previously on "The Flash"...
Together, you and Cynthia
could be an unstoppable duo.
You wanna be the new Breacher?
Your Thinking Cap and the dark matter
- is what caused this.
- I know!
How long before
everything I know is gone?
DeVoe has taken out everyone
who's gotten in his way.
He created 12 meta-humans,
just so he could
steal their powers.
Why does he need their powers?
The fire that burns down Team Flash
will also light the path
to the Enlightenment.
Since the age of Enlightenment,
when reason, debate, and the
search for truth flourished,
the world has improved
by nearly every measure
in human advancement,
and continues to do so.
There is no doubt in my mind
that as technology continues to bloom,
so will all of humanity.
Professor DeVoe?
You disagree?
Well, uh, yes, I guess.
Just, I have a more realistic view
of humanity whenever
technology is concerned.
What do you mean?
Well, you spoke of the Enlightenment.
One only has to look at
history to find the answers.
Okay, let's.
Life expectancy over
the past two centuries
has increased from 30
years to nearly 70 years.
And-and we should assume
that's a good thing?
Each new day, we have to share
very limited resources
with anything up to
200,000 newborn babies,
most of whom will end up living
in abject poverty and famine.
Well, thank you very much,
Professor Doom and Gloom.
Remind me never to take
one of your history classes.
Perhaps you should. There's
much I could teach you.
The Taoists, in pursuit of immortality,
discovered gunpowder.
Alfred Nobel created the Nobel Prize
so he wouldn't be remembered
as the man who invented dynamite.
History has shown us time and time again
that whenever a
technological advancement
can be used to hurt
humanity, it will be.
You can't blame technology for the way
men choose to use it, Professor.
You can't ignore that the best of ideas
by the smartest of men often have a way
of becoming corrupted.
You've located everything we need.
And now the time has come to retrieve it
so we can finally...
enlighten the world.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Uh-oh.
Hey, babe.
Uh, it's me. Just checking in.
For my dad.
He... really wants to know your answer
about taking the Breacher job.
I think his exact words were:
"That little son of a
Breach better tell me,
or they will never find the body."
Yeah. But you know what?
He's retired. He can wait.
So just take as much time as you need.
- Okay? It's, um...
- Don't say it's fine.
- You know.
- It's fine.
- Oh, God.
- Okay.
So, just five me. Whenever.
Okay. Bye.
Ramon, speed lab. Now.
Good! Good, good, good.
Good, good, good good, good.
Thing we're gonna do
to get Killer Frost
to appear, get that massive spike
in your adrenaline
production that we need,
is, Ramon is gonna use his vibes
to shake you up on the cellular level,
and let's see if we
can't get your old friend
Killer Frost to come out to play.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
Well, I mean, like any hypothesis,
you have to test it to get an answer.
It's what we've all done since
the fourth grade, known as the...
Scientific method?
Right you are, Allen!
Of course. Ah, here he is.
Okay, good. So get in position.
Don't worry, I lowered
the amps on this thing.
Ramon, you set?
Yeah.
Snow, you ready?
I'm ready.
Three, two, one, and...
Nothing.
All right. Ramon, more power.
Set? Three, two, one...
All right, this isn't working.
You know what, Ramon? Full power.
Wait, hold on, hold
on. What do you mean,
full power? We don't
want to blast Caitlin
across the speed lab.
Well, you need to get a
spike in her adrenaline.
- Harry, she could get injured.
- Yeah.
God, this is... Look, this is
gonna work, okay? Nothing has changed.
All right? Snow's DNA tests,
they confirm it. Her meta-DNA
was not spliced by Noah's powers.
You mean Melting Point's powers.
Right, that's what I said.
Melting Point's powers.
- No, you didn't.
- I did say that.
But, Harry,
there's no dark matter
in her system anyway.
We're just trying to
spike her heart rate.
What do you mean,
there's no dark matter?
Harry, you knew that.
We all did.
We did? We did. No, I know.
I just, I think I
just, you know, forget.
I forgot.
You forgot?
Harry, are you okay?
No. He's not.
Harry, you're...
Losing my intelligence? Yes.
The injection of dark
matter from the Thinking Cap
apparently overwhelmed my synapses.
Instead of making my
brain faster, it's...
slowing it down.
Why didn't you tell us this sooner?
How long until...
No way of knowing.
I mean, there are days
I can think clearly
and other days...
I... I can't.
The good news is, um,
from what I can see,
the regression seems to be reversible.
Okay, great.
I'll start working on it full-time.
No, you won't.
I did this to myself,
and I-I thought "Oh, you know what?
"Use that Thinking Cap, and then I can
outthink Devoe and then stop DeVoe."
I was wrong. Now here we are.
Okay, well, we're gonna fix this.
You and I both know
there's a ticking clock...
and I can't help anyone like this.
Yes, you can.
How?
Look, guys.
Ralph...
Caitlyn's powers, now this.
DeVoe knew how to break us apart, but...
I mean, we're all still here.
We're a family.
That's how we're gonna beat DeVoe.
All right, Allen.
All right.
Vandermeer Steel.
Smaller than I expected.
The first step to our Enlightenment
is as simple...
As opening a door.
Alloy 1771.
Now, the gallium antimonide
substrates within these
can harness power at 400% efficiency.
The precise amount, I calculated.
You can pick 'em up.
Freeze!
You should let us leave.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
How are you...
We have what we need.
I suppose we do.
Code Red! Code Red!
Clifford. This is unnecessary.
You knew there were gonna be casualties
when we began.
This is his own doing.
Yes, my love.
What are we dealing with?
First of all, we're trying to determine
what was in that vault.
Watch your step right here.
There was no drilling,
there was no lock picked.
And the only thing anybody would tell us
about what was in the vault was that
it was some sort of
secretive technology.
Also, security guard here
was a 24-year-old,
apparently shot himself.
Wait, a robbery and a suicide?
He was newly married.
Has an infant at home.
This is smelling like
some meta madness to me.
Who else can "Kilgore" a retinal scan
and "Dibny" a vault lock?
Okay, well, I'm gonna
go interview some people,
see what I can find out.
All right, Cisco and I will try
to figure out what DeVoe stole.
All right. I'll be over here.
Okay, so. Where should we start?
I'm thinking: if we can gain acc...
to their files...
Alloy 1771?
It's the only item missing
from the inventory files.
Or I can just... stand
here and look pretty.
Hey, know what you can do, actually?
You could vibe the gun.
The file didn't say what Alloy 1771 was.
So we need another way to learn
why DeVoe would want it.
Uh, vibing and DeVoe
do not mix, remember?
Yeah, I know, man. But I mean,
what are we supposed to
do? It's the only way.
Barry, I don't really feel like
getting blasted into a wall right now.
I'm sure there's another way we can
find out what this is that doesn't
require me getting a migraine.
It is a solar panel.
Constructed of metal that absorbs
and multiplies the sun's energy
at 400% efficiency.
What would DeVoe be
doing with a solar panel?
Nothing, on its own.
He's gotta be building something.
Look, I-I need you to vibe the gun.
Maybe I should put this
in movie terms for you.
Everything in DeVoe's wake is
like the "Home Alone" house.
Okay? It's booby-trapped.
I would need to double my powers
just to even attempt to vibe the gun.
Well, hold on. I mean, could...
Could Gypsy double your powers?
- That's a good idea.
- No, not.
Not what?
Gypsy's busy.
Her dad just retired.
She's having to do double the work.
Earth 19 is a mess
right now. She's swamped.
Cisco.
Combining your powers could make it
so we know DeVoe's next move.
Thanks for meeting me.
- I need a favor.
- Okay.
I need you to distract
Cecile for a while.
What for?
Well, that's the thing.
I can't tell you, because if I do,
she'll read your mind and find out.
Why can't Iris do it?
Because Iris knows exactly why
I'm trying to distract Cecile.
- Ah.
- And therefore Barry knows.
Which means that Cisco knows, Kid knows.
- Whatever you need.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
You're welcome. All right.
Lose my mind, become a babysitter.
Oh, come on.
Listen, if anybody's gonna
reverse what's happening,
it's gonna be those
kids at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I mean, they love you, Harry.
And they will never
stop trying to help you.
- So don't lose hope.
- Right.
And that is how I aced
my intro to heat transfer
my first year at university.
Bravo.
Ducked and run.
I miss those days.
I was young and foolish and brave.
And now you're just foolish.
To agree to a date with someone
I first met as they were so rudely
disagreeing with my
professional opinion.
Foolish, maybe.
Yeah, no one's ever
challenged me like that.
It was refreshing.
Ah, maybe you are right
about technology's distracting us.
It certainly can destroy moments.
Although, sometimes...
technology...
can create them as well.
Thanks for coming to help us, Gypsy.
You two are up.
So, how do we do this?
Okay, so to co-vibe, we
have to be totally in sync.
All right? Our minds have to be on
exactly the same page.
Just like always.
Yeah.
Oh. So that was weird.
Why? What did you see?
I don't know, a-a dock?
Um, looked like a shipping container.
Number 16.
That must be what DeVoe
is gonna steal next.
He's gonna have to steal it from us.
All right.
It looks like we made it in time.
Whatever's in this container,
we can't let DeVoe have it.
Actually...
it's what's in... this container
you can't let me have.
Well...
what was in this container.
Hit him!
Gratitude...
for the workout, brief as it was.
Later.
Damn it. Damn it!
Why didn't we see the
right container number?
Someone's vibe wasn't
clear enough, Cisco.
Are you blaming me?
You lost your focus, what can I say?
Yeah, getting hit against
a metal container wall
sort of does that.
You know, I hit that wall too.
I'm perfectly focused.
Oh, well, if you're so focused,
then why'd you let him get away?
Don't even try and put that on me.
I'm sorry, I didn't put that on you.
You put that on you.
I'm gonna put my fist in your face,
- is what I'm gonna...
- Is that how we'd work together
if I took the job?
Guys. What job?
I brought that metal piece
from the shipping container,
in case we want to try
co-vibing later, but...
think we both saw
where that led us, so...
So you said... Breacher retired.
He offered you a job on Earth
19 to replace him, didn't he?
Mm-hmm.
You know, another shot in the dark,
but you haven't actually given Breacher
or Gypsy an answer yet.
Mm-mm.
Which way you leaning?
I wanna be with Gypsy
more than anything.
It's just complicated.
Hey, no, man, I get it.
But look, I mean...
maybe...
you guys working together to end this
will make the decision
easier, for both of you.
What if she doesn't want
the same thing as me?
I mean, you're never
gonna know unless you ask.
And listen, Cisco, I mean...
we can't beat DeVoe without you.
You're our secret weapon.
You and Gypsy just need to be
on the same page for
that weapon to work.
Yeah, and I don't know that we can be.
All right, well...
let me help you.
- Barry.
- No, I... hold on.
So that's gonna end well.
Last one.
Okay, we, uh, need food.
We need wine.
Lots of both. Go.
I'll unpack.
Clifford!
Go. Hurry home.
I can stay, if... You're sure?
- Yeah.
- I really should.
Last chance.
_
Me, hunter!
Me hunted feast for my queen!
You don't believe these things you wrote
in this journal, do you?
This reads like some
radical's manifesto, Clifford.
It is a realist's awakening.
You declare war against every
technological philanthropist.
Men, men, men.
Pushing us to the brink of Armageddon
with their "inventions."
No, they want a better mankind.
Don't be naive, Marlize.
The severity of our society's failings
require extreme ideas if ever we were to
restore some semblance of balance.
"Technology has become a cancerous cell
in our social biology.
Exercising it... would
require a total purge,
not only of the material world,
but also human consciousness"?
This is not balance! This
is lobotomizing people!
It is rebooting the masses' brains,
to let them forget their
technological crutches!
They are babies with pacifiers!
Oh, and who will teach them?
You, Professor?
How does any of this help humankind?
Don't you see? Marlize...
Our technology is killing us.
You and I, we can fix this.
Together.
As partners.
We can lead them, all
of society, humanity,
on the true path to Enlightenment.
Hey, Harry.
DA Cecile Horton.
Joe said you needed to adjust
my mental activity dampener.
Yes. Joe... yes.
I have to do that. It's,
uh, it's not a big deal.
It's a standard procedure.
That's, yeah. Okay.
All right. I'm in.
Well, it's installing, so...
now you just... you just sit.
And wait.
For a long time.
Okay. What is happening
with your thoughts right now?
With my... okay.
So... there was an
incident with dark matter...
Yeah, I know, I know,
Joe told me about that.
- That's not what I'm talking about.
- What do you mean?
Your thoughts are screaming at me.
It's like they start to form,
and then, it's like,
the more the ideas appear...
- The more they disappear.
- Exactly.
Well, that explains my "can't" days.
What does that mean, Harry?
It means, DA Cecile Horton,
that the more I try to use my brain...
the sooner I'm going to lose it.
Barista. Another one, please.
Uh, make it a double.
Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Can't a woman caffeinate in peace
around here?
Hey. Look. Hey!
I know why you're upset,
but it's all right.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, Cisco just thinks
if he takes the job,
he'll be letting us down. But, I mean,
he just needs to follow his own heart,
do what he needs to
do, not worry about us.
He knows that.
Wow. That's actually really great.
So now... all you guys have to do
is talk to each other.
Yeah. Well, that part's
not so easy, so...
Yes... it is.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Don't even think about. No!
Okay.
Don't ever "whoosh" me again, all right?
Totally, I'm sorry. Um, Cisco.
What is going on?
Just getting 'em back
on the same page, okay?
Cisco, Gypsy is upset, because, frankly?
I mean, it's taking
you too long to accept
Breacher's job offer. Duh. And Gypsy.
Cisco, he's-he's just worried
about abandoning his team.
I mean, it's not that
he doesn't want the job.
Right? Okay, so...
Now you both know, right?
And you can dive in and...
work this out... Let's talk about this.
CCPD is reporting two more break-ins
at tech manufacturers... Boeing Lab
and the Jamison Institute.
More hardware was stolen.
- DeVoe.
- Was anybody hurt?
Three fatalities, all
of them security guards
in high-level clearance
areas, just like at Vandermeer.
He's taking whatever he wants,
killing anybody that gets in the way.
Guys, I-I'm sorry, but
we have to figure out
what kind of machine
he's building, right now.
Look, we have to try.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh, God, are you okay?
- I saw that one coming.
- You okay?
- I'm good. Thank you.
They okay?
Tests show, physically, they're fine.
As a couple, not so much.
Where are you going?
I need to get these two back in sync.
I mean, we gotta get
ahead of this somehow.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down, cowboy.
What do you mean? Why?
Maybe you've done enough already, okay?
Cisco and Gypsy are
clearly going through
something, and, you
know, it's not up to us
to counsel them through it.
Well, then who is it up to, Iris?
- Just stop for a second...
- We can't stop.
The second we do,
everyone could fall apart.
The team's hanging on by a thread.
- But we are hanging on, Barry.
- For how long?
I mean, look at what's happening.
DeVoe is killing innocent people.
He's stealing pieces of
tech, for God knows why.
Just trying to keep up with
him is tearing us apart.
Babe... you can't put it on yourself
to hold everyone together.
Cisco is family.
And when family hurts, we all hurt.
I get that.
But sometimes you can't answer
their questions for them.
Sometimes, you just have to support them
while they find them on their own,
whether they're together
or they're apart.
What?
That's it.
The pieces of tech don't fit together...
because they're not supposed to.
He's not building one thing,
he's building multiple.
Harry, I know this is hard.
Well...
it is hard, DA Cecile
Horton, because my brain,
the one thing that has defined me
for, well, pretty much my entire life,
is about to...
vanish, and then who will I be?
You'll be the exact same
man you've always been.
Yeah, but dumb.
Same man. Way less intelligent.
Harry.
There are lots of
ways to be intelligent.
Not just using your head.
Right.
Wait.
Do that again. Harry!
- Do what?
- Do it again! Do it again!
Right?
- How did you do that?
- I saw it!
Inside your mind, before it vanished.
In... wait. So you can...
Write down what you're thinking.
- Before it...
- Disappears.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Marlize? I brought the sample.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Okay.
All right.
- Fingers crossed.
- Yep.
Here we go.
Cheers.
- Yes!
- Yeah?
- Show the others.
- Got it.
Hello?
Marlize.
It's me.
Clifford.
I need you to come home.
I can't.
I'm making a difference
here... I'm changing lives
for the better. These people need me.
I need you.
I'm sorry.
I can't be with someone that thinks
that society is a disease, that believes
that our world is being
plagued by technology.
I am nothing without you.
You're a brilliant man
with a great future ahead of you.
What kind of future do I have
if you are not by my side?
I just wish that you could show
the same compassion
for the rest of humanity
as you do for me.
Listen to me, Marlize, I...
my thoughts, I cannot...
I-I just... I just don't think that...
Marlize?
Marlize!
So... what were you gonna say?
Before we were so
alarmingly interrupted.
Look, I just...
Cisco, I...
Don't want you to take the job.
Oh.
That is such a relief.
Because I don't want anything to change.
Not only have we not
been on the same page,
we haven't even been on the same planet.
Literally.
We've been doing this
back-and-forth thing
for almost a year,
negotiating who gets
to go to whose Earth
and when, just to see each other,
and on the off-chance we
do get to see each other,
there's, like, a countdown
until one of us has to leave,
and I'm tired of it!
I don't want to have to
Breach to see the woman I love.
I want to wake up next to her.
Every morning.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying I want more.
I'm saying I don't want Breacher's job,
but I do want you.
I want you too.
What am I supposed to do?
Pack up my entire life, everything?
Forget about my job,
my responsibilities...
- No, no, no...
- Move here?
No, no, that's not what
I'm asking you to do.
I would never ask you
to leave the Agency.
I know how important that is to you.
But tell me,
and tell me honestly...
this, what we have...
Is this enough for you?
Yes.
It is.
Well, it isn't for me.
Hey, guys? I need you both in the Cortex.
- Why?
- I know what DeVoe's doing.
It's not one machine.
They're machines. Machines
that work together,
but they're still separate.
Satellites.
Separate satellites working together
for a single purpose?
So this guy really is a Bond villain.
DeVoe would need a massive amount
of computational power
for them to be able
to talk to each other.
Something to triangulate navigation
between each satellite.
So, like, a quantum computer?
Mercury Labs just put a whole system
of quantum computers
online, at their home base.
That's where he's going.
Okay, great. This time,
we catch DeVoe by surprise.
Behold.
The key to communicating
our message of the Enlightenment.
Polynomial time computing.
And a dream shall
soon become... reality.
Clifford!
Uh-uh. Don't move.
Barry! Knock him out, and then cuff him!
On it!
Gypsy, now!
Stop it, you're killing him!
Cisco, look out!
Barry, hit him again!
Enough!
Caitlin.
Caitlin, what the hell are you doing?
Bringing her back.
DeVoe is creating a sonic pulse.
You need to get out of there before...
Oh, I get it. You'd
like me to frighten you
into becoming your better half.
Gladly.
- DeVoe!
- Ugh.
Children should be seen, not heard.
I'm very sure seeing your bestie die
would be frightening enough,
but I can't kill the Flash.
Well, not just yet.
My plan for the Enlightenment
requires his further participation.
You, however... are
a lot less fortunate.
Barry, he's gonna kill Gypsy!
Now, do you feel that?
Around your throat?
That is the gravitational equivalent
of my boot busting your windpipe.
She's innocent. Leave her alone!
Clifford...
This isn't part of our plan.
Cisco, wake up! Wake up!
Our plan is to save them.
Well, you can't save everyone, my love.
DeVoe!
Perhaps.
But I won't watch you kill
an innocent life again.
Yes, you will.
Please. Clifford.
Remember who you are.
Is this truly the lesson
you wish to bestow today?
Get the case.
Cynthia!
What happened? Come on, it's okay.
What did he do to her?
Hey, talk to me. Come on, it's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
No thefts have been reported
in the last 12 hours.
So DeVoe managed to get
everything he needed.
And we still don't know
what his next step is.
You know, he said something
about the Enlightenment.
The hell's that supposed to mean?
I know what he's thinking.
I know what he's planning.
We know what he's planning.
- Harry, wait.
- What?
I can give them the CliffsNotes version.
No, no.
The component parts stolen
to create each satellite
will possess a 30...
cubit quantum system, okay,
and each system... is c-capable of...
Each system is capable of redirecting
concentrated dark matter back to Earth
in 10-million-megawatt bursts.
Which... Level of which
is toxic enough to affect
each and every human brain on the planet
and reboot them back to a...
Reboot them.
Back to a simplified state.
Just like mine.
DeVoe wants to remove the intelligence
of everyone on Earth?
Yes.
Exactly, Barry. Exactly right.
I'm really gonna do this.
You treat me...
like I am the only
woman in the multiverse,
and I want more.
What is wrong with me?
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'm sorry.
Nothing's wrong.
Nothing at all.
I guess mayby sometimes,
one plus one just equals two, you know?
What are you gonna do?
Wait.
Good-bye, Cynthia.
Bye, Cisco.
Surprise!
What is this?
It's your baby shower, baby!
This is why you were singing
"The Girl From Ipanema"
in your head all day.
He has been planning this for days.
Oh, this is so sweet!
I feel really guilty
pulling everybody away
at a time like this, but...
It's the perfect time to celebrate.
Surrounded by family.
You guys!
This baby is gonna be so loved.
Aww.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Why don't you go talk to him?
Hey, man. Are you okay?
Not really, no.
Do you want some space, or...
Actually, I got plenty
of that right now.
I'm sorry for pushing the two of you.
I think you both did
the right thing, though.
Then why does it hurt so much?
Caitlin.
Look, I don't think you
should do that again.
You could have gotten yourself killed.
- I have to get her back.
- We will.
No. I will.
Clifford.
Ow! It's fine.
It's fine.
When the line cut out, I came.
Immediately.
I thought I'd lost you.
You'll never lose me, Clifford.
You were right.
Technology has become a cancer.
Driving civilization to consume itself.
A militia group found out
about the water purifier
that I created.
And they just killed dozens
of-of people to take it.
Women and children slaughtered.
For a simple piece of technology.
Your journal.
Wrote of a world where humanity forgot
that this technological
menace was capable.
But what I didn't tell you...
was that I saw the
truth in it even then.
And it frightened me.
And that's why I ran.
And I'm not frightened anymore.
You believe.
I believe in you.
Enlighten them, Clifford.
You're the only one who can.
I'm nothing without you.
The chair will rejuvenate
your fractured scaphoid.
Prepare the satellites for assembly.
I said, prepare the...
No!
Initially, we set out
to enlighten the world.
Now you want to rule it.
I am leaving you, Clifford.
Nothing can get in or out.
You dare orchestrate an exodus
on the eve of humanity's
greatest reckoning?
You made a vow.
To my husband!
But my husband is dead.
The Thinker's first victim.
The Enlightenment will
come for you too, Marlize.
I will be all that remains.
Oh, Clifford.
You are nothing without me.
Special delivery!
Wow! You're super pregnant!
Looks like you're due about
21 days from tonight, I'd say.
I-I mean, if I were guessing.
Sweetheart, who is it?
Uh, someone sent us a diaper bag.
It looks like it's a gift from someone
who wanted you both to
know how special you are.
Someone who understands
that time is precious
and right now is all we've got.
- Aww.
- Relatively speaking.
- Dad?
- Hey, look what we got.
Oh! Who sent that? Wally?
Wally already sent us a bassinet,
which apparently was owned by Moses.
Was there a note?
Who was it?
Some delivery girl.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --