- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Caitlin!
- Dad.
- I'll always love you.
- You took our daughter
back to the future?
- I can't trust her.
Thawne is manipulating her.
- Follow my instructions
and we will defeat Cicada,
destroy his dagger,
and save your father.
- You created
your own Speed Force?
- Yes, I did.
- And I can access it
to go back in time.
How could he leave me?
- Nora...
- How could he stop
loving me?
[voice echoes]
- She's gone.
- Gone where?
- I don't know where.
I only know when: 2019.
[electricity zaps]
[tense music]
- Gideon, scan servers
for blueprints
from McCulloch Technologies.
♪ ♪
Gotcha.
[intense electrical zapping]
Gideon, infiltration analysis.
- Yes, Nora West-Allen.
The odds of accessing
this location on your own
are 1 in 3 million.
Shall I send a request
to Barry Allen?
- No, Gideon.
I need people
who can actually help me.
[dramatic music]
[electricity zapping]
- Tachyon scanners set up
at every half-mile interval
across the city.
- And the seismometer
is searching for sonic booms
in the hundred-megahertz range.
- As for the satellites,
I've got Carrie, Charlotte,
Miranda, and Samantha scanning
for her yellow-purple
lightning signatures.
I am clearly the Samantha
of this group, right?
- Yeah, okay, Miranda.
- Ugh.
- So, technically,
if Nora uses the Speed Force...
- We'll find her.
[monitor beeping]
Kinda thought
she'd pop right up.
- If she's even here.
How can you guys be so sure
that she even came back from
the future in the first place?
- Because Thawne sent her.
He showed her a new way
to time-travel,
something that can't
be detected.
- But as soon as she starts
running again,
we're gonna be able
to bring her home.
- Well, Team Flash,
Nora West-Allen is not the only
time traveler who's absent.
- We've been running down
abandoned buildings,
foreclosed condos...
- Anywhere that Grace Gibbons
may have hidden
her younger self, but...
- We got bupkis.
- And we have no idea why
she stole the Cryo-Atomizer,
except that it was worth
killing my dad for.
- Hey, if you need more time...
- Yeah, we're more than capable
of chasing
a wild goose or two
on our own.
- Thank you, I'm fine.
I'd rather be working.
- On that note,
I'm happy to help you
follow that lead
on the atomizer.
- Really?
What about... Sherluck?
- Sherloque.
Do you think any of you will
get this right at any point
at any time in your life?
Sherloque.
No, I'm going to continue
the quest for Nora West-Allen.
I... feel somewhat responsible.
- Hmm.
[phone vibrates]
- Hey, it's CCPD...
there was a break-in
at an architecture firm
on 34th and Williamson.
Meta-suspect.
- Citizens reporting
an explosion there.
- Sounds like you guys might
need an extra set of hands.
I'll grab my gear.
[device chirping]
- Oh.
There's an alert at my dad's
old lab in the Arctic.
We should check it out.
[phone chimes]
- Yeah, better wash
my long johns.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
[phone chimes, vibrating]
You gonna get that or...
- Yeah, I'm going to get it,
but I know already
it's Renée Aldler...
- Adler.
With these emoticon pictogram
things that she send me.
- Oh, master detective like you
can't decode a few emojis?
- I can decode these emojis
no problem, huh?
Heart, she like me.
Kissy face, want to kiss me.
Peach, eggplant, she like
fruit and vegetable.
At this point
with the other Renée Aldlers,
we are not keeping secrets
from one another.
- Well, I did it.
Every exercise,
every intention,
and now that Kamilla and I
are hunky-dory...
- You have completed
the Book of Ralph.
- I sure did.
- Thank you for your service,
old friend,
but your job isn't done yet.
Shirley, I think you
could use this.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What, do you think I need
help with a breakup?
- Oh, come on.
Look, Addendum C...
- Appendix four.
- A guide to taking your
relationship to the next level.
It worked for Cisco.
- [scoffs]
Barely worked
for young Ralph Macchio.
No, no, no.
This guy, he's chicken, right?
Even in his
current relationship,
he's too afraid
to tell this girl
that he's actually Vibe, right?
- I'm actually not afraid.
I'm gonna tell her
when I'm ready.
It's just hard to navigate
the meta-life,
personal-life balance.
- More like chicken-life
balance, hmm?
- Man, you're a chicken
personal-life balance.
I can tell her whenever I want.
- Well, then tell her
right now, why don't you?
- You want me
to tell her right now?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell her right now.
I just got...well, you know.
I have spotty reception
in the elevator.
- Come on out and do it.
- Well, you know,
I gotta get to work.
- Come on out and do it.
- I gotta get to work.
[scanning device trilling]
- I just talked to one
of the architects here,
and G. Simone &amp; Associates
used to do
all of this high-profile
design work...
casinos, banks,
military bases...
but apparently, last year,
they had been working
with an anonymous client.
- So because our thief
covered his tracks,
we have no idea
who that client might be.
- Hey.
Look at this.
Look at these hard drives.
Fried from the inside,
like in a massive power surge.
- A server like this would
have a surge protector, right?
- A typical
metal-oxide varistor
protects against
a thousand joules.
- How many joules does
a lightning bolt have?
- A billion.
- What, you think
this was Nora?
- No, this couldn't have been.
I mean, our scanners
would've picked her up.
- Yeah, about that...
I just picked up a frak-ton
of background
particle radiation.
- Particles?
Tachyons?
- Negative tachyons.
- That's a thing?
- I mean, negative tachyons
can't generate
lightning, right?
- Unless negative tachyons
don't just offset positive ones
like we thought.
Maybe they actually
siphon positive tachyons.
- Stealing speed from the
Speed Force like a parasite?
- That's what Thawne
taught her how to do.
She's using negative tachyons
to run and avoid our scanners.
- Yeah, but why would Nora
be trying to avoid us?
- I don't know, but if
she's stealing blueprints,
this ain't gonna be
her last stop.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Pretty paint job.
- Predators know
these colors get you stung.
- Yeah, it's always
a great idea
for a thief to draw
attention to herself.
- At least I don't fly around
in a fuzzy green sweater.
Didn't think I'd recognize
Weather Wizard's kid?
- It's Weather Witch.
I have a name, okay?
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
- Don't call me that.
That's their name.
- I heard you took your
robot bee act to Star City.
Something about
curing a spinal tumor?
- Well, I heard you and your
other half were in Bolivia.
Or did Silver Ghost ditch you?
- Van Zandt talked a big game.
- She tried to recruit me too.
What did she want to call us?
Young...
[deafening pounding]
[bones cracking,
organs squishing]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
Rag Doll, right?
You blew up
the Seaver Building.
Bee-utiful.
- And whom do I thank
for my mysterious invitation?
- Wait, I got
an anonymous offer too.
This wasn't your job?
- I thought this was your job.
- Actually, I invited you.
- You want us to work for you?
- Not for me.
With me.
One big score split four ways.
- What's the catch,
goody two shoes?
- No catches, no tricks.
Just one condition.
No killing.
- [laughs]
- [scoffs]
- Well, this has been
really fun, guys, I'm out.
- If anybody dies,
the cops will be all over us.
- Yeah,
you would love that, huh?
I was surprised that the Flash
isn't already here.
- I'm not working
with him anymore.
- Look, you can
put on your leather
and you can act like
a bad girl all you want,
but you will never
be one of us.
- What about the ice patch?
If you don't trust me,
why did you stop that test car
from running me over?
- Is she for real?
- It was cold.
Water freezes.
- Not like that, it doesn't.
Look, these past few months,
I have been through a lot.
I'm not the same person I was.
♪ ♪
- Okay. Prove it.
What's the job?
♪ ♪
- McCulloch Technologies.
It's the largest manufacturer
of military-grade weapons
in the country.
- So why does a speedster
need our help
to pull off a smash-and-grab?
- McCulloch builds and tests
all of their weapons here.
The Forge.
And it's protected
by a meta-human dampener
that makes A.R.G.U.S.'
look like a bug zapper.
- So, you need us for our tech,
because it won't be affected.
- McCulloch's hosting
an expo tonight.
That'll give us cover
to get on the property,
but breaking into the Forge
is where things get tricky.
- There's no way this score
is worth the risk.
- Look. See these weapons?
There's a hundred more
like these inside.
Each will go for a million
on the black market, easy.
We just need to make
one quick pit stop first.
We need to rob the Flash.
[dramatic music]
- Okay, pretty safe bet
She-Cada was here.
- Better check it out.
See if we can figure out
what she took.
- Yeah, that is if I can get my
fingers to start moving again.
- Whew.
- You think there's any chance
Frost could help us out
with some sealant up there?
- I don't think
she's coming out today.
- She still having a tough time
with your dad's death?
- I mean, Frost protected me
for so long
that I don't think she's ever
felt pain of her own before,
not like this.
- Well, I-I think I could
help with that.
♪ ♪
Here.
- "Ralph's 27 Steps
to a Better Mourning"?
I don't think
Frost would respond
very well to a pamphlet.
- Oh, come on. Look.
Uh, number 10:
go see your dentist because
you should be doing that
at least twice a year
and you've been slacking,
and it'll give
you something to do
other than dwell on the pain.
[ice shatters, cracks]
- There.
Now will you shut up?
[mysterious whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Told you I'd get her
to come out.
Cecile: Guess what?
G. Simone &amp; Associates
has spent the last year
working for
McCulloch Technologies.
- The weapons manufacturer?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
They just built
a factory in Keystone.
- Missing blueprints.
Top-secret facility.
[sighs]
I think we might have
a heist on our hands.
- You think Nora's
going after these weapons?
- No, maybe she's just trying
to get them off the market.
You know, like the time
that Barry and Ralph
were gonna buy
the Toastmasters.
- She's on a mission
for Thawne.
He doesn't think that small.
Hey, Barry is scanning
for negative tachyons.
Why don't you and I dig
into what kind of weapons
McCulloch is making?
I know this whistleblower
down at the DOD.
Maybe she could offer
some insight.
- Uh...
Iris, are you sure
there isn't anything else
you'd like to talk about?
♪ ♪
- Look...
when I saw Nora in 2049,
she was so upset and so angry,
but she knew that
I wanted to bring her back.
Then she comes back
to this time
and...and she doesn't even
come home?
I mean, even if
she's mad at Barry
or she wanted
some kind of sci-fi weapon...
- Then why didn't she just come
to the rest of us for help?
- There's gotta be
a good reason.
I know it.
♪ ♪
- Come on, Nora.
[sighs]
She's avoiding us.
She's stealing blueprints.
I mean, she could really
get into trouble out there.
- But you think she'll return
if you do find her?
After all, she has good reason
to be angry at all of us.
- Uh, what?
Don't lump me in with you two.
- I was pissed.
She was pissed.
But we've both had time
to... get over it,
and she's still Nora.
If I tell her
she can come home again,
I'm sure she'll stop
working with Thawne.
[monitor chirps, beeping]
Is that Nora?
- It has to be.
She's in the Starchives.
♪ ♪
- Nora.
- Hi, Dad.
♪ ♪
- Hey, where you going?
- Nora is my responsibility
as well.
I must speak with her.
- Hey, hold that!
[elevator chirps]
One of our motion sensors
just got tripped
in the sewage system.
- Sewage system?
Mais non.
Nobody could fit down there.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[bones cracking]
- [roars]
- Is that
Spencer Young's phone?
What are you doing?
- You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
- Nora...
I shouldn't have left things
the way that I did.
All right?
♪ ♪
I want you to come home.
We all do.
You just have to stop
working with Thawne.
Rag Doll:Target acquired.
- Copy that.
- Are you talking to someone?
- [scoffs]
What do you think,
I'm talking to Thawne?
He's in the future, Dad.
I can't exactly call him up.
- I didn't say that.
- Yeah, but you did say
that I couldn't come home
if I was still working
with him.
You still don't trust me.
- Nora, trust takes time.
- Then what's to stop you
from sending me back
the next time
you get pissed at me?
Nothing.
Because you've given up
on me again.
Given up on me
like you do every time!
- Nora, what are you doing?
- You know, I came back here
to meet you.
And the second I got here,
you started pushing me away.
And then you left me
in the future.
You just dumped me
in the middle of the street
and walked away!
- You have to stop.
- And you didn't come with Mom
to bring me back.
Because you don't want me here.
You don't want me at all!
- Nora, please!
- I hate you!
[electricity crackles]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Nora broke into
the Starchives.
- I'm sorry, what happened?
- Nora broke into
the Starchives.
I thought I could stop her,
but I couldn't.
She stole
Spencer Young's phone.
- Spencer Young's
hypnotizing phone?
- Yes.
- Barry, it's okay.
Did you at least find out
what she's doing?
- No, no. I tried.
I-I thought I could convince
her to come home.
But...
her face started vibrating,
and...
and then her eyes...
her lightning...
it was red.
Just like his.
I thought we had time
to reach her,
but he got to her.
Thawne really got to her.
- Uh, guys,
there's a blinky red light
thing on the computer.
Another alarm went off
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Guys, this was only
five minutes ago.
- Joss Jackam and Peter Merkel?
How would they get
into S.T.A.R. Labs?
- Nora had someone in her ear.
It was a coordinated assault.
- But that would mean
that she's working...
with them.
- [sighs]
- [sniffs]
Barium.
We're in Keystone City.
- Well, we got a Rag Doll,
a Weather Witch, and, uh...
hold up, is that
crazy bee girl?
Hey, girl!
What's going on?
What a throwback.
- What the hell
is he doing here?
are you doing here?
- Oh, no.
She's with them.
- I said I wanted Ramon.
No one else.
- Yeah, well,
they were together,
and you said no killing,
so here they are.
both: Killing?
- This phone was synced
to Spencer Young's DNA.
We need you to hack past the
coding so we're able to use it.
- [snickers]
- Why are you laughing?
- I'm sorry,
I don't mean to blow up
your spot, fangirl,
you see, it's just, um...
I've done this exact
same thing before.
We need to hack a weapon.
Let's kidnap Cisco.
I mean, what, did you join a
Rogues cover band or something?
[both laughing]
[dramatic music]
- How's this for a cover band?
♪ ♪
- Oldie but a goodie.
- Look, XS,
I owe you an apology, hmm?
Never should've exposed
your secret the way I did.
I put my pride in front
of the family that took me in...
your family...
and your family loves you.
I'm sure you heard.
Your father told you
as much today, right?
- You saw your father?
You said you were robbing
the Flash.
- No.
No, don't you get it?
Her old man is the Flash.
- Look, you don't have to worry
about the Flash, okay?
Just get Ramon started
on that phone.
- Hey.
Boot scuff marks.
I'm thinking
she hit this thing.
- Yeah.
Intravenous electrolytes.
I mean, those can be used
to treat coma patients.
- So maybe she grabbed them
for Grace Junior.
Hell, yeah.
I knew your "Grey's Anatomy"
thing would come in handy.
- Ralph, why did you
really bring me here?
Was it to help
Killer Frost and me?
The same way you helped
Cisco get over Gypsy
and Sherloque with Renée?
- What are you talking about?
I mean, we're a team.
It's what we do.
We help each other.
- Yeah, but the minute you
got the Book of Ralph back
from Cisco, you tried
to give it away again.
Don't you want to use it?
Try and find someone
special for yourself?
[gentle music]
- Caitlin...
look...
Book of Ralph...
works great
for other people, but...
never actually worked for me.
I know I'm not...
built for love.
♪ ♪
And that's okay.
- Ralph Dibny, you are kind,
intelligent, and compassionate.
And most of all,
you put the needs
of others before yourself.
So that means
you are built for love,
and you deserve someone
who loves you back.
♪ ♪
- Caitlin...
I'm sorry, I just don't
feel that way about you.
- Ugh. Gross!
Oh, come on, you idiot.
- Sorry, I got my...
I got my wires crossed.
Jeez.
- Hey...
I think this might be
the fridge
that Cisco was
telling me about,
the one that he rewired
as an incubator.
And now the top shelf is empty.
- Okay, what was on
the top shelf?
- Cisco's prototypes
for the meta-human cure.
[tense music]
I think I know
what Cicada is planning.
- [groans]
Last time a group of women
had me tied up like this...
- They were your ex-wives?
- No, their attorneys,
actually.
- Am I gonna end up like you?
Married to the job?
Keeping secrets
from everyone I know?
- Well, actually,
in my current romance,
I'm not the one
keeping secrets.
No, no,
I meet Renée Aldler...
- Adler...
- And then I discover...
she's a meta-human.
- And she hasn't told you yet?
- No, monsieur.
Can you believe that?
- So if you know the truth,
and you're bottling it in,
doesn't that mean you're
kind of being dishonest?
[tender music]
Chicken recognize chicken.
- Hmm.
And yet, are you
really a chicken...
Monsieur Bawk?
Or are you not sharing your
secret identity with Kamala...
- Kamilla.
- Because...
you're not super-satisfied
with your secret identity?
♪ ♪
- Are you saying
I don't want to be Vibe?
- Well, let's examine
the evidence, shall we?
You spent this past year
sans powers for the first part,
and the second part
curing powers.
Perhaps being honest
with Kamala...
- Kamilla.
- Begins with being honest
with yourself.
Think about that.
♪ ♪
- So what we know is that
Nora put together a team
to break into here,
McCulloch Technologies,
a weapons manufacturer.
- But not just any weapons.
The city has contracted
these guys to clean up
the shrapnel from
the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite.
- Let me guess:
none of that crap
ended up in the dump.
They used it to make meta-tech
like Spencer Young's phone.
- My source says
that McCulloch is debuting
a new line of products tonight.
- That's a perfect cover-up
for a break-in.
We have any theory
on Nora's motive?
- Actually, Cicada's dagger
dampens the abilities
of meta-humans nearby,
but it wouldn't have
any effect on meta-tech.
So maybe Nora wants
to catch Cicada?
- Or do something worse.
- Barry, there's no way.
- This is exactly
what I was afraid of, Iris.
Thawne's been manipulating her.
Now she's acting like him,
talking like him.
- That doesn't mean that she's
capable of killing Cicada.
- She's working with Rogues.
She kidnapped Cisco
and Sherloque.
We don't know
what she's capable of.
- So what do you want
to do, Barr?
- We bring her in.
We use Cisco's force fields,
Ray's nanites...
we're bringing her in,
before she steps
anywhere near that building.
- Hey, Barry.
Hold on.
Hey.
We can't keep treating Nora
like she's some kind
of super-villain, okay?
We're just gonna push her away.
- What are we supposed to do?
Just let her keep
taking advantage of us?
- No.
We see where she's coming from.
We try to figure out
why she's doing this.
- It doesn't matter why, Iris!
This is Thawne.
It's his plan.
- Well, maybe his plan
isn't so bad.
[solemn music]
- What?
- [sighs]
- Maybe...
I thought...
I thought we were
past this, it's...
it's not okay for her
to work with Thawne.
You saw him.
You said he's manipulating her.
- And I said
that he cares about her.
He's worried about her safety...
- No, he needs her, Iris.
He needs her.
- Or... he's changed.
Barry, Thawne is the one that
convinced me to come back home
and try and patch
things up with you.
- Thawne.
Thawne gave you advice?
- [sighs]
Look, I know
it sounds insane,
and I know this must be
hard for you to hear,
but, Barry, ever since
I got back home,
the same question
keeps running through my mind.
What if Nora is right?
What if Thawne really is
trying to redeem himself
and that he does want
to stop Cicada
and the only reason
that Nora hasn't come back home
is because she knows
that you don't trust her?
Look...
Barry, having Nora in our lives
has made us better people.
Isn't it possible
that she did the same thing
to Thawne?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Jenni Ognats?
I thought the idea
was to not draw attention.
- Oh, what, so now that you
know my dad's the Flash,
you don't trust me?
- Hey, you're the one
who doesn't trust us.
Isn't that right...
Nora?
Yeah, your secret identity,
it's really not worth much.
♪ ♪
- Feels like nothing about me
is worth much lately.
My dad left me,
after everything that I've done
to try and help him.
You know what the most
embarrassing part is?
There's this tiny, little,
weak part of me
that still wants him
to walk through that door
and take me home.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- My dad left my mom
at the maternity ward.
She couldn't look at me
without seeing him.
She made sure I knew it too.
So the day I turned 13, I ran.
I didn't leave town at first.
I stayed under the overpass
with all the other runaways.
And I thought for sure,
one night, I'd look up
and I'd see my mom.
She never showed.
- Sorry.
- I'm not.
When people tell you that
family is always
gonna be there for you,
they're full of it.
- Mentors will always
let you down eventually.
- Parents will break you.
- Yeah.
That's why we
have to stick together.
[dramatic music]
- Yeah.
- Hey, it's done.
- Come on.
Nerd's done with the phone.
♪ ♪
- One reprogrammed
meta-tech phone,
now with visual and auditory
hypnosis capabilities.
♪ ♪
Plus unlimited data.
You gonna let us go now?
- What, so you can run
right back to the Flash?
How stupid do you think I am?
Any bugs in there?
- It's clean.
- Good.
Now make sure
they can't try anything else.
♪ ♪
[bees buzzing]
Come on.
This score's not
gonna steal itself.
[ominous humming]
Cisco:You're not gonna
get away with this.
- Hey.
Thawne:I'm not gonna get away
with it?
- Cisco's old speedster trap.
- You think that's gonna
work for Nora?
- I don't know.
I'm not sure I'm ready
to find out, though.
Hey, look, I'm sorry
about, um...
how I was acting earlier,
I just...
seeing Nora
looking so much like him...
- No, I get it, Barr.
That guy's always
gonna be in your head.
Mine too.
And you were right.
Nora broke the law.
And there should be
repercussions for that.
But whenever you guys
step out of bounds,
I always have to
remind myself,
the detective side says
there's the law.
But the father side says
there's also what's right.
And... I'm always gonna choose
to be your father first.
♪ ♪
- Maybe that's my problem.
- What?
- I was ready
to give up on her.
You know, I mean,
If I'm ready to do that,
it makes me feel like...
even after everything
we've been through,
I'm not a good parent.
You know, I mean,
maybe I never will be.
- Come on, Barry.
You know that's not true.
You're going to be
an amazing father.
- I wanted her to leave.
The second that she got here,
I did, I...
I've held back from her.
It still doesn't feel right
when she calls me Dad.
- Well, you didn't
call me Dad till...
it was here, in this room,
right after you got
your powers.
But you know why that was.
You already had a dad.
Henry.
And when the whole world
thought that
that man was a criminal,
Barr, you...
You thought he was perfect.
- Do you think Iris is right?
Nora's plan, Thawne's plan...
could be a good thing?
- I don't trust that man.
I never have and I never will.
But I do...
trust my granddaughter.
And if we're gonna
bring Nora home, Barr...
you're gonna have
to trust her too.
♪ ♪
[buzzing and humming]
[mysterious pulsing]
- Oh, thank Crom.
I might've given you
unlimited data,
but I also gave you
spotty reception.
- Nice work.
- All right.
The bees are in drone mode.
So if we move very,
very slowly...
Man, what in the world?
- What?
I was trained
in the art of escape
by Thaddeus Brown
from Earth-51.
- Yeah, well, help me escape!
- That's a good plan.
So, um...
Count backwards from ten.
- Ten...
Ow!
How did you do that?
- Trade secret.
- Okay.
[bees buzzing]
- So...
[clears throat]
You're not fireproof,
are you, Monsieur Ramon?
- Am I fire...
oh, God.
- Oh.
Ah.
No, no.
Hey!
[speaks French]
[shouting]
[both panting]
That's all of them?
- I think so.
- Good.
Because Nora West-Allen
is in grave danger.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you for your patience,
ladies and gentlemen.
With the kind of technology
we're displaying tonight,
security is our
highest priority.
- Visitor IDs, please.
- You bet.
[device beeping]
- Okay, here we go.
Right this way, ladies.
The last ten months have been
very exciting
here at McCulloch.
Buyers from the Army and Navy
are already waiting for us
in our state-of-the-art
demo room.
- Uh, what's behind that door?
- Ah.
That's what our engineers
have dubbed the Forge.
It's where we develop and test
our new weapons.
Unfortunately, it's only
accessible to employees
with the highest
security clearance.
[lasers firing]
[men grunt]
- Remember.
No killing.
[dramatic music]
[electricity crackles]
- That's a Montgomery 4000,
30-ton vault door.
It'll only open
from the inside,
so the only way into the Forge
is through there.
♪ ♪
[bones cracking]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Mm, cozy.
- Ready, clown?
- Are you sure you can fit
through that thing?
♪ ♪
- This shall be my aria.
- Remember, once you get
to the other side,
the dampener will take away
your powers,
so get out quick.
♪ ♪
[bones crunching]
- Yeah, I'm gonna vomit.
[Rag Doll groans]
[rattling]
- Mm, mm, mm...
Open, sesame.
♪ ♪
- Stay with the hostages.
We'll grab you on the way out.
- See you soon.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
- That's one serious
meta-dampener.
- Whoa.
♪ ♪
Last part of the plan.
Load up.
- Sorry, XS.
[dramatic music]
Change of plans.
- Good evening, Central City.
We've prepared
a special show for you.
- Tonight's festivities
will feature several
expendable worker bees...
the employees
of McCulloch Technologies.
- Unless the Flash comes down
here in the next 30 seconds
and reveals his identity
to the world.
Gucci?
[dramatic music]
- You don't want the money?
- [laughs]
Oh, no.
We want the money.
We just wanted to make
a name for ourselves first.
- So, what, outing my dad makes
you legitimate Rogues?
I trusted you.
[both laughing]
- Oh, God.
You sound just like
Silver Ghost...
when I left her in Bolivia.
At least you'll die fast.
I'd say it's been
about 30 seconds, right?
- Yeah.
- Right?
Okay.
- Wait!
I am here.
- All right, Speedy.
Show us your true identity.
Mask off.
- Dad, please.
You do not have to do this.
- I have to.
I am a man sitting alone
at the dinner table.
♪ ♪
- Is he drunk?
- See, when you're in position
to feed the world,
it can make it hard
to be a father.
You have to constantly
ask yourself,
is what's right for the world
what's right for your child?
- Hey, can we get on with it?
- Yes, um... yeah, uh...
- No.
- What?
- Did you seriously think I was
gonna fall for this again?
- [stammers]
[yelps]
- Ha!
I phase right through
your blast.
Ha! You can't stop
the Flash!
- No, I think the jig is up.
- Confused?
Don't be.
[devices chirping]
- Holy shrap.
- How the hell
is this even possible?
- We bypassed security
while you were busy
with General Cloud.
And then you walked
us worker bees right inside.
- You're outnumbered, ladies.
Drop your weapons.
[intense music]
- Don't let them
hit that dampener.
- Get the hostages out of here.
We'll handle the Rogues.
[laser fires]
- Okay, this way.
♪ ♪
We gotta get back in there.
- Yeah.
[bones crunching]
What the hell is that?
- You don't want to know.
[electricity crackling]
[sparks sizzling]
[gun clattering]
- Cisco, we need
our powers back.
Can you do something
about these bees?
- Hold tight.
- [shrieks]
- Iris!
[bones crunching]
[grunting]
[yells]
- All right, we're not gonna
last here much longer.
I'm gonna create a diversion.
Get ready to shoot
the dampener.
- No, no.
Dad, it's too dangerous!
- [groans]
- Dad!
- [grunts]
- [sighs]
He's lucky I don't throw
his ass off a roof.
- Nobody out-techs me.
[monitor chirps]
♪ ♪
[bees spatter]
- Damn it.
Ramon's in my phone.
- She's not getting out
of this one alive.
- Nora, wait!
- [yells]
- Dad! You've been hit.
[dampener powers down]
Are you okay?
- [panting]
Yeah.
I'm not the only one.
- You were here with me.
The whole time.
- I abandoned you once.
I'm never gonna do it again.
♪ ♪
So we should probably...
- Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
[triumphant music]
- The young Rogues.
Not the nicest friends
you made there, kiddo.
- Yeah, I... thought
I could control them,
steal the weapons back
after we lifted them,
but I got in over my head.
Even if it was
for a good reason.
- Nora, killing Cicada
is not a good reason.
- No, I-I wasn't trying
to kill Cicada.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
I needed this.
It's a weapon built
from the solar reflector panels
from the S.T.A.R. Labs
satellite,
capable of destroying
any object down to its atoms,
and it's the only thing that
can destroy Cicada's dagger.
- Nora, why didn't you
just tell us this?
- Because I wouldn't
have believed her.
'Cause it's Thawne's plan.
- I knew how angry Dad was.
And then you came
to the future without him.
I just thought
he'd never believe me.
Plus, I had to stay in
a seriously unschway headspace
to use the negative
Speed Force.
But I know now.
I don't ever want to leave
you guys again.
And if that means not following
through with Thawne's plan,
I'm okay with that.
- I think we should use it.
- You what?
- Barr, are you sure?
- We have to stop Cicada.
I'm never gonna like
where this plan comes from.
But if this thing works...
sounds like our best shot.
- You really believe him?
- I believe in you, Nora.
[tender music]
And I'm sorry
that I made you feel otherwise.
- Dad...
that stuff I said earlier...
- I deserved it.
I-I...
I shouldn't have left you
in the future.
I shouldn't have put
conditions on you coming home.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
♪ ♪
- We both do.
We're never gonna
leave you again, Nora.
I promise.
♪ ♪
- So what's the verdict?
- Nora's story checks out.
This thing has got
a prismatic battery
supercharging
its reflector panels.
So if anything's gonna
destroy that dagger,
it's this mirror gun.
- That may be easier said
than done.
- Why's that?
- We figured out what Cicada
took from my dad's lab.
It's your cure prototypes.
- Why would she need those?
They're just prototypes.
- No, they're not
just prototypes.
They're failed,
broken versions of the cure.
If a meta-human takes that
without the proper treatment...
- They would die.
Cicada has a lethal virus
on her hands.
- That's why she stole
the atomizer.
So she can spread the virus.
- She has weaponized the cure.
- This is it.
This is the nightmare.
- Cicada's gonna kill
every meta-human in the city.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- A rare, old bird
is the pelican,
whose beak can hold more
than his belly can.
He can hold in his beak...
enough food for a week.
But I'm...
both: Darned...
if I know...
how the hell he can.
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.