Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust
into the future,
and I saw him murder
the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
It's definitely a meta.
I think this is someone new.
- I'm Cisco, by the way.
You must be Gypsy.
So is this good-bye, then?
- For now.
- Caitlin, you do not
want to do this.
- Time for me to own
who I really am.
- You're one of the strongest
people I've ever known.
You can win this fight.
[warbling tone]
- Jesse!
- No, no.
- What's wrong?
- Grodd.
He's got my dad.
He has him in Gorilla City.
[dramatic music]
[creature roaring]
♪ ♪
- [grunting and panting]
[creature roaring]
♪ ♪
[creature shrieking]
[creature roaring]
- It's been two weeks
since he disappeared.
I mean, no one's seen
or heard from him since.
- Slow down.
Just start from the beginning.
Okay, why did your dad
go to Gorilla City?
- Wait, can we slow down
even further?
What the hell is
a Gorilla City?
- Okay, so...
[clears throat]
There are sentient,
highly intelligent
evolved gorillas in Earth-2.
And they all live in a city
deep in the heart of Africa.
- We sent Grodd there when
he went after Fay Wray here.
- Grodd's there?
- Mm.
- Why on Earth, any Earth,
would your father
want to go there?
- I mean, we received
a mathematical cryptogram
at our S.T.A.R. Labs.
It was highly complex.
It took a week to decode it,
but my dad and I did.
- What did it say?
- It was an invitation
from the gorillas
to my dad.
- Why Harry?
- They wanted to meet him.
So he mounted an expedition
with ten other people,
and they went into the jungle.
But they failed
multiple check-ins,
and a search party
went in after them.
But all they found
were the bodies...
all of them beaten to death.
[somber music]
But no one's seen my dad.
♪ ♪
I mean, is he...
- No.
No, he's alive.
They...
they went to a lot of trouble
to get him there.
They need him for something.
We're gonna figure out
what that is.
- Oh! There you guys are.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Are we going for coffee
or what?
- Dad!
- Ah, oh.
Yes, that's how you say
good morning, people...
with hugs.
Hi!
- Jesse, that's not
who you think it is.
This is H.R.
You met him briefly before
you left last time.
- At your service, madame.
- He's Harry's replacement.
- Some would say improvement.
- Um, this is Harry's daughter.
- Yeah.
- He's been kidnapped.
- He...I didn't know.
I'm so s...
I thought...
- Sorry about that.
- I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry I took the smile
from your face.
- What are you
thinking about?
- [sighs]
The future.
This headline from the future:
the city's still recovering
from a gorilla attack.
- So you're thinking
this headline
and Harry being taken
are tied together.
- I mean, it can't be
a coincidence, right?
Harry getting lured
to Gorilla City?
Grodd must be planning
something.
- Seems like he's planning
to come back to this Earth.
- And not alone,
by the sound of it.
- If we rescue Harry,
then maybe that stops
whatever Grodd's planning here,
and maybe that changes
the future.
- Which would change my future.
Joe: Mm.
So we save Harry,
we save Iris.
But you're not sure.
- No, but...
I'm going either way.
Harry's my friend.
I'm not gonna just abandon him.
I'm going back to Earth-2.
- And I suppose you'll want
somebody to come with you
who's gonna open
those breaches for you?
- We had so much fun
last time.
- Fun-ish.
I'm in.
- I'm gonna come too.
I have a special connection
with Grodd.
Maybe we can use that
to get through to him.
- Yes, okay.
- Great, yeah, I'm coming too.
- No.
I'm sorry, Jesse, no.
- Look, I didn't come here
for you to take all the risk.
I'm going to help.
- Your dad would kill me
if I let you come along.
- I'm a Speedster now, okay?
I can take care of myself.
- I know, which is
exactly why
I need you to stay here.
I mean, this city
needs protecting
while we're gone.
Besides, maybe you can teach
Wally a thing or two.
- Wait, what is he
talking about?
- Um...
[vibrating]
- Wow.
So you're...
you're a Speedster now
- Yeah, we're both
Speedsters now.
- Great, yeah,
that's, uh...
[clears throat]
That's awesome.
- I, um...I thought she'd be
more excited than that.
- Hey, Julian, would you maybe
be able to cover for me
at work for the next few days?
- Few days? Why?
- I...I just, um,
have a thing...
we're...it's just...
it's Flash stuff.
- Such as?
- [exhales sharply]
A friends of ours is lost
on a parallel Earth,
and we're gonna go get him back.
- A parallel Earth?
- Yeah.
- This is the...
this is the multiverse.
[exhales]
I'm fascinated.
And do you often travel
to other Earths?
- No, I...
well, when I have to.
Look, Julian, will you
just tell Singh that,
I don't know, I'm under
the weather or something?
It's...you know, it is kind of
what we do on Team Flash.
We cover for each other.
- What does Caitlin think of all
this multiverse hopping?
Does she approve?
- She's coming with me.
- You're letting her go?
- It's her choice.
- Allen, it's not
a wise move, surely.
She can barely control
her cold powers as is.
I mean...
- We might need her for Grodd.
- Grodd? Gr...
Telepathic gorilla?
- Yeah.
- Where...where are you going?
Are you going
to Planet of the Apes?
- No, it's just a city
of them, okay?
Will you cover for me?
- Are you going
to Planet of the Apes?
- I'm not going
to Planet of the Apes, okay?
Calm down.
Will you cover for me?
- I got you.
Yeah, of course.
- Okay, thank you.
See you in a few days.
- All right, now.
- And make sure Wally doesn't...
- I won't.
- Because, you know, sometimes
he can be a little...
- Barry...
- You know,
if given the opportunity...
- Barry, I am very good
at bossing my little brother
around, okay?
Don't worry.
- All right.
- Just please don't do
anything stupid.
- You mean like voluntarily
going to a city of super apes?
- I'm being serious.
Rescue Harry.
But other than that, you...you
don't have to do this for me.
- Everything I do is for you.
- Good.
- Y'all know Wally
can hear you, right?
- Sorry, Wally.
- Be safe.
Hey, you see anything hinky,
you run.
Listen to me.
I don't need to tell you that.
- I promise.
- All right.
[sighs]
- [laughing]
- Detective.
- [laughs]
- Hmm.
[giggles]
Indiana Jones much?
- Cisco, my friend,
this is not my first expedition,
and believe me,
this is the perfect attire.
- Wait, Julian,
what's going on?
I thought you were gonna
cover for me.
- I spoke to Captain Singh.
He thinks
we're at a morphology conference
up in Bludhaven.
So if it's all the same
to you...
- All right.
- You don't have to come,
Julian.
You don't even know Harry.
- [chuckles] A chance to travel
to another dimension...
I mean, I wasn't
gonna miss that.
- We're not going sightseeing.
- Neither am I.
- Well, damn.
- All right, Jesse, Wally,
you make sure this city's safe
while I'm gone, all right?
- We will.
- Hey, Barry.
If you...if you see my dad,
just tell him...
- You'll see him
real soon, Jesse.
Speedster's honor.
[dramatic music]
All right, let's do this.
- Okay.
Earth-2, here we come.
[warbling tone]
♪ ♪
[energy surging]
[panting] How was that?
- Bloody brilliant.
- [laughs]
- Wow.
[creatures grunting]
- Well, we made it.
♪ ♪
- Welcome to the jungle,
baby.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Earth-2 Africa.
Not hot.
Guess global warming's
not really a thing here.
[bug buzzing, hand slaps]
But bugs are.
- Someone please
help me out.
How exactly does saving
someone on this Earth
prevent an attack on ours?
- If Grodd is planning
to attack,
he's gonna need to open
a breach to our Earth,
and the only one over here
that can open one is...
- Harrison Wells.
- Harrison Wells, yeah.
So if we save him
from Grodd,
then he can't get
to our Earth,
the attack never happens,
we change the future,
and we're one step closer
to saving Iris.
[footsteps tapping]
- Hey.
You want to go for a run?
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
Maybe later.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
- Look, I know I haven't been
great at keeping in touch.
It's just everything's
been so crazy
trying to train with Barry
and shadowing him,
and I just haven't had that
much time for other things.
- Yeah, or other people.
- That is not what I meant.
- No, look, I...I get it.
Trust me.
It's not easy
being a hero, is it?
- No, but I love
every minute of it.
- Great.
- Are you sure you're okay?
Because...
- Yeah.
I'm just worried about my dad.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- [whispers] Hey.
♪ ♪
- I hope we didn't
interrupt you two.
- [sighs] Nope.
Nothing to interrupt.
- Mm.
- Aren't you...
you aren't happy she's back?
- I am.
I just wish she felt the same.
Ever since she got here, she's
been acting so weird with me.
I...I don't know if it's
because I have powers
or if it's just me.
- Wally, she's probably
still just upset
because her father's
missing, right?
- Yeah, it's hard to focus
on other things
when something like that
is weighing you down.
- Yeah, Wally.
She'll be fine.
Just give her some time,
and then, you know,
lock it down.
- Uhh, lock it down, hmm?
- Yeah.
What, you think
I didn't notice
that your Facebook profile
still says "single"?
- What? I mean, technically,
I'm still single.
[alarms beeping]
- What was it?
- Ugh, robbery in progress
at O'Sullivan Bank.
- You two go.
[rousing music]
[whooshing]
[papers rustling]
♪ ♪
- Come on, let's go.
[whooshing]
- Didn't hear the news, huh?
- What news?
- [laughs] That you don't
mess with Kid Flash.
- We got to get back
to our friends.
They're expecting us.
- Yeah, they picked
some real winners.
- I know, which is more
than I can say for you two.
♪ ♪
- Be right back.
[whooshing]
[blows thudding,
men grunting and groaning]
[whooshing]
Sorry, I...
I had to stretch my legs.
- Mm.
- Hey, guys, come out.
[indistinct chatter, applause]
- Oh, it's...it's nothing
to see here, guys.
It's just a couple fools getting
their asses handed to 'em.
[applause]
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, thank you.
[laughs]
[applause continues]
♪ ♪
[device beeping]
- Ah.
[sighing]
Want some water?
- I'm okay, thanks.
- It's important to stay
hydrated on a parallel Earth.
- So weird being back here
on this alternate universe.
This is where
I met my doppelganger,
the evil one.
Killer Frost.
- Ah.
- She's the one I'm always
afraid of becoming.
- And where is she now?
- Dead.
- That's not gonna happen
to you, Caitlin.
[pensive music]
- I'm glad you came
with us, Julian.
You're a nice addition
to the team.
- Yeah, well,
I live for danger.
[device beeping]
- We're close, guys.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[beeping continues]
[device trilling]
- Do you hear that?
- This is it.
♪ ♪
[trilling continues]
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
- It's a trap.
[darts whizzing]
Ugh!
[all groaning]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [echoing] Welcome, Caitlin.
Knew you'd come...
Flash.
[dramatic music]
[gorillas grunting]
♪ ♪
[eerie music]
[distant roaring]
- [groans]
[creature growls]
[foreboding music]
- [sighs]
- You guys all right?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Yeah, me too.
- I've lost my gun,
but I'm all right.
- Well, looks like you're gonna
have to phase us out of here.
♪ ♪
[faint buzzing]
[buzzing fades]
- I can't. I...
I don't know.
Something's holding me back.
Can you open a breach?
[warbling tone]
[warbling fades]
- No dice.
- Yeah.
I don't think it's the cell.
I...
Grodd must be dampening
our powers somehow.
- Okay.
[footsteps thudding]
♪ ♪
- Harry?
[sighs]
You're all right.
- Wells. Hey!
You got to help us
get out of here
before the gorillas come back.
- Hello, Flash.
[growling and screeching]
- Grodd.
- What?
That's Grodd the gorilla?
He's talking through Wells?
That's a...a thing?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sort of trips you out
at first, but trust me,
you get used to it.
- Grodd, let him go.
This is between you and me.
- Not yet.
I need him.
- For what?
Why'd you lure him here?
- For you.
Need your help.
- Help? Got a funny way
of asking for it.
- You sent me here!
Remember?
[growling]
[roaring]
To live in this hell!
Where I am forced to serve
under the rule of Solovar.
- Who's Solovar?
- Leader of Gorilla Kind.
Ruler of Gorilla City.
And now...
he wants to rule the humans.
He will bring war
to your Earth.
- Why?
- He has seen many conflicts
between gorillas and humans.
He is afraid the humans
will attack,
but now that you're here,
he will bring the fight to you.
- So you lured us here
to stop him?
- As trespassers...
you will be sent
to the arena
and executed.
- What? How about a signpost
at the front?
"All trespassers
will be executed."
That wouldn't be
the worst idea, would it?
- Will be Solovar's great honor
to kill you...
himself.
- Mm.
- But, Flash...
if he were to be defeated,
the other gorillas
would see his weakness
and would no longer
follow him.
- Well, I'm not
gonna kill anyone,
not even a gorilla.
- Kill or be killed!
This is the only law
Gorilla Kind understands.
- How do you benefit
from this, Grodd?
- Solovar falls.
I take his place.
I rule the gorillas,
and I promise to keep them
in Gorilla City.
♪ ♪
- How do we know
we can trust you?
- Because...
even though you sent me away,
your Earth is still my home.
And there are those among you
I will never forget.
[ringing]
[footsteps thudding]
- [echoing] Kill Solovar,
and Central City
will be spared.
Fail, and see your home
turned to ash.
[dramatic musical flourish]
- Hey, Jesse,
you got a sec?
Did I do something wrong?
- [sighs] I don't...
I don't think so.
- Okay, then why are you
being so cold with me?
Jesse, come on,
you can talk to me.
I know that this is about
more than just your dad.
- [sighs]
[pensive music]
Look, I guess...
I guess I thought one day we'd
figure out a way to be together.
You know, but now that you have
your powers, it's...
It's like I never
hear from you.
- Jesse, if...if you would,
I want you to stay.
- I can't.
- Why?
Because of your dad?
Because Barry
is going to find him.
- Look, you don't know that,
okay?
You don't.
♪ ♪
[sighs] When I first
got my power,
you were so lost
not having yours.
You know, and I thought
maybe part of the reason
why you liked me was...
'cause you were attracted
to the speed and not me.
- [chuckles]
- I know, I know, okay?
But I saw you
out there today...
being Kid Flash.
Okay, and you were complete,
Wally.
You were scary complete.
- I could have all
the speed in the world.
I'm not complete without you.
♪ ♪
Stay.
[insects buzzing and trilling,
creatures roaring faintly]
- Barry, do you really think
you could kill this Solovar?
Do you think you could
take a life?
[footsteps booming,
creatures growling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- It is as I feared.
The humans court war
with Gorilla Kind.
Why did you not tell me,
Grodd,
more humans
had entered the city?
- I was about to inform you,
Solovar.
- [roaring]
Why? Why are you here?
To study us like animals?
Make us your pets?
- No, no.
I'm...I...
[sighs]
We came here in peace.
[stammers]
We entered your city
by mistake.
Uh, we mean you no harm.
Please...
just let me and my friends go,
and I promise,
we'll never come
back here again.
[ringing]
- My brethren have seen you.
Your fate is sealed.
You will all die by my hand...
in the arena...
so that all will know
that Solovar's justice
is wise and swift.
♪ ♪
- All right,
I'll make you a deal.
I'll fight you in the arena...
just me.
But if I beat you,
you let my friends go,
and you leave us alone
for good.
- [grunting]
- I accept.
Humans and their arrogance.
First you will suffer.
Then I will
grant you each...
a horrible death.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[gorillas growling
and screeching]
♪ ♪
[gorillas growling
and screeching]
- Speedster versus
super gorilla.
Best worst video game ever.
- Do you really think that
Barry can beat Solovar?
- Well, he'd better,
for all of our sakes.
[horns blaring]
- It's starting.
[gorillas growling
and screeching]
[horns blaring]
♪ ♪
- After you die,
your friends will follow you
into the black.
- We'll see.
- Okay, Barry.
I got a plan for you.
It's all about
the speed punches.
- Speed punches.
Come on, Barry.
- [roaring]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[gorillas growling
and screeching]
♪ ♪
- [moans]
- Change of plan, Barry.
It's all about
the running away.
[footsteps thudding]
[whooshing]
- [roaring]
♪ ♪
- What about a lightning throw?
- Yes, Barry, lightning throw!
- Worth a shot!
♪ ♪
- [roaring]
[heavy crash]
♪ ♪
- That's 0 for two.
- [whispers] Come on, Barry,
get up.
- [groaning]
- All my days, this is quite
the reversal of our fortune.
[suspenseful music]
- Reversal...
♪ ♪
Barry, it's time
to pull a reverse Flash.
- [roaring]
- Do it!
[energy pulsing]
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
He did it!
He actually did it.
He bloody well did it.
- [panting]
[gorillas grunting
and screeching]
♪ ♪
I won't kill him!
I won't!
- [grunting]
- I know you all fear humans!
[panting]
You think we want war
with Gorilla Kind!
[sighs]
We don't!
[panting]
We're not all murderers
and killers!
We only want peace!
♪ ♪
Which is why
I'm sparing your leader!
We call it mercy!
- [growling]
[echoing] Take him out.
[dart whizzes]
- [grunts]
[ominous musical flourish]
♪ ♪
[water dripping]
[gorillas grunting faintly]
[groaning]
Oh...what happened?
- Congratulations.
You won.
- What about Harry?
- He's still catatonic.
- [groans]
[ringing]
[groans]
- Flash.
- I won.
Solovar promised
to let us go.
- No.
- No? What do you...
I don't understand.
- Solovar's words
mean nothing now.
- You never had any intentions
of letting us go, did you?
- I told you I needed you.
I could not defeat
Solovar in combat,
but you could.
You did, and now I am
the ruler of Gorilla City,
and all the gorillas
will follow me.
[ominous music]
- Solovar never wanted
to attack Central City.
You do.
- You took my home
away from me,
and now I will take it back!
The gorillas saw
what you did, Flash.
They saw you defeat Solovar,
and now theyare
afraid of humans
and will do anything I order,
and I will order them
to invade your Earth,
and your city will burn.
- You were planning
this the whole time.
- Yes.
Father taught me well.
Always think ahead.
And I had plenty of time
to think
in cages built by you
and then by Solovar.
- Then why don't
you just kill us?
Huh? Since we already did
your damn dirty work for you.
- Still need you.
- I'm not doing
anything for you.
- Not you, Flash.
You.
[eerie music]
- Me?
- You will open the breach
to First Earth.
My army will cross that breach,
and all the humans
in Central City
will burn before Gorilla Kind!
- Grodd, you are smart,
maybe smarter than all of us,
smart enough to know
that you cannot do this.
Intelligence and violence,
they're opposites
from each other.
What you want to do,
it's not logical,
not for someone
as wise as you are.
- You forget, Flash,
I am an animal.
I am a gorilla.
Kill or be killed!
- I'm gonna
get out of this cell,
and I'm gonna stop you.
[ringing]
[body thuds]
- [sighs]
- [roaring]
No, you won't.
You will die.
[dramatic musical flourish]
[insects trilling and buzzing]
[low warbling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Snow?
- You okay?
- I...
I have a headache, I guess.
[sniffs]
Ugh!
[exhales sharply]
And I think...
I...is that me?
I smell.
- That counts as okay.
- Jesse, my daughter.
Where's...
- She's fine.
She's on Earth-1.
She's totally fine.
- [sighs]
Barry?
Cisco.
You guys all came for me?
- A city of evil genius apes.
Sounded like fun.
- Well, I don't
deserve it, but...
thank you, Snow;
thank you, Barry,
Cisco...
Indiana.
- It's Julian Albert,
thank you.
And I came along for...
I live for danger.
- Looks like you came
to the right place.
- I still can't phase
through the bars.
We have to find a way out
of here so we can stop him.
- You keep saying that,
but what if we can't get out?
What if we're stuck here?
What if this is the way...
- Well, we can't think
like that.
♪ ♪
While there's life,
there's hope.
♪ ♪
- And if there isn't life?
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Grodd needs me
to open the breach
so he can attack Earth-1.
What if I wasn't alive
to do that?
- You planning on dying?
- Only if you kill me.
- [scoffs]
- Look, this is something
we have to consider.
Right now, I can't think
of any other way to stop them.
They'd have no other way
of getting to Central City.
- He's right.
Cisco's death would change
the newspaper headline
in the future.
- Headline?
- It's a long story.
- But it would also make
another one come true,
the one about Killer Frost.
♪ ♪
- You want me to kill you?
- Think about it.
Grodd doesn't know
you have cold powers.
You might be able to use them.
- Cold powers?
She...you have cold powers?
I knew it.
I knew that you and I
did not get Barry
out of that mirror.
- Wait, now.
Caitlin.
If you kill someone,
there's no going back.
You'll be Killer Frost
for the rest of your life.
Now, I did not come all this way
to see that happen.
[pensive music]
- Did you come here because
you "live for danger"
or to protect me?
♪ ♪
- I just don't want to see you
become something you're not.
♪ ♪
- Okay, Cisco.
I'm not gonna kill you, and
neither is anyone else, okay?
So let's come up
with the next best plan
that doesn't involve
murdering one of our friends.
- No, Cisco's right.
It's the only way.
One of us has to die.
[somber music]
- [humming]
[tapping rhythmically]
Ho!
Hey.
- Hi.
- What you doing up there?
- Just, uh, hanging out.
- What're you...
what're you thinking about?
- [sighs]
Wally.
He wants me
to stay here with him.
- Ah.
[chuckles]
Yeah, he does.
[laughs]
Guy is no dummy.
Congratulations.
Oh, that's great.
Love...
Nothing like young love.
- Yeah, I just...
I don't...
I don't know
if it's the right thing.
- Why?
- He's on his own journey.
Besides, my dad just got
captured by gorillas.
And if...if he does come back,
how could I ever
tell him I'm leaving?
- Well, 'cause you're human.
That's...that's how.
That's what we do.
Look, my point is this.
When it comes to love,
you got to go for it.
You know?
Everything else be damned.
'Cause if you don't,
you're gonna end up being
the kind of person that lives
the rest of their life
with regret.
I mean, I know that telling your
dad that, you know, you're...
you're switching Earths,
that's gonna be a difficult
conversation to have,
but one that you've to go for
if you want to be happy.
But that's, you know,
just my opinion.
What do I know?
I'm just a handsomer guy
than your dad
with a song in his heart.
Good luck, Jesse.
♪ ♪
- [sighs deeply]
[footsteps thudding]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[footsteps continue]
[deep growl]
- [voice breaking] He started
coughing...violently.
And then he clutched his side
and keeled over.
- [grunts]
- The injury...
it must have ruptured
one of his kidneys.
♪ ♪
He went into shock.
His heart stopped.
I couldn't resuscitate him.
[door clanging]
- [growling]
♪ ♪
Cold.
- [sobs]
He's dead.
- [growling]
He was of no use
to me anyway.
[roars]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[growling]
- [whispering]
He's gone, Barry.
Grodd is gone.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
[low trilling]
- Come on, mate.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- [gasping]
♪ ♪
- Yo, it worked!
- Shh!
- [softly] It worked.
- Allen, Allen,
you all right, mate?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good.
- I didn't freeze
you too much, did I?
- [gasping, exhales sharply]
No. I'm good.
- Well, then...
let's get the hell
out of here.
- Yeah.
[grunting]
♪ ♪
Go!
- All right.
- [whispers] Hallelujah.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
Let's go.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
All right.
We should be far enough out
that you should be able
to use your powers.
- We need a breach
open right now.
- Guys, we got to go before
they realize we're gone!
[distant roars]
- It's too late for that.
[gorillas roaring,
footsteps pounding]
- Run!
- Open a breach!
- Time to warp out
of this madhouse.
[suspenseful music]
- All right, go.
[grunting]
[warbling tone]
- [roaring]
[ominous music]
[roaring]
[reflective music]
- Hey, gang, who wants to take
their mind off their troubles
with a "sure to take your mind
off your troubles" game
of charades?
I'll go first.
Okay, ah, let's see.
Movie...I mean...
one word.
[shivering]
[electronic beeping]
♪ ♪
- Dad!
- [sighs]
[laughing]
Aww.
- You okay?
- Good, yeah.
I'm sorry you guys missed it.
- I ain't.
- Ohhh.
- Word of advice:
don't volunteer
for these things.
Nothing ever tries to rip you
limb from limb
if you don't volunteer.
- I'm fine.
I'm so fine, thanks...
thanks to our friends,
our good friends.
- You're welcome, Harry.
- Wow, I...I think...
I just forgot
how handsome you were.
- Oh, I forgot.
He's...you're still here.
- Yeah.
Still here.
- I guess we have your tactical
and technical genius
to thank for getting us
out of that fix.
- No, no, nah.
- Nah?
- Nah.
You were completely
right about him.
He's a total fraud.
He's not even a scientist.
And I'm sure
you couldn't even remember
an ATM code if you tried.
- [scoffs] All those...
all those numbers.
- It's only four digits.
Why is he still here?
- Because we couldn't
do it without him.
- I thank you, Francisco.
- Fran...Francisco?
- Don't ask.
- Yo, so what actually happened?
You fight some really
super-smart apes, or what?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we did.
And they were smart,
but today, at least,
we were a bit smarter.
[dramatic musical flourish]
- How's he doing?
- He's gonna be okay.
He's got some
cuts and bruises,
but Caitlin said he just needs
food and a little sleep.
- Okay.
- Hey, I'm...
I'm sorry for being
an epic basket case lately.
- My, um...my dad
was kidnapped once,
and it turns your world.
- You turn my world, Wally.
Look, I...I need you to be
honest about something.
- Of course.
- When my dad wakes up,
if I tell him that I love him
and I'll always be
his daughter
but that I want
to move to Earth-1,
what would you think about...
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- That's what I think of that.
- I'm glad we think alike.
- [clears throat
and coughs]
I see you're...
you took my love advice.
You know, when it comes
to scientific advice,
mine is sometimes specious,
but when it comes
to affairs of the heart,
well, I consider myself
a genius.
- Okay, yeah,
we're gonna go now.
- Yeah.
- Okay, great.
Congratulations.
I'm happy for you.
Invite me to the wedding.
[slurps]
He's gonna be so pissed.
[whimsical music]
- Caitlin.
Wait.
[sighs]
Listen, if I overstepped,
then I apologize.
Just, after drinks
the other night...
- You were willing
to risk your life for me?
- I've been doing a lot
of silly things recently.
I thought adding one more to
the list wouldn't do any harm.
- I like you, Julian.
I do.
And I like that you like me.
But I'm also afraid
of my powers...
and not what they
could do to me,
but what they could do to anyone
who gets close to me.
- Caitlin, I'm not afraid.
- You should be.
Fear me, Julian.
It's not a threat,
just...
good advice.
[gentle music]
- Okay, fine.
I'll fear you.
You know what really
helps me when I'm scared?
- What?
- Just a good fillet steak...
bit of béarnaise
on the side,
mashed potatoes...
does the trick ever time.
- Really?
- I promise.
I think we should find
a local steak house
and be terrified together.
♪ ♪
- Sure.
Together it is.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Well...
- Hmm.
- We did it.
- You did it.
- No, uh, we all did it.
We changed the future
without changing who we are.
If we can keep doing this,
we can stop Savitar.
Wherever he is, however
he's gonna come at us,
I can stop him.
I know it now.
- How do you do that?
- Do what?
- Stay positive in the face
of overwhelming odds.
- [chuckles]
Because I plan on living
a long life with you,
and nothing's gonna take
that away from me.
- Good.
[tender music]
So does that mean
no more nightmares?
You're finally gonna get
some sleep tonight?
- Well...that last part
is entirely up to you.
- Oh.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[gorillas growling]
- Like I told Flash,
always think ahead.
Now you will open the breaches
and very soon,
Central City
will fall before Grodd.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.