Cleaned, corrected, HI removed
and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on the Flash...
You're him.
The Reverse-Flash.
I'm Eobard Thawne.
And the Flash's speed
is the key
To my returning to my time.
I've been teamed up with
Mason Bridge, who is a legend.
You're the guy who thinks
Harrison Wells
Is some mad genius?
What do you know about him?
I think that maybe
you were right about Dr. Wells.
- Which part?
- All of it.
Come on.
Sweet dreams,
my beautiful boy.
- Mom!
- Barry, no!
- Get back!
Mom!
All right, this is everything
That we know
about Harrison Wells,
Which is actually not a lot.
Didn't you read a whole book
about him?
Yeah, 600 pages,
And the big takeaway is,
he's enigmatic.
Your mom was killed
by a speedster.
Wells' machine turned you
into a speedster.
That's way too many coincidences
for this old cop.
Do you think that he wanted me
to become the Flash?
Everything he's done
Since that night
you got struck by lightning...
Bringing you to S.T.A.R. Labs,
Giving you the suit,
training you...
It's all been
to keep you safe.
And to make me faster.
Wells once said that he needed
more speed from me.
Why?
I don't know.
But he wants something
from you, Barry.
We just need to figure out
what it is.
Well, let's go get him then.
Let's get some answers.
We can't do that now
as much as we might want to.
Joe, you had your suspicions
about Wells
From the very beginning.
You thought that he might be
the man in yellow.
Except the blood from
your house didn't match him.
All right, so maybe he's not
the Reverse-Flash,
But you think that he knows
what happened that night.
He may have the key
to getting my dad out of prison.
Whatever Wells wants
from you,
It started 15 years ago.
He's been patient.
Scary patient.
You gotta listen to me
on this.
We have to be
just as patient.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Wow. Look.
Wow.
Henry?
Henry!
- Henry!
- Henry?
Nice name.
Tricked ya.
Look who's back.
My tricks.
My treat.
But I'll give you
something good to eat.
Today's special.
A city in ashes.
The Trickster proudly
welcomes you all
To the new disorder.
Talking in the third person.
That's never a good sign.
You're just mad
because he named himself.
Actually, he didn't.
20 years ago, Central City
was hit by a series
Of terrorist attacks.
One man killed at least
ten civilians, two cops.
That guy called himself
the Trickster.
Whoa. Someone was rocking
the unitard.
James Jesse?
Like Jesse James,
only more twisted.
Where is
this Mr. Jesse now?
He's serving several
life sentences at Iron Heights.
He was just about
the most dangerous thing
Central city had ever seen.
You mean until the
particle accelerator blew up.
Um...
Barry and I will go see this
James Jesse at Iron Heights,
See if he can give us something
That can help us
catch his groupie.
I'll analyze the video and see
if I can figure out the source.
Hey, Joe.
Is Barry doing all right?
He seems cranky.
Even the Flash wakes up
on the wrong side of the bed
Some mornings.
He's fine.
- Mom!
- Nora, hold on!
Run, Barry, run!
Gideon, what's happening
to me?
Your latest time jump
against the Flash
Caused a massive drain
on your powers.
Your cells contain no trace
of the speed force.
That's impossible.
Your ability to move
at super-speed
As well as travel in time
has been completely depleted.
How am I supposed
to get back?
You can't.
Never seen this part
of the prison before.
Yeah, I had to have this cell
specially built
For James Jesse
about five years ago.
Why is that?
A criminal psychologist set up
weekly visits with him.
James talked the shrink
into committing suicide.
Oh, you're gonna need these.
Okay.
Gentlemen.
Please, be seated.
I'm Detective Joe west.
This is Barry Allen.
Uh, we'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Mmm.
I can smell them in your pocket.
Yesterday, hundreds
of these parachute bombs
Were released
throughout Central City.
Huh.
Fun idea
But not
an effective delivery system.
How many died?
No one, luckily.
You know, when I was free
and at my height,
A day without casualties
was like...
Well, like the cubs
winning the pennant...
It just never happened.
The explosives they found
in all the parachute bombs
Had the same explosive
composition as the bombs
You set off 20 years ago.
That's impossible.
I never told anyone
that formula.
The signatures are
an exact match.
He called himself
the Trickster too,
Just like you.
He is nothing like me,
Detective.
Nothing!
Do you know who he is?
Oh.
If I did, I would tell you,
So you could find him,
cut off his head,
And throw it
right in his face.
No, this is obviously
the work
Of a rank amateur at best.
A mere pretender angling
for my throne.
I hear you.
So...
Help us catch him.
Prove there's only
one Trickster.
Trying to trick the Trickster,
Joseph, hmm?
No.
There's only one way
this could happen.
Whoever he is,
He must have found my lair.
I ask only one thing,
When you find
this schtick stealer,
This gimmick grabber,
this pathetic wannabe, fake,
Make sure your safety's off.
Something has happened
to Mason Bridge.
No one has seen or heard
from him in a week.
Well, he's a journalist, Iris.
Maybe he's on a story.
Then why hasn't he answered
his phone or his emails?
Maybe he stumbled on the wrong
story and he's laying low.
You don't know him
like I do, Eddie.
When mason is on a story,
nothing is getting in his way.
I mean, he considers threats
minor annoyances.
Then maybe he's on a bender
or he met a girl
Worth disappearing
for a week over.
Look, he also said that
something weird was going on
At S.T.A.R. Labs.
Eddie, something has happened
to him.
Something bad.
I can feel it.
Please.
Look, Captain Singh
has everyone
On the Central City park
bomber.
But as soon as I can,
I'll look into Bridge.
I promise.
Okay.
This looks like nobody's
been here since the '90s.
Yeah, look at this thing.
You really think
Jesse doesn't know
Who this new Trickster
guy is?
He seemed pretty ticked off
that someone
Was besmirching his bad name.
Joe.
Let's see what he's got
stashed in there.
Yeah.
- Damn.
- You good?
The copycat...
he took everything.
Hey, c-can we have
a second?
- Yeah, sure.
- Just...
Dad. Hey.
Barry.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Joe and I have
some questions for an inmate
About a bombing case.
Dad, listen, I'm close.
The man that
put you in here...
I'm getting close,
closer than I've ever been.
Barry, we have
talked about this.
I know, and I'm done talking.
You're not gonna pay
for another man's crime anymore.
Just hang in there, okay?
Joe, what's he talking about?
Like he said, Henry,
just hang in there.
What?
No candy, fellas?
That storage space you
sent us to was booby-trapped.
You can never be too careful
With your private things.
You were protecting nothing.
Your secret stash was empty.
What do you mean?
No firearms,
none of your explosives,
Nothing.
Whatever you had in there,
It was stolen, all of it.
No.
He's stealing my legacy.
Whoever this is,
you need to find him.
I will not let this...
this...
- Trickster?
- That is my name! Mine!
What was in that room?
What were you keeping there?
A bomb.
A really big bomb.
How big?
Bye-bye, Central City.
Cisco.
Yo, this Trickster guy
just posted a vlog.
You gotta see this.
I'm sending you the link
right now.
Okay.
Denizens of Central City,
Or those of you who remain,
Welcome to boom day.
I'm very proud to report
that my first trick
Was an exploding success.
Show him.
But I think you all deserve
Something much, uh, bigger.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- So for my next trick...
Take off my mask, you fraud.
Keep your eyes glued...
Pretender. Sham.
Take off my mask.
Take off my mask!
This was posted a few hours ago.
Whoever this Trickster is,
he's certainly not shy.
Well, not every criminal
likes to hide in the dark.
Cisco, can you trace
where the video was posted from?
I tried, but this guy
is using some crazy
Felicity-caliber scrambler
like I've never seen.
The origin of the upload's
coming from hundreds
Of different locations.
Until he uploads another video,
it's gonna be tough.
This psychopath has the
capability to destroy the city.
Hey, I said tough,
not impossible.
Barry, we'll catch him.
We always do.
Mr. Allen,
A word please?
I know what's going on
with you.
I know what you're thinking.
Do you?
I know going up
to Iron Heights prison
And conversing with Mr. Jesse
has brought about feelings
Of your father.
How could it not?
Yeah, no, it's, uh,
It's been really tough
knowing that my mom's killer
Is still out there.
Of course.
But we'll find him, together.
You have my word.
Thank you.
For now, how about we focus
On finding this Trickster
before anybody else gets hurt?
I have to go.
But thanks for the pep talk.
I'm always here for you.
Research laboratories
unconnected to the government,
Unconnected
to any business interests
Or any of that kind of stuff.
And then we build right downtown
In the heart of the city,
in the epicenter,
And we become
the heart of the city.
We become the heart
of the nation.
We change the way you think
about the sciences,
And then...
What?
Just that my father
would have loved you...
As much as I do.
Well, I wish
I could have met him.
Oh.
And what would you call
these laboratories?
Well, we, Tess Morgan,
Would call them
"the technological engineering
Scientific studies,"
or T.E.S.S., for short.
Well, that is
very, very sweet.
But how about...
"scientific and technological
Advanced research
laboratories,"
Or S.T.A.R. Labs,
for short?
Because in the vast night sky,
you, Harrison Wells,
are the only star I see,
that's gonna get you kissed.
I thought you were
a full-time reporter now.
Why are we meeting here?
I still have a key.
And this is kind of
our place, right?
What's up?
My coworker Mason Bridge
is missing.
He's not at home.
He's not answering his phone.
I mean, it's not like him.
I am really worried that
something bad has happened.
I'm sure he's fine.
That's what Eddie says.
That's what everyone is saying.
Please, will you
look into it?
For me?
For you.
Thanks.
Um, are you okay?
You seem like you have
a heavy heart.
Sometimes I'm not sure
why I wear a mask with you.
Well, maybe one day
you'll take it off.
Heads up.
Trickster's broadcasting again.
Can I borrow your laptop?
Um, sure.
Help...
Help yourself.
Get ready for the games
to begin!
I have... A bomb.
It's a big bomb.
It'll make a big bang
and then a big hole
and then a big drop
in the pop...ulation.
But never say the Trickster
Is not fair.
The bomb is somewhere between
52nd street and avenue B.
I want all units,
every uniform, every detective
Searching that area
right now.
Somehow we need
to alert the Flash.
Something tells me
he already knows.
Guys, I can't find it.
I need your help.
There's nothing on traffic cams
or CCTV.
I retasked
the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
To scan the area
for incendiary devices.
A bomb that large
should be giving off
Some kind of thermal
or chemical signature.
Well, then
why can't you find it?
Because it's a trick.
The bomb's not there.
No, it has to be.
I'm gonna keep looking.
That is what he wants,
for you and the police
To keep running around
in circles.
There is something else
going on, Barry.
I can feel it.
Now, trust me.
- I'm gonna keep looking.
- Barry?
Why doesn't he just
listen to you?
I found it.
Uh-oh, there's an explosion
at Iron Heights.
This was all a diversion.
The prison was
the real target.
James Jesse.
I guess he's tricked us all.
Joe, there's no bomb
in this city.
It was a diversion
so the Trickster
Could help James Jesse
escape.
I know.
We just got surveillance footage
from Iron Heights.
Jesse got away.
Barry, look,
they took a hostage.
Well, who did he take?
A guard? The warden?
No.
Your dad.
You have to admit,
That was one hell of a trick.
I cannot believe
we're finally in the same room.
I mean, you're my hero.
You need a better
role model, kid.
Can't you see?
He's just using you.
Why did we bring him along?
Huh?
Because his son
works for the CCPD.
Should we find ourselves
in a jam,
A cop's dad makes
an excellent bargaining chip.
Right.
I wouldn't worry too much about
what the cops might do to you.
Really?
If the police aren't able
to find you,
Trust me, the Flash will.
Here's hoping.
So what's next?
In your last letter,
you said you had something big
In mind for when you got out.
I've had 20 years to come up
with the perfect trick.
It's going to be
my masterpiece.
My Mona Lisa.
My Breaking Bad season five.
They gave me cable in prison
so I'd stop killing the guards.
Right.
There's just one thing
I've been dying to ask.
Why did you choose me?
Because I knew
you had the strength
To fulfill my legacy.
Besides,
It was in your blood.
Wait.
What do you mean in...
in my blood?
The real reason
I tracked you down
And groomed you to be the best
you could possibly be, Axel...
I am your father.
We were able to identify
the other Trickster.
His name's Axel Walker,
age 25.
Apparently him and James
have been corresponding
Through snail mail
for over a decade.
I should have been there.
We're gonna find
your dad, okay?
Definitely.
I guess I should have
listened to you.
Sorry, I am so tired.
I think I'm just gonna
put on my pajamas,
Go straight to bed
when we get home.
- Really?
- No.
Definitely not
wearing pajamas.
Hello.
No, no, no.
Tess.
Tess! Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Tess. Tess.
Oh, thank god.
You gotta help me.
Please help me.
Oh.
She... she's...
What are you doing?
Help. Call someone!
Call anyone!
Can't you see she's dying?
This woman has been dead
for centuries.
Help!
You okay?
Do you think my dad
is still alive?
Yes. Yes, he is.
Of course.
Jesse only took your pop
to use as leverage.
He might be crazy,
but he's not stupid.
And everyone upstairs
is looking to find him.
So now I'm supposed to just
Leave my dad's fate
in the hands of a man
Who may have had something
to do with my mom's murder.
Joe, I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
It just doesn't make
any sense.
I mean,
if Wells is a murderer,
Then why does he want
to help me?
Why has he helped me
stop so many criminals?
Or saved Ronnie?
Why didn't I see this?
I spent 1/10 as much time
with him as you did,
And he almost had me
believing in him.
Almost.
Look, whatever else he is,
He is Harrison Wells.
You love science.
He is science.
It's like you made
best friends with Einstein.
You're saying I wanted
to be tricked.
You always want to be
the person
Who sees the best in people.
I've been a cop for 25 years.
All I can see is the flaws,
The lies,
The dark thoughts
that people think I don't see.
I wish I could be you.
As fast as you are,
that is your real power.
Don't let Wells
take that from you.
I don't know
Why he's helping us.
All that matters
is that he is.
I can't lose my dad, Joe.
Barr.
Barr, come on.
Come on.
Hi. Iris west, I'm with
Central City picture news.
Thanks.
Champagne, miss?
Oh, thank you.
We're almost out
of champagne.
Then the fun's
about to begin.
Oh, Mayor Bellows, hi.
- This is a lovely party.
- Thank you.
Welcome, welcome,
Central City's finest.
How about a toast
to Mayor Anthony Bellows?
He doesn't just yell
at his staff, he bellows!
You see what I did there
with the wordplay and the...
- Tough crowd.
- Excuse me.
Who are you?
How quickly they forget.
James Jesse, your honor,
A.k.a. the Trickster.
And I'm here to relieve you
fine people from all your money.
Because we know
if you're in this room,
you've got loads of it.
What makes you think
that anyone in this room
Would give you a cent?
Because that champagne
they just slurped down
Like so much fruit punch...
I added a little something
special to it.
Trimethylmercury 32.
Poison.
Without the antidote,
you'll begin to feel the effects
In about, oh, um...
One hour.
I remember you.
You got to the party
about an hour early.
I offered you the very first
glass of champagne.
An hour is plenty of time for
all of you to call your bankers
And transfer everything you have
to the account number
On the bottom of your glass.
Once my young friend and I
are rich,
You'll get the antidote.
If any of you decide
to call 911 instead,
Well, then we switch
to lead poisoning.
Anything?
I'm scanning all
the traffic cams in the city.
- I got nothing.
- Hey, baby.
Iris?
What's up?
How many of you feel
the trimethyline 32
Coursing through your veins,
hmm?
That's him.
That's Jesse.
- Cisco, can you ping her phone?
- I'm on it.
Trimethylmercury 32 is a
relatively fast-acting poison.
Is there a cure?
Yes. We can start synthesizing
the antidote right now.
Cisco, where is she?
City hall.
The mayor's having a fund-raiser
there tonight.
Barry, do not underestimate
the Trickster.
Well, hello.
You know,
I've been in prison
for 20 years.
Then you'll know the routine
when you get sent back.
Where's Henry Allen?
He's where you'll be soon.
Heaven!
Are you familiar
with the movie speed?
Keanu Reeves, Sandra Bullock?
See, you're the bus,
and that's the bomb.
A kinetic bomb, actually,
and if you go below
600 miles per hour,
it'll explode.
Same thing happens
if you try to remove it.
Ooh, it's active.
Run, run, run, run, run.
Cisco!
He wasn't lying.
That thing's linked
to a speedometer,
And it will blow
if you stop moving.
I can't run forever.
There's gotta be a way to get it
off him without damaging it.
Barry, do you see
any walls nearby?
Why?
Because I need you
to run into one.
Or more accurately,
through one.
What?
If you vibrate
at the natural frequency of air,
Your body... your cells will be
in a state of excitement
That should allow you
to phase
Right through that wall,
Leaving the bomb
on the other side.
- Should?
- You can do this.
I believe in you.
- I can't.
- Listen to me, Barry.
Breathe.
Feel the air.
Feel that wind on your face.
Feel the ground,
your feet lifting you up,
Pushing you forward,
and the lightning...
Barry, feel the lightning.
Feel its power.
Its electricity pumping
through your veins,
Crackling through you, traveling
to every nerve in your body,
Like a shock.
You're no longer you now.
You're part
of something greater.
of a speed-force.
It's yours.
Now do it.
- Oh!
- Barry?
Oh, that felt weird.
Oh.
I'm good.
- Ooh, I like it.
- Look at that.
Lobsters on me, kid.
It's okay. You've all been
given an antidote.
That wasn't very sanitary.
Now where is Henry Allen?
You're going to prison
either way, James.
All right.
You always did look good
in red.
Wow.
Half of this stuff didn't even
exist when I was practicing.
Yeah, well, I'd be happy
to give you
A crash course on all of it
if you get out.
I'm gonna shut up now.
It's okay.
- Dr. Allen?
- Yes?
I'm feeling the need
to give you a hug.
Absolutely.
I will always accept a hug.
Thank you.
Wow.
You gotta tell me.
What does it feel like when
you're running down the street
Like a bat out of hell?
There's no feeling like it.
I bet.
Actually, you're all heroes
in my book,
Especially you,
Dr. Wells.
Thank you
For everything that
you've done for my son.
Well, your son is
an extraordinary man, Dr. Allen,
And I will do everything
in my power
To ensure Barry's future.
It's time, Joe.
- No.
- No?
- Okay.
You seem like
you could use a hug too.
Your father is
an extraordinary man.
You're lucky to have him.
I'm lucky to have you too.
Ahh!
Who are you?
My name is Eobard Thawne,
But that name doesn't matter.
Not anymore.
It won't matter for many years.
The only thing that really
matters is who you are.
Harrison Wells.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
In the year 2020,
you and your wife, Tess Morgan,
Successfully launched
a particle accelerator
That changed the course
of history.
I need it to happen a bit sooner
if I'm going to get back.
Much sooner.
- What is that?
- My way home.
You see, they're not coming
to save you.
They're coming to save me.
Hey, Joe.
Desk sergeant said
you were looking for me.
Eddie, yeah.
Uh...
Sit down.
It's about Iris.
She's looking into
Mason Bridge's disappearance.
We can't let that happen.
Detective.
Eddie, we need your help.
Brazil?
Why... why would
mason move to Brazil?
Apparently there was
a girl involved,
And he decided to go hike
the amazon with her for a year,
You know, live off the grid,
Write his memoirs
or something.
Wow. I guess you really
don't know anyone.
No, you don't.
Hey, baby, everything good?
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
Um, dinner will be ready
in a jiff, okay?
Okay.
She buy it?
I think so.
Keeping her in the dark,
it's for her safety.
That is debatable,
and we will have that debate.
But for right now,
what's our next move?
How do we figure out
what Wells is up to?
When Wells was talking me
through phasing
So I could get the Trickster's
bomb off my wrist,
The way that he described
my being the Flash, running,
Feeling the wind
and the power,
It's like he was talking
from experience.
What are you saying?
I don't know how...
But he's the man in yellow.
Harrison Wells
is the Reverse-Flash.
I got an 11-80,
possible 10-54,
County road J,
requesting immediate assistance.
Copy that.
Units en route to your location.
Sir, we're gonna get you
out of here.
Can you tell me your name?
Do you know who you are?
My name...
Is...
Harrison Wells.
Greg, move your head.