(This film is based on
a true story.)
(Names, characters and events
have been dramatized.)
Come on...
You should've slowed down.
It's banged up.
Are you okay?
- Yes, and you?
- I'm fine.
Why did you drive so fast
at night?
- Photos look good?
- What?
There's no need for that.
What are you talking about?
Photos are important
for insurance.
Don't change your story later.
It's scratched up...
(The Gangster, The Cop, The Devil)
(August 2005)
Another murder took place
near Cheonan
early this morning.
Many murders and missing person
cases have been reported
since last year,
but the police have not closed...
We want to close them, too.
Close cases,
go on vacations, and get promoted.
Turn off the siren!
No one in this town gives a damn.
Not a single person here.
- It's a filthy world...
- You're right.
Look at those gangsters.
Those guys need a serious beating.
Where you going? We're on a case!
Like hell we are.
Does it look like one?
- Tae-seok!
- See you at the scene!
- You can't even do that?
- I'm sorry.
Seriously.
Please walk through.
- Go ahead, I'm a cop.
- Sir!
I told you
to stay out of my sight.
Block the entrance.
Step aside.
It's a hot day.
Why are you here again?
Does a cop need permission
from gangsters to be here?
Sir!
Detective!
Please head back.
Today's a bad day!
Is something up today?
The traffic is messed up,
and so are you.
Okay.
Here. Please go away.
You bastard,
what do you take me for?
How dare you try to bribe me?
Here you go, bastards.
You should be careful.
Why are gangsters
trying to stop a cop?
Continue.
I hope you win!
Boss!
That damn cop's here.
Put it down.
- Wrap him up nicely.
- Yes, boss.
I received $200
in gift certificates.
Taking our 10% cut,
your prize money is $180!
What the heck?
Open it.
Salute.
Screw that.
You're charged with illegal
conversion of gift certificates.
Remain silent or don't.
You could retain a lawyer,
or you could not.
Let's go.
Sir!
Come in for a second.
Please come in.
Buddy, come out.
Put them on nicely.
Good morning, boss!
It's me.
Your bastard's back again.
What?
I sent him to a crime scene.
What's he doing there?
Ask the bastard yourself.
Tell Hur I'm heading there.
You can't do this to me
after taking a cut every month.
Since you took it all
for yourself,
your boys are making a mess
at my workplace.
I told you not to exchange
in the shop, didn't I?
Start an exchange shop
under someone else's name.
Do that or share the stakes.
You know the game.
I don't do petty business.
I'm busy making machines
and opening new shops.
Can't you cut him off
before he comes over?
My boys have families to feed.
Okay, I'll take care of
that bastard.
What?
"What"?
Are we buddies?
Where are you?
Heading to the crime scene.
I'm hanging up.
I don't want friends like you.
Let me just shut off...
- the fan.
- Come here.
Stop in front of there.
Sure, as you wish.
- Thanks for the ride.
- Thank you.
Come on, sir!
I gave you a ride!
It's a give-and-take!
Here's my payment.
Kneel on the ground!
I'm gonna call the cops on you!
Damn traffic jam...
Where the heck have you been?
There's a crowd already?
Get rid of them.
Reporters! One moment, please!
Take photos later.
I'm really sorry.
Could you make way?
Secure the scene properly!
What have you been doing?
Hey! Move aside!
You came so late.
A crowd's gathering!
People are gathering!
Good day.
Did you check his ID?
We're checking his plate number,
so we'll find out soon.
He died only a few hours ago.
Between 3 and 5 this morning.
Cause of death is either
blood loss or a heart attack.
That's my initial impression.
Kiddo, come take some photos.
Hey, Seo-jin! Come over here!
Look into this.
I told you not to call me by name
at the crime scene.
My apologies, Chief Cha,
salute, take a look.
What is it?
A rear-ender?
It does look like it... or not.
I hope he didn't die over this.
I'd prefer a random killing.
Thanks for the other day.
For turning my boy into a cripple.
There are rules for a reason.
Anyway.
Our businesses are separate, but
we share machines and engineers.
All right.
But we gotta resolve
the turf issue, no?
Be flexible.
- Sang-do.
- Yes, Dong-su?
If you only eat sweets,
you get toothaches.
Don't stir up trouble and just
manage the shop I assigned you.
Everyone has their limit.
If you cross mine, you're dead.
I don't even cross the road.
Steve Jobs said,
"Stay hungry."
I got no capital and no investors,
so I'm still hungry.
Sir.
My boss is being lenient
because you two are friends.
That's why he's giving you
the tech and engineers, too.
The slot arcade business
is nothing like fighting over
these bars and clubs!
Are you nuts?
In front of our bosses?
Give us what?
You should be kissing up them!
What the hell!
Bastard!
Is this how you train your men?
Look at him glaring at me.
Hey, Dong-su.
Why are you being almighty
after giving me the crumbs?
How can we keep the peace
like this?
Come here.
Yes, boss.
Can't you see we're talking?
Come here.
Look at this jerk.
We can work peacefully now.
Suck it up!
It's good.
(Cheonan Police)
Choi Jung-gyu, 46 years old.
No enemies, debts, lawsuits
or anything like that.
Autopsy report was clear.
Over a dozen stab wounds.
It looks like an amateur job.
He just went nuts.
But it feels too unusual
to be an amateur job.
No evidence was left behind.
No footprints, blood, hairs,
fingerprints, nothing.
Since the wallet's gone,
it could be a robbery,
but it wasn't for a lot of money,
so maybe not.
People kill
for the smallest things.
Briefing's over,
Get the captain of Unit 1.
Yes, sir!
Yes, Chief.
This case is likely
a robbery-homicide,
so look for anyone
with similar criminal records.
Right away, sir.
You guys, back up Unit 1.
It's the same suspect
for all three cases.
Which cases?
July 15, West Mountain reservoir.
July 23, Boryung Sunbeach Motel.
And, last night's case.
A knife was the murder weapon
in all three cases.
Seeing length and width
of the knife,
it could be the same knife.
No, it is the same knife.
It's a serial killing case.
We're not in the States.
We can't get guns.
Everyone kills with knives.
Freaking nonsense.
There are over 1,000 murders
a year.
By your logic,
half of them are done by one guy.
Are you nuts?
Who are you to mess with
another jurisdiction's cases?
Does the killer care
about jurisdictions?
If we don't catch him soon,
there will be problems.
He's too careful to be
indiscriminate.
He could strike again at any...
You work so easily.
These aren't salad ingredients!
You can't just toss them together!
I'm not randomly mixing them.
These cases are a week apart
in the Chungnam region.
Our informants got nothing.
It's intuition.
Screw your intuition.
Didn't your intuition lead you
to a gang-operated arcade?
You had that much free time?
They're not criminals?
Gangsters and killers
are cut from the same cloth.
Jung Tae-seok, what's with you?
Are you so desperate
to get promoted?
Geez...
Yes, that's what I'm after.
After arresting the killer.
The briefing's over, come out!
Let's grab that killer.
I'm not drunk. I'll drive myself.
But, sir...
Take the boys and head back.
Yes, boss.
That's correct, Mr. Chairman.
Hur may act rash,
but he's a smart man.
He won't stir up trouble anymore.
Yes, don't worry.
Have a good night.
I'm sorry.
The road was slippery.
It looks fine. You can just go.
What?
But I still hit you...
I'm fine, you can go.
Are you really okay?
Yes, it's fine.
Bastard!
Dammit!
What the hell?
Who are you?
Come here!
Who's there?
It wasn't Hur.
I've never seen him before.
It was Hur, boss.
He's not in the gang world.
His attack felt cold,
but emotional, too.
It felt different.
Who else would try to attack you
in our line of work?
Give me that.
It was too dark to see properly...
(White sedan, Daejeon 23XX plate)
- Get out!
- Find it no matter what.
Be careful there.
We're friends.
Sorry to bother you.
The patient looks so damn comfy.
What is it now?
I brought a box of Red Bull.
I heard you got poked.
I got a call from the hospital.
You must be so embarrassed.
You're a don, after all.
Likewise, you're a cop, after all.
Cops are so incompetent.
That's why bad things
keep happening to model citizens.
Oh my...
Model citizen, Jang Dong-su.
Tell me everything
about that night.
I'll catch him for you.
I can probably catch him faster.
Yeah?
Wanna bet?
Spill it, jerk.
I'll catch him for you.
Fine, do you mind?
I tripped at night and got hurt.
Right, at night.
You gotta watch where you walk.
Unlucky bastards can trip
and fall on multiple knives.
Jang's car is a black Mercedes,
3849, right?
Got it, I'll call you back.
Bastard...
Rear collision.
White sedan.
I was right, you bastard.
(Wishing you a fast recovery!
Hur Sang-do)
Jeez, look at you.
You okay?
- Have a seat.
- I'm fine.
I feel so bad,
I can barely look at you.
What will happen now?
You got jumped even before
the ink on the contract dried.
What'd you like me to do?
A ton of my boys are cripples now.
Pay their hospital bills
and some compensation,
and hand over the flagship
and Sungan shops.
I'll make sure your boys
are well compensated.
And the shops?
Was this your plan all along?
Dong-su.
If I'd done it,
would you still be alive?
Think carefully.
I'm really curious, too.
Who'd do a number on you
like this?
I'm off.
So embarrassing!
A gangster getting stabbed!
I'd just kill myself!
Trust me and give me
two men on this case.
I'll close them in one go.
Why don't you just
request a furlough?
I barely have enough men
to run this department.
Why do you want to
take someone else's work?
Chief, it's a huge case.
Close one, and more will follow.
Like a super-long train.
Buzz off!
There's a witness
who survived the attack.
A witness came forward?
Jang Dong-su.
What? Jang Dong-su?
He was stabbed a few days ago.
A two-hour surgery
barely kept him alive.
Listen to yourself.
Think for a second.
What kind of psychotic idiot
would attack a gang boss?
The killer's not involved
with the gangs.
I'm sure of it,
he's a serial killer!
Shut up!
This is a gang matter.
I'll assign it to Unit 2.
I'm warning you,
don't get involved.
Get out!
Go easy on covering his ass.
This isn't the time for that.
What? Cover him?
What is it then?
You little bastard!
Let's say you're right.
But still, Jang is the victim.
Will you get a warrant
for his arrest?
Or go arrest him without one?
How many crimes has he committed?
We gotta get him now,
and mess him up.
He's about to burst.
If we don't do anything,
he'll kill the killer,
and we'll be left with
three open cases.
How can Jang find him?
He's a gangster, not a cop.
It's not even work to find someone
with his boys.
Also, Jang saw...
the killer's face.
Get out.
You're not making
an ounce of sense.
Get out!
Why don't you
talk to the landlord?
What am I supposed to do?
I gotta work to make money!
What? Birthday?
Why is the baby's birthday
so important?
I'm tired as hell!
I haven't slept in two days,
don't nag me about a birthday!
Your baby's birthday?
What?
That kid you mentioned.
Give me that.
Sharp face.
Thin cheeks. Angled chin.
Long and narrow nose.
Lips bigger than the nose...
That's pretty close.
You shouldn't have had the kid.
It's not his fault.
Find him before the cops do.
Understood, boss.
Bro, where are we?
Who are you?
Thank you for your cooperation!
We're locking down
illegal slot arcades!
Everyone should stay put!
Where's the boss?
Get him down here!
Yeah? Hold on.
Okay, go ahead.
Jang is so adorable,
he's a scheming bastard.
63 out of 97 machines
have been meddled with.
Should I get a warrant?
Hold on.
Let me ask him.
So, should I get a warrant?
What do you want?
The one who stabbed you.
Tell me everything,
and I'll look the other way.
What if I don't?
Since you're paying off my boss,
I'm nothing to you, huh?
Listen, Jang.
The guy who stabbed you...
he's a serial killer.
He's a bit strange.
He's different from other psychos.
You're the evidence.
What the heck
are you talking about?
Why do you think
he messed with you?
Most psychopaths go after girls,
or people who are weaker
than they are.
But this bastard kills
indiscriminately.
If we don't find him soon,
more people will die.
What the hell's your problem?
Hand over the info
and do your gangster stuff.
It's a win-win.
I'll catch him, put him on trial,
and lock him up for good!
And then what?
Nothing. It's over.
That's it?
When the country's biggest
luxury casino is built
on the penthouse
of this skyscraper,
the entire area surrounding
our Zeus building
will become the hottest spot
in town.
Enough of this crap,
I heard this place's gone to hell.
Dammit!
Everyone who lined up for
pre-construction units has left.
Naturally, investors are
delaying their funding.
Weird rumors went around
after your incident.
The Chungju region
is another problem.
Hur's boys are moving in
on our turf.
You still haven't found him?
We found his car
on the national highway.
His car?
It was parked at a rest stop
for a few days.
My boys found it.
Where's the car now?
We brought it back.
There was a murder
a few days ago in Sintanjin.
And this.
Dumped or lost,
they found this 3km away
from the car.
Keep this safe.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
It's me.
What a surprise.
You know
the Sintanjin murder case?
What about it?
That bastard did it.
What?
How do you know that?
We found his car there.
I'm at the top of my game.
I got here by risking my life.
Then some guy comes along
and grabs my ankle.
What else can I do?
I gotta cut his arm off.
I can't cut my ankle.
But that guy disappeared
without a trace.
After ruining
a gangster's reputation.
Buddy.
Whoever messes with me
must take responsibility.
Reputation is everything
to a gangster.
I'll chop him up good
and put him on display.
You're telling a cop
you'll kill a man?
We do things that the law can't.
A bad guy will catch
another bad guy?
No.
Two bad guys
will catch a worse man.
His car key.
Do you not see me as a cop?
I could arrest you right away.
You can't. Why?
You want him more than me.
I'll provide manpower
and foot the bill.
We'll share the tips,
and help each other out.
And at the end?
Split the bastard in half?
Whoever catches him keeps him.
So, if I catch him first,
we go by the law,
and if you catch him,
you'll bury him?
Join me if you want.
Okay, it's a deal.
You'll regret this.
A handsome fellow.
How old was he?
About mid-30s.
Rain and darkness
obscured my vision.
Keep in touch using this.
A gangster catches
the devil with a cop.
This is freaking good!
A gangster catches
the devil with a cop.
This is freaking good!
Bastard.
You and I are in the same boat.
I gotta have some insurance.
It's not like
we can draft a contract.
You went high tech
and recorded me?
Damn!
This gangster is trying
to use his brain!
This is why I can't trust
police officers.
I've been too lenient with you.
Listen, bastard.
When this is over,
I'll lock you up first, you jerk!
He stabbed Jang Dong-su, too.
He's behind the Sintanjin case.
What does this mean?
If we go my way,
we can close five cases at once.
Mid-30s, average male height.
Judging from his pattern,
he only kills at night.
Location is not a factor,
and he only uses a knife.
It's one of two things.
Persistence, or always ready.
No other clues so far.
I made a deal with Detective Jung.
We'll catch him together.
Obviously,
we won't tell the chief.
How can we trust cops?
How can we trust gangsters?
Trust who?
We need manpower
to catch the killer.
This isn't a case
we can handle ourselves.
Let's get the chief involved.
And then what?
Major Crimes will barge in,
get the media involved,
and get all the glory.
That's not all.
The chief is protecting Jang.
This is the only way
to solve this case.
Otherwise, the chief
will be really screwed, too.
Jang has seen the killer's face
and has his car.
But, his sketch alone
isn't good enough.
We need fingerprints and DNA.
We'll use the gangsters
to find the killer,
and then we'll move in
to catch him.
I'll use them
and toss them away afterward.
We're tax-paying citizens, too.
Let's get support from the cops
for once.
On the outside, it looks like
a cold, abandoned warehouse,
but thousands of arcade cabinets
are built here,
and distributed
all over the country.
Bastards.
We'll get something out of this.
Hopefully his hair, fingerprint,
or even just the smell of him.
No, we gotta absolutely
find something.
We'll comb every inch.
Let's begin.
Let's leave all the grunt work
to Jang,
and we'll go through
all the cases so far.
This is the Sintanjin murder
security cam footage.
His unique pattern is,
he has used a vehicle
in all the murders so far.
He's always on the move,
making him harder to catch.
We know of four open cases,
but there has to be more.
Don't forget to look at them
from a serial killer angle.
If you find anything,
report to me.
He's a ticking time bomb.
He could pop up anywhere.
Look into other regional cases.
Try not to look too conspicuous.
Okay?
- Okay!
- Yes, sir.
We'll lock up the gangsters
after the case is over.
Nice and clean.
It's ultimately up to us
to catch the killer.
Before that, let's get rid of Hur.
Son of a...!
Are you insane?
What are you doing here?
What the hell do you think?
I was waiting for you.
I think you broke my back.
You shouldn't have
surprised me like that.
I was so startled.
Give me some.
- That feels good.
- Could you look into this?
It's urgent.
What is it?
Nothing special.
I found some hairs and blood.
ID them for me.
Jung Tae-seok.
What's with you?
This isn't like you.
What's wrong?
It's a filthy world.
I want to get my hands dirty.
You're right. It is filthy.
He's weird one.
He left the weapon for us to see.
"Murder cases and cops
are lost at sea."
"Crying over spilled milk."
Now a gang boss is dead.
What will you do?
What should we do?
If you got a mouth, say something!
The Hur case...
is assigned to Unit 2.
They'll investigate it.
What are you doing?
Stop staring at the monitor!
Get out!
Right this second!
Do whatever it takes
to help solve these cases!
At least look like
you give a damn!
Walk straight!
Yeah, speak.
Buddy!
Do you wanna die?
What is it?
This is nothing special?
I just got the results.
I don't believe this...
What? Tell me quickly.
The DNA of most recent Chungnam
murder victims was detected.
Really?
Anyone else's?
Anyone else
other than the known victims?
No.
That doesn't make sense.
Did you do it properly?
There was no one else!
But that's not the issue.
Something messed up happened.
Hold on a second.
Go ahead.
The DNA of the truck driver
and the puppy mill owner
were both found on
the Hur murder weapon.
What?
It means one person did them all.
This'll officially be classified
as a serial killer case.
I gotta go.
Jang Dong-su! Was it you?
It was you!
I'll call you back in a bit.
Answer me, you bastard!
Dammit, are you nuts?
Dammit!
Your idiot's back.
He thinks this is his home.
Who else? Your minion!
Let's talk later.
What's a cop doing
with a gangster?
And you're not a cop?
Huh?
Tell me, you jerk.
Did you kill Hur Sang-do?
Yeah, I killed him.
I am so damn stupid
for trusting this bastard.
You trusted me?
A mutt would laugh at that.
Nothing's changed.
We'll still catch him together.
Got it?
When...
this is all over,
I'll investigate you properly.
Whatever, buddy.
The murder cases in the region
since July this year
were found to be the work
of a serial killer...
These cases were handed over
to Major Crimes
in cooperation with
the Cheonan Police,
after the cases remained idle
for a while.
The murders were handled
by various regional
police departments,
but by centralizing
the investigation,
there's new hope
for finally closing the cases.
I wish this ordeal would wrap up,
so residents can be at peace.
Let's cross to our reporter
at the scene...
You're here early.
Dong-chul.
I'm outside Ace Hotel,
where the murder took place
on September 3rd.
The victim of this crime
is said to be Hur Sang-do,
who led a violent gang
in the Chungnam region.
He was said to be
in a turf war with...
If you had handed over the case
from the beginning,
it wouldn't have come to this.
Murder isn't some child's play.
You guys only ruined
the damn investigation.
Nice language in
someone else's house.
- Detective...
- You got a problem?
Am I wrong?
Yeah, man.
I got a problem all right!
You bastard!
Come at me!
- Bastard!
- Hey! Stop!
A knife was found at
the scene of Hur's murder,
and the DNA of other victims
was discovered.
A special task force was set up
to investigate not only Hur,
but other victims as well,
as all the murders
are likely committed by
one killer...
That wasn't me...
The task force consists of the
Major Crimes and Homicide units
as well as the country's best
serial killer profiler,
in order to conduct
a thorough investigation.
They will also have the help of
forensic scientists.
The police are expecting
huge turnout of gangs
for the funeral of Hur,
and they will remain vigilant.
I'm surprised to see you here.
Of course I'm here.
He was my friend.
Hello?
Get over here now!
Why should I?
Clean up your own damn mess!
Get over here!
Who are you?
(Hur was killed with my knife
by someone else)
If you want to kill him yourself,
you better find something.
If Major Crimes gets him first,
you and I are both screwed.
Is this what your entire life
is like?
I pity your sorry cop ass.
Don't commit any crimes,
you moron.
If people like me weren't around,
you would be out of a job.
That's life. There are predators
and there is prey.
There are stabbing victims.
He attacked me from behind.
I was defenseless.
But I still took his knife
and stabbed him.
Hey, hey, stop!
What is it?
You also stabbed him?
I did, why?
I think I found something.
What the hell?
Bastards.
Jang, what's going on?
Who are these guys?
Worthless bastard.
Move!
Go to hell, you bastard!
Hey, buddy!
Hey, hey! Bastard!
Hey, stop.
It's over. Stop it.
You better go.
I'll wrap it up here.
It's... it's okay.
He just bled a lot.
It's just blood...
Get out of here, you bastard!
With enough evidence
to arrest Hur's killer,
the police stated that capturing
the suspect is a matter of time.
The suspect's limited methods
of killing
and his active area are...
Honey, where are you?
Having a nice nap when we are
having so many problems?
What's with his face?
Wake up, moron!
What have you been up to lately?
What the...
Where are you going?
Here, take this.
It's a kidnapping case.
Soon-ho's already there.
Meet up with him.
A kidnapping case?
Why's that important now?
We got a serial killer to catch.
Not that again!
Can't you see Major Crimes
in the office?
They're working with Unit 1,
so take care of this.
I told you this was the work of a
serial killer from the beginning.
Now, Major Crimes and Unit 1
have the case?
What the hell do they know?
They're clueless losers!
I've had it!
What did you say?
Shut your face!
You claimed it was a serial killer
without anything to back it up.
Did you bring a piece of evidence
or a witness?
If you were such a hot shot,
why isn't he behind bars?
Dammit...
The victim was a prolific
venture capitalist.
Tae-seok!
The assailant should be close
to him. Look into it quick.
Are you involved in something
with Jang?
What's with that face?
There is something.
Cut the crap.
Ask his colleagues
about his women.
How many times already?
Why do you keep changing
the meeting spot?
Is he even alive?
If you want the money,
put him on the phone!
This is the last time.
Come to the snack bar.
Right this second.
What are you doing? Go inside.
Did you come by
to drop off the bag?
Leave it with me.
Why is she giving the bag
to that woman?
What the hell?
Why don't you just tell the world
you're here with cops?
Who's that on the roof?
It's him! Roof!
Dong-chul! He's north-bound!
Where is he?
Lure him into the main street!
Hey!
What the hell were you doing?
Soon-ho, block him from your side!
Stop!
I don't see him!
He's right there!
The main street!
Bae, where the hell are you?
I'll head down!
I don't see him here.
- I'm gonna kill you!
- Where did he go?
Catch up!
Up the stairs! Now!
Freeze!
He just turned the corner,
block him from the front!
Which way did he go?
Over there! That way!
Go that way!
Why did you take the bag?
You didn't know what was inside.
Why are you shouting at me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Someone asked me to take it.
Who was it?
Tell us, or you're going to jail!
I've never seen him before!
He ate alone and asked me
to take the bag for him.
He gave me $20.
What did he look like?
He looked normal.
He only ate?
He drank a bottle of Soju too!
The Dew.
Where's the bottle?
Only the labels are different.
All the bottles are the same.
Have fun.
Screw labels...
- Dong-chul!
- Yes, sir!
Just the Dew, got it?
- It's not...
- Just the Dew!
I don't believe this!
The bottles are the same!
Don't work too hard.
Are you serious?
What about
the steering wheel cover?
The result will come out
today at the earliest.
I'll charge $2,000 per machine.
Thank you.
I'll send tech support
if you need them.
Isn't that too cheap, Jang?
If Jang can fulfill his end
of the deal,
we are happy, aren't we?
I don't know if I should take
such a good deal.
Look at how Hur ended up.
Watch out, everyone.
After Jang got stabbed,
Hur got killed.
His lieutenant disappeared, too.
Stick with eating your meal.
What are you doing here?
Look for this guy first.
We got a weird fingerprint.
It's not quite damaged.
He could've smudged it.
I found him with
what little print he left behind.
His whereabouts are unknown.
A similar print was found
on the steering wheel cover, too.
He hasn't come home
in about three months.
Did he say anything?
When he leaves for a job,
he's away for a month.
He's been away
quite a while this time.
I reported just in case.
Any problems with him?
No, not a single problem.
He never misses his rent
and never drinks, either.
And he's a faithful Christian.
He lives a clean life.
He's a good man.
'Basis of Mankind'
'Who Raised A Monster?'
'Night Darker Than Death'
'Sacred Violence'
We got a weird fingerprint.
It's not quite damaged.
He could've smudged it...
017-684-2784!
Find everything you can
about its owner!
And do you have the
kidnapper's voice file?
Send it to me right away,
right this second!
I heard you paid a ton
for his funeral.
You're one loyal guy.
Do me the same courtesy.
I told you to just eat, didn't I?
So damn yappy.
Why are you ruining
this nice lunch?
I'm looking out
for your damn best interests.
Eat your damn words!
Please continue.
I sent you a photo,
so check it now!
Give this a listen!
This is the last time.
Come to the snack bar.
Right this second.
I'm sorry.
The road was slippery.
But I still hit you...
Kang Kyung-ho, 35 years old.
He was abused by his father
and grew up in an orphanage.
He has no prior record.
He calls his 70-year-old mother
every day.
He uses burner phones.
His calls were from Choongchung
until August,
but he was calling from all over
the country afterward.
We traced his calls.
He mainly calls from Ansan,
and mostly from this district.
- Daekyung?
- That's right.
There are a few colleges there,
so there's tons of cheap rooms
and apartments,
and thousands of old houses.
What a hassle...
Which means...
he hid here after stabbing Jang.
Bastard.
Where are your manners?
Jang?
Is he your friend, you jerk?
You damn gangster.
How are you police any different?
Bastard!
Don't you dare!
- Damn bastards!
- Let go of me!
You wanna die?
Come here.
Buddy.
If we don't catch him,
we're all screwed,
don't you know that?
If we're on the same boat,
we gotta see this through
no matter what.
Let's just do it!
- You all got the photo?
- Yes, boss!
You have one mission.
Find this bastard at all costs!
Yes, sir!
Keep a low profile,
and if you see anyone
who resembles him,
call these guys at once.
Five men to a team,
and each team leader reports in
every 8 hours, 3 times a day.
Centering around
Daekyung district,
scour your designated area
and expand your search.
Cheap bachelor pads,
motels and inns.
I've never seen him before.
Short-term rentals, leased places,
and long-stay apartments.
Check these places without fail!
In the afternoon, check downtown.
Scour the markets, terminals
and other public areas.
Check the bars, arcades,
internet cafés,
karaoke bars
and other shops at night.
Got that?
Yes, sir!
Go to the Joongho district!
That place closed down!
Yes, I'm outside. Hurry up.
Okay.
When's the bus coming?
Hey, kiddo. Come over here.
Take this.
- I'm fine.
- Take it!
Okay...
Thank you.
What about you?
Study hard.
Hey, Jang Dong-su!
This is no time to have
a group dinner!
You gotta feed them
when you give them work.
Oh-sung will be here soon.
Where's yours?
What the...?
- You there!
- Yes?
Don't take random things
from strangers!
He's a gangster!
You look more like a gangster
than him.
What?
Don't laugh.
- Good bye!
- Be careful!
Thank you, sir.
- Our dicks may be many!
- But we have one heart!
- Until end of time!
- We are one!
Thank you, boss!
My dick's all tingly,
seeing you all.
Screw my life.
I can't believe
I'm in league with you all.
Stick to your own damn job.
We risk our necks for this.
You salarymen don't.
You're still a damn gangster.
Have a damn drink on me.
Just say thank you
when we give you good booze.
I brought in this liquor,
so drink freely.
You've got a finger in the pie
in every type of business.
You want in?
Should I?
You should.
You look the part.
You'll go far in the gang!
Shut your face and have a drink.
Fine, pour me one.
No.
I didn't turn away.
There's grease in my glass...
Dal-ho! Sing us a song,
this mood sucks.
Dude, I used to be
a boy band trainee.
I'll sing a kick ass song
for you all.
One! Two!
One, two, three, four!
Hey, be quiet.
Turn that up.
The high school victim
was on her way home
when she was murdered.
Considering how young
she was at the time,
the police are ruling out
revenge or vendetta,
and point to sexual assault
or cold-blooded murder
as potential reasons...
Oh-sung.
- Get the hell up!
- Yes, boss!
Search everything near
the 32 bus route!
What did we miss?
Northern Dohwa, Western Worpo,
and 1km from the central square!
Move faster!
He's here for sure. Stay alert.
Come up from Daekyung.
We'll go down from Songgun.
I'm searching the central square!
I think I found him.
Dohwa motel district.
Gather our men.
Search the cars, too.
Witness found, Dohwa motel!
Don't just search the motels,
look into nearby bars
and karaoke places!
Excuse me, I'm a cop.
He's staying in Room 304.
What's with you all?
Tell me! Where is he?
He left just now.
Sir, I found him.
Stay alert. We have to get him!
Stay in your car
and see if he comes back.
Don't take any action.
We have to get him in here.
Just do your job, prick!
Cancel the search party.
Send just three men here.
Buddy, don't move.
Get down.
Glad to see you, bastard.
Stupid bastard.
He drives like a retard.
Hey!
Stop the car, you jerk!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Damn them!
Bastard!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to get him!
Over there!
Bastard!
Damn it...
Hey! Oh-sung!
Oh-sung, no!
Wake up!
Over there...
Damn it...
Don't forget you're a superstar.
Remember, you're a superstar.
Open your heart...
Where are you?
This bastard is mine now.
Where the hell are you?
Track his location!
He took the killer. Find him!
Fasten your seat belt.
You can't die before I kill you.
- Stop at a rest stop.
- What?
I'm starving.
This is fun.
How are we different?
That's pretty obvious,
can't you tell?
How dare you stab me,
you puny bastard?
Isn't it fun?
Playing with a man's life.
He drove down to Cheonan.
The toll gate camera caught him.
Bastard...
Do you know when it feels...
the best when you kill someone?
Shut the hell up.
Do you like minced meat?
I'm gonna chop you up nicely,
and distribute it all over.
Bastard.
It's this moment,
when life and death
is in your hand.
Give it a go.
Get on with it.
Kill me!
Do you even listen to yourself?
Did you think you'd live
after killing all those people?
That's why you should kill me.
Die quietly. If you talk,
your blood will squirt.
Sorry, buddy.
I'm still a cop.
Nice to meet you, you bastard.
Kang Kyung-ho,
you're under arrest for homicide.
Even a devil like you...
can retain an attorney,
and has the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can be...
used against you
in a court of law.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be appointed to you
with tax money, bastard.
What the hell?
Isn't it obvious?
He's a serial killer.
Sir.
What are you doing?
Go home!
Pack up!
Come here, baby.
One moment please! Make way!
Let us through! Make way!
While investigating a kidnapping
case from September,
Cheonan police obtained
key evidence that led to Kang.
He's currently being treated
for minor injuries,
and he'll be investigated
by the police
before being handed over
to the prosecutor.
Next up.
Slot arcades are becoming
a societal problem as of late,
and the prosecution traced how
these arcades are funding
violent gangs, and is in search of
Zeus gang leader Jang.
Jang operates several dozen
slot arcades,
and has made a fortune
by illegally modifying
and distributing arcade cabinets.
His current whereabouts
is unknown.
You did everything, right?
No.
You've convinced the world
that he's the killer, but what?
No evidence?
All we've got is circumstantial.
There's no concrete proof
that he killed them.
Even if I was a judge,
I wouldn't give him
the death penalty.
What's this?
It's a knife.
The knife that you killed with.
What's your life concept?
No matter how I think of it,
I can't figure you out, why?
Because you're not human.
Then what's yours?
To be a good cop? A model citizen?
You can't answer me.
Who has a life concept?
We live because we do.
I wore gloves for my first kill,
but they kept slipping
and wouldn't move like I wanted.
You gotta stab in one go!
That feeling when it goes in...
You can feel it
from the tips of your fingers.
Something like that.
And these pictures.
What is it?
The order's all wrong.
Is there proof that it's mine?
And even if I get
the death penalty,
you know I won't die.
What the...
I'll kill you! Allow me!
If you receive the death penalty
without evidence,
then that's murder.
The real devils are those who
commit crimes with kind faces.
Think about it,
as creators and enforcers of law.
Do you really have that right?
If you're innocent, then I am too.
Did you state that
you've never seen this knife?
I did.
This knife was used
to kill five victims
between July and September, 2005.
Objection, Your Honor.
The state has not provided
any concrete link
between the knife and him
during this trial.
It cannot be implied that
the knife belonged to him.
Yes, you're right.
This knife has nothing to do with
the defendant.
At least until now.
Your Honor, we'd like to request
a sole survivor
of Kang's vicious knife attack
as the state's next witness.
Witness, please take the stand.
You got balls
showing your face in front of me.
Damn, you look terrible.
We're paying tax for you to arrest
and kill those bastards.
That's what the law is.
It arrests people
and punishes them, too,
and it protects us, dammit,
that's what it is for.
Shut the hell up.
You should've let me kill him!
You're my last resort.
Let's kill him with law.
What the hell are you saying?
Turn yourself in.
Are you out of your damn mind?
Did you kill Hur Sang-do?
Yes, I did.
I've had it!
Once this goes public,
you and I are both dead.
Don't make me use this.
Surrender and become a witness.
You're the only witness.
With you on the witness stand,
I can link him to all his murders!
Let's just die together.
I swear that the evidence
that I shall give is the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help me God.
Your Honor.
The state's witness is
a wanted head of a gang,
who is accused of
several serious crimes.
There is no link between
his role as a witness,
and as a suspect of other crimes.
I agree.
Witness,
how can you verify that you
were stabbed by the defendant?
Guys like me who get
stabbed regularly
can't forget those who stab us
until they are buried.
That bastard was the one.
I had this sketch made
as soon as I got stabbed.
Your Honor, that portrait is
simply a personal drawing,
it has no substantial
or scientific merit as evidence.
Your Honor,
this is the witness'
hospital record
immediately after the attack.
The witness is a gang boss.
Getting stabbed is normal for him.
He could've been treated
for someone else's stabbing.
He's violating
the defendant's rights
and the law's authority.
Damn, that bastard talks a lot.
- Hey, Lawyer.
- Witness!
If your family had been killed
the same way,
could you talk like that?
The defendant's rights?
Why does he deserve any?
That bastard killed people
for fun.
I'm a bad guy too,
but he shouldn't be alive.
Evidence?
I'll show you.
That night, he forced me out
of my car by crashing into me.
Then he stabbed me
twice in my side,
and after some struggle,
he stabbed me in the chest.
While trying to take his knife,
I got cuts in my fingers.
If I was a normal man,
I'd be dead too.
Take his clothes off.
I stabbed his left chest.
He will have a wound there.
And check his hand.
You'll find a lot of scars.
Those who use knives
get minor cuts during stabbing,
and break their nails, too.
And lastly,
that bastard wrote this.
Analyze his handwriting,
and you'll get a match.
For reference,
Hur Sang-do was my friend.
(Hur was killed with my knife)
Hur and his lieutenant
are both dead.
I feel bad for Oh-sung,
but if Kang spills everything,
we can blame Oh-sung for it.
(Hur was killed with my knife)
Considering the defendant's
extremely violent tendencies,
willful negligence of human life,
and the pain felt by the victims,
his sentence is decided
by weighing the offenses.
Ergo, defendant Kang Kyung-ho
is sentenced to death.
(61st Police Appreciation Day)
Thank you, sir!
Salute!
The boss is coming!
Let's greet him!
Good afternoon, boss!
I got a condition.
What is it?
Put me in the same jail as him.
We played this game
with the lives of three men.
We need to finish it.
(The Gangster, The Cop, The Devil)
(DON LEE AKA MA DONG-SEOK)
(KIM MOO-YUL)
(KIM SUNG-KYU)
(Written and directed by
LEE WON-TAE)