Look at them.
Praying for a miracle
that isn't coming.
Who knows?
Maybe it's my curse to leave
one betrayal behind,
only to find a greater one
here amongst the stars.
They could've stopped this.
But none of them had the strength
to do what must be done.
But I do.
So what is it like walking
to go get coffee when you can run
4,000 miles an hour?
It's nice slowing down every once
in a while, even for the Flash.
Is Frost joining us?
No. Last night I sent her on
a two week Eat Pray Love tour
because she's still
pining over Mark Blaine.
I thought
she was mad at him all summer.
And fall.
But she still misses him,
even though I told her
he's a jerk who is
never going to change.
Let me guess, she didn't care?
Yep, she said,
"The heart wants what the heart wants."
She's always been such a romantic.
I have learned one thing
watching Frost go through all this.
For the first time since Ronnie passed,
I think I'm really ready
to get back out there.
I'm... gonna start dating again.
That's awesome.
I'm really happy for you.
Thank you. Now if I can just get
some oat milk for my coffee.
Two bullet trains on the Calvert Railway
are going to collide.
Barry, that's 50 miles
south of Keystone City.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen,
authorities are now confirming
that despite a massive explosion
caused by today's railway accident,
no lives were lost
during this horrific event.
It appears our city
has the Flash to thank once more.
That was amazing!
You got everyone to safety
in what, 20 seconds?
Twelve actually. Try your coffee.
Wow. You have seriously leveled up.
If only you could teach Frost
how to do the same.
I mean, bypassing anyone
who calls themselves "Chillblaine,"
I think would save her
a lot of heartbreak.
I mean, Frost dating anybody,
is a first for her, right?
And everybody you dated before Ronnie,
I'm guessing that was you leveling up.
You know, it's a process.
Maybe just give Frost space
to do the same.
Captain Kramer,
while supportive of your transparency...
...you have been criticized
for your decision
to disband the city's meta task force.
Some people thinking that it will
increase meta-crime across the city.
Do you care to comment?
Once I came to terms with being a meta,
it helped me realize how important it is
for everyone in Central City to receive
equal protections under the same laws.
So you felt as though the meta
task force was unfairly targeting
marginalized sections of the populace.
Yes, which is why its time has passed.
Great. Thank you, Captain Kramer.
This is Iris West-Allen
for Citizentopia.
Thank you for listening.
That was great.
It was great. Come in.
Allegra, you remember Captain Kramer?
- Hi.
Well, I have an appointment
with Chief Singh,
so, thanks.
You wanted to see me?
Yes. So the last six months
have been pretty intense.
I'll say. We have three new reporters,
an IT intern and an office manager now.
Plus, online circulation's
over two million,
and your new podcast's
frickin' brilliant.
- Thank you.
- Oh, we need faster internet.
Should we call the new landlord?
Sue Dearbon bought the building.
I think we can fix our own internet.
Roger that.
But seriously, I just
don't see how you do it all
and still find time
for an op-ed each week.
Well, I can't.
So the bullpen needs
a supervising editor.
Someone who decides
which stories we cover
and then assigns and pre-edits copy.
Which is why I am promoting you.
Wha... Iris...
Well, I've barely been staff for a year.
I'm not ready for that.
- Well, I think you are.
- You do realize you have people on staff
who are more qualified
to handle that sort of thing?
I mean, Vanya, she's got ten years
of experience under her belt.
Or that annoying Taylor,
just graduated summa cum laude
from Barnard College.
Even the old guy was a war correspondent
in Beirut.
Aariz is my age. Girl!
Look, now that we're
CC Citizen Media, I am busier
with more and more
administrative duties.
- Iris, are you sure?
- You got this.
I believe in you.
What is this?
A candlelit pizza dinner,
from our favorite place in Milan.
Oh, thank God, I was too tired to cook.
I can't imagine why.
Team Citizen's
been in overdrive these days.
Plus, Deon's still helping to stabilize
your temporal sickness
with regular treatments.
It's a lot to handle.
I told you I'm fine.
Plus, you're not exactly
an underachiever yourself, Flash.
Nice work at Calvert Railway.
Thanks.
I guess we both earned a night off.
And without kids, too.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
It's great having Bart and Nora
stop in all the time from 2049...
But if we're ever going to have a baby,
we need some alone time, Mr. Allen.
- Great.
- Yeah.
- Ray?
- In the flesh.
What, uh... What brings you
to Central City?
Oh, well, you guys said
I could always crash here
if ever I was in town,
and I'm here attending CCTC.
But my hotel is overbooked,
and it's impossible to get
a conference hotel room
at the last minute.
So I figured I'd take you up
on your very kind offer.
- Oh, that makes sense.
- Doesn't it?
Are you guys having pizza?
Is it gluten-free?
- No, it's from Italy.
- Oh.
So, where is Nora?
Did she come with you?
No, she's saving the world
one kid at a time
and loving it.
Am... Am I interrupting?
- Never.
- No.
Really? Great!
So is this a sofa bed
or like a sheets-and-blankets-on-top
sort of thing?
There is a guest bedroom
at the top of the stairs.
Aw! You guys are the best.
- I'll get the rest of my bags later.
- Okay.
- I thought he could shrink things.
- Yeah.
Trucks at loading dock.
Copy that. Transport team's here.
What the hell?
In three seconds,
the two on the outside
will draw their weapons and advance,
while the other two
hold their positions.
Jack, you're up.
I could have melted your faces instead.
Guess you drew a lucky hand.
Ooh, their minds
are full of fear, Ten.
Show them who has the winning hand.
- Jackpot.
- Oh, crap.
My King, you know the drill.
I guess he folded.
- Well, that's no fun.
- Either way,
that was damn fine work, My Queen.
Well, it's easy when you can see
each card before it's dealt.
My Queen.
- Now what?
- We raise the stakes.
There you go, Iris.
Uh, Ray, how often do you talk to Sara
and all the other Legends?
Well, not very often.
Nate and I do have
a standing drinks night once a month,
but he's rarely
in the same century or year.
Yeah, that may be
why I haven't heard from him lately.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Kind of.
Yeah, it was really hard
leaving the Legends,
but since then, Nora and I
have been more connected than ever.
And, you know,
I've been able to get back
to my other true love, pure research.
Plus, my life's more balanced now.
It's not just "I'm the Atom,
and science takes a backseat,"
you know so, yeah, to, uh...
To second acts.
I'll get it.
Is this year's Legacy Honoree
in the house?
Hey, Chester. Yeah, come on in.
Chester, Ray. Ray, Chester.
Ah, so you're the new team tech genius.
Nice to meet you, Chester.
Likewise.
I've been a big fan of yours ever since
reading your papers on quantum qubits.
So you're pretty stoked
about the con this year, huh?
Oh, are you kidding me?
Ever since I found out you were
going to be this year's Legacy Honoree,
I kind of took the liberty of signing up
to be a CCTC volunteer.
I'm going to be your liaison
for the entire event, if that's cool.
Like, if you're all right.
Sounds great.
Cool, because I already have your whole
itinerary planned to sweet perfection.
So, um, I'm late for work.
So, Ray, Chester, I'll pop by
the convention center later.
- Don't you dare...
- See ya, I gotta go.
Aw, he forgot his breakfast.
That's a bracelet. You know what?
I have to go, too... deadlines.
You got the list of questions
for the interview later, right?
Sure do. See you at 4:00.
Heard some paroled ex-cons
went shopping without their wallets.
OG meta-criminals, actually.
Jack, Ten, King and the Queen, they
call themselves the Royal Flush Gang.
They were Central City's
very first meta-threat.
You worked that case, too?
Actually, no. The first time
they pulled a job, I was...
...kind of under the weather.
It's weird. Their MO is stealing cash
from casinos, not microchips.
Well, at least no one was killed...
this time.
Everything okay, Captain?
This is the kind of case the meta
task force would have been assigned to.
Uh, so your mimic powers,
how exactly do they work?
They only activate in times of stress,
when my adrenaline spikes,
and the effects are temporary.
That's good.
Yeah.
Allen, does me being a meta
make working for me more difficult?
No, ma'am. It's already
tough enough as it is.
I'll let you know
as soon as I find something.
Okay.
So I've gone over everyone's ideas
and they're great.
But what I'd like to do is start with
last night's break-in at Mercury Labs.
It's not news, not in this city.
It's a high-tech theft
at a huge R&D corporation...
Which happens all the time in this town.
- Was anyone killed?
- No.
- Was the Flash involved?
- No. He isn't.
- Tragedy sells papers, folks. Sorry.
- But... That's not the point.
We should look into the rumors of
embezzlement inside the mayor's office.
Scooping a major scandal
before our competition...
Will make Iris happy.
Get in touch with someone
at the mayor's office.
I got 1,000 words to finish on
the Shark's new GM for Iris, too...
Wait. What 1,000 words?
Well, I know the mayor's
executive assistant.
I need someone on this Mercury break-in.
Vanya, I really need you
to run with this tech heist.
I'm going to follow up
on the Calvert collision this morning.
My source in the county planner's office
says it's going to cost several million
to repair the damage.
Talk about a budget crisis.
Plus, that is what Iris would want.
Well, hold on. Wait, guys... seriously?
We found this
at the train collision site.
I thought Kramer had you working
on the Mercury heist instead.
Yeah, I am.
You are,
but you think that it's related
to the Calvert train collision?
I will know in a minute.
While working evidence
from the Mercury Labs heist,
I found charred marks
on the guards' weapons.
Marks exactly like those.
Yeah, I was right.
Heat signature is the same as the burn
marks on the weapons at Mercury Labs.
Laser burns delivered
with pinpoint precision.
Jack's trademark.
Okay. Okay.
Even if it is the Royal Flush Gang
behind all of this, why?
Why would they go through
all the trouble
of causing a massive railway collision
when they haven't even
stolen anything yet?
I asked myself that, too.
Then I found out
what was being carried in this case.
A bleeding-edge, beryllium core,
which is a highly unstable power source.
And that's what caused
the trains to explode.
No, beryllium-based detonation
would have leveled
a surrounding ten-mile radius.
The core wasn't in the case
when the trains collided.
Which means the real question
is why is the Royal Flush Gang
changing their MO
to become tech thieves?
Korber, what's going on?
Iron Heights just lost power
for three seconds,
during which every cell door
unlocked and opened.
Now they've got a thousand inmates
roaming the facility.
Barry, if they get out...
Yeah, I know.
Barry, what happened?
I got the inmates back in their cells
before anyone got hurt.
But we've got a bigger problem.
Looks like the Royal Flush Gang
just leveled up, too.
Well, I am impressed.
A schedule timed to the minute,
including a coffee stop to recharge.
Best. Handler. Ever.
Oh, you're getting a whole lot more
than java at Jitters, my friend.
How about a dozen CCTC
entrepreneurial hopefuls, each with
their own game-changing startup idea,
ready to pitch in three minutes or less
to Ray Palmer, business behemoth,
scientific genius.
Am I right?
Okay, okay.
Come on. Let's go
make some dreams come true.
- Chester.
- Yeah.
What made you think that...
Oh, I just know how much
you used start-up investments
to expand Palmer Tech.
You just got, like, a nose for science.
But I also know you've been out
of the game for a little while,
so I figured I'd help
jumpstart the magic.
- Okay.
- And don't worry about Tech Con,
because your interview with Iris
isn't for another 90 minutes.
So we got time.
Hey, I got your back, man.
Thank you.
But I'm not worried about my schedule.
Oh, right, right.
You need a cronut first, obviously.
- Excuse me, can we...
- Chester.
Chester...
I don't want to start
another tech business.
It's like I told Barry and Iris,
the only thing I want
to pursue these days is a balanced life.
That's why I haven't worn
the Atom suit in ages.
Uh-huh. But you're...
You're a Legend.
Was a Legend.
Now I suppose that's what Team Flash
is for.
Look, I know how
that might sound for the Atom,
but Ray Palmer's priorities are his wife
and working in his own lab.
I hope that you can understand that.
Yeah. No, no, I get it.
And, I am, uh... I am so sorry.
- It's okay. It's okay...
- Everyone.
Today's pitch sessions
are officially canceled.
- What?
- No, that's not fair.
Guy, guys, guys,
we are impinging on a great man's time.
So get... Go on, go on. Come on.
Sorry, everyone.
I still believe in you.
I like your sweater.
And I will, um, leave you
to get your privacy on,
and again I am...
I'm so sorry.
Chester, I...
Thank you so much for coming.
It's so exciting to have you here.
When I founded this conference
five years ago, I never would have
dreamed we'd get coverage like this.
- Well, this is pretty impressive.
- Yeah.
Hey, your press pass
gets you into our after parties.
Are you a fan of filk music,
by any chance?
Boss. Excuse me.
Can we talk?
We'll gab later.
- Hey.
- So I totally blew it at the office.
I told you I wasn't ready.
You got resistance from the staff.
They barely listened to me.
I'm pretty sure they think I don't have
enough experience, which I don't.
And they think that my suggestions
for which stories to cover are wrong.
Yeah, I figured that might happen.
Then why put me in charge?
Because you can handle it.
And dealing with this is a part
of growing into your new position.
Well, I am not growing.
I'm crashing and burning.
Iris, I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
How do you know?
Because you're exactly what
CCC Media needs.
You have a point of view
that's entirely your own.
And you know the city better than anyone
in that room, you grew up here.
You not only survived Iron Heights,
you came out on the other side a hero.
I could melt Taylor's face.
You went from juvenile delinquent
to voice of the people.
And I'm talking about your writing,
not your meta-powers.
Your articles speak to people
because you're one of them.
That's your point of view.
It's also how CCC Media
speaks to the city
and why people respond so strongly.
Okay, but being a journalist
and being in charge are way different.
Look, I know that it's scary,
but think how you leveled up as a meta.
I'm sure that was scary, too.
Try terrifying, but somehow I knew
I could handle an upgrade.
Okay, then do that at the office, too.
Your point of view
is perfect for this company.
You've already learned how to own it.
Now go sell it.
Go.
Sell it.
Turns out the Royal Flush Gang
kidnapped a prisoner named
Jared Haywood.
Had any luck tracking them down?
Not yet.
What about the Mercury Labs chip?
Chester's still trying to figure out
why the Royal Flush Gang would need it.
- Okay.
- Not anymore.
Turns out that chip is so cutting edge,
it has, like, a thousand
different applications,
so, sorry, I blew it.
It just seems to be my thing today.
Hey.
What's going on, Chester?
I'm sensing a whole lot of sadness.
Yeah. Aren't you supposed
to still be with Ray?
I have resigned as Ray's liaison.
Turns out, I messed that up, too.
I'm like, dead to him.
Oh, my God, Cecile. I am so sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
No, no, it's okay. Hey,
you gotta go easy on yourself.
How?
The day I'm having, I feel like
I might as well just
gamble my per diem away
at the craps table with Grandma Runk.
And Tech Con's paying
in cryptocurrency this year,
which barely feels like real money,
even though it totally is.
What if the Royal Flush Gang
didn't change their MO?
Chester, can we find out
if any Star City casinos
also take cryptocurrency?
Yeah.
Hot damn! Turns out they all do.
Guess they'll happily take your money
however they can.
And check this out.
These casinos have over 50 mil
in their digital coffers.
So what exactly would
the Royal Flush Gang need
to pull off a heist like this?
A computer with a next-level microchip,
massive power source to run it...
and an expert in cyber-espionage
to execute the hack.
They didn't change their MO.
They just leveled up.
Okay, how do we stop them?
The second the hack starts,
I can trace it and ping the location.
And I'll be ready.
So, it's all done?
Transfer completed.
Who wants to be a millionaire?
I do.
Exactly.
And since more people means
smaller shares for us.
Someone's out of chips.
What the hell, man?
We've planned this for years
and now you're gonna kill me?
Of course not.
Jack is.
I'm all in.
It's over, people.
Haywood's back in Iron Heights.
Who wants to go next?
Oh, usually I know when to fold 'em.
You know, 50 million, it's a lot
to leave on the virtual table.
And since my Queen is a psychic,
who knows everything
you're going to do before you do it,
go ahead, Flash. We call.
Four to one. I like these odds.
Go ahead, Flashy.
Pick a card. Any card.
Execute a full house maneuver,
all of you. Now.
Hey, bud.
What? This is impossible.
I read your mind.
I saw what you were planning
and then I trumped your hand
by going all in. How did you...
You can read minds?
I can think at super speed.
Your thoughts, after I read them,
you reshuffled the deck!
I guess the house doesn't always win.
I am so sorry, folks.
I know today did not go as planned.
But the rocky road of science
will not stop me
from bringing you
the best Tech Con coverage ever.
Hey Chester, you left before
I could thank you for help...
Yo, yo, yo it's my fellow science geek,
CSI Barry Allen!
- Hi.
- Good to see you, man. Good to see you.
- So, ixnay on the ashFlay talk...
- Yeah.
Thanks for coming
to my livestream, dude.
- Sure.
- And this is his first Tech Con ever.
- Somehow that's true.
- Yeah. Yeah, so...
- Barr.
- Yeah.
How awesome is all this?
It's pretty awesome. Have you seen
the Magnus Labs' Saturn simulation?
Dude. I was in it.
You can get in it?
Hey, Ray! There's Legacy Honoree,
Ray Palmer.
Come say hi.
You've seen some of these displays?
Yeah, I mean, the imagination
on display is just stellar.
- Hey, Chester...
- Welcome to my livestream, Mr. Palmer.
But hey, it's been a great
first day of webcasting.
So, how about we take a break?
- Good, 'cause then we can talk about...
- See you in ten, party people.
- Hold this please.
- Okay.
...talk about what happened earlier.
Well, he's not avoiding me.
Chester surprised me earlier
with a pitch fest
to mentor aspiring scientists and...
the intention of forming a startup
with one of them.
That sounds great.
And it would have been before, but...
I've grown a lot the last few months.
So, what? You don't miss any of this?
- I'm still a scientist, Barry.
- Yeah.
But, you know, if I start another
big tech company,
next thing I know...
I get lost in all this again.
This is all so intoxicating
and... I don't want
to fall back into the trap.
I get that, but...
I'm not the same that I was,
the first time I put on the cowl either.
I'm faster, more confident,
more at ease with myself.
Yeah. You've grown, too.
Yeah. One of the ways that's happened
is learning to take time out
to help Team Flash grow, too.
I've learned just as much from them
as they've learned from me.
It's like being a CSI.
Every day I work with
all my fellow officers
in all departments.
I mean... I do miss
scientific collaboration.
It's like I told Chester,
I'm not a Legend anymore.
And I don't have the C.C.P.D.
So what?
You're Ray Palmer, Legacy Honoree.
If you want something
that doesn't exist, invent it.
This copy is damn well-written.
What exactly are you looking for?
If you even know.
Look, these stories aren't bad.
They're well sourced. Thorough.
But, CCC Media is about more
than just providing facts.
It's the voice of the people,
which means
it needs to have something to say.
It's literally the opposite
of objective journalism.
How about we leave
the editorializing to Iris?
Okay, it's right there in the name.
Central City Citizen.
Yeah, you guys landed
some pretty major interviews,
but every person's voice
in this city deserves to be heard.
Not just the most famous
or high-profile ones.
So what, we're not even supposed to talk
to the DA or the mayor anymore?
Yes, talk to them.
But then go talk to the janitor
who cleans the mayor's office
or a mom working two jobs
just to pay her bills.
Because corruption in this city,
it affects them more than anyone.
Don't you guys see?
When we're at our best,
our readers see themselves
reflected in our stories.
So, try again.
But this time...
remember who you're writing for.
You've already
accomplished so much...
...and now you're a CCTC Legacy Honoree.
What's next for you? Retirement?
Uh...
Well, honestly I...
I'm not sure.
That question's come up
for me a lot today.
And, you know, I have been doing
a ton of research lately,
but, I also don't want to repeat
my previous achievements.
So, I guess I'm having
conflicting thoughts about it.
It's a tough decision.
So, you know what?
Maybe we should all find out together...
next year.
Okay, and on that note,
let's thank Ray Palmer
for joining us today.
You all should run.
While you still can.
Everybody go.
Go!
Flash,
don't make this difficult.
Show yourself.
I'm not gonna let you hurt anyone.
Why don't you just tell me
what it is you want?
Of course.
I came a long way to find you, Flash.
And now that I have,
I'm going to kill you.
Whoever you are,
if you're looking for a fight,
you found one.
Oh, snap!
Time for Flash to do what he does best
and kick some butt.
You're nothing like I expected.
Not that it matters.
Those who were once good
die just as easily.
- Oh, well, that's not good.
- What is that thing?
Oh, I'm picking up some
seriously advanced tech readings.
You just have that thing
in your back pocket?
No, I just picked it up
from right there.
Oh, yeah. Tech Con, right.
I think Barry's gonna need
a helping hand.
Wait. What?
Like a superhero team up with the Atom?
What changed your mind?
My friends. An old one and a new one.
But I'm still not a Legend.
Man, you're a hell of a lot more.
I was born amongst the stars, Flash.
Trapping me in a vacuum was pointless.
Now surrender...
and I promise you won't suffer.
And the suit still fits.
- Hey! You been working out?
- Yeah, thank you for noticing.
- All right, you ready?
- Yeah.
Flash! Atom! Who are you firing at?
Yeah, yeah. He's right behind you.
Oh, now I know how Diggle feels.
This guy isn't just strong.
I think he's messing with our minds.
Correct.
This isn't your fight, Atom.
Now leave while you still can.
Everyone has a weakness.
I'll keep him occupied.
You can't fool me
with a speed mirage, Flash.
My mind is too powerful.
Wait, you said I was good once.
What happened to me? You owe me that.
As you wish.
Bear witness to a coming Armageddon
that you create ten years from now.
One that destroys your own planet.
It's already happened, Flash.
That's why I, Despero, have to kill you.
It's how I save our world.
No!
- Man, whatever you did...
- Any time, Flash.
- Hey!
- Hey, you guys okay?
Yeah.
Where'd that thing go?
I don't know.
Barry, you know you're not destined
to destroy the world, right?
Yeah, I know. But the visions Despero
showed me seemed so real.
And he said "our world."
But what does that even mean?
I don't know... yet.
What if he's mind-punking you?
Like how he made you and Ray
see an illusion during your fight?
I don't think he was.
Every test I've run on Barry shows that
he's completely fine,
mentally and physically.
Well, I scanned the residual feelings
that Despero left behind
inside your mind,
and there was no doubt.
Despero was telling the truth.
He really did see those things.
Which means everyone's in danger.
No, no. There's no way that you're
the bad guy in this situation.
What we need to do right now
is find out the truth.
I have a bad feeling it's gonna find us.
Once Despero gets back
from wherever Ray sent him.
Yeah. Well, the tech inside
his belt was so complex,
I could barely recognize
the navigation system.
So, instead of sending him to a specific
location, I tried a random setting.
Who knows where he went.
- Or when he's coming back.
- Barr...
how do we beat
a ten-foot-tall red alien,
who thinks like Grodd
and punches like Fuerza?
By figuring out
what kind of alien he is.
Get that and you may have some idea
of what his weaknesses are.
- Like Kryptonians.
- And Kryptonite.
Great idea. I'll call Alex
in National City.
Yeah. So what do we do?
Well, he took our best shots
like they were nothing.
- We need to be ready.
- For what?
The fight of our lives.
Iris.
This account of Despero
fighting Flash and Atom,
it's amazing.
Is Barry okay?
Yeah, it's just Despero is like
no one we've ever faced before.
Any notes?
Just one. Publish this.
Now. People need to read it.
You saw everything and survived.
The city needs to know it can, too.
By the way, I read the revised articles
that you had Vanya, Aariz
and Taylor write.
And?
We're going straight to print
with all of them.
Whatever you did to inspire
quality work like this,
it must have gotten through.
Thank God.
But they're still not happy with me.
Mm. Welcome to management.
Are you sure you don't
need me to stick around?
Nora can handle any
supernatural emergencies while I'm gone,
and like you said, Despero
could come back any minute.
It's okay. We're on it,
and if Despero comes back again...
The Atom will embiggen, yeah?
No? All right. Keep working on that one.
Chester, what you did
back there at Jitters...
- Was a huge mistake, I know...
- Was the best gift possible.
Between that and helping Barry
again as the Atom,
I have now realized
that there's a middle ground
to this whole balance thing.
Which is why I want to return the favor.
So, what if I created
a non-profit organization
to fund young scientists
like your Jitters friends?
- That would be awesome.
- Great!
I was thinking I could call it
the Quincy P. Runk Foundation,
if that's okay?
Barry told me about your father.
Oh!
Uh... Yeah. If you ever need, like,
a consultant or anything like that.
I know who to call.
Oh, and, Barry...
There's one sure way to prove to Despero
that you'd never destroy the world.
What's that?
Just show him who you really are.
Like you do with this team
each and every day.
Barry, we got an alien signal
coming in hot.
Barry, are you sure about this?
Yeah, it's like Ray said,
the only way to convince Despero
I'm not a threat,
is to show him who I really am.
Prepare to die, Flash.
Every life ends sooner or later.
Wise words from a dead man.
Despero, I'm not going to
fight you again.
Really? I'm disappointed.
Striking down a defenseless foe?
Well, there's no pleasure in that.
So you enjoy killing?
Twist my words at your own risk!
You wanted to kill me.
I'm not running anywhere.
Neither am I.
In another time, on another world,
we could've fought side by side,
you and I.
There's great strength in you, Flash.
But I've seen your future.
The lives you take,
the betrayals you revel in.
You're the most dangerous kind of killer
because you hide in the body of a hero.
I'm not a killer.
I'm not whatever you think I am.
I can prove it.
If you let me show you the truth.
Or are you gonna take an innocent life
just to prove you're right?
You're either very stupid or very brave.
I can't decide which.
Find out. Scan my mind.
See for yourself, then decide.
I see no deception in your mind.
But I do see truth... and honor.
Flash, you're asking me
to risk allowing the future
I've already witnessed, to unfold.
I'm sorry.
There's too many lives at stake.
Don't you see? This is why I came back.
This is the purpose
that I swore to uphold.
What if you're wrong about me?
I've spent my entire life
protecting this world.
All I'm asking for is a chance to prove
I'd never turn my back on it.
Why should I believe you?
Because my name is Barry Allen.
And I have nothing to hide.
Your boldness impresses me, Flash.
And has earned you a stay of execution.
You now have seven Earth days to prove
that you won't become the monster
I've already witnessed in the future.
If you can't convince me in that time
or if I find any trace
of a darker nature,
I will end your existence.