My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S. T.A.R. Labs
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
The Quark Sphere, filled with
Barry's unique genetic marker,
and programmed to track his specific DNA
using the electrical current
of the Speed Force.
Once we track Barry
and we pull him out,
the Quark Sphere will trick
the Speed Force
into thinking he's still there.
What's happening?
We're moving so quickly
that everyone else is still.
- Flash?
- Flash.
I'm your father's doppelganger.
- Jesse, you're a speedster.
- Yeah. It's pretty cool, right?
- Everything okay with Jesse?
- Yes.
I just spent the summer
assembling a support staff for her,
but then Jesse goes
and kicks me off the team.
They took a vote, I'm out.
I don't even have
a home to return to now.
- Oh, Barry. What...
- Iris.
- I'm...
- You're moving with me, okay.
- What?
- You're moving as fast as I am,
like in the courtroom.
Why? Didn't you...
- I can't. I can't.
- What's wrong? What?
I can't save us this time.
Ready when you are, Barry.
- I'm ready.
- Are you serious?
Come on, Cisco, just one more.
"She said, two hours ago."
Look, you know he's not gonna stop
until he makes it through.
Come on. You know how Barry gets.
- One more.
- Thank you.
All right. Here we go.
Three, two, one. Now!
- Damn it! One more.
- Iris.
Uh, Barry. Look, why don't we take five?
No. Not until I get this. All right?
Come on.
- Listen, Miyagi.
- What?
I've been here all day
opening breaches, all right?
So unless you wanna
rub your hands together
and do some magic shoulder pop...
- I'm not rubbing your shoulder.
- That's what I thought. I'm taking five.
- Hey, come on.
- I'm taking five!
I don't understand
why I can't get this.
Well, probably because
you've been up all night.
But that shouldn't matter.
Look, Barry.
A breach closes in three picoseconds.
DeVoe's could shut even faster.
Look, I'm just saying that this
might not even be
the best plan to catch him anyway.
It's a plan, you know.
It's the only one we have, right now.
And what if he uses his force field
against you?
You don't know how to get out of it yet.
I don't know, Iris, but, I mean,
we need something.
We have no leads
on the next three bus metas.
No way to track DeVoe.
No way to stop him.
I mean, he can't be this smart.
I'm sorry, but, I mean,
we've been at this for months,
and we have nothing.
I mean, maybe that's the problem.
You know,
sometimes you have to take a breather
and let the answer come to you.
Do something else for a bit.
Like what?
Like date night, for starters?
You know,
we haven't had any quality time,
just you and me, since our honeymoon.
Which was severely cut short.
- I know we're the Flash, but...
- We're also Barry and Iris.
No, you're right.
All right. I'm gonna make
a reservation, tonight.
Someplace very romantic.
Mmm.
Sounds perfect.
How is it we live together,
work together,
sleep in the same bed together,
but it still feels like
we don't spend any real time
as husband and wife?
Allen. West-Allen.
Cortex, now!
I have no idea.
Let's go.
What is this?
This is a signature field
mapping every time
DeVoe's gone in and out of his lair
in a pocket dimension.
- All of these?
- All of them.
So, how did you do this?
I didn't do it, actually. Ramon did.
But all I did was just come up with
a really complex and eloquent algorithm
to track the warping signatures...
Don't do that, all right? Don't do that.
Don't be modest, all right?
It's unbecoming.
- You're unbecoming.
- You wish I was unbecoming.
Do you know that these are DeVoe?
These are DeVoe, all right?
This is when Marlize
grabbed him from Izzy at Lawrence Hills.
This is when he showed up
at Iron Heights Prison...
This is DeVoe's house.
And this is the alleyway
in the city center
where he abducted you.
- How long has this been going on?
- Wait for it.
- The past three years.
- Three years?
DeVoe orchestrated everything
to get the people he wanted on the bus.
He's been planning this a long time.
We've got a planner, just like Thawne.
Just like Thawne.
So, how do we use this?
All we can do right now
is just wait for the next marker
to appear.
Try to get the jump on him.
That, and keep an eye on Ralph,
using the old buddy system.
Has anyone seen Ralph today?
No, he's downstairs moving in.
He's very nervous.
- I don't know why.
- I don't know why either.
He's a superhero.
People with powers
are ready for anything.
God! Son of a breach!
- Sorry.
- Jesse?
Just came in through the breach room.
Hey, Jesse. Welcome back.
What are you doing here?
Wally's not here.
Uh, you know an apology cube
usually works better
when there's an actual apology on it?
You get the sentiment.
What's this?
That is a mental activity dampener.
It's for DA Cecile Horton.
It keeps her from hearing
other people's thoughts.
Kinda clunky.
That's what she said.
Literally, that's what she said.
The second version is more streamlined.
- And what's all this?
- Those are thoughts.
Musings how to stop DeVoe.
Wow. He's really in your head, isn't he?
Yeah. A lot of people are nowadays.
Thanks to you.
Look, I thought you wanted me
to come here
so we could talk about this.
No, I want you to stop
bringing up your mother.
I will, once you deal with her death.
- I have.
- No, you haven't.
Yes, I have. She died!
Years ago, she died.
There's nothing I could do to save her.
End of story. Life goes on.
Yeah, for everyone but you.
Look, Dad, when Mom died,
you didn't talk about it.
- There's nothing...
- Ever.
And you've been upset
ever since.
You've been miserable.
You make everyone around you miserable.
I mean, why do you think
I asked you to leave my team?
Your team is a bunch of idiots.
- Okay.
- No offense.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
I came here to stop DeVoe.
No, you stayed because of DeVoe.
A distinction without a difference.
Dad, there's always going to be
some bad guy to stop,
or algorithm to write,
- Yeah.
- or problem to solve.
Yeah. That's my point exactly.
Look...
I didn't want to talk about her death,
but I did.
And it helped a lot.
Trust me. You're never
going to be able to move on
with your life
until you talk about this.
Jesse! I can't! I...
Look, Jesse.
Your mother...
You'll never understand.
Yeah. I guess I won't.
What?
Get down!
- You all right, Jonesy?
- I'll live.
Here, put pressure on it.
Help's on the way.
Who the hell are these guys?
They came out of nowhere.
I don't know. But they want
whatever is in that container.
Where is that?
One of the hangars out at Wade airfield.
My Dad said
CCPD was escorting A.R.G.U.S. there
this morning for something.
- He's there, Barry.
- Yeah. We gotta go.
- We'll meet you there?
- Cool.
I'll come, too.
I could use the distraction.
Come on, Flash.
Guys, seven officers
and A.R.G.U.S. agents down.
They just blew open
an A.R.G.U.S. transport container.
West side of the hangar,
one armed assailant inside.
Got it.
Come on.
It's ready.
Stay down! Hands, head!
Move, move!
Just you and us now.
Nice work, everyone.
It's over.
For all of Central City.
No.
Barry?
We're too late.
- That's a nuclear bomb.
- I know.
And its core
has already gone critical.
I know.
The second we slow down, it's over.
I know. That's not helping.
Well, how long do you think we have?
We just have to keep moving
until we figure out a way to stop it.
Okay, we could run it to the Badlands.
No. If we run that long,
it will speed up the reaction.
We won't make it outside the city
before it explodes.
But we can't run everyone
outside the city.
I know.
We're talking
hundreds of thousands of people.
Even if there were
more than just the two of us,
there's not enough time.
Wait, that's it. Jay Garrick.
- What about him?
- He might know what to do.
Go to Earth-3, get him,
bring him back here as fast as you can.
- Okay?
- Okay.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
I need you right now, man.
Hey.
Whoa. What is going on?
You're moving with me at super-speed.
What? Is this what it looks like
when you run?
More or less.
I have to say, it's a little uneventful.
Hey. Come with me.
I'm guessing
this is our Ark of the Covenant.
Something like that, yeah.
Whoa.
Yeah, that will definitely
melt your face.
That looks like
an experimental fission engine,
deuterium isotopes.
That would make this
an inertial confinement cage
to stop the radiation.
But with enough pressure,
the isotopes inside, they split,
they produce heat, they produce light.
Starts out blue, turns yellow,
turns purple and then it's game over.
Just please tell me
there's a way we can undo it.
I think we are way past that point.
- We have to do something.
- I...
What if...
what if I breach it to a dead Earth?
- Like I did with Fallout.
- Of course. Yeah.
That's a great idea.
All right. Do it.
What's wrong?
I think I might be all breached out.
I don't know. I think I breached
one too many times today.
No, that's not it. The breach is
a folding of space-time, right?
So when we're moving this fast...
When we're moving this fast,
when we're moving in Flashtime,
then we don't have the time necessary
for a breach to form.
- Exactly.
- Then that means I can't...
That means I can't...
Hey, hey. What's wrong?
I don't know.
You're not a speedster.
Your body can't handle
moving this fast very long.
I gotta let go, all right? Come here.
All right.
Wait. Ask Harry. He'll know.
I hope so.
- Wells...
- How...
- Allen. Why are you touching me? The...
- Hey.
Listen.
Am I in... Am I in...
- Yes, you're in Flashtime. Yes.
- "Flashtime"?
- What is Flashtime?
- Cisco just came up with it.
Wait. You did this with Ramon
before you did this with me?
- Hey, hey, we don't have time!
- Listen, the alarm...
Yes, the alarm that we left for
was an A.R.G.U.S. transport,
it had a fission engine in it.
And it exploded?
That's why I'm in this Flashtime...
Wait. Jesse. Where is Jesse?
No, she's fine. She left. She went to...
Okay, Allen. That's great.
Because if this city is gonna explode,
you need to send her
as far away from here as possible.
Listen. Listen. She went to Earth-3
to get Jay Garrick.
- She's coming back?
- Yes. We need his help.
- Allen, no, no, no. You cannot let her...
- Right now, I need your help, okay?
- How do I stop the reaction?
- You can't stop it, this.
What do you mean? Then what do I do?
You have to send it away from here.
- I can't. We tried.
- Cisco...
- Open... open a...
- Cisco can't open a breach. He can't.
- Because there's no time.
- Exactly.
- But you can.
- What do you mean?
- Allen, you can.
- No, I can't.
- Listen to me. Allen, listen to me!
- What are you talking about?
Space-time breaches
and the portal to the Speed Force
operate under different physics.
You open a portal to the Speed Force,
you send it there.
What will it do to the Speed Force?
- What is... Why am I weak?
- Wells. I know. Wells...
- It's the speed.
- Hey. Listen to me.
- Will an explosion that... I know.
- The speed's affecting...
Will an explosion that big
affect the Speed Force?
I don't think so.
What? What do you mean,
you don't think so?
- Wells, hey...
- What the heck?
Get her out of here. Allen. Allen...
How'd you do that?
Um, I'm not sure.
I've been able to do it ever since
I came out of the Speed Force.
That's a hell of a new trick.
- Look, right now...
- I know.
Jesse showed me the nuke.
We're in trouble, kid.
Well, I don't know. Wells has an idea
that he thinks might work.
Yeah, what is it?
We send the bomb into the Speed Force.
Let it detonate in there.
- Like hell, you will.
- What do you mean? Why not?
Because, Flash, if you do that,
we may lose the Speed Force forever.
What do you mean,
we might lose the Speed Force?
An explosion of that size
could destroy it completely.
If that were to happen,
every speedster across space and time
would lose access
to their speed instantly.
Every speedster?
Even if it got rid of Thawne
and every other evil speedster
in the multi-verse, you cannot do this.
I won't let you.
Well, I'm sorry, Jay.
If this is the only way to save
everyone in the city, I have to.
Barry, listen to me.
Harry didn't know anything
about the Speed Force, okay?
None of us really do
and this isn't just about speed.
You're talking about destroying
an essential element
of the multi-verse.
Nobody knows
what the consequences will be.
You were trapped in there
longer than I was.
If anyone can understand...
Then what, Jay?
What's your idea?
Okay, look. I mean,
did my dad have any other ideas?
No, but we couldn't talk
for very long.
Jay, I'm sorry. I just...
No. That's all right, kid. I get it.
All right. Back to basics.
In nuclear fission,
enormous energy is created
by a chain reaction of atoms
splitting and releasing neutrons.
It's nearly impossible
to reverse this process.
But theoretically,
you could restore stability.
How?
One way is to offset the loss
of mass by nuclear fusion.
Great.
You have some sort of machine
lying around here
that can generate that kind of energy?
- No, we don't.
- But the other way,
considering our predicament,
seems more promising.
Which is what?
Cooling it down.
We need to hurry.
Hey.
I see all these frozen people
around me, Flash,
and this time it's not my fault.
We need your help.
Three of you, now. What's going on?
- The cargo in this container...
- It's a nuclear bomb.
Yeah, and it went kaboom.
- Dandy.
- Come here.
It's toasty in here.
We need you to cool it down.
You want me to cool down
a nuclear reaction
that's already gone critical?
- You're serious?
- Quickly, please, Miss Frost.
All right. Let's give it a whirl.
Didn't go quite how I expected.
Try... try again.
No, no.
So that's what heat feels like.
You're burning up. Come on.
All right. It's okay. All right.
I have to let you go. All right?
Barry...
Don't let Caity die.
Okay.
Now what?
Guess we have to find
that fusion machine after all.
- Wait a second.
- What?
What if we're the machine?
How so?
Well, you said that we could
offset the energy of the bomb
with the energy from nuclear fusion.
Theoretically.
Right, and the reaction
that container is giving off,
I don't know,
three million tons of energy?
Give or take.
So, three megatons of energy,
that's three billion joules.
Each lightning bolt gives off
roughly one billion joules, so...
So if we all throw a lightning bolt
at the same time...
It could be enough.
That's enough.
That will work. Let's do it.
Jay! Hey.
Hey.
I'm not used to going this long.
- Hey, hey. It's okay. It's all right.
- Damn legs.
Don't work like they once did.
It's okay.
I'm not gonna be able
to finish this one, Flash.
- I'm sorry.
- Just rest.
I'm so sorry.
Barry, the two of us can't produce
enough lightning power
to offset the energy from that bomb.
I mean, even if we had full speed,
which we don't... At least, I don't.
We have to send it into the Speed Force.
You heard what Jay said.
And Harry said it would be fine.
No, he said he thinks it would be fine.
Barry, my dad never thinks anything,
he knows.
Jay was right. We can't do it.
Damn it!
Okay, what if... I don't know,
what if we run back in time
and stop this bomb from ever going off?
No, Jesse. We can't do that.
Yeah, well,
it's kind of our only option.
It's not an option.
Even if it saves the city
and everyone in it?
It's not saving them, okay?
The second you alter the timeline,
everything changes,
especially the people you love.
Trust me. I learned that the hard way.
Well, maybe a new version of my dad
isn't the worst thing in the world.
Look, Jesse,
whatever problems you two have,
they're not gonna get solved
by forcing him
to do something he doesn't want to.
He has to make that decision.
Oh, God.
The reaction's combustion's
reached its final phase.
I think we're slowing down.
So everything else is speeding up.
Barry, I don't have any more ideas.
Me either.
I don't know how much longer I can run.
You have to get out of here.
Use the speed you have left
to get back to Earth-2.
- Your dad wanted you to leave.
- Yeah, I heard.
So you'd be safe, Jesse.
He loves you, all right?
More than anything.
Go.
- No, I can't just...
- Go.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could tell you this
while you could still hear me.
I know how happy Mom made you,
and how sad you are now that she's gone.
But I just... I don't know why
you won't talk about it.
I don't know, maybe you don't need to.
I just want you to be happy again.
That's all I've ever wanted.
And I don't know
the PSI...
Come on, come on, come on.
No, this won't work. Damn!
Oh, God,
I think it's happening.
- Oh, Barry. What...
- Iris.
- I'm...
- You're moving as fast as I am,
like in the courtroom.
What? Why, didn't you...
- I can't.
- Oh, my God. What?
I can't.
I can't save us this time.
What do you mean you can't save us?
- There's a bomb.
- What?
A nuke. It's already gone off.
I can't stop it.
Wait... but... there's got to be
something that you can do...
No, I tried. We tried everything.
We tried lightning,
we tried cooling it down,
breaching it to a dead Earth.
There's nothing that would work.
- I don't know what to do.
- Okay.
- As soon as I stop, it's gonna...
- I know. I know.
It's okay. Hey, it's okay.
I don't know how much longer
I can hold out.
- I'm so tired.
- Okay. It's okay, Barry.
Oh, my God, you're burning up.
- I've been at this for a while. For me.
- Okay.
- Hey. Look at me. Look at me.
- I'm sorry.
No, don't be sorry.
Look at me, be here with me.
- I'm...
- I love you. Okay?
This isn't exactly the quality time
I was imagining,
but it's still nice.
Every moment with you, Barry,
has always been nice.
Every moment.
You're my lightning rod, Iris.
What?
You said
you tried to use lightning. How?
We tried. It didn't work.
If it was powerful enough,
it could've fused the split atoms,
it could've negated the effects
of the bomb.
But I can't do it alone.
I can't generate that kind of energy.
No, you can't, but the Speed Force can.
What?
When you went into the Speed Force,
the lightning from the storm...
One of those bolts would be
more than enough,
but I can't...
How could I draw that out?
No, listen. When we freed you,
Cisco and Caitlin,
they used a Quark Sphere
programmed with your genetic marker
to trick the Speed Force into thinking
that you were still in there.
- I just need to get that sphere.
- Yeah.
The storm will chase me.
It's like you said.
A lightning rod
to bring out the lightning.
- Come back to me.
- As fast as I can.
Here we go.
Jesse.
You're here.
I'm here.
Barry? Barry! Barry!
Flash! Flash!
Flash.
Are we dead?
- No.
- That's good.
Today, I showed you
how easy a city can fall.
Mark my words.
Nuclear power will bring
only destruction to the world.
You'll see it again.
And when you do,
you'll all remember
the name Veronica Dale,
and fully understand my actions.
Eden Corps. Eden Corps!
Eden Corps!
I feel like she's saying, "Eden Corps."
As in blasting everybody back
to the days of the Garden of Eden.
This was to air after the city fell.
Found her manifesto at her apartment.
Environmental activist
turned animal-liberator,
turned domestic terrorist.
Turned cray-cray.
How did she find out about
the A.R.G.U.S. drop, anyway?
Somebody must have tipped her off.
DeVoe.
But why would he, or she, whoever...
Why blow up the whole city?
Why kill nearly everyone here?
Maybe there is no method to the madness.
Well, this was fun, as usual.
But it's time for the old crimson comet
to head back home.
Thanks for your help, Jay.
Yeah. If it wasn't
for you two and Jesse,
it'd be a completely different story
in the news right now.
You were a big part of that, Iris.
Credit where credit's due.
My sentiments exactly.
So when you get home, you need to rest.
Your glucose levels are pretty low.
Thanks. When I get back,
I think I'll be doing nothing
but getting rest.
Meaning?
I've been at this hero game a long time.
A long, long time, and after today,
I'm thinking about trying my hand
at something new.
Like what?
For starters,
training someone to take over.
There's another Flash on your Earth?
There will be,
as soon as I'm done training her.
Her?
What, do you think we're good
with the Speed Force?
Well, if not,
we'll find out soon enough.
- Always a pleasure, Flash.
- Always.
So, you need to rest as well, mister.
No running, no Flash.
Your system's taxed.
- I'm good.
- You will be, but you're not yet.
That's right.
Anything comes up, we got it.
Iris, make sure this man rests.
I'm on it.
- Long time.
- Yes, it was.
You know,
I realized a couple of things
when I was in Flashtime.
Yeah, what's that?
Well, I'm more than fast enough
to catch DeVoe.
We just need to know
when he's coming out
of the pocket dimension sooner.
Yeah. We'll figure that out.
What's the other thing?
You were right about taking a breather.
Just a moment with you,
being grounded again.
Everything becomes more clear.
Scooch over.
Sorry about date night.
Don't be.
Power bars and sweatpants.
It's all I really need.
Uh, this is my exit.
You... oh.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Jesse, the reason
that I can't talk about...
You know what? It's okay.
You don't have to explain.
I don't... I don't?
I thought that's what you wanted.
Yeah, um...
I don't know, I thought making you
confront all the emotions
that you have with losing Mom
would help you move on
and be happy again.
But I can't decide when you're
ready to do that. Only you can.
- So, I'm sorry.
- No, don't be sorry. It's okay.
I do want you to know though,
if the time comes
and you want to talk about it,
I'm here.
Actually, if that's the case,
why don't you stick around
for a little bit longer?
- What, you wanna talk now?
- No. I'd like you to listen.
Have a seat.
I'm gonna fix this to your forehead.
What is that?
It's the streamlined version
of DA Cecile Horton's
mental activity dampener.
- Nice upgrade.
- Thank you.
But I thought this was supposed
to block out people's thoughts?
Not anymore.
Now, it allows you to hear them.
Your mother.
I don't know how... I don't...
You see, when you have a love,
had a love,
like your mother and I had,
and you lose that love...
Anyway, um,
maybe this will help you understand
why it's been so hard for me.
Because, in the vast night sky,
you are the only star I see.
Mom.
She's a miracle.
Jesse.
She's just like me.
Sweetie, come here.
Be with me.
Thank you, Allie.
- So...
- So.
Jesse seemed better when she left.
So do you.
Did you guys have a nice talk?
Well, it was actually more of
a listening session than a talk,
but we're good. Yeah. Both of us.
That's good, Harry.
- Yeah. And what about you?
- What?
Come on. I know you well enough to know
that something's on your mind.
What is it?
It's Killer Frost.
What about Killer Frost?
I don't know anything
that she says or does.
It's scary and alarming
to have this person
that you know nothing about
living inside of you.
But for the first time,
I remember what she did.
What do you remember?
Barry taking her into Flashtime,
trying to freeze the bomb...
Mmm-hmm.
And Killer Frost being worried.
Worried about what, about dying?
About me.
Interesting.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to drop that.
- It just slipped out of my hands.
- It's okay.
My first Killer Frost
and I go and ruin it.
- That's...
- Typical... typical me.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
I just get so clumsy when I'm nervous.
What are you nervous about?
I'm supposed to be meeting
some people here for the first time
and I've got the jitters.
Which
is what this place is called.
Hey, it is.
- Apt name, don't you think?
- I do.
It's funny. You know, you get nervous,
you get the jitters, you go for coffee
and the caffeine acts as a stimulant,
which makes you shaky,
which could also be known as...
- The jitters.
- Exactly.
Okay, right. I get it.
Okay. We're gonna go.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- I'm really very, very sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
Good luck with your meeting.
I hope it goes well.
Thanks.
It did.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::