- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back
from the future to help,
she changed the present,
and now our world is
more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Let's dance, crickets-y.
- How can she still come out?
- Because she's immune
to Cicada's dagger?
- The shards
weren't dampening my powers.
They were removing them.
We could make
a meta-human cure.
- What this is?
- What is that, Nora's journal?
- Have you seen
this code before?
- Yeah, right after Barry
came out of the Speed Force.
- It's a time language.
- Time language?
Where does one learn
something like that?
- I created it, actually.
- Clever girl.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- My God, Orlin.
You scared
the living daylights out of me.
- Did anyone follow you?
- Of course not.
It's been weeks since
you fought the Flash
at the hospital.
If anyone knew you were here,
you would have
found out by now.
I got you some groceries
and some Meloxicam
for your injuries.
- I don't need it.
- Good to hear.
- How's Grace?
- Nothing's changed.
She's stable.
CCPD hasn't left
and they're not leaving
any time soon.
- Well, I need to see her, Doc.
- That's not possible.
- Don't tell me
what's possible.
- You're angry.
Good.
For all the pain
your family has suffered
at the hands of those metas,
you should be.
But right now there isn't
anything you can do for Grace,
so put that anger
towards something else.
I have a friend
who feels the same way
about meta-humans
as we do,
and he wants to help you finish
what you've started.
♪ ♪
Orlin?
It's time to get back to work.
♪ ♪
- This is it.
The only thing between us
and our big score is one
reinforced concrete wall.
Don't hurt yourself, Bork.
- Can't hurt Bork.
But Bork can hurt you.
Hyah!
- [coughs]
That should do it.
[electrical buzzing]
- The hell?
Hyah!
[thumping]
[blows landing]
[grunting]
Ah!
- You're one, too.
- Ah!
Ah!
[squelching]
♪ ♪
- I don't know what's crazier,
how big this guy is
or the number
of incised wounds on his body.
- Well, and the depressed skull
fracture points to impact
with hardened surface,
but cause of death
is definitely
repeated stabbings.
- Yeah, looks like
someone was really angry.
- Look at these wounds.
Doesn't it look like they have
the same depth and diameter
as the ones on Gridlock's body?
- Yeah, and like Block's
and Raelene Sharp's.
[phone buzzing]
- Yeah.
Iris just got a tip.
Another meta-human was murdered
in her apartment, same C.O.D.
- Dad, these aren't one offs.
- No.
- Cicada's back
and he's on a killing spree.
- Okay, well, there's got to be
a lead in one of these attacks
that can help us track him.
We'll get the team on it.
- Killer Frost, seriously?
I can't take it anymore.
- Uh, Caitlin,
is everything...oh.
Alter-ego confab.
Seen enough episodes
of "Sister, Sister"
to recognize a sibling spat
when I see one.
- Oh. So,
I'm trying to help Cisco
with his meta-human cure,
but every time
I start working on it,
Killer Frost takes over
and messes with my equations.
Like this.
She changed all my
heterozygotes into asterisks.
- Oh, I thought those
were just tiny snowflakes.
- [sighs]
- So she's not on board?
- No, and I don't
exactly know why.
- Can't you just ask her?
- Oh, I've tried.
But every time we
start talking about it,
she starts singing
Barney's "I Love You" song.
- Ooh, that's cold.
- Yeah.
- What about Cisco?
Is he having any luck?
- Not yet.
He went to
the Tannhauser off-sites
so he could concentrate.
He says it's quiet there.
- Yeah.
Quiet like a tomb.
- So I think if I can isolate
the genetic marker
that bonds human DNA
to dark matter,
I can reverse engineer
the process
and unravel it
to create a cure.
- That's great.
- Yeah, except I need meta-DNA
that hasn't fully bonded
with dark matter yet.
- Of course,
because as we all know
with genetic modification we...
Why?
- Because that's the only time
when I can identify
where the marker
is in the genome.
- Okay, so you need DNA
from a meta-human
who was created recently?
- Yeah, ideally
in the last eight months,
but everyone I can think of
has been killed by Cicada.
- Right.
So where the heck do we look?
- The lone decrypted entry
from the journal
of Nora West Allen:
"The timeline is malleable."
Why that's the only one
that translated?
And why is she interested
in the timeline,
and maybe more important,
why is she hiding
this interest?
[comms ringing]
- IRIS:Sherloque,
we need you in the cortex.
- But of course.
- Kira May,
Dwayne Geist, Carl Bork.
All three metas who were killed
by Cicada last night.
- So Cicada's killed
almost as many people
in the last 12 hours as he has
in the last eight months?
- And it doesn't look like
he's slowing down anytime soon.
- Well, we need to stop him
before he hurts anyone else.
- Sherloque, do you have any
ideas on what to do about that?
- Not at the moment, but any
time I run into a road block
in an investigation,
I do what I always do.
I just pursue
a different avenue.
We'll find him.
Something will bring him to us.
Something like...
[alarm blaring]
- Satellites picking up
dark matter flare.
It's him.
- Something like that.
- Suit up.
We don't have a lot of time.
- Not without precautions.
For Killer Frost.
- She doesn't need a weapon.
Killer Frost is the weapon.
[dramatic music]
- Powers or no powers,
I will mess you up.
[grunting]
[moaning in pain]
♪ ♪
[energy buzzing]
- Ah!
- Negate this!
- [muffled screaming]
- Hold on.
Help!
- We need Caitlin.
- We need to get her
to a hospital.
Here, come with me.
- [whimpers]
- [straining]
[energy buzzing]
- Ah!
- [gasping breaths]
[slashing]
Aah!
♪ ♪
- No!
[crunching]
- Aah!
♪ ♪
[ice crackling]
- Nora.
Hey, Nora, Nora?
Okay, Nora...
Nora?
♪ ♪
[somber music]
- Well?
- Cicada caused
an axial burst fracture
in her L3, L4, and L5
vertebrae.
He also severely displaced
her fourth thoracic vertebrae.
It's not good.
- But her speed healing
is going to kick in, right?
♪ ♪
Right?
- Cicada's cut flooded
her body with dark matter.
It's affecting her powers.
Her speed healing
should kick in...
for now.
I'll keep monitoring
her progress.
♪ ♪
- Barry.
- It's okay, she'll heal.
It'll be all right.
- [wheezing breath]
- Nora?
- Oh, what happened?
- Honey, um...
- Oh, why does it hurt
to breathe?
- It's gonna hurt
for a little bit.
- Why?
I can't move my legs.
Um, why can't I move my legs?
Mom, I can't move my legs.
- Nora.
- Mom?
Mom, why can't I move my legs?
- Nora, look.
You can't move
your legs because...
Cicada broke your back.
- What?
So I'm paralyzed?
What, forever?
- No, no, not forever.
- Well, for how long then?
- We don't know.
- Mom...
- Hey, I got here
as fast as I could.
Joe's still in Tibet.
I left him a message
to get back ASAP.
- Hey, it's all right.
He should stay with Wally.
- Oh, my God.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How is she?
- It's not good.
- I'm so sorry, Barry.
- Hey, I don't care
how we do it.
We need to stop Dwyer now.
- Well, I agree.
- All right, Well,
I'm gonna call Cisco.
We should get him back here.
- No, no, no, he...
he should finish the cure
he's working on.
His time is better spent there.
Sherloque.
- Oui?
- Earn your money.
How do we track this guy?
- Well, I think the first thing
we should do
is concentrate on the victims.
Look for a connection.
Take a look here for example.
This man, Geist,
has a spider tattoo
on his neck,
generally indicating he was
caught in some form of web.
What kind of web?
A prison web, perhaps.
And Kira May...
- She was wearing clothes.
- Of course she was
wearing clothes, Giraffe.
- No, she was wearing clothes
that are two sizes too large.
- Two sizes too large.
- Recent rapid weight loss.
It's a common side effect
of solitary confinement.
- Right.
- And Carl Borg...
- And Carl Borg, this report
says he had a droopy eyelid
which is nerve paralysis,
common side effect
of consuming too much borat.
- Or as it's known
on this earth, bruno.
More commonly known
as prison wine.
- Prison wine.
All three of these meta-humans
were former criminals.
- Look at this.
It's a meta-human
arrest log from 2018.
Look at the first three names.
These were his victims.
He's killing
in the order of this list.
- This list has addresses,
employment information.
It's got license plate numbers.
This is everything
Cicada needs to find them.
Where would he even get this?
- I think there's only
one place, right?
[dramatic music]
- There's a killer still
at large in our city.
People are afraid of being
out in the streets.
I'm getting 100 phone calls
a day about this guy.
I want neighborhoods
re-canvassed.
I want evidence re-examined.
Jonesy!
Take your unit and paper
the city with Dwyer's photo.
I want this guy.
Let's go get him!
[indistinct chatter]
Allen?
- We need to talk...
in private.
- All right.
♪ ♪
What the hell is this?
- That's how Dwyer's
getting his victims.
- This is from our database
of meta-humans?
Well, it doesn't prove
he got it from CCPD.
- Doesn't it?
- He could have broken into
another precinct
or hacked into
the CCPD database.
- David Dwyer is a machinist.
He's not a hacker.
- Somebody gave this to him.
Somebody here!
- Okay, Barry,
maybe we should go ahead
and let Captain Singh
look into this on his own.
- Yeah,
I think that's a good idea.
♪ ♪
- [scoffs]
- [sighs]
Thank you, David.
CECILE: Hey, Barry.
Barry.
- [sighs]
- Barry, where are you going?
- I don't know, Cecile,
but I gotta do something
before Dwyer kills
all the people on that list.
- Hey.
What if we use it, too?
- What?
- The list.
Three years ago, Joe asked me
to help get meta-humans
transferred out of the city.
- Yeah, I remember.
You told him not to do it.
- Yeah, well, that was before
I knew what I know now.
Besides, those metas
were active prisoners.
These metas, they've already
served their time.
- Look, even if we got 'em out
of town, it wouldn't matter.
Cicada's gonna
track them down eventually.
They need new names,
new identities.
We don't have the resources
to do that.
- No, we do not.
But the Feds do.
They give
this kind of protection
to regular humans all the time.
It is about time
they start offering it
to meta-humans, too.
I am going to go call in every
favor I have ever banked
and I am going to make
this thing happen,
and in the meantime, you need
to go get them somewhere safe.
- All right.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- So, can you try
wiggling your toes?
- I can't.
- Again?
- Anything?
- I don't feel anything.
- Okay, well, Cicada's dark
matter has left your system,
so you should be
healing soon.
I mean, since my last scan,
your spinal axons
have grown five millimeters.
- That's something, right?
- It's progress.
Maybe not quite the speed
we were hoping for,
but it's something.
I'm going to go run
a few more tests.
- Hey.
Don't give up, okay?
Growth is growth.
- Normal axon growth rate
reaches five millimeters
a day in a large nerve.
With speed healing,
mine should be over 100.
- How do you know that?
- [sniffling]
I took neuro-regeneration
in my fifth grade STEM class.
- I took fractions
in fifth grade.
[both laughing]
- What if I don't heal, Mom?
What if I never get better?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Can I just be left alone
for a little bit, please?
- Yeah.
Okay.
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
- I respect your right
to protest the cure, Frosty,
but even for me,
that is excessive.
- Well, maybe Caitlin
will get the hint now.
- Uh...
- Snow and Frost are having
creative differences.
- I'll get Caitlin.
- No, I-I need you, actually.
We need to get all those metas
to a safe house
before Cicada finds them.
- Oh, and you think
they're going to listen to me?
50-50 on that.
I haven't quite lived up
to my name.
But I do know where
we should start.
[ominous music]
[electric buzzing]
- Doesn't look like
anyone's been here in months.
- Maybe the rumors about
Amunet skipping town are true.
- We're not here for Amunet.
We're here for her pet snake.
And the thing about snakes is,
they're always lurking
in some dark corner.
[wind rushing]
Hello, Norvock.
- Frost, thank God it's you.
♪ ♪
- Those are Cicada's targets,
but we need your help
rounding everyone up
so we can get them to safety.
- Because they're not going
to trust a bunch of masks?
- They will if you tell them
it's for their own good.
- Some of these guys
are bad news.
You sure they're worth saving?
- Are you?
Cicada's not going to stop
until every meta
in this city is dead.
Is that how you want to end up?
- Damn.
What did he do to you?
- We've arranged
for everyone to enter
a witness protection
program.
Federal agents will lead you
out of the city
to safety tonight.
- All right.
I'm in, but only if I'm the
first one on that transport.
- Nice of you to look out
for your fellow metas.
- I look out for me
and me alone.
- Then let's get
to rounding up.
- Yup.
- David.
- If this is about that list...
- It is,
but it's not what you think.
I need your help.
- [sighs]
With what?
- I'm having those metas
moved to federal protection,
which is where you come in.
- What do you need?
- Road blocks, tonight,
from Linsin to Webber Avenue.
I know, David, I know,
but I can't risk
any incoming traffic
during the scheduled transfer.
- I'll make it happen.
- Thank you.
[elevator dings]
[sighs]
- Officer Jones.
You all right?
- Never better.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[electrical zapping]
- I'm tired of waiting.
This Cicada,
he wants to kill us?
I say we kill him first.
- You can't.
We're your only chance.
- So you keep saying.
- Look, if you're too dumb
to recognize the truth,
then you can go,
but you're on your own.
I'm not going to watch anybody
else be broken by this maniac.
- He's telling the truth.
I saw Cicada kill Carl Bork.
- Bork's dead?
- His dagger
took away our powers.
I ran, Bork fought.
That's why I'm here
and he's not.
So, yeah, leave if you want,
but I'm gonna listen
to these guys
and stay alive.
♪ ♪
- That was quite
the speech back there.
Almost seemed like
you actually wanted
to save those meta-humans.
- No, you know me
better than that.
- No, I don't think I do.
- I used to be a good guy,
you know?
I worked at the Central City
Zoo, watching the reptile cage.
We were open the night the
particle accelerator blew up.
After the blast
shattered all the cages,
I had to pull
an elapid snake off a kid.
Then that dark matter hit.
- What happened to the kid?
- [grunts]
He's fine.
But what do I get, huh?
A snake in my head?
And a psycho killer
that wants me dead?
That was the last time I put
anyone else before myself.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
You know, it's almost like
a small part of me feels
sorry for that guy.
- Why?
He's only out for himself.
- Come on,
he's clearly terrified.
I know what that's like.
You're going to tell me
that you've
never felt fear like that?
- No, why?
- Really?
Not even a little bit worried
about Caitlin making the cure?
[zapping]
♪ ♪
- Is that everyone?
- Everyone except Shawna Baez.
A meta that calls herself
Peek-A-Boo?
Anyone know where she'll be?
- Try the Sundollar on Eighth.
♪ ♪
- All right.
[zapping]
[sighs]
- Bar's not open yet.
Not even for you, Flash.
- [sighs]
Shawna.
I need you to come with me.
- I didn't do anything
this time.
- I know.
You're not in trouble.
All right,
you're in danger.
I want to take you
some place safe.
- Like your science prison?
Sorry.
- Shawna?
Please.
Somebody is trying to kill you.
- Someone's always trying
to kill me.
See ya around, Flash.
[tense music]
[stuttered zapping]
What did you do to me?
- [whispering]
Shawna, run.
♪ ♪
- Who the hell is that?
- Take this,
press the button.
When a breach opens,
jump into it.
[dramatic music]
Go!
♪ ♪
Hyah!
[blows landing]
- Come on, come on...
♪ ♪
[strained breathing]
- Make this thing work.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- They're all terrified.
I can feel it.
- Maybe now they believe us.
- Hey, we're almost
through this.
We are going to get all
of these people to safety.
- Even if we do, Cicada's
not going to stop killing.
Not until...
- Until he's dead.
- I didn't say that.
- You didn't have to.
The anger that I feel
from you says it all.
- How am I supposed to feel?
He almost killed Nora.
- Barry, I understand, I do.
That man hurt your child.
But this anger
that you're feeling,
I have felt it before...
from Cicada.
Honey, if you let it,
this rage will consume you,
the same way
it's already consumed him.
Wait, I have felt this anger
from someone before.
At CCPD.
Oh, my God, Barry,
I think I know
who leaked the list.
- Then let's go get him.
- No, no, no, you...
you stay here.
You get these metas
to the drop.
I can handle the rest.
♪ ♪
[hopeful music]
[footsteps approaching]
- Ah, well, look.
Neurological delight.
Why, you'll be back
on these feet
and chasing Cicada
in no time.
- I hope so.
- Yes. In the meantime,
maybe you can help me
do the same.
- Oh, I already told
the team everything I know
about the Flash museum.
- Flash museum, right.
Do you think that
I could look at the archives
from that Flash museum?
After all, I have made a career
out of noticing things
that other people miss.
Maybe it's not a problem
to bring those archives
for me to look at?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Or maybe it's easier
for me to go there?
- You want me to bring you
to the future?
- Mm.
It's a great suggestion.
Is it even possible
for a non-speedster
to go into the commodity...
What'd you call it? The, um...
- The Speed Force?
- Speed Force. Right.
- Uh, I'm not sure.
- Mm.
Right.
Well, perhaps that's a question
for someone
with more experience.
- Sherloque.
- Mm?
- Can I talk to you
for a second?
- Excusez-moi.
♪ ♪
- That's my daughter in there.
- Yes, so?
- And I'm going to do whatever
it takes to protect her.
Even from people
who I thought were her friends.
So I'm gonna need you
to tell me right now
why you're
investigating Nora.
- Invest...no, no.
Quoi?
No one's investigating Nora.
Maybe I'm investigating
Nora a little bit.
- Why?
You think, what,
Nora is hiding something?
- No, um...
How can I say this?
Sometimes
when you're a detective,
you see a story
and you follow it.
And there's different tracks.
You follow down the track.
With Nora,
I am following down this track.
- Do you know how many stories
I've chased
that went absolutely nowhere?
- Mm.
- So many that I stopped
chasing them for a while
instead of doing
what I should have done,
something you suggested,
actually,
which is going down
a different track.
- Mm.
- That track is the wrong one.
♪ ♪
Careful
with your little monocle.
Learn to take notes
like everyone else.
Nora!
Oh, my goodness.
[both laughing]
- What do you want, Ralph?
- I know it's none
of my business
why you're afraid of a cure,
but for what it's worth,
I'm a meta,
and I'm all for it.
And after talking with most
of those people out there...
So are some of them.
- Oh, yeah, I can see that.
I just don't understand why.
- It might save their lives.
- It's not that simple for me.
- Why not?
- Because, just like Norvock
didn't ask for his snake,
Caity didn't ask for me.
So if one day she wakes up
scared of being a meta-human
and decides to take that cure,
her powers don't
just disappear.
I do too.
That's what
I'm really afraid of.
'Cause if I'm gone
who's going to protect her?
- It's witching hour.
♪ ♪
- I get why
you're scared, but...
you need to know that when
DeVoe made you disappear,
all Caitlin talked about
was getting you back.
So maybe as much as you want
to protect her,
Caitlin wants
to protect you, too.
- I went after three of them
tonight and they weren't there.
Did you tip them off?
♪ ♪
- No, I swear.
After what that Spencer woman
did to me
with her meta-tech,
I want them all gone.
- Then what happened?
- The D.A.
She figured out
you're targeting everyone
on the list I gave you.
The contact of mine
with the Feds
says they're being picked up
and put into
protective custody.
Tonight.
- Where?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[helicopter blades whirring]
- Boys and girls,
your ride's here.
[whooshing]
- What the hell?
- Everybody get back!
[electrical buzzing]
- Thank you, Flash,
for bringing them all to me.
♪ ♪
- The chopper's
not going to be able to land.
Take everybody out the back
and get them on it somehow.
- Come on.
[dramatic music]
- No, he's mine.
Hyah!
[blows landing]
[helicopter whirring]
♪ ♪
- All right, we're out
of the dampening field.
Shawna, can you help?
- Every meta for themselves.
- What now?
- I don't suppose you can
run up my arm, can you?
- Ralph,
what are you planning to do?
- Remember, Baby Giraffe,
they took a leap of faith
with you.
- That's why I'm going to take
a leap for them, Shirley.
All right, everybody.
Straight line, single file,
tuck your arms in.
[dramatic music]
[stretching sound]
♪ ♪
Keep this thing steady.
- Roger that.
♪ ♪
- Stand there!
Tuck your arms.
♪ ♪
[epic music]
[blows landing]
♪ ♪
- You can't win this fight.
- I bet I can.
We haven't been
formally introduced.
They call me Killer Frost.
Let me show you why.
[ice crackling]
[blades clanking]
♪ ♪
[slashing]
- Ah!
[grunting in pain]
♪ ♪
- Ugh.
[energy buzzing]
[thudding]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[whooshing]
- Killer Frost, duck!
♪ ♪
- You saved me.
- You saved them first.
Nice work.
Let's get out of here for real!
[whooshing]
[ice crackling]
- Give him hell, Flash!
[electrical buzzing]
- Okay, you see,
the metas are on the move.
Bravo.
- Something's wrong with Barry.
- What?
I've never seen these kind
of readings from Barry's suit.
- He's channeling over 2.86
billion joules of energy.
That's a combined equivalent
of...of almost
three lightning bolts.
- Cicada's powers allow him
to sustain injury
but not that much.
- Barry.
IRIS:Barry.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
He's not going to stop.
- You're never gonna hurt
my daughter again!
♪ ♪
Aah!
- Dad!
No.
- [panting]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I let him get away.
- No, you brought me back.
[heartfelt music]
♪ ♪
- Alright, the Feds
have processed Norvock
and the other metas,
giving them new identities,
so everybody's safe.
- Satellite hasn't registered
any unaccounted for dark matter
so, wherever Dwyer is,
his dagger's not in use.
- Psh, after the beating Barry
gave him, ain't no way
he's using that dagger
anytime soon.
What?
He got what he deserved.
- Oh, no, I think
we appreciate your groove.
Also I think that Killer Frost
and the Flash combination is
enough to maybe have Dwyer
not want to show his face
around here any time soon.
- Dad, are you okay?
- I'm good.
What matters
is that you're okay.
- [chuckling]
- How's it feel
to be up and running again?
- Super frickin' schway.
- Uh, wanna know what's
not super frickin' schway?
Cicada knowing exactly
when and where
our secret transport
was taking place.
- Mm.
Inside job, right?
Cicada clearly has
a inside man, only...
- Only what kind of cop
would help Cicada
kill innocent people?
[phone beeping]
- One that's going to have to
answer to D.A. Cecile Horton.
- Captain,
you wanted to see me?
- Come on in.
- Officer Jones,
this was printed
off of your hard drive.
Copy of the list of metas
that Cicada's been pursuing.
Funny thing,
it is the same list
that we know you accessed
on your home computer
just this week.
- Care to tell me
why you decided
to aid and abet
a murderer?
- No, that's not...you don't
know what you're talking about.
- Really?
A woman used meta-human tech
to take control of your mind.
She made you do things
that you were certain
you would never do.
And that frightened you,
didn't it?
It frightened you
and it made you angry,
and you went ahead
and you embraced that anger
and you let it
drive your every move.
Betrayal.
Revenge.
Escape.
- [struggling]
The metas in this city
have no respect for human life.
They don't deserve
to breathe our air.
- You swore an oath to protect
the citizens of this city.
Every one of them.
Get him out of my sight.
- [grunts]
- You know, your instincts
have always been sharp.
But knowing he was going
to try to escape?
Could have swore you were
reading Jonesy's mind.
- [laughs awkwardly]
It's a funny thing, yeah.
Since Jenna was born,
I've been
a lot more in touch
with my feelings.
- [chuckles]
When Joe gets back,
the two of you
will be a force
to be reckoned with.
- Oh, we already are.
- Killer Frost,
you shouldn't have.
- KILLER FROST:It's the
closest  you're getting
to an apology from me,
so...
- Well, maybe that's why
I can hear you
without the M.A.D. 2.0.
Or maybe it's because
you've stopped hating me.
- KILLER FROST:
I didn't hate you.
I thought
you were being stupid.
There's a difference.
- Hey, you know I'd never take
that cure, right?
- Even if it means sharing
a body with me
until you get old and grey?
- Of course.
You're a part of me
that I never want to lose.
I promise, I will do everything
I can to protect you.
- Right back at you, Caity.
Now, don't get all soft on me,
but I got you
a little something.
Check the cooler.
[inspiring music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Frosty.
Oh, Caitlin.
Is that a ball of ice
with blood inside of it?
- I think Killer Frost
took it from Cicada.
Ralph, this isn't just blood.
This is a DNA sample from
a recently created meta-human.
- So Killer Frost came around.
- Yeah.
She did.
- KILLER FROST:Ugh, I said
don't get soft. - [laughs]
- Begin handwriting analysis.
♪ ♪
As I suspected,
the journal of Nora West Allen
contains two
different types of handwriting.
So...
There is a mastermind
behind the scenes.
The only question is...
who?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[peaceful music]
- Okay, 47 tacos
is officially my limit.
- I think that's
anyone's limit, honey.
- A healing speedster's
gotta eat.
- Healed, Dad.
I'm fine.
I promise.
Hey, uh,
dinner again tomorrow night?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Nora? Um...
I just...
just want you to know
how much we love you.
♪ ♪
[zapping]
- See?
She's back to her old self.
And so are you.
- No, I'm not.
In fact, I don't think
I'll ever be the same.
All of this has made me realize
that, I don't know,
I just...I never knew I was
capable of even caring
for someone as much
as I care about Nora.
- I did.
I've never met anyone with
a bigger heart than you, Barry.
So it's no surprise to me
that you are
a fantastic father.
Just like you're
a fantastic husband.
- Cicada's a father, too.
What if the key to defeating
him is appealing to his heart?
- How do we do that?
- By saving his child.
♪ ♪
We need to wake up Grace.
[epic music]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Greg, move your head.
[lightning zapping]