Previously on The Flash...
It's a samurai.
Bring me the Flash,
or else your city falls.
Barry's still stuck in the Speed Force?
I'm gonna get him out.
But I need your help.
Barry? It's me, Iris.
Loud, cloud, proud!
Please come back to me.
Barry, Iris is in trouble!
Flash is back!
Flash, welcome home.
The Flash is back in Central City.
You came back to me.
I'm not going
anywhere ever again.
Not only is this the most modern,
lavish penthouse on the market,
it also has one of the best views
in all of Central City.
Join me on the balcony.
See for yourself.
I couldn't care less about the view.
Is it your most expensive listing?
- Yes, but the price is negotiable.
- I'll take it.
Yes!
Just let me lock up,
and I'll ride down with you.
Sorry. Not sure
which button does what.
Schmuck.
Damn it.
Dana. Yeah, listen,
I think I'm in some busted elevator...
I don't know...
No.
Just take those old records
Off the shelf
I'll sit and listen
To 'em by myself
Today's music
Ain't got the same soul
I like that old-time rock 'n' roll
Don't try to take me to a disco
You'll never even get me
Out on the floor
In ten minutes I'll be late for the door
I like that old-time rock 'n' roll
What?
Whoa.
No...
- Barry. Hi.
- Hey.
- You're up early.
- Yeah.
Doing what, exactly?
I'm just catching up on
all the TV I missed
while I was stuck in the Speed Force.
When you've been gone six months,
the world is a minefield of spoilers.
But Cisco hooked me up
with a 1,000-times sped up version
of my favorite shows.
Jon Snow died. Oh, he's alive.
And here I was thinking you'd need
a jump-start for your loopy brain.
Nope. Brain good. All of me is good.
Joe needs me. Crime scene.
That's okay.
I should probably get started
on our neglected wedding plans.
It's gonna take me forever
to get through this binder. So...
No, don't worry about it.
I'm done with it.
- You're done?
- Yeah.
I locked in a caterer,
I got you your favorite flowers.
I put a deposit on a venue
with an amazing view.
I got that seven-tier
raspberry chocolate cake.
Well, I guess you've got
everything covered.
So, my lovely fiancée
can remain stress-free.
Save me a bear claw?
Oh, no promises, Speedster.
You whoosh, you lose.
- What do we got, Joe?
- Not much to go off.
The only witness
was an elderly resident,
and she's still pretty rattled.
Hey.
Mr. Allen. Six months
and five minutes late.
Sorry, Captain Singh.
Thank you again for granting me
that extended sabbatical.
But I'm back, I'm ready to work,
and what can I say?
It's a beautiful day.
Sorry. What are we dealing with?
Well, I hope you had
a light breakfast.
No, I had a good spread, actually.
Pancakes, sausage, fruity cereal...
Whoa.
He's everywhere.
Far as we can tell,
it dropped him 100 stories.
Were you able to ID the vic?
Yeah. Kurt Weaver.
Worth billions. Capital "B."
What do you think, Mr. Allen?
You see the impacts on the ceiling?
And the repeated
lateral stress fissures on the frame?
This guy didn't just drop,
he was shaken to death.
Excuse me. Coming through.
CCPD Tech Consultant.
That's right. Look at the badge,
that means it's official.
He's aware that badge is plastic, right?
Fellas. So sorry I'm late.
The curls were not cooperating
this morning.
Good Lord.
Why would you show me that?
We think this is because of
some weird technical glitch.
And you're our weird tech expert.
It's completely ruined sriracha for me.
Yoink.
- That shouldn't be there.
- What is it?
It's encrypted code.
This wasn't a glitch. This was a hacker.
The Cortex's quantum algorithm
should decrypt this code in no time.
That should help us ID
our new hacker.
But while we wait, I've got
a little welcome-back gift for you.
Come, come. Walk with your boy.
Gather 'round, class.
Kablam!
I mean, that was a cool reveal
and everything,
but I've seen that suit.
I've actually already worn it.
Yeah. We all know you gave Barry's
suit a nice little fancy makeover.
Yeah, but you don't know
what you don't know.
And under all this red beautiful,
I've built in self-repairing armor,
nano-liquid circuitry,
full-spectrum scanning,
and a whole bunch of other big words.
Chief among them...
Your very own custom-made HUD.
This thing is loaded with maps,
schematics, delivery menus.
You know that Thai place
you love so much?
- Yeah, the one with the pad see ew?
- You know how we pad see do.
Dude, this is awesome.
What else does it do?
Well, lucky for you, I even wrote you
an instruction manual.
- Yay!
- Come on, we're not cavemen.
- Really good work.
- I know!
I'll look at this later.
Um, I gotta get back to CCPD.
And you can blame this on Cisco,
but I'm thinking Thai tonight?
Honestly, babe,
I'll probably be too tired to eat out
after our evening training session.
I canceled that.
Don't worry about that.
You canceled it?
Yeah, I mean,
I don't think we need it, right?
Besides, I'm back.
I'll make a reservation, okay?
It must be so nice having Barry back.
Yeah. Yes, it is.
But...
Well, I mean,
it's just gonna take some time
for him to get used to the new dynamics
around here, that's all.
Yeah.
You know, when Ronnie and I went from
just working together
to working together and dating,
we had some trouble communicating.
I mean, Barry and I
communicate just fine.
Yeah. I'm just saying,
we actually went to couples therapy
and it really helped a lot.
I appreciate the advice, Caitlin.
Really, I do.
But, you know, Barry and I have
known each other since childhood.
You know, we don't need therapy.
I mean...
- We're Barry and Iris, right?
- Right.
Thanks, though. I mean, I don't have
anything against it. It's just...
You're Barry and Iris. Gotcha.
Unauthorized breach incoming.
We gotta move.
Don't change, don't change,
don't change, don't change...
Caitlin, let's go!
You ready?
For anything.
Hey, hey! Whoa, whoa! Hold your fire!
- Hey.
- Girl...
Hey, you wanna give me
a little more notice next time?
You know people who want to kill us
come through here, right?
Oh, my bad, guys.
Cisco, that was very heroic of you
to just jump in,
protecting Gypsy like that.
It's very impressive.
Dude, I'm protecting you from her.
She would've vaporized you guys.
Pfft.
He's not lying.
As you were.
Okay.
- So, you almost ready for our date?
- Yeah. Almost.
Um...
I hit a snag in trying to decrypt
this hacker code for the CCPD.
I mean, you know how we do.
It's just kind of like The Matrix...
You care about none of this.
Just give me, like, one hour.
Two, tops. And then...
It's you and me, promise.
You're lucky you are so cute.
- And you are amazing.
- Yeah.
And you're so right
about the cute thing, too, huh.
- BRB.
- Okay.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Guys, there's a car going 120,
swerving between lanes.
Someone's going to get killed.
- You both need to get out there.
- That's one car. I got it.
Yeah, but I can...
I can help you.
Help! Help!
Okay, guys, it's a runaway.
The driver's trapped inside.
I'm gonna change his trajectory.
Okay. Then turn him left.
There's a turn-off
for runaway trucks coming up.
Just clear a path, and the car
will come to a safe stop there.
No, no, no,
I'm gonna push him right.
That street's empty.
I can help him there.
Barry, you can't go
down that road.
What? Why?
Because they started construction
on that street three months ago.
No, no, no, no, no.
I know a guy almost died,
but what happened to this sexy beast
here today is the real tragedy.
It could've been a lot worse.
I'm sorry, guys. This one is all on me.
Okay, so, my dad talked to the driver,
Tim Kwon, he's fine.
He's gonna question him and see
if they can figure out who did this.
- Cisco, what do we got?
- Beginning auto-topsy, now.
That is the same weird code
from the elevator murder scene.
- Wait. Doesn't that mean...
- Our hacker's got a hit list.
Can you crack it?
Man, I've been trying to
crack this code all day.
It looks like a virus.
Well, yeah. Because it's
a computer virus. I mean...
No, no, no. Scooch.
Oh, I feel violated.
- It looks like an organic virus.
- But with a digital sub-base.
Our killer isn't just hacking
machines, he's controlling them.
Our hacker's not a hacker.
He's a meta.
Is there a connection
between the two victims?
There's nothing online.
But their names, Weaver, Kwon,
they sound very familiar to me.
I started collecting these tech
magazines in high school, they're...
Those are the magazines
you collected in high school?
Okay, that's hurtful.
That's really hurtful.
Anyway, I'm 90% sure
that's where I read those names.
Okay, great. Start digging.
Barry, can I talk to you
for a second?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, about what happened, I'm sorry.
I should've listened to you.
It's just sometimes when I'm out
there, things move so fast,
and I'm really excited
to be the Flash again.
Anyway, I hope you're not mad.
And you are. You're mad, aren't you?
No, no. I'm not mad.
I just think with us being engaged,
and now we're working together,
that it's more important than ever
that we communicate.
I completely agree.
Good. Because Caitlin mentioned
something earlier,
and I sort of dismissed it. But now, I'm
really thinking that it could help us.
What is it?
Couples therapy.
- Couples therapy? You...
- Mm-hmm.
- We're not, like, in trouble, are we?
- No, no. No, of course not.
I just think that any couple
that's doing everything we're doing
could use some advice.
Mm-hmm.
We're just talking about a tune-up.
I mean,
there's nothing wrong with that, right?
A tune-up. Right, yeah. I mean...
Sure. If it's what you wanna do,
then sure, yeah. Let's try it.
Great. 'Cause we've got an appointment
in 30 minutes. I'll get my purse.
What?
Later.
- Hi. Iris?
- Hi.
- Hi, Barry.
- Hello.
Hi, I'm Dr. Sharon Finkel.
I am so sorry I kept you waiting.
No, no. It's fine.
Thank you for squeezing us in.
Well, you made it sound so urgent
on the phone.
No. Not urgent.
I'm excited. To dive in.
- Right?
- Oh, absolutely. I love therapy.
- Oh, have you been before?
- Just once. When I was a kid.
- After my mom died.
- Oh, your mom...
But I'm okay with that.
I mean, I'm not okay with it, obviously.
I mean, I'd prefer that she was alive.
I just meant that
I've already dealt with it.
So, I don't think
it's worth writing down.
These notes are just for me.
No one is judging you guys.
Yes, we know.
Well, my dad died, too.
Just for your notes.
So, Barry,
Iris filled me in a little bit
about the two of you
on the phone before.
- Getting married.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's been a long road,
getting here.
First, us growing up together.
And then I was engaged
to someone else.
- Okay.
- That's worth a write-down.
He's actually dead, too.
You two have had to deal with
a lot of trauma.
- Well...
- No, not...
- Eddie and Ronnie.
- I mean, a little.
- My mother, H.R.
- Not too much.
- Laurel. Snart.
- Some.
- We've been to a few funerals.
- Yeah.
So, Barry, why do you think Iris
wanted you two to see me today?
Well, Iris and I,
we recently started working together.
You see, I went away for a while on a...
- Business trip.
For six months.
I guess now, yeah, we're just
learning to get back in sync.
To sync up again. Is that right?
Well, there's no right or wrong, Barry.
Right.
I think we could work on
listening a little bit more, right?
Yeah.
Or else, someone could get really hurt.
Like if they crash their car into a
brick wall, going 100 miles per hour.
She means that emotionally.
Do I?
Hello, mamacita. They don't
make 'em like you anymore.
What the hell?
Easy, it's just the Motherboard
of the Month, July of '07. Okay?
- Look at her. Err.
- I kind of wish it was a girl.
Baby, it's been hours. You guys
haven't made any progress yet?
No mention of Kurt Weaver or Tim Kwon,
or any connection
between the two of them.
Until now. Got 'em.
Take note, people. It's only hoarding
if it doesn't pay off.
Okay, so, that's Tim Kwon,
that's Kurt Weaver,
that's Sheila Agnani...
Who's that guy?
- Sorry about that.
- No. It's definitely my fault.
You don't have any idea
who would want to do you harm?
Not even a gut feeling?
No. I mean, everyone loves
a billionaire, right?
No, I have no idea.
Grenade! Everybody, move!
So, what would you say
your goals are for this session?
Well, I just want to know that
Barry hears my concerns about our
issues with miscommunication.
- I gotta go.
- You gotta go?
- He's gotta go.
- Yeah.
Sorry. This was... Sorry.
You're gonna write down that
he ran out of here, aren't you?
Yes.
Get down!
Everybody okay?
I don't know, it must've been a dud.
Same corrupted code. Same guy.
Someone very creatively tried to kill
Tim Kwon and Kurt Weaver.
Where's Kwon now?
He ran out of here,
scared out of his mind.
He wouldn't even wait
for a protected escort.
But the good news is, I found
a connection between our victims.
Four years ago,
Kurt Weaver and Tim Kwon
created an app in their garage
with two other programmers.
Some kind of malware called Kilg%re.
And then they sold it off
to a big tech company.
So, that's how they made their money.
I saw this guy. He was here.
Ramsey Deacon.
Looks like we found our meta.
And for some reason,
he's going after his old partners.
It's like Silicon Valley
if Richard went nuts and started
killing everyone at Pied Piper.
I feel like he's got more of
an anarchist Gilfoyle vibe.
Erlich, maybe.
Guys, I love that we're so confident
in our ability to apprehend villains
that we can have this debate,
but, hi, what about her?
That's Sheila Agnani.
She's like a big deal tech guru now.
She could be next on Deacon's list.
We'll definitely have to protect her.
Yeah, well, my dad and Wally
can do that, right?
- I'm on it.
- Great.
- I'll keep working on the code.
- Sure.
Sorry about therapy.
It's okay. I told Dr. Finkel
that you had a work emergency.
- True. Kind of.
- Yeah.
And she had a cancellation
this afternoon,
so, we should get over there.
- Don't want to be late.
- No. Yeah, let's get back in there.
This guy is a living computer virus.
That's a new one.
Look at this code. From the elevator,
to the car, to the bomb robot,
this code keeps changing,
but I can't figure out why.
Okay, we have to remember
that it's not just digital,
it's bio-digital.
Most organic viruses mutate
to avoid being killed.
So, if we manage to create
digital antibodies,
then we can shut this guy down.
Oh! Nice one!
Hi.
I'm so glad you're here.
'Cause I truly, deeply,
from the bottom of my heart,
I am sorry,
but I'm gonna have to cancel our date.
If you're gonna vi-blast me,
can I at least pick the spot?
It's fine, Cisco.
- I get it.
- You get it?
Yeah, what's not to get?
You have to work, so...
We will cancel our date.
Well, good luck, you guys.
I hope it works out.
What a cool chick.
She took that so well.
No. No, she didn't.
When a girl says she gets it,
what she really means
is she doesn't get it at all.
I'm confused.
Don't be. Very simple.
You, my friend, are in so much trouble.
You just had to fall for the girl
in head-to-toe black leather,
didn't you?
We're back. That was quick. Even for me.
That's funny.
Inside joke between us.
Work emergency aside,
I have a sneaking suspicion that
you'd rather be somewhere else, Barry.
No, no. I mean, we do have
a big work thing
that we're dealing with.
- It's important.
- Yeah, but so is this.
You know, if we're not on the same page,
Barry, people could die.
- Ah.
- Metaphorically.
No. No, no, don't hold back.
Turn to Iris, look her in the eyes,
and tell her what you wanted to say.
I don't know... Well, I...
I said I was sorry about this morning.
Iris, turn to Barry. Talk to him.
It's not just this morning, Barry.
You canceled training the other day
without asking me.
Training?
- Swimming.
- For a marathon.
It's a triathlon.
Anyway, I didn't think canceling
training was that big of a deal.
Yeah, but you made
all those wedding plans, too,
and you didn't consult me.
I was trying
to be a good fiancé.
I'd think most brides would be happy
that their future spouse cared about
helping with the wedding.
That is a good thing, right?
Look, I don't know... I mean,
I guess our wires have gotten crossed
a few times the last few days,
but I think that hardly rises
to the level of a crisis.
After everything
we've been through together,
you and me, we're Barry and Iris.
We're the gold standard.
I am so in love with you...
Then how could you leave me?
You left me, Barry. You just left me.
Standing there alone.
How could you do that?
All the listening devices are in place.
Well, keep your ears open.
Gotta make sure she's safe.
Yeah.
What? I like punk music.
Tim?
What the hell, man?
You can't just come into my house.
'Cause you wouldn't return my calls.
I really...
If it's about your weird crush,
let it go, Tim.
- We are not happening.
- Sheila, listen.
Deacon's coming for us.
He wants payback for
what we did to him.
What did we do to him?
Kurt scrubbed any connection
between us from the net.
So, as far as the world's concerned,
we're innocent.
But we're not.
I should have never let you talk me
into going along with this.
And now, Kurt's dead.
Deacon killed him.
- He did not.
- Oh, yes.
He did.
Well, this is a nice house.
How much did you pay for it?
Ten mil?
Let's talk about this.
We can make it right.
Shut up, Tim!
You could have had all this, too.
This all could have been yours.
Kilg%re was my idea.
And you three stole it away from me.
Somebody had to.
Otherwise, it would have just been
a halfway clever idea
that died in someone's garage.
- Sheila...
- No. I'm not
going to apologize
because after four years,
you finally found some balls.
I found something else.
Something I never had with my family
or at MIT,
- or with any of you.
- Really?
And what was that?
Power.
You're not still diabetic, are you?
Those new computer-controlled
insulin pumps
are a real lifesaver.
Way too much insulin...
Well, that can be lethal.
And how should we kill you?
He put her in insulin shock.
Glucose.
Deacon took him.
He took Tim.
No sign of Deacon or Kwon
on facial recognition,
traffic cameras, nothing.
We don't even know
if Kwon is still alive.
We gotta move fast.
Where were you two?
- Dry cleaners.
- Wedding... Cleaners. Dry cleaners.
Cisco, where are you
with those bio-digital antibodies?
I'm nowhere.
Actually, no, you know what?
I am somewhere.
I'm in the doghouse.
Apparently,
the pan-dimensional doghouse.
I don't know if this doghouse
has a door or a window.
But if it did, I'd be jumping out of it!
It's okay, I'll go talk to him.
Has everybody lost their minds?
She must think I'm blowing her off,
but I'm just trying to do my job.
I guess the word "reschedule"
doesn't exist on Earth-19.
Okay, I'm gonna go out on a limb here,
and guess that the reason
you can't focus on science
is because you're so worried
about what's going on with Gypsy.
I'm sorry,
I didn't hear anything you said.
But I think I figured it out.
I think I can't focus on anything
'cause of this whole Gypsy situation.
I think
I'm just gonna have to talk to her.
What a great idea.
Hey.
What's up, Cisco?
You're mad at me.
- I said it was fine.
- No, no, no.
Rule number one, when
a girl says it's fine, it's not fine.
Amen!
I'm gonna go.
Rule number two,
you don't blow off a date
with your favorite person.
The day got away from me.
Let me make it up to you.
Okay? Date night tomorrow?
No, Cisco, it had to be today.
- Why today?
- Because today is One-One-One Day.
- One what... What?
- One-One-One Day.
What is that?
One-One-One Day on my Earth is...
It's the day that you celebrate
with the one...
With the one you love, all right?
It's when one soul plus one soul
equals one soul.
- That is so sappy.
- Yes.
It is sappy and it's stupid
and schmoopy,
but there is something about you that...
It makes me want to do stupid,
schmoopy things.
And I hate the word "schmoopy"
and people who use it.
Well, that is the sweetest and
angriest thing you've ever said to me.
Why didn't you just tell me that?
Because I was embarrassed, Cisco!
So, you know what?
Let's just forget about it.
Because the day is already over,
and I would really like to forget
that I ever brought this up.
No, no, no, no.
I will not forget it, okay?
You are important to me.
And if One-One-One Day
is important to you...
One-One-One.
That's it.
I gotta go.
It's like he doesn't know
that he's a dead man.
Hey.
I don't know why I thought
that we didn't have to talk
about what happened.
You were so happy I was back.
I am happy. You're everything to me.
Look.
I had to explain
to our friends and family
why they had a save-the-date
for our wedding but no invitation.
I had to constantly lie
about why you were gone.
You don't know the looks people gave me
because they knew that wasn't the truth.
You know,
what they must have thought about us,
what it made me think about us.
Iris...
It's not like I wanted to leave you.
I had to put on a brave face for
everyone, but it was killing me inside.
And I think part of why
I didn't talk it through with you
is I was afraid.
I was afraid
that you would tell me to stay.
And I wouldn't have been
strong enough not to.
Barry, how do you know what
I'm gonna say if you don't ask me?
I'm here to help you.
Especially when everything seems lost.
But you have to let me.
Sometimes, it's not about us.
Or the team.
Sometimes, the weight of the whole city
falls on my shoulders,
and it's up to me to carry it.
I'm the Flash.
See, that's what you don't get.
When I put this ring on my finger,
it wasn't just about you or me anymore.
It was about us.
You are not the Flash, Barry. We are.
Guys, we need you.
It's about Deacon.
I have something to confess.
Kurt Weaver, Sheila Agnani and I,
we stole the Kilgore malware program
from Ramsey Deacon.
We sold it for billions.
But it was all his idea.
We got rich and he got nothing.
I guess that explains
why Deacon's got such a vendetta.
Cisco, if he's live streaming,
can you track the signal?
In, like, two seconds.
Papa loves having his own satellite.
What are you going to do
when you find him?
- Hit him with this.
- What is that?
Deacon's powers are derived
from the binary code in his DNA.
So, we created a compound
encoded with a numerical string
pattern of ones and zeros
to invert the order of the code.
Ones become zeroes and vice versa.
One plus one plus one.
All right, we're on it.
- Send us the location once you have it.
- Okay.
Let's do it.
And now, you know the truth.
We stole Kilg%re from Ramsey Deacon.
He is the real victim.
Good.
- You forgot one thing.
- What?
You didn't say goodbye to anyone
who's gonna miss you.
You ever play wishbone, Tim?
He and the others destroyed my life!
Listen, I know you feel wronged, Deacon,
but that doesn't give you a right
to take his life.
I smell technology in your suit.
What have you got in there?
Oh, crap.
I can't move.
Weapon system online.
Targeting.
Run.
Call me Kilg%re.
Barry, what's happening?
It's Deacon.
He's done something with my suit.
Remote access complete.
You put your voice in Barry's suit?
Well, it had to be somebody,
and my voice is soothing.
How much tech did you put in the suit?
So much.
I've actually always
been a huge Flash fan
this past couple of years.
But this is like having
a giant action figure.
Frak me! He's locked me
out of my own programming!
Do something!
Barry, get away from him!
It might lessen
his technopathic hold over you.
I can't!
Who you talking to?
Someone listening in? Can't have that.
Barry?
Barry! His comms are offline.
You have a defibrillator.
How about I stop your heart?
Hello?
You have a collect call from...
- Guys, help me!
- We accept the charges!
The suit's still freaking out!
Well, get it off!
Nope, I can't get it off!
That would be the deadlock function.
I built it in case
he ever got knocked out,
so, a bad guy
wouldn't reveal his identity.
It seemed like a smart idea at the time!
Flotation Mode activated.
What?
What the hell
does he need a raft for, Cisco?
He runs on water!
He might lose his speed out there.
What's he going to do then?
He might drown.
You couldn't just put
an oxygen tank in the suit?
That's a good idea.
How is this thing still intact?
Cisco!
Babel Protocol activated.
What? What's the Babel Protocol?
Why am I ticking?
It's the self-destruct sequence.
- What?
- Self-destruct?
I'm sorry, have we not faced an evil
version of Barry before? My mistake!
Well, how do I stop it?
Hell, no.
Oh, God.
Cisco, there must be something
we can do.
Not as long as this thing's
powered up.
Come on, come on.
Barry, can you hear me?
Iris! Hey, I'm sorry. Okay? I'm sorry.
Just tell me what to do, and I'll do it.
You need to throw a lightning bolt.
At what?
Yourself.
You want him to do what?
It might short the suit out,
give him back control.
Or it might set off
the self-destruct early.
Or it might stop his heart!
Barry? Barry, you need to listen to me.
Okay? We can do this.
Okay. I trust you, Iris.
Then run, Barry. Run.
Barry?
Oh, Tim, I know I have
the coolest superpower ever but...
I'm kind of tired.
Hello, gorgeous.
Here, on Earth-1,
we celebrate One-One-One Day today.
Even though I have zero idea
what that means.
Or what any of
your Earth's holidays mean.
I mean, I literally cannot believe
you celebrate a day called
St. Shaquille O'Neal's Day.
You guys have a magical elfling
in a red suit
that breaks into your house
and eats your cookies.
Actually, he's the boss of the elves,
so maybe do your research before.
What I do know is
how special you are to me.
And how sorry I am that I didn't
get to spend yesterday with you.
Well, I guess you were busy
catching a deranged killer.
Baby, we are always catching
a deranged killer around here.
True.
But I will always make it up to you.
I mean that.
You just gotta let me know
when it's this important.
I will.
All right, then.
You ready to get your schmoopy on?
'Cause, you know,
my schmoopy game is real strong.
This is cruel and unusual.
How will I survive in here
without my Kindle?
You ain't touching anything
electronic ever again.
There's three layers of
signal-dampening walls
between you and the world.
No wiring, not even a light bulb.
There's technology everywhere
these days.
That's fine.
We just have one question for you.
The particle accelerator explosion
four years ago,
you were living in Silicon Valley.
So, if you weren't here that night,
how did you get your powers?
Oh, wow.
You're not going to believe it.
It was really something, though.
A real life-changer.
And do you two
want to know the best part?
I wasn't the only one.
So, good luck, gentlemen.
I think Central City
is about to have its hands full.
Thank you for letting us
see the prisoner, Warden Wolfe.
My pleasure.
Did you get what you needed?
- We think so.
- Well, not to worry.
This so-called Kilg%re
isn't going anywhere.
We'll take good care of him.
How is it possible that Deacon's a meta
if he didn't get his powers
from Wells' particle accelerator
blowing up?
However it happened, we will
figure it out, and we will be ready.
After Cisco gets all that tech
out of your suit.
You don't need fancy gadgets
to be the Flash.
- You are the Flash.
- No. We are.
Did I miss something?
Ah, one of my childhood favorites.
Schubert's unfinished eighth symphony.
Unfinished until now.
You didn't.
It was surprisingly simple to
extrapolate the remaining movements
once I familiarized myself
with the body of his work.
All 600 of his works?
I woke up early this morning.
Do you have an update?
Subject One has been located.
He's safe.
Locked up in the meta-human
wing of Iron Heights as we speak.
He's right where you wanted him.
What do we do now?
Now, we find the others.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::