- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers.
All of them.
- DeVoe has absorbed
the powers of Killgore,
Hazard, Black Bison,
Brainstorm, and Dwarfstar.
- I'm gonna take DeVoe down.
- Just like Izzy
would have wanted.
- DeVoe orchestrated everything
to get the people
he wanted on the bus.
- We got a planner,
just like Thawne.
- This is
an intelligence booster.
I'll finally be able
to outthink the Thinker.
- [groaning]
- [grunts]
- Daddy!
- Pleased to meet you, sir.
- The last two
remaining bus metas...
Janet Petty
and Edwin Gauss.
- Ralph.
- Ready.
- Enact double scarlet's
speeds-turn.
Three, two, one...
- Wait!
I got a better idea.
[whistles] Over here,
Doc Ock.
[dramatic music]
Watch this, Master Splinter.
♪ ♪
Turtle power!
- Shut it down.
[sighs] All right,
let's run it again.
We got to make this work.
- Does he know that?
- Ralph?
Ralph!
- What?
- One more time, please.
Follow Barry's plan?
- You know, the one where I
spent hours of my precious time
programming realistic
holograms for you.
- Which...[chuckles] bravo
on that by the way. [kisses]
- Thank you.
- Look.
Just morph yourself into Barry.
There'll be two Flashes,
Thinker won't know
which one is which,
and we'll confuse him.
- Kind of a "her" actually.
- Ralph, you're missing
the point of this exercise.
- No, I get it. I was
just doing a little improv.
- But this isn't
standup comedy.
- Yeah, I know that, but
if you just let it play out,
it would have worked.
You could have done
some improving
of your own.
Comedy comes in threes, man.
- We're trying to protect you.
DeVoe's coming.
We need to be ready.
All of us, okay?
- I still think
it's a pretty good plan.
I hide my face.
I save my ass.
We'd make a fortune.
An improv group made up
of superheroes?
We can take it to Washington.
We'd be the DC Comics.
- No, Ralph.
- First rule of improv
is say yes.
- Would it kill you to take
training seriously?
- Would it kill you to open up
your mind grapes just a little?
- Hey.
We'll get there.
Eventually,
but we'll get there.
- He's just making a big joke
out of the whole thing.
- It's just the way
he is, Barry.
- I know, but I mean,
he needs to think
like a hero, stay on point.
DeVoe's thought of everything.
We can't just wing this one.
- Look, we'll figure it out.
We always do, right?
Melting Point's
on our team now.
We just have to find
the other two bus metas,
and we'll be in good shape.
- Yeah.
Where are we with tracking down
Edwin Gauss and Janet Petty?
- No, no, he's...
- What?
- He's still...shh...
- I ca...[groans]
- Working on it.
- I can't work
with all this noise.
[flatulence]
- [laughs] That is disgusting,
Harry.
Really, grow up.
- Really?
- It wasn't me.
That was expensive.
- Harry, look.
Every time you try
to locate these guys,
it's the same thing.
I'm telling you.
You just crack that thing open.
It's probably broken.
- It's not broken!
It's just finding these two
is complicated.
- Why is that?
- Because this dude,
Edwin Gauss,
flat out disappeared
the day Allen
came out of the Speed Force.
No credit card charges.
No bank withdraws.
No social media posts, nothing.
Gone.
- What about Janet Petty?
- Just as tricky.
I asked Joe
to pull her file from CCPD.
Her first known record wasn't
until she was 13.
Some sort of a nomad.
Last known address:
Iron Heights.
- What she in for?
- Trifecta of
breaking and entering,
trespassing, and burglary.
- But what we should
be worried about is
where is she now
and what are her powers?
- Is that really her handle?
"Null"?
- Okay, well DeVoe needs both
of these people
for whatever he has planned,
so we have to figure out
where they are.
- I will, Allen, if I can
get a little peace,
a little quiet,
and no interruptions.
[dramatic music]
- [groans]
- Great.
- [growling]
Cisky.
- Breacher?
[gasping]
- I need your help.
- Little bit
of a mixed message here.
- I was hunting Lord Crucifer,
leader of the Tenth Circle.
His cult of bloodsuckers
ambushed me.
They had me surrounded.
- So you were attacked by...
vampires?
- Hundreds of vampires!
The battle was fierce,
but I managed to dismantle
his entire force.
But when I went
to finish off Crucifer,
something happened to me.
My powers...they were gone.
- What do you mean?
- I couldn't vibe blast.
Crucifer got away.
He must have done
something to my powers.
- Has this ever happened
before?
- Never.
But Cynthia always said
you were an intelligent man,
well-versed
in the meta science.
- I'm glad to hear Gypsy
still remembers who I am.
Hey, you're her boss.
You would know
the answer to this.
Does she ever get a day off?
- Cynthia is very devoted
to her job.
But in regards to your skills...
- Yeah, yeah.
Let me guess.
You think she's wrong.
- No.
What I want to say is
I think you can fix me.
- Oh.
Well, sir,
we would be happy to...
run some tests
in the Speed Lab.
You know, see if
everything's okay.
- Thank you, Cisco.
Now I must get some tea.
- He didn't insult me once.
- Nope.
I just hope we can help him.
- [clears throat]
- How was your rest, my love?
- Wonderful.
I've never felt more
rejuvenated
and ready to
realize our dream.
- [coughing]
- Clifford.
- [shaky inhale]
The additional dark matter
from our subject metas is...
overwhelming this host's body.
- How long do we have?
- At the present rate,
just over a week's time.
- No.
I will not allow it.
It may be possible to adjust
the biomass index,
recalibrate the energy
distribution...
extend
your current host's life.
Odd.
There are already plans
for such an adjustment
partially designed.
- I attempted
the same course of action.
Though my mind for engineering
is nowhere near
as gifted as yours.
- Well, you got a good start.
I will be able
to complete these designs
within a few hours.
Rest, my love.
I will handle everything.
- You always do.
And then we will continue
on our search
for the remaining
two bus metas.
- You mean three.
The Weeper
is still at large.
- Yes.
Three. [chuckles]
Perhaps my mind is being
affected as well.
Hm.
- Come on,
put your back into it!
Put your fat back into it!
[groaning]
This stinks, man.
This is too heavy,
and you're too weak.
Let's get the big dolly.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
[dark tone]
- [whistles]
[tense electronic music]
♪ ♪
- Dude, the crate's gone.
We got to call the boss.
[music intensifies]
♪ ♪
- Well, well, well, well.
[laughs]
If the crown fits.
- We were moving...I
was telling the guy,
"It's gonna take all night
to move this stuff."
- Okay, remember,
let's just be discreet.
Neither one of us are supposed
to be here.
Can you do that?
- Can pigs fly?
- No.
- They can if you
put them on an airplane.
Think, Allen, think.
- [sighing] Okay.
- Just here
with your chai latte,
Detective West.
- Subtle.
- It was gone...
- Will you excuse me
just a sec, okay?
- Hey.
What happened?
- Robbery.
Stole the Kahndaq Dynasty
family crown.
It was brought here
for the museum exhibition.
The security guard said
that it was being transported
in a steel-plated crate,
weighs about 200 pounds.
Suddenly disappeared
without a trace,
and then reappeared
completely smashed.
- So was anything else missing
in the museum?
- Just the crown,
nothing else is missing.
- Should I, uh, stretch
around the perimeter?
Check things out?
- No, no.
I mean, I can tell from here,
to cause that type
of impact, the case had
to be moving at
at least 55 miles per hour.
- So we're looking
for a meta
with super strength.
- I mean, maybe.
Are there fingerprints
on the case?
- I'll have them dust it,
send the results in.
- Why wait?
I can just grab the tape.
Get the prints right now.
- No, hey.
- It was definitely
Killer Frost,
and she looked at me.
- Ralph!
- Whoa!
[exclamations, murmuring]
Dude!
I need this job!
- Allen!
Look what you did.
- Threw it at me!
That's you, bro.
- [grunting]
Die, Plastoid, die!
[grunts, panting]
- Again.
- [grunting]
[groans]
- All right.
Uh, I...I think...
I think
that's enough.
All right, hey, look, Breacher,
I know you're clearly very...
frustrated, uh...
Don't stress, okay?
We're gonna figure this out.
And once we do,
we're gonna fix it.
I promise.
[tense music]
- Cisky.
Look.
I'm sorry for the way
I treated you.
But when you fix me,
I'll give Cynthia more time
to be with you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Now...I'm hungry.
- We can fix that, too.
Um, there's donuts
in the downstairs break room.
Help yourself.
It's a huge selection.
Yeah.
Try the pineapple fritters.
And don't forget to try
the nacho donuts.
Those are really good.
[light, playful music]
[snaps fingers]
Looks like things
are looking up
for your boy Cisco.
- Yeah...
- What?
What...what is it?
What is wrong with him?
- Nothing, really.
He seems to be in good health.
There's nothing abnormal
in his bloodwork,
and his body scan showed
no signs of cellular damage
despite years of using
vibrational powers.
- Okay, so then why the face?
- Because Crucifer didn't take
his powers from him.
Father Time did.
- He can't blast
because he's getting older?
- Mm-hmm. Powers like yours
requires a lot of energy.
And when that energy
starts to dwindle...
- Vibe blasts are...
the first things to go.
- I think you have
to tell him.
- He's never, ever gonna let me
see Gypsy if I tell him.
He's probably gonna
send a knife
flying right through my skull
if I tell him.
- He might.
But it's the right thing to do.
[mug shatters]
[dark ambient music]
- What the...
Initiate chemical analysis.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- A $40,000 vase?
It's not like it was made
of gold.
- Actually it was, and you two
can't go to crime scenes
anymore,
PIs or not.
- Don't give me that look.
I was just trying
to speed up the process
finding this meta, Allen.
Which is taking forever.
- Wait, we got a hit.
Jeannie Williams.
Oh, wait. We got multiple hits.
- Jane Liska, Judy Newton.
She's used like
17 different aliases.
- Okay, so how do we find her?
- We can't just wait for
her to rob somebody else.
- Well, we don't have to.
[helmet powers up]
We have the many variations
of her façade.
Right, we simply plug
these many variations
into the facial
recognition software.
- See if we get a hit.
- Exactly right.
- That's starting
to come in handy, Harry.
- That's 40 minutes ago.
Corner of Orchard and Broome.
- Orchard and Broome?
What's over there?
- Not what.
Who.
Come on.
- What do you...
- Come on.
- It smells like liverwurst.
- Yeah, wait till
we get inside.
Open up!
- Okay, stick to the plan.
We question her.
We find Null. We cuff her.
- Got it. A little good cop,
bad cop action.
- [sighs]
[light music]
- Who the hell are you?
- Your worst nightmare.
- Uh, Joe [stammers]
- Detective Joe West, CCPD.
We got a couple questions
for you, scum bag.
- Hey, only my closest friends
can call me that.
[laughs]
- Word is, there's
a new cutpurse in town
who likes fancy jewels.
Last seen in this part of town.
PI Barry Allen.
- [muttering] PI Barry Al...
- Show him.
Show him!
- Oh, Barry Allen,
I know all about you.
Spectacular fall from grace.
Tragic, really.
- Yes, thank you.
Just take a look.
- Huh.
[catcalls]
- We're guessing
she came here
for help to wash the
sparklies.
- Oh, I should be so lucky.
Certainly wouldn't mind
a drop-in
from a lovely looking lassie
like this, you know what I
mean?
But unfortunately
not in my cards.
I'm sorry.
Can I keep this?
- I will mess you up
for lying in my face.
- Ralph.
- Ralph?
- There's no Ralph here.
- Joe...
- I'm Detective Joe West,
the baddest...dad cop
you've ever come across.
- As God is my witness
I am not lying.
I'm not.
Oopsy-daisy.
- I knew it.
[whispers] Joe West doesn't
make any mistakes.
- Okay.
Where'd she go, Earl?
[dramatic music]
- Deal's off.
- Damn it.
♪ ♪
- Cuffs.
Cuffs!
- Allen...
- Uh...
- Oh...
[dramatic string music]
♪ ♪
- Babe, you okay?
- I just want to get down
from here as soon as possible.
- Maybe you should try
to burp yourself down
like Charlie Bucket.
- Ralph.
- Anything?
- Well, as best I can tell,
Null's powers effect
the density of his cells.
It's like you've been filled
with helium.
- Terrific.
- Always knew you were
a lightweight.
- I swear Ralph...
- Hey, is there a way to
reengage gravitational...
- Gravitational force.
- [straining]
- Huh, turns out...
not necessary.
- [whispers] Do not let go.
- Based on Barry's
standard mass
and the gravitational force G
and taking into account
the half-life decrement
of Null's dark matter infusion,
this effect should
eventually just...
wear off.
[quirky music]
- Wear off?
- Your cells should
return to normal
right about...
- What the hell?
- [gasps]
[thud]
[groans]
- Now.
- Two for the landing,
but perfect ten
for the thud noise.
- Why are you joking
right now?
I mean ser...what the hell
was that back there?
Pretending to be Joe?
- I committed to the bit.
I couldn't blow my cover.
- Ralph, what if that had
happened outside on the street?
I could have floated away
into the stratosphere
or fallen to my death.
- I would have figured
something out.
- [exhales] Out of the 12
bus metas we have found,
DeVoe is in control
of seven of them.
If he gets Null,
it'll be eight.
If he gets control
of her powers,
we're talking
about your life here.
- Sorry, I was just thinking
about the end of "Lost."
[imitates explosion]
I mean, were they in purgatory?
What did Kate really see
in Jack?
- Ralph.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, man,
but I'm benching you.
- Why?
- Because you're constantly
in the middle
of a comedy routine
instead of doing
what you should.
if you had just tossed me
the cuffs,
we would have Null right now.
- Yeah, or she could
have ran out the door,
and I stretch the cuffs on her
when she didn't see it coming.
It's fine.
- [sighs]
Look, I'm doing
what's best for you.
- No, you're not.
You're doing
what's best for you.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Display, complete
physiological results
for DeVoe, Marlize.
Cortisol levels low.
Recent display of tachycardia,
repetitive pupil dilation.
[sighs]
Display serotonin level.
319 nanograms.
Levels found in patients
using psychoactive narcotics.
How is that?
[dark music]
♪ ♪
Subject four's still at large.
Created to provide
widespread euphoria...
Or feelings of love.
[dramatic music build-up]
♪ ♪
- What if we put him
on an all-alkaline diet?
Full of antioxidants.
- Nope.
- Okay,
what if we...
Oh, what if we make
a super shake
full of, like, enzymes
and...and...and probiotics?
- Neither of those are gonna
work long-term, Cisco.
- Okay, well, we got to come up
with something, right?
[laughs] I mean,
how old is this guy anyway?
[ball bounces]
This guy's old.
We have to solve this.
'Cause I don't know about you,
but I actually like my life.
- I know this isn't
the easy answer,
but I think you have
to tell him.
- Cisky!
- Oh, hey, you.
We were just talking about you.
- I've tasted all your donuts.
Where's my cure?
- Well, it's a little, um,
it's a little complicated.
- [growls]
- But! You are lucky,
my friend,
because your fix
is as simple
as taking one of these
little pink pills.
- Blue.
- [clears throat] Blue pills.
Right there.
- "Anta-hista-mine."
- That's right,
an antihistamine.
See, "stamine,"
that's Latin for stamina.
Which you have plenty of,
you know.
You have so much of it that
it's actually hurting you.
But this antimatter pill...
it's gonna level you
right out.
Oh, you're taking it now.
He's...he's taking it now.
- [grunts]
[grunts]
Why is my vibe blast
different?
- I think it's a side effect
of the pills.
Hasn't been thoroughly
researched yet,
but you know, there's
headaches, nausea...
different, uh, color vibes.
- I'm cured.
Thank you.
- Anytime.
[clicks tongue]
- You do realize
you're just making this worse?
- Nothing on Null so far.
Harry's gonna try
something else.
We'll find her.
- We have to.
Even if Ralph does everything
in his power to screw it up.
- Barry.
That is not his intention.
- Well, he could have
fooled me.
- It's his life.
I mean, if there's
anything he cares about,
it's losing it.
- Well, he's gonna lose it
if he doesn't start
thinking like me,
like I taught him.
- Thinking like you?
- [murmurs]
- He's never gonna
do that, Barry,
and you can't expect him to.
[alarm buzzing]
Oh, boy.
Robbery
at Central City Jewelry.
Man, she loves bling.
- I'm on it.
- Wait, you need backup.
- Well, Ralph's too much
of a liability right now.
He stays benched.
- Caitlin, Cisco?
- They're with Breacher.
It would take too long
to wait for them.
- Then what's the plan?
- The plan...
is "occulation."
You said her fingertips,
they illuminated
when she used her powers.
That means dark matter
accelerant, that means
powers are generating
from the optic nerve...
What I'm trying to say is
Null can't gravitate
what she cannot see,
so you vibrate beyond
the speed of sight as you
approach her eye line...
- I'll be invisible
to her.
It worked against DeVoe.
- Let's try it.
- [sighs]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- What the...
Didn't see that coming.
- It's kind of the point.
- No,you didn't see
that coming.
See, I call it my getaway car.
- [screaming]
- 'Cause either the person
in there dies,
or you let me get away.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
[panting]
- You okay?
It's okay.
Just stay here.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts] This useless piece
of trash is...useless.
It's like I'm so dumb
I can't even come up
with a good synonym for
this useless piece of trash.
- Harry, no one could
have predicted
that Null would
have picked herself
out of the cuffs
or taken a hostage.
- Nor did either of you
predict
the location
of a 120-pound woman
using the curvature
of spacetime
caused by the uneven
distribution of mass
yet still somehow
failed to account
for the gravitational pull
of a 4,000-pound car
floating right above her head.
- Scientists have spent decades
trying to understand relativity
and quantum gravity.
- This is not about
understanding gravity, Allen.
It's about understanding her
or not understanding her.
As it turns out, DeVoe
can somehow
calculate human behavior.
- Harry, stop.
Look, I'm the one
that let her get away.
You did your best.
- Did I, Allen?
Really?
This is the second meta
to evade the dampening cuffs.
It's been almost a year,
and where are we?
And where's DeVoe?!
- What?
- Nothing, it's just...
you went out into the field,
you had a plan,
and...it didn't work.
- But they do for DeVoe.
Harry's not wrong.
DeVoe's gone over
every possible outcome
before making his plans.
- Which we can't do,
and neither can Harry.
- Well, then what are
we supposed to do?
I mean, you just want us to
adlib like Ralph wants us to?
- Barry, you didn't see it,
but when you were gone,
Ralph rose to the occasion.
He cracked jokes.
He thought outside the box.
I mean, he got the job done
in the way that he knows how.
So, the question is,
are you upset with Ralph
because you think
he's screwing around
or because he's not
following your plan?
[soft music]
- Breacher!
I thought maybe
we could have a drink.
I don't know,
you strike me as kind of
a tequila guy, so...
[tense music]
Oh, crap.
♪ ♪
- You've come back to die,
Breacher.
[dramatic music]
- The time has come, Crucifer.
Die, vampire, die!
- Frack me, he's gonna die.
- Die!
[grunts]
- [hisses]
- Wait a second.
- Hey, back up, yo.
Yo, "Dusk Till Dawn", I think
it's time you saw some sun.
- Idiot, sunlight doesn't hurt
this type of vampire.
- What?
- [snarling]
- Time to go.
- Whoa!
You said your
antimatter-histamine
would cure me.
- Yeah, I did say that,
didn't I?
- [growling]
You lied to me.
You said you could fix me.
Now I'll fix you.
[grunting]
- Breacher, stop!
Your vibe blasts don't work.
And they're not gonna work.
- Why not?
- Because of your age.
I should have told
you earlier.
It's just I know how special
our powers are,
and you were so happy at the
thought of having them back.
And I miss your daughter.
I just wanted to
see her again.
I'm sorry, Josh.
- [grunts]
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
[whispers] I hate you.
[electric whooshing]
- You did the right thing.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Just wish he knew that.
- Clifford is lying to you.
He is drugging you
with sedative tears
to keep you idle.
[crying] Please.
Please, remember.
Escape.
New lemonade recipe.
Save.
Already exists?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Please don't forget.
He's lying to you.
He's drugging you.
He's a monster.
You must escape.
- You always save it
under the same name.
- [whispering]
Escape now.
- Every time,
you discover it.
It's quite clever, really.
I would expect nothing
less from you.
- How many times have
I been through this?
- Too many.
But that is of no concern.
Because with tears
from the Weeper
mixed with Dominic Lanse's
powers...
I can alter your memory.
- So that's why you
created the Weeper.
You didn't need
a potential host.
He was...
- For you. Yes.
I knew that
the same thing in you
that I fell in love with
had the potential
to destroy us.
Your humanity.
I couldn't let that get
in the way
of us achieving our goal.
The Enlightenment.
- Clifford, I am your wife...
- And I love you.
But you are nothing
without me.
- This is an interesting place
to hang out.
- You come here to suck the fun
out of being benched?
- I...
No, I came for your help
actually.
- You want help from the guy
who can't take anything
seriously?
- Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been
so quick to judge.
But with DeVoe...
so many steps ahead of us,
it just...
To see you joking around
in the middle of this
just made me feel like you
weren't taking it seriously.
- I know this is serious.
I watched...
I watched Izzy die
in front of me.
I'm scared out of my mind.
- Well, you know, you got
an odd way of showing it.
- Yeah, well not everybody
grew up with a super dad
like Joe West who makes it easy
to talk about your feelings.
When I was ten years old,
my dad walked out
on me and my mom.
And I was terrified.
But my mom,
she was even more afraid.
So, you know, I just
started making jokes.
Started doing stupid gags
and funny bits
and whoopee cushions.
Anything to push her fear away.
And the thing is,
after a while I started to push
my fear away too.
- I had no idea, Ralph.
- It's not that I don't care
about beating DeVoe.
It's not that I don't care
about being a great hero.
It's just that ever since then,
anytime that I'm afraid,
I either hide...
Or I make jokes.
- Barry, we found Null.
Central City Museum.
- So what do you say?
You want to get off the bench?
I really could use your help.
- Well, if doo-ty calls.
You get it?
- Yeah.
Let's just go,
all right?
[indistinct chatter]
[classical music playing]
♪ ♪
- Now, this is my kind
of party.
- Listen up, people!
Anything that shines,
shimmers, or sparkles
goes in the bag.
Ooh-oh, I love me
some sapphires.
- You're out of your mind
if you think I'm giving
this to you.
- Oh, give it to me?
No, no, no.
No, no.
There's no need for that.
No.
I'll just take it.
- Oh...
[whimpering]
- And the rest of you,
♪ sparklies ♪
- [screams]
- [grunts]
- Just hold on, all right?
Just hold on.
[dramatic music]
It's over, Null.
- So, back again.
Oh, with a friend.
- A good friend, actually.
We hang out on the weekends.
I know where he lives...
- No getaway cars this time.
- Right.
No cars.
But there are an awful lot
of passengers.
[crowd screaming]
- Oh, my God, she's gonna send
everyone into the atmosphere.
- Allen, you gotta get everyone
out of there right now.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- All right, that's everyone.
Where is she?
- Whoa!
- No!
- Lookin' fly, Flash!
Back to business.
- Oh, God!
- [straining]
Aah...aah!
- Guys! I can't reach him!
- Cisco, you have to
breach him somewhere.
- He's too high
in the atmosphere.
I don't have aim like that.
- Let Ralph improvise.
all: What?
- What?
Barry:Yes.
Just do something
Dibny-esque.
Be your own hero.
Just do it fast.
- Uh, Dibny-esque.
Right.
Um.
- All about that bling.
[metallic clicking]
Barry:Ralph!
- That was your plan?
He's gonna fall to his death.
- I know what I'm doing.
Barry:Any time, Ralph!
- 10,000 feet.
He's falling fast.
Now 5,000 feet.
- [screaming]
- [muttering]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
Barry:Oh...ah...
- Ralph did it.
- [laughs] Nice work, Ralph.
Nice work.
[panting]
[farting noise]
- Classy.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- [chuckles]
[farting continues]
- Ralph.
- All right,
Null's in the pipeline.
She's not too happy about it.
- Well, she's a lot safer there
than she is on her own.
- Just one more bus meta
out there.
- Better find him
before DeVoe does.
- Where's Harry? Isn't he
supposed to be working on it?
- He grumbled something
about something and then left.
- I'm fluent in Harry grumble.
He said he was
gonna work on his cat,
or he was making himself
a turkey wrap.
- Well, I'm gonna
head over to CCPD,
do some more digging
on this Edwin Gauss.
Ralph.
Why did
a scared-sounding Earl Cox
call me saying
he was clearing your tab?
- [laughs] Uh, I...
[exhales] I have no idea.
That's really weird.
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys, would you help me
in the, uh, Speed Lab?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Work on some improv?
- Yeah.
- Ha.
- You were great out there
tonight, man.
- Thank you.
I had a lot of help.
And I had a great teacher.
- You helped me realize that
I can't always take
everything so seriously.
Even when it comes to Thinker.
- Wait a second.
Are you telling me
that I, Ralph Dibny,
taught Barry Allen, superhero
extraordinaire, a lesson?
What could this mean?
- Means you're a great hero.
And you make this team better
by being on it.
- [deep voice] Ah,
the circle is now complete.
When I came here I was
but the learner.
Now I am the master.
- It's also good to be humble.
- But how can I be humble...
[whooshing sound]
When I am swollen with pride?
- Cisky!
- Ah...jumpin' jellyfish!
I like your new threads.
- Yeah.
[sighs]
I went back to my earth.
Saw my reflection in my knife.
I saw an older man.
- I'm curious.
Have you never looked
in a mirror before?
- I'm not a teenage girl.
- Okay, you're not
a teenage girl.
- But I realized...
time to hang up my coat.
This is my new uniform.
Like it?
- Yeah.
Retirement suits you.
So, what do you do
with all this time?
- There's a dragon farm
on Earth-47
that I've always wanted
to visit.
- A dragon farm?
[laughing] Okay.
Get your Khaleesi on.
- I'm not a Khaleesi.
- Okay, you're not a Khaleesi.
- But I just wanted
to tell you, Cisky,
good-bye forever.
Oh, wait!
Just one more thing.
Now that I'm retired,
there's an opening
at the Collection Agency.
I would like you
to replace me.
- Wait, I'm...I'm confused.
- You want to see
my daughter more.
Work with her.
Together you and Cynthia
could be an unstoppable duo.
So what do you say, Vibe?
You want to be
the new Breacher?
[pensive music]
- [clears throat]
- How was your rest,
my love?
- Wonderful.
I've never felt more
rejuvenated
and ready to realize
our dream.
- [coughing]
- Clifford.
- [inhales shakily]
The added combination
of dark matter
from all our subject metas is
overwhelming this host's body.
- How long do we have?
- At the present rate,
exactly one week's time.
- No, I will not allow it.
It may be possible to adjust
the biomass index,
recalibrate
the energy distribution...
extend
your current host's life.
Odd.
There are already plans
for such an adjustment
partially designed.
- I attempted
the same course of action.
- Well, you got quite
a good start.
I will be able to complete
the designs in under an hour.
Rest, my love.
I will handle everything.
- You always do.
And then when you
complete your work,
we will continue on our journey
to find the remaining
two bus metas.
Team Flash has captured
subject 11.
Now it's time for us to act.
[dark tense music]
[soft edgy music]
♪ ♪
[electronic whine]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
- Good evening, Dr. Wells.
It's been 1,078 days
since we last spoke.
How can I be of service?
- Hello, Gideon.
A lot has changed since then.
- Greg, move your head.