[The Flash theme playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[If You Leave Me Now"
by Chicago playing]
[dinging]
[stomach growling]
- [server] Have a brilliant day.
- [man] Yeah, thank you.
You too.
Morning. What can I get you?
- Where's curly-hair lady?
- Sara?
She's out sick. Or at least,
- that's what she says.
- Oh.
[whispers] She's
got a new boyfriend.
What can I get you?
Usually it's my usual and she usually
has it ready because I'm usually late.
Well, don't keep me in suspense.
Um, it's a PB and
BRHC on a roll.
Okay, so...
- "PB" would be peanut butter, I'm assuming?
- Yes.
"BR," bananas, raisins. "H,"
honey. "C," cheese on a roll.
Aren't you blessed
with a fast metabolism.
Are you running a
marathon or something?
You know, my sister ran a
marathon once, God rest her soul.
She's not dead.
She's just exhausted.
- We get it, Sharon. You ran.
- [cell phone ringing]
But everyone has to
work in the morning.
Yeah, I have to go to
work, three minutes ago.
And, sorry, I'm in sort of
a rush for the sandwich.
You can't rush a
good sandwich, dude.
[cell phone ringing]
[Barry] Alfred,
really can't talk.
Good morning, Mr. Allen.
No, I'm late.
And I'm starving, and
curly-haired girl isn't here
and her name is Sara,
and she has a boyfriend.
We have a situation
at Gotham General.
A robbery gone wrong.
This is the middle
of the morning.
Why is our bat-friend
even awake?
Call Superman.
That was my first thought.
Sadly, he's otherwise engaged.
- active volcano in Central America.
- [Barry] Classic.
What about Diana?
My other first thought.
Rather annoyingly,
she's not picking up.
How many first thoughts, exactly, did
you have before you first thought of me?
[server] ...never about her.
- This is about you.
- Hi, sorry. Is my sandwich...
[server] I learned my lesson
on the boat last year.
Stuff my sister comes out
with when she's drunk.
Personal comments about
my mom's friends as well,
which I think is what
I say about her...
[pulses, electricity crackling]
[The Flash theme playing]
[pulses]
[electricity crackling]
- [girl] Oh, my God!
- [music stops]
Flash!
- Hi. Thank you.
- I love you.
- You seem very nice also.
- Oh, my God!
- No way!
- I think I'm gonna die!
Patching you into Mr. Wayne.
- No, please don't.
- [line rings]
Oh, my God.
Sorry if this sounds weird, but are
you actively eating that candy bar?
Maybe you could throw it to me?
- In the name of justice.
- [girl] Yes, yes.
[Bruce] I need you
here now, Barry.
Hi, Bruce. Yes, I'm...
coming.
[The Flash theme resumes]
[electricity crackling]
["Bad Fun" by The Cult playing]
[song ends]
[people yelling in panic]
[rumbling]
[man] No!
No, no!
Bruce, this is a huge mess.
Why aren't you here?
[alarm blaring]
[Batman theme playing]
[tires screeching]
[The Flash on comms] Bruce, why does
it sound like you're fleeing the scene?
Falcone's idiot kid decided to
try to play in the big leagues.
He put a crew together and broke
into the lab at Gotham General.
Stole a highly deadly virus.
I intercepted them, but
they blasted their way out.
You can handle the
hospital, Barry.
Somebody has to save the rest of
the world, so I was gonna do that.
If you don't mind.
Sounds about right, Bruce.
[beeps]
"Thanks for saving me
from the sinkhole, Flash."
Barry, gas and water
pipes ruptured.
In the basement.
Right.
On it. [sighs]
[glass cracking]
[nurse] Can you open it?
- I think it's locked.
- It's jammed.
God, it's not working!
Oh, please!
[building rumbling]
[cooing]
[The Flash] Look, Alfred.
I've come to accept
that I'm essentially the
janitor of the Justice League.
Which sucks.
But I've come to accept it.
But...
I can't help but notice...
that it always seems
to be a bat-mess...
that I'm cleaning up.
- Right this way. Eyes forward.
- Yes.
- Stay together, now.
- Yeah, I know, right?
Look out!
[tires screeching]
- Wow. Whoa.
- What?
[sirens wailing]
If my calculations are correct,
and history will prove
they usually are,
the foundational damage is about to
cause the collapse of the east wing.
- [The Flash] East wing's fine.
- [nurse] All right, I got you.
Which is good because
my speed is lagging.
- [beeping]
- Running on empty, Alfred.
- [low rumbling]
- Do you hear that?
That's my stomach.
[rumbling]
No, no.
It's the collapsing east wing.
[screaming]
[continues screaming]
[Alfred] Barry, 30th floor.
There's a baby...
Shower.
[choral music playing]
[beeping]
[baby crying]
[crying]
[beeps]
[growling]
[nurse screaming]
Oh!
[barking]
[screaming]
Mr. Allen,
you've made me very proud.
And a lot of mothers very happy.
- [microwave dings]
- Oh!
[cooing]
[screaming]
Yeah.
Okay.
I understand that these events
can be psychologically scarring.
You should seek the services of
a mental health professional.
The Justice League is not
very good at that part yet.
Trust me.
God.
[tires screeching]
[Batman theme playing]
- Shake him off!
- [tires screeching]
[grunting]
[yells]
[cries out]
If that briefcase
falls into the water,
it could wipe out half
of Gotham by lunchtime.
[yells]
- [Batman] Damn it.
- Please don't drop me.
Oh, God, no. Please,
please don't.
No!
[Wonder Woman theme playing]
Sorry I'm late.
Watch your step.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Nice suit.
Looking good, Flash.
Oh, uh... Thank... Uh...
And you...
are welcome.
My ego's far too big to say
"thank you" to someone else.
Hmm.
I developed this...
all-powerful persona to compensate
for my childhood trauma...
I, too, have childhood trauma.
[man] Batman seems crazy.
-The Lasso of Truth...
-Billion dollar. She's the mother...
[Wonder Woman] never gets old.
I'd do a lot better just giving all my money away. Yes,
if I really wanted to end crime, I should end poverty.
I know sex exists.
I've just never experienced it.
Damn it.
Well...
I have to run.
Yeah.
Always a pleasure.
The sex thing was a metaphor...
for gothic literature.
There was just no way
to recover from that.
Just let it go.
Well, I'd really love to stay
and clean up more mess...
but this little superhero
needs his breakfast.
Goodbye, Flash.
Yeah. Bye, Batman.
Well done, Mr. Wayne.
Will you be home
for breakfast, sir?
- [Batarang whirring]
- [Al Falcone groans]
Yes, I think so.
The road to destruction.
This was never about her.
This is about you.
You have to stop
living in the past.
Now, was that fast
enough for you?
[student] Morning, professor...
[indistinct chatter]
Ah, look who's here.
[Barry] Shut up, Albert.
Every day. I don't know
how you do it, Barry.
What'd you, like,
crawl here, bro?
- Is he mad?
- Well, you're getting fired.
-[Albert] You're getting murdered.
-Oh, no, no, no.
Let me guess.
Your alarm clock didn't go off.
- No...
- Oh, your dog ate your alarm clock.
Your alarm clock ate your keys.
Your keys' grandmother died,
and they need a personal day.
- It was none of those things.
- What was it this time, Barry?
It was, um, something else
that was far less outlandish.
And I know I missed
the meeting...
but I'd still really like to present
these case files for potential review.
I think we rushed these cases.
- We need to reopen them.
- Oh! Rushed?
We got a backlog six months deep,
and you want us to move slower?
You need to focus your motion.
Do the work, close
the case, move on.
[sighs]
You have a lot of
potential, Barry.
You shouldn't still be getting
me coffee after all these years.
You're right.
That's... That's true.
Go get me a coffee.
[laughs]
- Two sugars? Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
[knocking on door]
You're gonna love this.
I'm very satisfied with the
ruling in the Johnson case.
The evidence our lab analyzed...
was more than sufficient
to be conclusive.
- I'm still working that evidence.
- Because of the diligence
and hard work and focus...
Barry was still working
on that evidence. [laughs]
Think if it were up to you
that we'd still be scraping
Ted Bundy's molars.
You know what? I'm so happy
you find this all so hilarious,
but we are dealing with real
people's lives, people's families.
And I don't think you can
grasp the gravity of that.
So, why don't you
leave me alone?
- [woman] Barry Allen?
- Iris West.
You...
know my full name also.
Yes, from school.
Aw, Barry, you didn't tell us
you had a friend from school.
- We actually didn't know that Barry had a friend.
- Wow.
[Albert] Yeah, what
does that make it now?
- One?
- One.
[laughs] You guys are so...
Um, bye, you guys.
Okay. Oh, my God.
That was just...
Um...
They're not really my friends.
They're my work friends.
Do you work here?
Yes, I do.
God, it's been a long time, huh?
Hmm.
I feel like we saw each other...
like a few years ago, right?
No, because...
we haven't seen
each other since...
college.
Ah.
Maybe I was just
thinking about you.
Well, I'm really
glad I ran into you.
- Yeah.
Your father's appeal
is tomorrow, right?
Yeah. How...
Sorry, how do you
know about that?
I'm covering it for the paper.
Oh.
How is he holding up?
Um...
Are you asking for the paper?
- No, I'm asking as a friend.
- Oh.
Although I'm sure the public
would want to know as well.
Well...
my only official comment
is that my dad is innocent.
Right.
I mean, no one...
would want to believe that their
father killed their mother.
What do you mean, "believe"?
My dad shouldn't be in jail.
My mom should be alive. It's
not about what I believe.
- It's about what the truth is.
- Right. No, yes, that's...
Oh, my God. That's
what I meant.
Right.
Sorry, I have no official
comment at this time.
[melancholy music playing]
[phone rings]
[automated voice] You
have a collect call
from the Iron
Heights Penitentiary.
- Do you wish to accept?
- Yes.
- Hey, Dad.
- [Henry Allen] Hey, Barry.
- How ya doing?
- I'm fine.
- You getting out much?
- Yeah.
Well, no. Uh, no.
But I, um, I ran into
an old college friend...
Iris West, today.
Didn't you have a
monster crush on her?
Well, she have a boyfriend?
- Why don't you ask her out?
- Dad, I, um...
I had a friend run the old security
camera footage from the store...
through this new
program he's developed.
And it's crystal clear now.
It's just...
you never look up, Dad.
You can't see your face.
So, without new evidence
to support your alibi...
we're just gonna need to start
thinking about the next appeal.
No, uh-uh. You need to stop
worrying about your old man.
Do that, you might actually
have time for a girlfriend.
But Dad, I don't want...
We've done this before.
This was a last-ditch effort...
and we'll go through
the motions tomorrow.
I'm okay, really.
You know, sometimes I even think it's
probably easier for me to be in here
than out there...
without her.
'Cause this way, I can
imagine she's alive...
out there living her life.
Barry?
You there?
Yeah, I'm here, Dad.
Hey, remember that sauce
she'd make on Sundays?
The whole house would
smell like basil, tomatoes.
And she'd put on my
sweats and start singing.
[somber music playing]
Yeah, what was that song?
I loved that song.
Remember that part.
[kid Barry] It's not fair.
[Nora] What's not fair, Monkey?
This question is stupid.
How many calculations can you
think of with an answer of 24?
There are a bajillion answers.
How am I supposed
to fit them all?
You are right. There are a
bajillion answers to this question.
Not every problem
has a solution.
Sometimes you just
have to let go.
[mild music playing on speakers]
Give your brain a rest and help
me make the pasta. Come on.
No. [curses in Spanish]
Henry?
[speaking Spanish]
I need you to do me a favor.
- I don't do favors.
- Okay.
Barry needs you
to do him a favor.
Oh, Barry! Yeah, anything.
I need another can of tomatoes.
You have a can of tomatoes.
I need another one.
I thought you guys went
to the store this morning.
But I forgot the tomatoes.
This looks way more fun.
Let's just let Barry
go to the store.
You drive, right, Squirm?
- What? No.
- Getting so big.
You can do anything.
Look at ya.
You're getting gray, actually.
- Green can, not the blue one, okay?
- Got it.
Blue can, not the
green one, right?
- No! Green can, not the blue one.
- What?
[upbeat Spanish song
playing on speakers]
Oh, God.
[song continues]
She's gonna start singing. Run!
Run, Barry!
[singing in Spanish with song]
I love you, Monkey.
I love you more.
I loved you first.
[both laugh]
[objects clattering]
[Nora grunting]
[Nora screaming]
[Henry] Nora?
Barry!
[Nora groaning]
[Henry] Barry! Barry!
Call 911 now!
[Henry on phone] Barry?
Barry?
Don't worry about tomorrow.
We always knew it
was a long shot...
[line disconnects]
Dad?
[automated voice] Your call with Iron
Heights Penitentiary has been terminated.
[breathing rapidly]
[somber music playing]
[tempo speeds up]
- [tempo increases]
- [yelling]
[music stops]
[gasping]
[distorting]
[slow motion scream]
[dramatic music playing]
[Iris] Barry Allen?
[overlapping voices
speaking indistinctly]
[David] ...evidence our lab...
You need to focus your motion.
Do the work...
She promised...
[server] Now, was that
fast enough for you?
[baby crying]
[nurse screaming]
[overlapping voices
wind down and stop]
[Bruce] So, you're saying
you went back in time?
- [Barry] Mm-hmm.
- Like in Pozharnov?
[Barry with mouth full] Yeah, like in
Pozharnov, except, but Pozharnov was a second.
This time I went
back a whole day.
[Bruce] So, let's imagine...
that it is, in fact,
possible for you to run...
faster than the
speed of light...
and in so doing,
travel back in time.
It still would be...
wildly irresponsible.
I knew you were gonna say this.
Yes, because, Barry, if you
were to go into the past,
any interaction you have with
your parents or yourself,
you step on the
wrong blade of grass,
you have no idea what the
consequences to that could be.
No, I know. The
butterfly effect, right?
- Yes.
- I get it. But Bruce...
I could fix things.
You could also
destroy everything.
I could save her.
I could save both of them. I...
I could save your parents.
[somber music playing]
Barry, these scars we have...
make us who we are.
We're not meant to
go back and fix them.
And there's nothing broken with
you that needs to be fixed.
Take it from an old guy
who's made a lot of mistakes.
Don't live your past.
Live your life.
Don't let your
tragedy define you.
What if it's supposed
to define me?
Your tragedy made you a hero.
And also made me alone.
We could hang out.
I mean, do you wanna get a bite?
Like, I'm still hungry.
Not this time.
Maybe some other time.
Yeah.
[Iris] Nice ride.
You have fancy friends.
Yeah, it was an Uber.
Exec.
Look, Iris, I really can't
talk about the case at all.
I'm not here as a reporter.
Can we talk?
- Come on in.
- [chuckles awkwardly]
I'm not gonna lie. It's a lot
tidier in here than I expected.
- Yeah? Yeah, well, um...
- Yeah. [laughs]
I'm a pretty tidy person.
[loud clattering]
- Can I offer you a drink?
- Sure.
I'll take a beer.
[Barry] Hmm.
[muffled clinking]
Beers, beers, beers.
I keep 'em in my fridge.
Thanks.
Sure.
Look, I feel really bad
about earlier.
I should've been more sensitive.
And, um, I probably could've
been less sensitive.
I mean, I can't imagine
what you've been through.
It's like you lost both
parents in one day.
I did.
I lost my mom to a tragedy,
and I lost my dad to the
failures of the justice system.
Is that why you got
into criminal forensics?
To try and fix the system?
Yeah.
Yeah, to fix it.
There's gotta be a
way to fix it, right?
I mean, that's kinda why I
got into journalism, too.
I could make it right if I
could just go back somehow
and warn them without them
knowing that I'd warned them.
I... thinking like that's
gonna... [chuckle softly]
drive you crazy.
"If I could just
go back in time...
and stop the guy
who did it." It's...
No, I can't do that, 'cause
that's way too much interaction.
[chuckles]
My dad wasn't even at home.
My mom sent him to go
get a can of tomatoes.
I think whoever broke into the
house thought it was empty.
And then my mom was in there
with the knife in her hand
and things went bad,
just this absurd
chain of events.
And it's like, this footage should've
finally supported my dad's alibi.
But instead...
three lives ruined
for a can of tomatoes.
Oh, my God.
What?
Well, that could be it.
If my mom doesn't forget the
tomatoes in the first place,
then he never leaves
and she never dies.
No one would even
have to see me.
Bruce said no interaction.
This is no interaction.
This is just quick
in, quick out,
back to the present, like
I was never even there.
That's how I fix it.
Oh, my God, Iris.
- Hmm?
- Thank you, so much.
- This has been great.
- Oh.
Um... I'm sorry.
I... I have to leave.
Okay. Right.
- Uh...
- [door closes]
I had a really great time, by
the way. We should do this again.
- [door closes]
- [objects crashing]
[Wonder Woman] Kal-El,
son of Krypton.
[Aquaman] This is a bad idea.
[overlapping voices]
[Bruce] So, you're fast.
[woman] Your dad's a murderer.
Your dad's a murderer.
Call 911 now!
Now!
[overlapping voices stop]
[crying]
[crying continues]
[exhales]
[sentimental music playing]
Hi, Mom.
Don't forget the tomatoes.
See you soon.
[crying]
Please work.
[kids]
[Nora] Happy Birthday, Barry.
- [Henry] Go, Barry, hurry up.
- [kids] Go!
[teacher] Congratulations
to the class of 2013!
[Nora, distorted]
I love you so much.
[grunting]
- [grunts]
- [The Flash yells]
[birds chirping]
[dog barking]
[mild music playing on speakers]
[startled shriek]
[speaks in Spanish] Monkey!
What are you wearing?
[Henry] Is that
Barry? And he's early?
What universe is this?
You've cut your hair.
Now you can see your eyes.
- You look terrible.
- Henry!
- You look old.
- You look beautiful, baby.
What are they doing
to you over there?
Leave him alone. He's perfect.
Come here.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I love you more.
I loved you first.
Go take a shower and change.
You smell like a
boot. Go, go, go.
[sighs]
"Old," seriously?
Well, no, I mean like mature.
He's at that age, he
wants to look old.
He, you know, gets
into bars that way.
How can I help?
Mm. Hey, Mom,
how was your day?
How was your month,
or your last 18 years?
Or that's a weird question...
'cause I was here.
But obviously, we share
those memories together.
Or I don't know, maybe we
could make some new memories.
Like we could go to the
aquarium, or the circus,
or to the park and you
could push me on a swing.
That's also weird
because I'm an adult now,
so I'd probably motivate
my own motion on a swing.
So, how was it this
week? How's school?
At school was... is good.
- Mm.
- School's been great.
I've just been working
really hard there on my...
studies.
Did you ask out
that girl from econ?
I know freshman year is about
going out, meeting people, okay?
Exploring things.
Experimenting.
[muffled vocalizing]
[Nora] But you have
to be very careful.
Oh, shit.
I... have to shit.
Outside.
[muffled yell]
[grunting]
Help!
Shh! Why are you here?
What year is it?
- No, no, no.
- Help!
That's my face.
You stole my face.
Think I'm having a
mushroom flashback?
- Is that a thing?
- How old are you?
Eighteen.
Whoa.
This is mad trippy.
So, we're, like, in the future.
No, wait. This is
not trippy, dude.
This is catastrophic. And no, we're not in the
future. I was supposed to be back in the present,
but I'm still in the past.
And there's not supposed
to be two of me.
You and I are not supposed to be
occupying the same reality at all,
let alone interacting.
I just can't believe I'm a
superhero who time travels...
No, no, no. You
are not anything.
Which is good. You don't want
to be a superhero. It's scary.
And I get bug splatter
in my teeth all the time.
Awesome.
Hey, do the thing again.
No, we don't have time.
- Mom!
- Shh!
What are you doing?
You're gonna tattle now?
- Do the thing.
- Fine.
[laughing]
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Happy?
Now undo it.
[sentimental music playing]
[muffled] I can't, I can't.
Ow.
[Nora] Barry, are
you okay up there?
[both] We're fine! I'm fine!
[Nora] Okay, Monkey.
So, do you have like a
plane that goes underwater?
Or like a boat that can fly?
How old are you, like 40?
Okay, you don't stop talking.
It's not charming. It's
abrasive and exhausting.
And, oh, my God. I am starting
to realize what people mean.
Just...
do me a favor
and promise me that meeting me
isn't gonna screw up space-time.
Broski...
I got you.
Shit, I'm in so much trouble.
What do you mean?
What do I do?
I could drug you.
Yeah, I could drug you,
and then you'd pass
out, you'd wake up
and you'd forget that
anything ever happened.
And it wouldn't be wrong,
right? Because you're me.
No! I mean, we shouldn't.
- Please don't... drug me.
- No.
No. Because here's the thing,
and I thought about it before.
I don't want to be drugged.
But I'm sure we can
think of another way.
Let's put on our
Barry thinking caps
and think of a
different solution
for memory loss.
Also, I'm a green belt...
in the capoeira,
and I have extensively
studied wrestler,
and I could just go
frickin' lunatic on you.
Besides, I have
a date tonight...
[speech stops]
Okay.
How hard do you have to hit
someone to make them forget stuff?
If I hit you in the past,
will it hurt me in the future?
Wait. You say you
have a date tonight?
Yeah. Wait, what
were you doing?
Uh, nothing. Who's
your date with?
This super babe
in my econ class.
- Iris West?
- Oh, my God!
Do we marry her?
You're going on a
date with her tonight?
That's why I need
Mom to do my laundry.
You don't even do
your own laundry?
Do you?
Okay.
- I'm actually gonna go.
- What do you mean?
Enjoy your life. Do you.
Change literally nothing.
- Um, I'll see you again never.
- I have a few more questions, though.
We have so much to
learn from each other.
[thunder rumbles]
Oh, great.
Well, you're leaving me.
And now the storm's
gonna ruin my date.
What day is it today?
Uh... Uh...
Sunday?
No, the date.
It's September 29th.
Shit.
This storm, this is the day.
- What day?
- The day I got my powers.
The day you get your powers.
- Powers?
- Listen...
I can't tell you why I
traveled back in time,
and I can't tell
you what I changed.
But, essentially, in
my version of reality,
I ended up interning at
the Central City Crime Lab
in my freshman year, and
that's where it happened.
Well, happens.
Tonight, September 29, the
accident that gives me my powers.
And if you're not there...
in 30 minutes...
then you won't get the powers.
Which means I don't
get the powers, maybe?
And then, that would
mean that I lose my way
of getting back in time
in the first place,
and then I literally have
no idea what happens.
Powers?
[thunder crashes]
[laughs gleefully]
Wait, but what about
our date tonight?
She might be our future wife.
There might not be a future...
if you don't come with me...
right now.
[thunder cracks]
Eight minutes.
How are we gonna to get
inside? What are you doing?
Would you stop whining?
This is gonna feel kinda weird.
- [vibrating]
- [grunting shakily]
[dramatic music playing]
We walk through the door.
[shushing]
[softly] Yes, it's okay.
It's called phasing.
Come on.
I love phasing.
[men speaking distantly]
Uh-huh.
Everybody moves.
[suspenseful music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[voice trembles]
[laughs nervously]
Well... this is it.
This is where I was sitting.
And actually, let me
take this for you.
Thank you.
Okay, I had just
opened those windows...
to clear out the fumes.
Right around now.
And I was sitting in that chair,
and I was right under
this shelf of chemicals.
And that's when
the lightning hits.
Wait.
- I get hit by lightning?
- No, no, no.
You don't get hit by lightning.
Okay, 'cause for a second
I thought you said...
The lightning hits
the chemicals...
which then you get bathed in,
- and that's what electrocutes you.
- Okay,
- but I don't want to be electrocuted, though.
- Sit down.
- No, you sit down.
- I already have the powers!
You already have the powers!
Exactly!
I am not getting
struck by lightning!
[intense operatic music playing]
[music crescendos]
[grunts]
[alarm blaring]
It worked.
[gags]
[groans]
It looks like you lost a tooth.
[groaning]
[crying] Oh.
- No?
- You lost a tooth.
[tense music playing]
All right. We gotta go.
[guard 1] What have we got?
[guard 2] The alarms
in the sterile lab.
[guard 1] Go check it.
Securing the entrance.
We've gotta phase.
[softly] Phase, phasing.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[straining]
Oh... [groans]
[breathes deeply]
[dramatic music plays]
- [music stops]
- [shoes squeaking]
[yells]
Shit!
[suspenseful music builds]
I'm slow.
[past Barry] Oh. Oh.
[Barry] Why is your
place so much nicer
- than I expected it to be?
- [past Barry] You like it?
Mom had to help decorate.
You know Mom.
Right, yeah. Classic Mom.
Classic Mom.
[grunts]
Hmm.
- What a day.
- Barry,
the accident gave you powers,
but took mine away.
So, I don't know how I get back.
Without access to
the Speed Force,
I don't know how I ever leave.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
- I might be stuck.
- Wait.
I have powers now?
Yeah, but...
- you... No, no, no.
- [gasps]
[squealing excitedly]
[objects clatter]
Holy speedballs.
Okay, I know this is
incredibly exciting,
because I went through it.
Speedy Gonzales!
Yes, I've done it
many times myself.
- You can't just start...
- [laughs, yells]
Shit.
["Alright" by
Supergrass playing]
[music distorting]
[grunting]
[yells]
[horn honking]
Oh, my...
[horn honks]
[tires screeching]
[comical music playing]
[music instruments sounding]
Ahh!
[horns honking]
[screaming]
[grunts]
- [horse whinnies]
- Okay, I'm leaving!
[comical music continues]
[power shuts down]
[people screaming]
[officer over speaker]
Put your hands up.
[music stops]
[distant sirens wailing]
[distant explosions]
[muffled clattering]
What did you do?
Nothing. Why?
Barry...
I could've told you about
the clothes. It's friction.
You run too fast, and regular
fabrics are gonna burn up.
It's the same reason why you can't
move people very far at hyperspeed.
That broccoli looks rotten.
Look, some things you can move.
Like, you can move,
for instance, a microwave.
But you can't move
something like, say...
- a baby.
- Barry,
it's like I've never
eaten anything before.
Everything has this vivid
flavor. Try a little.
Just take a little bite.
That's bad, isn't it?
[laughs] Yeah, this is not
good. No, I was kidding.
- [gags]
- I'm amazing. We're amazing.
I'm so hungry.
Hey, wait.
I wanna try that phasing
thing. How do I do that?
You don't. Not yet.
Okay? It's very complicated.
Takes a long time to train your
body to be able to speed up
whilst your molecules slow
down enough to pass through
the molecular structure
of solid objects...
[muffled thud]
[woman downstairs screams]
[woman] Get out of here!
- [muffled footsteps running]
- [sighs]
[door opens]
You've gotta start letting
me finish my sentences.
Are we always this sleepy?
And hungry and naked?
Well, the first two, yes.
The third one, no. I've
figured that part out.
And honestly, if
we're gonna do this
there's a lot I'm gonna
have to explain to you.
So, a good place
to start, I guess,
is that, yeah, the original suit
- was actually made out of this polysynth...
- [snoring]
Or we'll
pick this up tomorrow.
[past Barry] So, the
suit is inside the ring?
- Yeah.
- What?
And I can have this?
No, you can't have
it. You can borrow it
so you don't kill yourself
using your powers.
[whispering gibberish]
You're gonna push this button
and the silk molecules are gonna
uncoil, absorbing atmospheric gases
and expanding the
suit to full size.
Ready?
[clinks]
[dramatic music playing]
[laughing]
It was so tiny...
You're supposed to put it
on before it hits the floor.
What, like change...
right here in front of you?
There's no one even here
anyway, Barry. Come on...
- [exclaims] Whoo, man.
- Tight.
It hurts.
You know where it hurts?
- In my dick.
- Okay. I know, I know,
but I don't need to know.
- Sorry, can we move on?
- Mm-hmm.
Here's what I'm thinking.
If I can train you
to move like I do,
then we can re-create
the Chronobowl.
Chronobowl?
In the Speed Force.
Speed Force?
-And then maybe we can find some way to get me back to the future.
-Back to the Future. Yes!
Eric Stoltz
is chur boy in that movie.
What an embodied performance.
You mean Michael J. Fox?
Back to the Future?
-Yeah, in the movie Back to the Future?
-[woman] Oh, my God! [people clamoring]
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
You need to take
the suit off now.
- Thank God.
- [distant sirens wailing]
[man on TV] ...reported
seeing a mysterious object
hovering above the
Australian seaboard.
- We've obtained footage from the sighting...
- Zod.
- and as you can see, the object...
- [past Barry] "Zod"?
- appears to be a flying ship of some sort.
- What's a zod?
[on TV] According to US
government officials,
satellite data
has confirmed the
presence of a spacecraft.
- We'll be sure...
- [past Barry yelps]
[static]
My name is General Zod.
I come from a world
far from yours.
For some time, your world
- has sheltered one of my citizens.
- No, no, no.
- This can't be happening.
- I request that you return this individual...
- [Barry] Not now.
- To my custody.
What's happening?
For reasons unknown...
Zod's looking for Superman.
What's a superman?
[police siren chirps]
[Barry] Superman is an
alien who lives on Earth.
I'm assuming still incognito.
But, yeah, he's an alien,
and he's very powerful,
and he's just the best.
And then Zod is an alien
from the same planet,
also very powerful,
but he's just the worst.
And Zod came here to find Clark.
- Wait, who's Clark?
- Clark is Superman.
- Oh. Okay.
- But then
Zod also tried to terraform the
planet with this World Engine thing,
and Superman stopped
him eventually,
but not before Zod killed
thousands of people.
- Yeesh.
- And at the time,
there was nothing
I could do, I've...
Wait, you...
You were there?
Yeah, I had just
gotten my powers.
[people screaming]
And I was still putting some
finishing touches on my suit.
[people screaming]
This thing, Zod's World Engine,
it started destroying
Metropolis, so I just went there
and I started trying
to save people.
[boy] Daddy?
[man] Listen to me!
Run away!
[Barry] There was
this kid, and I...
I got him, but then...
I couldn't get his dad.
Daddy!
[solemn music playing]
[metal groaning]
It was all I could do,
save that one kid.
Only Superman could stop Zod.
But not in time to
save those people.
And now it's about
to happen again.
But...
if I can find the
entire Justice League,
Superman and the
rest of the band...
Right.
Then maybe I can
prevent the whole thing
from ever even happening at all.
- Um, give me your laptop.
- Okay.
What is that smell?
Ugh. Could be anything.
Honestly.
Who's that?
Oh. That's Gary. That's
the smell. It's...
- [snoring]
- Don't worry. He's breezy.
[Barry] We can do this.
Uh, let's see, Victor Stone,
Gotham City University.
[woman screams, muttering]
Oh, this is my roommate, Patty.
Patty...
is your roommate?
And that's her
boyfriend, Albert.
What's up?
[in sing-song] Good morning.
Oh, sorry. And, uh, guys...
This is my cousin.
Barry.
[past Patty] Whoa.
I'm starving.
Okay.
Victor Stone, Gotham
City University.
Yes. Here he is.
Victor Stone, star
quarterback for the Knight...
Shit, okay.
He's not Cyborg yet.
Wonder Woman.
Wonder Woman!
Las Vegas residency.
Illusions, juggling, and zebras.
No. That is not Diana.
- Aquaman.
- Aquaman?
Is that like a super mermaid?
[Barry] No, Albert,
he's not a super mermaid.
Okay? He's half
Atlantean, half human
with superhuman strength who can
control marine life with his mind.
So, like a super
mermaid? [plays keyboard]
No, Albert!
[laughs] That is
what you described.
[Barry] We'll just
try Arthur Curry...
Maine...
lighthouse.
[whimsical music
playing on keyboard]
Here we are. Thomas
Curry. That's his dad.
Uh, phone.
- [phone rings]
- Hello.
- [Barry] Hello, Thomas Curry?
- Yes.
Could I speak to Arthur?
Is Arthur around?
You wanna speak to my dog?
What? No, no. Um, sorry. Uh...
- Is this Thomas Curry?
- Yes.
- And you work at a lighthouse?
Okay, and your wife is
the queen of Atlantis?
-[man on TV] Will you accept this rose?
-[woman on TV] Yes.
Uh, no.
Uh, right, but maybe, maybe...
um, a fishlike woman
washed into your life
- at some point or another?
- Very funny, asshole.
[line disconnects]
Arthur Curry was never born.
- What?
- This is a disaster.
I-I-I completely
destroyed history.
Like Eric Stoltz.
Okay, why do you keep
saying, "Eric Stoltz"?
Eric Stoltz is Marty McFly.
- What?
- Time travel?
Oh. We talking "BTTF"?
Come on, who is this guy?
Okay, yeah, no, I know.
I've seen all of them
and Eric Stoltz is
not Marty McFly.
[Gary] Really?
Then explain Marty McThigh here.
I can't explain
that to you, Gary.
That's not your thigh.
It's the wrong actor,
and it's upside down.
[Gary] Is it?
[whimsical music continues
playing on keyboard]
The point is that
in Back to the Future
Marty McFly is very famously
played by Michael J. Fox.
The guy from Footloose?
No, that's Kevin Bacon!
-Bacon.
-[past Barry] Kevin Bacon's Maverick
with the volleyball, the
gay guys, and the planes?
-Top Gun.
- Top Gun, right?
- [Barry] No, no, no.
I completely broke the universe.
[whimsical music continues
playing on keyboard]
Marty McFly is Eric Stoltz.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
I created a world
with no metahumans.
And now there's no one to
defend us from Zod. Albert!
[stops playing keyboard]
There's no Cyborg.
There's no Aquaman.
There's no Wonder Woman.
There's no Superman.
There's no Batman.
[past Patty] I'm Batman.
[dramatic musical sting]
What, you... What
did you just say?
I'm [burping] Batman.
[all laughing]
Batman exists?
- Hundo p.
- [Gary] Yeah, dude.
Nobody knows who he really is,
- but he exists.
- [Barry] Right.
Well, uh, we...
my cousin Barry and I,
have to go to that
cousin's dinner.
Now.
But it was a pleasure to meet
- you all.
- [Albert resumes playing keyboard]
- And Gary.
- [Gary] Barry.
- Barry.
- Gary.
Barry!
[mysterious music playing]
[car stops]
What, are you frickin'
kidding me with this place?
[gate creaks]
What is this, hell?
It's open.
[exclaims]
- Look at all this cool shit!
- Okay, Barry, don't touch anything in here.
["25 Or 6 To 4" by Chicago
playing on speakers]
Hello?
Bruce?
Bruce, are you there?
Oh, boy.
[Barry] Hey, I didn't
know you painted.
They're good.
Bruce Wayne?
[song continues
faintly in other room]
Bruce?
[song fades]
[past Barry] Hey, check
this out. There's, like,
bells connected to every
room in this house.
Hey, maybe we can
find this Bruce guy...
if we just ring all
these bells, right?
[Barry] You don't understand how servant
bells work? Those are all the bells.
- You ring them from all the other places.
- What?
You don't have, like, Downton
Abbeyin your universe?
Downtown Abbey's?
The chain of, like,
family-style restaurants?
They're like, it's like
cheaper Bananabee's.
Oh, you know what I'd
really go for right now?
Abbey's sizzlin'
zucchini squares.
- [man grunts]
- [grunts]
[song continues]
Okay.
- [cries out]
- [glass shatters]
[past Barry laughs]
[laughs harder]
You know what, man?
I've had it with you.
[song continues]
[groans]
[Barry screams]
[song stops]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[mysterious music playing]
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy who lives here.
We're looking for Bruce Wayne.
- [grunts softly]
- [neck cracks]
You hungry?
Following the broadcast
earlier from General Zod.
The individual
they're searching for
- is still at large.
- So...
The president has yet to respond
to the broadcast from earlier,
and other foreign
leaders are said to be...
you're the same person as him...
- but from an alternate timeline.
- Yes.
In which...
you and I are friends?
Yeah, you're like
probably my best friend.
- Okay.
- [Barry] Well, but you're a bit...
you're, uh...
- chronologically different.
- Older.
That's what I can't understand.
I traveled back in
time from here to here.
Yet somehow,
everything's all changed
back here.
- Or like when you were born, so...
- [older Bruce] Well...
time isn't linear.
Right?
Right.
At some point
you probably saw a
movie that told you
that if you went back
and changed the past,
you'd create a kind of a
branched timeline, right?
Like, look.
New present
- and new future.
- [past Barry] Yeah.
Well, time doesn't
work like that.
That's not how time works.
When you go back
and change the past
you create a fulcrum.
You put yourself on a whole
nother strand of spaghetti.
New future. New past.
[spaghetti snaps]
It's retrocausal.
It goes both ways.
Actually, it goes many ways.
Maybe some other time.
Okay, but in an ontological
paradox model, there's not...
What you did was you
changed the future
and you changed the past.
If a person
is stupid enough
to mess with time...
what you eventually
end up with is this.
The multiverse.
Some strands run
almost parallel.
There will be inevitable
intersections,
and others that are just...
wildly divergent.
What it is...
is a hot mess.
It's a crapshoot.
It's all just a crapshoot.
What does the parmesan mean?
The metaphor's over.
It's just a garnish.
And I'll tell ya something.
A person would have to be
an idiot
to play craps
with the space-time continuum.
Yeah, an idiot.
Here.
[slurping] Mm.
Are you joking with the
chewing noises right now?
So, uh, you're the reason
this Zod character
is about to destroy the Earth?
Maybe.
There's a guy called Superman
who can stop Zod?
- Yeah, yeah.
- And flies?
Shoots lasers out of his eyes?
Yes, he flies, and he shoots
lasers out of his eyes. Yes.
No one said "Superman"...
that might be a
little on the nose?
- You call yourself Batman.
- Yeah.
I don't call myself
Super Batman.
[laughs]
Wait, he's Batman?
What did you think
we were doing here?
I thought this was
the cousin's dinner.
He's... Bruce Wayne is Batman?
Not really. Not
so much anymore.
You know...
they don't really need me.
Things have changed.
Gotham's now
one of the safest
cities in the world.
Well, I... I need
you. We need you.
In my timeline,
Batman's our
strategist, our leader.
The world needs Superman. You're
the best detective in the world.
You're probably the only person
who can help me find him.
So, will you help us?
[heroic music builds, stops]
Pass.
[Barry stutters]
Like pass the salt?
Bruce?
[crows cawing]
[Barry] He doesn't
want to help us...
we're gonna use his bat shit.
Bat shit?
Yeah, his bat stuff,
his bat things.
Stand on that thing.
Okay, remember when you
phased through the floor?
- Yeah.
- So,
- I need you to do that again.
- [vibrating]
- [heavy thud]
- [past Barry] Ow.
- [sighs]
- [hatch creaks]
What is this place?
[mysterious music playing]
[enthralling music playing]
[machines whirring]
[bats screeching]
[computers trilling]
[past Barry] Dude!
This place straight beeves!
"Beeves"?
[shrieks excitedly]
[yelling]
[panting]
Barry!
I almost died
in an abyss!
12,805 Clark Kents in the US.
Is this what I think it is?
[majestic music playing]
Holy shit!
I used to see this thing on
the news when I was a kid!
Okay, well...
refine search.
Date of birth.
- Wasn't born. He arrived.
- [past Barry] Oh!
Oh, Barry, look!
I'm busy.
With what?
Looking for unidentified objects
entering Earth's atmosphere
anywhere near Kansas
in the last 50 years.
He has a back door into NASA.
'Course he does.
Yeah, but Barry, check this out.
This bag laughs.
[wicked laughter]
Okay, can't you take
anything seriously?
Stop messing around.
Dude, come on.
Have you seen this place?
It's amazing! [echoing]
Hello!
Has the gravity of this
not sunk in for you?
Stop messing around, Barry.
I won't say it again.
Yeesh. Sorry, Mom.
Shut up. Shut up.
You have no idea
how lucky you are.
No idea!
You take everything for granted.
You don't even appreciate...
You just walk around
thinking that you're so funny
and so cool.
And it's embarrassing,
because you're not
any of those things!
Hey, screw you, man!
I've done nothing but
everything you've asked.
You made me get
struck by lightning!
I phased naked through the floor.
And I terrified Mrs. Johannson.
Now I'm probably
gonna have to move.
You won't even tell
me why you're here.
But will you at least tell me
why you're being so mean to me...
for no reason?
You used Monkey as a dartboard!
Wait, what?
Forget it.
The monkey? Wait...
So, you're mad at me
for playing with a toy?
It's not a toy.
Mom bought us that monkey.
'Cause she calls us Monkey.
She gives us monkey
stuff all the time.
Right.
Look...
I'm sorry.
[sentimental music playing]
I'm not very good with people.
Even myself.
Oh.
Come on, dude.
You're... You're not that bad.
You can just be kind
of a dick sometimes.
But let's face it. I
am pretty obnoxious.
But I just get excited.
Come on. This place
is pretty cool, right?
Yeah.
All right, well, um...
I'll let you work.
[sentimental music continues]
[moans softly]
[Barry] I know you're there.
You know what I'm stuck on?
That thing you said,
with the spaghetti.
You said there were certain intersections
that would always be inevitable.
You had an Alfred.
My Bruce has an Alfred.
Different worlds,
different times...
yet there it is.
Certain people,
certain events, certain
strands of spaghetti,
drawn to each other
like... like magnets.
I've read all about
temporal paradoxes
and causal loops.
But this is more than that.
Inevitable intersections
are something none of the theories
could have anticipated 'cause,
well, how do you explain
that except for...
fate?
If you are listening,
sorry about your parents.
I'm just trying to save mine.
There has to be a way.
- [sighs]
- There is a way, Barry.
Just keep trying.
Keep trying, Barry.
[device beeps, pulsing]
[device clicks, pulsing stops]
[metal creaking]
[Batman theme playing]
[Barry] Found him.
Barry, wake up.
Clark's being held by a mercenary
group in a Siberian black site.
Get up, Barry.
The goat's on fire. [yelps]
We're going to Russia.
[yawns] Sweet.
[yawns] Mm. Coffee.
How are we gonna get to Russia?
- [gate opens]
- [bats squeaking]
[Batman theme playing]
[older Bruce] I'll help
you get this Superman.
Then, you're on your own.
- [cup shatters]
- Oh!
You're...
You are, you're...
[music builds]
Yeah.
I'm Batman.
[engine starts]
[Batman theme playing]
[engine whooshes]
So, what's the plan?
We're just gonna, what,
grab Superman and dip set
before the block is hot?
I don't know.
[whispering] Hey,
you should ask him.
[controls beeping]
- [whispering] You ask him.
- You should ask him.
Yeah, I'm not gonna ask him.
Why not? I thought Batman was
supposed to be your friend.
Not this one. Not this Batman.
-[older Batman] We're here.
-[automated voice] Activating hover mode.
- Ejector seat on.
- Ejector seat.
- [whirring]
Okay, there are stages.
You're strapped to
your parachutes.
Hey, where's yours?
[metal clicks]
[dramatic music playing]
Whoo! This rips dicks!
[whooping]
[yells]
[ominous music playing]
[older Batman] All
clear. Let's move.
[rousing music playing]
- [music stops]
- [wind whistling]
- Okay!
- [rousing music resumes]
[coughs]
Good. Everybody's
fast now but me.
-[past Barry] Why is it so cold?
-It's the Arctic, Barry.
-[past Berry] Where'd he go?
-I don't know. Just follow the footprints.
Superman would be
down there for sure.
[wind gusting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[metal clangs]
[clangs]
[thuds]
[speaking Russian]
[alarm blaring]
Yeah. Okay.
[shouting indistinctly]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[amusing music playing]
[slowed gunshots]
[Barry grunts, shudders]
What did you do?
I had to move you. But
I just did it a little.
[retches loudly]
[shouts indistinctly]
[metallic thud]
[dramatic choral music playing]
This might hurt.
[soldiers yelling]
- [continues retching]
- Just let it out.
[soldiers groaning]
[screams]
[speaking Russian]
[grunting]
[alarm blaring]
Let's go.
[dark choral music playing]
[Barry] That's where
you keep Superman.
Like a big scrotum.
[dramatic music playing]
[keypad beeping]
[buzzes]
- [keypad beeping]
- [system buzzing]
He's gonna hack the Soviet security
cyberscrotum with a flip phone?
[trills]
I tried all the combinations.
[metal thuds, creaks]
[past Berry] Yes!
[dark choral music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[past Barry] Shit.
[Barry] Kal-El?
It's not him. We've gotta go.
Wait.
We can't just leave
her here. Look at her.
[alarm blaring]
I'll grab her. Just go!
[tense music playing]
I got you.
[music halts]
I'll handle this jabroni.
[scientist screams, grunts]
What the...
[screaming]
Barry! Somebody shot me!
- [screaming]
- [Barry] Time to dip set!
[soldiers coughing]
[tense music playing]
[soldiers shouting in Russian]
[past Barry] You,
you lead the way!
- Go!
- Not that way! Not that way!
[shouting in Russian]
[past Barry] Oh, God!
- [yelps]
- Cover!
[clangs]
No!
[exhales]
[clangs]
[Barry] It's coming
around. Hurry, hurry.
[speaking Russian]
[grunts]
No, no, no! This is bullshit!
[metal groaning]
[clangs]
No!
- Come on.
- [grunts]
Let's go.
You didn't tell me
we could get shot!
Why would you
assume we couldn't?
[soldiers shouting in Russian]
[yelps]
Oh, great! To die at
the feet of a Sputnik.
Oh, man! I need this knee!
- [Barry] Stay calm. It'll heal.
- Come on.
[screams in pain]
[beeping]
[alarm continues blaring]
- How much do you weigh?
- [Barry] 180.
Each. Plus her, 440.
[beeping]
[soldiers speaking Russian]
[older Batman] Hold on.
[beeping accelerates]
[soldiers screaming]
[shaky screaming]
[grunting]
[wind howling]
- [running footsteps]
- [soldiers speaking Russian]
[Barry] Oh, great.
They're here.
They're over here, too.
[past Barry] Smirnoff Ice.
- Yes. Smirnoff Ice.
- [Barry] Hi.
- [Barry groans, coughs]
- [past Barry] Stop them!
-Yep.
-Okay, they're serious. Barry, shut up.
[past Barry] Yeah, okay.
What's the play?
Batman, what do
we do? What now?
[music builds]
Now...
we try not to die.
- [soldiers shout indistinctly]
- [gunfire]
[soldiers screaming]
[grunting]
[soldier screams]
[past Barry] Oh, you guys
should've seen that in slo-mo.
[dramatic music builds]
- [pensive music playing]
- [water dripping]
[Barry] Yeah, I'm just realizing that
I didn't really think this through.
There are good Kryptonians...
and then there are very,
very bad Kryptonians.
[whispering] And I
was very confident
that we were just
gonna find Superman,
and if we found Superman,
then this would all
be super simple.
- [woman] Who are you?
- Holy Funyuns.
Hi.
- I... I'm Barry.
- We're Barry.
We were trying to find Kal-El.
But we found you instead.
What do you want with Kal-El?
We were trying to rescue him.
Why?
Because he's my friend.
Do you... Do you know him?
[whispering] She
looks mad. Get ready.
She might do laser vision, or she
might do, like, a freezy breath...
- or she'll just start throwing crazy...
- My name is Kara.
Daughter of Zor-El.
Kal-El was my cousin.
- Right, and who's Kal-El again?
- It's Superman.
- No, 'cause you said that was Clark.
- Who's Clark?
Clark is his human name.
Clark.
[soft music playing]
He was an infant when we left.
The last son of Krypton... I...
I was sent to protect him.
It looks like he
never made it to Earth
in this universe.
Our pods, they must
have separated.
Wait, so you thought a baby
was gonna protect us
from this Zod guy?
General Zod is here.
He must have tracked
my pod's signal.
- I have to go. [groans]
- Whoa, whoa, wait.
Well, you need to recover your
strength. Actually, Barry...
take her to the roof
and put her in the sun.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Whatever, like if, I mean,
you're solar powered.
Good for you. I've
been trying to...
- [Kara panting]
- Oh, uh...
We'll take that with us.
[enthralling music playing]
Um, am I cool to...
turn around?
Are you dressed
in a red cape?
[breathing heavily]
You're levitating?
[indistinct voices whispering]
- [traffic noises]
- [dogs barking]
[indistinct voices talking]
- [noises stop]
- [groans softly]
Is it always this loud?
[sighs]
Is it loud?
Are you, uh, good?
Do you feel, um...
strong yet, or...
[hawks, spits]
[past Barry gasps]
Yep, that seems, uh,
seems strong. You know...
old man Barry, down there,
says if we don't
stop Captain Zode,
he'll kill thousands of people.
Billions of people.
Billions?
Of your people.
- They're good people.
- Good people?
We came to this planet
looking for a safe
place to live,
and they put me in a cage.
Yeah. A lot of
humans are dicks.
But then
there's babies and ballerinas.
And entertainment wrestlers.
A lot of humans
are worth saving.
Maybe to you.
But I'm not a human.
I'm a Kryptonian.
She's gone.
I have to get my powers back.
If I can re-create the accident
that gave me my powers...
maybe I can reconnect
to the Speed Force...
and maybe we'd stand
a chance against Zod.
Or kill yourself in the process.
Tell me something.
If you get your powers back,
you can go anywhere.
You can go to another timeline,
another universe.
Why do you wanna stay...
and fight to save this one?
Because this is the
world where my mom lives.
I went back in time to save her.
I'm not gonna lose her again.
The kid doesn't know, does he?
How do you tell someone
something like that?
I lost my parents...
but that pain...
made me who I am.
I'm not sure I know who I
am without it, actually.
[wistful music playing]
I spent a lifetime...
trying to right the
wrongs of the past.
As if
putting on a cape
and fighting crime
would bring my parents back.
You actually did it.
So...
I guess the plan is
to douse yourself in
industrial chemicals
while electrocuting yourself?
Yep.
Want some help?
[rousing music plays]
[Barry] Hell yeah. That
would be incredibly useful.
I've actually already
borrowed some chemicals
and your soldering iron,
and I'm sitting
in your bat-seat.
Is that like a faux pas?
[pilot on radio] Wilco,
Lima, Zebra, be advised...
[Commander] Air
Command to Bravo 601.
[pilot] Primary teams,
please confirm your AORs.
[foreboding music playing]
[engines whine]
- [soldier 1] Green teams ready to move.
- [soldier 2] Standing by!
You bring me nothing? Hmm.
I gave you a warning.
Your failure to deliver
the Kryptonian traitor
is being taken as an act of war.
[blade slices]
-[soldier 1] Fire, fire, fire!
-[soldier 2 on radio] We have contact, contact!
Weapons hot! Weapons
hot! Open fire!
No. [echoes]
[soldier 2] Air support
now! I repeat, air support!
[tense music playing]
[engines whooshing]
[dramatic music plays]
[thunder rumbling]
[dramatic music playing]
Okay, when I throw the switch,
the current should
run up the wire
and draw the lightning
right to the kite.
Here, put that on.
It's heat and impact resistant.
Should protect you a little.
Right, but the point is
for me to not be protected.
Okay.
You're gonna need to
be out of the way.
I will.
Let's get electrocuted.
This is going to work, right?
Of course it's gonna work.
Nothing we haven't done before.
Besides, this time
we have Batman.
What could go wrong?
Uh, for the record, I
think this is insane.
Get back.
[thunder rumbling]
It's fine. It's fine.
[machine starts up]
[electricity crackling]
Just you and me
again, Mr. Lightning.
[dramatic choral music playing]
Do it!
[music halts]
[lightning striking]
[dramatic music resumes]
[screaming]
[past Barry] Wait, what? No!
No, wait! Stop! Stop!
- [groans]
- [crackling stops]
[Barry shuddering]
- [coughs]
- [soft searing]
Oh, God.
Barry, no.
[breath shudders]
Go again.
But...
Please.
[machine powers down]
The circuit is fried.
[shudders]
[whooshes]
[hopeful music playing]
[breathes heavily]
[thunder rumbling]
[hopeful music continues]
[thunder crashes]
I've got you.
[thunder crashing]
[blasting]
[soft music playing]
Hey. Barry.
You're okay. It's
like last time, right?
So, you gotta heal now.
[soft searing]
[electricity crackling]
Look, look, look!
It's working. It's working.
- Yeah, it's working. Yeah.
- [coughing]
[past Barry] Yeah, he's
healing. He's healing.
Oh, my God. He's okay.
Dude, you scared
the shit out of me.
[rousing music playing]
- [music halts]
- [squeaking]
- [eerie music playing]
- [deep rumbling]
[indistinct distorted noise]
[distorted voice yells]
[roars]
[gasps]
[indistinct TV chatter]
[groans]
You're awake.
How you feeling?
Slow.
Maybe this will help.
[heroic music builds]
Ooh... Ooh!
Yes!
Dude, come on! Irresistible!
Man, feels good to be back.
Yeah!
And what are we wearing tonight?
You like it?
I-I made it myself out
of that old Batsuit.
But you know, I made it
our colors and everything.
Well, check this out!
- [suit squeaks]
- It's a bit more loose.
It beeves.
Dude...
you really mean that?
I mean, I don't...
I don't know what it
means, exactly, to beeve.
But it seems like it's positive.
What are you doing?
You came back.
I'm glad you're okay.
I have to ask you something.
When you found me in that
hole that they put me in...
and I wasn't Kal-El...
why did you help me?
Because you needed help.
Do you know what this
symbol stands for?
- Supergirl?
- It means hope, right?
Hope, yeah. Does it mean hope?
Krypton was a beautiful place.
We are a people of hope,
not war.
[reporter speaking on TV]
I'm coming to you
live from Metropolis,
where minutes ago, the
mysterious flying...
[Kara] Zod may be from Krypton,
but he is not my people.
So, you're saying...
Yes.
I will help you fight Zod.
[past Barry] Yes!
[older Batman]
Interesting group.
What did you say, uh...
we were called again?
We're the Justice League.
[Barry] No.
- No?
- Well, I mean, kinda.
We are short
one literal goddess...
one friendly Terminator
and super mermaid.
And we could definitely
use a Batman.
Are you in?
- [heroic music builds]
- [exhales]
You wanna get nuts?
Let's get nuts.
[stirring music playing]
In my world, Superman showed up
right away when Zod called him out.
So, as of now, we're
in uncharted territory.
What I do know is that Zod somehow
controls the World Engines,
which will be
destroying much more
than just Metropolis now
with every passing second
that we don't stop him.
Barry, what are you doing?
What?
Our kids are gonna
wanna see this.
Your kids?
Well, you know, like everybody's kids.
I mean, the children of the world.
They're gonna wanna see this.
[older Batman]
We're getting close.
I'm gonna stay airborne and
take out their sky power.
And Barry, just so we're clear
what that essentially
equates to is you and me
versus the entire
Kryptonian army.
Chill.
We need to buy Kara enough
time to take out Zod.
Oh, and remember that your suit
doesn't dissipate energy like mine
so you need to take breaks,
otherwise you're gonna
build up too much charge.
- Wait, what?
- [alarm beeping]
[missile whooshes]
- [explosion]
- [past Barry yelps]
[screams]
[past Barry screaming] Dang it!
- [older Batman] Hold on!
- [screaming]
- [past Barry] Okay!
- [Barry] Hold on.
The humans we came to protect?
They don't know
we're on their side.
[dramatic music playing]
- [music halts]
- [suit squeaks]
[dramatic music resumes]
[sinister music playing]
Zod.
Kara Zor-El.
We've been waiting for you.
[soldier 1] Go, go!
[soldier 2] Cover!
[soldiers screaming]
- Drag him out, drag him!
- You go! I'll cover!
[soldiers screaming]
- [giant grunts]
- [soldiers groaning]
Okay, and the space giant...
and Mistress Murder...
- are our responsibility, too?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Don't think about
them, okay? Calm down.
We're just gonna start
with those guys over there.
And yeah, they're Kryptonian, and
we won't be able to kill them,
but we can slow
them down for her.
One at a time.
Okay? I'm gonna disarm them,
and then you'll engage.
Punch 'em.
Come on, Barbie.
Let's go party?
[The Flash theme playing]
[grunting]
[grunts] Okay, ow!
Oh.
[grunts]
[vibrating]
Okay. It's okay.
You're okay. Come on.
Jesus, they're fast.
Yes, but not as fast as us.
Terraforming has begun.
This world must die
so that ours may live again.
[energy charging up]
[energy blasts]
Oh, my God. We gotta
go. We gotta go.
Dan, Danny, go, go!
Krypton is gone, Zod.
Your uncle...
Jor-El...
hid the key
to Krypton's rebirth
inside a Kryptonian child.
All the genetic material needed
to start again
coded inside the DNA,
then sent to Earth
in an escape pod.
He's not here. You have failed.
We found him.
We intercepted his pod.
But your cousin was
not the one we needed.
You are the one.
Kara Zor-El.
It is your blood...
we must harvest.
What did you do to Kal-El?
Your sacrifice that will allow
Krypton to live again.
[shouts] What did you do?
The infant did not survive.
[screams]
[dramatic music playing]
[heroic music playing]
Look, new plan.
I'm gonna create a
cyclonic diversion.
And you're gonna
just come in, hard.
Feet first this time.
[soldier groans]
[yells]
Yes!
Barry, did you see that?
Be careful. You're
accumulating too much charge.
What if I just Emperor this guy?
- [The Flash] No, no, no!
- [yelps]
[sighs]
[both grunting]
[yells]
[groans]
Barry, that was actually
only half stupid!
But if you're gonna
do that and not die,
you need to complete
the circuit somehow.
Try putting your hands
together, like this.
Oh, shit.
- You're ready.
- Let's go!
["Salute Your Solution"
by The Raconteurs playing]
[clanging]
- [yells]
- [clangs]
[energy blasts]
[music continues]
I'm going after the big one.
[alarm wailing]
I've been hit.
[tense music playing]
[The Flash] Bruce, do you copy?
- Where's Kara?
- You go find her.
Bruce!
[automated voice]
Ejection mode failure.
[grunting]
[grunts]
[trills]
[General Zod grunts]
[dark music playing]
[Kara grunts]
- [device whirring]
- [groaning laboriously]
Rest, Kara Zor-El.
Going down.
[alarm continues wailing]
But I'm not going alone.
No, no, no, Bruce!
Bruce, eject!
Bruce, just eject...
[engine whining]
No!
[past Barry] Kara.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Isn't supposed...
Not supposed to happen...
[brooding music playing]
Kara's dead.
They're both dead.
But they don't
have to be, right?
'Cause we can go back.
- Like you did.
- You're not fast enough yet.
You sure?
- [yells]
- Barry!
[The Flash] Barry, wait!
[rousing heroic music playing]
Is this back enough?
Yeah, I guess so.
Listen, Barry, I...
[rumbling]
What? It's okay.
We can fix this.
You know what
you're gonna change?
I know what I'm gonna change.
[gripping music playing]
I'm going after the big one.
Bruce, pull off. That
gunship is shield-protected.
Roger that.
Bet he's not.
[The Flash] Who? Space giant?
Yes, yes, please take him out.
[giant roars]
[grunts]
[roars]
[grunting]
[engine whining]
[heroic music playing]
Yes.
[yelling]
[The Flash theme playing]
[punches landing]
[exhales deeply]
- [Kara yells]
- [grunts]
[groaning]
[sinister music playing]
- [blade stabs]
- [Kara grunts]
[Kara grunts]
[grunting]
[bomb beeping rapidly]
[explodes]
[breathing heavily]
[bomb beeping rapidly]
[explodes]
[breathing heavily]
[solemn music playing]
[groaning]
No.
Hey.
It'll be okay.
Not this time, kid.
Maybe some other time.
We can't bring you back, can we?
You already did.
[inhales sharply]
[past Barry] Come on, Barry.
Gotta get up. Come on.
- Barry.
- We go again.
- [giant roars]
- [gasps]
[The Flash] Barry.
[giant roars]
Let's just go.
Barry, come on. Let's just go.
Barry, there's no point.
[giant roars]
Barry!
[rousing heroic music playing]
[giant roaring]
[energy charges up, blasts]
- Phase!
- [vibrating]
- [groans]
- Okay, I have to pull it out.
- I have to pull it out.
- No, I'm okay.
You have to phase again.
Barry, phase again.
I'm okay. I just
should've stopped sooner.
[The Flash] Ow!
[both grunting]
[gasps]
- [phone vibrating]
- [past Barry yelling]
[Kryptonian groans, whimpers]
Again.
Barry.
Okay, can we please
just take a minute?
Sorry, dude. Yeah,
bro, of course.
[laughs] That's the whole thing.
We can take as much
time as it takes.
No, that's not
what I mean. Hey!
- [roars]
- [screams]
[solemn music playing]
[up-tempo music playing]
- [music stops]
- [grunts]
Okay, you good? Come on.
I need you in there. Let's go.
Barry, please,
just listen to me!
[yells]
[groans]
[up-tempo music playing]
Where were you?
What, you just stand
here the whole time?
Barry, this is an
inevitable intersection.
You have to stop. Barry!
[grunts]
[vibrating]
No, Barry, wait!
Barry, listen. [echoes]
There's something
I should tell you.
I went back in time initially
- because...
- Yeah, because Mom died.
How do you know?
It doesn't matter. Does it?
You know that I have
to undo what I did.
No.
It's not a mistake.
We can save her.
And we can save them.
No, we can't.
This is what Bruce
was talking about.
Barry, this is inevitable.
We can try a million times, and
we're not gonna be able to fix this.
No matter what we do...
this world dies.
Today.
Look around.
[distorted rumbling]
Look at the damage
we're causing.
Now we have to stop.
Okay?
Look, I was just
doing my laundry.
You're the one who came and
told me that I'm a superhero.
And now you're saying what?
[stutters] You
don't want me to be?
Well, guess what!
It's too late!
I am... [echoes]
the Flash.
And I can save everyone.
Nobody dies!
Barry...
not every problem
has a solution.
Not every problem
[sentimental music playing]
Sometimes we just
have to let go.
[Nora] Sometimes you
just have to let go.
Let go of Mom?
She'll always be alive,
somewhere in time.
Always.
Just not for us.
You're full of shit, dude.
I'm going back.
[shouts] You're going
back to kill Mom?
No!
You're staying!
You stay, right here.
Just give me one more time.
Barry, stop!
You, stop!
[ominous music playing]
[yells]
[dramatic choral music playing]
[screaming]
[dramatic choral
music continues]
[grunts]
Feel like we got off
on the wrong foot.
Let's start again.
I'm the Flash.
What's your name?
I've lived...
more than you can dream.
- [crackling]
- Not an answer.
Do you, like, rehearse that?
[electricity surging]
Whoa.
Get out of here, Barry!
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[searing]
[past Barry] That scar, you...
Oh, my God.
So, you're... You are...
Yes, I am...
you.
We are so close.
I've got it almost figured out.
How long have you
been doing this?
Time is inconsequential.
Come on, Barry.
[whooshing]
[rumbling]
[dramatic music playing]
[man] Up in the
sky! It's a bird!
[woman] It's a plane!
[man 2] It's Superman!
[distant explosions]
[majestic music playing]
[explosions]
[heroic music playing]
[Catwoman]
Purrfectly foolproof.
[Joker cackling]
[early Batman] Only the
Joker would think of that.
[Joker cackling]
[creature chittering]
[screams]
[creature growling]
[heroic music continues]
Please just look at
what's happening.
These worlds...
[exploding]
they're colliding
and collapsing.
We did this.
[breathes heavily]
W-We're destroying the
fabric of everything.
You have to stop.
It stops once I've fixed it!
It's not entirely
your fault, Barry.
I pushed you out of the
Chronobowl on that September 29
so you could start
me on this path. Hmm?
How do you like our
endless paradox?
I made you create me...
and now you're the one...
in my way.
No matter how close I get
to winning this fight...
you go back
and let Mom die.
You're the inevitable
intersection.
And you do have to let go.
What's he talking about?
You're my hero.
[screams]
[groaning]
What did you do?
Hey, hey. Don't worry.
It's gonna heal.
[choking] I just wanted to...
[past Barry mumbles]
You tell Mom I love her.
[breathes laboriously]
[somber music playing]
[rumbling]
[music building]
[heroic music playing]
[muzak playing on speakers]
[baby crying]
[crying fades]
Don't forget the tomatoes.
[baby cooing]
I used to love that
cereal when I was a kid.
Yeah.
My son goes nuts for it.
They stop making it.
[stutters] Well, I know they were
talking about discontinuing it.
- Do I know you?
- No, I'm not from around here.
I was just visiting my mom.
Maybe I know her.
What's her name?
She's the best...
and kindest person in the world.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm really gonna miss her.
[sniffling]
[gentle music playing]
I know I'm just...
a random lady in a store.
But do you want a hug?
Mm-hmm. Sure.
- [tearfully] I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't say that.
Your mom must be grateful
you came to visit her.
She's very lucky to have you.
I'm very lucky to have her.
Ah! You have to tell her that.
Moms like to hear
these kind of things.
Believe me.
[gentle Spanish song playing]
[sniffles]
[cries softly]
[breathes deeply]
[sighs deeply]
Love you, Mom.
[inhales deeply]
I love you more.
I loved you first.
Bye.
I'm back.
Shit!
Court!
[indistinct chatter]
[whooshing]
[grunts]
original trial was initially...
I'm so sorry.
As I was saying...
the same security
camera footage,
Exhibit F in the original trial,
was initially
considered useless,
but has now
been enhanced,
using the latest tech
from Wayne Enterprises.
It confirms
the alibi
Mr. Allen has argued,
and his son, Barry,
has corroborated, since day one.
Here.
[audience murmurs]
Right here, you can clearly
see my client, Mr. Allen,
reaching for a can of tomatoes
on the top shelf.
[sentimental music playing]
[audience chattering]
[sighs in relief]
Mr. Allen, Mr. Allen, can you tell us
a bit more about what happened, please?
Well, um...
the tomatoes moved from the
bottom shelf to the top shelf,
and subsequently,
uncooked the spaghetti.
Unquote.
I'm sorry, that makes absolutely no
sense. What are you talking about, sir?
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- The allegations, the trial...
We're good here. Thank you.
[reporter] statement
in the court.
- Did I give a good quote?
- Yeah.
Spaghetti.
Hey, speaking of food,
I was thinking, um...
you should ask me to dinner.
D-Dinner with me?
[chuckles softly]
Yes, a date, Barry.
Iris West, do you
wanna dinner-date me?
- I'd love to.
- Thank you.
I'd love to also.
Call me.
[singing "Pedro Navaja"]
[cell phone ringing]
- Bruce!
- [distorted] Congratulations.
Thank you. You have no idea how
good it is to hear your voice.
I... I have so much to tell you the next
time I see you, Bruce. You were right.
Okay? And I didn't listen.
And things did get
very, very weird,
but I put everything
back, I promise.
I'm pulling up now.
Oh, great.
- [reporter 1] Get the shot.
- [reporter 2] Sir, sir!
- [bodyguard] Back up, please.
- [reporter 3] Shot!
[reporter 2] Sir, I'd like to ask
you for a video for the Daily Planet.
- [reporter 4] Wayne! Wayne!
- Step aside.
Was it backed by
your own allegation?
Who the fuck is this?
[bodyguard] He's not
answering any questions.
Hey, Barry.
No, wh-where's...
You're, you... No.
You can't...
You... You're not Batman.
What's wrong with you?
Huh.
- [Barry chuckles haltingly]
- [chuckles]
[chuckles forcedly]
Well...
[dramatic music builds]
[music halts]
["This too Shall Pass"
by OK Go playing]
[The Flash theme playing]
[dramatic choral music playing]
[somber music playing]
[up-tempo music playing]
[captivating music playing]
I've told you it's
my metabolism, right?
I can't get drunk.
I can't get drink either.
Listen. Listen, I'm, 'cause
I'm trying to... No, no, no.
'Cause what I'm trying to explain as
simply as I possibly can, I promise...
They were all Batman.
They were all Bruce Wayne.
But each of them was a
completely different person.
- So, on the other line-time...
- Timeline.
I'm the same guy?
Yeah. Actually, pretty much.
You're lovable, furry...
loyal, motivated by bacon.
All right, listen.
Thank you for making it more
simpler for me, Mr. Simple More.
-Yeah, I'm doing my
best.- -[Arthur mumbles]
Look, you're missing
the larger premise here.
In my timeline, when I...
All right, come on.
- Up, up, Broseidon.
- [grunts]
All right, come on.
I thought you were gonna
sleep on the couch. [stutters]
Arthur, I live right here.
Harry?
I live right here. It's okay.
[water bubbling]
[flaps lips]
Okay.
Oh, hey.
[grunts] More beer.
Go fast. Oh, here! Here.
Here. Pay with this.
Arthur, this is
Atlantean treasure.
You... You tell them that.
-Yep.
You're a sailor.
He's fine.