I'm here to kill you, Flash.
So, get ready to fry.
(GROANS)
Bring it on.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
Told you.
Zoom always wins.
Zoom sent me here to kill you.
But I didn't want to.
But you were fine with killing Linda Park.
It was the best bad idea
I could come up with.
Leave her body for Zoom to find.
He'd think I was dead and I'd be free.
How was he supposed to know
where to find her body?
Just let me go.
Let me disappear.
You would spend the rest of your life
looking over your shoulder,
never knowing when Zoom is coming.
Okay.
Then what's your great idea?
How were you supposed to contact him
after you killed me?
I was supposed to get something.
Something I could only get
if you were dead.
And then throw it through
the breach as proof.
And then what?
Then he'd come for me.
Confirm the kill and bring me home.
-Why do you want to know?
-Because I want to find him.
You really don't.
He's gonna keep coming for me.
He's gonna keep kidnapping people like
you, forcing them to do what he wants.
I have to stop him before more people die.
You can't stop Zoom.
Yes I can. I will. But I need your help.
Zoom wants Doctor Light to send him
your new emblem?
Yes. We need it for bait.
If we can get Doctor Light to take
my emblem, throw it through the breach,
then Zoom will come to collect my body
and we can trap him.
You know it took a lot of work
to make that emblem, right?
This is the woman
who was willing to kill Linda
in order to escape Zoom, but now
she's willing to help us catch him?
She knows it's the only way.
Before I left Earth Two, I worked on a
serum to dampen Zoom's speed.
All we would need is for Ramon
to develop a weapon to deliver it.
Oh, great, that could be
this year's cold gun.
Maybe another criminal can get it
and then we'd have Sergeant Slow.
I would never let that happen.
Sergeant Slow is a terrible name.
Are we forgetting how much more powerful
than Barry Zoom seems to be?
I mean, if Barry can catch bullets,
what's to say Zoom can't catch
whatever you shoot at him?
Surprise, the element of surprise.
All we would do is rig a projectile to
fire as Zoom crosses into the breach.
He can't stop what he can't see coming.
-That's great.
-Thanks.
(SIGHS) Joe, voice of reason here?
We need a plan, that's as good as any.
As long as he can deliver.
Don't underestimate me, Detective.
-(PHONE VIBRATING)
-Oh.
Patty needs us back at the station.
I'll meet you there, all right?
Are you just forgetting everything Jay
told us and supporting Wells now?
Oh, no, I don't trust Wells at all.
I just want to see what he's up to.
I figure, we give him some rope,
he'll hang himself.
Yeah, I'm totally with you.
I think he's hiding something.
Look, my hunch after interrogating
suspects all these years,
something's not right with this dude.
Barry told me about this thing you can do?
-Oh, God.
-Vibing.
Just relax.
Can you do it with Wells?
I can try.
HARRISON: Incapable?
Well, let me tell you something.
If you're
incapable of aligning the quantum helix,
and by the way, the sole purpose
of your employment here at S.T.A.R. Labs,
could you save me some time and effort,
could you go out there and find someone
who can actually do your job for you?
There it is.
Work voice.
When I was little, and you used
to bring me to S.T.A.R. Labs with you,
it used to freak me out,
how differently you talked here
than when you're at home.
You and your mother, both.
Shouldn't you be at school?
I graduated high school
when I was 15, Dad.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Right.
I can miss a day of college.
Ah, that's my Jesse, always so quick.
So?
So.
Is it true? (SIGHS)
Is what true?
What The Flash said about you
at the press conference,
that your particle accelerator
created the meta-humans?
-It is... (SIGHS) Jesse...
-Look, why didn't you just tell me?
Jay Garrick, it turns out,
is much faster at assigning blame
than he is at actual heroics.
-Dad, The Flash is a hero.
-Uh-huh.
Hey, I've never understood
why you disliked him so much.
But now I know it's because he knew
what you'd done.
What I've done at S.T.A.R. Labs
is change the world, Jesse.
Unlocking the mysteries of the universe.
And when you don't have
the key to the lock,
sometimes you have to kick in the door.
You should get to school.
Don't worry. I got my education today.
You're my joy, Jesse Quick.
JOE: All right. Talk to you later.
WOMAN: See you, Joe.
Great, you're here.
Good morning to you too, Patty.
Yes, I was up all night
working on the Doctor Light case.
I've been trying to anticipate
all the powers she might throw our way,
you know, on the premise
that she can manipulate light energy.
-I appreciate it, but...
-Did you know
that light energy
can be turned into hard light?
I mean, that doesn't even
sound like a thing, but it is.
-Seriously, Patty...
-No,
and on the other end of the spectrum
is invisibility.
Look, it's just hypothetical
but I think that...
The Doctor Light case is closed.
Oh. Uh...
Okay, can you tell me why?
No.
No?
-Okay.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Are you good?
Yeah. I'm fine, your dad just shut me down
in a big way.
-What do you mean?
-(STUTTERS)
I don't know, it just... You don't think
it's because you and I kissed?
No, I don't think he knows.
I didn't say anything.
But I can talk to him if you want.
No, no, no.
(STUTTERS) I'll talk to him.
You know, he's my partner,
we should have trust and communication.
Are you sure?
I don't mind talking about that kiss.
It was a good kiss.
Yeah, yeah. Although, the memory,
it's a little foggy.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
I might need, like, a reminder soon.
Okay.
-Hey.
Have you had any word from The Flash
about the meta-human that killed Larkin?
No. Not yet.
But I know he's working on it.
You know, maybe I could talk to him.
Linda, I don't think that's a good idea.
Look, Larkin is dead,
which makes it really hard for me
to concentrate
on field goals and doping scandals.
I don't want to sit around being told not
to worry my pretty little head about it.
I get that. Believe me, I do.
Then tell him I want to help. Please.
I can't let this woman who looks like me
hurt anyone else.
I'll ask again. But trust me,
Flash has everything under control.
Crap.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Doctor Light's gone invisible!
Lock the doors!
Shut the doors!
The door is not responding. None of
the security protocols are responding.
She's hacked the system.
Barry, Doctor Light is escaping!
Where is she?
Doctor Light managed to hack
into the lights of her cell.
The whole building runs on fiber optics
that operate on pulses of light.
So, she turned off the dampeners
and used her powers.
I told you how dangerous she was.
You should've listened to me
and sedated her.
I thought I had convinced her
that helping us was the only way
she'd free herself from Zoom.
-Well, you thought wrong.
-Yeah.
Okay, look. Doctor Light is gone.
So, instead of assigning blame, let's try
to figure out what we're going to do next.
Do you think she's going to try
and take Linda again?
I had Iris bring Linda to the house,
just in case, to keep an eye on her.
How are we doing with the speed-dampener?
I think we isolated the composite.
And we're modifying the dart
the Arrow used to take down Wells.
He's not Wells, I'm Wells.
Whatever, Harry.
But we don't even really know
if this thing works.
HARRISON: Until we try it, no.
This will be a field test.
So, can we end this scintillating
staff meeting and get back to work?
Or how 'bout I say
what everybody's thinking.
Maybe it's a good thing
that Doctor Light is gone.
Maybe it's the universe stopping us
from doing something really stupid.
No. No. Keep going. I'm gonna figure out
another way to get Zoom.
Hey, slow your roll. I wanna talk to you.
Joe, look, I know what I'm doing.
Okay, I don't.
So why don't you clue me in?
I'm trying to stop Zoom.
I thought you were on board with that.
I'm keeping my options open.
I don't understand
why you think we have a choice.
Zoom wants me dead.
The meta-humans
that he's sending from Earth Two,
they don't care
how many innocent people get in the way.
Look at what happened
to Iris and Linda's boss.
He was just collateral damage
in Zoom's war.
The next time, that could be you, or Iris.
I'm just wondering
if going after him now is premature.
I mean, we barely know anything
about his abilities.
Wells does.
You're putting a whole lot of faith
in the man
wearing the face of your mother's killer.
I think we should find Jay,
get him to help us on this.
Nah, Jay made it pretty clear
that he doesn't wanna help get me killed.
And we can't just sit around and wait
for Zoom to make his next move anymore.
We can't.
Aren't you the one who told me
life isn't about playing defense?
Sometimes the only way to succeed
is by working the offense?
I think at the time we were talking about
your high school football tryouts.
You said you'd never bring that up again.
Hey.
I just wanted to say,
using the, uh, tungsten composite
to dampen vibrations, that was...
It's pretty brilliant.
What are you doing?
I'm congratulating you.
Don't touch me.
Wow! Try to give a guy a compliment...
You're not trying to give me a compliment.
You're trying to meddle into things
that are none of your business.
-What did you vibe about me?
-Nothing.
God. Why? What's there to vibe on?
Don't touch me.
If you have questions, ask them.
Otherwise, stay away from me.
So?
God.
You'd think the serial killer version
would've been the bigger jerk.
Uh, what happened when you touched him?
What did you see?
Oh, I didn't see anything.
Well, go touch him again.
(STUTTERS) No. He's onto me now.
Well, you'll have to keep trying.
I mean, I think Joe's right.
Something must have happened between
Wells and Zoom that made this personal.
MALE NEWSCASTER: The hero of
Starling City, formerly known as The Hood,
has been unmasked
as billionaire Robert Queen.
Robert was marooned on an island
when his boat went down in the Pacific,
an accident that ended
with the tragic death of his son, Oliver.
Robert Queen was thought dead when...
Excuse me, I'm receiving word...
There has been an attack
at Central City College.
The science building is the focus
of another meta-human attack.
We are just receiving video.
Please be advised.
We're being told that the footage
you are about to see is...
Hey, Jesse, it's Dad. Can you...
I... I just... I saw on the news...
Just call me, all right? Let me know
that you're okay, that you weren't...
Witnesses report
that The Flash arrived on the scene,
but not before the hostile meta-human
escaped with a hostage, a female student.
We have not yet ID'd her
and there is no indication
as to why she has been
specifically targeted.
(SIGHS) No. No.
(SIGHS)
Joe, Detective, can we talk for a minute?
If this is about Doctor Light...
No. Yeah. No. Uh, maybe.
But, okay, look, I think I figured out
why you've been a bit shut down
the last couple of days.
-Really?
-Yeah,
I feel like you're not being
completely transparent with me,
but I think that it's my fault.
Look, you're a great, excellent,
wonderful detective,
and I think you could sense I'm not being
completely transparent with you.
And you're right. Look, we're partners.
We need to be completely honest
with each other, no secrets.
-Patty?
-Barry and I kissed.
There's something
to being too transparent.
No. No, no, no, I think that it's great.
Everything is just out there,
right out in the open.
Whatever you and Barry do in private
is your own business.
Okay.
So, you're not mad at me?
I promise you, I could care less.
(SIGHS)
Great.
I feel so much better.
Is there anything, you know,
maybe you've been meaning to tell me?
We're partners,
totally transparent with each other.
Uh...
Nope.
Cool.
-Hey.
Are you guys having a dinner party?
You would think.
I know, I know.
It's just,
sometimes cooking helps me to relax.
Oh.
Have you heard anything
about Doctor Light?
Am I still in danger?
Um, we're not really sure.
Come on, I'm going crazy here, Barry.
Yeah, she is.
-(OVEN DINGS)
-That is the cake. Hope you're hungry.
She's not kidding. There's enough food
in there to feed an army.
(SIGHS) She must be terrified.
Uh, more like furious.
Larkin died trying to protect her.
And it only makes it worse if the person
who did it looks just like her.
I mean, trust me, if Linda had
Doctor Light's powers right now...
What?
I just... Linda and Light,
they're identical,
so identical that Light even thought
she could fool Zoom.
And now we have Light's suit.
You don't have to say anything,
I know, it's a terrible idea.
No, no, no, it's not.
We make Zoom think
that Linda is Doctor Light
and use her to draw him out.
It's too dangerous, right?
Let Linda decide.
I mean, she's desperate
to catch the person
who's responsible for Larkin's death.
And she deserves the chance to help us.
-Okay.
-(SIGHS)
I still don't understand why we're here.
I thought your dad said
not to leave the house.
Someone wants to talk to you.
Who?
Ms. Park. I need your help.
Whoa!
(CHUCKLES) Dude.
How long you been sitting on this?
It's important to have hobbies.
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
This is ridiculous.
No, it's not.
You look just like Doctor Light.
And with these gloves
that Cisco rigged up,
you'll be able to do what she does.
Don't worry, they are totally safe.
-Ish.
-Ish?
Oh, come on, it's gotta be believable,
so they really do fire and explode things.
And you are gonna have to
let her hit you with those blasts,
once she gets the hang of it.
Who exactly came up
with this terrible idea?
CISCO: Okay, it's not a terrible idea.
The suit can absorb the blasts.
For real or "ish?"
What does a terrible idea
look like to you, Cisco?
Okay, you know what?
I like to think
I can see the bright side of things, okay?
Positivity, people.
All right, all right.
So, just hit the ones of me, okay?
-Got it.
-Great.
I'm Doctor Light.
(EXHALES)
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Uh, you know what, I'm just gonna
adjust those a little. Screwdriver.
Coming! Coming.
(CHUCKLES) It's just...
Okay. So, um, do the opposite of that.
And we'll have it.
(SIGHS)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(GASPING) It's on fire!
(SCREAMING)
-Ooh, sorry.
-(PANTING)
My bad.
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
-I did it! Did you see that?
-THE FLASH: Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
THE FLASH: Y'all good? You okay?
Sorry.
Okay. No offense to Linda
but there is no way she can pull this off.
Well, maybe if she didn't scream
every time she fired.
Yep! Linda had a rocky start,
but she can pull this off. I know she can.
All right, did you find someplace
near a breach
where we don't have to worry
about civilians getting in the way?
Yeah, there's a place by the docks
that's usually deserted at night.
Awesome. How are we doing
with the speed dampener?
My tests indicate that it should work.
It will work. I'll tune up Ramon's gloves,
make sure they work better.
Okay, great.
Hey, we're actually gonna go through
with this?
Yeah, we're doing this.
I'm gonna have Iris get Linda ready.
Yeah, I'll go talk to him.
Barry, hold up.
Hey, what?
You saw what happened in there.
Linda's not ready.
She is, she's ready enough.
Why are you pushing this?
Wait, why do you think? I want to get him.
Get who exactly?
Is that a real question?
You tell me.
I'm not sure this is even about Zoom.
It's starting to feel like
you're still chasing the Reverse Flash.
Reverse Flash is dead.
Yeah, but after all he did to you,
you weren't the one that stopped him.
We all worked together.
Yeah, and Eddie got him in the end.
I mean, that doesn't
make you feel cheated,
like you didn't get your revenge,
and stopping Zoom is the next best thing?
Look, all I'm saying is, if you're gonna
ask people like Linda to risk their lives,
you better be sure
of exactly why they're doing it.
Look, I'm sorry
I'm a terrible super-villain.
I don't need you to come here
and make me feel worse.
That's not why I'm here.
It doesn't matter. I... I can't do this.
I just don't have it in me.
THE FLASH: That's not true.
You're one of the strongest women
I've ever met.
You can do anything.
And you know that about me
based on what, exactly?
(SIGHS) Linda,
you are trusting me.
So, I need to trust you, fully.
I know that you can do this...
Because I know you.
Holy crap.
I've made out with The Flash.
Listen, I just want to bury the hatchet
and say thank you for all your work.
You're welcome.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
I think maybe the trigger mechanisms
are just sticking.
-I think it's just a little bit of...
-It's not the... Don't. No, it does not...
(SIGHS) I'm just gonna
clean this up really quick.
-Do not touch me!
-I'm just trying to help!
(JESSE SOBBING)
I know Wells went to the other Earth. Why?
JESSE: I don't know. I swear.
Your loyalty is admirable, Jesse.
(SCREAMING)
I'm sorry.
Joe. Doctor Light.
-I thought we settled that.
-No, we didn't.
She's still out there on the loose.
A meta-human who just murdered a man.
Why aren't we doing something about it?
Look, none of this makes any sense,
and you're not talking to me.
All right, all right, all right.
Look, it's a bit complicated,
but we're not going after Doctor Light
right now.
I need you to trust me, Patty,
for a few days or so.
Are you somehow involved in this?
If you're asking if I'm dirty, no.
But I need some time
to take care of some things.
I trust you, I do.
I wouldn't be your partner if I didn't.
But this is about you not trusting me.
Patty, I trust you.
Not enough.
A few days?
-Hey.
Do you wanna grab maybe dinner tonight?
I could use your opinion about something.
-I can't tonight, I'm sorry.
-Sure.
I would. Joe and I actually... Joe and I
have a thing that we've got to do tonight.
Some other time.
I would much rather
be spending the evening with you.
Seriously, if I could cancel these plans,
I would.
But can we do dinner tomorrow?
Yeah. I would like that.
All right. I'll see you.
Uh, good luck with your thing.
Thanks. I think I'll need it.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm here to kill The Flash
and no one can stop me!
(WHISPERS) How's that?
Uh, it's a little too much.
Uh, stop messing with the earpiece.
Yeah, you don't want to dislodge it.
Right. You... You told me that. I'm sorry.
No, no. You're doing great, Linda.
All right, Doctor Light. Here I am.
But we're gonna skip the part
where you say you're gonna kill me
and go right to the part
where I don't let you.
I'm here to kill you, Flash.
Wait, what are you doing?
We're skipping that?
(WHISPERS) Yes.
I am loyal to Zoom, so get ready to fry.
Next time we're doing this,
I'm writing better dialogue.
BOTH: Next time?
Uh... (YELLS)
(GROANS)
Gotcha!
-Yeah, you did.
-Real good.
All right.
(GROANS)
Bring it on.
Hmm. (CHUCKLES)
(YELLS)
Told you.
Zoom always wins.
-You're okay, right?
-Yeah, yeah.
I had to make it look good.
Here it is, Zoom! I did what you wanted.
Now bring me home!
Come on. Come on, come on.
This is everything he wants, right?
Come on, Zoom.
(WHISPERS) Hey, stop fidgeting.
I'm sorry. It's been an hour and I landed
in a ridiculous position.
My foot fell asleep.
He's probably just waiting
to see if you're really dead.
Any minute now, he's gonna strike.
(SIGHS)
No.
I'm sorry. I probably screwed up somehow.
No, Linda, you did great.
JOE: So, Wells ain't taking this well.
-Mmm-hmm.
-How about you?
Yeah, it just sucks, you know.
But you were right, a little bit,
about this not being just about Zoom,
about it being about the Reverse Flash.
-Okay.
-But not for the reason that you think.
Not because I didn't beat him.
It's... Wells,
he said something to me on that video
before he confessed to my mom's murder.
He said that even if he was dead,
that he still won because I wasn't happy.
That I'd never really be happy.
How the hell would he know?
He knew me. He knows future me.
That's future you.
This is the you here and now.
I still think that Wells was right.
Ever since I went back to that night
and I didn't save her,
I didn't save my mom, I just...
There's just been this void in me.
You know, I just feel like
that is always gonna be there.
For better or worse. Wells, he knew me.
Better than I know you?
He may have stalked you for 15 years,
but I raised you.
Look, Wells said what he said to you,
to mess with you.
To get in your head one last time.
If you listen to him, you let him win.
I know. I don't want that.
You're responsible
for your own happiness, Barry.
Forget about Wells.
Think hard about what you want
and what makes you happy.
Go out and get it. It's as simple as that.
-All right?
-Yeah.
(LAUGHING) And look at their eyes.
Amazing.
-(SIGHS)
-(CHUCKLES)
-Good to see you guys.
-Bye, Patty.
(LAUGHING)
Hey, have you seen this video
of babies' expressions
as they go through tunnels?
Their faces are priceless.
I'm not baby crazy or...
(CHUCKLES)
What did I do to deserve that?
I've just been thinking
about what makes me happy
and getting to know you makes me happy.
We should do more of that then.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Hey.
You know, I wish I could have
kept the gloves. At least.
(CHUCKLES) What would you have
done with them?
-Raves. Duh.
-(CHUCKLES)
That is not what you were thinking about.
I was thinking about a lot of things.
Like how everything that's happened to me
the past few days,
is the best story I can never write.
Ooh. Tell me about it.
(CHUCKLES)
Do you ever get used to it?
Keeping a secret that big?
No.
It's pretty heavy.
I need a good night's sleep.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna head out.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, hey, if we're gonna
be The Flash's sidekicks,
we should probably
join CrossFit or something, you know?
-Oh. Yeah, girl. (LAUGHS)
-Yeah.
Bye.
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(GROWLS)
Linda! (PANTING)
There you go.
It's like you think these things just grow
on trees or something.
And we threw away
the last one for nothing.
You have been going over this footage
dozens of times,
everything went exactly according to plan.
If it had, Zoom would have shown up.
Maybe Light was wrong.
Maybe he can't see through the breaches,
or maybe he finally decided to give up.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hey, Iris, slow down,
I can't understand you.
(BEEPING)
Zoom has Linda.
He's on the roof.
(CHUCKLES)
-Put her down.
-You like to fish with bait?
I do too.
(LINDA WHIMPERING)
(GROWLS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
You need to get out of here. Okay?
No. You can't fight that thing.
It's a monster.
Just go.
Zoom cannot be human.
He is. Or was.
How the hell is Barry
supposed to defeat that?
Why is he running away?
He's not. He's not scared.
Oh. He's gonna thunderbolt him.
-What?
-Jay taught him how to throw lightning.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Did you guys see that?
See him catch a bolt of lightning
with his demonic claws? Yeah, I saw that.
Jay was right. He cannot do this alone.
He's not alone.
CAITLIN: Run, Barry.
No. I'm gonna see
if Wells' speed-dampening serum works.
What do you want from me?
Everything.
You want to be me? Is that it?
You want to be a hero?
Heroes die.
Only if you can catch them.
How is Barry gonna match Zoom's speed?
Genius. He's not going to match it,
he's going to take it out of the equation
altogether.
-What are you talking about?
-Terminal velocity.
The highest velocity
attainable by a falling object.
-Falling through the air?
-Yeah.
Free-fall fight.
Their drag force
equals the downward force of gravity,
making the net force zero, making...
Equal velocities. That is genius.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Never forget. I am the fastest man alive.
He's killing him.
Barry.
You're next.
(GASPS)
Barry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Look at your hero.
(CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING)
This man is no god.
He is nothing.
(GASPING)
The days of The Flash protecting this city
are over.
-Hold your fire!
-Put him down!
Now, what will you do
without your precious hero?
Shoot that thing, now!
Nice try.
-Anything?
-No.
-Do you have him?
Barry.
ZOOM: Harrison Wells.
You thought you could defeat me with this?
I made a mistake.
Yes, a costly one.
(GROANS)
Good-bye, Flash.
You too weren't fast enough.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
No. No!
Stay with me. Stay with me, Barry.
Stay with me. Please, Barry. Please.
This is all you. If Barry dies, you die!
Joe! Barry's vitals have stabilized.
Let's let him go.
No, Caitlin.
Why? What good does that do for Barry?
It's gonna help me.
Joe, stop!
Who's Jesse?
How do...
Jesse's my daughter
and Zoom has her. You've...
-You did vibe me.
-Yes.
What did you see?
I saw your daughter. She was with Zoom.
But she's alive?
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Zoom sent you here like the others?
You kill The Flash
and you get your daughter back?
The only way I get my daughter back
is I capture Zoom.
Do you understand? You love Barry.
I love my daughter.
And none of these children are safe
as long as Zoom is here.
I tried on my Earth to capture him.
I failed.
I thought I could bring him down here
with Barry's help.
I was wrong.
Hey. I think he's waking up.
CAITLIN: Barry.
Barry? Can you hear me?
Hey.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You scared the crap out of us.
You were gone for a long time.
How bad is it?
Bad.
If you didn't heal so quickly,
I'd be very worried.
Linda. How is she?
She's fine. She's staying out
with some friends out in Coast City.
Zoom?
Let's... Let's worry about Zoom
when you're up and about.
Okay?
Oh, no. You're staying put.
Yeah, seriously. You got your ass kicked.
No, guys.
I can't feel my legs.