All clear, Ms. Kramer.
Four scans and three weapon checks.
I like the way you think, Agent Cooper.
Were you this serious
back at Fort Dakota?
The army fights
terrestrial threats, ma'am.
Here, it's that, plus a little extra.
- I know what you mean.
- As for the added lockdown?
We're gonna need it
for what you're proposing, ma'am.
The famous meta-human Killer Frost
will be sentenced today...
- So much for re-branding.
- Cecile, how bad is this?
Typically, Frost's charges carry
a sentence of ten to twenty years.
But today Judge Tanaka
is gonna weigh that
against all the good
that she's done as a hero.
And given that Frost
hasn't committed a crime in four years,
I can make a case
for a lighter sentence.
Eighteen months,
maybe less, with parole.
I mean, she already pled guilty
and skipped her trial.
What more does the court want?
They want to know whether or not
you are responsible for your crimes.
This is a load of crap.
You've saved the city
and more lives than I can count.
Jitters named a freaking
drink after you.
Exactly.
You know, I say we just make
like A Few Good Men
and just shove the truth
down the city's throat.
Guys, we're not looking for a loophole.
I did these crimes.
Caity, I know you want to help,
but ever since becoming my own person,
I've realized that if I don't own up
for my choices,
I'll never be able to move on.
What about all
the good things you've done?
About the life we're building together?
I miss you too.
But until I pay for what I did,
the rest of the city
won't look at me the way you all do.
Isotopic signature detected.
- The Forces. One of them is close.
- It's coming from Keystone City.
- Seismic isotopes.
- It's the Strength Force.
Barry, you have to go.
This is the chance we're waiting for.
- Listen to the cosmic lady. Go.
- She's right.
If Fuerza's back, people need the Flash.
We've got Frost's back.
Iris is running comms.
I'll come with you.
If that monster is here,
it won't be a match for us both.
You sure this is the right location?
Yeah. Satellites confirm it.
Fuerza should be right in front of you.
Why? What are you seeing?
Either our satellites
need to be recalibrated or...
The Strength Force is
better at hiding than we thought.
Keystone Cares. That's a nonprofit
that helps those in need.
Why would Fuerza be there?
So as you can see, Your Honor,
my client has already demonstrated
that despite her past mistakes
Frost now only wishes to serve this city
alongside our greatest protector,
the Flash.
Still, she's aware
that justice must be served,
which is why she's seeking
a fair punishment,
not only because it's
the right thing to do,
but to prove once and for all
who she really is.
She's a flawed person,
who has changed her ways
and become a hero in her own right.
Well argued, Ms. Horton.
Counselor Strong, would the State
like to make an opening remark?
By her own admission,
the meta-human known
as Killer Frost is guilty of crimes
that have endangered
the peace of our city
and the safety of our citizens.
And the State finds it absurd that
a former DA would romanticize
this narrative to avoid punishment.
It's early, and I haven't
had my coffee, Counselor,
but I don't believe the defendant
is asking to avoid punishment.
Agreed, Your Honor.
But the State has one goal.
To ensure that this
extremely dangerous criminal
no longer threatens our good citizens.
Which is why we believe
she must have her powers erased.
Your Honor, that is highly irregular.
I'll decide that, Ms. Horton.
Ms. Strong, please continue.
In lieu of prison, the State moves
to submit alternate punishment.
That Killer Frost
be compelled by this court...
to take the meta-human cure.
Kramer is damn good.
We're here looking
for a lighter sentence.
She's arguing that since felons
are prohibited from owning firearms,
Frost's powers are weapons
that the State can take away
using the cure.
A cure that C.C.P.D. only has
'cause we gave it to them.
A cure that's supposed to be voluntary.
How can Kramer just force Frost
to take it like that?
Is that even legal?
Yeah. You would be surprised
what can become legal
when you've got the full force
of the American justice system
behind you.
It can be pretty scary sometimes.
What if we forget the deal?
Just take the ten to twenty years.
Prosecution's not even
seeking jail time anymore.
Kramer is all about the cure.
She wants Frost neutralized forever.
At least it can't get any worse.
Actually, it can. I just spoke to Mom.
She's gonna run some more tests
to be sure, but we think that because
you are uniquely born from meta DNA,
if you take the cure, it could harm you.
- Maybe even kill you.
- This is insane.
Okay, no one is touching Frost.
- We're gonna stop this, right?
- Hell, yeah.
Okay. We need to fight fire with fire.
Hack Kramer, dig up dirt.
Whatever it takes to save Frost.
No. I didn't just turn myself in so
that I could go and break the law again.
We're doing this by the book
or not at all. Okay, Caity?
- Okay. You're right.
- Something still doesn't sit right.
Why would Kramer go so hard
to take you down?
I have no idea.
But all I care about now
is stopping her.
Well, we do that by convincing the judge
that you deserve prison time
and not the cure.
I've got some case law books back
at the office that we need to look at.
And, Joe, I think you can help me out.
- Okay. What are we really doing?
- I like your hacking idea.
We need to think bigger.
Frost's life is on the line.
Guys, I'm still picking up
Fuerza's isotopic signature in the area.
- You still don't see her?
- No, nothing yet.
Fuerza's signature is seismic-based.
Maybe she hides underground.
There's a lot of people here.
We should run them all away,
before things get dangerous.
No. The Forces want
to feed off our powers, Barry.
That's probably why this thing
attacked you in the first place.
Using our abilities too early,
even if it's to save others,
could put them in danger.
Yeah, I guess that is possible.
There's still so much we don't know
about these Forces.
We know all we need to.
They're dangerous.
I still remember how they attacked me.
Eating me alive.
I could feel it. It's pure evil.
I know. I felt it too
when Psych attacked me.
Wherever these things came from,
they have to be stopped.
- Yeah, I'm not so sure.
- What do you mean?
Well, the Sage Force is clearly
dangerous, and Fuerza too,
but do you remember
what Chester and Cisco
said about Deon, the Still Force?
That he was just a kid
who wanted to be left alone.
Yeah. I mean, does that seem like
a vicious energy feeder to you?
Something doesn't add up here.
Barry, the creature that we're hunting
killed someone and tried to kill you.
We can't let ourselves be fooled by the
human facades these Forces hide behind.
Underneath them,
these Forces have only one goal.
To destroy everything they touch.
You need to remember that.
Barry,
we've got another hit,
and it's coming from the next tent.
Great. Just put those
extra rations just over...
Wait. Are you two volunteers?
Uh, no, we're...
- No, actually.
- No? Oh.
Sorry. It's been a pretty busy morning.
I'm Alexa Rivera,
the field supervisor for Keystone Cares.
What can I do for you?
Mic check.
One, two, one, two.
- You ready?
- I sure hope so.
Officer Korber? I'm Caitlin Snow.
I was detained here the other day.
- It was a misunderstanding,
- Right. I heard.
- Sorry that happened.
- It's okay. It's all sorted now.
But when they released me,
they didn't return all of my belongings.
Really?
Yes. I'm still missing
a necklace and a bracelet.
- The bracelet used to be my mother's.
- I'm sure they're still in lockup.
Mm.
If you just want to fill out a 10-67
for loss of property, I'll get them.
Great.
Cisco, is the coast clear?
I am back-looping
the security cameras now.
You've got two minutes
before they're back up.
Which way am I going again?
This whole breaking into C.C.P.D. thing
is freaking me out.
When we gave them the cure,
they stored the surplus in the armory.
That's where you're headed.
- Uh...
- Just turn right.
Your other right.
All right. You're gonna attach
the inertial oximeter to the door.
It's gonna send out a pulse that will
neutralize all cure samples on site.
Almost there.
Can I help you?
You seem lost.
I'm from The Citizen.
I'm here for our interview.
Caitlin, Allegra needs backup.
Kramer's got her pinned.
Sorry about that.
- No one told me about any interview.
- They had to. I contacted your office.
They said you were
in charge of meta affairs.
- And clearly you were never told.
- No, I wasn't.
Okay, look, this is a huge scoop for me.
Could you just give me ten minutes?
How much time do I have left before
the cameras turn back on?
Twenty seconds. We have to deliver
the oximeter now or we're screwed.
Please. If I go back empty-handed,
my boss is gonna kill me.
Ten minutes. That's all I'm asking.
- You've got five.
- Thanks. Let's go sit.
Whoa. You should really
get that checked out.
Yeah. I'll have someone
take a look at it.
Ten seconds. Go, go, go, go, go.
The cure has been neutralized.
Now get the hell out of there
before I have a heart attack.
Wait. So am I under arrest?
No, no, no, no, no.
I am with C.C.P.D. but I'm a CSI.
- I don't arrest people.
- But you think I'm guilty of something.
Great. I'm never gonna
catch a break, am I?
I'm sorry. I don't follow.
Okay, fine. Yeah, it's true.
I was an addict.
Then I hit rock bottom
and that was a wakeup call.
So I got clean. I went to school.
I could have worked in a hospital.
But this is where I belong,
helping people just like me
turn their lives around.
Look, I've been to rehab,
and I don't have a record,
so whatever crime you're investigating...
No, no. It's nothing like that. We...
Um...
It's gonna sound kind of crazy,
but we've been scanning
the city for a new meta,
and for some reason,
our readings led us to you.
Seriously? I'm not a meta.
We're not so sure.
Well, then what do you want from me?
Alexa, we'd like for you
to come to S.T.A.R. Labs with us.
We work with a team there
that can conduct a simple,
painless test.
Tell us what we already know.
That you're the monster
who attacked Central City
and killed a man,
and tried to kill me too.
I have never
seen you before in my life.
And I'm not going anywhere with you.
Especially not S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah, I've heard of them.
They're the ones that started
all this meta stuff in the first place.
- Alexa, hold on. We just want to help.
- No, you hold on.
I am not a monster.
And if you don't mind, there are people
who actually need my help.
Please don't contact me again.
I don't see why you're so upset.
We know that woman is the thing
we've been searching for.
No. We think she might be.
But now we'll never learn the truth
because you scared her away.
Barry, the answer is simple.
If she won't come to us, we'll make her.
- What?
- We move in the blink of an eye.
She'll never know.
And by the time she does we'll test her.
And if she's innocent, return her
before she takes her next breath.
Nora, I know you're new to all of this,
but we don't just grab people
and test them against their will.
- Why not?
- Because...
- Lives are at stake.
- That's not how this works.
Well, maybe it should.
Barry, you and I know
what this thing is really capable of.
Now all I'm asking is for you
to trust me
and do what needs to be done.
Is that really too much for me to ask?
You're asking him to give up
a part of what makes him a hero.
So yes, Nora, it is too much.
Barry... it's your choice.
Captain West.
You're here to make
a statement on behalf
of the defendant. If you please...
I admit under oath that Frost
hasn't always been
on the right side of the law.
But I can also say that she has
put her life on the line
countless times to save others.
How so, Captain?
Frost has fought alongside Earth's
greatest heroes to save the world,
which means that she's saved
every person in this room,
including those who want to lock her up
for being who she was,
not for who she is today.
And, Your Honor...
I don't understand how this court
can force Frost to take that cure
without sacrificing what it stands for.
Justice.
Thank you, Captain West.
Your word goes a long way in this court.
Thank you.
In fact, I believe I'm ready
to deliver my verdict.
Your Honor, we have a new update
regarding a relevant incident
that could affect your ruling.
If it pleases the court...
Proceed.
Earlier today,
the meta-human cure supply
at C.C.P.D. was rendered inert.
It is now completely unusable.
The State suspects foul play
by the only person with motive
for such bold treachery.
- Killer Frost.
- No, I didn't do it.
It wasn't me.
I have not been to C.C.P.D.
- I have been here.
- Let me handle this, please.
Objection. Your Honor,
this is speculative nonsense.
Sustained. Prosecutor, do you have
evidence for your accusations?
Yes, Your Honor.
C.C.P.D. security cameras were hacked at
the exact moment the cure was destroyed.
We wouldn't have found out
if not for Ms. Kramer's
expertise in military intelligence.
She uncovered the hack herself.
It was me, Your Honor.
I did it. Not Frost.
- And I acted alone.
- She's lying, Your Honor.
Killer Frost is clearly
behind this crime
because her criminal past
is the same as her criminal present.
- I am not a criminal.
- Order.
I did it. I told you.
- I said order.
- Everybody, sit down.
Now, Ms. Strong, considering the cure
isn't a viable option,
can the court assume the State
is no longer seeking it as a punishment?
On the contrary...
And where exactly did you get that?
My colleague Ms. Kramer
knows the magnitude
of the meta criminal
we are dealing with.
So she contacted A.R.G.U.S.
on behalf of the State
and had them replicate the cure
based on C.C.P.D. samples.
We should have 100 vials
ready by nightfall.
All we need is your decision,
Your Honor.
Very well.
I'll retire to my chambers
and make my decision.
- Court is adjourned.
- All rise.
This is for your own good.
What just happened?
We just lost.
Babe, please tell us
you know a way out of this.
I'm sorry,
but I don't know.
I don't know how we're gonna keep Frost
from being forced to take the cure.
What's Kramer's deal anyway?
Kramer's had it out for me
since before I was arrested.
My gut tells me
she's still hiding something.
We need a miracle. And fast.
No, we don't, because we are Team Flash,
and we have more than enough resources
to figure this out.
Caitlin, we already
went that route, remember?
And all we did was make things worse.
Okay, well, I can't just sit here
and do nothing, okay?
Because Frost is my sister, and I have
to do everything I can to protect her.
Guys, I need to talk to Caitlin.
Alone.
You want to explain yourself?
Caity, you made me a promise
that we would fight this
the way I wanted to.
Okay, but that's the thing. Okay?
You are not fighting this.
You skipped your trial
and look how that turned out.
And whose fault is that?
It's Mom.
She got the test results back from
how the cure will affect your meta DNA.
Thank God. She says you'll be fine.
The cure will take away your powers,
but it won't harm you.
You're gonna survive.
Great. Whatever.
Frost, this is the miracle
we've been waiting for.
- This is gonna save you.
- By erasing my powers?
You heard Cecile, okay?
Even if we can convince the judge
to give you prison time,
you're looking at
ten to twenty years easy.
Then I'll take it.
Why would you give up
two decades of your life
when there is a perfectly safe solution?
Changing who I am is not a solution.
How the hell can you even ask me that?
You're the one who said
the cure should always be a choice.
Then why won't you choose this?
Do you remember when
the Sage force attacked
and I told you my greatest fear?
It's living life without you.
I am terrified of living a life
that you're not in.
Frost, you are my sister.
I love you. And I cannot lose you.
And if I take the cure, you will.
Caity, don't you see?
It's not me you're trying to protect.
It's yourself.
The Flash.
That CSI sent you, didn't he?
Alexa, I know everything you've heard
today probably sounds insane,
let alone terrifying.
But if you give me a chance,
I think maybe I can explain
why it's so important you get tested.
I already know why.
You were there
when Fuerza attacked Central City.
I was part of a team building
low-income housing that week,
and I just remember feeling so angry
when Abra Kadabra
destroyed our worksite.
I don't remember much else.
I've been having blackouts.
Just waking up in strange places
not knowing where I've been
or what I've done.
When was the last time it happened?
When this thing attacked.
What if... Oh, my God.
What if I am this monster?
Help me find out. Trust me.
I know how scary it is
to not have full control of yourself.
I haven't felt this way
since before I got clean.
I don't know if I'm strong enough
to know the truth.
I just feel so weak.
Alexa, the person who received
these cards is not a monster.
You've dedicated your life
to selflessly helping those in need.
Finding out the truth about yourself,
it's the same thing.
You'll be keeping people safe.
I don't know why...
but I feel like I can trust you.
All right, Captain West,
let's finish reviewing this so we can...
Joe arranged a little meet cute for us.
You and Captain West seem awfully close.
- I wonder why that is.
- We're poker buddies.
- What do you want?
- To know why you hate me.
Did I hurt you or someone you love?
Then why do you want
to take my powers away?
How is that justice?
You've got a lot of gall
lecturing me about justice.
You only turned yourself in
after years of evading the law
when you were surrounded by my officers.
That's not doing the right thing.
That's called getting caught.
Look, I'll go to prison,
do my time. Fine.
But forcing the cure on me?
I don't deserve that.
The court will decide what you deserve.
This isn't just about what you've done.
This is about what people like you do.
Right. So you hate all metas.
Very original. Cicada with a badge.
I don't hate all meta-humans.
Just the ones who pretend to be heroes.
I lost an entire platoon
because I made that mistake.
On my orders,
they followed a meta
I thought was a hero into a hot zone.
But he fooled me.
By the time I realized his betrayal,
20 soldiers lost their lives,
lives I was responsible to protect.
Never again.
This isn't just about me.
You want to go after all meta-humans.
Only the criminals.
But your sentence will set
the legal precedent.
First you take the cure.
Then any meta who endangers
the good of the people
will have to follow suit.
You cannot be serious.
I admire your fight.
But there is nothing
you can do to stop this,
'cause in the end, justice always wins.
You know, this whole waiting
for a verdict thing, it sucks.
Frost, I am so sorry. You're right.
I wasn't thinking about what you wanted.
I was only thinking about what I wanted.
It doesn't matter.
Kramer's gonna win and every meta in
the city is gonna lose because of me.
Kramer's trying to set a precedent
that any meta accused of a crime
can be punished with the cure.
I was just thinking about
all the meta lives that will hurt.
I don't even care about myself anymore.
I just want to help them.
Hey.
Aren't you supposed to be the one
telling me not to worry?
That we'll figure it out.
That's the thing, sis.
I think I just did.
Okay. This place is even
more intimidating on the inside.
Alexa, I know you're nervous,
but the Flash promised to keep you safe,
and we're gonna keep that promise.
Barry's right. And I'm sorry if
I startled you earlier, but don't worry.
Something goes wrong,
I'm sure the Flash will show up
and take care of everything.
Come with me. Speed Lab's this way.
It's been quite the long day,
but before I render my verdict,
I understand the defendant
would like to make a statement.
You ready for this?
Here's the deal.
Taking away a meta-human's powers
isn't the same thing
as taking away a gun from a criminal.
Erasing our powers
is erasing our identity.
It's saying, "Hey, you were made bad.
Change that."
But shouldn't justice be about
changing the way a person acts,
not the way they were born?
I get it.
You fear us because we're different.
You'd feel safer if we were the same.
But different can't be cured.
It's here to stay. We're here to stay.
Some of you only think of me
as the criminal I used to be.
Back then, I was only interested
in protecting myself.
But then, I found someone else
worth protecting.
And protecting that person led me
to protecting the whole city.
And slowly I changed.
I learned how to be selfless
instead of selfish.
I learned that I'm my best self
when I am protecting other people.
So with the help of someone close to me,
I've made a decision.
It's okay.
I am submitting a request
for life in prison without parole.
Your Honor, prison time is not
the punishment the State is requesting.
Correction, Your Honor.
The State's own words made very clear
that their only goal was,
and I quote, "to ensure this
extremely dangerous criminal
no longer threatens our good citizens."
Are those your words, Counselor?
Yes, Your Honor.
Then I'll remind Ms. Kramer she isn't
counsel and kindly ask her to sit down.
The court would like
to ask the defendant
if she's fully aware
of what she's proposing.
Yes, I am.
As am I that my judgement
will set a precedent.
A ruling for the cure
sets it as a viable punishment.
A ruling against it
takes it off the table.
Like my old law professor used to say,
in order for justice to be blind,
sometimes she must open her eyes
to ugly truths.
Therefore, I hereby sentence
the meta-human criminal
known as Frost...
to life in prison without
the possibility of parole.
Captain, I'm all packed up.
Just thought I'd say goodbye.
Good luck.
Listen, I know
we've had our differences,
and maybe that's an understatement,
especially after today,
but I just wanted to tell you,
despite our personal frictions,
you have my respect.
I admire your commitment to justice.
The feeling's mutual.
Truth is, I may not always
like your methods.
Sometimes I downright despise them.
But I know a good cop when I see one.
- Only that's not all, is it?
- No.
Make sure you're always checking
which side of the line you're on.
Hm.
Hush now
Don't explain
There ain't nothin' to gain
I'm glad that you're back
Don't explain
All my thoughts are of you
For I'm so completely yours
I don't want to hear nobody chatter
'Cause I know you cheat
Every meta in town
will know what you did for us.
Right and wrong don't matter
When you're with me, my sweet
Hush now
Don't explain
You're myjoy
You're my pain
My life
Is yours, love
Don't explain
So I just lie here?
Yeah. These arc radiators
emit isotopic energy.
I'll be using this tablet to gradually
expose you to those same isotopic waves.
- Are you okay?
- No. I'm scared out of my mind.
You're gonna be fine. I promise.
So if you're right about all this,
won't I change?
'Cause if that happens,
I could hurt someone...
You won't hurt anyone.
We're only administering a tiny dose.
Just enough to trigger
the smallest change
inside you on a microscopic level.
So if something is inside you,
our instruments will tell us.
Are you still sure you want to do this?
- Ready?
- Yeah. Her baseline is steady.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Just the way you inspired Barry
to reach out to Alexa.
You really are his lightning rod.
Alexa, can you hear me?
Get away from...
- Hey, it's okay. You're gonna be okay.
- No, I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
I am that thing.
What am I gonna do?
You're gonna be all right. You're gonna
be all right. Okay? You're safe here.
We're gonna help you deal with this.
I promise.
- Nora?
- You still don't get it.
If I don't end her now,
she'll sacrifice me
to get what she wants.
- My life.
- Wait. Listen to me.
I know you're scared.
We can still help her.
You should be helping me. I need your
powers to defeat her, and you promised.
But now you're breaking that promise
and I know why.
You may be his lightning rod...
but I'm the lightning.
Thank you.
Time to choose a side, Barry.