The Vatican announced today...
that Pope Paul VI has canceled his
Sunday blessing... due to ill health.
His physician has ordered total bedrest...
and cessation of all activities.
The purpose of this meeting is to ratify...
the motion passed by our
shareholders in New York.
What do you think about Altobello?
A very talented man.
He has kept the peace between
our Sicilian and American friends.
The saint of reason.
The Corleones left drugs, so New York
is weak, and Palermo is strong.
Your enemies always get strong
on what you leave behind.
Who could give the
order for that massacre...
and still pressure the Vatican deal?
Only Lucchesi can reach
between these two worlds.
Is there someone in the
Church we can turn to?
Someone we can tell our problem to?
Cardinal Lamberto.
A wise and good man... very influential.
He will see you.
Politics and crime,
they're the same thing.
Burns the moon in the sky,
and I burn with love
Fire that wastes away like my heart
My soul cries in pain
It has no peace,
what a terrible night
Time passes, but day never comes
There is never sun,
if she doesn't return
Burns my earth and burns my heart
She is thirsty for water,
and I am thirsty for love
To whom can I sing my song
If no one appears at the balcony.
Pope Paul VI, Supreme Pontiff
of the Roman Catholic Church,...
died last night at 9:40 p.m.
The Pope was 81 years old,...
and had been in poor health
for the last several months.
I am honored, Don Altobello, that you've
come from Palermo to visit me.
Hey, the little kid! He's grown.
Do the donkey for me.
It's been some time since
we did business together.
You are my "ace in the hole,"
as we say in America.
I have a stone in my shoe.
You can remove it.
Only one stone?
"Oh father, my father!"
"Give me some time
to pray to the Lord."
The Baroness of Carini had
betrayed her husband...
and fallen in love with her cousin.
"There will be no forgiveness!"
Her father stabbed her
through the heart.
Father, where are you going?
Would you like a ride?
I know you.
You're Mosca of Montelepre.
You were an assassin then,
and you're an assassin now.
I know Michael Corleone
is at your house.
I will pass through the gates with you.
What is it? What's wrong?
They found Don Tommasino shot.
Is he dead?
My master is dead.
Blood calls for blood.
I must have revenge!
Some day, you may have
to do a difficult service for me.
Command me.
I will avenge him!
Totals...
Lorscheider, 1 vote.
Siri, 11 votes.
Lamberto, 99 votes.
Do you accept your
election as supreme pontiff?
Oh, God, shed light on the decision
they have taken on my behalf.
I accept.
By what name do you wish to be called?
John Paul the First.
I will do things "right away,"
rather than in "a little while"...
Mr. Lucchesi's house?
I bring a message
from Michael Corleone.
Let him in.
Tea, Your Holiness?
It will help you sleep.
This is from Vincent Corleone.
Your Holiness?
Eminence.
The Holy Father is dead!
Speak... tell me.
You have lost the faith of the people.
He who builds on the
people builds on mud.
And Michael Corleone's message?
It's very important.
I must whisper it in your ear.
He's clean.
Power wears out those who don't have it.