Okay, this is insane.
- We need more Compound V!
- Absolutely.
We need more Supes!
More Supes! More Supes! More Supes!
Come with me.
What are you doing here?
I'm sleeping in a basement
beneath a pawn shop in East Flatbush.
I never wanted that for you.
We have
Ryan's best interests at heart.
- I want us to be a family.
- They flew me up and showed me!
This house, the neighbours are fake.
You're fake.
No! Ryan!
You have five minutes
to make your opening...
There's a supervillain
on your school campus.
You hear the calls of distress.
You witness a violent display
of superpowers.
What do you do?
I'm Sheriff Ed Flanagan,
and I'm here with Homelander
to talk about school safety.
On the first report
of an active supervillain,
a hero will immediately
rush to your campus.
But to stay alive in the moment,
remember, stay calm and follow the LAW.
Lock all doors and windows.
Arm yourselves.
Your teacher should have
an authorised firearm.
But use whatever you can.
And wait for a hero.
Unfortunately, the possibility that
you will experience a supervillain attack
grows more likely every day.
By having an action plan,
you can increase your chances of survival.
And survival is all that matters.
- Coverage of the attack...
- Jody! Where's my flag pin?
How should I know?
Well, I can't go to this thing
without a flag pin.
Bob, before he makes any decisions,
just let me talk to him.
One, the president doesn't like you,
he used the word "standoffish."
And two, he's decided.
He's declaring a national emergency,
bypassing the FDA,
and authorising Compound V for use
by law enforcement and first responders.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- I wish I were.
Doses are going for 5 million a pop.
Pentagon's got a big order in,
and ICE is next in line.
You can't release V into the mainstream,
we're talking an avalanche of Supes.
It's suicide.
In one hour,
I will be standing at the memorial service
for the fallen heroes of the House attack,
with my flag pin!
Giving my thoughts and prayers
and pledging to keep America safe.
The best way to do that
is with Compound V.
We know. We there, remember?
Covered in my chief of staff's brains.
There was no terrorist, it was Vought.
It's a fucking coup.
- A bunch of their guys died too.
- To cover their own tracks.
For the record, I agree with you.
And I hate this.
But you've got no proof.
Folks are scared.
If Vought took a shit
in the middle of Fifth Avenue,
they'd throw a ticker tape parade.
- Here's what we do have, Bob...
- Oh, let me guess.
A tape of me fucking my kid's nanny
at her daughter's quinceañera?
Release it, please, I'm begging you.
A plumb gig at Fox
and this shithole in my rear-view?
Sounds dreamy.
Okay, what if we got hard proof?
A witness? Anything?
If you could get
Jesus Christ himself,
or maybe Homelander
in front of a camera, sure.
I really am sorry.
I'm nervous about driving
in the city.
You'll be okay. The plan again?
Okay, drive straight to Gen's in Sedona.
Cash for gasoline, no hotels.
- I don't wanna leave you here.
- I'll be fine.
The anxious boy? Really?
With the moist handshake?
- Mom! God.
- Okay. All right, okay.
Um.
You need a new one.
I...
I'm not gonna wear it.
I don't care if you wear it.
I just want you to have it.
I love you.
I love you too.
You be safe.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Hey.
- What's going on?
- They've lost their minds.
The RPG releases
an electromagnetic pulse on impact.
Should cut through
Stormfront's plasma bolts.
- How sure are you?
- It's a guesstimate.
So that's Stormfront.
And thanks to Starlight, we know
that Noir needs any fucking tree nut.
How about A-Train?
Enough epinephrine
to blow up that motherfucker's heart.
- Hey, we can't just kill everyone.
- That is exactly what we're gonna do.
Listen, you heard Mallory,
she said all we need is another witness.
Wile E. Coyote.
Always chases Road Runner.
Always with an elaborate plan.
Always fails.
I always say, why do this, Coyote?
All you need is an AR-15
and "meep-meep," no more.
Exactly. See? We're just gonna shoot
Road Runner in the fucking head.
That won't stop Vought.
That won't stop Compound V.
If you kill these Supes,
Vought will just make a thousand more.
I'm gonna top those cunts too.
Great. So that's settled.
- We're just supervillains now, huh?
- Vought attacked the country, Hughie.
Fuck them all.
What if I testify?
Escaped convicts
don't have a ton of credibility.
No, but maybe I know someone who does.
Give us the day.
Hughie.
See you later.
...officials are still trying to determine
the perpetrator of the Capitol attack.
The Department of Homeland Security
has issued a crimson terror alert.
In Washington, all government buildings...
- How's Noir?
- Unresponsive.
They don't think there's brain damage,
but it's hard to tell.
Noir's a vegetable.
Lamplighter's a charcoal briquette.
Starlight's in the breeze somewhere.
And you're, what, fine with it?
Yes, because none of that matters anymore.
Because of this.
So far, no terrorist group
has claimed responsibility...
- All right. So, you didn't do this.
- I wish I'd killed Vogelbaum.
- But, no, it wasn't me.
- Right.
And there's no supervillains
on American soil.
- None that we know of.
- Then that means...
It's Edgar.
Maybe. I mean, he is pretty smart,
especially for his kind.
...Compound V to members of the military
and law enforcement...
Hey, smile. This is good news.
Yes, there have been sacrifices,
but we are this close
to no more premieres or paparazzi.
Or screaming fans
or any of that dancing-monkey shit.
We have to make sure that
the right people get the doses,
but it is a whole new world.
What about the wrong people?
Couple of billion of them,
they're not just gonna sit there.
Don't worry, silly.
Frederick had a solution for everything.
Okay. There's something really important
that I've been meaning to ask you.
Last I checked, you're not 57 years old.
So, come on,
why is it always, always Billy Joel?
- I'm 57 on the inside.
- No, really. Please.
It was just the music
in my house growing up.
I did some somersaults
to "You May Be Right"
that were pretty thrilling to watch.
♪ Only the good die young
That's what I'm saying... ♪
Butcher is right, you know.
We've already tried
to take Vought down the right way.
This isn't gonna work.
This is not gonna stop Compound V
from getting out there.
So it's hopeless?
Just kill them all, let God sort them out?
I mean...
Then why are you even helping me?
Why did you save me at the Tower?
They were gonna hurt you.
You could've gotten yourself killed.
I mean, after the way that I treated you,
you had every reason to give up on me.
So why didn't you?
I just... would never.
That's why I'm helping.
You were stupid to text.
Everyone's looking for you.
Where's Elena?
This is the guy?
Um...
I'm... Hi. Hughie.
He's even more of a twink
than in the photo.
I could split that shit like dry firewood.
Big fan.
I need to ask you something.
It's a lot.
- I need you to testify.
- Testify?
On the record.
Against Vought, against Homelander,
Stormfront, everything.
- And why would I do that?
- Because things are really bad, and...
you're our last chance.
Pass.
- Look, I get that it's dangerous.
- It's suicide.
- But that's not the reason.
- Well, then what is?
I'm tired.
We're all tired,
but they're hurting people.
Sooner or later,
they'll hurt someone you love.
Am I talking to you?
Look...
I get that it's easier
to just disappear inside of yourself.
Trust me, it's all I want to do.
But we can't, Maeve.
We can't.
- This is a war now, and we...
- Shut the fuck up.
Christ, you...
Haven't I done enough for you?
Didn't I save your fucking life?
It doesn't matter what we do.
Nothing changes.
Nothing ever changes or gets better.
And I'm tired.
Just leave.
Go!
Take your fucking twink
and get the fuck out of here!
Okay.
Come on.
Monsieur Charcuterie, we need you. Now.
He said he lives under a pawn shop
in East Flatbush!
- He has to be here! Help me.
- Let her in.
Billy. They took him.
- They have Ryan.
- Who's got him?
I appreciate you
coming all this way, Stan.
Well, I can't exactly be seen
with you at the Tower now, can I?
- Fresca?
- No, thank you. Awful stuff.
So you had a chance
to look over our proposal?
He publicly confessed
to a sexual assault, Alastair.
And we've made a substantial investment
in the Deep's rehabilitation.
Our internal research bureau
shows an impressive Q rating.
He's an asset to Vought
in these troubled times.
Oh, what sort of commission
is the church getting these days?
Forty percent? 50?
Sounds like you're open to reinstatement.
That's fantastic.
What about A-Train?
You do need a speedster
since Shockwave exploded.
Harder sell.
One has-been back is redemption.
Two is weakness.
Stormfront has problems with him.
And at the moment, I have to indulge her.
What's her problem with A-Train?
I understand that she was among
your grandfather's first followers,
back when the Collective was a start-up.
I can neither confirm or deny that.
Then your internal research bureau
knows exactly
what Stormfront's problem is with A-Train.
Deep is still a win.
- Shall I have Business Affairs reach out?
- Please do.
Let me walk you out.
Sons of bitches.
Okay, yeah.
Voilà.
Jambon buerre. Simple,
but it's the ingredients, you know?
- Thank you.
- Diet Coke with lime, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
We've heard a lot about you.
I'm sorry, I wish I could say the same.
- Are you all close with Billy?
- Yeah.
I mean, sure.
- Why the hesitation?
- Well...
let's just say he ain't really close
to a lot of people. You know?
- Well, except you, of course.
- I'm close to him.
I am.
- All right, lads, give her some air, eh?
- Yeah.
So Ryan ain't on
any of their social media.
Which is good on one hand,
but it don't help us none.
- So you think he's in the Tower?
- Not sure.
You stay here. Rest up.
I'm gonna go do a little digging.
Hey, Billy.
I'm sorry. I have no right to ask you
to help me after what I said to you.
Look, don't you worry, all right?
I will find your son.
Thank you.
Fuck off, you lot.
What is it, Samantha?
Mr. Edgar,
normally I wouldn't put this through,
but the man says it's life or death,
and you know him.
- What's his name?
- William Butcher.
Hi, hi!
We've been having
a super fun time in here.
I've been googling
the names of the cats in Cats.
- Can you believe Ryan has never seen Cats?
- What happened to your hair?
- Nothing.
- Hey, buddy.
Sorry we had to leave you all alone.
Dad's work can sometimes get pretty crazy.
He hasn't been alone. I've been here.
I got him all these dipping sauces.
You didn't wanna play
Vought Tournament of Heroes?
- I'm the main guy.
- I was working on my states.
States?
Yeah, I write down all 50 states
as fast as I can
in either alphabetical order
or geographical order.
- You're giving yourself homework?
- Mom says that learning is a gift, so...
Mm. Mm.
That mom of yours, she sure does
have some cute little sayings.
Do you think maybe I could call her?
Hey, Ryan.
I get it.
I would feel lonely too,
if I was cooped up all day by myself
in this West Elm Death Star.
Mm-hm.
How about we take a field trip?
What do you say, Dad?
Welcome to Planet Vought.
Have a super day.
Let's give a warm hero's welcome
to Cashket who's turning five today.
Welcome to Planet Vought.
Would you like to try our new
Brave Maeve Rainbow Veggie Burger?
Holy shit!
Here you go, maestro.
- Pretty cool, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey, wait until you try
the Big Homey with bacon.
It's so good. And, uh...
And the Mocha Noir Shake?
It's amazing.
It won't be lumpy like your mom's.
- Homelander?
- Hey.
- Can I get a selfie?
- Ask the boss.
Kidding. Of course you can.
Stormfront, I love you.
Can I get a selfie?
Oh, sure. One at a time.
- Homelander! I'm a huge fan.
- Kids first.
Can I get a picture?
- All right.
- Homelander!
Hey.
Hey. You okay?
I want my mom.
Okay, I got you. I got you.
Thank you, everyone. Excuse me.
Thank you. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Stay back, please.
Please, please, please. Just stay back.
Stay back. Thank you.
- New bling?
- Mm-hm.
Donna got it for me.
I'm pretty sure she got it at Duane Reade.
Oh, gosh, moms.
The gift that keeps on giving. Forever.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
Oh, no, it's fine.
No. No. I'm an asshole for bitching
about my mom when yours is...
My mom's not dead.
She's not? Oh, it's just
you never mentioned her, so...
She left when I was six.
Oh, wow, shit.
I'm really sorry.
That's where Billy Joel comes from.
She and I, we used to have
these dance parties.
She was fun.
She made awesome
Seven costumes for Halloween.
And then one day,
she just left and never called again.
Not even a card.
You know, it was like some
silent alarm went off and she was, like,
"Well, fuck them, time to go."
No, I'm sure that that's not it.
What would you call it?
I guess that's why I always
just kind of hang in there,
no matter how bad it gets.
'Cause I don't want to be like her.
That's kind of clingy and pathetic,
isn't it?
No. No. It isn't.
At all.
What's up, shitbirds?
What the fuck? What the fuck?
- How did you find us?
- Please.
I can cover the boroughs in three hours.
I went looking, that's all.
- I'm surprised your heart can take it.
- My heart is just fine.
- Take a step closer and I'll show you.
- Hey, I saved your life, asshole.
Now you're coming after us?
We're even now, bitch.
Holy shit!
Is this true?
Everything makes more sense now,
doesn't it?
- Where did you get this?
- I didn't get it, okay? I was never here.
You got that shit on your own. Yeah?
But why are you doing this?
'Cause I want back in, so I need her gone.
Fuck that Nazi bitch.
Would you ask Mario if he could whip up
some of those Gruyère puffs?
Would you like an order?
They're worth the cheat day.
I assume you got a man out there,
with a clean shot?
More than one.
Then I'll skip the fucking hors d'oeuvres,
if you don't mind,
and we'll just cut straight to it, yeah?
You mentioned on the phone
that you could help with Homelander's son.
I must say, I'm not sure what you mean.
That boy is your only possible
contingency against Homelander.
Now, that contingency don't work
if they're off playing Ward and the Beav.
I can fix that.
Thank you, Alvin.
Homelander's a friend.
Why would I betray him?
Because you're a ruthless bastard.
That's hurtful.
You turned a racist piece of shite
into America's sweetheart.
Now, what word would you use?
Stormfront's good at making people angry.
Angry people want Compound V.
Compound V raises our stock price.
I'd have preferred V remained a secret,
but we play with the cards we're dealt.
It's not ruthless, it's prices per share.
That's all.
Maybe you should
take a look in the mirror, mate.
'Cause that bitch should bother you.
Of course she does, but it's not about me.
I can't lash out
like some raging, entitled maniac.
That's a white man's luxury.
So it's just business then, eh?
When, Mr. Butcher, in history
has it ever been about anything different?
And what makes you think
that you can control that racist bitch?
Look, I've got to get across town...
I can get the boy away from Homelander,
all right?
How?
That's my business.
When I got him, I'll call your people,
they zero in on this cell signal,
and come and scoop him up.
And then you do a better fucking job
hiding him this time, yeah?
You have my word.
I will get Rebecca and Ryan
somewhere safe.
No. Not Becca. Becca stays with me.
But that's the whole point,
that he's raised by his mother.
Find him a new fucking mum.
I'm taking my wife back.
That's the deal.
And what happens when Rebecca
shows up at my doorstep,
begging to be reunited with her boy?
You say it's the only way
you can guarantee
Ryan's protection from Homelander.
'Cause as you know,
a mother will do anything
to protect her son.
And you call me a ruthless bastard.
You tell me where he is...
and I'll do the rest.
- Where's Ryan?
- He's inside.
- He doesn't want to talk.
- So go in, anyway.
No, no, no. I've tried.
He wants to be left alone.
You are the strongest man in the world,
and you're scared of a little boy.
He's your blood.
Just talk to him.
Be the man I know you are.
New York. North Carolina.
North Dakota.
Ohio. Oklahoma. Oregon.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no. Buddy, don't you be sorry.
I should've known better.
There were just so many people.
Yeah, there was.
You know, I remember
the first time I was in a crowd.
Probably didn't bother you.
I was terrified.
All these people staring at me
and reaching out, trying to grab me,
and egging me on to use my powers.
I just... I felt like I was drowning.
Well, what did you do?
Well, I took off.
I flew away.
They found me 80 miles down the I-9,
crying my little eyes out.
You cry?
Yes.
But I'm a man, so not in a long while.
But who knows? Maybe, uh...
maybe next time, you'll fly away.
Maybe with me?
Look, I know you want me to be like you,
but, Dad, I'm not.
Son...
I didn't just wake up one day
and fly out the door.
That's not how it works. I had to learn.
Only I didn't have anyone to teach me
'cause the doctors that, um...
The people that raised me,
uh, were scared of me,
so they kept their distance.
And I had to figure it all out
by myself, see?
Well, you don't have to
go through any of that.
I'll teach you.
Really?
I love you.
Hey, did you find anything?
They got him in a cabin up in Rochester.
- What?
- I mean...
Becca. She's great.
We talked earlier, and she's really great.
You're really... You're great.
Easy, tiger.
How'd you get on?
I guess you got fuck all?
No witnesses.
But we definitely found fuck all.
I'm not sure
I'm using that term properly, but...
Here.
Fuck me.
This is a jackpot.
Well done, you two.
This'll do nicely.
All right, listen up, you lot.
Getting the kid back ain't your fight.
I ain't gonna ask you to come along.
Lick my big Black balls, Butcher.
Sorry, Becca.
You done asked us to lie, spy,
do all kinds of fucked up shit for you.
Now we finally get a chance
to do something good,
and you think we'll take a pass on that?
We're in.
Of course we're in.
All right.
Let's get a shift on.
What?
You remember the range at Fort Bragg?
I was a better shot than you.
Well, you had a bloody good teacher,
didn't you?
I like your friends. Especially Hughie.
He's, uh... He's good for you.
Look, Becca, you ain't coming with us.
No, bullshit. Ryan doesn't know you,
he'll never come to you.
It's too dangerous,
I ain't gonna lose you again.
He's my son and I'm coming.
I need you to promise me something.
I need you to promise me
that you will save him no matter what
and you will get him back to me.
- Yeah. Of course.
- You realise this isn't just about me.
He can't grow up like Homelander.
You have to think of all of the people
out there that he would...
Swear to me, then.
Swear to me on your brother's soul.
I swear to you.
I swear to you on Lenny's soul.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
I can use your help loading the car.
What if it happens again?
When I see Stormfront...
Stormfront...
...what if I freeze?
"Freeze," yes?
Sorry, I'm still learning.
Look...
If there's one thing I know,
it's that you can take care of yourself.
So when the time comes...
you'll know what to do.
Let's go.
Keep going. You got it.
That's it, don't give up.
That's it, that's it. Keep going.
Little more, little more, you got it.
Hey, that's okay.
You'll get it, you'll get it.
Um...
I know what. Imagine...
Well, sometimes, it helps
to imagine someone you hate. Okay?
So try that.
But at home, when I say "hate,"
I have to put a quarter in the swear jar.
Well, there's no swear jar here,
so you can hate away.
But I don't really hate anyone.
Well, that is very sweet, Ryan.
But it's not something we can afford.
We're under attack.
We are?
Bad guys want to hurt us
just because of what we look like.
They want to wipe us from this Earth
just because of the colour of our skin.
Really?
It's called White Genocide.
We're gonna need people like you
to protect our kind.
Hm.
All right. So let's try again.
Go for it. Imagine...
You gotta be fucking kidding me!
What?
Are you sure this'll work?
Don't worry, it will work.
This is nothing compared
to the raves I used to set up in Algiers.
Do you dance?
Of course I dance.
What is the point of life without dancing?
She's on the move.
I see her, Frenchie.
We gotta go now. You close?
One moment, mon ami.
- Holy shit. It just broke.
- News from Vought Tower,
concerning Stormfront
and alleged Nazi ties.
Stormfront may be 100 years old.
What's even more incredible,
we have authenticated photos
showing Stormfront with Nazi High Command,
including Goebbels and Göring.
Based on the photos, it is now believed
that she was the wife of Frederick Vought,
who was, of course,
the founder of Vought International.
Already, an intense international outcry
has emerged under...
I can't believe I actually
have to say this, this day and age,
but Nazis are bad.
It's catchy.
- You ready?
- Oui.
But the question now is,
how can we possibly
let Vought release Compound V
in light of this
unprecedented malfeasance?
- What's malfeasance?
- A Nazi in Seven Tower?
- Was she part of the attack?
- It's a... Never mind.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Stay here.
Now!
Ryan! Hey!
Hey. Hey.
Hey, bud. Hey.
- Mom?
- It's me.
- Mom, Mom, Mom!
- Come here.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean anything I said.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean any of it.
- It's okay.
- Got to go.
- I love you so much.
You're okay.
We're gonna go, okay? Come on.
Who's that?
That's my husband.
It's all right. Come on.
I got you.
Come on, to the car. This way.
What the fuck?
What the hell are they doing back?
Butcher, this wasn't the plan.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Take my car.
Get them both to Mallory.
Get them both safe.
- No, no, that's not part of the plan.
- The plan just changed.
M.M., you're the only one
I trust with her.
Hey. What's happening? No.
M.M.'s gonna take you
to a woman with the CIA.
What? No, you have to come with us.
I cut a deal with Stan Edgar.
What?
I cut a deal that when I got Ryan,
that I would call Vought.
They were gonna come and take him away,
and you'd never fucking see him again.
What?
But, fuck me, I couldn't do it.
Bedroom's clear.
- Kitchen's clear.
- All rooms secure.
Butcher? You here?
Did I hear you say "Butcher"?
- What's going on?
- Do you have the boy?
Where is my son?
Where is my son?!
I'm not leaving here without you,
I don't care.
I was gonna sell you out.
I fucking well might do it again.
You didn't, though.
You didn't and you won't.
You can't have a cunt like me
around that kid.
I don't wanna pass my shit on to him.
Don't say that. You have to come with us.
You raise him right.
Raise him right,
and I'll make sure they never find you.
Don't you say that! Stop it.
Stop, you have to come with us.
Becca, we are out of time.
Please...
you gotta let me do this.
You got to let me
do this one fucking thing.
Becca!
There you are, you slippery little bitch.
I'm assuming it's you
who sent all those lies to the press.
They're not lies.
The pictures are clearly deepfakes,
and you're a lying slut.
Here we go, yeah?
People love
what I have to say.
They believe in it.
They just don't like the word "Nazi,"
that's all.
Are you all right?
- You all right? Yeah?
- Ryan. Ryan, Ryan.
Ryan! Ryan!
Ryan? Come here.
Are you okay?
Go! We'll hold her off.
You're okay.
What about the truth?
What truth?
What is the truth?
And what are you laughing at?
She says the truth is,
she's gonna stick her boot
up your Nazi kitty.
- Annie!
- Come on, the RPG!
It's in the car! It's our only chance!
Hey, Kraut.
♪ You've got them all by the balls ♪
♪ Causing waterfalls, Stonewalls
Bar brawls ♪
♪ Climbing stalls at concert halls ♪
♪ To you they crawl, body sprawl ♪
♪ Smoking Pall Malls
Close call, stand tall ♪
♪ Doll, you make them feel so small ♪
♪ And they love it ♪
Eat my shit, you Nazi bitch!
Die, you bitch!
Girls do get it done.
Fucking bitch!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Come here, Ryan.
Not on your life.
You're not like her, Ryan.
You belong with us.
Stay the fuck away from my son.
We love you, Ryan.
You fucking bitch.
Stop! Stop it!
Stop, please! Stop it!
Stop, you're hurting her! Just let her go!
Let her go!
Stop!
Look at me.
I like to see the light go out.
Stop!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
No. No.
No. No, no.
- Hold on.
- Please.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Help us!
Somebody help us!
It's not his fault.
You make sure he knows that.
Yeah?
He's good. He's good.
He's good.
You promise me you keep him safe.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
Mommy.
Mom...
Mom, please.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ryan?
Did you do this?
I didn't mean to.
Let's go.
Come here.
Come.
Ryan.
Come here.
No.
He's mine.
What, are you gonna blow yourself up...
to save the little shit
who fucking murdered your wife?
I promised.
Have it your way.
Stop.
What are you doing here?
You're gonna let them go.
And if I don't?
- Please!
- Don't die with them.
Let them go.
You're gonna stop hunting Starlight.
You're gonna leave me and Elena alone.
Take my daughter!
Or I release this.
If you do that...
I'll destroy everything and everyone.
Great, as long as everyone sees
what a fucking monster you are.
As long as no one ever loves you again.
Homelander! Homelander! Homelander!
We believe that Stormfront
was the sole perpetrator
of the attack on Washington.
In the light of Stormfront's atrocities,
the release of Compound V
has been placed on indefinite hold.
Homelander.
Mr. Edgar, a follow-up question.
Are there any more
Compound V terrorists out there?
Thanks to the heroism
of Queen Maeve and Starlight,
Stormfront has been neutralised
and is being held
in an undisclosed location.
I would personally like
to apologise to Starlight,
who was wrongfully accused
of sabotage and conspiracy.
Welcome back to the team.
And I know that you and Maeve
are two of the best,
most loyal friends that I could ever have.
We are your heroes.
We are here to serve and protect you.
Stormfront's violation
of that special relationship,
of that trust, is unacceptable.
And she will be punished.
Justice will be served...
Justice will be served.
She will be punished.
As the leader of The Seven,
I give you my word, no one will ever...
Gentlemen, thank you for coming.
Always happy to see you, sir.
I'm afraid we had an incident
at the Archives.
Someone broke in
and stole PDR on Stormfront.
PDR?
Private data reserve.
No one saw the thief come or go.
Isn't that right... A-Train?
That was you? Dude!
I didn't know, sir. Fuck him.
I would never go behind your back.
Please, just let me explain.
I think it showed initiative.
Stormfront's been critical of the church,
and Vought needs to take
a firm anti-Nazi stance right now.
Wait.
Does that mean...?
I just spoke to Stan Edgar.
You're back in.
- Fuck, yeah!
- What? Yeah!
Yeah! A-Train is back, baby!
- Yeah!
All right.
- Finally.
- Yeah.
I'm back too, right? Right?
I'm anti-Nazi.
I'm sorry, Deep,
but they only had one slot.
One hero is redemption, two is weakness.
So they took him?
Fuck, yes, they did!
Well, shit!
Peace out, bitch! Ha, ha!
You have to be patient, Deep.
We'll get you into a few more courses,
up to Level 7.
I don't wanna pay for more courses!
Deep, please calm down.
I signed over my bank account to you.
I filled out all those
fucking children's workbooks,
I married some weirdo
who gives terrible blowjobs.
I did everything you asked,
and when I found out that we're all just
fucking space spores, I didn't laugh.
I did everything you asked.
Because you said you'd get me back
in The Seven, you fucking promised.
I'm sorry, Deep, but you are acting
like a toxic personality.
I think you should leave.
Fuck Fresca.
- Look at you.
- I know.
I know.
But if Billy Butcher
can do the right thing,
then there's got to be
some kind of higher power.
You know?
Are you sure it's safe for you
to go back into the Tower?
No.
No, I'm not...
but if you jump ship
and you let the assholes steer...
then you're part of the problem.
And...
someone taught me something
about hanging in there.
I've been thinking about that lately,
the hanging in there.
And I think maybe I am too clingy.
No, you're not.
Sticking with people
just because I'm terrified of losing them?
I... I can't do that anymore.
I think it's time I go off,
stand on my own two feet for once.
Right. Um...
Yeah, no worries. We'll, um...
We'll just be friends, then.
Oh, God, no. No, no, no,
I'm still gonna cling onto you.
I'm not fucking crazy.
So if you weren't talking about me,
who were you talking about?
I'm scared.
This here...
belonged to your mum.
This is St. Christopher.
She gave it to me a long time ago...
and told me... it would keep me safe.
And it has.
Mostly.
Now your mum...
is gonna help keep you safe.
Come on.
Now, remember what I told you.
Don't be a cunt.
William, I'm so sorry.
Vought's gonna want him back.
Let me handle Vought.
You think he'll turn into his father?
Becca didn't think so.
I pray she's right.
All the charges against you and the boys
have been dropped,
even for the crimes you did commit.
You're a free man.
And the White House
is opening an Office of Supe Affairs.
Victoria Neuman is the new czar.
She's sneaking me
some off-the-books funding
for a team that can
keep tabs on the Supes.
If you're interested.
♪ I may not always love you ♪
♪ But long as there are stars above you ♪
♪ You never need to doubt it ♪
♪ I'll make you so sure about it ♪
♪ God only knows what I'd be without you ♪
♪ If you should ever leave me ♪
♪ Well, life would still go on
Believe me ♪
Where to?
♪ The world could show nothing to me ♪
Dancing.
♪ So what good would living do me? ♪
♪ God only knows what I'd be without you ♪
I can do... whatever I want.
I can do whatever... I want.
I can do what I want.
I can do whatever the fuck I want!
Congratulations on the appointment,
congresswoman.
It's about time
we had an Office of Supe Affairs.
Well, I know it was your intel
that took Stormfront down, so thank you.
Yeah, and that's just the start.
We have enough dirt to ruin a dozen Supes.
It'd be a death blow for Stan Edgar.
That is, of course,
if you're open to, uh, expediting
the church's tax-exempt status.
Small price to pay.
- Call my office, set up a meeting?
- You are one of the good ones, Vic.
See you soon.
See you.
- Here's the research you asked for.
- Thank you.
- And your 2:00 is waiting.
Hugh Campbell.
I don't know how to repay you
for what you did.
You know, I can think of a way.
Oh?
You can... give me a job.
You serious?
Uh...
What about your team?
Don't get me wrong,
I still want to fight Vought. I just...
I want to do it the right way,
not covered in quite as many guts.
Look, the truth is,
I never totally fit in with the guys.
And...
I think it's time
I stand on my own two feet.
- They know you're here?
- I haven't told them yet.
When can you start?
♪ Come out, Virginia, don't let me wait ♪
♪ You Catholic girls start much too late ♪
♪ Aw, but sooner or later
It comes down to fate ♪
♪ I might as well be the one ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ That's what I said ♪
♪ Only the good die young
Only the good die young ♪
♪ You might have heard I run
With a dangerous crowd ♪
♪ We ain't too pretty
We ain't too proud ♪
♪ We might be laughing a bit too loud ♪
♪ Aw, but that never hurt no one ♪
♪ So come on Virginia, show me a sign ♪
♪ Send up a signal
I'll throw you the line ♪
♪ The stained-glass curtain
You're hiding behind ♪
♪ Never lets in the sun ♪
♪ Darlin', only the good die young ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ I tell ya
Only the good die young ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪
♪ Oh, she never cared for me ♪
♪ But did she ever say a prayer for me? ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Come out, come out, come out
Virginia, don't let me wait ♪
♪ You Catholic girls start much too late ♪
♪ Sooner or later it comes down to fate ♪
♪ I might as well be the one ♪
♪ You know that only the good die young ♪
♪ Tell you, baby ♪
♪ Only the good die young ♪