- On the heels of the
Cold War, Barry Goldwater,
a business man and a five
term United States senator
from Arizona decided to run
for the election of the presidency-.
He had a substantial impact...
- Are you excited for summer?
- Yeah.
- Are you gonna see your friends?
- No.
- Why not?
- Don't have any.
- So you'll be with your brother?
- Yeah.
- But Milo I think
we've seen each other enough
that we trust each other, right'?
- Yeah.
- You know you can
answer honestly with me?
- Yeah.
- There are no consequences.
You understand you don't get in trouble?
- Yeah.
- Have you been
hurting any animals?
- No.
- Not at all, not even thinking?
- Maybe thinking, but no.
- So you're thinking about that?
Tell me about that, tell
me about the thoughts.
- It's nothing, just thoughts in my head,
but I don't do it, not anymore.
- Where you going?
Come here.
- Fuck him up G.
- Hold him.
- Hit him.
Stop it retard.
That's nasty.
You got to run bro, that was tucked up.
- That's right you
better run little bitch.
. Hey-
- Did you buy milk'?
- No.
- We need milk.
- Did you pay the internet bill?
- No.
- I need the internet.
- Then pay it.
Get milk too.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Do they eat all that?
- Yeah well they scoop
out, they pull out that stomach
and they eat the whole
stomach lining eventually.
- Milo.
- What?
- You gotta
disappear for a few hours.
- Okay.
- Hey freak.
Don't ignore me mother fucker.
- Yeah it's time to go home freak.
- Yo lock up your dogs.
- You're a weird
ass mother fucker yo.
- The elevator's broken.
This way.
- Hello?
Could you help me with my bags'?
Thanks so much.
- What floor?
- Nine.
What's your name?
- Milo.
- Holy shit, thanks again.
- Goodnight.
Does that hurt?
- What the fuck'?
- I'm sorry, I saw you here earlier.
- Yeah.
They're dicks.
You want a drink'?
- Sure.
I guess that was a stupid question.
- What?
- Does it hurt?
" Sex?
Not really.
- No.
- Oh,
yeah I mean it's like,
it's like a release.
Well it's not like I'm
making that arm any uglier.
- What's that?
- Psoriasis.
It's not catchy or anything, don't worry.
- Can you catch it from blood'?
- What?
- Like can I get it from your blood?
- No no no it's not like that.
- Can I see?
Can I see'?
- Oh my god gross.
- Sorry-
- I mean, I mean kind of sweet, but gross.
Oh you're really into...
- Vampires.
- I was gonna say scary movies.
- No, vampires.
- Like Twilight?
- Yeah, no.
I don't know, I haven't watched it.
- Well you should they're really good.
- Do you want to watch a video?
- The average American
consumes 120 pounds of beef per year.
In a typical month
slaughterhouses across the country
will kill nearly three million cows
and 385,000 lambs.
Each individual on the assembly line
has his own specialty...
- I need to go, I'm
late for this thing so.
- Yeah.
Sorry.
- It's fine, I just, I just have to go.
- What the fuck you doing'?
- Nothing.
- Let her go.
- Look at her, look at her.
- Hello?
Hello?
- Milo!
Hey, Milo wait up.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Where are you going'?
- Home.
- Walking?
- Yeah.
- Cool, can I walk with you?
- Sure.
- Do people ever tell
you you don't talk a lot'?
- No.
- Really?
- No one ever speaks to me.
Sorry for showing you that video.
- Don't worry about it.
My friend Leo loves sick videos like that.
He used to show me that
kind of stuff all the time.
I mean it's no big deal I just had to go.
- No, it's fine.
- Do you ever think about suicide?
- Not really.
Can't kill myself.
- You can't kill yourself?
- Yeah.
I can't.
- Like against your religion'?
- I mean, yeah sure, it's just the rules.
It's just the way it is.
My morn killed herself.
- Oh my god, I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
It's just something that happened.
Goodnight.
- Goodnight.
- Do you want to go to the
movies with me tomorrow?
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay, cool.
- What time?
- Noon.
I'll stop by your place.
- Hi.
Ready?
- Did you like it?
- I thought it was interesting,
I liked the music,
but I still think Twilight is better.
You should see it, or read it,
you know at least the first one.
- I prefer Let the Right One In.
- What's that?
- Maybe I'll show it to you some day.
- Okay.
You know you're the only
one who hasn't like,
immediately asked me what I'm doing here.
- Do you live with your parents?
- No my grandfather, he's pretty awful.
I mean I guess the best
thing about him is that,
is that he's slow so he
can't catch me that often.
- Catch you?
- Yeah he's a violent motherfucker.
Put a cigarette out on me last week.
I almost went to the cops.
- Well,
guess you don't like your grandpa much.
- Yeah it's fucked up.
- Where's your dad?
- He's dead, they're both dead.
- On.
Mine too.
- Really?
- Yeah, my dad died when I was like eight,
but he got sick when I was like six.
I mean it was, it took a
long time for him to die,
but when he did die it was
like a release you know?
He was yelling and screaming all the time.
- Jesus.
- Yeah, it is what it is.
It's just, I bet the vampires in Twilight
aren't very realistic.
- There's no such thing
as a realistic vampire.
- There is.
I mean more realistic.
I mean, vampires don't twinkle.
- Okay so what are vampires like?
- Well, I think it starts
with drinking blood,
like you have a need to.
It's like when you have
a cut on your finger
when you're a little kid
and you're sucking on it
but eventually that's not good enough
so you switch to animals
and stuff like that
and then you know, people.
And well you change a lot
after the first person you kill
and you change a lot more
after, after one after another.
But I think when you first
start oft being a vampire
all the stuff you see in the
movies doesn't really matter.
Like you can go out in the
sun and you can eat garlic.
I don't even think the
church stuff is even true,
like maybe it's a
religious vampire you know?
And I don't think you get bit,
I think it's like a disease you get.
- Wow.
Which book is this?
- It's not a book it's
just how I think it is.
Vampires existed before books did.
- Well the sun kills them in True Blood.
- I did not watch that show,
it did not look like it was
gonna be realistic at all.
- Oh my god you should it's so good
and this one, in this one episode,
the vampire that makes Eric
starts feeling like really
bad about what he does
so he kills himself, he like
goes up on a roof I think
and then the sun comes
up and just kills him.
- I mean it could be true
but I don't think a
vampire can kill himself.
- Why not?
- I don't know it's
like an animal instinct.
- So, they get to live forever?
- Maybe.
I don't know yet.
- Do you go to their graves'?
- No.
I don't go to my mom's grave,
I wouldn't even know where to go.
- What do you mean?
- My brother handled everything
and he doesn't like to talk about it.
- You didn't go to the funeral'?
- No, they said I shouldn't.
- Well then why not ask him'?
- I don't think that's a good idea,
he's weird about it, he
doesn't like to talk about it.
- That's so fucked up.
Would you go if you knew where she was?
- I guess.
- I'm gonna find
her, I mean, do you mind?
- I guess not.
- I'll go with you to yours
and then you can come
with me to mine, deal?
- Okay.
- Cool.
- Yo freak!
- No no that's not good
enough freak come over here.
- No no just keep walking.
- It's best if we go.
- What's up, who's your girlfriend?
- My name's Sophie.
- Hey why you slumming
over in the ghetto Sophie'?
- Haven't you seen her,
she live around here.
- Yo that ass, no fucking way my nigger.
- You all right white bitch?
I'm sorry I don't mean no
offense I'm just playing.
So why you living here white bitch?
- I live with my grandfather.
- Is he that mean old white motherfucker
up on the ninth floor?
- Can we go?
- Of course you can go I
ain't your fuckin' daddy.
Tell your brother I said hi freak.
Come on man.
- Jungle fever.
- Fuck them man.
- They seemed nice.
- They're in a gang.
Some of them have killed people.
- Don't, that was sarcasm.
- I had fun tonight, I'm sorry about...
- Goodnight.
- Yeah.
Milo.
Wake up.
- What?
- There's some white
girl waiting outside for you.
- Hound her.
So what's your favorite vampire movie?
- I guess the most realistic,
like I like Martin a
lot, it's this 70's one,
and it's good, it's realistic,
and Near Dark is really good
it's pretty cool and realistic
and the one I was telling you
about, Let the Right One In.
I'm not sure how realistic it is,
I mean like she can climb on walls
and I think maybe they're
just really good climbers,
and Shadow of the Vampire, it's good,
it's pretty cool and realistic.
- Do you miss her'?
- I guess I do.
It was about the making of Nosferatu-.
- I miss them.
I forgot to bring flowers.
- What does it matter
whether you brought flowers or not'?
She's not gonna know.
- You want to talk?
- Not really.
- Yo it's that white girl again
she's at the door.
- Tell her I'm not home.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Go ask him.
- Yeah'?
- Yeah, ask him, now now now.
Hey, hey bro, little brother.
- Hey kid.
- Hey what's up man.
We were just wondering
if you knew where we could buy some C?
- Yeah, please, or
we could give you some molly.
- Dude don't, don't sell anything.
Dude we're just wondering, you
know, could you help us out,
if you knew someone or?
- We're visiting from out of town
and we were hoping to
party tonight.
- Yeah I'll help you.
- Cool.
- Come on.
- Yeah awesome.
Alright I'll be right back.
Hey wait up.
Hey!
Oh Shit-.
- Come on.
- Hello?
Hello?
Yo I'm gonna leave,
this is kinda fucked up.
Hey what's up?
You guys must be them, right'?
I'm looking for some C or
some molly if you got it.
- Wait hold up what?
- Cocaine or molly?
- Oh so you think everybody
that live up in here
is a drug dealer?
- No, dude this kid sent me here...
- Why the fuck you asking for
drugs if you don't think that?
- Whoa, whoa okay, I'm sorry,
I don't think anything...
- You don't think you fucking racist.
- Whoa, I'm not racist okay.
- That's exactly
what we fucking need.
- Fuck, you a cop?
- Okay this is just a
misunderstanding I think.
- This is a misunderstanding,
this motherfucker.
- Okay I'm just gonna go now.
You guys are on the door.
- Now shut the fuck up.
Little G, Little G,
hey what should we do with this dude huh?
- Let's fuck him up.
- You hear that?
- Dudes come on look.
- Get him, go ahead
get him, fuck him up.
- On shit.
- Yo what the fuck is wrong with you
hitting a little kid huh?
- What the tuck do you think this is huh'?
You come up here talking about drugs
and then you're gonna swindle Little G?
Hey man, stop crying, come over here.
You want to hang with us'?
Shoot this bitch.
- What?
- Chill.
Shut up.
You gonna do it or not?
- Wait what are you doing?
Wait, please, please.
- Oh shit wait.
I didn't know he was
gonna pull the trigger.
- Come on man!
- Well I had the safety on.
- What the fuck are we gonna do now?
- Shit, come on, speed out, come on.
- Hey!
Hey you, tell me where Mike is.
Stop, hey!
- You passed my building.
- Hold on just a minute.
Oh yeah, right here looks good right'?
- Do you think they're gonna snitch?
- Thanks Milo, stay safe.
- Welcome home.
Where you been last night?
This place been crazy.
- Yeah I bet.
- We were on TV.
- We were?
- Our building.
Someone killed a white
boy in the basement.
- No shit?
- Yeah, it's been crazy, it's
been on all the news channels.
- Cool.
- Why are you avoiding me?
- I'm not avoiding you.
- Liar.
- I'm not a liar.
- Well liar I got you this.
It's Twilight.
- I see that.
- Promise me you'll read it?
- I promise.
- Milo?
What are you doing in here?
Come on get out.
Are you gonna tell me
what the fuck is going on?
I heard you talked to the police.
- I didn't talk to them, they took me in.
- Then why'd they give
you a ride home then
if you didn't talk to them?
- They said that if I didn't help them
that they'd make it seem like I snitched.
- Hey they'll kill you
if they even think you talked to them.
- I didn't tell them anything.
- Alright, you know it
doesn't matter what I think.
You saw it?
- Yeah.
- Shit-.
Did they see you see it?
- No.
I don't know.
- Milo I can't protect you from them.
You know that right'?
- Lewis, stop.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Lewis.
- And don't trust the
cops either, alright?
They're frame you tor that
shit just 'cause they can.
- Okay I get it.
- Listen to your older brother.
- Alright I understand.
- Alright.
- So this is what you do, you sit up here?
- I study.
- That's cool.
Do you believe in God?
- No.
Do you?
- I guess.
Yeah.
I had a feeling that you didn't.
- I mean like, I think we're all special.
I believe in that, I guess it's magical,
but I don't think anyone intended anything
and I think when you die you're just,
you're just gone.
- Don't say that, it's so fucking creepy.
- It's true, I think.
- Okay, okay moving on.
What would you do with a million dollars?
- What if I told you I had $1,000,000?
- Then I'd steal it.
- You would?
- No,
but I'd ask to borrow some.
- What would you do with it'?
- Get out of here, you know, move out.
- Where would you go?
- Anywhere.
But I have a cousin in Alabama.
She let me stay there.
I could pitch in, probably go there.
- Cool.
- Okay so what would you
do with a million dollars?
- I've got plans.
- That's it'?
- Yeah, I've got plans.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Asher.
- Bye.
- Yo Milo.
You talking to five, O?
- No.
- That's not what we heard.
- You heard wrong, I don't do that.
- That kid screamed like
a little bitch right?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Oh come on you don't think he screamed
like a little bitch?
It's alright, Malik said he saw you there.
Right Malik?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Don't act fucking smart okay?
- I'm not.
Can I go?
- This ain't over.
- Do you want to do it again?
Stop.
So I'll see you tomorrow then?
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Uh-huh I see you bro.
- Lewis.
- What?
That was nice.
- Lewis!
- What?
- What day is it?
- Friday.
- No, the date.
- 14th-.
. Hey-
- Hey, what's up?
- Nothing.
Can I watch TV with you'?
- The neighbors heard me screaming
and threatened to call
the cops so he let me go.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I don't think I need to
go to the doctor or anything.
I just really don't want to go back there.
- She okay?
- Yeah.
- Can I stay here'?
- Sure.
- Where's the ChapStick?
Where's the ChapStick?
- Don't you think you
should get your stuff'?
- You really thought I've
been in the same outfit
for like a week?
- And borrowing my clothes.
I mean it's tine, it's just,
you have to eventually right?
- Yeah.
- You can stay here as
long as you need to.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Are you sure you don't mind me not coming?
- It's fine.
Used to spending time by myself anyways.
- Thanks.
Oh and then...
- Oh we'll get your stuff.
Think I've convinced Lewis to come.
- Okay let's see.
- We'll do it, see you soon.
- Hi.
. Hey-
- Sorry I was, I was
wondering if you had a stamp,
and an envelope?
- No.
- No?
- I don't know.
- Okay, okay then.
- So you really like him?
- Yeah, I do.
- Hi, I'd like to cash this check
and pay these two bills with it.
And can I get a money order?
- She didn't say anything, she just left.
- Hi.
I know,
I know you saw that stuff,
but if we could meet then,
if we could meet then I could explain.
- Seven,
two, three, four, nine, seven...
- God damn you.
- Fucking.
- Fucking faggot.
- You fucking loudmouth bitch.
Shut up.
- I warned you.
- You look like shit.
- When you were there did you kill anyone?
- No.
No.
I saw a lot of parts,
you know like body parts after bombings
but no I never killed no one, why?
- I was just wondering.
- You do what you have to do,
no matter what.
Whatever it is you're doing,
there's someone doing a
whole lot worse, you know'?
- I guess.
- No, ain't no guess,
you gotta remember that.
No matter how bad you think you done
there's somebody doing a whole lot worse
who's doing now.
- You think?
- You can trust me, I know.
I fucking know.
Ain't nothing you doing as
bad as what people are doing
all the time to each other.
You know what people
just close their eyes to
and let happen.
You know I bet whatever it
is you're worried about,
it ain't nothing compared
to the shit that goes on.
- Yeah.
Goodnight Lewis.
- Goodnight Milo.
- What?
- Milo and Lewis.
You know it's like she gave us names
she knew we get our asses kicked.
- Yeah.
- I miss her.
- I miss her too.
- Hi.
I'm sorry for leaving like that
and for not speaking to you.
I wasn't snooping I was just
looking for a pen and paper.
I didn't even really know what it meant,
but it kind of freaked me out.
I mean I shouldn't have
just left like that.
I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
- So, so what was all that?
Are you working on a book about vampires,
a crazy killer or something?
- It's nothing that matters any more.
- Really, 'cause it
seemed really detailed.
Did you come here to write more'?
- I'm not writing anymore,
I'm making a plan.
- Shit, you're just
giving all this to me?
- Yeah.
- Why the fuck would you do that?
- So we can trust each other again.
I never spoke to the cops.
- Is this stuff hot'?
- Yeah, very.
- You got all this yourself?
- Yeah.
- How?
- I broke into places.
- It's a lot of valuable shit.
- So we're cool?
- Yeah motherfucker whatever.
- Okay.
- Wow.
- Lewis said girls like flowers.
- They mostly do.
Thanks.
This was nice.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- What?
- What's with your fucking crazy eyes?
- Huh?
- Drink?
- I wanted to give you something.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's for you to go to your cousin's.
- Where did you get it?
- Don't tell anyone you
have it, just, just go.
- Do you want to come with me?
I mean you have to come with me.
- I can't.
- Why not'?
- You wouldn't like me in the end.
I'm not good, I never will be.
- No but I already know that you're crazy.
- I'm not going, just,
just make sure you go.
- Milo.
- Drop the fucking gun!
- Women's history in this regard
tries to merge two approaches,
that have been used in the past.
There's contribution history,
which views women as...
- Can I go?
- You know we can't end early.
- Can I draw?
- What would you draw?
- I've been drawing the sun a lot lately.
- So you heard huh?
- No.
- They arrested all of them.
Andre, Troy, Mal, all of them.
- You mean all your old friends?
- Yeah.
Don't remind me.
You didn't know'?
- No, why would I?
- It's on the news even.
They say they killed that
white boy in the basement
and some white family in the Village.
- Really?
- You didn't know'?
- No.
- Yep-
- I just wanted to see if you left.
Call me.
- Hey freak.
- Hey.
Now you're not calling me?
Call me back, maybe come and meet me?
- I read Twilight,
I thought it sucked,
not very realistic at all.
I've been thinking a lot
and maybe a vampire can kill himself.
I mean maybe not kill
himself but arrange it.
Like if he could do something
and know that it would get him killed.
That would get around the rule I think.
I'm not sure vampires
should, are meant to be here,
I mean I know they've always been here.
But I mean if you can
only exist to hurt people
and you know better
then maybe it's better to
decide not to exist at all.
♪ When you have no one
♪ No one can hurt you
♪ In the corners
♪ There is light that is good for you
♪ And behind you I have warned you
♪ There are awful things
♪ Will you miss me when I have burned
♪ And will you eye me with a longing
♪ It is longing that I feel
♪ To be missed for or to be real
♪ When you have no one
♪ No one can hurt you
♪ Will you miss me when I have burned
♪ And will you close the others eyes
♪ It would be such a favor
♪ If you would blind them
♪ There is absence, there is lack
♪ There are wolves here abound
♪ You will miss me when I turn around
♪ When you have no one
♪ No one can hurt you