Cleaned, corrected, dashes removed
and capitalization fixed by Tronar
My name is Barry Allen,
And I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
But secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
And find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on the Flash...
Ronnie was vaporized
in the accelerator
When it went critical.
Ronnie's alive.
I saw him, Cisco.
Firestorm.
I wanted to talk to you
about firestorm.
We had some rudimentary success
with our stage one testing.
- Professor Stein...
- Professor Martin Stein?
He was our team leader.
I know what really happened
to him that night.
In the mass of energy.
Looks like...
- Ronnie.
- And Professor Stein.
The dark matter
merged them together.
So how does a superhero
get ready for a date?
Same as everybody else.
♪ This hit, that ice cold
Michelle Pfeiffer ♪
♪ That white gold ♪
♪ this one's for them
hood girls ♪
♪ Them good girls,
straight masterpieces ♪
All right.
Everyone tells you to just
be yourself.
♪ Got chucks on
with saint Laurent ♪
♪ Got to kiss myself,
I'm so pretty ♪
But who is that really?
If you change one more time,
I'm gonna shoot you.
♪ Uptown funk you up
♪
♪ whoo, come on ♪
♪ uptown funk you up ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ say what? ♪
♪ Uptown funk you up ♪
♪ uptown funk you up ♪
Punctual.
Yeah, yeah, that is
what my friends call me:
Mr. Punctual.
Is that lonely-looking flower
for me?
Is this dumb?
I thought about getting
a full bouquet,
But then I thought
that was weird.
No.
It's awesome.
All right.
Mm.
Okay.
Yes!
Victory.
I told you these were the
spiciest tacos in Central City.
Oh, I thought
you were bluffing.
I never bluff.
Just say it, I am the champion
of all things spicy.
You are the spice champion
of Central City.
Well, this requires
soap and water.
- I'll be right back.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Robbery at the convenience store
On brand and Paulson.
Man, come on.
Kind of on a date.
Can't the cops get this one?
Fine, but when you read
in the paper tomorrow
About that poor little old lady
getting robbed...
How do you know
it's a little old lady?
Please,
it's always a little old lady.
Okay, all right.
No little old lady.
Your move, Allen.
What's next?
So what's wrong with you?
Why hasn't someone
snatched you up yet?
Oh.
It's work.
Just a sec.
Hey.
- Hello.
- Hey.
I know you're on a date,
but we got a jumper
On 52nd and Waid.
Sir, please,
you have everything to live for.
No, I don't.
Are you gonna let me go
back up there?
No.
Well, thanks.
Yeah.
What was that for?
To see if I wanted
a second date.
And?
Let me see one more time.
Definitely.
Quentin Quale.
Can I help you, young man?
Haven't been called that
in quite some time.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
We went to school together.
You're one of my students.
No, classmates.
University of Chicago,
class of '74.
We protested the war.
Make love, not napalm,
remember?
Look, I don't know if this is
some kind of practical joke...
I know about your brother.
The truth is,
he committed suicide.
You found the body.
I never told anyone
about that.
You told one person.
Martin?
I need you to help me.
Dude, you are a crime-fighting
lady-slaying machine.
Oh, god, it was so cool.
She was so cool.
We're going on another date
tonight.
Tonight? Really?
Aren't you worried
about moving too fast?
No. What do you mean?
It's a second date.
No, no, no, no, I meant
going too fast, hurrying.
Look, I mean, you're fast,
But there's fast,
and then there's fast.
Am I being subtle enough?
- You're really not.
- Cisco's right.
With your increased blood flow
and increased heart rate,
Theoretically, your speed
could cause you to...
You're gonna need to think
about a lot of dead puppies.
Like, we're talking
a whole kennel.
And baseball.
Cold showers.
You know what?
Nuns.
Okay.
It is just a second date.
A second date? With who?
Uh, with Linda Park,
the sports reporter.
Hello?
That's great.
Linda seems great,
and you're great.
So... Great.
Hey, I gotta go.
I gotta help out a friend.
Everything okay?
We just got here.
Yeah, I'll see
you guys later.
Quentin Quale
was attacked near his lab
At concordance research
last night.
There were several
unsubstantiated reports
Of the so-called "burning man"
In the area
following the attacks.
Burning man?
Caitlin, weren't you asking
about him a few weeks ago?
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
Thanks for meeting me.
Sure.
What exactly are
we doing here?
That's Barry's old house.
Where his mother
was murdered?
I have a theory about
who might have been involved
In Barry's mother's death.
I thought you and I could
reexamine the crime scene,
You could apply
your technical expertise
And help me prove
who really did it.
For sure,
we should get Dr. Wells
And Caitlin in on this.
No, we should keep this
between us
For the time being.
If too many people know,
Barry will find out,
And I don't want
to involve him
Until we know
something definitive.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm Detective West.
This is Cisco Ramon.
Oh, please, it's Sherry,
like the drink.
What can I do for you,
Detective?
I don't know
if you were aware,
But there was a homicide
in this residence
Approximately 15 years ago.
Oh, I know.
We've reopened
the investigation.
Do you mind if we come in
And take another look around?
Oh, not at all.
Thank you.
Do you live alone?
Yes, I'm divorced.
Well, it appears
letting Ronnie roam free
Is no longer an option.
He's not even Ronnie anymore.
He's Martin Stein walking
around in Ronnie's body,
Like a vampire.
Is there a reason
that Stein's brain
Is in control
of Ronnie's body,
Not the other way around?
Simple Darwinism, I suspect.
A brand-new organism
will select
The strongest parts of itself
in order to survive.
Survival of the fittest.
In this case, Ronnie's body,
stein's mind.
In any event,
he badly hurt an innocent man,
And we have hunted
meta-humans for less.
Caitlin, we need to know
that you're on board
With what needs to be
done here.
How do we find him?
Quentin Quale, the scientist
that Ronnie attacked,
Is a former colleague
of Martin Stein.
If Martin is indeed in control
of Ronnie's body,
He may be trying to figure out
exactly what's happening to him.
What do we know about him?
I don't even know
what Stein looks like.
Martin Stein.
That's Stein?
It is.
I've seen him before.
When?
On the train, the day
the accelerator exploded.
Super cool, isn't it?
Uh, S.T.A.R. Labs,
I mean.
Yes, it's...
Super cool.
Trust Harrison Wells
To build a particle accelerator
with a bit of style.
Most scientists
don't have an appreciation
For the value of aesthetics.
Albert Einstein said,
"once you can accept
"the universe as being
something expanding
Into an infinite nothing
which is actually something"...
"wearing stripes
with plaid becomes easy."
I thought people your age
Didn't read actual books
anymore.
Oh, I'm the only one.
Oh. Mm.
Physics.
Hobby or endeavor?
Both, actually.
I'm a CSI.
I work for the Central City
police department.
Really? You look
too young for that.
That is what they tell me.
Are you gonna watch
the accelerator turn on tonight?
I wouldn't miss it.
They say
it's going to change the world.
I hope so.
Carson station. Carson station.
Oh, this is my stop.
- It was nice talking to you.
- You too.
Maybe I will see you
there tonight.
Excuse me.
I'm taking a girlfriend.
Not my girlfriend,
she's just, uh...
Sorry... she's just
a female friend
Who I'm not dating yet.
The doors are about to close.
Yeah.
Don't turn it on!
Caitlin, whatever happens...
of course
I've heard of S.T.A.R. Labs.
Martin was always vocal
about the competition.
S.T.A.R. Labs is actually
helping the CCPD
Looking into your husband's
disappearance, Mrs. Stein.
Oh, please.
Call me Clarissa.
The Conway prize
for scientific advancement.
Martin was very proud
of that one.
I'd always hoped to win
one of these myself.
Oh, and look at that.
He won it three times.
Takes a special kind
of person
To make Dr. Wells
jealous.
Well, Martin had a talent
for making people jealous.
Even me.
I sometimes think Martin loved
his theorems and experiments
More than he did me.
I'm sure that's not true.
And you haven't heard
from your husband
Since he disappeared.
No.
Mrs. Stein, could I
show you a photograph?
Have you seen
this person before?
Yes, I have.
- Who is he?
- Um...
He's just a person
of interest
In your husband's case.
When did you see him?
I started getting the feeling
that someone was watching me,
And sometimes I still do.
And about a month
after Martin disappeared,
That young man
showed up here.
What happened to me?
A month...
A month.
Clarissa.
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
Under the loose stone.
You leave a key for me there.
I'm always losing mine.
Losing my keys.
Losing my mind.
I'm going to call the police.
Where is my body?
I see my life,
but I can't reach it.
Please send someone.
There's an intruder
in my house!
So it appears Martin Stein
and Ronnie Raymond
Have something in common
besides sharing a body.
They both feel the need
to protect the women they love.
Clarissa said she feels
like she's being watched.
Well, then,
This has all the makings
of a stakeout.
But Barry's got
a date tonight.
I'll cancel.
No! No, go.
If we need you here,
something tells me
We can get you back
in a hurry.
I'm not picking up anything.
Not even with the super light.
Super light?
Well, technically
it's a multi-spectrum,
Ultraviolet laser-enhanced
scanner that detects
Molecular schisms
in the 600 mega-volt range,
But I figured "super light"
was easier to say.
Right, but what does
it tell you?
Nothing we didn't
already know about that night.
Okay, keep looking.
Ahem.
Uh, can I get you boys
something to drink?
Water? Soda?
Wine?
Uh, we're fine.
Thank you.
Well, if you change your mind,
I've been told
My strawberry daiquiris
are sinful.
I will not judge you.
Okay, Barry's mother's body
was found here,
Knife beside her,
Blood spatter on the wall
belonged to Nora.
Joe, I think...
I just think maybe
it's been too long,
And everything's different.
Except that mirror.
Sherry must have bought it
at the estate sale.
Oh, my god.
Silver nitrate.
The compound used
in photography.
It was often used
to back vintage mirrors.
If there were two speedsters
there that night,
The sparks from their movement
would have generated
Enough flashes
to actually expose images
Onto the silver nitrate.
You saying what
I think you're saying?
This mirror might
contain photographs
Of what actually happened
that night.
Hey!
You look great.
Well, I have
a big date tonight,
And I kind of wanted
to impress the guy.
I think I can speak
for that guy
And say that he is
super impressed.
So is this your place?
It's awesome.
Yeah. Well, not entirely.
I grew up here.
Is it really lame
that I live at home?
Not at all.
I still live with my parents.
Really?
No.
That would be so lame.
All right,
so here's the plan.
First, a dinner reservation
at paper clip.
Then a round of mini-golf,
followed by Mal Duncan,
Who is playing
at an underground jazz club.
But my foster dad
has a connection there,
So he hooked us up.
And if you're not
sick of me by then,
We can get froyo.
Or...
want some of my fries?
No, thanks.
Why would he come back here?
Because this is his home.
I don't mean
the actual house.
I mean Clarissa.
She's his home.
We all want to go home again.
You know, where we feel safe.
Where we feel loved.
Ronnie's your home.
Not anymore.
Remember what I told you on
your first day at S.T.A.R. Labs?
"A scientist's work
is never finished."
A scientist's work
is never finished.
Well, my work did this
to Ronnie
And did this to Martin Stein.
But it's not finished,
and it won't be
Until we bring them
both home.
So I'm assuming
you have Barry on speed dial?
♪ You and me, we made a vow ♪
Mm!
Whoa! What's wrong?
That felt amazing.
I just got a little excited.
I would hope so.
Sorry, Linda, I'm just, um,
A little worried about, um,
Moving too fast.
It's okay.
I hate slow.
♪ Denying every tear ♪
I'm sorry, I should check
Just in case
it's an emergency.
Ah!
Okay.
♪ I still need you here ♪
I'm so sorry.
It's important.
Not that this isn't important.
It's just that, um,
this other thing
Is time sensitive...
ah!
Otherwise there's no way
that I would be leaving you.
No one in their right mind
would leave you.
Um, your shirt's
on backwards.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay.
I will text you, all right?
Uh, no, I'll call you.
I'll call you.
Or how about I just...
I'll just do both, okay?
I'll do both.
I'm so sorry.
Professor Stein.
Hey,
I'm not here to hurt you,
And I know you don't
want to hurt anyone else,
So if you could just not...
Flame on.
No!
Well, that was terrifying.
I sent Sherry to the movies.
Trust me,
the best show in town
Is going to be
in here tonight.
So you're telling me
you can get actual photographs
From this thing?
The science is solid.
It works exactly like
an old film camera.
I developed
the mirror backing,
And fortunately for us,
The lightning went off
about ten times that night.
Multiple exposures.
Now you're getting it.
I went ahead
and enhanced them digitally
And, just for kicks,
Decided to extrapolate
a 3-d hologram
From the original 2-d.
Cisco.
Lights.
Camera.
Action.
Wow.
Can you play it again?
Slower?
There, there.
You see that?
Huh.
Next frame.
This wallpaper's new.
Oh, man.
Is that blood?
We had a husband
who was holding
The same weapon
that killed his wife.
We weren't looking
for any other suspects.
That blood belongs
to one of the two speedsters
That was here that night.
Maybe the one
that killed Nora.
I'll get a sample kit.
I got you.
That's great.
Linda, hey.
Hey!
So I hope it's cool
that I came by.
Yeah, of course.
I was just writing
a column on the combines.
Oh, sweet,
how are they doing?
Well, they were up
two goals to none last night,
But then they blew it.
Wait, we're not talking
about hockey anymore, are we?
No. We're not.
Look, I am so, so sorry
that I left you like that.
I'm... I'm not
that kind of guy.
Well, let me tell you
what kind of girl I am.
I work in a hard business,
and I work hard in it.
And so I'm very picky
about who I choose
To spend my free time with.
I chose to spend
some of it with you, so...
Tell me, Barry Allen,
did I make the right choice?
Yeah, you did.
It just that something important
came up.
And not more important
than you,
It's just sort of, like,
an equal level of importance
Type situation...
And... and usually I can
do both,
Um, but it's just
that I have to, um...
I have to go to work.
I'm so sorry.
It's a police emergency.
Can we talk later tonight?
I'm not
going anywhere... Yet.
Okay, thanks.
- Hey!
Sorry, gotta go.
Uh...
Hey!
What's up?
Bye.
Hey, can I ask you
a question?
Yeah, sure.
So, um, you and Barry
are like bffs, right?
The best of bffs.
Has he ever actually
dated anyone before?
Because he's simultaneously
surprisingly good at it
And really, really bad at it.
I don't know.
He's... Barry.
What was
his last girlfriend like?
You know, he hasn't really
had a girlfriend in a while.
I don't know,
maybe he's just not ready yet.
What do you mean?
You know, I mean,
he was into someone,
An unrequited love thing.
You know, he had
feelings for someone,
And they weren't
really reciprocated, so...
Yeah, maybe just
give him time.
Sure.
There he is.
Looks like the tracker
Barry placed on him worked.
Professor Stein?
Ugh, I told you
to stay away from me.
And I will,
but there's someone else
Who wants to talk to you.
Martin?
Do you know who I am?
Clarissa.
Is it really you?
I don't know.
I hear the other
inside of me.
He wants to go home to her.
But we can't.
I want to be me again.
Martin...
What's my favorite color?
You could...
you could never decide,
So you chose stripes.
You shouldn't see me
like this.
I see you.
I see you, Martin.
These people can help you.
They say they can.
Please let them.
Please... Help us.
Well, we got him.
Them.
Now what?
Well, Stein clearly thinks
He can separate himself
from Ronnie's body
Using nuclear fission.
What do you think?
What do I think?
Is it possible?
Theoretically.
But splitting an atom
and splitting a man
Are two
very different things.
I don't suppose it's necessary
to point out you're all staring?
Our apologies.
It is remarkable.
I feel clearer than I have
since the accident.
What did you give me?
A cocktail of anti-psychotics,
depressants,
And mood stabilizers.
The same formula used to treat
dissociative identity disorders.
I assume this was your idea?
Very clever, Cait.
Don't call me that.
Please.
I apologize.
We'd like
to run some tests on you,
If you don't mind.
Of course, Dr. Snow.
Hey, I'm so sorry I had
to run out like that again.
Uh, police business.
That's funny, because
I just called the station,
And they said that you had
taken some personal time.
I'm not mad, Barry, I swear.
But I do think
that we should call it.
W-wait, can we
talk about this?
What do you mean?
Look, I know
how hard and weird it is
Trying to date someone new
When you're still not
over someone.
What are you talking about?
You and Iris.
Me and Iris, we're not...
Who told you that
I was hung up on Iris?
- Hey.
- Hey, what's up?
Uh, why would you tell Linda
that I had feelings for you?
I did not say that.
Wait, did I?
Okay, Iris, this isn't funny.
I mean, I like this girl.
I know,
and I am happy for you.
Really? Because I don't...
I mean, right now
It sort of feels like
you don't want to be with me
And you don't want anyone else
to be with me either.
I have wanted nothing more
than for you to meet someone
Who is amazing.
And I did!
And you went out of your way
To convince her
that I was unavailable.
Look, I'm really sorry.
Great.
Wait, do you want me
to talk to her?
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
Don't talk to her.
I'll figure this out on my own.
I just need you to know that
I don't have those feelings
for you anymore.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Yes, yes, yes!
See? We got
two different blood samples.
- One for each speedster.
- That's right.
One is a-positive,
And the other one's
ab-negative... super rare.
I'm gonna run them both through
the CCPD criminal database
To see if I get any matches.
Can you run them
against a specific person?
Yeah, sure, if we
have something to match it to.
Who are we looking at?
Dr. Harrison Wells.
I thought we were trying
to solve Barry's mom's murder.
We are.
And I'm asking you
to keep this between us.
You think Dr. Wells
killed Barry's mom?
No way.
He didn't even know Barry then.
Why would he kill his mom?
I don't know yet.
But I do know
that Wells keeps secrets.
And this may be one of them.
Dr. Wells
is a great man.
I was nothing
when he gave me a job,
A chance to change my life.
He has helped so many people.
He's not a murderer.
Cisco, I'm a cop.
I'm good at reading people,
So I know I can trust you
with my suspicion.
When I go talk
to the family and friends
Of a murder suspect,
Somebody I know is guilty,
And I tell them the person
they love is a killer,
Guess what they all say.
That's not the person I know.
I think I'm done
being a cop for today.
Are you comfortable?
A little warm.
Ronnie used to always
run warm.
Not that warm.
Can I talk to him?
I'm sorry, my dear.
I'm not sure
it works like that.
I can feel him though.
I have these memories.
Memories that I know
aren't my own.
One is particularly strong.
Piedmont state park?
It's famous
for the Hudson falls.
I know that I've never been,
But I can remember
those waterfalls perfectly.
That's where Ronnie
proposed to me.
He loves you very much.
That I can feel.
Dr. Snow, can we
see you for a minute?
Excuse me.
You okay?
Yeah, it's just confusing.
What isn't confusing is
what's happening to him now.
Ronnie's body is rejecting
stein's atoms
Like a host
rejecting a parasite.
The resulting instability is
causing an exothermic reaction.
I worry if his temperature
continues to rise,
It'll set off
a chain reaction.
And then what happens?
He could go nuclear.
Ronnie.
Not Ronnie.
Martin Stein.
Cisco Ramon.
Your colleagues are
in the next room,
Not so subtly discussing
my condition.
That's not freaky at all.
It seems Ronnie's fight
with the Flash
Has exacerbated
the firestorm matrix.
It's unstable.
Exponentially increasing
the rate of fission
Inside his body.
Well, how long does he have?
If his temperature keeps
rising at the current pace,
No more
than a couple of hours.
But you can fix it, right?
I mean, you... you can separate
them before it's too late.
Any attempt we make
to separate the two of them
Could be catastrophic...
a nuclear explosion.
And a nuclear explosion
of this magnitude
Would level this entire city.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless the host body
were no longer functional.
You want to kill Ronnie?
No, I don't want
to kill Ronnie.
But in this scenario,
Ronnie is the host body.
If you kill Ronnie,
you kill Stein.
That's two people.
I don't know how else
to stop it.
And my guess is that
if Ronnie and Professor Stein
knew the consequences
that we were all facing,
they would make
the same decision.
It's two lives for millions.
Can you give us a minute?
Caitlin...
I've already lost
Ronnie once.
I'm not going to do it again.
You said we have
a couple of hours.
Use them.
Dr. Wells,
you don't really think
we should kill Ronnie,
do you?
Stay here, Cisco.
Hey. Sorry.
Um, can I get you anything
or...
A glass of Chateau Haut-Brion
Pessac-Leognan 1982
might be nice.
Or maybe it wouldn't.
This body's taste buds
would obviously
Be different from my own.
Perhaps I'm now
a light beer man.
There are worse things to be.
You mean like
a living nuclear bomb?
You know.
Unstable nuclear fission
was always a danger
In the transmutation process.
Plus, you all argue
very loudly.
I'm sorry.
But my friends
are gonna figure out
How to fix this, I promise.
I remember meeting you,
Mr. Allen, on the train.
You were headed
to S.T.A.R. Labs with a girl
But not your girlfriend.
Yeah.
I'm not sure that
I have any girlfriend.
You know,
Einstein was not only brilliant,
He had
a great sense of humor.
How did it go?
"Any man who drives safely
while kissing a pretty girl
Is not giving the pretty girl
the attention she deserves."
If I learned anything
this past year,
Life's too short not to live.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I gave you an out.
- I don't want an out.
I don't wanna date someone
who's into someone else.
I'm not into anyone else.
I'm gonna prove it to you.
This is the Naga Jolokia
Or the ghost pepper.
It is
the world's hottest pepper
Measuring 401.5 times hotter
than Tabasco sauce.
If you do not agree
to go on another date with me,
I will eat it right here,
right now.
You're bluffing.
I never bluff.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine, yeah.
- You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Mm!
Yes!
Yes, I'll go out with you.
That pepper could have
killed you, nerd.
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
I won't let my job...
Or how bad my mouth
is burning right now
Come between us.
My spice champion
of Central City.
A crude weapon,
if I may say so, Dr. Wells.
I couldn't agree more,
Gideon.
But it will do the job.
Gideon,
can the tachyon prototype
Be converted
into a quantum splicer?
Theoretically,
but I must warn you, Dr. Wells,
Converting the tachyon prototype
will delay your timetable.
There's not going to be
a timetable
If Central City goes up
in a mushroom cloud.
Hey. Anything?
I have an idea.
It's a bit of a hail mary,
But Cisco and I
are going to give it a try.
Thank you.
I'll get Professor Stein.
Looking for the Professor?
Yeah, he's gone.
You guys almost done?
Hang on. Hang on.
I found Stein.
He's in the badlands.
Middle of nowhere, 30 miles
outside of Central City.
- Minimum safe distance.
- He's sacrificing himself.
How much time
does he have left?
12 minutes.
And...
We're done.
What is it?
This is a quantum splicer.
Will it work
to separate them?
We'll know in 12 minutes.
Now, Barry, even you
can't outrun a nuclear blast,
So you get this device
to Professor Stein,
And you get out of there
as fast as you can.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going with you.
- No, you're not.
- It's too dangerous!
Barry doesn't know
how to operate the splicer.
Cisco's gonna talk me
through it.
There's not enough time.
Let's go.
Go!
What was that?
Uh, comm system's
on the fritz.
I'll be right back.
Cisco.
I'm not proud of it,
but I ran the samples.
One wasn't identified,
and the other had a match.
Cisco, you're hesitating.
Was it Wells?
No, it's not Dr. Wells.
I told you,
he has nothing to do with this.
But I know whose blood it is.
It's Barry's.
We already know
Barry was there that night.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
The sample had high levels
of p16.
That's a protein that builds up
in the blood as we get older.
And these levels were
way too high for an 11-year-old.
This sample was from Barry
as an adult.
Professor Stein!
What are you doing here?
You can't be here!
Get her out of here now!
Please, look, Ronnie's still
in there somewhere.
All those people... Clarissa...
I won't let them die!
It's better I end this now.
We can separate you!
We can stop the explosion.
How?
A quantum splicer.
It's a fission device
designed to bombard your atoms
With as much energy
as they experienced
In the particle accelerator
explosion.
It should be enough
to separate you.
Please, Professor,
you have nothing left to lose.
Ronnie, if you're in there,
I love you.
That was from him.
I look forward to meeting you
in person, Professor.
It's not working!
He's not gonna make it.
He's gonna blow.
Get out of there.
Barry, get out of there now!
- No! No!
- Caitlin, we have to go.
Run!
No!
Sir, we have
a thermonuclear detonation
Approximately 30 miles northeast
of Central City.
Deploy the rapid response team,
sergeant.
Bring me firestorm.
Greg, move your head.