Oracle, it's Huntress. Come in.
Huntress,
the comms are barely functional.
Barbara, can you hear me?
I need more time.
The wave's coming too quickly.
You're gonna have to evac right now.
I'm sending Alfred relevant data
before the wave hits.
Oracle? Oracle, please answer me.
Sending all relevant data...
We've only located four
of the seven Paragons
needed to save the multi-verse.
We could find the last three if...
It's repairing a Paragon detector, okay?
It's complex stuff.
Did someone call for backup?
- Iris.
- Cisco, thank goodness.
I need another genius intellect, stat.
That's why I'm here.
And that is a Super doppelganger,
which is super weird.
Holy All-Star Squadron.
Hi. Hi, how are you?
Ralph Dibny. Elongated Man.
Ready to help kick butt.
Ignore him. It's his first crossover.
Listen, the anti-matter wave
is still ripping its way
across the multi-verse.
We have to get everyone we can
to safety.
Calculations still show that Earth-1
will be the last place
for the wave to hit.
I just heard from
Alex and Brainy on Earth-1.
Everyone we saved from Earth-38
is still accounted for.
Then we should bring as many people
to Earth-1 as we can in the time being.
Let's get a rescue team together,
save who we can across the multi-verse.
I can use my psychic abilities
to stay in connection
with the Waverider.
And I'll go as well.
Parallel Earth Rory still has Jonathan,
so I'll run comms and keep
everyone updated.
- Supergirl?
- I'll stay here.
We have to find a way
to get our world back.
Wait. I think we did it.
I think we fixed it.
Guys, we already know all this.
It's buffering.
So, maybe a little patience.
Huh, why am I not surprised?
That's new.
Uh, who the hell is that guy?
Dr. Ryan Choi, physics professor
at Ivy Town University on our Earth.
Well, I guess we know our next stop.
Ray? Ralph?
Ivy Town, it's my old stomping grounds.
Let's go.
With all the Paragons identified,
our next priority is determining
how to stop the anti-matter wave.
Sorry to interrupt,
but Mr. Diggle has arrived.
How could you let
this happen, Sara?
You of all people!
- It's complicated.
- It's not complicated.
I wasn't there when he needed me.
Digg, we are working on
bringing him back,
the same way
that he brought me back. Remember?
You're talking about
a trip to Purgatory?
Yes.
Fine, count me in.
And there's...
There's something else.
Digg, it's Lyla. She's...
She's gone missing.
- What?
- Nobody saw her leave.
She was there one minute
and gone the next.
Well, she has the ability
to teleport. So...
So there are now infinite possibilities
for Lyla's location.
You... Listen to me.
I am not losing Oliver...
and Lyla.
So cut the crap and tell me
how the hell do I find my wife.
You heard him. Where is she?
Harbinger could very well be
with my adversary.
The Anti-Monitor.
"The Anti-Monitor."
Is that set in stone,
or can we workshop that a little bit?
This is why I have been
preparing all of you.
Testing and pushing you to your limits.
I needed your courage,
your honor, your strength of will...
even the truth of your convictions.
Everything that makes you
the greatest heroes
on this Earth or any other,
because that's what it will take
to defeat our opponent.
And what exactly does this guy want?
To eliminate the multi-verse
and replace it with another universe.
One that he can control,
just like every other megalomaniac.
I should have foreseen
my connection with Harbinger
could be perverted to his ends.
"Should have"?
Just tell us how to get her back.
I want to find her
just as much as the rest of you.
But I cannot rewrite
what has already been written.
I can only attempt to save what remains.
You know what to do
to get Oliver's soul back.
I'll watch over his body.
And I promise you, I will keep you
updated on Harbinger.
Copy that.
Cisco, maybe you should
call Kamilla back?
No, no, no. That wasn't a phone call.
I'm triangulating
anti-matter wave particles
- on the Earths that are left.
- Why?
I'm trying to locate
the source of the wave.
And according to this,
it's hidden in a subterranean region
right in our own backyard.
Meet me in the cargo bay in five.
Cisco Ramon.
Didn't I just leave you?
You are not a Paragon,
but you do have a purpose.
Vibe must live again.
No.
No, my powers are gone.
And there's a reason for that.
You must answer the call
whether you wish to or not.
Okay. Maybe you didn't hear me
under those voluminous
muttonchops of yours...
Now, go.
Serve your higher purpose.
Are you still sure you want me to go?
Yeah.
Go find Ryan Choi.
And hurry back.
- Where did Barry race off to?
- Perimeter search.
Make sure this isn't a trap
set up by the Anti-Monitor.
Ugh, that name makes me want to barf.
Nice to have you back, Vibe.
- Let's just get to Nash's work site.
- Right this way.
Huh, that's new.
We gotta get in there.
Who's there?
Nash? Is that you?
I am no longer Nash. I am... Pariah.
And I'm here to bear witness.
- To what?
- Tragedy.
Uh-huh.
New name.
New suit.
Guess no one's consulting me
anymore, huh?
Wait, what exactly happened?
I searched these tunnels
as Nash for Mar Novu.
To kill him...
expose him as a false god, and now,
I'm being controlled by another god.
And that's the...
Anti-Monitor?
He laid a perfect trail
for me to follow,
but all along he was manipulating me
so that he could gain a foothold
in this universe.
Why didn't you resist him?
His will was too strong,
and now I am forced...
to bear witness
as he destroys world after world.
That's why we're gonna stop him.
Now, can you open that door?
I cannot.
My memories as Nash
are somehow lost to me
as Pariah, but you can.
- By vibing those memories?
- Yes.
What did you see?
The way in.
You think the book can bring back
the destroyed Earths?
- Oh, too good.
- I don't have time for this.
Tell us how to use the book
or lose an arm, your choice.
Did the strong-arm tactics work
in Gotham City?
The book channels ancient
and endless power.
It takes immense willpower
and focus to make it work.
- What did you focus on?
- His hatred.
For Superman.
Got it in one.
But that was easy
for the book to provide.
You try to use it on the scale
that you're talking about,
and it could drive you mad.
Like Deegan.
Kara, there's no telling
what kind of ripple effect
this could have.
I'm supposed to be
the Paragon of Hope, right?
Maybe this is my role,
to bring back my Earth,
and Argo, and all the others.
I have to find a way to fix this.
See you soon.
So why did we take a detour
to another parallel Earth?
With so many Earths already gone,
the pillars of magic are crumbling,
leaving me the worse for wear.
So, I can't get us into Purgatory.
But don't worry, squire.
Luckily, I know a guy.
Oh, you're gonna love her.
She's pretty much up for everything.
Always a pleasure to see you, Luci.
It's time.
Excuse me, ladies.
Seems like you're not the only ones
who want a piece of me.
I'll see you later.
Johnny!
Ah, I'd like to say it's a pleasure
to see you on my Earth,
outside my club, but it's not.
Hello.
Don't believe we've met.
Lucifer Morningstar.
"Lucifer Morningstar," as in...
The Devil. Yes, exactly.
So tell me, what is it you desire?
I...
I, um...
I desire to get my father back.
Oh.
Daddy issues. Why didn't you say so?
Look, I don't know if you have
an Oliver Queen on your world,
but ours has shuffled off
this mortal coil.
A soul retrieval, blah, blah, blah.
The worlds are ending.
It's all very biblical, John.
Okay.
Okay, I'm only doing this
'cause I owe you for Maze.
Yeah, you do.
You remind me of my brother, by the way.
Tall, dark, annoyed by me.
You gonna help us or not?
Oh... Flirt.
The Devil always sees through on a deal.
Take this card.
You'll have a limited time
once inside Purgatory,
and once the picture completely fades...
Our souls will be decimated,
blah, blah, blah.
And trapped in eternity forever,
so I don't recommend it.
Consider us even, John Constantine.
- "Constantine."
- Is it? I don't care.
Always a pleasure doing
business with mortals.
He forgot to tell us what to do.
Did he now?
Huh.
Welcome to Purgatory.
Looks a lot like Lian Yu.
Which is Mandarin for "purgatory."
Lovely little coincidence, eh?
Any idea why Dad's soul
would choose to come here?
Souls choose their prisons.
This place must be
what Oliver thinks about
when being trapped for all eternity.
It's a funny thing, too, considering
his memories are probably missing.
What are you talking about?
The second that
Oliver's soul landed here,
his memories would've been...
How can I put it?
Squeegeed.
So, we'll have to make him remember us.
Bollocks. We'll have to get
a move on as well.
This card is already beginning to fade.
When you work with the Devil,
you never know quite
what you're getting.
No pressure there, right?
Perimeter's clear.
There's no sign of any
quantum tower on Earth-1.
What are you doin' here, Pariah?
Behind this wall, his domain.
What Mr. Green Jeans is trying to say
is once we get inside,
we can actually stop
the anti-matter wave
right at the source.
All right. Let's do it.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Whoa.
This place has some crazy
vibrational frequency
surging through it.
This place is the nexus
between the anti-matter universe
and your own.
Behold, anti-matter cannon.
This is the source of the wave.
Guys, I think this blur is alive.
- I'll check it out.
- No!
- Barry!
- What happened?
It's a forcefield.
I couldn't get through.
It's the Flash.
From Earth-90.
He's trapped on that treadmill.
That's Barry Allen from Earth-90?
How did he get there?
The Monitor sent him away.
You will not do to this Earth
what you did to mine.
He wound up in a netherverse
where the Anti-Monitor found him,
corralled his speed, used it
to build his anti-matter cannon.
Test-fired it...
destroying Earth-2.
Harry's gone?
- Jesse...
- Pariah, how do we stop the cannon?
The forcefield that contains this
is anti-matter-based.
As such, anything made
of positive matter cannot penetrate it.
We have to get the Flash
off that treadmill.
The Monitor said, "Vibe had to live."
That he had a purpose. Maybe this is it.
Here goes nothing.
Thank you for the reprieve...
but you gotta put me back on it.
Guys.
The Anti-Monitor designed
that treadmill with a fail-safe,
so that if I ever got off of it,
it would erupt,
destroying all remaining Earths at once.
We only have a few minutes.
Pariah, how... Pariah?
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
Amanda, please.
I know the red skies are freaky, honey,
but I'm sure it's just atmospheric...
Dr. Ryan Choi?
...disturbance.
Babe, I gotta go.
Wow, is that really you?
Dr. Ray Palmer.
O-M-gosh.
I'm Ryan Choi.
It's so wonderful to meet you.
Your second paper
on subatomic density manipulation
was the foundation for my work
on miniaturization.
Wow. Thank you. You know...
Okay. Dr. Choi, we need you
to come with us right now.
Look, you've seen
the red skies outside?
The world is ending.
Dr. Palmer,
who are these people?
We are superheroes
and, Ryan, we need your help.
Sure, Dr. Palmer.
Good one.
Next, you're gonna tell me
I've been nominated
for the Breakthrough Prize
in Fundamental Physics?
Okay, we don't have time for this.
Seeing is believing, right?
- Tissue?
- You're... Elongated Man?
Are you superheroes, too?
I know this sounds cuckoo, pal,
but you're what's called a Paragon,
which is a fancy word for saying
we need your help
to save the universe.
Dr. Choi.
If the world's ending,
I need to go home.
Please, Ryan, we really need your help.
No, you don't. I'm no hero.
I'm a husband.
And if this is the end,
I have to be with my wife and kid.
I'm sorry.
Another Earth is gone.
There's only seven left
in the multi-verse.
It's ironic.
I'm watching the biggest
event in history,
the destruction of every Earth,
and no one will ever read the story.
These Earths are not
the only worlds destroyed.
My world died.
My family.
What were they like?
Hmm.
So full of life.
They were everything to me.
If only I cared as much for them...
as I did my work.
I now understand why
you're such a good reporter, Ms. Lane.
Clark?
Couldn't save them.
You wanna take a minute?
Looks like you could use a breather.
When I put this on, this crest,
I made a promise.
To keep fighting, no matter what.
Hey, why did you add black to it?
Because, Lois,
even in the darkest times,
hope cuts through.
Hope is the light that lifts us
out of darkness.
I must go back.
He never quits, no matter
what Earth he's from, huh?
Now you're just talking to yourself.
It's getting worse.
- Put me back on that treadmill.
- No. All right, we'll find another way.
- Where am I?
- Who are you?
Send me back to Freeland! Now!
Calm down, Electric Guy.
The name is Black Lightning.
Enough!
I did not bring you here,
Jefferson, to fight.
I brought you here to save lives.
Who the hell are you people?
I am Pariah. This is Jefferson Pierce.
On his Earth, an educator,
a father, and a hero.
- What do you mean, my Earth?
- There are multiple Earths, Jefferson.
Many Earths, like this one.
Your Earth...
has just been destroyed
by a wave of anti-matter.
So... So, Lynn, my girls?
They're gone.
I transported you here
to help us save humanity.
You should have saved my family, not me!
- Not me!
- Jefferson!
I'm so sorry.
Right now we need your help
to stop this anti-matter wave.
I can't imagine how you're feeling.
But I do know how it feels
to lose your family.
What would they
want you to do right now?
Please. All worlds could die.
What do you need from me?
That machine behind you
is the source of the anti-matter wave.
We have to disable it,
but we can't get near it.
Can you contain that much energy?
Let's find out.
Don't. You open that book
and you do not know what will happen.
To you, to all of the Earths
you're trying to save.
I have to, Kate.
Those people, they need help.
And we are doing our best
to help who we can.
- That is not the answer.
- Then what am I supposed to do?
Just be okay with
all those people dying? Like Bruce?
Believe that if life's supposed to end,
just let it?
No, of course not. But if you open
that book, it will destroy you.
I have to do this.
Then I have to stop you.
You won't be able to.
You'd be surprised.
I wish things were different...
Kara.
I wish I was hopeful, like you.
But one thing I do know
is if you take a chance on that book,
and it doesn't work,
and something happens to you,
we're all doomed.
Tick-tock, people.
Black Lightning is gonna kill himself
if we don't solve this soon.
And we need more time.
Every second that we waste here,
another Earth dies.
And that wave gets closer to my wife.
I was married once, too.
Tina always said that keeping me running
was her purpose in life.
So, as someone who's been running
for 30 years,
let me tell you, sometimes,
in order to find your purpose as a hero,
you gotta take a couple steps back.
Reverse the way you see the situation,
and see a bigger picture.
That's it.
I know how to stop the cannon.
This is what the Monitor meant
that day in the time vault.
This is what I've been running towards
all these years.
It's time for Flash to vanish in Crisis.
Reversing the treadmill's
directional velocity
could make the anti-matter wave recede
and funnel back into the speed cannon.
Destroying the machine and the wave.
Ending this once and for all.
Freeing me from
the Anti-Monitor's control.
Where is the future? Right here.
And whose life is this? Mine.
What are you gonna do with it?
Live it. By any means necessary.
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna find him.
You don't know that.
Dad's soul could be lost forever.
Family is everything to Oliver.
He'll come back to us.
Oliver, wait, man.
Listen to me. I see you, man.
And I'm so sorry that I wasn't there
to have your back during Crisis,
but I'm here now.
And I need you to come back to us.
You're my brother.
I can't lose you, man.
I can't lose you.
Hey, John.
- Mia, you came.
- Of course, I did.
They're beautiful.
I didn't get to introduce myself
earlier, Dr. Choi.
I'm Iris West-Allen from Central City.
Are you a superhero, too?
No. I'm just like you.
Look, I know this is a lot to ask,
and you're right
to want to be with your family
when things go bad.
What about you? You clearly have someone
in your life you care about.
Don't you want to die holding them
when the world ends?
My husband is not like us.
He goes out there as a superhero
day after day
and faces whatever he has to
to keep his city safe.
That's really brave, Iris,
but that's not me.
- See, I'm nothing like your husband.
- No, no, you're not.
You're human.
And we have a purpose, too.
We remind superheroes
what they're fighting for.
My wife, Amanda and I,
just had a baby six months ago.
Simone.
I might not get to see her grow up.
Don't you want to hold her
knowing that you had a hand
in making the world safer?
I need to go tell my wife
I'm gonna be late for dinner.
Just got word from Lois.
Six more Earths are gone.
This is the only Earth left.
- At least now we have Ryan.
- Yeah.
How'd you know what to say to him?
Iris.
Hey. What is it?
What if this is it?
What if...
stopping the wave
is my purpose as a Paragon?
I mean, what if it's the sacrifice
I have to make?
Well, if this is it, then I don't want
you to die without me, Barry.
I don't want you to be alone.
I'll come with you.
No, you can't come, Iris.
I may be the one with superpowers,
but your intelligence,
your resourcefulness, your heart...
That's your superpower
and that's what's gonna help you
convince Ryan Choi to be the hero
he needs to be.
Barry, I don't want to live
this life without you.
I don't want to say goodbye.
When I put this ring on your finger,
I promised that I'd always
come running home to you.
And if we're apart, for however long...
know that wherever I go,
I will be running home to you.
Are you still sure you want me to go?
Yeah. Go find Ryan Choi...
and hurry back.
I'll see you soon.
- Caitlin.
- I don't wanna say goodbye.
You two were there the first time
I opened my eyes as the Flash.
I couldn't be the hero I am
without you guys.
- Tell Joe and Iris I love them.
- We will.
Sorry, kid, but this has to happen.
- Barry, what are you doing?
- I'm momentarily stealing your speed.
You play this speedster game
long enough,
you learn some neat tricks.
Wait, why are you doing this?
Novu said the Flash must die in Crisis.
He never said which one.
You're a true hero, Jefferson.
I can't thank you enough.
Open the breach.
I need to get in that forcefield.
- No.
- Do you want your friend to die?
Let me do this. Let me save you all.
Cisco, don't.
Cisco, come on.
Thank you.
Keep riding the lightning, son.
I know you'll make us all proud.
Barry! He's gonna die, Cisco.
You made me team leader.
And sometimes, the leader
has to make the tough choices.
We can't stay here.
- Let's go.
- No.
Let's go.
- No, I'm not going.
- Barry, let's go.
- I'm not going.
- Come on!
I have faith in you, Tina.
Well, the truth is,
I have faith in you, too.
I hate to break up
the reunion,
but this really is our cue
to make like a tree
and get Oliver's soul back to his body.
- Let's go.
- Oliver Queen!
- Who are you?
- Jim Corrigan.
- Ah, not the one I know.
- But I'm also someone else.
I'm something else.
A Spectre.
Take a hike, crazy eyes.
In another life,
I was a decorated police officer,
a hero in my own right.
But then I was called
to a higher purpose.
It's your turn now, Oliver.
Only you can light the spark, Oliver.
It is your destiny.
- What is my destiny?
- To save everyone.
Otherwise, all universes,
all the people you love, will perish.
I'm sorry, but I have to.
- Dad, no...
- It's gonna be okay.
It's going to be okay.
- What now?
- Dad, wait.
I love you...
What happened?
Dad wouldn't come back with us.
I'm sorry, Sara.
The others fare any better?
Barry's team stopped
the anti-matter wave
with one Earth left.
I need a drink.
I appreciate you helping us, Jefferson.
I know what you've lost.
My world.
I lost the love of my life.
My two daughters.
Nothing will ever be okay again.
I know.
That Flash, the Flash from Earth-90,
he looked just like my dad, Henry Allen.
He was a resilient man.
He spent years in prison
for the murder of my mom.
A crime one of my enemies committed
and framed him for.
Through all that,
he never lost his light.
Times like this...
I try and do the same.
My father, uh, Alvin Pierce,
he was a good man, too.
Reporter.
Spent his life giving a voice
to the voiceless.
He was murdered when I was 12.
But I still carry the lessons
he taught me to this day.
I passed them along to my girls.
My girls.
Anyway, I get it.
Look, I don't think Henry or Alvin
raised any quitters.
So, we should honor their memory,
and rage...
against the dying of the light.
Dylan Thomas.
Well, all right then, Flash.
It's Barry.
Barry Allen.
Jefferson Pierce.
Hey, Kara, listen.
I get you wanted to bring
those people back.
You have the biggest heart
of anyone that I've ever met.
I just don't want to see you get hurt.
You know, I gotta say,
for someone who's unsure
that they were the Paragon of Courage...
Took a lot of guts to do what you did.
Maybe. But I have hope
that there's a better way.
Which is why...
Which is why I wanted to give you this.
Kryptonite. Why do you have that?
It was Bruce Wayne's. He lost hope.
And I never will.
Keep it.
I have the courage
that you'll never have to use it.
Attention.
Iris, Ralph and Raymond
have returned with Dr. Choi.
Iris. I told you
I'd come running home to you.
- If it wasn't you, then...
- It was the Barry Allen from Earth-90.
Everyone, this is Jefferson Pierce.
We wouldn't have been able to stop
the anti-matter wave without him.
Wait. So, the Superman thing is real?
Oh, damn. After all these years.
And this is your Paragon of Humanity,
Ryan Choi.
Scientist, super brain,
and ready to help save the universe.
How do you guys plan on doing
that exactly?
Well, Kara decided not to use
the Book of Destiny.
It was too risky.
The Harbinger, unlike me,
can travel anywhere she wants.
So, how do we find her?
By whatever means necessary.
Well, we can start by trying to re-task
the Waverider's satellite search grid.
- Lyla.
- Johnny.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I tried to get word to you
that I was doing recon on Earth-1,
but the deaths of the other Earths
is affecting my abilities.
Where were you on Earth-1?
I...
- I can't remember.
- It's okay.
- I thought I lost you, Lyla.
- Not that easy.
I just wish I could remember
what happened.
We'll figure this out.
What if the Anti-Monitor
wanted Harbinger back on the ship?
He's been controlling her
the entire Crisis.
And controlling you.
Only allowing you to appear
when he wants you to see...
A great tragedy.
- Lyla?
No!
It is time to end
the age of heroes.
And everything you hold close.
Lyla.
That is no longer your wife,
John Diggle.
- She has been taken by...
- The Anti-Monitor.
Murderer!
This is for my girls.
Lyla.
You have to fight him, Lyla!
The fate of all humanity lies
with you now, Pariah.
- What can I do?
- You will know when the moment arrives.
Pathetic. It was foolish
to try to stop me, Novu.
No, Mobius.
It was foolish to allow your creation
in the first place.
Goodbye.
Alert. Earth-1 is gone.
We're all that's left.
It is done.
The infinite Earths are gone.
Soon, only the anti-matter universe
will remain.
Warning.
The anti-matter wave
will hit the ship in 28 seconds.
I know what I must do.
What's happening?
Iris.
Everyone
to the bridge. Now!
- Where did you send them?
- Somewhere you can't touch them.
Wherever they are,
they're gonna fight you.
By any means necessary.
To their very last breath.
- What the hell just happened?
- Where are we?
This is The Vanishing Point.
What does that mean?
It's a point outside of time and space.
What happened to the Waverider
and the others?
The Anti-Monitor.
He used Harbinger to attack us.
Pariah must have sent us here
knowing that the Anti-Monitor
couldn't follow.
Well, we have to go back.
- We have to go back right now!
- Barry, we can't. They're gone.
No...
Something's wrong.
- Kal. Kal.
- Something's wrong.
- Hey, Kal, hey.
- I can't...
- Come on.
- Please, fix...
Fix it.
What do I do?
No! No!
Oh, I am so happy that worked.
Lex, what did you do?
Well, I held the Book of Destiny
and I saw you seven Paragons
due to be stranded
at The Vanishing Point.
And I thought
destiny could use a little re-write.
So, uh...
What do we do now?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::