ZOOM: I know you're here, Harrison Wells.
And you did not come alone.
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
You can try to hide,
but I'm the fastest man alive.
I will scour this city
until I hunt you down.
And when I do,
all of you will feel my wrath.
MALE REPORTER: C.C.P.N. is reporting
that Dr. Harrison Wells,
the infamous founder of S.T.A.R. Labs
who uncharacteristically
has gone unseen for nearly four months,
is now a wanted man.
These images and messages went up moments
ago throughout Central City by Zoom.
Have you seen Channel 52?
You're not safe here, Dr. Wells.
Zoom's looking for you.
I know what he's doing. Alert security.
Evacuate S.T.A.R. Labs.
Lock down the facility.
-What about you?
-Don't worry about me, Henry.
Just get everyone out of here now.
Now! Go!
Harry... Don't shoot!
(SIGHS) Damn it, Ramon.
(SIGHS)
Where's Allen?
-(PANTS) Zoom took him.
-What?
We tracked down Deathstorm and Killer
Frost, met my doppelganger, Reverb.
Super evil guy, super evil powers.
The three of them almost took down Barry
until Zoom showed up, killed Cisco-2,
killed Deathstorm for hurting a speedster,
but then he left Killer Frost alive
and then took off with Barry.
How are you still alive?
Looks like he cares even less about me
than you do, Harry.
No. No, Zoom doesn't do anything
by accident. Did he follow you here?
I've seen Heat like 50 times, okay?
I know how to shake a tail.
He didn't follow me. But check this out.
I jacked these from my dead ringer.
I think we can tweak these puppies,
use them to find Zoom.
Damn, it.
Ramon, we don't have time for this.
Zoom is hunting us. Zoom is hunting us!
We need to make an alternate plan
because if we don't, Zoom is...
Stop thinking like that, okay?
We're gonna find Jesse and
we're gonna find Barry. I know we will.
ALLEN ON TABLET: Hello? Is anyone there?
Okay, whoever's responsible for this,
oh boy, we're gonna have words.
The two of us, okay? This is not okay.
Barry-2.
Dr. Wells, this is very disappointing.
I mean, the two of you
should be ashamed of yourselves.
You can't just lock someone
in a room like this.
How long was I in here for?
Barely a day.
One day?
Oh, geez, my wife's
going to be worried sick.
-Dr. Wells.
-Yeah?
Doctor, I'm not sure
if you're aware of this,
but my wife is
a very well respected detective
in the Central City Police Department.
She's gotta be very upset.
Whoa, this is heavy.
It certainly is. And I'm sorry, fellas,
but I demand to know what the heck
is going on here. This instant.
Barry, this is a very long story.
Ramon, we don't have time
to tell right now.
We're sorry we locked you in that room for
a day, but right now you need to leave.
-You need to gather...
-(ALARM BEEPING)
-What is that?
-He's here.
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(GUNS COCKING)
Do not move!
Where are Wells and his friends?
(SHUDDERS)
Dr. Wells. Hey, what the heck is going on?
Oh, Zoom's after us.
Zoom? Why would Zoom be after you?
That's part of that long story
I was telling you about.
I don't know if I can... (GASPS)
Deal with something like this.
-You have a time vault?
-Yeah.
I'm an enemy of Zoom and need a place to
hide when something like this happens.
-Get in.
-Yes, sir.
That's Zoom. That's Zoom.
Ramon.
-(WHIMPERING)
-Shut him up.
(WHIMPERS)
(GASPS)
Okay. Breathe, breathe, breathe.
-(BREATHING HEAVILY) Same as the...
-Fake wall.
He's not gonna fall for another fake wall.
We need to move.
We need to find a different place to hide
and make a plan.
Wait. Wait. Hey, hey, hey. No.
I think before we do anything,
you have to explain to me
everything that is going on here.
JESSE: You're wasting your time.
I used to think I could escape too
when I first got here,
but there's no way out.
Who is that?
I don't know.
He's been here since Zoom brought me
to this place.
Look, stop, okay? Just please stop.
Jesse, I think he might be
trying to help us.
Nothing is going to help us.
That's not true.
We're gonna get out of here.
Your dad's gonna find us. I promise.
You sure have a lot of faith in a man
who only cares about himself.
You know,
I actually thought that at first, too.
But it's not true.
Every decision that he's made,
every action he's taken since we've met,
it's been to save you.
You dad hasn't given up on you, Jesse.
Don't give up on him.
(GASPING)
-(SOBS)
-Believe what you want,
but the only reason
that you're still alive
is so I can kill you
in front of your father.
And the only reason
your father's still alive
is to get me your speed.
Once he does that, he will die, too.
NEWSCASTER: Up after the break,
earthquake-causing meta-human
leaves citizens shaken and wondering
where is the Flash?
It's finished.
The breach, it's stabilized again.
Barry, Cisco and Wells
have 20 hours to get back.
You're amazing.
When it comes to stabilizing breaches,
maybe.
Not so much when it comes to fighting
meta-humans.
You were a little rusty.
I was too slow.
Geomancer's still out there, Caitlin.
He has to be stopped. I have to be ready
in case he attacks again.
-How much longer until the Velocity...
-Eight.
Velocity-Eight is ready?
I need to finalize the compound,
make sure the extracellular matrix
stays intact
so you don't lose your speed as fast.
Okay. Great.
What is it?
After your last encounter with Geomancer,
I ran some tests.
The Velocity-Seven is reacting
with the damaged cells in your body.
It's causing more cellular degeneration.
Well, I have faith that the next batch
won't do the same thing.
Jay, I can't keep giving this to you
if it's hurting you.
If it'll help me defeat Geomancer,
you might have to.
Until Barry gets back,
I may be the only chance this city has.
I don't know how this is possible,
but you somehow made basketball
sound more boring than baseball. Fix this.
Scott Evans. Your new editor.
-Oh. Iris...
-West. I know.
You wrote the story
about the recent Geomancer attack.
-Yeah, I did.
-I'm not running that.
What? Why?
It's a fluff piece to try to make people
feel good.
What they need to know is the truth.
The Flash might not always be there
to save them.
You disagree?
I think that he's saved a lot of people
in this city.
But where is he now?
I need to run a real story.
Okay, uh, what if I could get you
an exclusive with the meta-human
that fought Geomancer?
This other Flash?
What? You're friends with him, too?
Just, um, (SIGHS) give me a little time.
Fine. But if it's the same
as the other crap that you wrote,
I'm gonna run something
about how the Flash
may not be the hero we all dreamed he was.
(SIGHS)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Iris. Hey, Iris.
-Barry, where were you last night?
-(SIGHS) Oh, my God.
My father died yesterday,
and you never even came home.
I know. I know, I heard. I'm so, so sorry.
What? You heard? You were there, Barry.
I actually was not there.
(STUTTERS) Yeah, okay.
Okay, look, come to my lab.
Just come up to my lab.
I'm gonna explain everything, okay?
I'm gonna explain it.
So (SIGHS) the Barry
from yesterday was not you.
(SCOFFS) No. No, look, I know that this is
hard to believe, but I mean,
it is just like that sci-fi series,
Commander Carl:
Space Marshal of the Galaxy,
where Carl gets sucked into a black hole
and ends up on another planet
that he thinks is Earth, but really
it's Earth of another universe.
Have you guys not seen... Oh, it's a
seminal episode. You should check it out.
So that's why you weren't wearing
your wedding ring yesterday.
-Well...
-And that kiss was so...
-I'm sorry, he got frisky with you?
-(SCOFFS)
No, no, no. Okay, I'm gonna have to find
this guy and give him a piece of my mind.
Well, don't give him too much.
Your husband tells us
you've been tracking Zoom.
-Yeah. I've been trying to. Why?
-We need to find his lair.
-"Lair"?
-He's a bad guy, I'm calling it a lair.
Zoom is looking for you.
Why are you going after him?
Zoom has my daughter and our Barry,
and we need to rescue them both.
Look, I wanna find Zoom just as much as
anybody, but no one can track him.
The only person who would know
where he would be hiding someone
would be a meta that's worked with him.
A meta like Killer Frost?
Yeah, maybe, but Zoom kept her alive
yesterday because she always obeys him.
There's no way
that she's gonna tell you where he is.
I'm not so sure about that.
If she loved Deathstorm
as much as my Caitlin loved Ronnie,
I think she'd be more than upset
at Zoom for killing him.
Look, finding her is gonna be just as hard
as finding Zoom.
But if anyone can do it,
my husband can.
Right. Yes, I can actually.
Um...
All right.
(SCATTING)
Okay, well, looks like Patty Spivot
was the CSI tech
on most of the Killer Frost cases.
She's pretty thorough, so...
What's that?
Oh, this is Killer Frost meta-data
collected from numerous crime scenes.
DNA trace movements, facial recognition,
temperature fluctuations specific to her.
My algorithm compiles all the data
and gives us an approximate location.
It works on most metas,
except for Zoom of course.
-He's too fast, never leaves a trace.
-That's good.
ALLEN: Okay. Looks like the best bet's
the woodlands.
-Best CSI in Central City.
-No.
-You know where that is, right?
-Yeah. Let's go.
Wait, I'm going with you guys.
You're gonna need some help.
-Okay.
-Iris.
Barry, Zoom and his followers
are the reason that my father is dead.
If I can stop him from killing
anyone else, I'm gonna try.
-Okay, then I'm coming, too.
-HARRISON AND CISCO: No.
No.
Barry, this is not what you do.
I know that, but...
I also know Joseph didn't like me
too much, but he was my father-in-law.
If you're going, I am coming with you.
All right. You can come,
but you stay out of our way.
Okay.
BARRY: That's not Morse code.
I know he's trying to tell us something.
We just have to find the pattern.
There's no pattern, Barry.
You know your dad,
who I'm pretty sure is one of the smartest
people to live on either of our Earths,
told me the only person smarter than him
was you.
He said that?
If that's true, we work together,
I know we can figure this out.
Worth a shot?
Okay.
Well, he never goes past five.
What?
He never goes past five knocks
without pausing, right? Listen.
Yeah, you're right.
I think I know what that is.
It's a five-by-five tap code used by POWs.
That would only get us to 25 letters,
and there's 26 in the alphabet.
No, not if you combine C and K.
They sound the same.
Let's try it out.
-Worth a shot.
-All right.
-There it is.
-It looks different than before.
That's because I realized that
there was a flaw with Velocity-Eight,
so I reformulated
the extracellular matrix and...
Velocity-Nine.
You know what they say.
Ninth time's the charm.
IRIS WEST: Hey.
Hey, Iris. You okay?
Yeah. I'm just a little worried
about the time.
Well, don't worry. They'll make it back
before we close the breach.
Um, actually, I was here to talk to you
about something else.
Oh, yeah, sure, what is it?
Well, my new editor (CHUCKLES)
wants me to write a scathing article
on the Flash not being able to protect
Central City from Geomancer.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I was hoping
to write an article about you instead.
Something that would calm people
until Barry got back.
You know, Iris,
I don't know if that's the best idea.
Well, I think that if people knew that
there was someone that could protect them,
it would really help.
Would you just think about it?
(ALARM BLARING)
Some crazy alarm's going on.
GEOMANCER ON TV:
Don't even think about running.
There's a new Flash in town.
You know, the one with the shiny helmet.
Not the speedster I was hoping to crack,
but let's see just how fast he is,
Central City.
-(RUMBLING)
-(PEOPLE YELLING)
-Give me the Velocity-Nine.
-Jay, we've no idea how long it'll last.
We don't have time to figure that out,
Caitlin.
-(GRUNTS)
-CAITLIN: Jay.
I'm okay. That just took a lot out of me.
But it sure felt good.
(ALL LAUGH)
That was amazing, Jay.
Thanks, I kind of surprised myself,
to be honest.
Caitlin deserves all the credit.
Looks like your Velocity-Nine's a winner.
I still need to run some tests.
(SIGHS) Iris, about the interview. Um...
I think that I have
everything that I need.
Great. (CHUCKLES)
'Cause I could really use a nap.
I'll, uh, be downstairs.
(SIGHS)
Two down, five across.
-It's J.
-J?
That's what you're tapping? The letter J?
All right, what's next?
A.
All right.
Five down.
Four across. Y.
J-A-Y?
You're spelling "Jay."
As in Jay Garrick?
He's alive, but he's on my Earth.
Hey, hey. Stop. Stop.
Look, I'm sorry,
I don't know what you mean.
Jay Garrick didn't come with us.
Look, just keep tapping, please.
We don't understand.
Please.
Don't talk to them again.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'm going to get out of here.
And I'm going to destroy you.
(GRUNTS)
All I need from you is your speed, Flash.
And you only need to be barely alive
for me to get it.
Stop!
Barry.
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
(GRUNTS)
Zoom just showed me
how to get out of this thing.
You're sure this is the place?
(PANTING)
This is definitely the place.
-You lost?
-(GUNS COCKING)
Or just back for more fun?
-We just came here to talk.
-Oh, really?
Do you bring your little toys
to every conversation you have?
Or do you just want to see me burn again?
Considering you killed my father,
the thought has crossed my mind.
HARRISON: Tell us.
Where does Zoom keep his prisoners?
You really don't know how to
use your abilities, do you, breacher?
It's a work in progress, Elsa.
Zoom killed the love of your life.
This hurts,
even for somebody
with a heart as cold as yours.
And you think
that would make me turn on Zoom?
The enemy of my enemy is my friend, right?
What? Don't tell me
it doesn't work like that over here.
If I tell you, he'll kill me.
But if I kill you and take you to him,
I bet he'd be pretty pleased with me.
Maybe even let me off my leash.
So take a wild guess.
What do you think I'm going to choose?
Move!
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS) That did not go as planned.
Her name starts with "Killer."
This comes as a shock to you?
(GRUNTS)
-We gotta move now.
-Yeah, yeah.
-I will cover you.
-Okay.
No, no, no. Hey, that's a horrible idea.
Hey, no. Hey, hey. No. Please, guys.
Okay.
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
Stop.
Or you'll never make another icicle again.
CAITLIN: I can't believe it.
What is it?
I think I figured out
how to save Jay's life.
Hey, Jay. Um, wake up.
Come to the Cortex. It's important.
It certainly is.
What do you want?
I like to watch heroes fall
and never get back up.
He always gets back up.
Hard to do that
when the Earth swallows you whole.
(GRUNTS)
Where is it?
Oh, don't go.
We're having so much fun.
-(GRUNTS)
-(YELLS)
IRIS WEST: Oh, my God! Caitlin!
Caitlin, are you okay? (GASPS)
Looks like this new Flash
isn't much of a hero after all.
Let's see what a seven will do
to S.T.A.R Labs.
(GRUNTS)
-Nice shot.
-I was aiming for his leg.
Where's Zoom's lair?
(GUN COCKS)
Where is it?
If I tell you, he will kill me.
He'll kill you anyway, Caitlin.
Stop calling me that. It's not my name.
Yes, it is. You just don't wanna hear it
because it reminds you
of someone you used to be.
Trust me, I know that person very well.
You don't know anything about me.
I know the Caitlin Snow on my Earth.
I know that when she loves someone,
that person is her world.
That person was Ronnie Raymond.
And he died, too.
That devastated her,
and I can see it's doing the same to you.
Zoom took that.
His daughter, my friend.
He's gonna take them away from us,
just like he took Ronnie from you.
Caitlin.
All you have to do is tell us
where he's keeping them.
And then you'll never hear from us again,
and then you can go.
Please.
Fine.
I'll show you where it is.
But that's it.
(STUTTERS) Where are we going?
Ascension Cliffs.
(GRUNTING)
God!
JESSE: Look, are you sure
you want to keep doing that?
You know, if Zoom catches you,
he's gonna hurt you again.
I don't understand why I can't
phase through this.
Well, your body would need to have
the same resonance as the glass walls.
I should be going more than fast enough.
It's something else. (EXHALES)
Maybe you're resonating
at a different frequency?
Yeah. Your Earth vibrates
at a different frequency than mine.
Same reasons Cisco can't vibe.
Is there any way
to make up the difference?
Only if I can go faster.
(PANTING)
HARRISON: Well, well, well.
ALLEN: We're going up there?
That's where Zoom's lair is.
A place only a speedster could get to.
They're like the Cliffs of Insanity.
So how do we get up there?
I can make you something to climb on,
darling.
Are you serious?
You want us to, what, just climb to the
top of those cliffs on ice? (LAUGHS)
Got any better ideas?
No, ma'am. I'm just...
You know, I've got...
You know, I'm wearing wing tips here.
They, um, don't have much tread.
Barry, Barry, um,
maybe you should stay behind, yeah?
No. Hey, no. I'm not letting you
go up there by yourself.
It is okay if you don't wanna go,
if you don't want to do this.
You're my wife.
I'm not leaving your side.
Okay.
-Can we go?
-Yeah.
I'm ready.
Let's go before I change my mind.
(GRUNTS)
-You really think handcuffs can stop me?
-I know they can.
Just like this boot on your neck,
it dampens your power.
Same goes for the six-by-six cell
you'll be calling home at Iron Heights.
All right, let's go.
Caitlin.
-So sorry I didn't come sooner.
-That's okay. Um...
Can I show you something?
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
My cells.
They stopped degenerating.
How is this even possible?
It appears that when the Velocity-Nine
is in your system,
it kick-starts your latent
regenerative capabilities
and your cells repair themselves.
And do you think you can get this
to work permanently?
I don't know,
but I think we're on the right track.
Caitlin, I don't know what to say.
This is...
You are...
(ALARM BLARING)
-What's that?
-The speed cannon.
-Geomancer's tremors must have damaged it.
-Okay. Come on.
Come on.
The breach isn't stabilized.
We need to fix this fast.
Otherwise, they're never going to be
able to come back.
So that was the sound that we heard.
Please tell me
it's not as bad as it looks.
-Uh...
-Come on, seriously?
They still have an hour left.
What if they're trying to get through the
breach right now and they can't?
Okay, the jolt disrupted the quark matter.
The electromagnetic insulators
are failing.
How do we fix this in time?
I don't know if we can.
Barry?
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Cisco.
Dude, we made it.
How did you find this place?
Had some help.
Don't even get me started on this guy.
Oh, boy.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Dr. Wells.
(CHUCKLING)
Stand back.
(GRUNTS)
(JESSE SOBS)
I'm here. I'm here.
Come on, let's get you out of here.
Okay.
Frost.
-A little help?
-Not part of the deal.
-Frost!
-CISCO: Hey, hey, hey.
Bringing us up here wasn't part of the
deal either, but here you are.
Something tells me you're not as cold
as I thought you were.
Maybe. Maybe not.
(GRUNTS)
What's going on? Why isn't it working?
I don't know.
I've never had this problem before.
Dr. Wells.
Carbyne. It's some form of carbyne.
This cell's made of some form of carbyne.
You'll never be able
to freeze him out of there.
You can't phase out of there?
Just go, all right?
Before Zoom comes back.
We're not leaving you here.
I can't get out of this cell. I've tried.
A lot.
I'm not fast enough to phase through this.
You got...
Just leave all right?
(SIGHS)
Just leave.
Do you know
what we did to get here, Barry?
We convinced her, Killer Frost,
to show us the way.
Then we climbed some insanely steep cliffs
outside on footholds made of ice. Ice.
And all of us risked our lives, knowing
Zoom was after us, to rescue Jesse
and you.
Now, I don't know you
and you don't know me, but
I can tell you that, today, I did things
that I never thought possible
because I needed to prove to my wife and
to myself that I could.
And now if I can do the impossible today,
so can you.
(EXHALES)
I'm just Barry Allen.
But you are the Flash.
If you tell yourself you can phase
out of there, you'll do it.
(SCOFFS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(CHUCKLES)
-Okay, let's go.
-Go.
Wait, wait. Hey, hey, hey.
We're not leaving him.
Barry, there's no time.
He's not going anywhere,
and neither are any of you.
Thank you for bringing them to me.
You double-crossed us?
He killed Ronnie.
Guess my heart is as cold
as you thought after all.
I can't believe you.
Just so you know, you would be
very disappointed in you right now.
Zoom, let them go.
All you need is me and Barry.
You're right.
I may not be able to kill you yet,
but I can kill them.
(SOBS) No, no.
I told you I'd kill you
in front of your father.
No. No!
Get out of here.
(GRUNTS)
Caitlin.
You were right.
He killed Ronnie.
Thank you.
I'm not leaving without him.
Barry, there's no time. There's no time!
I can't hold him forever.
All right. Hey, I'm coming back for you
when this is all over, all right?
-Go!
-I'm coming back.
Jay, we need to do something.
Our only chance is to reboot the
electromagnetic insulators
and hope the quark matter
redistributes equally.
-How we do that?
-We have to do it manually.
But you can't be near the stabilizer rings
when they power on
or you'll get sucked into the breach.
Not if I create a vortex
to counteract the pull.
You can't do both at the same time.
Cait.
I have to try.
I'll help you.
What? Dad, no.
Look, if it brings Barry back to this
Earth, I'm doing it.
-Are you sure?
-The more we talk about it,
the less sure I'll be,
so let's just do it.
Okay.
There's an override switch
on every stabilizer ring.
I'll create the vortex,
and you flip all of them.
-They should all reboot.
-Got it.
Once that's done, you power up the cannon.
The breach should stabilize.
And what if it doesn't?
We're all out of luck.
The Velocity-Nine is running out.
Jay.
I guess now we know
how long the Velocity-Nine lasts. (GRUNTS)
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. Yeah.
I just hope they are.
-Hey.
-I'm fine, I'm just a mess.
You guys need to get out of Central City,
all right?
Any place you think
you'll be safe from Zoom?
Yeah. We have some family in Atlantis
that can help us.
Yeah, okay, good.
You may not have been struck by lightning
over here like I was,
but today, you risked your life to save
somebody you didn't even know.
That's a hero, Barry.
Thank you, both.
Barry, is my father still alive
on your Earth?
Yeah, he is.
Give him a hug for me, will you?
I will.
(GRUNTS)
Hey, you guys need to get someplace safe,
too. Where are you going?
(SIGHS) The only place we can.
-Dad, we can't just leave.
-We have to, honey.
What? You want me to leave everything
I have here?
My friends, my family? I mean, my life?
You don't have a life here anymore.
Neither do I. Zoom is too powerful.
I can't stop him.
And as long as he is here,
he's gonna hunt us down.
-Until we're dead.
-(ALARM BEEPING)
Wells, if you're coming with us,
we have to go.
Come on. Come on.
It's almost time.
I don't care what time it is.
After all we did to stabilize this breach,
we're not closing it until they show up.
You all hear me?
Cisco!
Get ready to close the breach for good.
Zoom's coming.
(GRUNTS)
Forgetting someone, Flash?
Let him go.
Close the breach.
Tell Jesse I love her.
Tell her yourself.
(GRUNTS)
It shouldn't be taking this long.
Close it! Close it now!
You did it. You made it.
Barry.
(GRUNTS)
No!