You got it!
Feel that power, lady!
Think about those bikini vibes.
You want to look like a giant jellyfish on
the beach?
Come on!
Hang in there, ladies.
You've got it!
All right, I hope I see you next week for
Sparkle Your Life.
We're going to work on the lateral abs.
You know the most difficult part to
sculpt.
But in the meantime, take care of
yourself.
Great job, ladies!
You've got it!
Happy birthday!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you!
I don't care about every fucking young
girl in this fucking town!
In the next few weeks!
Look, I'll make it simple.
We need her young.
We need her hot.
We need her now.
Hell, the old bitch has been able to stick
around for this long.
That's the fucking mystery to me.
Oh, Oscar winner, my ass.
When was that?
Back in the 30s?
What?
For King Kong?
No, I don't give a fuck what we promised
her.
This is network TV, not a fucking charity.
Find me somebody new!
Now!
Hey, did you know that a woman's fertility
starts to decrease by the age of 25?
How old is Jennifer?
Are you ready to get busy?
It's like when you see someone fart on
screen.
People just love that.
I mean, that's just the way it is.
For you or me, people are just people.
And I have to give people what they want.
That's what keeps the shareholders happy.
And people always ask for something new.
Renewal?
It's inevitable.
At 50?
Well... it stops.
What stops?
What?
Um... You know, the um...
the um... the um... the um...
Oh, George!
Oh!
I'm sorry, I gotta run.
Harvey!
George!
Those ratings are insane!
You're a genius!
Oh, what a mess!
Well,
it's your lucky day, Ms. Sparkle,
because we have X-rayed you from head to
toe and you don't have so much as a crap
molar.
So, you are good to go.
Uh, vaccination, okay.
Not currently on our medication.
By the way, I just want to say my wife is
a huge fan.
Um... blood type... Oh,
hey, it's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Oh,
uh, that's an emergency, I'm sorry.
Here, I have to have a... Bye.
One moment.
There's just one last exam to perform.
I thought he said I was good to go.
Is there a problem?
No, it's perfect.
You're a good candidate.
I mean, you're good to go.
I wish you the best.
Lizzie?
Lizzie Sparkle?
Oh, my God, I can't believe it.
Fred.
Fred from 10th-grade homeroom.
Oh, Fred.
Of course.
You haven't changed a bit.
You're still the most beautiful girl in
the whole wide world.
You know, I followed your career.
What a success.
I mean, wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
Hey, why don't we go out maybe for a drink
sometime now that we're, you know,
reconnected?
Um...
Oh, of course, I'm stupid.
You're super busy.
But you know what?
Why don't you give me your card?
I mean, you never know.
Um, here, what do
I... Oh, this will do.
Don't look at my cholesterol levels.
They're a disaster.
Oh, God.
There.
Now you've got it.
Have you ever dreamt of a better version
of yourself?
Younger.
More beautiful.
More perfect.
One single injection unlocks
your DNA, starting a new cellular
division that will release
another version of yourself.
This is... the substance.
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you.
And everything is you.
This is simply a better version of
yourself.
You just have to share.
One week for one.
And one week for the other.
A perfect balance of seven days each.
The one and only thing not to forget.
You are one.
You can't escape from yourself.
Yes?
Yes.
Hello.
I'd like... to order.
Address?
1057 Beverly Canyon.
Write this down.
35 North Byron Alley.
35 North...
You are the matrix.
Everything comes from you.
And everything is you.
This is simply... a
better version of yourself.
Hello.
Hi.
We'll let you know by next week.
Thank you so much.
I'm just dying to get the part.
Great dancer.
Too bad her boobs aren't in the middle of
her face instead of that nose.
Next!
Looks like everything sure is in the right
place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
Sue.
I'm Sue.
Where is she?
Where is she!?
What a gorgeous little angel!
You're hired.
We want a show that's just like you.
Beautiful and happy.
People want to be happy.
We air in two weeks, so let's get to work.
I'm gonna let you organize the rest with
my assistant, uh...
Um...
Um... Um...
Um... Isabella?
Isa, isa, isa.
Who has time to say that?
We're gonna make you Cindy.
It's shorter.
It's better.
So, I'm gonna let you organize everything
else with Cindy.
Oh, um... Before you go, I just have
to mention a small scheduling issue.
I have to be out of town every other
week...
to take care of my mother, who's very
sick.
I want you for this show, and we will work
around any mother, brother, fucking sick
puppy that you need to take care of.
Gorgeous.
With a pure heart, people are gonna love
that.
So you jump out.
Touch her out.
Contract.
And five, six, seven, eight.
Elbows.
Where have you been?
We've all been wanting to have a drink
with you for your departure.
Anyway, we all chipped in, and we got you
just a little something to keep you busy.
It's French.
My wife.
She swears by it.
Oh, I love my wife.
Oops.
I gotta run.
But it's always great to see you.
Which is the most valuable seafood to
start?
Expensing stock options.
Most of the nation's...
Bob and Judy, are you ready?
Know what you'll be toting around for the
rest of your days?
Regret.
Of Seville, kids on the phone.
The antelope and the deer moving about.
A hunt through the Texas...
Sorry.
I thought that Ms.
Sparkle... She moved out.
I'm the new tenant.
Sue.
Oliver.
You wanted to complain about something?
Oliver?
What?
No?
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no,
I think it's, like, awesome
when there's stuff
going on in the building,
you know what I mean?
I'm actually quite handy if you ever need
me to be of aid in any way.
I got a sack of tools and I got a big
hammer.
You know what I mean.
Anyways, I live right here, so you know
where to find me.
Anytime.
Day or night.
Later.
Hi, everybody.
I'm Sue.
And it's time to pump it up.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Thank you so much, everybody.
I'll see you next week.
And in the meantime, take care of
yourself.
Wait, Sue.
Just wait for me.
Don't eat too fast.
I'm coming.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'll be right back.
No!
What did you do?
You seem even more beautiful than before.
No.
Yes?
Yes, hi.
This is Elizabeth Sparkle.
I'm 503.
Yes.
Yes, hi.
There's been a slight misuse of the
substance.
A few extra hours were accidentally used,
causing an alteration.
So I'm just looking for the procedure to
reverse it.
What has been used on one side is lost on
the other side.
There's no going back.
No.
I don't know what she was thinking.
And obviously, she was drunk.
Remember, there is no she and you.
You are one.
Respect the balance, and you won't have
any more inconveniences.
You got to move!
Sue!
I just saw you on TV.
Holy moly!
Makes me want to join your class.
Hey, you don't get private lessons,
do you?
Hey, um...
What about a drink at, um...
My place tonight.
Come on, don't be shy.
I see you standing behind the door there,
gorgeous.
All right.
Take your time.
But it's a date.
What can I get you?
Um, mocha latte.
It's long, isn't it?
Excuse me?
Seven days.
Did you follow me here?
I was just curious to find out how things
were going for you.
Each time you feel a little more...
lonely.
Don't you think?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
It gets harder each time to remember that
you still deserve to exist.
That this part of yourself is still worth
something.
That you still matter.
Has she started yet?
Eating away at you?
Fuck!
Watch out!
What?
You're still the most beautiful girl in
the whole wide world.
Hello?
Hi, Fred.
It's Lizzie.
Hello?
Sorry, I'm in shock.
Wow, wow, wow.
I thought I'd never hear from you again
after...
Oh gosh, no, no, not at all.
I've just been really busy lately.
So listen, I was thinking that...
maybe we could get together and grab a
drink?
Are you still there?
Sorry, I'm in shock again.
I could book Luigi's at eight?
Eight at Luigi's?
It is.
I will see you tonight.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
And we're back!
Okay, here we go everyone, clear the set
please.
First positions, thank you.
Roll cameras.
And in three, two, one.
Squat, squat, squat.
Circle bells,
contract, contract, contract.
Head between your legs.
Cut.
Um, I'm sorry, I thought I...
thought I... I just got distracted.
Not a problem, let's get right back to it.
Back to one please.
Sorry, it's the control room now.
The director said he saw something bizarre
on the monitor.
Bring up the replay on camera two.
Camera two.
Forward.
Can I have my dressing gown?
Sorry, it's in your dressing gown.
Well then go and get it.
Let's just take this frame by frame.
I need five minutes.
Yes.
This balance is not working.
I barely have any time
to enjoy myself while she
wastes seven days stuffing
her face in front of the TV.
Remember there is no she and you.
You are.
What's happening?
Where is everybody?
The taping has been cancelled.
What?
Why?
Sue.
Harvey wants to see you in his office
immediately.
Okay.
I'll go change it.
No, he said now.
I'll get right to the point.
We can't keep you on the morning show.
But why?
I just started.
Ratings are through the roof.
We started at forty-two.
But now we're up too late.
Two hundred and sixteen.
It's phenomenal!
People love you.
They adore you.
They want more and more and more of you.
That is why we have decided that we want
you to host the New Year's Eve show.
You mean the... The
network's biggest show.
Fifty million viewers live.
You can't go higher than that.
That's gonna be intense.
We only have a few months to pull it off.
So, are you in?
If you don't open the door when opportunity
knocks, you won't get another chance.
You of all people know this.
Just one more day and then I have a whole
week off.
We can switch.
We're doing the cover of Vogue.
Just one more day, okay?
No!
Yes.
She didn't respect the balance.
She's stealing more and more time from me.
Completely, without consideration of the
consequences.
She's a selfish bitch!
Would you like to stop?
Stop?
You are the Matrix.
If you are not satisfied,
you can put an end to the
experience and go back to
being just you on your own.
Would you like to stop?
Will it go back to the way it was before?
What has been transferred won't come back,
but you can stop the experience as of now.
Would you like to stop?
To go back to being just you on your own?
No, no.
I can't stop.
She just...
I...
The balance just needs to be respected.
So respect it.
Just stop it, stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it.
Stop.
Just a little something to keep you busy.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, she is here.
The superstar of the moment, Sue.
Are you ready?
Let's welcome her.
Sue!
You popped up out of nowhere on our
screens like a tornado.
I don't think anybody was really prepared
for this whirlwind.
It all started with the morning show.
And rumor has it that you are up for Tom
Grant's next movie.
Wait just a moment.
I'm being told that you are going to host
the New Year's Eve show.
Can you confirm this?
Yes, that's right.
Oh my God, that is huge news.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
Where are you from?
How did you get discovered?
I want, we want to know everything.
Well, I mean, there's really not very much
to tell.
I'm just a girl from a very small town in
Indiana.
I'm sure that you've never heard of it.
In fact, it's not even a town.
I'm not sure you could really even call it
a village.
It's a farm, perhaps?
But ever since I can remember, it has
always been my dream to be on screen.
This is my dream.
As a child, I used to put on shows for my
family.
Oh, your family.
How sweet.
So, everyone is aware that you replaced
Elizabeth Sparkle.
And no doubt about
it, you stepped in, you
turned up the volume,
and you rocked their world.
Were you a fan of her show?
Um, well, well, I can't, uh, I can't really
say that I actually watched her show.
You do know that we're not exactly from
the same generation.
And you have to admit, it was a bit old
-fashioned.
Jurassic Fitness, really.
Jurassic Fitness, it needed a change.
I'll fucking show you.
You wanna see some Jurassic Fitness?
But my mother was a huge fan of hers.
So, every morning, rain or shine,
Sparkle Your Life was on TV.
So, in a way, I grew up with her.
Whether I liked it or not.
I guess that's why you can say we have
some sort of connection.
Some sort of connection.
You wouldn't exist without me.
It is time, ladies and gentlemen,
for our final question.
The question that we ask each and every
one of our guests.
Okay.
Would you share one of your little beauty
secrets with us?
Just one little trick of yours that helps
you look so incredibly stunning.
I mean, look at you.
I don't know.
Say it!
Let me think.
Tell them who your little beauty secret
is.
I guess... Why don't you
just show them right here?
Here's your little beauty secret.
I guess I just try to be myself.
To be sincere and grateful for all that I
have.
And to always remember to leave with my
heart.
America, sweetheart.
I just...
I try to be myself.
Stop it.
You're taking it from me.
That's your little secret.
Stop it!
You have to control yourself!
I can't go back inside her.
Ugh!
Gross!
Old!
Fat!
Can we move to bed?
Yes.
I'll be right there.
Hi, this is an emergency.
There's, uh... There's
no more stabilizer fluid.
Hello?
It's fucking 503!
Yes.
I'm telling you, this is urgent.
There's no more stabilizer fluid.
It means you've reached the end.
What do you mean, the end?
You've drained it all out.
If you want more, you must let the fluid
regenerate.
Tell me how to do it!
I need to stabilize myself right now!
You simply have to switch.
Uh, excuse me?
The switch reboots the
fluid secretion process,
so you can continue
to enjoy the experience.
No, no, no, no, no.
I can't switch!
I can't!
Especially not now!
There is no other option.
Sue?
Sue!
Babe?
Sue?
You alright?
Should I start all about tomorrow?
Babe?
Sue?
Is something wrong?
Are you a little cranky because you're
related business?
Sue, open the door.
Come on, Sue!
Is that funny?
I need to take a piss.
Sue, open the door!
Open the door, Sue!
Come on!
Open the door!
The fuck?
Get the fuck out!
Who's this?
Who the fuck is this?
Then leave me alone!
What the fuck?
Yes.
It's 503.
I want to stop.
Are you sure?
Once you stop, you can't go back.
I want to stop!
I want to fucking stop!
We'll deliver.
Sue, I want to...
Are you sure?
Once you stop, you can't go back.
You will simply remain on your own.
Just on your own.
Shut the fuck up!
I can't do this.
I need you.
Because I hate myself.
You gotta get ready.
It's our big night.
Come on, they're gonna love you so much.
Come on.
What?
You're the only lovable part of me.
You have to come back.
You have to come back!
Come back!
Come on.
Come on!
Oh,
no!
Oh!
You got an
hour and a half of makeup.
Here.
Then we gotta enjoy the fitting room.
Keep your dress.
After that, we have one final test on
stage for lighting the sound.
We have a bit of downtime before the show
starts.
You got it?
You good?
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
Dress!
Wonderful.
Perfect.
There you go.
Good?
You get the dance lights?
I'm gonna be right back, sorry.
Oh!
Sue,
they need to see you on stage to set the
lights.
Huh?
Have you ever dreamt of a better version
of yourself?
More beautiful, more perfect.
Sue!
Who's there?
Okay, so I'll wait for you on stage.
Sue?
Let me introduce you to the shareholders.
They have been dying to meet you.
Is everything... okay?
So smile!
That's what we want tonight!
Pretty girls should always smile!
Come on, come on, come on!
Girls, come on!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on, we gotta go!
Tiffany!
Cindy!
Ashley!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Feathers!
Are you ready for tonight?
I just need a better version of myself.
Please give me a better version of myself,
please!
Please!
Come on!
Looks like everything sure is in the right
place this time.
Please say your name, age, measurements.
Pretty girls
should always smile!
At last, we're starting to worry.
Hurry up, you're up in five.
You will not be disappointed.
She's my most beautiful creation.
I have shaped her for success.
One!
I'm so happy to be with you tonight.
I miss you all so much.
I love you.
- The monster!
- Shoot the monster!
Monster!
In the middle of her face instead of that
nose.
Next!
Pretty girls should always smile!
At fifty, it stops.
Please!