My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster, Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him
murder the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power to change the future.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force,
I accidentally ran to the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
- How are you gonna tell Dad?
- I'm not.
If you guys got something going on,
I hope you know you can talk to me.
Every night when I go to bed,
I'm afraid that I'm gonna wake up...
Her.
I didn't ask for these powers, just like
you didn't ask to be used by Savitar.
So, you're telling me
that every time I'm blacking out...
You've become Alchemy.
Alchemy can restore the powers
that people had in Flashpoint.
What Alchemy did was not your fault.
I'm saying that at this point
in his training,
you're faster than Barry.
It's crazy how fast I've gotten
in such a short time.
And I'm gonna need you
to get a lot faster.
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar,
you are.
So this is it, huh?
Yeah, this is
the starting line to our race.
Cisco's set up sensors
all along the course,
and he'll be tracking our speed
all the way to the finish line
on the other side of town.
No, I meant, this is it,
the day the greatest upset
in speedster history goes down.
Wally...
man, this isn't
about winning or losing, okay?
This is about training
so you can get faster
and beat Savitar and save Iris.
- Yeah. Which I'm gonna do.
- Okay.
But first I'm gonna make you eat my dust.
I'm sorry.
Okay, you know, there is a reason
they call me the fastest man alive.
Cisco, you good?
Ladies and gentlemen, the Central City
Speedster 500 is about to begin,
but first, I've got five-to-one odds
Barry takes down Wally.
- Any takers?
- Yeah. Game of speculation?
Are we... We're betting? Yeah. No, I'm in.
On my Earth, financial wagering was banned
after an unfortunate incident
with Vice President Al Capone.
- Well, lucky for you, you live here now.
- Yes.
Put me down for $20 for Barry.
- Joe, got to be in it. Come on.
- No, not me.
That's a Sophie's Choice
I'm not gonna make.
$80 on Barry.
Mama needs a new confocal microscope.
All right, H.R.,
you put your life in my hands,
so I know for a fact you like high stakes.
How much you in for?
Wallace's recent speed tests
ensure that he is a lock.
- Put me down for an Abe Lincoln.
- Hmm?
$100. Whatever $100 is on this Earth,
put me down for that.
Guys, we're ready.
All right, all right. All bets are in,
and may the odds be ever in your favor.
Gentlemen,
start your engines.
- Ready.
- Get set.
Go.
At the first marker, one-third
of the way in, Flash is in the lead,
- or is that Kid Flash?
- Kid Flash.
Come on, Little Joe from Kokomo,
mama needs a new pair of shoes.
Come on, Wallace. Down the lane!
I think he's done this before.
Ooh! Second marker, Wally's in the lead.
- Yeah, Wallace! That's my boy.
- You mean, that's my boy.
That's your boy. I wanna double down.
I wanna double down on that right now.
Oh! H.R., big spender. You serious?
Serious? Serious as a heart attack, Rich.
Guys, they're neck-and-neck.
And almost at the finish line.
- Oh!
- Oh-ho! Yes.
Pay up.
Hmm?
Now?
Do you guys take IOUs?
Come on, man! That didn't count.
You know I can't phase yet.
Man, you just saw me do it, right?
And you have to be ready to face
any obstacle that's put in your path.
Yeah, well, don't worry, Barry.
I'm gonna get faster.
Pretty soon, I'm gonna be faster than you.
Oh, yeah? Well, until then,
what's my name?
Joe, hey, this one is, uh...
Pretty ghastly, Detective, I warn you.
- That's the body?
- Yeah, why?
'Cause he died less than eight hours ago.
Eight hours?
He was a chef here, Stuart Holzman,
and the owner confirmed
that he was working last night.
That's a lot of damage
in a short amount of time.
- We thinking he's a meta?
- Possibly.
Although certain chemicals
can cause a similar reaction.
Yeah, any acid with a pH below two.
Precisely.
We could be looking for an aggressive
variant of a necrotizing fasciitis.
A flesh-eating disease.
In a restaurant?
I'm never eating out again.
Hey, so an autopsy might help us
hone in on what really did this.
Yes, I agree.
Unfortunately, County denied my request
for a 3D-image medical scanner, which
would make short work of the process.
Okay, well, we have one at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Allen, this is an active investigation.
There is protocol to follow.
Surely?
Not if we're gonna figure this out.
Okay. I'll bag the body myself
and meet you there.
Great.
Iris.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just running up
against a deadline, so...
Since I have you both, I wanted to ask,
um, Cecile's daughter, Joanie, is in town,
and I was thinking
that maybe we could all get together,
if you don't think it's too soon.
I mean, I haven't exactly been dating
Cecile for that long...
It's not too early, Joe.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And Jitters,
is that cool, or is that too casual?
Dad, don't worry, okay? It's great.
Joanie's gonna love you.
I love my kids. I'm gonna set it up.
Thank you.
All right.
It's nice to see him so happy.
- Yeah, it is.
- Are you okay?
Hey, I need to show you something
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Okay.
Look.
That's the name
of the restaurant where we just were.
- Yeah.
- I spoke to the owner,
and he said he doesn't think
that the restaurant can survive
an attack like this,
that they'd most likely have
to reopen under a new name.
- It's all coming true, Barry.
- No.
I thought things were changing.
Things are changing, okay? They are.
I was supposed to stop Plunder, right?
And instead Wally did.
And we're gonna stop Savitar, too.
I'm making sure of it.
What if we can't stop all of this?
I'm scared, Barry.
Okay, look.
Maybe we should tell Joe.
No, no. No, we agreed that we wouldn't.
Besides, you saw him earlier.
He's planning for a future with Cecile.
If we tell him about Savitar,
it's all he's gonna think about.
I can't do that to him. I won't.
Okay, whatever you want.
But listen to me.
I promise you,
I'm doing everything in my power
to make sure that
that future never happens.
Okay.
You think this is what it's like
to be a character on CSI?
What do they hope to gain
from that examination?
They're trying to find
the exact cause of death.
Once we know that, we'll have
a better idea of what we're dealing with,
but until then, we need to train.
I'm gonna teach you everything I know,
starting with phasing.
Yes! Finally.
You know what we should do?
We should concoct some simulations
to help Wallace learn this new skill.
What do you say, Francisco?
I've got one word for you, "Quebracho."
- Let's go.
- Quebracho!
What's his name?
Doesn't really matter much now, does it?
Of course, we should call him by his name.
After everything he's been through,
he deserves that much respect.
"He" is a corpse,
thus impervious to such bedside manners.
Well, thank goodness 'cause I'd hate
to have to subject him to yours.
Victim is male, between 30 and 40,
with a highly necrotized epidermis.
We plan to do a full-body scan
and a chest wall retraction...
Julian, look.
The decay continues
even after the tissue's dead.
This is not a bacteria.
Or any other disease
known to medical science.
That was one crazy set, man,
and I'm telling you, Rob,
you keep wailing on that saxophone,
you're gonna be running up
to Lee Jay Thompson in no time.
All right, have a good one.
Catch you laters.
All right. All right.
Whoo!
- Do I know you?
- Unlikely.
But I know you, Julio Mendez.
Man, that was some set.
Your cover of "Dock of the Bay"
took me to a different time and place.
Well, I'm glad you dug the set, man.
Hey, before you go, uh,
I'd just really like to shake your hand.
Yeah, anything for a fan.
What did you do to me?
What you deserve
for all the pain you caused me.
Oh!
No. Ow!
That hurt like...
Like you ran into a giant wooden wall?
'Cause you did.
That was not just any big wooden wall.
That's double-reinforced quebracho.
That's like the strongest stuff
on the planet right there.
Well, fantastic choice, Cisco.
Well, it shouldn't matter
if it's wood or steel or stone.
If you're moving fast enough,
you can phase through anything.
Even molten lava? You know,
if you ever ended up in a volcano?
You know, I still don't get it.
How do you do this?
All right, here, watch.
When you vibrate
at the natural frequency of air,
your body, your cells,
will be in an excited state
that'll allow you to phase.
Yeah, it's not really helping.
What exactly do I do?
Connect with your body, right?
Connect with the air. Be pure electricity.
You have to feel everything
that's around you, all right?
So go fast and feel things. Yeah.
No worries.
You can do this, Wallace.
Okay. All right, all right.
You can do this.
All right, again. Yeah?
You got this.
- This isn't working.
- It's not working.
You've been training him. What's worked?
You know what works with that guy?
Vocal encouragement.
You got this, Wallace!
I don't know why you ask him.
Well, what did Wells do with me?
His plan was more methodically constructed
than John Doe's in Seven,
and he had a bit more time to work it out
by, give or take, 15 years.
Well, we don't have 15 years.
I have a crime scene. I've got to go.
I'll be back.
Just make sure he keeps practicing.
Go, Wallace!
Body was found by that bicyclist.
Same MO as the first one.
This victim was performing
here last night.
He's a lounge singer named Julio Mendez.
Julio Mendez?
Has anybody seen Detective West?
In Flashpoint, he was Captain Mendez.
Sorry, in Flashpoint,
this alternate universe that you lived in,
he worked at the CCPD?
Yeah.
Wait a second. The other...
The other vic, Stuart Holzman,
do we have a photo of him?
- Yeah.
- Can I see it?
The one on... That's him.
What is it?
He was a cop there, too.
So this is the second dead cop
from Flashpoint?
Yeah.
We've got to figure out who this guy is.
Well, if we hurry, there's still a chance
we can get some
of the attacker's residual DNA
before this corpse disintegrates,
but we've got to move quick.
Barry, you can help with that.
All right, come on.
- Anybody see me?
- Damn, I barely saw you.
Look, we've got to get going.
Hey, Joe, hold up.
Look, I know how excited you are for
this coffee thing with Joanie and Cecile,
but I think we should hold off.
I don't think it's a good idea right now.
Barr, these two attacks
don't establish a pattern.
- Well...
- And, besides, I'm a cop.
If I canceled my plans every time I was
in danger, I'd never leave the house.
I hear you. I would just feel a lot better
knowing you were someplace safe.
Name a place safer than a coffee shop
with my two speedster sons.
Meeting Joanie is important to Cecile.
Therefore, it's important to me.
Some things are worth taking risks for.
All right. Let's get out of here.
Anything?
Aside from this body
disintegrating before our eyes,
nothing unusual.
There must be a heightened point
of necrosis somewhere. Look.
We have less than 50 minutes
before this corpse disintegrates into ash
like the last one.
We need to find it now.
I'm aware.
This might be
a faster process if I did it alone.
You know,
I've done autopsies before, Julian.
I'm sure you have.
This might just be
a quicker process if I did it alone.
What are you doing?
The gradation is darker
on the palm of his hand
from the point of contact.
I see. I see.
You know, I used to think
Barry was overreacting
when he complained
about sharing a lab with you,
but now I understand his frustration.
Believe me,
no one is more frustrated than I.
You do realize that it's possible
not to be a jerk all the time, right?
Yes. Yes, yes, yes.
Two strains of DNA.
One of them must be from our killer.
But, you know,
there's something else here.
One of the DNA strains
has an element in it.
Have you ever seen anything
like that before?
I have...
In all the meta husks created by Alchemy.
Which means the meta that killed
our two innocent people
was created by me.
- French roast for Cecile.
- Thank you.
Non-dairy green tea latte for Joanie.
You're not much
of a coffee drinker, Joanie?
Well, I used to be, but then I learned
hot roasted coffee beans
contain cancer-causing levels
of acrylamide.
Well, damn.
Uh, Joanie, Cecile says you're at Coast U?
- What are you studying?
- I'm undecided.
Are you leaning towards anything?
Not really.
Uh, Coast U's pretty far, right?
Do you ever miss Central City?
Actually, I like it better there.
Well, there is one thing
I miss about Central City.
- What's that?
- You're gonna regret that you asked.
Kid Flash.
She's a little obsessed.
Kid Flash is the one thing
you miss about Central City?
Whoa, Barry, slow down. You don't have
to be so skeptical about it.
Kid Flash is cool.
What do you like best
about him specifically?
- Well, he's fearless, and he's brave.
- Yeah.
He's a hero.
And he's probably pretty cute
under that mask.
Yeah, I think so, too.
Come on, Joanie. Honey, Kid Flash?
He's a showboat. He's snapping selfies.
He's leaving graffiti bolts on buildings.
- Okay, that's his signature move.
- That's kind of his signature.
Yeah, well, from what I hear,
the Flash is the one
who's actually saving people.
Sounds like Cecile's Team Flash.
Uh, Joanie, my dad would never brag
about this, but he knows Kid Flash.
You do?
- Mmm.
- Is my mom right?
Who is the real hero, Flash or Kid Flash?
Mmm...
They both are.
They both do great things
for Central City.
Okay, but if you had to choose?
I don't...
I don't think I could choose.
Yeah, but if you, like, had to.
Um, could you go get me
some cream, Wally, please?
Yes.
This is work. I'll be right back. Sorry.
Hey, what's up?
Barry, we got some DNA
off Mendez's corpse.
We were able to match it
with CCPD records.
The meta's name is Clive Yorkin.
We're sending you his info now.
Detective Joe West.
Long time no see.
- Do I know you?
- You don't remember me?
You and your cronies
had a very fun time ruining my life.
Not gonna let you do that
this time around.
I think you have the wrong guy.
No, no. You're the Joe West I remember.
Look a lot more full of life now, though,
but don't worry. I can change that.
- Everybody, get back.
- Joanie, go.
Everybody, get out of here.
Everybody, go! Go!
Yes, everybody, run.
I only want him.
You can't hide up there, Detective.
No one can hide from me anymore.
- Joe.
- One more step, and I'll shoot.
Didn't work then, won't work now, either.
Told you.
Stop.
Ah! You can't touch me, Speedster.
I knew it. Kid Flash is a hero.
Well, thank God for Kid Flash.
He's gone.
This guy's got the touch of death.
Yeah, he does, and it's not just people.
Anything he touched turned to ash.
Joe, I really think you should
just stay here until we find Yorkin.
No, I'm gonna go check
on Cecile and Joanie.
They were pretty shook up.
Dad, are you crazy?
This guy wants to kill you.
If it wasn't for Wally and Barry,
he could have.
He could have killed any one of us.
Come on. We have been through
much worse metas than Yorkin.
What?
Iris, I'm fine. We're all fine.
We're not losing anybody today.
Maybe not today but soon.
"Soon"? Wait. What are you saying?
- Iris.
- Wally, he needs to know.
Needs to know what?
When Barry threw the Philosopher's Stone
into the Speed Force,
there was an explosion,
and he was propelled to the future.
The future?
It was a few months from now.
What he saw was himself
standing before Savitar,
and me,
right before Savitar killed me.
You're saying that,
in a few months, you die?
Unless we can change the future, Dad.
Which we're gonna do, Joe, okay?
I'm not...
We're not gonna let this happen.
How long have you known about this?
- How long?
- A couple weeks ago, Joe.
And you're just telling me now?
That's my daughter.
Dad, I didn't want them to say anything
because I knew how you would react.
This is not something
you keep from your father, Iris!
You should've known that,
and you should've, too.
I know, Joe.
Look, I can even understand
why they didn't wanna tell me
because they didn't grow up
under the same roof that you did.
They don't know.
They don't know what my baby girl
means to me, Barry, but you do.
I know.
- Joe.
- I...
I'll talk to him.
I'm gonna go to CCPD,
see if I can find anything
that might lead us to Yorkin.
Well, that went swimmingly.
Joe's right.
We should have told him before now.
What you should've told him
is that I'm the one responsible,
that the meta trying to kill him
is one that I created.
Julian, you can't change
what happened to you. It's not your fault.
You keep saying that, but it is my fault.
People are responsible for their own
actions. To say otherwise is just...
It's just a way
to make yourself feel better.
Is that what you think I'm doing?
Making excuses for things
I've done in the past?
You know, I'm really starting
to regret bringing you in here.
Come on, Dad.
Hey, Dad, it's me, calling again.
Look, I know you're upset,
but, um, give me a call back, okay?
I love you.
Honey?
Good evening, Iris West.
It's Iris's panic alarm.
She's at the apartment. I'll call Barry.
No, no, no. I got this.
He's at CCPD, and I'm closer.
Okay, go.
You know, initially,
I wanted your dad dead,
but then I thought,
if I really wanna make him suffer,
I should kill his daughter instead.
This is not how I'm supposed to die.
Well, I'm pretty sure it is.
No, stop!
Too late, Kid Flash.
Me or her.
I got you, baby girl.
I'm not going anywhere.
Elevated heart rate. Temperature's 104.
The decay's reaching
her subcutaneous tissue.
I'm here, all right? What happened?
- Yorkin went after her.
- Why didn't you call me?
- Because I was here.
- You call me! All right?
We have to give her something.
There has to be something we can give her.
It's not bacteria. Antibiotics won't work.
We have to do something.
Nothing's not an option.
Okay, what do you do
when a banana ripens too quickly?
Put it in the freezer.
That's brilliant.
Caitlin, you can freeze her arm.
It will stop the spread of decay
and give us some time to find a cure.
I trust you.
I can't, even if I wanted to.
We're not talking about a cold blast.
This is a specific
and continuous cold stream.
Too high a temperature,
and the decay spreads.
Too low, and frostbite will destroy
your nerve endings.
And that long using my powers,
I could lose control.
Caitlin, you're strong, okay?
Stronger than you know.
You're not going to lose control.
Caitlin. Try, please.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
It worked.
Thank God.
Are you okay?
So far, so good.
Wally, where are you going?
Out of the way,
where I can't screw up again.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Hey, look, what I said back there...
No, you were right.
We should've called you.
I just thought... I thought I could do it.
I thought I was ready.
Obviously, I'm not.
That's not on you.
I wasn't fast enough, Barry.
That is totally on me.
No, not really. It's not. All right?
Look, when I got these powers,
I was really lucky in a weird way.
You know, I had a lot of people
helping me through all of this.
I had Wells, both of them,
and Jay and Zolomon.
I mean, two of them turned out
to be bad guys,
but even they were good teachers
who really taught me how to use my powers.
I just don't think
that I've been that for you yet.
You're telling me everything
that I need to learn.
I'm just not getting it. I...
No, that's not it. It's... I've been...
I've been letting you coast by on
your raw talent, which you have a lot of,
but teaching, it's a lot more
than just doing something
and expecting you to follow.
It's about inspiring and empowering you
to use your gifts to succeed on your own.
That's what I need to do.
That's what I'm gonna do from now on,
so the next time
you're out there and you're alone,
you will win.
Deal?
Deal.
H.R. and I just came up with a way
to track down Yorkin,
and it's crazy,
like "defies time and space" crazy.
Okay. Here's what we know.
We know Yorkin's going
after cops in Flashpoint, right?
What we don't know
is who he's going after.
But if we find out who they are,
then we can be ready for him.
Right. So how do we do that?
- We vibe Flashpoint.
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore.
Stop you right there, B.A.
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore
in this universe.
But in quantum mechanics,
- the Daughter Universe Theory tells us...
- Universe Theory.
For every decision you make,
a universe exists where you don't.
Yeah, I actually went to that class.
You better be going to all your classes.
Okay, so if there is a universe
where you stay in Flashpoint,
Francisco here could vibe it.
And you're sure you can do that?
No. No, not at all, but Gypsy did say
I could do some pretty incredible things
with my powers.
Yes, she did.
Things I'm not ever aware of yet,
so things I haven't even imagined.
Well, let's get to imagining.
- All right.
- What do you need me to do?
All I need you to do is just stand there,
focus on Flashpoint, okay?
Focus on CCPD,
Joe, Mendez, that part of it,
and I'll take care of the rest.
It worked! I'm here.
Huh.
For some reason, I thought
Flashpoint would look a lot different.
Okay, all right, if I were Joe West,
where would I be?
He was at the same desk.
Got you.
If it wasn't for this takedown,
we'd be having a different conversation
right now, Joe.
Understood, Captain.
Joe's in trouble.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for today's perp walk,
we have a literal degenerate.
The one and only, Clive Yorkin!
Here we go.
Captain Mendez, Detective West,
thanks for the assist.
Couldn't have bagged
this goon without you.
Get him to Iron Heights.
- Stone.
- "Stone."
That was the other cop.
And let me tell you,
she loves her perp walks.
Laura Stone, she's a PI.
Yeah, that's her.
It was you, Mendez, Holzman, and her.
You guys took down Yorkin in Flashpoint.
Well, then that means she is the only one
that Yorkin hasn't gone after yet.
Classic example
of saving the best for last.
I'm on it. You guys stay here
and try to figure out
how to catch somebody we can't touch.
- Joe West. Long time no see.
- Hi.
I wish it were under better circumstances.
Listen, you're being targeted by a meta.
Sweetheart, take a look over there.
I'm the only one doing the targeting here.
That chick's husband is paying me twice
my going rate, so scram.
Look at this.
The guy that's coming after you
can do that with one touch.
Attention, all passengers.
The Star City Express is
now boarding on platform two.
- How about we multitask?
- All aboard, please.
Hey, Julian. You have anything?
Look, it's early days,
but first tests show that her blood
is attacking the cells in her body.
Wait. That's the opposite of how
my blood causes cells to regenerate.
Precisely.
Can we use my blood to save her?
Listen, I don't think that
your blood is the key to saving Iris,
but I do think it might be exactly
what we need to take down Yorkin.
All is not lost, mate.
Oh.
- The decay is spreading.
- Why?
I don't know.
Caitlin.
- Caitlin.
- I'm losing control.
Okay, all right, it's spreading.
We need you.
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
Just a little bit longer, and she's dead.
How's that for changing the future?
I know who you are, Caitlin,
and you do not wanna do this.
This is who I am. You said it.
It's time for me
to take responsibility for my actions.
Time for me to own who I really am.
Who you are is Caitlin Snow.
I know firsthand
the battle going on inside of you.
I know what it feels like.
When it happened to me, I lost, all right?
I was weak, and I let it win.
And I did...
I did horrible things to a lot of good
people, and you don't have to do that.
You're not gonna do that.
You're stronger than I am, Caitlin.
You're far stronger than I am.
You're one of the strongest people
I've ever known.
You can win this fight.
Iris needs your help now.
It's all right. It's gonna be all right.
And how do you know
this guy's coming after me, Joe?
We have pretty reliable intel.
Look, Laura, this is not someone
you should be ignoring.
He's dangerous.
He's already killed two cops.
He tried to kill me and my daughter.
Well, I've certainly pissed off
a lot of people in my day,
but the only thing I fear now is
forgetting to clear my browser.
Consider me warned.
Oh, my God.
- What is that?
- It's Joe's panic alarm.
He must be on that train.
There is no way that train can stop.
It's not gonna stop in time.
We have to get everyone out of there.
We don't have enough time.
What is happening?
Everybody, brace yourselves!
We're gonna move the train.
- How are we gonna do that?
- I'll vibrate it.
I'll vibrate it fast enough
that it can phase through this.
You can do that?
I don't know, I've never tried before.
All right.
Everybody, hold on!
Is that even possible?
We're about to find out.
Holy Kardashians!
Barry? Barry?
We're good, man.
Took a lot out of me, but it worked.
Yeah, maybe,
but we've got another problem.
Yorkin's back.
You know what they say, Kid Flash.
If at first you don't succeed,
try, try again.
You have to stop him.
I don't have it in me right now.
I need you to get your blood into him.
It'll counteract his cells
and negate his powers.
How am I supposed to do that
when I can't even touch him?
You're gonna phase it into him.
You know I've never done that before.
And you just watched me
do something I'd never done,
but I did it because I had to.
All right?
I know you can do it, okay?
I need you to believe it, too.
Now, run, Wally. Run.
It worked. I did it.
You sure did. Goodbye, Kid Flash.
Oh, look at that!
Your powers are neutralized, Yorkin.
- What did you do?
- I won.
Hey, Iris.
Hmm...
Dad.
The last time I was this happy looking
into your eyes, you'd just been born.
Hey.
It's okay. You're okay. Yorkin's done.
What happened?
I'll tell you what happened.
Wallace was a total badass.
That's what happened! Translate.
Yeah, he phased his speedster blood
into Yorkin and neutralized his powers.
That's the science behind it.
I had a great teacher.
And me?
Once Yorkin's blood was stabilized,
we actually managed
to get an antidote that cured you.
You'll have to wear
the bandage for a few days,
but, other than that,
you're absolutely recovered.
Thank you. I know what you risked for me.
I had some help.
Couldn't have done it alone.
It was all of us working together.
Yeah. Really proud of everybody.
Great job. Big ideas today.
My point is,
if we're gonna save Iris from Savitar,
we're gonna have to up our game.
No more lies,
even well-intentioned ones.
We have to be completely real
with each other.
- I agree.
- I agree with Joe, too.
From here on out, complete honesty.
- Honesty.
- Namaste.
All right, get some rest, all right?
Check on you in a bit.
- Barr.
- Yeah?
Savitar's prophecy of someone dying,
was that Iris?
Yeah, but it's not gonna happen.
Look, I'm glad
she comes first in your life now.
If you're gonna date my daughter,
that's the way it should be.
You're still a close second.
It's just heartwarming.
It's just truly heartwarming.
You're already crafting a version
of this for your book, aren't you?
"And peace finally descends
upon the Family West."
"The West Family"? "Family West."
Right, it's time I get to work.
At this hour?
Yes, there's still
one husk meta out there,
and I intend to find him. Good night.
Hey, Julian.
Hey.
I don't think you're weak because
of what happened to you with Savitar.
The strength
that I found to stay in control,
that came from you,
so thank you.
Well, I wasn't gonna let Iris die
at the hands of Killer Frost, was I?
I knew there was a good guy
inside of you somewhere,
one that the rest of us
would like to see a lot more often.
Good night.
Do you wanna get a drink?
Uh...
- What, as in now?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I'd love that.
- Hey.
- Hey!
What brings you to my neck of the bullpen?
Oh, Joanie's headed back for midterms.
We just thought we'd come and say goodbye.
Aw.
I was hoping a redo on the coffee,
seeing as the last one went off the rails.
- Yeah.
- Are you kidding me?
I got to see Kid Flash
in action right up close.
Well, we got a lot
of stories about Kid Flash
I can guarantee you never heard.
Maybe we can tell you them
over dinner next time you come to town?
I have a long weekend next month.
You sure you're ready to commit
to something that far in the future?
I am absolutely sure.
Hmm?
Good.
We should go.
- Good luck in school.
- Thank you. See you.
- Bye, babe.
- Bye.
Okay.
Good as new.
Actually, it's better than new
with the three extra locks that I added.
Which you didn't have to do.
Well, Cisco did offer
to build us a custom security door,
but we've both seen how well those things
keep people out of S.T.A.R. Labs, so...
I like deadbolts. Deadbolts work.
Just with what happened here,
I wanna make sure you feel safe.
I do.
About everything?
You know, you've been saying for weeks
- that you were gonna save me from Savitar.
- Mmm-hmm.
And while I trust you with my life,
it was hard not to feel scared.
You know, sometimes it feels like
the Flash is this guy my boyfriend becomes
when he runs off to save other people.
Like, I'm the only one
who doesn't get the Flash.
He felt separate from you.
But yesterday, when you saved me,
I remembered
that I have no reason to be scared.
- Mmm-mmm.
- The man I love is a superhero.
I love and trust you,
Barry Allen, the Flash.
I love all of you, and I always will.
I love you.
That was so nice.
- Jesse!
- No, no, no.
What's wrong?
Grodd, he's got my dad.
He has him in Gorilla City.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::