[tense music]
- [sobs]
♪ ♪
Iris.
- Bashir: So that worked.
- Wha...what just happened?
How are we still alive?
- Iris?
[sobs]
I don't understand.
- Neither do I.
What did you do?
- As-as soon
as Nora came in,
I kn...I knew you were right.
I could see the hate
in her eyes.
Real anger issues...I mean,
no match for me.
But I...I wanted
to protect you all.
So I...took care of it.
- You made her think
we were dead?
- You made us all see it.
It wasn't a nightmare,
that was an illusion.
I didn't know you could
do that.
- Yeah...
- [scoffs]
Neither did he.
You were just trying
to save yourself, you jerk.
- Hey, hey, hey.
How about "Thank you, Bashir"?
That was baller the way
you stopped that mean lady
from murdering us.
- I don't get it.
Why would Nora attack you?
- I think she sees me
as competition.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Barry:Have we been
able to locate Nora?
- There's no sign of her
on our satellites.
She could be anywhere.
- She's probably out there
somewhere,
Sith-corrupting Deon.
- I'm the reason he ran
to Nora.
If anything happens
to him...
- He's a god too,
won't he be safe?
- None of us are.
Not anymore.
- Yeah, she's right.
It's only a matter of time
before Nora senses
the other Forces are alive.
Iris, it's up to us.
We have to protect them.
- If Nora wants Bashir
and Alexa dead, then...
We need to hide them.
- Hide them?
Where? A.R.G.U.S.?
- Guys, there's nowhere on
Earth to hide
from the Speed Force.
- Then we won't hide them
on Earth.
There's only one place
Nora can't go.
A place where she didn't exist
for a few months.
- Like, in the past?
- When Nora first died?
Does that place still exist?
- It's a moment in time.
A dead zone that she can't
access,
but a Speedster can.
I can take Bashir and Alexa
and once they're inside...
- Once we're inside.
They're my responsibility,
too.
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbles]
- Cecile:I swear, that
kid of ours
can sleep through
absolutely anything.
- Reporter:
Breaking news coming in
regarding the storm.
Central City...
- Babe, what happened?
- Multiple lightning strikes
took out a wall in
Iron Heights.
Two dozen inmates escaped,
most of them metas.
- Oh no, what about Frost?
You don't think that...
- No.
This storm is the perfect cover
for criminals to lay siege.
[groans]
- You regret giving up
your badge, don't you?
- Well, if I hadn't...
I could help stop this.
People are gonna get hurt,
or worse.
- No, no, please don't do that
to yourself.
- [sighs]
I can't help anyone
from a couch.
- Yeah, maybe not,
but you know what,
you can do more
than you th...
[lightning cracks]
- Cecile!
Cecile, Cecile.
[thunder rumbles]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- This is the Speed Force?
- It was.
- It was nice of the
Addams Family
to lend you their place
for the weekend.
- All right, I'm gonna
go find Deon.
If Nora somehow finds
the three of you first...
- Yeah. Use the transmat orb
that Cisco gave me.
- The hyper-tachyon particles
inside will pull
any organic matter back
to Central City.
- We'll be safe.
Go save our family.
- Wouldn't you say goodbye?
That was rude.
- Is he gonna be okay?
- Yeah, I'm sure it's...
it's nothing.
You should get some rest.
There's no telling how long
we're gonna be here.
- [exhales]
♪ ♪
[tense tones]
- Nora: I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Where were you?
[dramatic music]
- Nora?
What happened to you?
- I couldn't feel you at all.
Which shouldn't be possible.
- You brought me here?
- I had to make sure
you were safe.
- From who? From you?
You tried to kill them,
Nora.
Even Iris.
- And I let you live.
For a reason.
Do you have any idea
what death is like?
It's an agonizing emptiness
that turns your soul
inside out.
And that loneliness
it brings?
It burns.
- Iris and I brought you back.
- You brought them back too.
As soon as I was reborn,
I could feel those new forces
trying to snuff out
my existence.
They wanted to drag me back
into the darkness, Barry.
But I won't let them.
Now bring my brothers
and sister to me...
[distorted voice]
Or your city dies.
[thunder rumbles]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- We've got Category 3 winds
and over 22 lightning strikes
a minute.
- It's Nora.
She says she's gonna
tear the city apart
unless I bring her all
three Forces.
I gotta find Deon
before she does.
- Oh, I got your back
on that, Flash.
I rebuilt the isotopic sensor.
Now, all you need to do
is sweep through the city
in a standard grid pattern,
and it'll sound off
once you're within
a hundred yards
of our teenage time god.
- All right.
- Now all you need is
a little mecha back-up.
- Not this time.
I need you and Chester
on comms.
- But Deon knows us.
We can help.
- Bringing Deon in
is my responsibility.
But we need to find
a way to stop Nora.
So focus on that.
[suspenseful music]
[lightning cracks]
[dramatic music]
- Frost: Mark.
You need to turn yourself in.
Now.
- [inhales sharply, exhales]
Ladies first, Snowflake.
After all, we're both escaped
prisoners tonight.
A little something else
we have in common.
- I didn't escape.
I came here
to turn you in.
- Yeah, that's still breaking
out of prison.
Look, before you try
to impale me again,
I just want to say...
I forgive you.
- You what?
You tried to murder me
last time.
- What do you want me
to say?
You're a hero,
and I'm a bad guy.
We all do what we gotta do.
Like this.
I really needed these biotech
interfaces for my work, so.
- So you stole them.
- Hey.
If I can ignore
your stabby faults,
then the least you can do
is ignore
my klepto ones, maybe?
Besides, I'm all done here.
You want to get a drink?
You already know I make
a mean martini.
- No, not happening.
- Come on, we had so much fun
last time.
You know, before the whole
attempted murder part.
- Would you stop bringing
that up, okay?
- You're probably right.
I will say this.
You are the first person
I've met in a very long time
that I don't want to try
and kill a second time.
♪ ♪
So how about that drink?
- No.
There is no freaking way
I would ever go out with you.
- Wait, hold on, are you...
Are you talking about dinner
and the whole nine yards?
- Look, would you just
stop doing that, all right?
- What? Just trying to get
a little clarity.
- That right there,
just...stop it.
- It is okay if you're
into me.
- For the last time,
I am not into you.
- Hm.
Then why don't you stop staring
at my six-pack?
♪ ♪
[lightning cracks]
- Caitlin: Tell me exactly
what happened.
- Lightning shot through
the window, I mean,
it was like someone wanted
to hit her.
- Maybe someone did.
Nora is controlling
this storm.
- Why would she do that
to Cecile?
- Why did she attack Iris?
Joe, don't worry.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to figure out what's wrong
with Cecile and get her back
on her feet, okay?
- Why do I feel like
the Brady Bunch
might of died in here?
- This place is an exact
replica of the house
that Barry and I grew up in.
It looks terrible now.
But it wasn't then.
- What was he like back then?
- Barry? He was...
small for his age.
- Bet he loved that
growth spurt when he was 13.
- Not really.
He was pretty clumsy.
- Wow.
Isn't this great?
Mom and the kids reminiscing
about old times.
- Anyways...
he was pretty sensitive
about it.
So I wanted to help.
I would place all of my books
on top shelves
where he thought I couldn't
reach them...
- Hey, baby sis.
Look what I can do.
Don't react.
This is just between us
siblings.
Nora's not gonna stop
until we're dead.
We need to face her
and fight together.
First, we need to get out
of here.
And I know how.
Are you with me or not?
- He was so proud of himself
when he pulled them down.
Made me smile.
♪ ♪
[device beeping rapidly]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- My life was supposed to be
on this field
as a football god.
Then I became
an actual god, and...
Somehow I still can't
make my life
go in the direction I want.
- [sighs]
- I wanted you to die.
Not them.
I just wish I could take
it all back.
- You don't have to take
it back.
Iris, Alexa, Bashir.
They're not dead.
- What?
- It was an illusion.
- Bashir.
It was him, wasn't it?
[scoffs]
♪ ♪
- Look.
I just wanted you
to feel the same pain
that I felt when you called
me a mistake.
All right? Nora's the one
who took it too far.
- You're not a mistake, Deon.
I'm glad you're here,
I know that now.
[thunder rumbles]
[sighs]
Deon.
Nora's looking for you.
- Oh, man.
She's the devil,
that girl.
Look, she's the one that
should have never existed.
You need to unmake her the same
way you were gonna unmake me.
All right? So, come on,
let's do it together.
- No, nah, I can't do that.
But I'm gonna find another way
to stop her, I promise.
After you're safe.
- Man, there's no hiding
from her crazy ass.
Look, old man.
Either you need to help me
take her down,
or I start running again.
- Deon, I'm trying
to protect you.
- Killing her is the only thing
that's gonna keep us all safe.
Why can't you see that?
- I said...
[breathes heavily]
I said...
We'll find another way.
- We...ain't doing jack.
I am.
- Deon.
♪ ♪
- How are we supposed
to keep people safe
and stop Nora?
- CCPD's evacuating people
downtown.
Let's call Team Citizen,
have them help get people
to shelters.
I'm gonna find Deon again
before he does something
he'll regret.
- Hey. What if he does kill
the Speed Force?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
It could save lives.
- Joe, you know that's
not an option.
- These are gods, Barr.
We're ants to them.
What are we supposed to do?
Just pray that it all
works out?
- These forces exist
because of me and Iris.
I have to do everything I can
to protect them.
- Well, at least you still can.
- Joe.
- Poor Joe.
First the job, now Cecile.
- I know, but right now
I need you guys to stay focused
on finding a way
to restrain Nora.
- Restraining a Force
of nature?
Barry, we've been putting
our heads together.
I just...I don't know
if it's possible.
- It has to be.
- We're doing everything
we can, I promise.
- All right, well, call me
if you have something.
I'm gonna keep searching
for Deon.
[lightning cracks]
[thunder rumbles]
- Leawood and Petersburg
are being evacuated.
Kamilla and I are gonna help.
Want to come with?
Might take your mind off
things.
- Allegra, things like that...
it's not your responsibility.
Sometimes there isn't
anything we can do.
- And that officially
makes you an old man
feeling sorry for himself.
Yeah, I talked to Barry.
Look, Joe.
You need to hear this.
You're not a cop anymore.
- I know that.
- So what are you?
Because I still see the man
who sat on a bomb
to save Cecile's life.
Or who helped
a juvenile delinquent
achieve her dream
of becoming a reporter.
You did those things.
Not because you had a badge.
But because you care
about helping others.
So...
What do you say?
- I can't leave Cecile.
- I get it.
It's your call.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
[lightning cracks]
- Nice look.
Big improvement.
- At least my alter ego doesn't
parade around in blue spandex.
- [scoffs]
- You two really are
like brother and sister.
- Iris,
that device Cisco gave you,
what if Nora finds us
and it doesn't work?
- Chester and Cisco
designed it.
It will.
- Okay.
But if Nora did find us,
she could overpower you.
Maybe I should hold on
to it.
- [scoffs]
What's up with you?
- Just give her the orb, Iris.
We're gonna take down Nora
before she gets to us.
- We're trying
to keep you safe.
- The last time that happened,
I died.
[dramatic music]
- [grunts]
- Give me the transmat now.
♪ ♪
- [inhales]
I'm sorry.
That was the only way.
- Are you sure about that?
- Wait, don't!
- Cisco:I mean, an
Einstein-Maxwell gravitational
trap
could hold Nora, but...
- But the coils would
need enough current
to power Las Vegas.
- Exactly, so...
[whoosh]
- Still no sign of Deon?
- No.
And the storm's taken out
more electrical grids.
Please tell me you've
got a plan.
- No actual plans yet.
Just...theories.
- Barry, look.
We've been racking our brains
nonstop here.
You could give us weeks
to solve this
and we still might not know
how to stop her.
I don't know how we win
this one.
[rumbling]
[alarm blares]
- Kinetic isotopes.
- It's Nora.
What do we do?
- Only thing we can.
♪ ♪
- You didn't bring them.
Do you want your world
to end?
- No.
And neither do you.
Nora, you and the other forces
were created by something just
as powerful as all this.
The love that Iris and I have
for each other.
That love is a part of you.
That means you're more than
just a force of nature now.
Our humanity is inside you
too.
So please stop.
- You still don't understand.
[thunder rumbles]
You feel that?
That wasn't me.
It never has been.
[rumbling]
That was a show of strength,
Barry.
Just like what happened
to Cecile earlier.
[lightning cracks]
- Sage.
- Just like what's happening
right now.
- Still Force.
You didn't create this storm.
- No.
Your children did.
And that's why
they must die.
- You first!
♪ ♪
- [panting] Help him.
- What happened?
- I found out the truth.
Everything that's happening
out there,
Nora isn't doing it.
The other forces are.
They have been the whole time.
- W-w-wait.
So Alexa, Bashir and Deon
are the bad guys now?
- And I thought Nora
was the problem.
- Nora: [echoing]You know
I'm the solution, Barry.
Your children's sacrifice
is necessary.
Three of them for 3 million
in return.
There's still time.
[distorted voice]
Now bring them to me,
before it's too late.
[thunder rumbles]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I couldn't stop him.
Just like I couldn't stop Nora.
What's even worse?
I'm not sure what the right
thing to do is anymore.
- Hey, you're doing
the best you can.
♪ ♪
- It's not enough.
- Barry. Hey.
- Iris?
What are you doing here?
Are you all right?
- They took off with the orb
and escaped.
I ended up halfway across town.
- Where are Alexa
and Bashir?
- They're going after Nora.
- Deon had the same idea,
now he's wounded.
- Barry, our plan didn't work.
What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
- Why is all
of this happening?
- Nora says the Forces
we created
are what's tearing the city
apart.
- And you believe her now?
- We do too.
[dramatic music]
For weeks, we've been
experiencing
Strength Force earthquakes
and Still Force
time anomalies.
But those were all force events
On a cosmic scale leading up
to this.
- And what about
the Sage Force?
- The test I ran on Cecile
earlier showed that
the lightning she was struck by
was composed
of electrochemical isotopes.
- Bashir's psychic energy.
- So it's not just
one Big Bad.
We're fighting the Forces
of the universe itself.
Talk about a family feud.
- Barry, how do we choose
between saving them
and saving our city?
[intense music]
- [grunting]
- It's okay to admit
that you like me.
[chuckle]
I'm a likeable guy.
- No, you're not.
I changed my mind.
♪ ♪
- So you did like me?
[grunts]
- Shut the hell up, Mark.
- Okay.
Am I crazy?
Or am I sensing some
wild chemistry here?
Huh?
Come on, tell me you're
not feeling that.
- The only thing I'm feeling
is my fist on your jawline.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
- [grunts]
Come on, Frosty.
I can counter everything
you do.
- You don't know everything
I can do.
Chill out.
[people screaming]
[lightning cracks]
- [screams]
- The entire city
is terrified.
- I know.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't protect them all.
- Barry, I can't lose
anyone else.
Not like Nora.
- Maybe we're not meant
to be parents.
I mean if we can't even keep
our own family safe...
- That's a load of crap.
Look, I've been feeling
so sorry for myself
that I've been neglecting
the people that need my help.
Baby girl.
You and Barry think
that you can't help your kids
because parents are
the only ones that can
keep a family safe?
- It's our job to protect them.
- She's right, Joe.
- Barry,
when you decided to be
the Flash,
I tried to talk you out of it,
said you were just a kid.
Did you stop?
- No, no, it just...
made me want to prove I could
make a difference even more.
- And you sure as hell have.
But Iris, when Barry can't
do it alone...
or those times when he is gone
like the first time
he went into the Speed Force.
Who took charge of this crew
and kept us safe?
You did.
You're always there,
side by side with him.
Just like now, taking care
of business.
[hopeful music]
You two don't get it?
Sometimes it takes a family
to protect a family.
♪ ♪
- Iris, we've been trying
to keep the forces apart.
- When we should be
bringing them together.
- I couldn't stop her.
- Because you're not supposed
to do it alone.
- Thought you wanted
to run and hide?
- Not anymore.
[rumbling]
- Guys?
We've got company.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- You both came back.
- Things are different now,
aren't they?
I could feel it.
- We both could.
- Sorry for almost
killing you.
- I tell you what,
you help us survive,
we'll forgive you.
Maybe.
- All right, no more running.
No more hiding.
It's time we face Nora.
Only we do it together.
♪ ♪
- Everyone ready?
[lightning cracks]
- Any sign of Nora yet?
- No, not yet.
[tense tones]
- Nora.
I brought them.
[lightning cracks]
I did what you asked.
- [distorted voice]
No you didn't.
You're going to betray me.
- We're connected Nora,
all of us.
Whether we like it or not,
we're a family.
That includes you, too.
- Stupid boy.
I can see I'm going to
have to kill you too.
[lightning cracks]
- Barry!
- Where the hell are we?
- We're...dead, right?
- No,
but somebody's about to be.
- Nora:Your children
did this, Barry.
This isn't how
it should be.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- So...
it's family game night.
Fine.
But I play to win.
[electronic beeping]
- I...I can't get a lock.
It's like the forces
are everywhere.
- They're all around us.
- Like cosmic forces of nature.
- That's why we can't
find them.
Because they're in
the Speed Force.
- [roars]
[all groan]
- [growls]
♪ ♪
- [yells]
[lightning cracks]
- What the hell just happened?
- She must of given up.
'Cause there are too many
of us to fight.
- No.
No, no, no.
We're not that lucky,
are we, Dad?
- [breathes heavily]
Bashir's right.
This isn't over.
[radio static]
- Iris:
Barry, can you hear me?
- Yeah, I'm all right.
We all are.
- Guys, I'm picking up
electromagnetic particles
gathering in the area.
- Is it part of the storm?
- No, no, it's as
if there's...
Some sort of collider reaction
forming over Central City.
[lightning cracks]
[thunder rumbles]
- It just keeps getting
more powerful.
If...
If this thing achieves
enough atomic mass,
it's gonna snap back
like a rubber band.
- Big Bang in reverse.
- How much time do we have?
- Chester:Uh, no idea.
It's like all four
isotopic forces are returning
to their original state.
Like when they were born.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- But in reverse.
- If that's our time table,
then we only have about
three minutes.
Maybe less.
- Barry, you have to keep
the Force Event
from reaching
optimal expansion.
We have 2 minutes
and 55 seconds
before the Forces snap back
and destroy everything
in existence.
- We heard.
Your thoughts.
- Apparently, it's hereditary.
- So what do we do?
- This.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[lightning cracks]
[eerie tones]
- You really can't
take a hint.
- And you can't kill me.
- It was worth a shot.
- Now that Daddy's gone,
there's no one here
to protect you.
Once you're all gone,
my future will be safe.
Now, surrender.
- Bashir, Deon, listen up.
We got one shot at this.
♪ ♪
- Little Sister,
what are you doing?
Are you hiding something
from me?
♪ ♪
[electricity crackles]
[somber music]
[sobbing] No.
No.
Hello?
Where is everyone?
[sobbing]
No...
[sobs]
No.
No, this is worse
than dying.
[sobbing] No.
Hello!
No!
No...
♪ ♪
[crying]
I'll be the only Force
for eons to come,
and I'll be alone.
All alone, I can feel it.
[sobs]
No, no.
Don't let it happen.
Please, don't let it happen.
Please don't let
it happen...please.
Don't let it happen.
- It's just one possible
future.
But you can choose another.
One where you're not alone.
Where you're part of a family.
Ours.
♪ ♪
[sobs]
Alexa...
Deon, Bashir.
Forgive me.
[sobs]
[intense music]
- He's not fast enough.
- He's gotta be.
[electricity sparks]
♪ ♪
[lightning cracks]
- Concentrate.
Then follow my thoughts.
[lightning cracks]
♪ ♪
[lightning crackles]
[all exhale]
- Oh, my God.
[both panting]
[soft music]
- Nora...
It's really you.
- You saved me.
You saved us all.
♪ ♪
[soft music]
- How do you feel?
- Like I'm home.
- Hey, nice crib.
- Meh, you should have seen
it before the remodel.
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
- This place feels different.
With you all here, I feel...
- Faster?
You are.
With all of us together,
you'll be faster than
you ever imagined, Barry.
- So what happens now?
- The four of us
expand this place.
Use it to bring light to
everyone in the universe.
Together.
- Sounds like a new beginning.
- For all of us.
I hope.
- I never really
had a home.
But this sure feels like one.
- I guess I never had
a real family.
Might as well start somewhere.
- I always knew I'd make
the big leagues.
Ain't nothing bigger
than this.
- We're so proud of all
of you.
- Iris...
How can I ever apologize?
♪ ♪
- You don't have to.
- But you believed me.
Through everything.
Thank you for seeing
my humanity
long before I ever did.
And Barry...
Today you really were
my hero.
- [gasps]
- [chuckles]
- [softly] Hi.
- You feeling okay?
- Tired.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
But okay.
[gasps] Where's Jenna?
- With Rob and David Singh,
it's okay.
- [relieved sigh]
- Caitlin says
that you're gonna be fine.
- Yeah?
- Thank God.
♪ ♪
- What about the storm?
And Nora?
- Team Flash for the win.
Again.
- Okay.
What about you?
Have you been here
the whole time?
Doing what?
- Looking after the people
who...
Need me the most.
- [chuckles, mutters softly]
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- I need to take these powers
to the next level.
So, come the next apocalypse,
I can be more than
just a human glowstick.
- Ooh, you should yell
a cool catch phrase
before you fire your bad ass
energy beams.
Like, "flame on"!
- You are such a dork,
and I love you.
- Not as much as
I love you.
- Oh, that's actually
not possible.
Because my love knows
no cosmic bounds, so...
- Oh, yeah?
Well...
[upbeat music playing]
- Oh, it's like that, huh?
- [clears throat]
- Kamilla...
[giggles]
- So, I binged a whole
"Chopped" marathon last week.
- [snickers]
Nice, nice.
I built a pair of
electronic sock warmers
for Grandma Runk.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Oh, I got eyes on the back
of my head ♪
♪ Go on
and give it a try ♪
♪ I'm ready for you ♪
[phone buzzes]
- [clears throat]
What's up?
Is that Barry?
- Yeah, please tell me
there's another apocalypse.
- It's um...
It's nothing that can't
wait till tomorrow.
[sighs]
"Chopped," huh?
[playful music]
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
- [gasps]
Frost!
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
Are you a fugitive now?
Because of this jailbreak?
- Eh, slipped out
of Iron Heights
just like the rest of the
meta-wing during the storm.
- But...
W-Why would you do that?
After everything
you've been through?
- Yeah.
Get some much needed exercise.
To beat up and put away
a dozen meta-humans.
- And what about
your sentence?
- Oh, even the D.A.'s office
has a heart
when it sees you on the news,
saving lives.
That, and a good word
from the Flash.
And I got out on probation
for good behavior.
- That's incredible.
- What?
- Nothing, you just...
I don't know, you seem
different.
[soft, curious music]
What?
- Fine.
I have a crush on someone.
- Who?
- It's a bartender.
♪ ♪
[H.E.R.'s "Lights On"]
- ♪ It's dark outside ♪
- It's weird that Alexa, Deon,
and Bashir are just gone.
- Yeah.
Everything feels different,
it's like...
I don't know,
we lost a part of us.
- Is this what
it's gonna be like
when our actual kids
go to college?
♪ ♪
I mean...
We'd have to actually...
Try and, you know.
- ♪ Fluent in the sheets ♪
♪ Can you read
in between me? ♪
♪ I ain't a stranger ♪
Any who, makes you wonder.
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ So we can skip
the word play ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Leave the lights on ♪
- Yeah, it does.
- ♪ Leave the lights on ♪
♪ Leave 'em, leave 'em
lights on ♪
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Iris?
Where are you going?
- I'm tired of wondering.
Let's start a family.
- I love that impulse.
- [chuckles]
- ♪ On ♪
♪ On, on ♪
- Greg, move your head.