Hey, you hungry?
I was thinking blueberry pancakes
for breakfast this morning.
Or I could get us something fun
from that Brooklyn's Best Bagels place.
They just opened
a new location downtown.
Iris?
Iris.
Thanks for the company, Cecile.
Anytime.
You know, I figured you'd be
working this time of day.
Oh, I was.
Yeah, I'm actually avoiding
a new meta client,
so I figured I'd get out of the office,
come over,
see what Team Flash was up to.
Well, we're all good here. Yeah,
the town is quiet. No alerts, no crisis.
Just sweet, sweet, silence...
Okay.
Barry, what's wrong?
Yeah, should we be worried?
It's Iris.
She's missing.
Satellites aren't picking Iris up
anywhere in the city.
I'm gonna expand the physical
search radius.
Cecile, anything?
Nothing.
I can't sense her either and I've
reached out across a five-state radius.
It's like Iris' mind has just vanished.
Same here, only worse.
Barry, Iris isn't registering
anywhere on the planet.
How is that even possible?
It's just like last time.
She's not here anymore,
at least not in this plane of existence.
She must've had another attack.
Now she's lost in time.
Okay, well, then we need Deon
to find her.
No one's seen
Deon since he disappeared,
and I can't access
the Still Force without him.
Okay, so...
So what do we do?
Okay, okay, it's a long shot, but,
look, when Iris was in Coast City,
it wasn't just her time sickness
that caused her to vanish.
Tinya Wazzo's powers did, too.
I can't believe you're serious.
You really want to try
and bring Frost back?
And I already have a plan.
I'm going to repurpose Eva McCulloch's
R-CEM chip
to replicate Frost's cryo genes
so I can create a new body for her.
Caitlin, I know you're hurting,
so am I, but listen to yourself.
It worked before, it will work again.
And what about the thing
that makes Frost... Frost?
I have already identified her latent
empathic genes on my DNA.
I'm talking about a soul
and you give me brain waves?
I'm also going to extract
her active imprints from her own DNA.
Look, I've already got the sample.
Unfortunately, the keratin in the cells
is decaying a little too quickly, so...
I'm going to need a better sample.
Are you talking about grave-robbing?
It's called an exhumation and I am
a doctor as well as the next of kin.
So getting approval won't be a problem.
We just, we need to do it quickly.
I know how this sounds.
Oh, like that old horror movie
Frankenstein Created Woman?
Does Team Flash know
what you're planning?
Didn't think so.
They wouldn't understand.
Neither do I!
Caitlin, have you forgotten that
you literally just tried to resurrect
your dead husband?
And it was a complete disaster?
No, I haven't, but that thing
was never Ronnie, okay?
Deathstorm used a physical form
that I love to try and trick us.
Look, this is different.
The science is solid. Trust me.
Yeah, mad science.
Mark. Mark, Frost was supposed to live
a full and complete life.
You both were, together,
and now that's been taken from you.
Don't you want that back?
What do you think?
You can process losing Frost
in whatever way you need to,
but as far as
all of this is concerned...
count me out.
Tinya, uh, can we talk?
Why? I don't know you.
I'm Barry Allen.
You know my wife, Iris West-Allen.
I'm really sorry,
but she's missing again
- and I don't know...
- Again?
Whatever. I don't care.
Your other half ruined my life.
You have every right to be angry.
I need your help.
The first time Iris disappeared,
she was with you.
You mean when I wiped her
out of existence like she did to my mom?
Are you okay?
What the hell?
Mom?
What did you do to my mom?
Tinya, she never meant to hurt anyone.
Well, I did.
Which is why you should back off.
Do you even understand
how your powers work?
Examining how they work could help us
answer what's really happening to Iris.
I don't care about Iris.
God, what is wrong with you?
You know, I was fine until Iris found me
and started spewing all that crap
about family and having faith in people.
She made me believe that I could have
the life that I always wanted.
And now that's gone
and it's never coming back.
So welcome to the club.
Deon, thank God.
- Iris is missing.
- Yeah, I know.
Yeah, she's in the Still Force. I've
been trying to track her down, but...
Hey.
No, don't, don't.
I've been infected
by Iris' time sickness, too.
I need you to find the Isotopic Sensor.
It's the only way we can track down
that particle that I placed inside Iris.
"We"?
Barry, I can't find her alone.
I'm gonna need your help.
Okay, but the sensor's damaged.
We're going to need to repair it first.
Okay.
Okay, do it fast.
I'll come back for you after.
This is how we get Iris back.
So you're saying that Deon
wants to do that by bringing you
into the Still Force?
Well, both of us, together.
I thought he said it was too dangerous
for anyone to go in there who wasn't,
you know, a god.
It's risky, but I trust Deon.
And he wouldn't suggest this
if there was any other way.
Well, Deon's right about one thing.
Our satellites can't trace
isotopic particles
across other planes of existence.
That's why we need you
to repair the sensor.
It's the only thing that can locate
Iris' temporal particle
inside the Still Force,
but once we find her, we bring her home.
Amen to that.
Not to question a god,
but why would Deon need help
tracking a particle
that he created himself?
Deon's not at full strength.
Iris' time sickness
has affected him, too.
Chester, how long will it take
to get the sensor running?
An hour, maybe less,
but Barr, how are you going to
get inside the Still Force
in the first place?
Deon's going to come back for me
as soon as he can
and we need to be ready when he does.
And you ran this plan past
the other Forces?
Nora, Bashir, Alexa,
they're all on board, too?
Uh, no, I haven't been
able to contact them.
Any of them.
And Iris' sickness,
it could have spread to them already.
Which would explain why
they've been radio silent.
If that is the case,
then maybe we should all slow down
and figure it out before we launch you
into a place where
we know nothing about, Barry.
There's no time.
Look, Joe, Deon is our only chance
at finding Iris.
If he says going into the Still Force
is the answer, then I believe him.
I'm going to get the sensor
from the Starchives.
Meet you in your workshop.
I should get back to CCC.
Got to keep the lights on
until Iris is safe.
- Barr, hold up.
- What?
Look, I am willing to do
whatever it takes to bring Iris home,
but something don't feel right
about this.
It's dangerous,
but we've taken greater risks before.
Yes, we have,
but are you sure about the facts?
Because you seem to be putting
a whole lot of faith in Deon's plan.
Because I know it'll work.
That's what Deon thinks you should do.
What do you think you should do?
That's just it, I don't know.
And Deon does?
Look, Joe, I owe Deon this.
As soon as I learned
about Iris' time sickness,
I should have spent every waking moment
trying to find a cure.
Even when she told me to stop pushing,
but I didn't.
Now it's worse,
plus Deon's affected, too.
If there's a chance I can find Iris and
make up for all this, I have to take it.
- Parliament-Runkadelic.
- It's Captain Kramer.
Yes. Yes, ma'am. How can I help?
Chester, I need a full analysis
on an unknown device
we found at a crime scene.
You're not busy saving the world,
are you?
No, no, Captain, your timing is perfect.
Barry's gone to where no man's
been before,
so I'm free to fly solo.
Great. Thanks. I'll see you soon.
Oh, you heard her, Chester P.,
the crime-fighting world
needs your mojo!
Mojo...
Mojo.
Seven out of ten.
Oh, damn, moving through dimensions
is getting harder. Is that it?
Yeah, are you sure we can find her?
There's just one thing. Where we're
going, there's only one way in and out,
and it's a bumpy ride.
So hang on, because things
are about to get real weird.
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
I've been here before.
- When Iris...
- First got sick, yeah.
Place is like a doorway.
I call it my front porch.
I can see everything from here.
This place is different than before.
Yeah, that's because it's
more dangerous now.
Welcome to the Still Force.
What's left of it.
Sorry about the mess.
How bad is it?
Ever since Iris got lost here,
things have been mad disorganized.
I mean, night becomes day
in the blink of an eye
and just as fast, it's night again.
And now it's getting worse.
You see, past, present and future
all exist here simultaneously,
but now the balance is all out of whack.
See what I mean?
All right, now, stay close to me
because if we get separated...
I could get lost, too.
Or worse,
You could get trapped in a dead zone
where time just repeats itself
indefinitely.
If that happens,
I'd never get you out.
Sensor's picking up Iris' signature.
All right.
Let's ease on down the road, man.
- We're getting close.
- Yeah.
...my decision is not...
Oh, one thing, once we find Iris,
let me try and stabilize her first
before we do anything else.
They need to know
what you've been hiding.
- All right.
- Taylor, don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
I know those voices.
They need to know... They need
to know what you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't... Don't.
This is my life, my decision.
It's not what you think.
They need to know what...
You've been hiding.
Taylor, don't. Taylor, don't.
- This is my life, my decision.
- What is this?
They need to know...
Been hiding.
It's a future moment
that's stuck on repeat.
They need to know what you've
been hiding. They need to know...
They can't move onward and become
part of the past.
My decision.
It's not what you think.
They need to know
what you've been hiding.
Taylor, don't.
My life... My life, my decision.
This is... This is my life.
How do we stop it?
We can't, not till we find Iris
and fix this whole place.
Help me.
Someone, please help me.
Please, I don't know
what's happening to me
and I have to get back to my daughter.
Renee.
Renee Wazzo, you're Tinya's mom.
Yes, do you know where she is?
I have to find her before...
She's trapped in here, too,
just like Iris.
We have to find her again.
Tinya thought she'd lost her,
but if her mom's alive...
Uh-uh. She's fractured,
just like me and Iris, all right?
We need to stick to why we're here.
Deon, we have to help her. Renee
has been lost in all this for weeks.
Hey! What we need to do is keep moving
or else Iris is history.
She's the key to everything, man.
Iris is close.
I can feel it.
Hi, thanks for coming in.
Oh, always happy to tech consult
for Central City's finest.
Also, I am in love with the artwork
in here. Is it, uh...
Indigenous, yes.
It reminds me of home.
Nice.
So I'm guessing this is
our mystery machine.
There was an explosion at
a halfway house downtown this morning.
The fire department
secured this from the rubble.
Apparently it was attached
to the water heater.
Was anyone hurt?
Well, that's the strange part.
C.C.F.D. got a call about
an imminent explosion
and by the time they arrived on scene,
everyone had already been evacuated.
Then this released an energy wave
that took out the entire building.
Damn. Folks could have died.
How many people were living there?
Thirty-seven at the time. We got lucky.
Halfway house staff have no idea
who led the evacuation,
so this device is our only lead.
I need to know what it is,
what it does and who built it.
Well, I'm picking up traces
of radioactive particles.
This thing was packing serious
kinetic energy before it went kaboom.
Maybe it's some kind of...
Some kind of, like, EMP.
Whoa.
That's quantum coiling.
Captain, whoever built this
got mad skills.
Everything all right, Chester?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm as good as a hydrogen-phat sunrise
over Jupiter.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm just, I'm going to take this back to
my workshop and do a full diagnostic,
you know, just to make sure
that everything's totally cool.
If that's fine.
Of course, I'll authorize it.
Okay.
Runk, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
I'm five by five by the wayside.
Just gonna pack up my things.
Vanya's the Editor-in-Chief?
This can't be right. Where is she?
What?
Tracing that particle should have
led us right to her.
Yeah, I know, I know, just hold on.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Deon?
We needed that to find Iris.
Sorry, Barr.
Gotta bounce.
What the hell?
I'm back home again.
With no way out.
Shark Stadium erupted in cheers
after XS' heroic save,
even without Impulse,
her partner in crime-fighting,
who was too busy partying
to answer his alerts...
Ugh! You are so disgusting!
It is clear that XS is the most
daring speedster to appear in years.
Good afternoon, Nora West-Allen.
How can I assist you?
Gideon, I need another word
for "daring" that isn't too flowery.
Of course, I have found 27... 27...
Gideon?
Where'd you go?
Nora.
Nor.
Deon?
Is that you?
Barry's trapped.
I can't help him, but you can.
Well... Where?
How am I...
Uh...
Oh, schrap.
Iris, come on!
This brunch reservation
ain't gonna get any later.
Joe, don't worry,
I'll make sure we're on time.
You guys got
any resolutions for 2022?
I know mine.
More family time.
Holy schrap! Thank goodness
I found you, Dad!
Nora?
This place is messing with me.
Dad!
- Nora?
- Hi.
You're really here.
Oh, my God,
I'm a supervillain.
Seriously, that's what
you're worried about?
Okay, then where's your meta-hunting
dagger or your purple head fan?
No, I'm serious, okay?
I'm the bad guy in all of this.
No, you're not.
Oh, yeah, Allegra, the microchip that
I found inside that thing was hard-wired
with a one-of-a-kind energy converter
that I created.
But you didn't build this one.
So, so what?
I still went live with the designs
on my blog last month.
What is this, anyway?
It's a quantum coil transformer,
which means it's extremely powerful
and dangerous
if used for the wrong application.
You know what?
You were right.
You're right. I should have never
put my designs online.
And never will again.
Chuck, you're overreacting.
Should have vetted my online posse.
Your posse could be anyone,
but, Chuck, you inspire people.
You don't send them to the dark side.
Think about it.
You said there were no casualties
because the person that built this
evacuated the place before it detonated.
Does that sound like a supervillain
or his accomplice?
No, Allegra, but I...
Then, believe me when I tell you
we're missing the real story.
And you're one of the good ones.
So... have a little faith in yourself.
Dad, how are we supposed
to get out of here?
I don't know.
You shouldn't have followed me here.
You were safer in 2049.
But Deon told me you needed my help.
Deon?
Deon's the reason I'm stuck here.
I never should have trusted him.
I mean, you and Mom created Deon,
- of course you're going to trust him.
- I know.
Joe tried telling me something was off
and I didn't listen.
I was so focused on trying to find
your mom,
I ignored the signs.
She's counting on me and I,
I keep letting her down.
I want to tell you something.
I mean, you're going to find out
in a few decades anyways,
but you know how
the other Nora was a CSI
and was following in your footsteps?
Well, I kind of did the opposite.
I'm a reporter.
And even though I love it, I...
I'm just starting out.
And sometimes I'm, like,
"How does Mom even do this?"
I'm proud of you.
So you're not mad I didn't join C.C.P.D.
like you and Grandpa Joe?
Of course not.
I'm just...
I'm glad you found a path
that's right for you.
So, the thing is, is that I'm having
a really hard time
finding my voice as a reporter.
But Mom is teaching me
to have faith in myself,
and listen to my instincts.
And if she were here right now,
she'd tell you to do the same.
And that everyone loses faith
in themselves sometimes.
Even heroes.
But learning how to keep
believing in yourself,
when the whole world
is telling you the opposite,
that's what makes a hero.
You really are your mom's daughter.
Well, I'm yours, too.
Maybe it's our belief in each other
that keeps us connected
just as much as the other stuff.
You're right.
We are connected.
Not just to our family...
Me and Iris, to the Still Force.
It's like you said, we created it.
Nora, I heard your voice
before you got here.
I think somehow, just for a moment,
I connected to the future
before it became a part of the present.
Or the past.
You must already have a piece
of the Still Force inside you.
If I can figure out
how to connect to it again,
and control it this time,
I can get us out of here.
Okay, I'm ready.
Okay. Remember, whatever remnant
of stillness that's inside me
won't be there for long.
You look like Uncle Wally when he taught
Bart how to create lightning constructs.
This is also how Wally taught me how to
make contact with the other Forces.
Nothing's happening.
Focus on Mom's brush.
She still has it in the future.
You can use it as an anchor.
What in the world?
In the world...
Barry, Nora, what are you two doing
in my living room?
Grandpa Joe, you can see us?
Plain as day.
Only you're glowing
with some kind of green light.
Barry, I thought you were
in the Still Force with Deon.
Dad, whatever you're doing,
it must be working
because if Grandpa Joe can see us, too,
the present must be stabilizing.
Barry, can you hear me?
Barry!
Grandpa Joe's gone.
And so's the brush.
Dad, are you okay?
Nora, the temporal stream.
I can feel pure Still Force energy
moving through me.
I can see the past,
present and future all at once.
I can see Jesse and Harry.
Cisco and Frost, too.
I can see Bart's children.
Your wife.
Nora, you're all so happy.
I see...
Max?
I'm getting married?
Who's the lucky lady?
Actually, don't tell me.
I can already feel the spark
inside me fading.
Take my hand.
This feels seriously weird.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Where's the exit in this place?
Memorial Park. It's the only way
in and out of the Still Force.
Schrap! What the hell happened?
It's a temporal barrier.
We have to hit it with everything we got
while trying to phase through it.
We're caught in a temporal loop.
Dad, we're never gonna get out of here.
You see, the past, present and future
all exist here simultaneously.
Yes, we are.
This isn't a time loop.
It's the Still Force pulling us
back into the past
every time we're about to escape.
Well, why would it do that?
Deon said the past, present
and future all coexist here,
so if we've already escaped,
the only way to stop us...
Is to keep us stuck in the past.
Nora, use the spark I gave you
to focus on the moment
that's already on the other side
of that barrier.
The moment you and I get back home.
Focus on the moment
you and I get back home.
We get back home.
We get back home. Home.
Home.
Wait, so you're telling me that you were
able to get out of there
because you already knew you had?
I know, it's totally surreal, right?
Barry, is there still a spark of
the Still Force inside of you?
Because if that's the case, then maybe
we can use that to help find Iris.
Not anymore. I tried to tap
into it again as soon as we got back
and I must have used every bit I had
to get us out of there.
- We'll have to find Iris another way.
- And we will.
You know, guys, there's one thing
that I still don't quite get.
Barry, why would Deon
want to trap you in the past?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm really worried about him.
I better get back to 2049.
Make sure Mom's still there
and that she's okay.
I'm gonna miss you guys so much.
- We're going to miss you, too.
- Sweet one.
But you're right, we need you there
to keep our family's future safe.
Bye.
I miss her and Bart
more and more every day.
Yeah.
And my baby girl.
Joe, about earlier,
I should have listened to you.
You know, you were right
about everything.
It's okay. We all stumble.
I'm just glad you picked yourself up.
Look, there's something else.
When I was in the Still Force
and I tapped into a tiny bit of it,
I could feel Iris, almost see her.
It was like a...
A spark of stillness was
inside her, too, that I could sense.
What do you think it means?
I'm not sure, but somehow I know,
wherever she is right now,
she's okay.
"No problem. Just remember, you can
message me anytime you need help...
...with a project, day or night."
You're feeling better.
Yeah. Yeah. Hey, you were right.
Yeah, there was more to the story.
And once I started digging, I remembered
where I'd seen this circuitry before.
WookieLover77 posted this in
the comments of one of my live streams.
He was asking the Chester Posse
for tips on renewable energy.
- It was all an accident, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
WookieLover77 volunteers
at that halfway house.
He was just trying to provide
the residents
with unlimited hot water
from a clean source.
Someone's a believer again.
Thanks to you.
You're welcome.
So I was thinking, you know,
Marco's birthday drinks are in ten.
How about I buy you a root beer?
You know, to say thanks.
And I could use one myself, actually.
- I would love that.
- Yeah?
It's me. Open up.
Go away.
Sorry about that.
I think you're gonna want to hear
what I have to say.
What is wrong with you?
First you blow me off and now you
break into my home.
What? I should...
I should call the Flash?
Well, that's your choice.
Just like this one's mine.
I'm going to help you.
And don't worry,
I'll pay for a new lock.
Now, you want to know why
I changed my mind?
Because you were right.
Frost and I were just starting
to build a life together.
And thanks to her, I was finally
becoming the man that I didn't even know
I'd always wanted to be.
Losing her broke me,
but losing her twice...
that'd kill me.
That's...
that's why I was so afraid to help you.
So...
If we do this,
I need you to promise me one thing.
We won't fail.
We won't.
I promise.
Let's get to work.