My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
Cisco, if you don't seal off the blast, people
in this building will die, including Caitlin.
- Don't look for me again.
- Ronnie's alive.
And he's out there, alone and scared.
Hartley Rathaway. One of the finest
scientific minds I've ever encountered.
Can't imagine how
you're gonna feel when you let me out.
Why would I ever do that?
Because I know where Ronnie Raymond is.
Honey. Honey.
Dana. Oh, God. Someone...
- Help!
- Please help us.
- Help us, please!
Get the power to that line shut down.
You guys, lay down the hose line.
- Help! Help!
- Help us.
- We're wasting time.
- Help!
Hold on.
Stay here, all right?
I got you.
Hey.
No.
My wife!
Dana!
Everyone, back away.
How did...?
I love you.
Thank you, Flash.
Dude, that was insane.
I mean, even I'm having a hard time
getting mad at you for dirtying up my suit.
When are we gonna consider it my suit?
- I'd be comfortable calling it our suit.
- Okay. Our suit.
Tonight was the fastest you've ever run.
Yes, your training is paying off. That
couple is alive tonight because of you.
I can still get faster. I know I can.
And you will one day. But for today,
I'd say you fulfilled your saved quota.
Proper rest is what you need, as do we all.
Better yet, what we all need is
a proper drink. Who's up for a round?
Dude, it's movie night with Joe. I can't.
But I'll see you guys tomorrow, all right?
- Bye.
- Night.
What about you? Drinks on me?
I think I'll pass.
You okay?
I was looking for my tablet
at your workstation, and I found this.
You said we should stop looking for Ronnie,
so I didn't stop looking for Ronnie.
Why?
Hartley, he said he knew
what happened to Ronnie.
Hartley Rathaway?
Who is currently locked up...
in our villain jail for going psycho
with sound waves?
Yeah, he's made some poor choices.
No argument there.
- But I looked into what he was saying and...
- Cisco, Ronnie's gone.
And it's time for me
to move on with my life.
Doesn't seem like it.
What's that supposed to mean?
Look, I'm not an expert on love.
But I think in order to move on
from Ronnie...
you actually have to move on.
Breach, level two.
Hold it right there!
Shawna?
There she is. Get her.
- Crazy cool, right?
- How did you do that?
Grab my hand.
- How the hell, Shawna?
- So you like?
Oh, I love.
Whoo!
Hey.
The security cameras
in half the prison are shut down.
Then Clay Parker, according to this log, who
was locked in his cell, somehow vanishes.
Not completely.
- What's that?
- It's a kind of organic particulate residual.
I found it on the floor in here,
just outside the cell, out in the hallway.
The trail led me all the way outside.
Dad.
So word around here is
Parker pulled a Shawshank?
Yep. And none of the other prisoners
heard or saw anything.
They wouldn't talk to you about it.
Leaves us with not a lot to go on.
Well, if there's anyone who could figure out
how Parker got out of here, it's you, son.
- Come on, Allen. Let's go.
- Duty calls.
So my dad just happened to come by?
The guard owed me a favor.
Thank you.
Thanks for getting
me out of that hell hole.
You would have done the same, right?
So...
- how the hell did this happen to you?
- Don't know.
After you got locked up,
I started not feeling right.
I was passing out for no reason.
Waking up in odd places.
Took me a while before I could control it.
As soon as I could...
I came for you.
So you can just jump wherever you want?
If I can see where I'm going.
We got a second chance, Clay.
We can leave Central City.
Do all the things we talked about.
I can't leave yet, baby.
I owe Marcus a lot of money.
I skip town before paying him back,
he'll find us.
But with what you can do...
we can pay off that debt.
Then we'll be free
and we can go anywhere in the world.
Together.
Not even Barry's cells move this fast.
I've never seen anything like it.
So Clay Parker is a metahuman?
Not so fast. The particulate
residue that Barry gathered...
at Iron Heights does contain Clay
Parker's DNA but also DNA of a woman.
Run her DNA against the C.C.P.D.
criminal database. See if you get a match.
Yahtzee. Her name's Shawna Baez.
Mostly petty crimes,
and this girl likes to party, apparently.
A long list of disorderly conducts at bars.
So I'm guessing we find her,
we find Clay Parker.
- Barry?
- Yeah.
In the meantime, let's track
these particulates and see how they work.
I'll be right with you guys.
I have had the biggest
craving for Thai food.
You said you knew
what happened to Ronnie.
And how he was still alive.
And you said Professor Stein was at
S.T.A.R. Labs the night of the explosion.
Yes, he was.
Why?
The mystery isn't why Stein
went to S.T.A.R. Labs that night.
It's why he didn't leave.
- Tell me.
- Can't. Have to show you.
You are not getting out of this cell.
Fair enough. But I know you, Cisco.
I know how much you looked up to Ronnie.
He was like family.
The family you built for yourself here.
I know how much
you wanna see that family healed.
Let me help you.
I don't believe you.
I'm telling you the truth, Cisco.
When you are ready,
you know where to find me.
What's that smile about?
I saw my dad today.
No glass. No phones. Just me
and him face-to-face. Joe arranged it.
- That must have been amazing, Barry.
- Yeah. I really needed it.
I'm sure he needed it too.
Were you there investigating the breakout?
- Mm-hm.
- That is a big story which I am not a part of.
My editor wants me writing
about the Flash and only the Flash.
- Is that a bad thing?
- I don't know.
I would like to be thought of
as more than the Flash PR flack.
I mean, if I don't write something soon,
I think I might lose my job.
Hey, we will find you a great story
to write about. Together.
Okay? You know I'm always here for you.
I know.
I didn't know you enjoyed
a bit of rough trade.
If I'm gonna let you out,
I'm not taking any chances.
Curiosity's a maddening thing, is it not?
What do you mean,
you've been asking around?
Do you know a Marcus Stockheimer?
Sure. He's some midlevel gangster.
Works mainly on the south side.
Word is Clay Parker
was a runner for Marcus.
When Clay got pinched, Marcus lost a lot of
money. Marcus doesn't like losing money.
So Parker can't leave Central City
until he's paid off his debt?
From what I'm told, if you're a member
of the Stockheimer crew, you get out...
first thing you do is pay them a visit
or suffer the consequences.
All right. No more playing cop.
Promise me.
I hear you.
All right.
You were gonna show me what happened
to Ronnie. Ronnie died inside the building.
- What are we doing out here?
- What do you see?
I don't know.
Buildings. Walls. Dirt.
Wells would be so disappointed
in your observational skills. Look again.
It's Japanese.
How can you speak six languages
and sound like a dick in every one of them?
It means "bomb shadow."
They found these all over Hiroshima
after the first atomic bomb was dropped.
This shadow belonged to Martin Stein.
The accelerator explosion did this to him?
You really don't see it, do you? You're gonna
gonna kick yourself when you figure it out.
Oh, man. You were full of it then,
and you're full of it now.
This is another one of your lame tricks.
We're going back into the pipeline.
You're not the only one
who understands vibrations, Hartley.
Those cochlear devices you're wearing...
- I've made a few adjustments.
- No. Please, don't.
If you know how to find Ronnie,
then you better tell me. Right now.
Please. Make it stop.
Please. I'll show you. I'll show... Aah!
Try that again,
and I won't make it stop. Ever.
I'm impressed.
Didn't think you had that in you.
You have to take these off
if you want to find out the truth.
And why is that?
It will look a little conspicuous
where we're going next.
Mm. I was analyzing the particulates that
Clay Parker and Shawna Baez left behind.
I found something very interesting.
When Clay's cells come into contact
with Shawna's, they adopt her properties.
Something bothering you?
Why would you ask that?
You're doing that biting-your-lower-lip
thing you do when something's bothering you.
Ahem. I'm fine.
Okay.
Cisco says I don't have a life.
- You don't, do you?
- I do.
I cook and I eat.
And I read and I help you.
So, what you're saying is you do everything
that has nothing to do with having a life.
You don't have to be rude about it.
Ha, ha.
Hey, I'm not doing any better than you.
My social life consists of running
at superhuman speed and Netflix.
We are quite the pair, Mr. Allen.
Yes, we are, Dr. Snow.
There's an armed robbery in progress. Two
suspects. Male and female. In their 20s.
Sounds like our metahuman
Bonnie and Clyde are at it again.
Time to ruin their social life.
Just a few bags, baby.
Enough to pay back Marcus.
These things are heavier than they look.
Oh, I've read about you. You're the Flash.
I've heard you're real fast.
Let's see if it's true.
Catch me if you can.
I can. Unh!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Not too many men can keep up with me.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
This is a bullet wound.
You're lucky it just barely broke the skin.
Guess I'm a lot faster
than a speeding bullet.
Shawna Baez. She can teleport.
As in, "Beam me up, Shawna"?
Yes. Of course. Quantum entanglement.
The ability to manipulate interconnected
particles over an infinite distance.
Or as Einstein put it,
"Spooky action at a distance."
Every time I got close, she'd disappear.
It was like we were playing a game of...
Peek-a-Boo. Come on, can't I name one?
How can I catch her
if I don't know where she's gonna be?
Everybody has limits, Mr. Allen.
Now that we know Shawna's powers...
we'll focus on those limits.
All right. Let me know.
I'm gonna change. I gotta go help Iris.
- Hey, Barry.
- Hey, Eddie.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I thought I'd see if you wanted help
writing your story.
That is so sweet. I would love to, but we're
going to dinner with Eddie's mom tonight.
- And we're late.
- Can we do it another time?
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- Great.
- All right.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Hey.
- What bars did Shawna and Clay frequent?
Uh, mostly south-side dive bars. Why?
I was just gonna check them out.
See if they fall into any old habits.
It's a good idea. I'll join you.
Everyone's wonderin'
Will you come out tonight?
Everyone's trying to get it right.
Get it right.
Hey.
What?
What? Nothing. Uh, you look...
really nice.
I don't always dress
like a high school principal.
So this is where Shawna Baez
and Clay Parker used to hang out.
It is, according to the files.
I thought we could kill two birds
with one stone.
Look for them
and get ourselves back out there.
You want a piece of my heart?
I keep making the same mistake.
Every time Iris falls,
I race to pick her up, thinking...
that one of these times,
things are gonna change.
But things are never gonna change.
I am just destined to be just a friend.
You're not pining for someone who burst
into flames and wants nothing of you.
What is wrong with us? We're in our 20s.
We should be having fun.
We should meet people. Go on lots of dates.
Well, here's to liquid courage.
Uh... That is very fast.
- You drank all of it.
- Excuse me.
I would like to start a tab.
Okay.
C.C.P.D. confiscated everything
from S.T.A.R. Labs after the explosion.
Video. Audio. Traffic-cam footage.
Okay. So?
I saw Martin Stein the night S.T.A.R. Labs
went boom. He walked right past me.
You see, Stein
specialized in transmutation.
Molecular transmography.
Quantum splicing.
Taking two things and making them one.
Let's go to the videotape, shall we?
Okay, stop.
Now zoom in a few clicks.
Now advance it frame by frame.
His eyes.
They turned to white just like Ronnie's.
Now stop. There. In the mass of energy.
- Looks like...
- Ronnie.
And Professor Stein.
The dark matter merged them together.
Explains why Ronnie hasn't
seemed quite himself lately.
It's because he's not.
He's Martin Stein.
You can't say I didn't keep up
my end of the bargain.
I figure that makes us even-steven.
Adios.
Uh, excuse me. Could I get some water?
- Yo. Excuse me. For real?
- Mr. Barry Allen!
Come on down.
Or up. Come up here with me.
Oh, come show them what you got.
Come on.
Barry. Barry. Barry.
Look at him go. He's so fast. Ooh, shh.
I'm not much of a singer.
And you're not much of a drinker.
We are gonna bring this place down.
Okay. Just... Good girl.
Get ready.
Summer lovin' Had me a blast.
Summer lovin' Happened so fast
I met a girl crazy for me
I met a boy cute as can be.
Summer days driftin' away.
To, uh, oh, those summer nights.
Well-a, well-a, well-a, unh.
You're fast and you can sing?
What can't you do?
Stop you from drinking, apparently.
I'm not even sure that was mine.
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- Okay.
All right. Can I close out my tab, please?
Hey, Stevie. Can my friend here tap out?
Sure thing, Linda.
Uh, thank you, Linda.
You're welcome, Barry.
How do you know my name?
Barry. Barry. Barry.
Yeah. Uh, sorry about us up there.
Are you kidding?
No, that was some of the best singing
that I've heard come from that stage.
You definitely made my ears happy.
Don't worry.
Thanks.
So, uh, was that your girlfriend up there?
Oh, uh, no. No. She's a friend.
Okay.
Reel me in so our love can begin again.
Hey, have you heard of this new phone app?
It's so cool.
Check it out. You just touch
someone's phone with your phone...
and it downloads your contact info.
Wow. That is cool.
See? You have my number.
What you do with it now is up to you.
Okay.
- Barry, I don't feel good.
- Yeah?
Okay. Come on.
You okay?
It's 80 grand. What I owe.
So are we square now?
Almost.
Heh, heh, oh.
Holy crap.
Glad you're impressed.
So are we cool now?
Absolutely. Couldn't be cooler.
Which is why I think we need
to keep working together.
With what I know and what you could do...
oh, we could be
looking at a very lucrative future.
Police. Everybody down.
No. Baby. Oh, no.
Hold it right there.
Damn.
Are we still running?
No, we are here.
Ugh. Vodka and super speed.
Not a good combination.
Ha, ha. Come on.
So are you gonna call her?
Who?
That girl.
The one who gave you her number.
I hadn't really thought about it.
Yes, you have.
But I know you. You won't.
You'll let her slip
right through your fingers...
because you think
you don't deserve happiness.
But what you don't realize is you need
a little saving too.
Little help, please.
Yeah. Okay.
There you go again.
Saving me from that evil dress.
Get in bed.
Did you sneak a peek at my goods?
Heh. I wouldn't be much of a hero if I did.
Yeah, but it's okay if you peeked a little.
You deserve a peek
for all the good stuff you do.
Drink lots of water.
Thank you for tonight.
I sang.
Anytime.
Hey, Barry?
Will you stay with me until I fall asleep?
Sure. Yeah.
Hi.
So loud.
Oh.
I just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
Let's just say I envy
your inability to get drunk.
I don't remember much from last night.
Yeah. That's probably for the best.
Summer lovin'
- Oh, God. That I do remember.
- Ha-ha-ha.
What's wrong?
Cisco has something he needs to tell you.
- Hartley's gone.
- He escaped from the pipeline?
How is that even possible?
I let him out.
Are you mad?
I can't tell with those glasses on.
I'd like to yell and wave my arms,
but I'm afraid I'd throw up.
Why? What were you thinking?
You know how dangerous he is.
Hartley said he knew
what happened to Ronnie.
I told you to let it go.
I didn't want you looking into that for me.
I wasn't doing it for you. I...
I sealed Ronnie into the accelerator
before it blew.
He told me to wait two minutes.
And I waited, but he didn't come back.
And I can't stop thinking, 10...
20 seconds...
and Ronnie
wouldn't be like he is right now.
I've wanted to tell you so many times.
I'm so sorry.
So you carried that around
this whole time?
Do you know what Ronnie
would say if he was here?
He would say that you did the right thing.
It wasn't your fault. What happened
that night wasn't anybody's fault.
Come on.
Don't we have a teleporter to catch?
We do have a teleporter to catch.
And fortunately,
we do have a promising theory.
Take a look at this.
Now, this is the normal behavior
of the particulate that Shawna left behind.
Watch what happens
when we remove light.
Shawna can only become entangled
with something she can see.
- Take away her ability to do that...
- She can't teleport.
Exactly.
So we just need to get her into a
dark space. How do we do that?
- It's a valid question.
- Hello?
What?
Yeah, I'll be right there. All right.
What's wrong?
My dad. He's been stabbed.
Dad, what happened?
A rather stern reminder, I'd say, not to
poke around Marcus Stockheimer's business.
Dad, I told you to stop.
Your dad called me with more intel.
It helped us track down
Clay and Shawna and arrest Stockheimer.
I managed to screw up
Marcus' big heist too so...
You two kept working together
and didn't tell me?
It isn't his fault. I did it to help you.
You getting stabbed and beaten
is not helping me.
Look, I don't get to feel useful
very much in here.
So if I can help you for a change,
I'm gonna want to be there for you.
Just like you've been there
for me all these years.
Yeah.
You said Marcus
had a big heist coming up?
Mm.
- Do you know anything else about it?
- Dad. Tell me who did this to you.
- It doesn't matter, slugger.
- You said you wanted to, so help me.
One of Marcus' boys.
Julius.
Okay.
What the hell?
Evening, Julius.
- How'd I get out here?
- You escaped.
When they catch me trying to escape,
they're gonna add five years to my sentence.
Ten, actually.
Unless you tell me where
Marcus Stockheimer's next job is gonna be.
Whoa.
Guards will be here any second.
I'd start blabbing.
Okay.
It's a TDK money transfer truck coming
from the federal reserve bank in St. Louis.
Supposed to be millions.
Delivery's around 8.
- That's all I know. I swear.
- That's right now.
Got eyes on him.
Hey! Hey, what about me?
I think we got company.
What the...?
Okay.
Let's go.
I got this.
Why the hell do you care what we do?
Are you a cop or something?
Something.
Come on.
Barry, remember. She cannot teleport if
she cannot see. Limit her field of vision.
No.
He left me.
There any way she can teleport out of this?
It's impossible. It's one-way glass.
It's mirrored on the inside.
No one dangerous is ever
gonna get out of this thing again.
Shawna.
Clay left you.
He's out there and you're in here.
You know what the crazy thing is?
I still love him.
Cisco.
Crazy is right.
Some people are worth being crazy for.
I'm sorry if I was a bit of a drunken mess
the other night.
- Actually, it was pretty fun.
- Yeah, it was.
You know what?
I think everybody's been right
about you and me.
Both of us have been hung up
on people for way too long.
If what Cisco says is true...
that Ronnie merged with Martin Stein...
then he's not alive anymore.
Time for me to move on.
Find someone new to be crazy about.
- All right. Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yes. Sure.
- Bye.
That's for you.
I thought maybe you could
help me out if you're willing.
This is about the breakout at Iron Heights.
Clay Parker. He's still on the loose.
And we need to catch him.
Why are you giving this to me?
Because you're a good reporter.
And the only one I know.
You're not the only one who's fast.
- Hey, what're you doing here?
- Hey.
You came to check on me.
That is really sweet...
- but I think everything's gonna be okay.
- I'm glad.
- I actually am not here to see you.
- No?
No. I have a lunch date.
- With who?
- Uh...
- Ready.
- Hey.
Oh, hey. You're our new stringer, right?
- Yeah.
- I'm Linda Park. Sports.
Iris West.
How did you two meet?
- It's actually a funny story.
- I'll tell you later.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- See you.
- Have fun.
So an actual date this time. Good for you.
You didn't tell her
your dad's in the slammer?
No. I read in a magazine
that that's a big turnoff.
Smart.
Hey, did you see this?
No. I haven't.
The Flash.
I saw him once in here.
Watched him save Joe's life.
Joe told me about that.
I guess he was lucky.
Hmm.
Lucky Joe.
Strangest thing.
I get roughed by up Julius, end up in here.
Next thing I know, Julius is caught trying
to escape. Claims the Flash broke him out.
Won't be seeing Julius for a long time now.
Guess I'm lucky too, huh?
Dad.
If I was the Flash...
don't you think that you'd be the first
to know about it?
Yeah.
Well, if the Flash were my son,
I'd tell him a few things.
First off, I'd tell him
it's a dangerous world, so be careful.
Then I'd tell him he's a hero.
And he's saving a lot of lives.
But the most important thing
for him to know, I feel...
is that his father's proud of him.
Power grid's been going haywire
in this sector.
This system's so antiquated.
What was that?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::