("You Got It All to Give"
playing)
♪ They had to raise us up
to listen ♪
♪ I had to pray to God
they'd see ♪
♪ If you stand your ground ♪
♪ Ain't gonna hold you down ♪
♪ 'Cause you got it all
to give ♪
♪ Baby, you got it all to give ♪
♪ Oh, ooh... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Baby, you got it all
to give. ♪
- (click)
- (music stops)
Obviously, a lot of it's temp.
I love it.
If we're airing on TLC
between My 600-lb Life
and Little People, Big World.
But we're not.
'Cause we're not
cheap reality garbage.
Sorry, Courtenay,
I thought, um...
I-I was trying to go for
something a bit more personable,
- down-to-earth.
- Not this down-to-earth.
I need them to look like
someone you'd want in the Army.
We here are not
fucking Heidi and Spencer.
We are The Seven, James.
And why isn't there anything
on Starlight?
She actually hasn't really made
herself available to the crew.
Where the hell is she?
Has a heavenly body
lost her luster?
Two weeks after
Starlight's shocking appearance
at the Believe Expo...
Social media is still buzzing
about her controversial speech.
Was it a breakdown
- or a triumph?
- Of course,
my thoughts are with Starlight,
and, uh,
I support her in every way.
What I want to know,
who's that dude
that stuck his (bleep)
in her face?
She should (bleep) that
(bleep)er in the (bleep)hole.
O-kay.
Of everything that I said,
that's what they focus on.
Hey. Eye of the tiger.
You and me, we have
a Panera gift card to win.
- No distractions. Come on.
- EMCEE: Ah, good one here.
Before joining The Seven,
which hero led
a search-and-rescue team...
- Mm...
- Oh, my God. -...after the 1994
Northridge earthquake?
Isn't it your job
to know this kind of stuff?
Eh...
- It's Lamplighter.
- Thank you.
Yeah, I had
all the trading cards.
Of course you did.
- (chuckles)
- ANTHONY: Hughie?
- Hey.
- Where the hell have you been?
After Gary's store,
we all thought that...
Oh. H-Hi.
Uh, Anthony.
Hughie's best-looking friend
since fourth grade.
(chuckles)
Hi, I'm Annie.
It's nice to meet you.
You look familiar.
- Did you go to Kennedy?
- She's, uh,
- new in town.- Mm-hmm.
- Fantastic.
So, what are we drinking,
New-to-Town Annie?
Mmm.
So, uh, Gretchen Scaramucci...
- No, no. (groans)
- ...she was bigger
than all the guys. Like,
André the Giant-big.
So when Gretchen says
she wants to beat
the living fuck out of this guy
for making a crack
about her girlfriend...
- Oh, you didn't.
- ...Hughie gives her
this Clint Eastwood stare,
like... (grunts)
- (laughs)
- And then, bam, runs,
like Forrest Gump-runs,
five blocks down
into a pet store
where he hides behind
this jumbo bag
of Kibbles 'n Bits
for four hours.
STARLIGHT:
Oh...
I'll be right back.
(laughing)
WOMAN:
I know it! I know this!
(Anthony exhales)
Surprised to run
into you here, man.
Yeah. Same goes for you.
I've been worried, asshole.
Ever since Robin, you...
you weren't answering
your phone.
Like, for all I knew,
you were chugging Drano.
I'm sorry, man.
Yeah, you should be.
No, really,
I-I should've called.
You think?
I'm okay.
Really. I-I just...
n-needed a fresh start.
Fresh start?
(chuckles)
Your fresh start
is way out of your league.
Um, you know that, right?
I am aware, yes.
(chuckles)
Annie's great, man.
Live your life.
That's what Robin would want.
(bells dinging)
- WOMAN: Sync mark.
- (beep)
MAN:
We're good.
- You rolling?
- WOMAN: And... action.
My grandfather built this place
with his bare hands.
He was, uh, an amazing man.
Oh, the old piano.
Every night, Mom would sit here
and she would play some songs
and...
I got to be honest, most of the
time, me and my dad would be...
we'd be making model planes.
I can almost smell
the... silver paint.
(sighs)
I really wish
he'd lived long enough
to see me fly
with the Blue Angels.
That would have blown his mind.
That's me in the middle.
(chuckles)
Love you, Mom, Dad.
(tapping)
Welcome to my bedroom.
The Baseball Hall of Fame,
you might call it.
Hasn't changed a bit.
Oh, there they are, the Tigers.
It's my little team.
I played shortstop.
Of course,
I couldn't show
everything I had.
But... let's just say we, uh...
we-we did a lot of winning.
(chuckles)
This is just, um...
Really just, uh...
It's so special to come back.
Hmm.
Uh, I'm sorry,
why is that there?
PRODUCER:
Sorry?
Who put the fucking blanket
on the bed?
Uh, R-Randy Set-Dec, I think.
Who's Randy Set-Dec?
He's-he's over there.
Randy, why?
You fucking asshole.
- Uh...
- Amateur fuck.
What just happened?
("Big Shot"
by Billy Joel playing)
Samaritan's Embrace,
led by Ezekiel
but bankrolled by Vought,
has been shipping Compound V
to 53 hospitals
across the country
since 1971
and gift wrapping it...
(exhales)
...gift wrapping it
- as polio vaccine.
- Are you telling me
God's not reaching up the twats
of American girls
and blessing babies?
Butcher, can you leave God out
of this?
H-Hold on, hold on.
So, no hero was born?
None of them? They're all just
kids dosed with the blue shit.
I mean, even...
Even fucking Starlight.
Do you think...
do you think they know...
what really happened to 'em?
What about Homelander?
Homelander's a black hole.
Never had any public records
and never will.
However,
every single other Supe...
juiced-up lab rats.
My God.
I'm trying to give
a tremendous fucking TED Talk
here, and this...
Frenchie,
can you control her, please?
I do not control her.
(scoffs)
Do you see
what I'm dealing with?
Well, spot on, M.M.
We got Vought for child
endangerment, drug trafficking,
and possibly the largest fraud
in American fucking history.
Raynor's gonna love it.
MOTHER'S MILK:
You better hope she does...
(continues indistinctly)
Uh, hi.
- (snarls)
- FRENCHIE: Hughie, no!
(clicking tongue)
No, no, no.
Not if you're attached
to that hand, no.
It's okay. Yeah.
Well, you know,
all of this, uh, it's...
But it's only part
of the story, no?
I mean, what about
our petite Lazarus here?
She's not an infant.
And she was injected
in a basement, not a hospital.
And there is the small matter
of that she rose from the dead.
Well, your feral pixie dream
girl ain't exactly dictating
her fucking memoirs,
is she, Frenchie?
I'm feeling
she's trying to communicate.
I mean,
she's been doing this for...
Maybe that means something, huh?
Yeah, maybe they're
just fucking chicken scratches.
Let's find out.
Nah, you've been burned.
It's not safe out there for you.
M.M.'s right. You got
to fucking stay put, son.
(scoffs)
Fantastique.
- All right, I'm off.
- HUGHIE: Okay.
I'll just, uh,
keep on Starlight then, right?
Her phone's been tits-up
for a week.
You wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
No.
But I can, uh... I can check.
All right.
You're with me.
- He is?
- I am?
What, to the CIA lady?
No. We're gonna go
on a little detour.
- You'll love it.
- (patting)
Come on.
ASHLEY: No, I have
been working with her!
I've been fucking working
with her! I can't believe this.
Who the fuck are you gonna get
to replace me?
I'd like to see
what bitch that is!
You okay?
(chuckles ruefully)
(exhales)
You know that pledge
you mentor during rush week
because she seems sweet
and a little naive
and she doesn't know
she's not supposed to wear UGGs?
(chuckles)
And then, once she's active,
she stabs you in the back,
gets you kicked out
of the house?
(scoffs)
- I'm sorry. I don't...
- It was
my big idea to book you
for the Believe Expo.
What could go wrong, I thought.
You were playing to your base.
At least I don't have to kiss
your ass anymore.
(knocking)
Come in.
Thank you for coming, Starlight.
You fired Ashley?
It was actually
a mutual decision.
She wanted to explore
different career paths,
and, um, we wished her well.
So, I would like you
to take this
in the constructive spirit
that it is intended.
Okay.
You are a selfish,
arrogant child.
Wow.
Back in Iowa,
I bet you watched a lot
of Queen Maeve's movies, right?
I did.
She was a rebel.
Didn't take anyone's shit,
didn't play by the rules.
That's what you wanted to be.
That's what American heroes are.
But it's a myth.
I should know,
because I wrote it.
The truth is,
dozens of people in this company
spent hundreds of hours
to create the thing that is you.
I never asked for that.
Then why don't you burn
the sparkly outfit
and become a cop?
You want to be a superhero.
You want to be famous.
But nobody's famous alone.
So, why don't you cut
the petulant diva shit,
show a little fucking gratitude,
and let us do our job?
No.
I'm sorry.
I mean,
I don't mean to be ungrateful.
But... no red carpets,
no reality TV,
and no Noxzema commercials.
And I want my old uniform back.
I'm gonna save people.
Then I think
we may need to reconsider
your position in The Seven.
And I think
that firing an employee
after she reported
sexual assault on live TV
might tank your stock price.
(sighs) Well, I hope
we can count on your discretion.
I'm sorry,
I don't do discretion anymore.
If anyone asks me who did it,
I'm gonna answer honestly.
Well, I think it's great
that you want to tell the truth.
I just don't know
to whom you're referring.
Oh, I think you know.
I think you've known
for a long time.
Thank you so much for coming,
Starlight.
I have a lot to think about.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(glass breaking)
Okay.
I mean, you take
Tek-Knight's Knightracer?
Had a carbon footprint
the size of a 727.
The thing literally shot fire.
Thanks to me,
now he drives a hybrid.
That's what the Green Crusader
initiative is all about.
To respect what's, what's
beautiful in the world.
- What's up?
- Hi.
So... everything.
(sighs) So beautiful.
COURTENAY:
Good. Let's reset.
Trash back on the beach, please.
Background, put the trash back
on the beach.
All right.
Um, well, we lost my dad
at a young age,
and my mom, she worked two jobs,
so, it was, uh, my older brother
Nathan who,
who pretty much raised me up.
And when I was three, it's like
these guys started shooting
in front of my building
and I outran the damn bullet.
(laughs)
That's kinda how
I figured out...
Can I, can I stop you
right there for a second?
What if we ixnay
the gun violence?
Maybe make it
a click more upbeat?
(laughs)
Yeah, yeah.
NATHAN: All right, little bro,
I know you're the fastest man
in the world and all that,
but your work ain't done.
Set. Go.
♪ Ring the alarm... ♪
Nope. You're off, bro.
Go again.
Go.
Nope. Go.
No.
No?
What is going on with you, man?
(exhales)
Here comes the A-Train! (grunts)
COURTENAY:
Hey, you knew Popclaw, right?
What? I don't, uh...
COURTENAY: You guys were
in Teenage Kix together?
You, you heard
she passed away, yeah?
Yeah, they're,
they're saying it was a stroke,
but between you and me,
I think it was probably
a drug overdose.
You want to maybe say
a little something in her honor?
I haven't seen her in years,
so, you know...
(elevator bell chimes)
Boy, you're really milking
this thing for all it's worth.
- Excuse me?
- This empowerment act.
I mean, every time
I'm on a red carpet now,
they're asking me
how I'm supporting Starlight.
But, hey, as long
as you're trending, right?
I know that you might not
get this,
but it's not an act.
I'm just trying to be honest.
Okay. Yeah.
When I was younger,
I read your autobiography so
many times that I wore it out.
I had to buy a second one.
I wanted to live my life
exactly like yours.
Because you didn't just break
all the bones
in your right arm
stopping that school bus
from falling off of a bridge,
but you also went to every kid's
physical therapy afterwards.
Just to show the world
that they were heroes, too.
You really stood for something.
(elevator bell chimes)
But now...
I'm pretty sure that was just
written by the marketing guys.
MAN (on TV):
...hunting for his own food.
When fully mature, this immense
predator of the sea
can reach sizes
of up to 25 feet in length
and over 4,000 pounds.
They can reach speeds
of up to 35 miles per hour...
Mon coeur.
Would you like me to change it?
Incroyable.
You talked to me.
- She talked to me.
- That's talking?
Well, she communicated anyway.
- She likes Shark Week, huh?
- I'll call BuzzFeed.
I wonder if she lived
by the water.
You know, you can't fool me.
Who is she? What does she want?
Why is she here?
She could be the key to it all.
- That's what you think, huh?
- No, that's not what I think.
Yes, you do. It torments you.
It's okay.
Listen, I got one word for you.
It's a surefire way
to solve this puzzle.
Once and for all.
Tell me.
Mesmer.
Mesmer?
You want help from a Supe?
He despise Vought, hates them,
hates the other Supes.
And the enemy of your enemy...
Frenchie, what part of "you're
burned" do you not understand?
Oh, come on. It's a quick trip.
She and I will hide in the van.
Let's go. In, out, boom, bing.
Boom, bing? Look, I'll tell you
what I can do.
I can... possibly
tattoo "fuck no" on your ass.
Ah, come on.
Best I can do.
You know...
I've seen you eat ice cream.
- Oh, my God.
- Chunky Monkey, I believe.
- Where is this going?
- Well, you know,
you take a spoonful...
a chunk of fudge, perhaps.
But then I see you
with the surface is uneven.
So what do you do?
You take another scoop,
you try to even it out,
which, tragically,
creates a corresponding divot.
Ultimately, there is only
but one choice for you, no?
To consume the entire pint.
No, you don't want to,
you don't want to.
But you must.
And I tell you why, my friend,
because you cannot bear things
out of order.
And she...
...she's out of order.
All right. You want to tell me
where we're going?
You don't do it anymore.
- What?
- You know that feeling you get
when you tip your chair back
too far,
and you catch yourself
just before you fall?
Yeah?
You used to look like that
all day long.
- (laughs)
- But now look at you,
neck-deep in shit,
cool as a cucumber.
You ain't half the twat
I thought you were, Hughie.
You know, you're always calling
people "cunts" or "twats."
But I just... I never really got
how that's an insult?
They're flexible,
take a pounding,
and they're
the reason behind, like,
98% of my life decisions.
BUTCHER:
You're doing good, Hughie.
And you're a good cunt.
Well, here we are.
Church?
Seek and ye shall find, me son.
Come on.
SHEILA:
Uh, some days are harder
than others, obviously, uh...
You know, the other day,
I-I wanted to talk to my friend
about all this, but I couldn't.
That's why this group
is-is so great.
It's so important.
I know it's wrong
to feel angry.
After all, Tek-Knight saved me.
I-I just wish he'd been
a-a little more gentle
with my spine.
LYDIA:
It's about acceptance, isn't it?
Letting go. Moving on.
Seth, you're up.
(Seth clears throat)
Hey... (clears throat)
Hey, everybody.
OTHERS:
Hey, Seth.
Uh, so I'm kind of a writer.
Uh, I work in marketing.
Uh, there's this one hero,
who shall remain nameless,
but has ice powers.
Ice Princess.
I'm not allowed to say.
Anyway, she, uh,
took a liking to me.
It was heady, man.
Intoxicating.
No one wants to fuck the writer.
Needless to say,
I fell for her, big-time.
(whispering): What kind
of nobber falls for a Supe?
SETH: Anyway, we were, uh,
you know, being intimate,
when she climaxed and
accidentally turned into ice.
Just for a second,
but I was, uh,
still in there,
at negative 346 degrees.
Same temperature
as liquid nitrogen.
As you can imagine, um...
...it snapped off.
(participants gasp)
The crazy thing is,
I still miss her.
It's like, that's the cost
of a mortal like me
for being with a god like her.
If a Supe done that
when she was happy,
imagine what one would do
if she found out
you'd been lying to her
from the get-go?
LYDIA:
Excuse me.
You have something
you'd like to share?
No, no. A-Apologies.
Please do, uh,
continue the Ice Capades.
LYDIA: We don't make
jokes or judgments here.
Why don't you take the talking
stick and tell us your story?
Nah, I'm good.
You know, I've seen guys
like you before.
Oh, I seriously doubt that.
The smirk, the jokes,
it's all a defense mechanism.
But you don't have
to do that here.
This is a safe space.
I said I'm good.
Time to move on.
Go ahead, Seth.
Give him the stick.
(participants gasp)
You, back off,
or I'll shove this stick
where your dick used to be.
You're a bunch of pathetic
Supe-worshipping cunts.
I bet you'd thank a Supe if they
shat on your mum's best china.
Did it ever occur to you
that they split your spine
or broke your dick
just for a laugh?
Where's your fucking rage?!
Your self-respect?!
Sitting here
in your little share circle.
Having a little whinge
and a moan.
Fuck "letting go."
You should be out there
with a fucking chain saw,
going after 'em!
Just a bunch of scared
fucking rabbits.
(stick clatters)
Supes are all the same.
Every fucking one of 'em.
(door opens and closes)
Uh, he's, um...
Sorry.
Oh, Ms. Stillwell, hey,
you wanted to see me, right?
Yeah, I'm running late.
Can you walk with me?
DEEP: Yeah, sure. Hey, look,
I brought a little present
- for your little guy.
- Ah.
Never, uh, too young to start
saving the world, right?
I'm gonna need you
to make a public apology.
And you're going to be taking
a sabbatical from The Seven.
- What?
- We are going to be stationing you
in Sandusky, Ohio for a while.
Okay, okay, look, I-I know,
I know, I know my brain wasn't
in the right place,
but, but my heart was.
And it's just that,
that damn Oceanland.
- They wouldn't let me...
- This is not about the dead dolphin.
This is about Starlight.
Starlight?
What are you... (chuckles)
What about Starlight?
Everybody seems to want to know
who she was referencing
in that speech,
and it is not going away.
It's only a matter of time
before she, or, let's be honest,
some of the other women,
speak up.
- So we need to get ahead of it.
- Okay.
There may have been
a misunderstanding, I know that,
but can't you just...
you know, handle it?
Like, like you do?
This is the way
we are handling things now.
I'm in full support of women
and their ongoing bravery
in speaking out.
(sighs)
(clears throat) I'm sorry...
let me start that over.
I'm in full support of women
and their ongoing bravery...
Fuck, I'm sorry.
Yeah, let's just cut.
I'm sorry.
MAN:
Scene take two. Alpha mark.
Starlight,
I hope you can forgive me.
- Harder to sell.
- To sell it. Yeah.
- Just a little harder.
- Perfect. Let's do that.
Speaking out.
We can all become stronger...
by listening. Okay.
I realize that my behavior
has caused Starlight
a great deal of pain,
and I sincerely apologize
for this.
Though at the time I believed
that our encounter
was consensual,
I now realize that, um,
I misread the moment...
Our new movie, Insurrection,
it's really exciting.
It's my first, uh, movie
with the, uh...
in the Vought Cinematic
Universe, uh, the VCU.
NARRATOR:
New York. The hearts
of seven million men and women
beat inside this city.
But there's only one person
who can see inside their hearts
and read their minds.
This man is the rapist.
(siren wailing)
There are no secrets from me.
(indistinct chatter)
("Fame" by Irene Cara playing)
♪ Baby, look at me ♪
♪ And tell me what you see ♪
♪ You ain't seen
the best of me yet... ♪
♪ Give me time,
I'll make you forget the rest ♪
♪ I got more in me ♪
♪ And you can set it free ♪
♪ I can catch
the moon in my hand ♪
♪ Don't you know who I am? ♪
- ♪ Remember my name ♪
- ♪ Fame... ♪
Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Okay.
"There are no secrets from me."
- There are no secrets from me.
Hey.
What number am I thinking of?
867?
Fucking amazing.
This guy's fucking amazing.
So, what am I thinking of?
I'm thinking the same thing.
Cool. (chuckles)
- Now, why don't I put this down.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Cool.
- Thank-thank you.
- Yeah.
- Mr. Mesmer.
- Ah, just-just Mesmer.
No "mister" necessary.
- You know, I'm a big fan, man.
- Thanks.
- Weren't you in Teenage Kix with A-Train?
- Yep.
Yeah. Yo, A-Train's
really blown up, hasn't he?
- Yeah.
- He's doing his thing.
Yeah, he's great.
I'm-I'm really happy for him.
- Yeah.
You a fan of the show?
Oh, nah, man.
I've never seen it.
- Okay.
- You know what I'm a fan of?
Your insider trading.
(exhales)
The way you brushed your hand
up against that Wall Street guy?
Brother, that shit right there,
now, that was ruthless.
I mean, Vought dropped you
like a hot potato afterwards,
which I think is some bullshit,
but with the SEC coming...
Who the fuck are you?
Why don't you take a peep
and see?
How do you know about Cleo?
There are no secrets from me.
Well, I work for Child Services.
My colleague Tina,
she owes me a favor.
See, she, just like I,
believe in second chances.
Cut the shit.
I lost custody three years ago.
Nobody believes
in second chances
for fuckups like me.
(panting)
(exhales)
She's waiting on you.
Tina. Hey.
- TINA: Hi.
- MOTHER'S MILK: It's good to see you.
TINA:
Good to see you, too.
Five minutes.
Next time you owe me.
MOTHER'S MILK:
I do.
Hey, Cleo.
(sniffles)
You remember your old man?
Hi, Charles.
I'm-I'm sorry that, uh...
I'm gonna try and be
in your life a little bit more.
Would that be okay?
I guess.
TINA:
Okay, Cleo.
We got to get back.
- Bye.
- Hey, uh...
I-I just...
I just want to know
you don't hate me.
I don't really know you.
Hey, wait, um...
So you can know me
a little better.
I don't have a DVD player.
Bye.
Thanks again.
I'll call you next week.
Okay. You all right?
(sniffling)
I can see her every month?
One hour, supervised.
You clean?
- I-I can be.
- Good.
Who do you want me to read?
What are we doing here?
My wife, Becca,
used to hum the Spice Girls.
Drove me round the fucking bend,
you know.
All day long,
walking around the house,
humming.
She was happy.
Now, fuck know why
she was happy with me, but...
she was happy.
Homelander raped her.
Jesus.
I-I'm sorry.
Not long after that,
she came and sat right here.
I know this
'cause she got tagged
in that security camera
right there.
She sat here for three hours.
Didn't move a muscle.
Then she just got up
and walked away.
That was eight years ago.
And nobody's seen her since.
Either Homelander killed her
or she killed herself.
Same difference.
You see,
I know what it's like
to lose someone.
You and me,
we're in this together.
For Robin...
and Becca.
That is why
you can't allow yourself
to be distracted
by another bird.
Especially not a Supe.
Just remember...
...who your friends
and who your enemies are.
(sniffles)
That is gonna kill somebody
when it lands in Boston.
Look, I heard what happened.
I am so, so sorry.
What kind of place
did you grow up in?
Well, I moved around a lot,
so, uh, it was
a bunch of condos.
So, what if I took you
to a house
you'd never seen before,
full of photos
of parents you never met,
toys you never played with,
Hardy Boy books
that you never read?
And then I asked you
how much all that fake
fucking bullshit meant to you?
How would that make you feel?
I wouldn't like that.
I'm really sorry
about the blanket.
It never should have been there,
and Randy Set-Dec
has already been terminated.
But right now...
we need to finish that tour
and to show how down-to-earth
and ready to serve you are.
And I need you
to tell the mother story.
Please.
Please do it for me.
(exhales)
It was actually my mom
who dragged me along
to my first
Little League practice,
and, uh, pretty soon after that,
I-I just loved the game
more than anything else
in the world.
So every year
she would bake me
a birthday cake
in the shape
of a baseball diamond.
And... oh, I got to tell you,
it was perfect.
Perfect.
Everything, down to
the last minute details.
Just like her.
MAN:
Cut. Perfect. So great.
- So we're done?
- Uh, yes.
Great.
MESMER:
So...
she can't talk or won't talk?
That's what
you're gonna tell us.
Anything in particular
you want to know?
- Everything there is to know.
- Well, that narrows it down.
Mon coeur.
Will you come?
Have a seat.
It's okay. Have a seat.
Gentle.
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
(takes deep breath)
(Mesmer sighs)
(gasps softly)
(grunts)
- (screams) Jesus fucking...
- MOTHER'S MILK: Goddamn it.
- Relax!
- No.
Everyone relax!
- Just-just go walk it off.
- Walk it off?
She broke my fucking wrist!
She didn't intend any harm.
Oh, could have fooled me.
Get out!
I'm going to the hospital.
Not till we get
what we came for, Mesmer.
- Fuck you! The session's over!
- Sit down!
(panting, sobbing)
Okay, listen.
- I was a field medic.
- (groans)
Don't look at her.
Look at me.
I can patch you up better
than any of those
oxy junkies in the E.R.,
or I can break your other wrist.
You decide.
(crying)
Good. Now, do you have
any bandages or a splint?
No, I don't have
a goddamn splint!
(ringtone playing
"Ride of the Valkyries")
- (panting)
- It's Butcher.
(whispers):
Be quiet.
- Butcher.
- Where are you?
Shake Shack.
Really?
Fucking magic, that place.
- What'd you get?
- ShackBurger,
uh, cheese fries,
- cookie dough concrete.
- Sounds good.
Does it taste like lies?
I got your phone linked
to my
Find-Your-Shithead-Friends app.
Now, where the fuck are you?
♪ ♪
Yes, this...
this is a superhero.
- This is good.
- Okay.
- We just keep...?
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, people are
always asking me, you know,
what it's like to live
with my coworkers, and...
the truth is,
we're all great friends,
you know, behind the scenes
just as much as we are to the...
uh...
Oh, hey, Elena.
- Hey.
- This is my friend.
I left a pile of messages for...
Yeah, that's what we are.
We're friends.
Can you ask them
to turn that off, please?
I'm gonna need
five minutes, okay?
(indistinct conversation)
Yeah, we're, uh,
doing a reality show.
- That's invasive.
- What are you even doing here?
MAEVE: I would never
turn up to your work.
- I was worried about you.
- I had a bad night.
This Teflon shit, it might work
for everybody else,
- but not with me.
- Will you keep your voice down?
Just tell me what's going on.
Did you ever think that, um...
...maybe I was just looking
for a hookup?
I know you think you know me...
- I used to.
- Yeah, used to. I've changed.
Yeah.
I still know you.
- Oh, come on.
- Afraid to be seen with me.
Afraid to ask for help.
Just... afraid.
Are you filming, Courtenay?
I told you to turn
the fucking cameras off!
We cut... we cut a while ago.
We're setting up a shot
for later.
- MAEVE: Fucking bitch.
- B-roll on the building.
All right, you can cut it, guys.
FRENCHIE:
It's okay.
Everything is okay.
(knocking)
(sighs)
Gentlemen.
Wow. Mesmer.
Hello.
Big fan.
Be with you in a minute.
(quietly):
Well, now we got to kill him.
No, we don't have to kill him.
Look, we made a deal
with the guy.
If he keeps his trap shut,
he gets to see his kid.
He's just a dad with his kid.
He's a fucking Supe with a kid.
What the fuck were you thinking,
coming here?
- You know better than that.
- Sometimes you get further
with people
by treating them like people.
BUTCHER:
Nice decor.
'80s serial killer.
Love it.
All right, then,
let's get cracking.
There's a camp in a...
in a jungle.
(indistinct voices in distance)
She's a soldier.
There's a-a flag
with a two-headed snake on it.
Two-headed snake?
Like...?
Yeah.
- With red rays behind it?
- What does that mean?
It's the flag of the
Shining Light Liberation Army.
Frenchie...
you're dating a terrorist.
Is this true?
(indistinct chatter,
birds chirping)
(takes deep breath)
♪ ♪
(laughing)
Ah.
(man chuckles)
FRENCHIE: There must be
more to all of this.
She can't be a terrorist.
Yeah, well, you just fucking
keep her under control.
Okay, so they smuggle in
a top-shelf extremist recruit
and pump her up with Compound V.
And then,
when she's good and ready,
they cut her loose
to wreak havoc.
- She wouldn't.
- HUGHIE: Wait.
Why would Vought give
Compound V to terrorists?
'Cause the only thing
more dangerous than a terrorist
is a Supe terrorist,
and the only way to fight it...
Is with Sergeant
Fucking Homelander.
Got to let the cunts
in the army now.
Those fuckers are creating
super villains.
And maybe there's more of 'em,
God knows how many.
Holy shit.
Okay, this is a clusterfuck,
even for us.
No, listen to me, okay? Maybe
that's what they want her to be.
But that's not who she is.
- That's not what she wants.
- And you know this
'cause she bends
your fucking ear off?
She saved my life!
She's not bad.
She just want to go home.
She's a fucking Supe,
just like the rest.
How many times do I have
to fucking say it, eh?
Mon coeur,
I know you understand me.
Please. Please.
Tell them who you are.
Tell them what I see.
No.
(sniffling, panting quietly)
(breath trembling)
The drawings are, uh,
palm trees in front of the moon.
It's where she grew up.
- (automatic gunfire)
- (woman screams)
(man shouts indistinctly)
They killed her parents.
They kidnapped her
and her brother.
Forced them to be soldiers.
(indistinct chatter)
(automatic gunfire in distance)
No, Kimiko...
You eat it.
She just wants to go back and
get her brother out of there.
Her name's Kimiko.
Kimiko.
Bonjour, Kimiko.
(Butcher sighs)
All right, take her back
to the safe house.
MOTHER'S MILK: Where you headed?
I'm gonna go see Raynor.
We've got more than enough
to get the Feds on board now.
You tell anyone what you saw
or heard here today,
and I'll cut your hands off and
shove 'em so far up your ass,
your fingers'll give us a little
wave out your throat, yeah?
Fuck off, wanker.
(door opens)
(TV news music plays)
NEWSMAN:
Some controversial news today
as the Deep went public
with his apology.
DEEP:
I realize that my behavior
caused Starlight
a great deal of pain,
and I sincerely apologize.
WOMAN:
Fuck you, fish dick!
(tires squeal)
Keep speaking your truth!
DEEP:
I'm in full support of women
and their ongoing bravery...
BUTCHER:
Never got the point of these.
To me, they always looked
like Granddad's bollocks
flopping in the wind.
Do you have
the Compound V or not?
I've got the Compound V...
proof that Vought's injected
babies right across the country,
and... something
even more fucking diabolical.
Worse than dosing babies?
Let's just say,
with these cunts,
there ain't no rock bottom.
Let's get it to the lab...
Not so fast.
(clicks tongue)
First things first, eh?
A list of your demands.
How in character.
Exorbitant salary.
Same for your team.
Office space,
in the Flatiron Building,
no less.
Security clearance.
Indemnity clause.
Legal protection.
A formal guarantee that
Homelander will be prosecuted
under the full extent
of the law.
Any of that a problem?
No, gonna pass it up the chain.
And, uh, while they hash it out,
you and I go forward
on good faith.
(Butcher chuckles)
I'm fresh out of good faith.
Now, you and I both know
that you can rubber-stamp
all of that.
So what's it gonna be...
Deputy Director?
I can give you...
everything you want
on this list...
Except?
Except Homelander.
You know what he's done.
(sighs)
I sympathize.
I really do.
- But it's suicide.
- Yeah, well,
- that's a small fucking price to pay, isn't it?
- Not for you.
For thousands of people
if you push him too hard.
You're fucking scared.
I'm fucking terrified.
And you should be, too.
Butcher!
(sighs)
NARRATOR:
This small-town girl-next-door
wanted to change the world.
STARLIGHT:
Since when did hopeful
and naive become
the same thing?
NARRATOR:
But the world had other plans.
DEEP:
Starlight,
I hope you can forgive me.
NARRATOR:
Battered and beaten,
a phoenix rose from the ashes
with a message so loud,
so raw, it couldn't come forth
as anything less than a roar.
Witness her power.
Hear her truth.
And I'm done taking
any more shit.
NARRATOR:
Watch her stand up
and fight back for all of us.
Citizen Starlight,
coming this fall from Vought.
- ♪ You're gonna hear me roar. ♪
- The house always wins.
I'm sorry.
MAN (on TV):
While little is known about...
(continues indistinctly)
...the blacktip reef sharks
can be found mating
in the summer months
off the coast
of Northern Australia.
I know you want
to go back to your brother.
But the people
who did this to you...
you know, they might be doing it
to others.
We can use your help
stopping them.
(TV playing in background)
(sighs)
It's your choice.
You give me a nod, and we go
to the airport right now.
MAN (on TV):
And is following her closely
in hopes of securing a mate.
When the female returns
his feelings,
she will swim slowly
in a sinusoidal pattern...
MOTHER'S MILK:
No.
Baby, why you want
to do me like that?
'Cause if you watch that episode
of Downton Abbey,
- then I'm gonna be one behind...
- (door opens)
and we're not gonna be able
to binge-watch together.
- (door closes)
- Just-just hold off
until I get home.
Uhp, there's a fight
in the yard, baby.
I got to go. All right.
How'd it go with Raynor?
BUTCHER:
No dice.
What?
BUTCHER:
Said she got cold feet.
Well, why?
Did you tell her everything?
Yeah, I laid it all out,
even the sample of V.
Said she couldn't
fucking authorize
that kind of action
against Vought.
Too much of a risk.
Hmm. Did she?
Fucking spineless cunt.
So we are royally fucked.
No, we ain't.
Fuck 'em.
We don't need 'em.
We got everyone and everything
we need right here in this room.
We'll take down Vought
ourselves. Yeah?
Yeah.
Where's Hughie?
- (panting)
- (line ringing)
TINA:
This is Tina Mitchell,
Department of Child Protection
and Permanency.
- Leave a message.
- (beep)
Tina, um, it's Mesmer.
You met me earlier.
(panting)
Um...
Cleo, uh, didn't really
want to see me today.
She was just being polite.
I'm pretty good at reading stuff
like that, so...
Um, you-you don't have
to-to call me,
um, or any of that anymore.
Just, um... it's-it's okay.
Just... just... please...
uh, look after her.
Thank you.
(panting)
I'm sorry.
The, uh, elevator was out.
Um, you...
you probably don't remember,
but, um, we've met before.
Oh, I...
I would never try and read you.
Let's be clear.
I don't know you,
and I don't want to.
A-Train said
that you have some information.
Yeah, we, um... we go back
to the Teenage Kix days.
- We-we still keep in touch.
- Oh, golly gee shucks.
What makes you think I would
give two fucks about that?
Now, do you have something
for me or not?
MESMER:
Yeah.
He said you were looking
for a, um, French guy...
and a black guy...
a skinny white guy,
British guy.
Where are these from?
Shitty little $85 camera
I put in my doorbell casing.
I know there's no reward,
but I was hoping
you could put in a word for me
at Vought?
I'll take any posting.
Uh, low five-figures
would be fine.
I just want to be one
of the good guys again.
(whooshing)
Oh, that's my phone.
- (crowd chatter)
- (music playing)
STARLIGHT:
I mean, I don't remember,
but my mom said
that when I was born,
I almost blinded the doctor.
So, I had powers from the start.
Why?
No, no, I'm just, uh, curious.
Mm.
Do you mind if we just...
not talk
about hero stuff tonight?
Yeah, yeah. Bad day at work?
Yeah. It's an understatement.
You know,
there's this beach
in the Bahamas
where the sand is pink,
like, cotton-candy pink.
What's it called?
Pink Sands.
(both laugh)
It's not
the most creative name,
but... let's just go.
Yeah. No, I can, uh...
learn how to play
the steel drum.
You can get cornrows.
How about tonight?
Book that ticket.
Are...
are we talking about this?
I don't know. I...
I just know that,
for me, New York has been such
an endless shit show.
Except for you.
Somehow, in the middle
of it all...
...you found me.
BUTCHER:
Hughie.
I thought that was you.
Ha. Oh.
Oh, I apologize.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
No. (chuckles)
Hi, I'm Annie.
Billy. Old mate of Hughie's.
Ah, boy, you really...
You have a lot of friends
showing up here.
Yeah.
Seems like it.
You're that new girl
in The Seven, ain't you?
Guilty.
Wow. It is a pleasure
to meet you.
And I must say
how marvelous it is
that so many more women are
in positions of power.
- You know what I mean?
- Mm.
You know,
i-if I'm perfectly honest,
Translucent's always been
my favorite.
What's he up to?
I think he's on a mission.
BUTCHER: Huh. Yeah, I think
I read that, actually.
He's been gone a long time,
though, hasn't he?
I do hope he's all right.
You know what?
I'm gonna go...
get us a pitcher.
- Ah.
- Billy, you like...
Let me guess.
Guinness?
- I like what you like.
- (both laugh)
All right. Be right back.
- Well, well, well.
- Butcher...
She's quite tasty
up close and personal.
- I get what you see in her.
- That wasn't what...
I thought
we had an understanding.
We do. We do.
- It... It's not what...
- Not what it looks like?
'Cause from where I'm sitting,
it looks like
you've got your tongue halfway
down the opposition's throat.
She is not the opposition.
She's a good person, okay?
I mean, she could help us.
- Help us?
- Yeah.
And what do you think
she's gonna do
when she finds out
you murdered Translucent?
When she finds out?
Give her my best.
("Big Shot" by Billy Joel
playing)
Where'd your friend go?
♪ Because you had to be
a big shot, didn't you? ♪
♪ You had
to open up your mouth ♪
♪ You had to be a big shot,
didn't you? ♪
♪ All your friends
were so knocked out ♪
♪ You had to have the last word,
last night ♪
♪ You know
what everything's about ♪
♪ You had to have
a white hot spotlight ♪
♪ You had to be a big shot
last night ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ And they were all impressed
with your Halston dress ♪
♪ And the people
that you knew at Elaine's ♪
♪ And the story
of your latest success ♪
♪ Kept 'em so entertained ♪
♪ Oh, but now
you just don't remember ♪
♪ All the things you said ♪
♪ And you're not sure
that you want to know ♪
♪ I'll give you one hint,
honey ♪
♪ You sure did put on a show ♪
♪ Yes, yes, you had to be
a big shot, didn't you? ♪
♪ You had to prove it
to the crowd ♪
♪ You had to be a big shot,
didn't you? ♪
♪ All your friends
were so knocked out ♪
♪ You had to have the last word,
last night ♪
♪ So much fun to be around ♪
♪ You had to have
the front page, bold type ♪
♪ You had to be a big shot
last night, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh,
whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa-oh. ♪