How do you feel?
Wait! Wait, no!
A little dizzy, but otherwise,
I think I'm okay.
Welcome to the team, Kamilla.
Your creation was unplanned,
but I know you'll make
a useful addition.
- Where's my counterpart?
- She's no longer a problem.
Now, I don't have much time
before Iris realizes I'm gone.
So, listen to me. This is important.
Six years ago, I created a device
capable of converting light into energy.
I called it a Prismatic Refractor.
It looked like this.
I need you to retrieve it for me.
- It's beautiful.
- That's a replica.
I made it here in the Mirrorverse,
but my R-CEM rejected it.
I... I believe it needs the original
in order to function.
What's the R-CEM?
A thing that will ensure the success
of my long-term plans.
Where do we start?
My husband, Joseph, he...
underestimated the value
of the Refractor
and sold it to Mercury Labs
a few months ago.
Find a way in.
Replace the replica out with
the original and you bring it to me.
- Do not let me down.
- Success is assured.
I've officially hacked every quantum
kinematic database on the planet.
You know what I found out
about artificial Speed Forces?
Thawne built one.
And... that's it.
And I doubt he's gonna tell us,
seeing how he's Linda Blaired
our pal Nash,
and, you know, he, kind of,
wants to murder the hell out of us.
If Thawne can figure it out,
then so can we.
In the meantime, we need to make sure
the Flash doesn't lose his powers.
- Yeah.
- The Speed Force may be gone,
but there's still a residual amount
of speed left in your DNA.
Until we figure out how much,
we need to manage your speed output.
How do we do that?
I call it the Speed Gauge.
It will measure the intensity
of the velocity you're using by color.
So, right now, it's black.
That's neutral.
Means you're not using any speed at all.
If you're using a minimal amount,
that's green.
The yellow is next, then orange
and obviously,
red is the maximum amount.
At this point, I don't recommend
operating beyond green.
And we're not just talking
about running, okay?
- Speed thinking...
- Speed healing.
...Flashtime. All of these things
could deplete your meta-abilities.
- You have to be careful.
- Guys, it's not that simple.
I mean,
I'm supposed to keep the city safe.
Team Flash!
It's your pal, Nash.
- Let me out!
- Guys, are we sure that's Nash?
Or Thawne playing possum?
Let's find out.
I hear you got an update for me
on the Carver RICO investigation?
Just sifting through the paperwork,
I found evidence of multiple cover-ups.
Homicides being filed as accidents,
missing person cases
buried by falsified paperwork...
And every victim...
has one thing in common.
You think Carver has a mole
inside C.C.P.D.?
Somebody has been helping him
evade criminal charges.
The question is, why?
This is outstanding work, Joe.
But investigating a mole,
that's a job for Internal Affairs,
not for us.
We can't trust IA or anybody
until we find out who Carver's bought.
I mean...
Barry agrees.
- Hold on. Flash has seen these files?
- Yeah.
Joe, this is not meta-related business.
Is there a chance
that this is becoming personal?
I mean, I would totally understand,
given what Carver's done to Iris.
This is still about bringing
a criminal to justice.
And we will.
But, Joe,
this is your first year as captain.
If your people think you suspect
one of them of being a mole
and you're wrong...
Have a look.
So, this Thawne...
Got the red eyes and vibrates, but...
he's also a Wells.
Yeah, that's him.
- How did you...
- I've been seeing a lot of Wells lately.
I mean...
Up here. A lot.
I don't know how many there are, but...
The Wizard Wells, annoying.
French Wells.
New York City Wells.
Actually, he's all right. And then...
- Harry Wells.
- Nash...
Harry's dead.
They're all dead.
Hey, guys. I think you should see this.
Let's go. Let... Come on!
- Let me out.
- So, at first glance,
Nash's brainwaves seem totally normal.
No anomalies or inconsistencies.
But when I take a look at them in 3D,
it appears that
there are multiple brainwaves
intricately tangled together.
When the multi-verse collapsed
in Crisis,
all of the Wellses must have channeled
into the only surviving doppelganger.
Multiple psyches camped out
in Nash's brain.
It's like Tyler Durden times a thousand.
Tyler Durden, great reference.
- First rule of Fight Club is...
- Hey, can we not talk about Fight Club?
Yeah, that's it. So how many Wells
are we talking about here?
How many universes were there
in the multi-verse?
What?
Yeah, wait... No.
This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, Thawne wasn't even a real Wells.
He killed Harrison Wells, took over
his body and fooled us for months.
This is the psychopath
we're talking about
that is trying to take over my body.
Let's get him out before he resurfaces.
Come on!
I mean, there is no medical procedure
or device
that could separate brainwaves.
Not on this stupid Earth,
there's not, but hello...
Multi-versal traveler, anyone, right?
I have a neuro-splicer here, in my bag.
Can you... can you get it, please?
Will work just fine.
Actually helped me out to stop
an invasion
of psychic starfish on Earth-26.
In the little... Yeah, that's it.
That was not pretty, although...
To be honest,
I don't know if the splicer can
separate thousands of brainwaves
all at once.
It will be, if we supercharge it
with the EMP from your gauntlet.
Yes.
Yes, the gauntlet, yes.
Just make sure
that when you charge the EMP,
that it's 1,500 volts per meter.
Otherwise, you risk...
I know. I know. Otherwise,
- I'll fry the circuitry.
- You'll fry the circuitry.
- I got it.
- Cisco, wait.
That was Thawne the whole time?
He couldn't have gotten far.
He doesn't have his powers,
so he can't time travel.
Yes, he can.
Look at us, Flash.
Two peas in a pod, just two speedsters
frustrated by the limits of their speed.
I'm nothing like you.
No, I'm the one
who's gonna get his speed back,
and when I do...
When I gain control of this body,
when I reconnect to my Speed Force,
you...
You're gonna be too weak
to stop me, aren't you?
Just like you were powerless
to save...
your daughter.
I miss my Little Runner.
Nora was never yours!
Do it. Do it.
I wonder, how much speed will you
have left after I'm gone?
Barry, no!
He tricked us.
Again.
Should've known supercharging the EMP
would cause a recoil loop.
Thawne always has a backup plan.
I checked the footage.
Thawne only went to the Starchives,
nowhere else.
How's Nash?
Better, now that
you're not trying to kill him.
Were you really going to do it?
- I don't know.
- Nash needs help,
not maiming.
You can't be here, Barry.
Why not?
Because your Speed Gauge registered
a massive loss of speed,
which means, not only does
using your powers affect it,
but so does your anger.
Caitlin, I'll be fine, all right?
And if I need more speed,
I'll use a booster like Velocity-X.
Oh, great. So, you're just gonna start
taking speed steroids now?
Barry, every test we've run
says that physiologically,
you have changed drastically.
So, we have no idea
what Velocity-X would do to you.
It could hurt you,
it could hurt others...
Other people are already hurt.
I mean, we have no idea
what Thawne is doing to Nash right now.
And he could do even more damage to you,
if he gets under your skin again.
Look, I know this is hard for you.
But you need to leave.
You can't trust yourself around him.
What you mean is,
you can't trust me around him.
Okay. Got your message about Thawne,
so I brought holy water,
uh, garlic, wooden stake,
salt, obviously,
and Ouija board.
- Cecile!
- What?
It's an exorcism.
It's not like we can be too prepared.
This isn't some kind
of vampire demon.
This is...
- This is something else.
- Oh, my God.
Everything that Nash is feeling inside
is still just...
raw hatred.
What we think of as Thawne
is actually just a series
of negative tachyons inside Nash's body.
So we gotta hit him
with positive tachyons
to force Thawne out.
That's why we need the PTD,
or the "Positive Tachyon Device,"
and not a Ouija board, no offense.
Okay, so...
- what do you need me for?
- You're gonna be my "Thawne Detector."
I need you to psychically monitor Nash
and tell me when he's free
from Thawne's influence.
You think you can handle that?
After what Thawne did
to the people that we love?
- Hell, yeah.
- Then it's time for an exorcism.
Worshipping a plant.
People are idiots.
Hey. Hey! Kid.
How did you get in here?
How did you get past my...
security drone?
All right. Who are you?
- What's your name?
- It's Maya.
You actually got it.
No one's ever pulled the Blood Bloom
out of the Wollip's mouth before.
Yeah, right. Well, the "Wollip," kid,
is just a statue rigged by the locals,
that's all.
I know.
You do?
You gonna get the treasure
out of the Bloom?
Yeah, I'm gonna...
get the treasure out of the Bloom.
What...
- You mean the crystals?
- No, I mean the treasure...
- What treasure?
- ...inside.
I don't know if they're...
Hey, hey, hey! Oh!
This?
It's worth three times more
than those dumb crystals.
I'm impressed, kid.
But...
you broke one of the rules.
You see, you never give anybody anything
unless you get something in return.
Nice hat.
Now, scram.
And when you tell your parents
where you got the hat from,
make sure you tell 'em you earned it.
I don't have parents.
Not anymore.
Maya.
How'd you like to do what I do?
What's that?
Mythbusting.
Archeological mythbusting.
That's what all this is for.
You like the sound of that?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think you'll be good at it.
Now, rule number one...
The prize is everything.
Are you gonna remember that?
The prize is everything. Easy-peasy.
Cisco, Nash is hurting.
What's happening?
I'm not sure.
It's my first exorcism.
Welcome to Hell.
I can't be here.
Too late.
All the pain that's being brought up
in Nash, it's overwhelming him. It's...
That's how Thawne gains his strength.
He feeds on that pain.
Then he's feasting on Nash.
From what we've heard
at The Citizen,
Mercury Labs is making
massive developments in clean energy.
We are and Dr. McGee is thrilled
to speak to you about it.
If you'll wait right here,
I'll go grab her.
- Thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
Is this the place?
According to my readings,
the Prismatic Refractor is...
here.
Nice.
- Another light-based meta?
- Must be one of Carver's.
Which means he's after
the Refractor, too.
We gotta get out of here.
But the Refractor... Eva said...
No, don't worry.
We'll let the Flash handle this one.
It's a meta robbery at Mercury Labs.
- Okay, I'll meet you there.
- No, Frost and I can handle this.
You need to stay here
and conserve your speed.
Doctor's orders.
- But, Caitlin, I...
- Doctor's orders.
- Put that down.
- Not happening.
Fine. Have it your way.
So,
you're the ice queen, huh?
What do they call you?
Call me...
Sunshine.
Ice versus sun. Guess who melts?
Flash? I said I had this handled.
Don't worry. This won't take long.
Flash, no!
Dr. Light sends her regards.
- Frost!
- Word around Black Hole is,
you're quite the badass.
You could've been one of us.
Freeze!
Frost.
You okay? Come on.
So, we're looking at not one or two,
but three Black Hole light assassins.
All of them are under Carver's payroll.
Each one more powerful than the last.
Sunshine reopened Frost's wound
from Dr. Light's photon bullet.
Her ice healing's working overtime.
This is my fault. If I had just listened
to Caitlin and stayed behind...
Hey.
You had a glitch in
your speed back there, didn't you?
I used Velocity-X to boost my powers,
but my body rejected it.
Caitlin warned me it could happen.
Look, I know
you don't like taking a backseat,
but until you can manage
your powers, Barry...
I know, I have to be more careful.
Do we know anything about Sunshine?
Only that she can disappear in sunlight
and melt steel.
Her name is Millie Rawlins.
Kamilla took a photo
before we got out of Mercury Labs.
We ran it through S.T.A.R. Labs
facial recognition and got a hit
at the Department of Defense's database.
Ex-military, special ops.
She, uh, was transferred
to the covert division
after the particle accelerator explosion
left her with the meta-ability
to bend sunlight.
Her call sign was "Sunshine."
- Do we know what she was after?
- Yup.
Mercury Labs says it's a one-of-a-kind,
advanced energy converter.
It used to be owned
by McCulloch Technologies.
They're calling it
a Prismatic Refractor.
Carver was stealing
his own technology? Why?
We don't know why yet, but...
I'm glad you two are okay.
Iris...
Oh, um...
Sorry, babe, my reporter brain...
- I'm glad you're okay.
- Yeah.
Shouldn't that thing be at C.C.P.D.
in evidence lockup?
Well, if Carver's trying to get this,
we can't risk his mole gaining access.
I put in a call to A.R.G.U.S.
Until they have it in their custody,
I'm not letting it out of my sight.
Well, we... we could keep it here
at S.T.A.R. Labs for the time being.
If Sunshine is as ruthless
as Dr. Light and Ultraviolet,
then she's coming
after that Refractor again.
And if she shows up at S.T.A.R. Labs,
the Flash isn't going
to be able to do anything to stop her.
Let A.R.G.U.S. take it.
Barry is right
about Sunshine.
What if she strikes
during the transfer to A.R.G.U.S.?
Let me worry about that.
Go see after your husband.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course, I was just about to.
You wanna get away?
I just needed a place to think.
Look, I know losing your speed is...
scary,
especially with Thawne showing up.
But, Barry, the man that I love
would not let limits
keep him from doing what he does best...
Taking down metas and protecting people.
The Flash isn't supposed
to have limits, Iris.
Look, if Thawne gets his powers back,
I won't be able to stop him.
Just like I can't stop Sunshine.
Well, maybe the Flash
can't stop them, but...
Barry Allen can.
I mean, so what the Flash can't run
as fast as he used to?
Barry Allen was taking down villains
long before the Flash came along.
Barry, you are just as much of a hero
as the Flash.
That's why the city gave you
the Medal of Honor.
I mean, are you really gonna let
C.C.P.D. handle Sunshine by themselves?
I don't see how I can help them
without my speed.
Barry, it's like,
you're stuck on this idea
that the Flash is supposed to be
limitless, but...
metas are the ones that have limits.
I mean, think about it. Where would
the Ringmaster be without his rings?
Or Cicada without that dagger?
Even Reverse-Flash and Sunshine,
they have their limits.
You just have to figure out
what they are.
You're right.
Sunshine does have limits.
I have to find Joe.
Hey, Kamilla.
I know where the Refractor's going.
Get ready to move fast.
Why are you keeping me here?
I went through your memories, Nash.
I plumbed your depths.
Came up with this little gem.
It's awful.
Isn't it? It's dark.
It's negative.
Nash!
- Nash!
- Maya.
Quite the overachiever. Right?
Perfect employee. A real go-getter.
When she went to go get
the sonic emitter
on the top of the highest peak
of Corto Maltese. Remember that?
And plucked that,
so determined to get the emitter.
Because, after all...
the prize is everything.
- Isn't it?
- Let me go!
Want out of this memory?
Be my guest.
You don't wanna leave this memory?
Why? Did...
- Did something happen in that cave?
- It was not my fault.
- It was not my fault. It was her fault.
- That's right.
It was not my fault.
- She died.
- It's not my fault.
It was all your fault.
It was her fault. It was not my fault.
It was not my fault.
I don't understand.
I've got the PTDs on full blast.
Thawne's negative tachyon
should be destabilizing,
but the neuron data isn't showing
any resistance.
If anything, his energy is intensifying.
What the hell's
he doing to you in there?
I can barely even feel Nash anymore.
I just...
All I... All I feel is fear and shame
all around him. I can't... I can't...
- I don't think I can take it any...
- Cecile, you okay?
Almost there.
These won't hold me.
What the hell just happened?
Thawne just connected
to his Speed Force.
If that happens again,
we lose Nash forever.
And the Reverse-Flash lives again.
A.R.G.U.S. secure transport
should be here any minute, Captain.
Good job, Korber.
Let me know as soon as they land.
Thanks.
- Hey!
- Captain.
I understand you're moving that thing
out of C.C.P.D. custody.
- I'm here to oversee the transfer.
- Really? Why?
Well, I did a little lunchtime reading
as you suggested.
And I agree with you.
I think Carver has someone
on the inside.
And we need
to investigate this ourselves.
Thank you, David.
I knew I picked the right man
to lead this precinct.
They're here. East loading dock.
- Let's roll.
- All right.
Thank you for coming, gentlemen.
We're all set?
- We're all set, Chief.
- Here it is.
Look out!
- Watch yourselves.
- Where'd she go? Where'd she go?
No one else
has to burn, gents.
Back, back, back, back, back, back!
Just turn over the Refractor.
We're not giving you a damn thing!
- Joe.
- Here.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Oh.
No!
Yup.
You're helio-kinetic.
So, without access to sunlight,
you're just an ordinary thief.
Limits suck, don't they?
So our house is clear.
The Refractor's safe and sound
with A.R.G.U.S.
You sure you're okay, Chief?
Yeah, I got a hard head.
Just ask my husband.
Hey, Joe, what if Sunshine was our mole?
No one would've seen her
doctor those files.
She is the perfect invisible agent.
Look, if we pin her down here,
she can be the brick
for building Carver's RICO case.
- You coming?
- No, you go ahead.
I have something else
I have to take care of.
Why isn't this working?
Thawne's tachyons
are proliferating at a rate
that exceeds the PTD's capabilities.
So, it's just a matter of time
before Thawne takes over Nash's body.
What happens to Nash,
and to the other Wellses?
They'll be in a living hell.
Trapped inside Thawne's psyche forever.
He'll be able to siphon their knowledge.
If he gets loose, we can't risk
him having Nash's mind and his gadgets.
We have to destroy these.
- Is that Allegra?
- No, it's a doppelganger.
Maybe that's why Nash
hung around so much.
Allegra reminds him of someone he knew.
Reminds him...
Reminds him.
Everything that he's been feeling,
all of his emotions, they remind me
of how I feel when I think
about Joanie or Jenna. It's...
It's almost parental.
But it's not just that. It's mixed
with the feeling that I had in '95
when my mom passed away.
Grief. Oh, my God, Cisco.
I think that Nash is caught up in a loop
and it's made out of
remorse and sadness.
- Negativity.
- I think that
Allegra's doppelganger died.
What could be more painful
than the loss of a child?
Cecile, if you're right,
then Thawne is holding Nash
in the memory of her death.
That's why Nash has to be the one
to expel Thawne.
We're gonna help him.
The M.A.D. 2.0...
We used it to get inside
The Thinker's mind.
This time, we're going inside Nash's.
And together, we'll force Thawne out...
from the inside.
You sure you wanna do this?
We can't risk you losing any more speed.
I won't. Trust me.
Hang on, boys.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
It was not my fault.
Not my fault.
Not my fault, it's not my fault.
It's time for you to go, Thawne.
You're too late, Flash.
Nash is mine.
Nash.
- Not yet, he isn't.
- Hey. Hey.
Cisco.
You came for me.
Yeah, but you're the only one
who can get yourself out of here, Nash.
You want Nash,
you're gonna have to go through me.
Aren't you a glutton for punishment.
Always there
to bear witness to the death
of someone you're trying
to desperately save.
No, you're not gonna win this time.
I think I am. Look at him.
Whatever is in there,
I think you need to go face it.
- No, no, I can't go in there.
- He's weak,
he's pathetic,
he's limited by his emotions,
just like you.
He wants you to stay here.
The more you suffer,
the stronger he gets!
- No, no.
- The prize is everything.
Allegra's doppelganger.
That's her, isn't it? She's in there.
Maya.
Her name was Maya.
In a few short moments, I'm gonna...
bust through Cisco's tachyon field
and then...
Then the fun's really gonna begin,
all fueled by poor Nash's grief
for his precious daughter.
You know a few things about grief
for a precious daughter, don't you?
No. Barry.
Barry, come on.
Don't let him get to you.
You didn't make the most of your time
with your daughter.
I taught her everything I know,
while you sat by and did nothing!
She made a bad choice, that's all.
She just made a bad choice.
- That's all...
- Nash, listen to me.
- She made a bad choice...
- Listen to me!
No, I cannot!
If you don't go into that cave,
you're gonna die.
I cannot go in that cave!
All you did was stifle her abilities.
You were an awful father to her.
I miss my daughter every day.
But I'm done letting that
give you power over me.
I watched Cynthia die...
and it hurt me in places
I didn't even know I could feel pain.
But I couldn't avoid it.
You can't heal if you avoid it.
You think that Nash and I
are limited by our emotions.
But you're wrong.
They give us our strength.
And we can use them
to overcome anything,
including you.
That's your greatest flaw, Thawne.
Metas are the ones with limits,
not people.
Not me,
and not Nash.
You have to face that memory.
And when you do,
I'll be here waiting for you.
I promise.
No, you're not getting past me.
You got this, Maya. Easy-peasy.
Nash, the last memory cell is here.
Grab it and I'll pull you back up.
Don't do it.
You got it?
I guess the cave doesn't wanna
let this thing go. It's stuck.
All right, well...
Okay, you're at... you're at the end.
- Don't do it.
- Remember your training.
The prize is everything.
Stop her.
No.
I got it!
Easy-peasy.
Maya.
Nash!
Maya. Maya!
Let it go.
Maya.
No!
Oh, no.
It was my fault.
She only did what I taught her to do.
Nash has taken control
of his pain.
- No.
- You can't feed off of him anymore.
No!
- It's over, Thawne.
- No!
Nash!
No.
No!
Hey, Nash, hey, I'm here.
- Are you okay?
- I will be.
I need a nap.
You're okay. You're okay.
Nash...
I'm here. I'm here.
It was my fault.
It was all my fault.
The satellite scans say
there are no traces
of Thawne's negative tachyons
to be found
in any organic matter on the planet.
As for Nash, Cecile confirmed
that she didn't feel any
of Thawne's energy inside him.
According to three-dimensional imaging,
Nash's brainwaves are Thawne-free.
I guess this means S.T.A.R. Labs
has successfully completed
its very first exorcism.
Thawne's gone, for now.
Right. Thawne's tachyons might have
dissipated, but they weren't destroyed.
Which means he's not dead.
Just formless.
He's probably out there looking
for another body right now.
Like a red-eyed, pissed off Voldemort.
When he comes back, we'll be ready.
I'm gonna go check on Nash.
Are you, uh...
Are you good?
Yeah.
I have someone I should check on, too.
What was it like?
Like being in fog.
You know what it was like?
It was like being underwater.
I... I could see, I could hear,
but it was...
It was hazy. I couldn't do anything.
Well, basically, it sucked.
You're free of it.
Free of Thawne.
As for the other Wellses,
their brainwaves are unfortunately
still entangled with yours.
So, they're as much a part of you now,
as yourself.
Right.
Wait, what?
Mmm-hmm.
You mean, I'm gonna keep hearing them?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna keep seeing them?
Yeah.
Crisis of Infinite Wells.
Well, I've had worse. Hey, look...
Credit where credit's due.
I know that without your help,
we don't get the psychopath
out of my body.
So, for that,
I'm grateful.
Thank you.
See you around Earth-Prime, kid.
Aren't you forgetting something?
I...
No, I don't think so.
I made a lot of discoveries
in my career, but...
she was the best discovery.
You know, she treated... She was...
She was like a daughter...
to me, so...
- And Allegra?
- What about Allegra?
Sure, she's not Maya, but...
you did help her with her powers.
But you know,
we got off to a rocky start.
There's no point in making it
a rocky ending.
- Nash.
- What?
- Pick a Wells. Any Wells.
- Do I have to?
No, it doesn't matter. I got off
to a rocky start with all of 'em.
- What's your point?
- My point is,
I get how difficult it is
to separate your feelings
about a person from their doppelgangers.
Did I ever tell you
about the time I met Harry?
You didn't. That's the Earth-2 Wells?
- The very one.
- All right, go ahead.
When I first saw him,
all I could see was Eobard Thawne.
But when I saw him, when I really saw...
Harry for who he was...
I became his friend.
He became mine.
Yeah, you got off to a bad start
with Allegra.
But it's not too late
to build something good.
You're a good egg.
You're not getting sappy on me, are you?
No.
Nope.
- Good.
He's right. Ramon.
You have a second chance with Allegra.
It's what we've been trying to tell you.
You think you're so smart.
And he's gone.
That's gonna take some getting used to.
Caitlin, I...
I need to apologize.
I didn't follow your advice...
and you got hurt because of me.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, Barry.
I'm on the mend. Feeling better already.
So, we're okay?
Always.
Status report. Nash is physically fine,
but emotionally destroyed,
and Cisco is completely bushed.
You guys make up yet?
Mmm-hmm.
- Thank God.
- Guys, are we sure
creating an artificial Speed Force
is the way to go?
I mean, anyone who came in contact
with Thawne's Speed Force got hurt.
Ours will be different.
Yeah, but we still don't even know
where to start.
Actually, I do.
Every time Thawne tried to hurt me
using Nora's memory...
really what he did was reminded me
how much I loved her.
Made me realize that she's the answer.
Nora's journal?
Thawne taught Nora
how to build a Speed Force.
Now, she can teach us.
And no one saw you?
C.C.P.D. was busy fighting Sunshine.
In and out and no one noticed.
So, my husband stopped looking for me...
but apparently,
still goes out looking for my toys.
You did very well.
And as long as we stick to the plan...
- Success is assured.
And I'm one step closer to liberation.