- She's dead.
You killed Alexa.
Nora:
Barry and I did it together.
That was the only way.
She was the strongest.
I needed every ounce of power,
including your strength,
to kill her.
- I'm supposed to protect
lives, not destroy them!
- I'm helping you clean up
your mess, Barry.
This is your fault.
The night you brought me back,
you created these monsters.
You and your lightning rod.
When you regained your speed,
I wasn't the only thing
you two willed into existence.
- That's impossible.
- Really?
Alexa was afraid to come here,
but she trusted you.
Why?
Because deep down, she could
feel a connection with you.
The same connection
that you feel with me now.
But, these new forces?
The way they've merged with the
people they chose as avatars?
It's corrupted them
because it's unnatural.
But once the other two
are gone--
- I won't help you kill again.
- Oh...
My beautiful boy.
You have no choice.
Because if you don't,
those things will kill everyone
you've sworn to keep safe.
Is that what you want?
Then, please, Barry...
help me.
- No.
- You have to help me,
damn it!
- Nora, stop.
- I will destroy
those other forces, Barry,
with or without your help.
Then you'll see that I'm right.
What a day.
First, Frost is sent to
Iron Heights for life,
and now Alexa's dead.
- I can't let this happen
again.
- I'll get to work.
I need to figure out
how Nora was able to...
- Kill a god?
- She could
because she had help.
- Barry, she tricked you.
- No, she manipulated me,
just like she's been doing
the whole time.
- Honey, I know how you feel,but...
not everything she did
and said was a lie.
I mean, there were moments
that felt real too.
That must mean--
- Iris, we can't trust her
anymore.
- What about
what Nora said
about you two
creating the other forces?
- I mean,
there's no proof.
- Well, what if we find out
if Nora's telling the truth?
If she is, then that means
the other forces
would have been born
the same day she was.
- I'll pull satellite scans
from the night we fought
Mirror Monarch.
- Please, and thank you.
- Okay, you see that cluster of
kinetic energy readings?
Pretty sure
that's the Speed Force
being reborn in the Speed Lab.
Whoa. There they are.
Three brand-spanking-new
isotopic signatures.
- Nora was right.
- We created the forces.
- Fuerza's dead.
Nora killed her.
- She killed
the Strength Force?
- And now she wants to kill
the other two forces.
- Maybe I should go to
San Francisco.
- What?
- My series of photos
on Eva's attacks
got accepted
at a gallery there.
- Babe, congrats!
Well,
I was thinking of going
to help them install
the exhibition.
I'd ask you to come, but I know
you have your perfect job
at S.T.A.R. Labs
and your amazing friends.
I mean...you're an OG member
of Team Flash.
You okay?
- Yeah...
Yeah, I'm fine.
This is an isotopic
scanning lens.
It can detect the signatures
of all four forces,
even kinetic signatures
from Speed Force Nora.
And if one's nearby--
- It lights up like
an overexposed landscape.
- In which case,
you run the other way.
- Okay? I'm serious.
I just want you to be safe.
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Ohh, it's Barry.
I gotta get back--they could
have found Nora...
or worse, she's come back
on her own.
- How bad is it?
- Okay--did Nora
kill somebody else?
- No, and I have a way to make
sure she never does.
- Okay, how?
- I'm here.
What's going on?
- I spent all night
coming up with a way
to fix all this.
- Okay, what's the solve?
- We need to wipe the new
forces out of existence.
- Barry, what are you saying?
- I want to go back in time...
and uncreate them.
- Barry, you're talking about
creating another Flashpoint.
You know we can't do that.
- Not if I can figure out
a way to go back
that doesn't affect
the timeline.
- Which would be impossible.
- Barry, look.
I know that you're devastated
about Alexa.
But uncreating forces?
That crosses a line.
- I convinced Alexa
to come here.
Her death is my fault.
If we don't get these new
forces out of Psych and Deon,
Nora will kill them, too,
so it's on us to fix this.
- By killing Deon and Psych?
- No, I'm not killing them.
I'm saving them from the forces
that took over their lives.
Whoever they were before this,
they can
go back to being those
same people again.
- And what about the other
force that was born that night?
Nora. If you uncreate her--
- We're only gonna target
the new forces, not Nora.
That's the plan.
- But if something
goes wrong,
Barry, you might
lose your speed.
- Then I lose my speed.
All right?
It's--it's worth the risk
to keep everyone safe.
- And what about the risk
to Nora?
Does her life not matter
at all any--
- Nora's not a person, Iris.
She never was.
Look, if we uncreate
these forces,
we can put everything
back to normal.
Hopefully that'll fix her too.
- Hopefully?
Barry, do you hear yourself
right now?
- Iris, I'm trying
to save people.
How--how do you not see
this is the right thing to do?
- The right thing to do
would be trying to
get through to Nora.
Just like how we beat Eva,
just like how we talked down
Abra Kadabra.
That is what we do.
- We tried talking to her.
All Nora did was double down.
- There's no reaching her.
Obviously we disagree on this.
- Yes, we do.
- I have to do it.
- Then you'll be doing it
without me.
- Wait...you want to go
after a force of nature?
- Yeah, if I can convince Nora
not to kill Deon and Psych,
then...Barry will see that
she can be reasoned with.
- But, how do we find her?
I mean, she's the freakin'
Speed Force.
- Well, if she finds us first,
at least we'll know
she's coming.
Holy crap...you guys gotta
see this.
You see that bright spot
at the center of you?
I think that's kinetic energy.
- Guys, this is gonna sound
really wild, but...
- Yeah, 'cause a ghost-hunting
lens isn't weird enough...
- But, if Barry and I created
these forces,
what if there's a little bit of
each of them inside of us?
- Like you're all connected?
- Wait, Iris...
when you're over by the door,
your glow was brighter.
Like there's something
in that direction
that was intensifying it.
What if...
- That something is Nora?
Guys, we can use me as a
divining rod to track her down.
- Yup, that's weirder.
- Elemental Force Particles?
- They're the particles
that created the new forces.
The lightning bolt
that rebirthed the Speed Force
was full of them.
- Now if we can extract
a sample
of these force particles
from the lightning,
then we can send out
an electromagnetic pulse
that'll seek out those
same particles,
wherever they may be
along the temporal spectrum.
- And you can erase the new
forces from existence.
That's not bad.
Small detail, though.
How in the world
are you supposed to
extract these particles
from a giant bolt of lightning?
- A few weeks ago when
Barry was Spock-Flash,
he modified the Tachyon
Enhancer to siphon
Mirror Monarch's
dark matter photons.
- So all we have to do
is tweak the Enhancer
to siphon Force Particles
instead of photons.
- Tweaking the
Tachyon Enhancer...
and then send out an EMP
to eighty-six the forces.
That's genius. I mean
it's foolproof, even.
But it still doesn't answer how
we're supposed to do this
and protect the timeline.
- I'll figure out.
Somehow, I will.
I'll figure it out.
- Man, I wish Nash Wells
was here.
I mean, he came up with
most of these equations
for the A.S.F. Machine.
I feel like
he'd crack this easy peasy.
- Modify the Particle Harness
Collector.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
- Roger that,
but where are you going?
- To get the one person that
can help us pull this off.
- Oh, no...Tess.
President Bartlett
just mixed up his meds.
That's not gonna be good,
but...great TV.
Whoa!
Allen. Allen.
I'm guessing
this isn't a social call?
- Not exactly.
We need your help.
- How bad is it?
- That depends.
- On...
- Whether or not you can help
us do the impossible.
- Well, well, well.
Honey, I'm home.
- Holy deus ex machina...
Timeless Wells.
- Perfect timing.
- Always.
So, apparently, there's danger
in Central City.
- Apparently.
- Well, let's get busy.
- Well, you really think
we can do this without
affecting the timeline?
- I know we can.
As long as we use me
as your guide.
- Harrison was there when
the forces were created.
So if we used the other "him"
from that night
as a beacon to lock onto--
- Hopefully I can go back
to that exact moment,
also bring Allen along
for the ride,
and he'll collect
the particles.
- Oof, wait, so you can travel
through time with a plus one?
- It should work...
When Allen and I go back
to that exact moment
that those dangerous forces
were created 17 days ago,
I will--I will create
a protective-time bubble
from that moment until now,
preserving those days
in this timeline,
and preventing
anything from changing.
- Which would also allow us
to wipe out the new forces
without altering
any of the events
that have happened
since then--
Yo! That is--that is trippy.
- Cisco, this will work.
- What about Iris?
- When she sees everyone safe,
she'll come around.
She has to.
- You're not convinced.
I wasn't either,
when Allen told me about this,
I thought of Tess.
I thought of my wife, and how
my future with Tess was...
ripped from me.
Until this gift...
which has allowed me to relive
every single day with Tess,
but only...
because I took a chance.
- All right.
I'm in.
- It's brighter.
We must be getting close.
She should be here.
- Maybe it was
a false positive.
- Maybe since Nora
is the Speed Force,
her isotopic signature
is all over the city by now.
- So what do we do?
- I don't know.
But we are running
out of time.
- Well, Cisco always says
you can't solve a problem
till you're asking
the right question.
- Isn't "Where's Nora's
kinetic energy leading us"
the right question?
- No.
The right question is
"Where's Nora?"
We've been trying to find
the Speed Force
when we should be looking
for... the person.
- So where would the real
Nora Allen go?
- Home.
Come on.
- Harness modifications
complete.
Let's get some time particles.
Actually, you know what?
Um...
Let me run just one more
diagnostic
on the collection disc.
[muttering] I just need
one more, just one more...
- Oh, frak.
Yo, yo, Deon.
What's--what's uh...
What's good, man?
- You tell me.
Something drew me here.
Was it you?
- I'm--I don't think
it was...
- Who's this?
I'm sorry, who are you?
- Who am I? Who are you?
- Who is he?
Look, guys, all's good
in the hood.
All right, look.
Barry, this is Deon.
Still Force.
And--and Deon,
this is Barry,
who's actually--
owner of this, uh,
fine establishment.
- So you're the landlord.
What's that got to do
with anything?
- Deon...
it's good to meet you.
- Actually, you remember me?
I was with him, you called us
one of the Urkels.
- Oh, yeah...the cornballs.
Cornball. He's so funny.
- Who's the egghead?
- Harrison Wells.
I'm a fellow--
Uh, visitor to Barry's place.
- You know, y'all are being
real friendly right now.
But I think--
I think y'all are acting
like that
because you're afraid of me.
Now why is that?
- No, we're just...
we're just making a--we're just
doing an experiment--
- Shut up!
Now...
why do I get the feeling...
you're reason I'm this way?
- Because that's true.
And I'm sorry.
I never meant
for this to happen.
So please let me fix it.
- Fix it?
Fix it?
So I'm a mistake?
- I didn't say that--
- You didn't have to.
I can feel it.
You want to destroy me.
- No, I want to save you.
Deon....Deon.
There are three other forces--
people like you.
One of them?
She wants to kill you.
Now, she's already killed
one of the other forces--
the Strength Force,
and she didn't care
when the person containing
that force died too.
So I need to make it so the
Still Force never found you.
It's the only way
to keep you safe.
Nah.
I like being me.
Oh, I get it.
- Yeah?
- No, I get it. I get it.
This is what you're gonna
use to do it, huh?
This is what you're gonna use
to make it like I neverexisted?
- Not you,
just the force inside--
- Man, I am that force!
Do you have any idea
what it's like
to be told that you
shouldn't be here?
I never asked to be born.
- Deon, listen to me.
Look at what you're doing.
Okay, you--you don't understand
what you are.
- Yeah, I do.
I'm a god.
Maybe it's time
you understood that.
- Deon, wait--
- Time to bounce.
-...right?
- What the hell
just happened?
- I think your friend Deon
just stopped time.
- Yeah, he does that.
- Why'd he leave?
- Because I couldn't stop him.
- Deon just aged the harness
a thousand years.
How bad is it?
- Pretty bad.
- But not hopeless.
See I figured if we can find
some way to--
somehow create some sort of...
I was working on the collection
disc when Deon showed up.
I figured I better hide it
just in case.
Chester.
You're a lifesaver.
As for the vest,
I'm used to working with junk.
I'll just need a bunch of
replacement parts
from my garage and she'll be up
and running in no time.
With a little help, that is.
- I'm with you.
- What's up?
- I think Deon's right.
We can't just...
uncreate these forces
like that.
- Uh--so what, we--we...
we should just give up?
- On this? Yeah, we give up.
Doesn't that feel like
the right thing to do?
- Cisco, Nora will kill him
if I don't do something
to prevent it.
Just like she killed Alexa.
'Cause she's not gonna stop
until all the forces--
and the people connected
to them--are dead.
Why can't you see?
I'm trying to save him.
- He doesn't want to be
saved by you!
He just wants to be given
the chance to be himself.
And Iris understood that.
- Look, every second that we
leave these forces
inside Deon and Psych,
people are in danger.
It's only a matter of time
before someone dies
in one of Psych's nightmares
or gets killed by some kind
of Deon time anomaly.
Not to mention Nora
declared war.
She doesn't care how many
people she kills
as long as the forces die.
- You're right.
Yes, you're absolutely right.
And something needs to be done
about that.
And I don't have
all the answers.
All I know is...
this can't be it.
- You guys understand, right?
I--I have to uncreate
these forces.
- Like I said, I am--I'm
Team Flash all the way.
But...
Cisco has a point, man.
- Harrison?
- If uncreating these forces is
what you feel in your heart
is right,
I'll take that voyage with you.
But all I ask is that you
think--truly think
about the choice you're making.
- Please fix the harness.
- Good luck.
- Iris, you were right.
These isotopic readings
are off the chart.
- Where are we?
- The old Allen house.
This is where Barry's mom
was killed.
He also said this is where the
Speed Force went when she died.
- Whoa.
That old car is hella vintage.
Almost looks brand new.
- Must be a collector
or something.
- We can ask him
when we're done.
Assuming we survive.
- Caitlin called me
about Alexa.
- So it turns out,
when Iris and I brought back
the Speed Force,
we also created
three new forces.
It's our fault that they're out
in the world hurting people.
Killing them.
So I feel like...
I have to be the one
to take them out.
- These forces.
You think
they're above saving, too?
- I think it would be safer for
everybody if they didn't exist.
- You remember when Wally
first showed up?
Man, it wasn't just that
I'd found out I have a son.
I found out
I have a son who kept getting
his butt in trouble.
Boy, he was mad at the world.
There was one point
he said to me that he wished
he had never been born.
So I tried to get close.
And he pushed me away.
I tried to give him space,
then he felt abandoned.
No parent is perfect.
But one thing I never
stopped doing
was trying.
And look at the man
he grew up to be.
Strong. Kind. Good.
- Yeah I get it, I--I do,but...
I mean, these forces?
They're not my children.
- You sure?
You said it yourself.
You brought them
into this world.
Look, I know they've all done
terrible things.
But what if they could change?
You never judge your kids
for who they are now.
You help them become...
who they know they can be
when they grow up.
So lead with love.
After that, it is up to them.
- This is Barry's old room.
Nora?
Psych.
- Hi, Mom.
- Esperanza, don't kill me!
- They're everywhere.
We need to keep them out.
- Psych, stop. You're hurting
them--please.
- Oh, they're hurting
themselves.
Sure, I pull back the curtain.
But what they see
is up to them.
Now, before I show you
your worst fear,
why were you looking for me?
- I wasn't.
- No...
You're looking for
the Speed Force?
Nora. Why?
Why are you so desperate
to find her?
Is it to hurt her?
- I want to talk to her
so I can help her.
- Are you sure?
Because I am
feeling the pain that she
has inflicted upon you.
How deeply she's torn apart
your relationships.
Your whole life.
Actually, the suffering
she's caused is
quite beautiful.
- That wasn't Nora.
She's lost control.
Just like you have.
But if you let me,
I can help you both.
I don't need your help.
Besides, I can feel
what you fear the most.
It's the person you seek.
Well, your wish is my command.
- Sweet dreams,
my beautiful boy.
You'll never measure up.
- Okay. It's working.
Now, when you're close enough
to cycle particles,
the disc will light up.
- Guys, I appreciate you
helping me.
- Make sure the proton
collection housing's
double-fused.
- We did.
And it's good to see you.
- What changed your mind?
- Look, this is dangerous.
And it doesn't feel right.
But I'm always gonna
have your back.
No matter what.
- Chester. Let's get it going.
- Okay, so. Barry.
All you need to do is
get close enough to the
Speed Force lightning to
collect a sample of each force.
The PHC and Timeless Wells'
time bubble should do the rest.
Theoretically.
- Ready?
- Nothing's happening.
You gonna--
- Wait for it.
Wait for it.
Incredible.
- We're at 100% organic speed.
- We need you...
I need you.
- I remember this moment.
This is where it all started.
- We should get to the roof.
- You think you can be
a good wife?
Good mother?
But you never will.
Everything you do pales
in comparison to me.
Besides...
how could you be a good mother
if you never even had one?
- I'm not listening to you.
- You don't have to.
You already know
it's the truth.
- No. You're not real.
- There's no escaping
your own fear.
- I know you're still here,
Psych.
- Very good. Mm.
It is not every day that
somebody can sense my presence
in their nightmare.
- I'm not just someone.
We have a connection.
I know you can feel that too.
- Perhaps. It's not going to
help you, though.
Escape one nightmare and I'll
just serve up another.
Because there's always more
terror to unlock.
- But before you
had those powers,
before you became a force.
You were a person.
I'm talking to that person
right now.
I have friends. I have a team.
They can help you fight this
monster that's inside of you.
We can help you regain control
of your body.
- What makes you think
I'm not in control?
- I know you didn't...
choose to have these powers.
And you shouldn't have to
go through this alone.
I know that we're not flesh
and blood.
But in a way...
I'm--I'm like a parent.
So please let me help you.
- Well, then there's something
I should tell you, Mother.
I hated my parents.
- The isotopic energy readings
are going down.
- The forces are dying.
- These fools gonna learn.
You mess with Deon.
You get dealt with.
- Another 20 seconds, and
they'll be gone forever.
Barry did it.
- Okay.
- Wait...wait.
What is that?
- I think that is an act
of creation.
- I have the particles.
Shouldn't the forces be dying?
- Perhaps they are.
Somewhere.
In time, but right here?
Right now?
They're being born.
- What are you doing to me?
- I wasn't able to get
through to him.
And now it's too late.
- Boss, we can't stay here.
- Allen.
You okay?
- Never judge your kids
for who they are now.
You help them become
who they know they can be.
- They're almost gone.
- 5%.
4...
3%...
2%...
- What's happening?
Everything just stopped.
- The numbers
are going back up.
It's as if the forces
are still here...
- Iris was right.
You all were.
I--
I couldn't do it.
- Iris...
I'm sorry.
- Yeah, me too.
- Barry, I--um...
I went looking for Nora.
I thought that if I could just
talk to her,
that I could fix everything.
But, um.
I ended up finding Psychinstead.
You were right.
I couldn't get through to him.
And it probably would have been
the same with Nora.
I should have listened to you.
- No, I'm the one who should
have listened.
- Harrison told me about
the birth of the forces.
Sounds incredible.
- It was.
Can't believe how close I came
to erasing them.
- What changed your mind?
- You.
Joe. Everyone.
Even the forces themselves.
I could...
I could feel how they would
affect the future.
All the speedsters' and heroes'
lives they'd shape.
Some of them were family,
Iris.
Our family.
- Barry, we both know how
dangerous these forces can be.
I mean, if you couldn't
uncreate them,
and I couldn't get through toPsych...
What are we supposed to do?
- Try again.
Together this time.
Joe helped me realize
that we can't judge
Psych and Deon
for who they are now.
We have to help them become
who they can grow up to be.
- 'Cause
that's what parents do.
Alexa.
- What happened?
- There was a tremor.
And Alexa sat up
and looked at me.
- Alexa's alive?
- She was for a second,
but she's not anymore.
Which doesn't make any sense,
medically speaking.
- What if us being back in sync
is what woke her up for
the moment?
- And then she reconnected
with the Strength Force.
- Is it crazy to think
that we did this?
- No.
'Cause we're all connected.
And if we woke her up once.
- Then we could bring her back
permanently?
Why is everyone looking at me?
- Listen.
I'd ask you to say, but...
I already know the answer.
- A man's gotta be
where his heart lies.
He's just gotta learn to
listen to it.
One more thing
before I go.
Whether it's me...
or any of the many Wells
predecessors,
I want you to know
that you taught us
every inch as much
as we taught you.
Maybe more.
- Yeah, I'm never gonna
get used to that.
You okay?
- Yeah.
For the first time
in a long while.
Yeah, I feel okay.
- Good.
Um...'cause I've been thinking
about something.
And after tonight,
I know I have to do it.
- Okay, that's just weird.
I was literally about to say
the exact same thing to you.
I have to leave
Central City.
Thank God.
- Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God.
Babe, what are you gonna
tell Team Citizen?
- What are you gonna tell
Team Flash?
- You're the one
who's after me?
You don't look so tough.
What are you?
- A reckoning.