My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on “The Flash”...
I stabbed your mother in the heart
- and I was free.
- [gunshot]
Eddie is his ancestor.
If Eddie dies, he'll never be born.
He's being erased from existence.
- Gideon?
- Yes, Professor Thawne?
- Where the hell am I?
- I was accepted
into the forensic science program
at Midway City University.
I'm leaving Central City.
Joe, you have a son.
Hi, I'm Wally. I'm Francine's son.
These races? That's the only way
that I can pay for my
mom's hospital bills.
Jesse's my daughter. Zoom has her.
Daddy? Please help me.
Don't let him take me back there.
I would do anything to get you back.
[bone snaps]
There are many reasons why we run,
but usually it's to avoid
what's right in front of us...
A decision to be made
or a dilemma we have to face.
Lately, for me, it feels like
running is all I've been doing.
What you got for me, Cisco?
You've been playing Good
Samaritan all morning.
Take a break.
Are you sure you don't
want to get to CCPD,
- give Patty your attention?
- No, I can see her later.
'Cause we cannot afford
to waste any more time.
What, 'cause we've just been
sipping Mai Tais since you got here?
I don't know what you been
sipping since I got here,
but Barry needs to get
better, stronger, faster.
We need to train to prepare for Zoom.
Oh, I see.
You haven't had your coffee this morning.
I had my coffee this morning.
Don't slurp.
- [slurps coffee]
- Don't. Don't.
- Don't.
- [extended slurp]
[computer chiming]
Runaway chemical transport
truck heading south on Kester.
On it.
[dramatic music]
[sirens wailing]
♪
Hey, I can't stop the truck!
Somebody rigged it!
Sorry!
You can't let that truck crash.
If you do, you'll take
out a whole city block.
Great. Thank you.
- Thank you for that.
- [honks horn]
[horns honking]
That was close, that was close.
Oh, and the plot thickens.
Uh, dead-end up ahead.
You got to get out of there!
Oh, come on.
Yes!
[sirens wailing]
♪
- That one was a little close.
- [tire iron clangs]
Nice! Now can you please,
please take a break?
- How's that for training?
- Great.
Look, we're gonna catch Zoom.
We got Turtle locked up in the pipeline.
All we got to do is use him
to figure out how to steal
Zoom's speed and then we'll
get your daughter back.
That might take longer than we thought.
Why's that?
Because Turtle's dead.
♪
Barry, we need you back here stat.
All right. I'm on my way.
♪
Gideon.
Was the trip a success, Professor Thawne?
I believe it was. I've finally figured
out what time period The Flash is from.
Now let's figure out a way to get home.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -
He better not be pulling a Juliet.
Yeah, that's right. I see plays.
- He's dead, Cisco.
- How'd this happen?
Preliminary brain scan shows
an acute brain aneurysm.
The night we captured him.
How's that for timing?
What does that mean? You
think I did this, Garrick?
This man is the key to us stopping Zoom,
the key to me saving my daughter.
Why would I want that?
Never understood why you
do anything, Harrison.
That's fine with me, Garrick.
Guys, look.
We need to figure out how to stop Zoom.
Everything we've tried so far has failed.
We need to start thinking
outside the box.
I mean, we haven't even figured out how
to close the breaches yet.
Maybe that's where we should start.
That's a good idea.
- I'll get on that.
- I'll help.
[cell phone vibrates]
I've got to get to the CCPD.
I'll check in with you guys later.
Okay.
Every time you think that
Wells is on your team,
something happens that
makes you doubt it.
Hey, I just wanted to see if you
could run this trace for me.
Someone messed with an ethanol
transport truck this morning.
They cut the brake line and
tampered with the gear shafts.
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
Wow. Backed up, huh?
I am, yeah.
Yeah, I guess I'll find
out what that's like
once I finish CSI school.
Yeah, you will.
- [whispers] Yeah.
- I guess.
Look, Barry, I know that you're upset,
but I was hoping it wouldn't
be like this between us.
Uh... [stammers]
I mean, what did you think
it was gonna be like?
I ju... I just thought we could
at least talk before I left.
You're moving. I don't know.
I mean, it just doesn't feel like
there's much to talk about now, right?
I guess not.
Hi.
- Hey.
I sort of overheard some of that.
Mm-hmm. Um...
Patty's going to CSI
school in Midway City.
She's moving in two days.
I mean, you don't have to let her leave.
She's wanted to be a CSI her whole life.
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Just went to see Francine and, uh...
she doesn't have much time.
I already said my good-byes, if...
If you want to do the same.
[keys clacking]
[computer chimes and trills]
It's not gonna work.
Closing the breaches, that's
like solving Einstein's riddle.
I solved Einstein's
riddle when I was ten.
Yeah, well, maybe Earth-2 Einstein
wasn't as clever as ours.
You realize this Earth
is my Earth-2, right?
Listen to this.
What if we can figure out
how to control my powers?
We could find Zoom, get the jump on him.
That's a good idea. You
should get on that.
I need your help, Harry.
What you need, Ramon,
is to figure out what
triggers your vibes.
Exactly, and I don't
know what triggers them.
It's completely inconsistent.
Sometimes it's when I touch
something that belongs to a breacher,
sometimes it just happens.
There's always a cause. Cause, effect.
Doesn't take Einstein to figure that out.
Okay, so what is the cause?
You saw when I tried to vibe Dr. Light,
when I tried to vibe you,
took a while to work.
Yes.
Yes, it did.
Meet me in the Time Vault.
For what?
[sighs]
[ominous music]
♪
Hello?
Harry?
♪
Of course, now he's gonna make me wait
in this freaky-ass braille room.
♪
- Hi, Cisco.
- [high-pitched scream]
Stop! Don't do that!
[grunts]
I figured out your trigger.
A rush of adrenaline.
Dopamine floods the brain.
And the quickest way to
achieve that result...
♪
Fear!
[dramatic music]
Do not move!
You can't be.
♪
What did you see?
The Reverse-Flash.
He's here.
[alarm blaring]
[dramatic music]
Oh, my God!
Christina McGee.
Who are you?
You're coming with me.
Flash.
Eobard Thawne.
You know who I am?
You died!
Good to know.
And guess what, Flash.
I know what time period you're from.
So that means very soon... you will die.
♪
No.
You okay, Bar?
I'm good, yeah. It's just a lot.
Eddie Thawne died, so Eobard Thawne
should have been erased
out of existence, right?
Not necessarily.
It's possible Eobard was
in the Speed Force,
protecting him like a bomb shelter,
keeping him alive and
his time line intact.
It's what's known as a
“time line remnant”"
A what now?
Here, let me... show you.
This?
This... is now.
Here, today.
This is the time Thawne comes from.
This is the moment you all
erased him from existence,
but since Thawne is from the future,
this is where his time line begins.
That's why he's still alive.
This Thawne has not yet traveled back
in time to kill Barry's mother.
He's here now in this time
period for the first time.
“Time line remnant.”
Explains why nothing's changed.
Yeah, it also explains why
he didn't know my name
or that we have met before.
To him, you hadn't. Not until the future.
If Thawne dies before he
can time travel again,
will that save Barry's mother?
No. That's not how it works.
In our time line, Barry's
mother is already dead,
and her death is a fixed point.
Nothing can change that.
All right, well, I'm gonna end this,
him, in this time once and for all.
Let's find Dr. McGee,
then we'll figure out
what to do about Thawne, okay?
I got to go check on Iris.
Ramon.
Caitlin, I know you're
worried about Dr. McGee,
but we're gonna get her back.
It's not that. It's Jay.
What about Jay?
He's sick, and it's getting worse.
When Zoom stole his speed,
it affected him on a cellular level.
We need to do something about it.
All right, like what?
I think we should replace his dying cells
with healthy ones
indistinguishable from his.
How do we do that?
We find his Earth-1 doppelganger.
There.
Tachyons?
A man in a yellow suit tried to steal
another tachyon prototype last year.
I must have gotten stuck here once before
and not been able to access
enough of the Speed Force.
Tachyons should do it.
I want you to isolate and accelerate
their energetic properties for me.
I don't know if I can do that.
♪
If you want to stay alive...
learn.
♪
Franny.
Hey.
How you feeling today?
Better now.
I'm gonna let you two talk, okay?
Okay.
Can I get you anything?
Oh, just that brother of yours
so all of us can be together
for the first time.
Yeah, he should be here.
His mother is leaving him.
Can't blame him for
being angry about that.
I just wish he'd get all that anger out
while I'm here to help.
Same thing goes for you, Iris.
One thing you learn when you're dying
is not to hold anything back.
You want to say something to me?
You need to say it while you can.
[somber music]
♪
I have so many great memories
from when I grew up.
Now when I think about those memories,
I can only wonder what
it would have been like
if you and Wally would have been there.
[voice breaking] I'm not angry at
you anymore for what happened.
I just wish you would have
come back to us a lot sooner.
♪
Because I would have forgiven you then...
just like I'm forgiving you now.
Mm.
[sobbing] I'm sorry.
Thank you. Thank you.
[sighing]
♪
[sobbing]
I don't know why this is so hard.
I barely even know her.
♪
The facial recognition
software at S.T.A.R. Labs
didn't find anything either.
No, but there's still
more databases to check.
We'll find his doppelganger.
- Thanks, Barry.
- Yeah.
Hey. Hi, Caitlin.
Hi.
Uh, can we... talk?
Uh, yeah, yeah, for sure.
Um, I'll let you know what I find.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What's up?
I didn't know you were
working with S.T.A.R. Labs.
Yeah, um, uh, yeah.
Joe and I help out every once in a while.
Really?
Yeah, I probably shouldn't tell you this,
but there's a lot of weird
stuff that happens over there.
[chuckles]
Is that what you came to tell me?
Um... [sighs]
You're just rolling with the
whole “me leaving” thing.
Yeah, well, I don't know
what to tell you, Patty.
Everyone in my life that I
love leaves at some point.
Kind of getting used to it.
You... never told me you loved me.
Yeah, I guess I don't
get that chance now.
I don't understand.
What is it? What's going on with you?
Why are you being like this?
My life is complicated,
and I don't want you
to have regrets, all right?
I don't want you to miss out
on something that you've
always wanted to do.
And I wish that things were different
for both of us.
You know, but they're not.
Sorry.
Me too.
♪
So what did you do to my goggles?
I added a wavelength trigger
to stimulate the fear
receptors in your brain.
Then I took what you already
had to induce slow-wave sleep,
upgraded it to get you
to stage-four sleep.
- [groans]
- No, this is good.
- This will give us more control.
- Okay.
Now I'll be able to dictate
how long you vibe for.
Put 'em on.
What am I gonna see?
I don't know. Never done this before.
You'll have to tell me so I can
steer you where you need to be.
Ramon, you want to find Reverse-Flash,
put on the goggles.
- Okay.
- Attaboy.
[sighs]
Go ahead.
[goggles power on]
[indistinct voices echoing]
Oh-ho-ho, yeah, man.
I'm in full-on vibe mode right now.
- What do you see?
- It's hard to explain.
It's different events.
Different events in time.
Concentrate on The Reverse-Flash.
Okay.
I see him.
Move toward him.
Okay, now what?
Try to picture him with Christina McGee.
Where the hell am I?
It's charged. You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
Yes, I did. Didn't I?
No!
[gasping]
Well, what is it?
She's dead.
Dr. McGee is dead?
Harry and I were trying to
hone my powers to find Zoom,
and then we ended up using them,
finding The Reverse-Flash,
and that's when I saw him kill her.
And then he left.
He left? What do you mean, he left?
McGee built him some
kind of speed machine
and he ran into and got
flung back to the future.
[sighs]
You'd need superluminal energy
to send someone through time.
- You mean like tachyons?
- Tachyons.
We can track their location
once they've been activated.
[computer trilling]
Anything? Nothing.
Cisco, you're sure that's what you saw?
- I'm positive.
- All right.
What else did you see?
There was all sorts of
weird tech everywhere.
There was a clock.
What time did the clock say?
9:52, I think.
How... how is that relevant?
It's 6:00 now.
Are you telling me I can see the future?
That's exactly what I'm telling you.
Those goggles are getting
named immediately.
But that means Dr. McGee is alive.
- That's right.
- Yeah, okay.
We have 3 hours, 52 minutes to
find her and stop Reverse-Flash.
Let's do it.
[rousing music]
- Spivot.
- Hey.
Can't get away from
those case files, huh?
Oh, just following up on a hunch.
You're gonna miss the action, right?
Maybe. A little.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- Miss you too.
- It's nice to know someone will.
- Wait, we talking about Barry?
'Cause it sounds like we're
talking about Barry.
[sighs] He kept telling
me there was stuff
he couldn't share with me and
I've been going a little crazy
trying to figure out what that stuff is.
Yeah, Barry's not great at sharing.
- Neither are you.
- What do you mean?
Barry just told me that, you know,
sometimes he helps you out with S.T.A.R.
Labs stuff.
Yeah, he does when he has
a few extra minutes.
I didn't know that.
I mean, the whole time
I've been working here
you never mentioned it to me,
but then I realized why.
I went through some of Barry's old cases.
All of them involved The
Flash saving the day
with details that Barry couldn't
have possibly even known.
That's weird.
Yeah, it... It is weird.
The only thing that does make sense
is that Barry is The Flash.
Have you ever seen Barry run?
He waddles like a slow-ass duck.
There's no way he's The Flash, Patty.
You know, when I started this job,
you told me I had to learn
how to lie to do it.
You're a terrible liar, Joe.
See you.
Nice nitrous kit.
You're gonna get caught
one of these days.
You know that, right? Get thrown in jail?
I'll stop racing when these
hospital bills stop coming in.
I saw Mom today. She says you
haven't been by in a while.
Yeah, she knows why.
She thinks it's because
you're angry with her.
I have every right to be angry.
Nothing for 20 years,
then out of nowhere,
she tells me I have a sister, I have...
I have a father.
Yeah, the same thing happened
to me too, remember?
But that shouldn't keep
you from seeing her
before you can't anymore.
No. Look... that's not what it is.
Then what is it, Wally?
I got to go.
Last year, my fiancé died...
unexpectedly.
One moment he was here, the next... gone.
I didn't get a chance
to say good-bye to him,
to tell everything he meant to me,
That he was my world...
that he was loved.
But today I got to say
good-bye to your mom.
My mom.
And it helped us both find peace
with what happened to our family.
Wally, don't make a mistake
you're gonna regret
the rest of your life.
Go see your mom while you still can.
[somber music]
♪
[computer trilling]
No sign of tachyon activity.
We're running out of time.
We've got to find them.
It'll take a few minutes for
the device to reach full power
once it's activated, but when we find it,
you're gonna have to get there fast.
- Hey, Barry.
- Yeah?
Have you found out anything
else about Jay's doppelganger?
There's no Jay Garrick on this Earth.
That's so weird. Everyone
has a doppelganger.
Maybe just ask Jay.
He's a good guy.
Just ask him. I'm sure he'll tell you.
Okay.
Hey. Hold on.
What's up?
We got a problem. Patty
knows you're The Flash.
- What?
- She caught me off guard.
I mean, I played it off, but
come on, she's a smart girl.
Anyway, she was going
through some case files
and you were acting all squirrely.
This is my fault now?
- No, it's nobody's fault.
- Oh, my God.
- Maybe you should tell her.
- No.
- Patty's trustworthy.
- It's not even about that, Joe.
I-I don't want another person
that Zoom or Reverse-Flash
or any of these meta-humans
can use against me.
I don't want it. Patty
can't get hurt over this.
[alarm blares]
Tachyons! 87th and Avenue J.
[dramatic music]
Must be one of Mercury
Labs' off-site facilities.
Hack into their se...
I've hacked in the security feed.
- And once that...
- I'm one step ahead of you.
[computer chimes]
Uh-oh.
Barry, hurry up!
It's charged.
You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
Yes, I did. Didn't I?
He's gonna kill her.
♪
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, get out of here, all right?
Go! Go!
♪
That was my way home!
You're not going anywhere.
♪
You haven't won here, Flash.
I'll find another way back.
You're gonna have to
get through me first.
You really think you're
fast enough to stop me?
Let's find out.
Catch me if you can.
♪
- [computer beeping]
- Oh, it's on.
♪
[computer beeping]
[grunts]
Get him, Bar.
♪
[grunts]
Not fast enough, Thawne. [grunts]
I will never lose to you again.
[both grunting]
♪
This war between us, it ends now!
[screaming]
Bar, you got to stop!
Bar, don't kill him! Just bring him in!
[groans]
♪
Get the cell ready.
Hey, he can't...?
Phase his way out? No, he can't do that.
It's the same cell we used to hold Dr.
Wells last year.
Barry, where you going?
- I'm going down there.
- No, you're not.
The more he learns about you,
the more you will alter the time line.
He killed my mom!
He's from the future. He
hasn't done that yet.
He doesn't even know you're The Flash,
and you need to keep it that way.
You already said that his mother's
gonna die no matter what we do.
There's ramifications
any time anybody messes
with the time line, and
it's impossible to predict
what those ramifications are going to be.
Barry, you caught him and you stopped him
from killing Dr. McGee.
In my book, that's a win.
This doesn't feel like a win.
[cell phone vibrates]
I got to go.
[tense music]
♪
So, what'd you want to talk to me about?
[light rock music playing]
My dad had multiple sclerosis.
Every day for years, I watched
this amazingly strong man fight
for his life... and lose.
So, I can't sit by and watch
another man I care about
fight for his life and not
do something about it.
I tried to find your doppelganger.
Same DNA, same cellular structure.
I could replace your dying
cells with his living ones.
But... you don't have a
doppelganger on this Earth.
Caitlin, there is a good explanation.
Meet me at Hofherr Park
tomorrow and I'll show you.
Why can't you just tell me?
Because you need to see for yourself.
[dark music]
♪
How'd you get your suit in your ring?
Who are you?
My name is Cisco Ramon.
And we know each other well, don't we?
We have a history together.
You could say that.
And that's all you want to know?
How I got my suit in my ring?
I want you to know that I'm the one
who figured out you were back.
I helped stop you.
Me.
And how'd you do that?
I have powers.
And I helped track you down
and I put you in here.
♪
That's quite the ability
you've been given.
And here's what's so ironic about it.
You gave me these powers.
Have fun thinking about that
while you rot away ithis cell
that you helped me build.
Bye, Felicia.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[plaintive music]
Hey.
Got your text.
I wasn't sure that you would see me,
considering you've been
avoiding me lately.
Patty, I haven't been avoiding you.
No, just, uh, busy...
you know, speeding around Central City.
♪
- I know you're The Flash, Barry.
- Patty, come on.
Please don't make me feel any more stupid
than I already do.
Look, I'm a detective and
I should have known.
I was just... I was so smitten with you.
Okay, look, what...
What you're saying, it's insane.
Look, you don't have to
lie to me anymore, okay?
I understand... I understand why
you didn't want to tell me.
I understand why you've been distant.
Look, I understand everything.
But just tell me the truth now.
Just be honest with me.
Just... admit to me you're
The Flash and I'll stay.
I can't do that. I'm not him.
♪
It's too bad. It would
have been nice to stay.
[voice breaking] Fight
crime during the day
and be with you at night.
[crying] But I was... I was wrong.
Take care, Barry.
♪
Is that you, Flash?
Why do you hate me so much?
I didn't always.
[ominous music]
I was obsessed with you.
For so long, I wanted to be The Flash.
I spent years figuring
out how you came to be.
Duplicated the reaction... and it worked.
[chuckles] I became like you.
Right, so what happened?
This ability to travel through
time revealed a truth.
My fate was to become
your greatest enemy.
I was never going to be The Flash,
so I became the reverse of
everything that you were.
The more people you saved,
the more you were loved,
the more I had to take from you.
That is why you killed my mother?
That's why you ruined my life?
Because you couldn't be me?
I became better than you!
I am the one thing you
cannot stop, Flash!
No, no, no.
Not anymore.
Our race is over.
And you lost.
I've learned what time
period you're from, Flash.
And one day soon, I'll learn your name.
♪
Caitlin: We need you in the cortex now!
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
What's happening?
He's experiencing an
uncontrollable amount
of electrical energy in his brain,
putting him in a prolonged
state of chronic seizing.
What? Can you stop it?
I don't know.
- Hold him down!
- We're trying!
- Sedate him, Snow, now!
- Come on! Come on!
Benzodiazepine. This should do it.
[dramatic music]
♪
Finally.
- [gasps]
- Oh!
What? What was that?
What's going on? Where the hell am I?
- Cisco!
- It's the time line.
What? What are you talking about?
When you... when you
captured Reverse-Flash,
we ruptured the time line.
That's what this...
All the blood and the
seizures and that and all...
Cisco is being affected to... to...
By the changes to the time line.
The changes to the past or the
changes to the present...
This is what this is. We
need to do something.
- We need to do it fast.
- Like what?
We need to restore the time line.
Barry, you need to get Reverse-Flash
and send him back to the
future as quickly as possible.
- What? Are you...
- Barry...
I just caught him! You
want me to let him go?
Keeping him here is killing Cisco!
Barry, if this is the
only way we can save him,
you got to do it!
Of Thawne! I can't.
Okay, all right, look.
I destroyed the tachyon
drive in the speed machine.
There's no way it'll
reach a speed necessary
to send him back home.
- You can.
- What?
Your speed coupled with Thawne's speed,
that'll be enough to catapult
him through the time continuum.
You can do it.
♪
All right. All right.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Time to send you home.
The time paradox. Yeah.
You've all messed with something
you don't understand.
Can you do me a favor and just shut up?
[laughs]
And how exactly are you
going to send me home?
Don't worry about it.
You fixed Dr. McGee's tachyon device?
No, I came up with a different method.
♪
Is that so?
Uh-huh.
Who are you?
♪
No one of consequence.
No.
I doubt that.
♪
I win again, Flash.
All you have to do is provide
him with enough momentum
to get him past the space-time barrier.
- All right.
- Hey, listen to me.
Thawne knows about you.
Right here, right now.
This is where he learns
about you, all of you.
It's how he knows about S.T.A.R. Labs,
how he knows about me...
The Harrison Wells from this Earth.
And there's nothing I can do about it.
There's nothing you can do about it.
This is his origin story,
and it's going to happen
no matter what you do.
But right here, right now...
you can send him back to his time.
You can save your friend.
You can save Cisco and then
move on with your life.
This could be a good thing.
You can finally let go of him.
I could throw him three
centuries from now.
He'll always be a part of me.
♪
Time to send you back where you belong.
We'll meet again soon, Flash.
I know.
And every time, I'll be ready for you.
♪
[suspenseful music]
Hurry.
♪
He did it.
[dramatic music]
♪
He's gonna be okay.
I don't understand what we're doing here.
Well, just like you, I
thought that if I could find
my doppelganger on this Earth,
I could replace my damaged cells
with some of his healthy ones.
And believe me, I was
just as shocked as you
when I couldn't find a
Jay Garrick anywhere
on this planet.
Took me a while to figure it out...
but eventually I found him.
[plaintive music]
His name is Hunter Zolomon.
Hunter Zolomon?
Why doesn't he have the same name as you?
From what I could gather,
his mother died during childbirth.
He bounced around from family to family,
but eventually was adopted
and raised by the Zolomons.
♪
But why does that mean he can't help you?
My DNA was mutated when
I became a speedster.
There's only one way to reverse
what's happening to me.
If we can catch Zoom, I
can get my speed back.
Then let's finally figure out
the best way to do that.
♪
[keys clacking]
[knock at door]
♪
- Wally, hi.
- Hey.
Um, do you want to come in?
No, I-I can't stay. I just...
I wanted to tell you that
I'm gonna take your advice
and go see my mom.
Okay.
Iris, I was... I was wondering
if you would come with me.
Yeah, yeah, I would... I would love that.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
Um...
♪
[groans]
My head feels like it's in a vise.
What happened?
I think you vibed one
too many dimensions.
Maybe I should stop doing that.
[laughs]
Yeah, he's gonna be fine.
How did you, um... get
the vibing to stop?
We sent Thawne back to his time.
You let him go?
I couldn't let him take
another person I cared about.
♪
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Okay, I think I need a Big Belly burger.
- Anyone?
- I'm good, thank you.
- Yeah, no pickles.
- Two triple triples, please.
You got money?
Mmm.
Rest up, all right? I'll be out here.
So, Patty... she's on a train
to Midway City right now, huh?
Mm-hmm, I had to let her go too.
Mm-hmm, I was thinking
about what you said,
that part of being The Flash
is that you have the ability
to do amazing things
that nobody else can do.
And we see now that a
hundred years from now,
you'll still be doing them.
But the other part is,
you're gonna be loaded with sacrifices,
and you're gonna have
hard choices to make,
and there's gonna be a lot
of things where eventually
you'll have to let 'em go.
You got to be ready for that.
I am. I'm ready.
That's my boy.
[cell phone vibrates]
That's weird.
- Hey.
- Patty: Barry, I'm on the train.
There's a... there's a man with a gun.
All right, hold on.
I-I-I'll get you help.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Is everyone okay?
- Everyone's fine.
It was a false alarm, but...
thanks for coming so fast, Flash.
[gentle music]
♪
Just want to make sure
everything's okay before I go.
Don't worry.
Everything's good.
♪
Good-bye, Barry.
- sync and corrections by Caio -
- www.addic7ed.com -