[GASPS]
MAN [ON TV]:
Hello! Hello there.
There's only two boxes left.
At this rate, we'll be finished by Easter.
[JOE CHUCKLES]
Don't even.
Okay, the only red-suited dude
I want in this house right now...
...is Kris Kringle, you got it?
[BARRY SIGHS]
[JOE LAUGHS]
Uh, these ornaments
are not gonna hang themselves.
Grandma Esther's recipe.
-Light on the bourbon.
-Thank you.
[PHONE RINGING]
I always loved her definition of "light."
And the Christmas tradition continues.
Detective West. Yeah?
All right.
Sorry, kids.
DA wants to ask me some questions.
Make sure there's nog left
when I get back.
No promises.
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
-What's happening?
IRIS: Heh.
Come on!
Come on. We're doing this already?
Christmas isn't for a few days.
-I couldn't wait any longer. Here.
-Agh. Okay.
Oh, wait! Me first. Heh.
-My mother's wedding band?
-A replica, yeah.
You were devastated
when you lost the real one.
-Our fifth grade field trip to the zoo.
-To the zoo.
You cried for weeks.
Here.
-You remembered.
-Yeah.
Steel trap.
I don't know what to say. Oh.
-My gift sucks in comparison, by the way.
-No.
-All right!
-Heh-heh.
It's supposed to be the best on the market.
I thought you could use a new one.
-It's lame, I know.
-No!
No. This is great. I love it.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, of course.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Hey, babe.
-Hey, Barry.
Nice ring.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's an exact replica of my mom's.
Barry got it for me.
Very thoughtful, Bar.
-So are we tree-trimming?
-Yeah.
Come on.
BARRY:
Merry Christmas.
Just a small token of my gratitude
for everything you guys have done for me.
I think I speak on behalf of my colleagues
when I say you've been a gift for us, Barry.
What's that?
This is compliments of Iris.
Grandma Esther's famous eggnog.
That's what I'm talking about.
Ahem. Maybe later for me.
Wouldn't wanna drink and drive.
-Did I say something wrong?
-No.
No, man. He, um...
This used to be his favorite time
of the year...
...but the accident happened before
Christmas, so it ruined the holidays.
CAITLIN: I'm gonna go get him a present.
Maybe that will cheer him up.
-Thank you very much.
-Yeah.
What are you doing for Christmas, Cisco?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
IRIS: The fact I asked you for your shirt size
should in no way indicate...
...that I am getting you something
shirt-related for Christmas.
Barry seemed a little odd today.
I'm pretty sure he wasn't psyched
I came by.
You ever think...
...he maybe might...
-...like you?
-Oh. What?
-No.
-Friends don't give friends wedding bands.
He wasn't...
He wasn't proposing to me, silly.
He and I are just best friends.
Well, then he won't be bothered by this.
A bit early...
...but I couldn't wait.
[SIGHS]
I figured, we'd been together a year now.
You pretty much stay there most nights,
anyway.
I love you.
-That's a yes, I take it.
-Heh.
CAITLIN: It was that
or Stephen Hawking's new autobiography...
...and we both know how he feels
about Hawking.
Okay, I'll talk to you later. Bye, Cisco.
MAN: Merry Christmas, doc.
-Thank you, Jimmy.
And to you.
Hey, doc, I know it's a big secret,
but can you give me a hint?
What exactly are you
working on in there?
The future.
[ALARM BEEPING]
Doctor, get inside. Lock down the facility.
[GRUNTING]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Hey.
What are you thinking?
The blood-splatter patterns
and trajectory of the remains...
Only a high-speed collision
could have done this.
But to cause this type of damage
to a human in this space?
Whatever hit them
would have to have been moving fast.
EDDIE:
Get this.
The witness says all he saw was a blur.
Sound familiar?
You saw a blur? What was it?
Whatever it was,
it was looking for something.
What did it look like?
Agh. Like a man...
...in some kind of yellow suit.
Okay.
I have to check my files.
Joe, you heard him.
The man that killed my mom, he's back.
I know.
He's been in town for a few weeks now.
He paid a visit to me at the house.
He took the evidence from your mom's case.
-Why wouldn't you tell me this sooner?
-I couldn't.
-Why?
-Because he threatened to kill Iris.
The witness described seeing a yellow blur.
Just like the one that killed Barry's mother.
Then we need to get cracking
and stop this speed psycho.
That... I wasn't trying to give him a name.
The crime scene at Mercury Labs
was on a floor with highly secured vaults.
-Witness said he was looking for something.
-He wanted it badly enough to kill for it.
What do you know about Mercury Labs?
Mercury was one of S.T.A.R. Labs'
major competitors until our little setback...
...and then it catapulted to the forefront,
led by...
...Dr. Christina McGee,
brilliant but egocentric physicist.
CISCO: It says here, Dr. McGee has secured
half a billion dollars in private funding...
...to develop, and I quote, "prototypes
for the technology of the future."
Well, I'll be...
Tina's messing with tachyons.
-Superluminal particles.
JOE: Of course.
So, what could someone do
with one of those...?
-Tachyons.
-Thank you.
Well, I don't know. Become invincible.
If you could devise a matrix stable enough
to harness their power, you could...
-...travel faster than light.
BARRY: He's gonna try again.
We need to get what Mercury has
and use it as a lure.
Exactly right.
Cisco, Caitlin, start engineering a trap.
-You got it.
-Of course.
Thanks.
Iris.
Caitlin. What are you doing here?
-Oh. It's been a long day.
-It's only noon.
-I didn't sleep much last night.
-Well, me, either.
Um, so I was catching up on your blog...
...and this story caught my eye about a man
whose head and hands burst into flames.
-The burning man.
-Yeah.
I haven't updated that story in a while,
but there are some reports I could send you.
That'd be great. Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
-Girl to girl?
-Sure.
Barry's been acting different
around me lately.
Like he's keeping
some sort of secret from me.
Is there anything that you know about
that I should know about?
Not that I can think of.
However, if you feel like
Barry's keeping something from you...
...you should probably
just ask him yourself.
Yeah. Thanks.
Of course.
-Yes, I need some caffeine.
-Okay.
-Barry Allen. Thank you for coming in.
-Dr. Tina McGee.
I assume this is about
last night's break-in?
Yes and no.
That's usually how things are
with you, Harrison.
BARRY: Whoever broke in was after
one of your prototypes.
You'll have to narrow that down.
We have hundreds of projects.
One containing tachyonic particles.
We've had encouraging success
with tachyons, yes...
...but there's still a significant gap between
our prototype and any real-life application.
We were hoping you would lend us
your prototype to use as a lure.
Us? You're assisting
the police now, Harrison?
I'm a consultant on this particular case.
Listen, once this man is apprehended
your prototype will be promptly returned.
You know nobody wants to ensure
the future's technology more than me.
I appreciate the C.C.P.D.'s concerns,
Mr. Allen...
...but Mercury is quite capable
of protecting its own assets.
Good luck with your manhunt.
Hey, Caitlin, check this out.
I think we can fashion
an electronic barrier. Right?
We set up a ton of super capacitors,
we smooth out the inflection points...
...and voilà, a kick-ass force field
to trap the Opposite Flash.
That was me testing out a name. Heh.
What do you think?
Are you okay?
[SIGHS]
Ronnie's alive.
I saw him, Cisco.
-I think he was following me...
-Caitlin.
Ronnie died.
He was vaporized in the accelerator
when it went critical.
Ronnie's alive,
and he's out there, alone and scared.
And I need your help to find him.
[SOUND OF THUNDER]
Ouch.
-Your bruise is already healing.
-Still hurts, though.
Not for much longer, honey.
Here, come on.
I'll keep the light on for you.
Were you ever afraid of the dark?
If I turn this light off now,
would you be scared?
-No.
-That's because I'm here with you.
See, you're not afraid of the dark, Barry.
You're afraid of being alone in the dark.
And that goes away
when you realize something.
You're never really alone.
Time for bed.
-I'm thirsty.
-Ah, now you're stalling.
But I got you covered, buddy.
Good night, slugger.
Sweet dreams, my beautiful boy.
You can turn off the light.
[SOUND OF THUNDER]
[NORA SCREAMING]
Mom! Mom!
HENRY:
Nora!
Barry! Heh.
I called your name, like...
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Your mom's case.
I used to study this board every day.
Lately, I haven't looked at it
as much as I should have.
I didn't know you did that.
I guess there's still some stuff about me
you don't know.
Eddie asked me to move in with him.
I said yes. Heh.
Wow. Heh.
You guys are moving pretty fast, huh?
Well, I mean, it's been a year.
Eddie thought you might
feel weird about it. Heh.
Well, I don't...
Why would he say that?
He thinks that you like me.
Romantically.
I mean, honestly,
it sounds even silly suggesting it.
Um...
Eddie's wrong.
And if I've seemed weird before,
it's just that...
...this year has gone by really fast...
...and I didn't realize how far along
in your relationship you were.
Heh.
That's what I told him.
Well, I guess I should get going.
Bye.
[SIGHS]
[SOUND OF THUNDER]
It was you.
You were the one in my house that night.
You killed my mother!
Why?
If you wanna know that...
...you're gonna have to catch me.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
Not fast enough, Flash.
[BARRY YELLING AND GRUNTING]
-Who are you?
-You know who I am, Barry.
I don't know who you are.
But you do, Barry.
We've been at this a long time, you and I.
But I'm always one step ahead.
It is your destiny to lose to me, Flash.
Just as it was your mother's destiny
to die that night.
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
He acted like he knew me,
like we'd done this before.
He was antagonizing you, Bar.
I would get close, and he'd pull away.
This was just some sick game to him.
You'll catch him, we'll help.
No, you don't get it, all right?
His speed, it's beyond me.
I'm not the fastest man alive. He is.
So how do we catch somebody
that even I can't keep up with?
The beautiful thing about force fields
is they're impervious to speed.
We're almost finished
fabricating the trap.
All that remains is for Detective West
to procure the bait.
I'm on it.
Barry, why don't you stay here?
No, Joe, today is not the day
to tell me to stay behind.
TINA: If the judge was gonna sign this,
he would've done so already.
You don't want this investigation to get
any more public than it's already been.
This has Harrison Wells written all over it.
I am not giving you my tachyon prototype.
It was quite the tour
of your facility, doctor.
You were fine
to let us dumb cops walk around...
...but I majored in physics
and chemistry...
...and I saw a lot of stuff that
Science Showcase Magazine would love.
So should I call their editors directly,
or just leave a few posts on their website?
You'll have the device within the hour.
I see why Harrison holds you in such
esteem, Mr. Allen. You're very much alike.
Nicely done.
-Hey, Joe, you got a second?
-Not now, Eddie.
I read the witness statement.
The Flash was there.
-I know you got something in the works.
-Yeah, but you don't want any part of this.
I got a task force approved to capture him,
and I want in.
I'm not asking permission, Joe.
Excuse me?
If my task force isn't part of this,
I'll go to Captain Singh.
I'll tell him something's going on
and you're not talking. I'm sorry.
You'd do the same thing if you were me.
Fine.
CISCO: We follow the ionized particles,
and that should lead us right to him.
The CPM's are increasing.
[DEVICE CRACKLING]
We should have told Dr. Wells and Barry.
CAITLIN:
No, not until we're sure it's him.
Oh, wow.
Look, Ronnie is not
like you remembered him.
-What does that mean?
-Just don't freak out when you see him.
CISCO: Oh, I really wish that was
because the batteries are dead.
CAITLIN:
Ronnie?
Ronnie.
It's me, Cait.
Look, I brought Cisco with me.
We're here to help you.
You were in an accident.
Do you remember?
I'm not Ronnie.
Yes, you are. You're Ronnie Raymond.
I'm not Ronnie. I told you that.
Now get away from me.
Look, we need to take you back
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
We'll help you remember who you are.
-Agh!
-Firestorm.
CISCO:
The tachyon device is in place.
BARRY: You think it'll work?
-It'll work.
So how do we advertise to him
that the prototype's here?
We'll take care of that.
What's the problem?
Look, Barry...
...me and Dr. Wells have spoken...
...and we think it would be best
if you weren't here for this.
What are you talking about?
-You're too close to this.
-Maybe you're not close enough.
If you hadn't been too scared
and warned me weeks ago...
...I could have been prepared for this.
I think we can all appreciate
Joe's concern for Iris, Barry.
That's why I have to be here.
I'm the best chance at catching him.
Not right now, not in this state.
This man stabbed my mother through
the heart and sent my father to prison for it.
This is my fight.
Not today, son.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
Caitlin...
...don't worry.
Hey.
Now that we know he's out there,
we will find Ronnie again.
Why?
So we can throw him in there
with all the other metahuman psychos?
I used to play this game in my head.
What would I give up
for just one more minute with him?
My house, my career...
...the rest of my life?
Today I finally got that minute.
And I wish I hadn't.
Seeing him like that, what he's become...
Dear God...
...I wish he had just died that day.
[SOBS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Merry Christmas, slugger.
Merry Christmas.
You all right, Barry?
I screwed up, Dad.
After years of searching...
...I finally found him.
I found the man who killed mom.
The man in yellow,
the one in the lightning.
He's out there, and I had him.
He got away.
I was so close.
I promised you
that I would get you out of here.
Every day you spent in here
has been because of him.
Until today.
Now you're in here because of me,
and I'm so sorry.
[SOBS]
Barry.
This is not your fault.
Look at me.
I know what you've given up.
Every decision you've made the past 14 years
has been because of me and your mom.
What you studied, why you became a CSI,
even with Iris.
-Iris?
-You're my son.
You don't think I know how you love her?
But you never pursued her.
You were too consumed with
what had happened to me and your mom...
...to let yourself have a life.
Well, let it go now, Barry.
Hear me now.
The man in the yellow suit...
...he's taken enough from us already.
Don't let him take any more.
[DOOR OPENS]
IRIS:
Hey.
Just in time. I am almost done.
Agh. Are there awards for tree-trimming?
Because this is award worthy.
[SIGHS]
Are you okay, Bar?
I love you, Iris.
Oh, I love you too.
When we were kids, I loved you before
I even knew what the word love meant.
And then my mom died, and I had
to go live with the girl I had a crush on.
Look...
...there were so many times
that I wanted to tell you.
Junior prom,
when I went away to college...
...when I came back from college,
nights that we stayed up talking...
...all the birthdays, all the Christmases.
But I never did. I just... I kept it in.
After I lost my mom and my dad...
...I was afraid
that if you didn't feel the same way...
...I would lose you too.
That's the irony.
I was so scared of losing you that I did.
I know I've had our whole lives
to tell you this...
...and you're with Eddie now, and I know
my timing couldn't be any worse...
...but I just...
I couldn't lie to you anymore.
I'm sorry.
[EXHALES]
Okay.
CISCO:
Sending out another pulse.
You certain this trap will work?
CISCO:
I've sent up three charges in open satellite.
If anyone's looking for tachyonic particles,
they'll know we got them.
Let's see what we caught.
Cisco, lights.
Sure thing, Dr. Wells.
Detective Thawne?
Would you like to read him his rights?
Joe, what are you doing?
Getting some answers.
Fourteen years ago,
you murdered Nora Allen.
I wanna know why. Why?
Dr. Wells, we meet at last.
What do you want
with the tachyonic particles?
My goals are beyond your understanding.
Oh, I don't know...
...I'm a pretty smart guy.
I knew you were exceptionally fast. Any trap
we manufactured would have to be invisible.
I knew your cells could repair themselves
at extraordinary speed...
...so you could withstand the damage
this is doing to your body right now.
The supercapacitors,
the containment field is fluctuating.
-They need to get out of there now.
WELLS: The reason I know all this...
...is because your powers are almost exactly
like those of the Flash.
Oh, I'm not like the Flash at all.
Some would say I'm the reverse.
Dr. Wells, evacuate. Get out of there now.
Dr. Wells!
[WELLS GRUNTING]
Cisco, turn off the barrier!
That thing's gonna get out.
Cisco, he's gonna kill Wells!
Find him!
[PHONE BUZZING]
Don't move or we will shoot!
I warned you not to hunt me.
[YELLS]
[BARRY YELLING]
Barry!
Our race is not yet done.
See you soon, Flash.
[BARRY GROANS]
Don't look for me again.
Why did it...
...not kill me?
I don't know, Eddie.
But you know more
than you've been telling me.
They're called metahumans.
Metahumans?
People with very powerful abilities.
You and me...
...are the only guys on the force
that know what's really going on.
And we need to keep it that way...
...so nobody else gets hurt.
Can you do that?
And the Flash?
Do you know who he is?
Yeah, I do.
He's the guy
that saved both of our lives tonight.
I've been going over the data. I don't know
why the containment system failed.
I must have missed something.
-I'm sorry.
-It's not your fault, Cisco.
But if you both feel a need
to apologize for something...
...you might start with not telling me
that Ronnie is still alive.
I asked Cisco not to say anything.
Once I saw what Ronnie had become,
I needed...
I needed time to see
if I could make him whole again.
-I'm sorry. I know you're mad.
-No.
I don't know what I would have
done differently in your situation.
I know I've made you a lot of promises.
I know I've not been able to keep them all.
But on my life, I promise you this:
We will bring Ronnie home.
JOE:
Hey, Bar.
You know, my mom traveled
around the world twice.
She spent a semester abroad in Spain.
She loved it so much
that after she graduated she went to Europe.
Didn't stop till she'd been
to a few dozen other cities.
She always wanted to go back,
but she never got a chance.
I offered to send you abroad
when you were in college.
Yeah, I know, I remember.
I couldn't take off.
I mean, the truth is...
...I'm stuck here...
...in Central City.
Fear has kept me in that living room
for 14 years.
[SIGHS]
Joe, I'm...
I was mad at you for being scared.
But...
...I mean, the truth is,
I was the one that was scared.
I've been afraid of the man in yellow for...
...my whole life.
That's why I lost.
When you first moved in with us,
I thought it was gonna be too much.
I'm already a single dad...
...finances were tough, and you were
a little boy who just lost his mother.
[CHUCKLING]
But, man, was I wrong.
Within two weeks you had changed
the dynamic of the house.
Suddenly the house was filled with this...
...light...
...this energy.
I mean, you brightened up everything.
You'd seen more darkness
than any man will in a lifetime...
...and you never let it dim your soul.
So there I was thinking that
I'm changing your life by taking you in...
...but the truth is...
...you changed mine.
So don't lose that light now, Bar.
The world may need the Flash...
...but I need my Barry Allen.
-Let's go home.
-Yeah.
-Hey!
-Hey.
-What are you guys doing here?
-I invited them.
Where's Dr. Wells?
CAITLIN: Uh, he wasn't feeling up
to a social gathering...
...but he appreciated the invitation.
-Eggnog?
JOE: Yes.
-Merry Christmas, Barry.
-You too, Eddie.
Hey, I...
I just wanted to say...
...I heard you're moving in together...
...and I'm really happy for you.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas. Heh.
JOE:
Mm.
A day like today, Grandma Esther's eggnog
seems a little light on the bourbon.
-Hey, Joe.
-Mm?
-I saw something weird tonight.
-Yeah, Cisco, I saw it too.
No, I mean...
...when the Flash and the man in yellow
were going bumper cars on each other...
...I was watching the electricity
coming off of them.
Yellow and red electricity.
When Barry was a kid...
...he saw red and yellow lightning
in his house the night his mother died.
There were two of them.
The man in yellow
may have killed Barry's mother...
...but there was another speedster there
that night.
IRIS:
Dad, it's time.
Okay, let's see.
[ALL LAUGH]
[IN REVERSE FLASH'S VOICE]
Merry Christmas.