- Previously on "The Flash"...
- Council of Wells.
Some of the brightest
minds in all the multiverse.
There's still another cryogenic
anomaly in my DNA.
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
The more I try to use my brain,
the sooner I'm going to lose it.
- They know what DeVoe's doing.
- Separate satellites working
together for a single purpose?
DeVoe wants to remove the intelligence
of everyone on Earth?
Just like mine.
Iris?
Sorry, babe! Go back to sleep.
Iris...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just one second. Let me just...
Let me just get this
last sentence down, okay?
Why... why are you still
awake? What is all this?
This is...
every file, every report, every footnote
that I could find on
DeVoe. I dug it all up
when I woke up in the
middle of the night.
I just... I couldn't
stop thinking about DeVoe
and his machine.
And now that he has
all of the satellites,
I mean, he could turn on
the machine at any point.
And not knowing is maddening,
but at least I know
what he's planned, right?
But everyone else in the
city, they are oblivious.
Which is why I decided
that I need to write
a piece about it.
- An article?
- Exposing every single detail
of his maniacal plan.
- Oh...
- I think that if people
in this city knew what he was up to,
then maybe they could
protect themselves.
Barry, I really think
this is exactly what we need
to change the tide against DeVoe.
So I'm gonna go upstairs,
I'm gonna take a shower,
and when I come back,
I need you to tell me
everything you know about
that flying chair
and how he uses it to body hop and...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So last night, Harry, Cisco, and I
were up all night writing
all the different algorithms
we could think of involving
the satellite tech that DeVoe stole.
We think DeVoe plans to position each
of his five satellites
at specifically calculated
- points around the globe.
- And when the quantum computers
in each satellite link up...
He'll use that network to basically emit
a series of dark matter bursts.
That will reboot the pre-frontal cortex
of every man, woman,
and child on this Earth.
Well, we need to nip this in the bud.
We can't let him
launch those satellites.
Yeah, but I mean, how are
we supposed to find him?
I mean, we haven't been able to register
DeVoe's pocket dimension
energy for days.
And with Null's gravitational powers,
he can launch these satellites
from any place at any time.
Yeah, he can.
What are you thinking, Bar?
I think we shoot 'em down.
- Whoa.
- There is one small problem.
DeVoe has Kilgore's powers.
Yeah, he can manipulate
any tech-based weapon
we fire at him.
So we don't use tech.
We use some kind of
organic matter weapon.
Right, like a...
Like a...
You know what? Let's split up,
see what we can find.
Ramon.
DeVoe's not acting.
Why is he not acting?
I don't know, but it doesn't matter.
But it does matter, though.
And if I had my intelligence,
I could figure that out. But I don't.
- I got to get it back.
- No, no, no.
What you need to do is be patient.
We're consulting with, like,
literally every scientist we know.
Why don't you consult with me?
No. Harry...
No, not dumb me, the other mes.
The council.
So I must admit, found your transmission
intriguing, to say the least.
But first...
I have a question for you, Harry Wells.
Tell me, Harry, how does
your "hypothetica"
thinking cap account for
the resonant inductive coupling
of the dark matter transfer?
- Well, the... the inductive...
- Am I speaking to you?
I cannot remember. Oh, wait. I'm not.
The little guy that must be
Cisco, put you in the box.
Put the box in the pocket.
Talking to Harry, a simple question.
How does it account for
the resonant coupling?
It, uh...
Ah!
Ha! I knew it! He doesn't know!
He doesn't know!
Ah! Simple Harry is
truly Simple Harry now.
- No. That's not what's hap...
- Ja, remember,
I put you in the box.
Put the box in the pocket.
Crush the box! In the pocket.
This is very simple what has happened.
Your "hypothetical" thinking
cap has malfunctioned, hmm,
and left the world's
once formidable intellect
a dum-dum!
- That's not what happened.
- Yeah, that's what happened.
That's what happened.
Poor Harry.
- Herr Wells...
- Ja.
Are you gonna help us or not?
- Not.
- Why not?
The Council of Wells is a council
of superior intellects
there to accept the challenge
of others with superior intellects.
It's called the Council of Wells
and not the Council of Dum-Dums!
- Loot at this man.
- I see him.
Is he not one of your own?
Are you telling me you're gonna betray
one of your own because
he doesn't meet some
arbitrary intellectual standard?
Ah! So you do understand.
Ja, unlike your
simple friend, here's what you
now must consider.
Auf Wiedersehen!
No, he's right. I am a dum-dum.
Hey, you are not a dum-dum.
Ramon, come on. Let's face facts.
I've lost most of my
science, lost most of my math.
Language will be next,
and there's nothing
- we can do about it.
- On the contrary, "mon frery"
we're the ones who created
that council of ding-dongs
in the first place, so if
they're not gonna help us,
that leaves us with one other option.
A new council, a smarter council.
A better council.
- Hey, Caitlin.
- Hmm?
Do you have any ibuprofen?
Reading up on all this organic matter
has given me an organic migraine.
Oh, thanks.
You have a little...
Oh! Acupuncture.
Ever since I found out I still have
a cryogenic anomaly in my DNA,
I've been doing every
medical avenue I can think of
to get Killer Frost to emerge.
Mm. You really do miss her, don't you?
Yeah. Killer Frost was a part of me,
and just as I was
starting to accept her,
she was taken away.
I'm running out of ideas.
Hmm, well, I know it's not
exactly the same, but I've had
my fair share of missing persons cases.
And what do you do
when you've hit a wall?
I try to attack it from
a different direction.
If that helps. Anyway, thanks.
We've been attacking this
from the wrong direction.
We know we need a tech-free projectile
to stop DeVoe's satellites,
so we've been looking
for an object when what
we really need is a person.
Amunet.
- Amunet Black?
- I know she's not
the ideal choice, but
Amunet's psychic-powered
alnico shards are not
only deadly powerful.
They're completely immune
to DeVoe's Kilgore powers.
Not ideal? I mean, she kidnapped you.
She tried to sell me into meta slavery.
And she ruined my
bachelorette party, I mean...
- That's not...
- I mean, you're right.
It's... it's admittedly not
as big of a deal, but you know
- what I'm saying.
- Yeah, we can't partner up
with Amunet. She's a criminal.
Snart's a criminal. So's Killer Frost.
We worked with them.
Look, even if we forgave Amunet
for everything she's
done... Which is a lot.
What makes you say she'd
be willing to help us?
I've seen a different side of her.
She's helped me before,
and I believe she'll do it again.
This isn't what I expected
Amunet's hideout to look like.
I might have made a few changes.
Really, boys?
You trying to get us killed?
That's The Flash, you morons.
And Caitlin may look like a librarian,
but she's a coldhearted beast.
Where's Amunet?
Really? No, "Hello, Norvock.
How you been?" You're not even gonna
introduce me to your new boss?
Oh, I'm not her boss. I'm just a friend.
Well, isn't that sweet?
Norvock, where's Amunet?
No one's heard a peep
from her in months.
For all I know, the witch is dead.
So Amunet's gone?
Well, apparently after her
deal with Warden Wolfe took
a nosedive, she's been out of
the meta trafficking business.
Caitlin, do you know
any personal details
that can help us track her down?
Oh, I don't know. Amunet's always been
a private person, sort
of unpredictable and rash,
kind of fly by the seat of your pants.
You know, when she kidnapped
me at Christmas, she said
she used to be a flight attendant.
I think she was on an airplane the night
the particle accelerator exploded.
Okay, that we can work with. Let's see.
Yeah, it looks like there
were 35 flights in the air
in Central City the night of the
particle accelerator explosion.
Cisco, can you access
the flight manifests?
Yes, I can, and I can take
the cruise credentials...
Cross-reference them in
the facial recognition?
Can you not read my mind?
- Huh.
- Her real name is Leslie Jocoy?
Maybe she's operating
under her real name,
- not her pseudonym.
- Well, she didn't have
a criminal record until
the particle accelerator,
- so... it's not a bad plan.
- Right.
CCPD's database has several
prior work addresses for Leslie Jocoy.
All right, let's pay 'em all a visit.
Okay. Dad why don't you
and Caitlin go check out
- the most recent address?
- I'll check out the rest.
- Sounds like a plan.
- And I should get back
to the loft. I need
to pick up a DeVoe file
- for my article...
- Hey, actually,
can I just talk to you really quick?
Um, yeah. Okay.
Just about your article.
I just think maybe
telling everybody about
a meta-human uber-genius
who plans on rebooting
people's brains...
Yeah, but if we don't tell them,
they might find out when it's too late.
Sure, but I don't... I
mean, the team's always liked
to keep what we're working on low-key.
Okay, well, I'll run the idea by them.
No. I-I don't mean no. I just mean...
maybe hold off until
you finish writing it.
Okay. Yeah, I'll hold off.
- You will?
- Yeah.
No, I mean, I get it.
We've never openly shared
this kind of information
with the city before,
and the team will be more
likely to agree with me
if I have a full article
ready for them to read.
So I am gonna hurry up and finish it.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Harry, I give to you...
the emotionally astute
Council of Harrisons.
- Hey.
- There ya are.
H. Wells, what... what
are you doing here?
Those other stiffs, well, they got tired
of my connections
making me tardy to their party, so...
They gave me the boot.
Gave you the... wait,
so I'm not the only one?
Nuh-uh, all of us been kicked out.
All of you have been kick...
You got me a council of rejects.
Well, they're brilliant rejects.
'Ey! Oh, whoa, whoa!
Who you calling rejects?
'Ey, look at this guy.
What are you, sta-nuts?
Allow myself to introduce myself.
Sonny Wells. Earth-24.
At your service. They
call me Sonny on account
of my sunny disposition.
You know, I think that
name kind of works for him.
'Ey, oh, the guy who must be Cisco.
My motto, personally, for me, my motto?
Be kind.
Rewind.
- Be kind. Rewind?
- They're still on VHS.
What?
Hello! Yes, bonjour.
So I am Harrison H.P.
Wells, the Earth-25.
So I must say that it warms me
to see us all bonded by
our faces and our hearts.
You see his scarf? I like that scarf.
Gonna get myself one of them
classy scarves like this guy.
That's a $10 scarf right there.
So anyway, without further ado,
it's time for me to
commence this meeting
with one of my poems, so... allez.
I never knew you.
- I never taste you.
- Mm, taste.
Never smelled you.
Until I do. And now I am hooked-ed.
Mm, saucy.
And, uh, what is this poem about?
- Bread.
- Oh, deep connection.
Food can feed the soul. You know, I once
had this experience
with a hot apple pie...
Okay, you know what?
That's enough sharing
from this side of the
table. How about we let
somebody else share?
Harry, you have the floor.
- No chance.
- Harry.
- No way.
- Come on.
Do the intro.
Why? No.
- I'm not gonna.
- Harry.
- What?
- You have to do
the sharing if you
want the helping, okay?
- Allez, Harry.
- 'Ey.
- I'm Harry.
- How you doin', Harry?
- Bonjour, Harry.
- Howdy, Harry.
We know his name.
So, uh...
here's the thing.
I'm losing my intelligence.
- Whoa!
- Oh, no.
And as Wellses, you
know how very important
our intelligence is, and
so I'm asking for your help
to get my intelligence
back so I can kick some...
So I can help my team.
Will you help me do that?
Non. Non, mais of course, Harry.
Of course we will help
him. We will help you.
Open your heart. We'll open your mind.
Come on, let's do this.
- Okay.
- Lovely.
Hey, Bar, we're at the market.
We'll let you know if we find her.
- Copy that.
- Amunet used to work here?
What did she do, bag groceries?
At least it's not human trafficking.
Let's look around.
Hey, look, when I told you
to look in a different direction
to find your alter ego,
I didn't mean team up with a criminal.
I know how that probably looks.
Yeah, it looks like you want us to work
with Amunet Black so she can help you
with your Killer Frost problem.
I mean, why weren't you
up front with the team
- about that?
- Because I thought
they'd say no if I had my own reasons.
Besides, I actually really
do think Amunet can help us
and help me with my
Killer Frost problem.
Well, how exactly can she help you?
Last year, when I was having
trouble getting a handle
on Killer Frost, I went to her.
She used a black market
piece of tech on me,
a splicer, helped me split Killer Frost.
And you're hoping she
still has this tech.
It worked before. It could work again.
Well, Caitlin you got to tell the team.
Damn.
Somebody saw "Molly's Game."
Mm-hmm.
Hang on a second.
CCPD. This is an illegal operation.
Everybody out of the room.
Leslie.
Caitie.
Leave it to your crafty little brain
to figure out my dark secret.
What are you doing here?
Calling your bluff. I
knew you were still alive.
No one could kill me.
What's with the accent?
It's part of my
disguise. Had to blend in.
Now I'm just your
average American blonde
making an honest living.
Well, a more honest living, yeah?
Besides, you know what they say.
A zebra never changes its stripes.
Flash.
Oh! Flash. You really do stop
all the crime in the city, don't you?
But not today.
We're not here to fight.
We need your help.
Oh, look!
A little hidey-hole for your outfit.
Hi, excuse me. You don't seem
too concerned that
DeVoe is about to launch
a bunch of satellites into space
that are gonna reset all of our brains.
Oh, no, my dear. I
find it very troubling.
The professor turning everyone
in the world into a dimwit
is tragic.
It's brilliant.
But tragic.
So will you work with us?
Help us stop DeVoe?
Just...
that thing...
Why do you still have it on?
My...
It helps me protect my identity.
No.
It's doing a terrible job.
- What?
- Yes, you see,
that stoic jawline, patrician profile.
You're so obviously
the speedster I tried
to procure from the warden.
May he RIP.
- Come on.
- I'm doing it.
- Hello, handsome.
- Hello.
To think I had The Flash in my grasp.
What a pretty penny I could
have gotten for that sale.
- Amunet.
- Yes.
- Focus.
- Ah!
Okay. So...
On the one hand, I am more dictator
than team player.
But on the other...
Professor DeVoe stupefying
the planet would be bad for business.
So I'll do it.
Unfortunately, there is a but.
There usually is one.
You see, in life, I have found
that bigger isn't always better.
But in this case...
You need more shards
to take out something
the size of a satellite.
So where'd you get those?
From the plane I was on the night
the particle accelerator exploded.
They were in the cargo bay
en route to a military facility.
Which conveniently never made
it to its final destination.
You see, normally I would just pop down
to my storage locker to
grab my big job stash,
but last week, a naughty boy... or girl
or non-binary gendered individual...
Snuck in and robbed the place.
Yeah, well, we should
check out your storage unit.
There might still be some clues.
I think I have an old CSI
kit back at the apartment.
Great. You guys are so good.
Sorry, excuse me. Where are you going?
To the kitchen for a spot of tea?
Why don't I take you?
Boy.
Oh, you prepare food in here?
It's not very sanitary.
I wanted to talk to you alone.
I didn't just bring you
here to help us stop DeVoe.
An ulterior motive.
How furtive and apropos.
After all, why go through all the hassle
of procuring me when Killer Frost
could quite easily just ice blast
those satellites down?
Killer Frost is gone.
I haven't been able
to get her to appear ever since DeVoe
used one of his powers on her.
Remember last year when I came to you
because Killer Frost was taking over?
You fixed me.
Mm.
My transmodular genetic splicer.
I need to use that splicer again.
Caitie.
One of the reasons why
I was so willing to help
you and your friends with
your professor situation
is because, well, quite literally...
it also benefits me.
But giving you my
splicer, not as beneficial.
What if I make you a deal?
You give me the splicer.
Killer Frost and I
will do you one favor.
Oh, that is a tempting offer.
But unfortunately my splicer
was stashed right alongside
my additional shards.
In your ransacked storage unit.
Okay, wherever we find your shards,
we should also find the splicer.
- Ding, ding, ding.
- So do we have a deal?
You'll give me the splicer
as soon as we recover it?
I'll even tie a little bow on it.
Ladies and gentlemen, hang
on to your wigs and keys.
Here we go. Harry, turn to
him, the guy who must be Cisco.
- Express yourself.
- Yes, it is best you commence
- with the "I feel" statements.
- Mm.
Wow, like "I feel a yearnin"
or "I feel aroused."
Okay, how...
How is this gonna make
me smarter than DeVoe?
'Ey! Again with DeVoe.
Why you so hung up on this mamalooch?
I think that DeVoe,
for you, this is a guy
that has... well, he's like a leech
upon you, sucking and sucking
and sucking and sucking and sucking.
And all you are left with... is doubt.
I like that. Nature,
red in tooth and claw.
You know, they say to
understand a man's actions,
you got to understand his heart.
Oh, okay, question.
How do you understand the heart
of a deranged maniac?
That guy who must be Cisco
makes a good point here.
Let's all close our eyes and...
take a moment and imagine
that we are all sociopaths
- trying to conquer the world.
- Ah, yes.
What is...
Oh, mais, Harry. Go on, allez.
Put yourself in DeVoe's shoes.
Close your eyes, Harry.
Now what do you see?
What do you smell?
How do you feel?
Dumb. Dumb.
This is not making me any smarter.
But aren't you smarter, Harry?
You must channel your aggression
into love.
I feel like you're mocking me.
Oh! An "I Feel"
statement! Winner, winner.
All right, all right,
all right, progress!
- On that note...
- Wait, wait.
We're not done here, are we?
- Yeah, we're done,
- Yeah, we're done.
- Oui, oui, c'est fini.
- No, no, no.
- Nothing's fini.
- Now, Harry...
You know what they say
about all work and no play.
Leaves no time for making whoopee.
And there he goes.
Look, H.P., come on, we're not done.
- We haven't done anything.
- Non, non, mon frère, désolé.
Parting, such sweet sorrow,
but I must bid you adieu.
Harry from Earth-2, adieu.
'Ey, Harry, everything you need...
you got it right in there.
Remember, you're unbelievable.
Ramon, remind me again...
what's... what's another
word for "huge"?
"Colossal."
Colossal. Great, thank you.
This... was a colossal waste of time!
Here we are.
This is where you kept your stash?
Well, I got something.
Some kind of substance on the lock pin.
Looks like they applied
it to break the door open.
Young man, David Caruso's
got nothing on you.
Thanks.
What is it?
Acid? Cyanide?
Oh, oh! Is it anthrax?
Hematoxic venom.
Oh, that grotty, manky,
plug-ugly prat dare betray me?
I take it she knows who did this.
Yep, and so do you.
- Norvock.
- And I guarantee
that snake for brains will suffer.
If Norvock thinks he can steal from me
and get away with it, he
has got another thing coming.
I can't believe this is happening.
Satellite's not picking
up any of your alnico metal
anywhere in the city.
Norvock may be a moron,
but he's not stupid enough to keep
the stash out in the open.
- Hey, did you find anything?
- Nope.
Norvock and the boxers
weren't at the ring anymore.
Of course not!
Because you and your gang
of heroes tipped him off
that something was up.
Have you expanded the satellite
beyond Central City?
- Yeah.
- What about trying
- facial recognition?
- Yes, of course.
And what about a geological scan
of the metal signature like last time
or having Cisco run
another algorithm to check
the electromagnetic fields in the city?
Yes, Caitlin. I've done all that.
I've run all the tests.
Bit testy with that, Frost. Just...
We're doing everything
we can, all right?
We're gonna find Norvock and the shards.
Caitlin.
Is this about her stolen shards...
or her tech?
What? What tech?
Amunet has splicer
technology that she used
to split Killer Frost last year.
I was hoping to use it
again to get Killer Frost
to come out, but...
it was hidden with her metal shards
in the storage container.
Why wouldn't you tell us that?
Because I made Amunet a deal.
If she helped me, Killer Frost would do
another job for her.
Well, that splicer tech
isn't your only hope.
Yes, it is, Joe. I have tried everything
that I can think of to
get Killer Frost to appear,
and that was my last shot.
So now she's gone for good.
Those weirdos with their feelings.
I'm done talking about my feelings.
What's your problem?
No, it just looked
like you were gonna...
What is this? What are you doing?
I am cleaning up my work station
because I'm not gonna need
it anymore since I'm not
getting my intelligence back.
You don't know that.
I don't know that?
Oh, I don't know that?
Ramon, what's done is done.
You spent all this time
bringing this council together
when your time should have
been used helping the team.
I wasted your valuable
time, and for that...
I apologize.
What are you... What?
- Spill some soup on me?
- No, no, no.
It's just, that was...
that was very real.
That was, like, a very...
Very genuine apology.
Well, I meant it.
Well, I can tell. There's no snark.
You're not throwing anything.
You're right. I'm not. Hmm.
The council might not have
helped your intelligence,
but I think they...
might have shown you a little...
empathy?
You know, DA Cecile Horton said
there's other ways to be intelligent.
Open your heart...
Open your mind.
But it's been so long
since I've been concerned
for other people's
feelings, though, you know?
You know what?
Maybe it is time I consider
someone else's feelings.
Well, I feel...
- DeVoe.
Right? Maybe the council had a point.
The best way for me
to understand DeVoe...
put myself in his shoes.
Yeah.
Is that what you were gonna say?
No, I was gonna say DeVoe.
- Okay.
- That makes sense.
- It does.
- Yeah.
Hey, anything on Norvock?
No, but I do have an update on DeVoe.
It's my finished article.
Barry, look, I'm just
as anxious as you are
about DeVoe, but I really think
that we need to arm the
citizens with information,
- not shield them from it.
- Iris, I'm just...
I'm trying to do
what's best for the city
- and the team.
- And look...
I think that telling
the truth is what's best.
I mean, if we give them all
of the facts to consider,
they will do the right thing.
But how can you be sure about that?
Look, Barry...
I can't deny that you've had
a tough year with DeVoe, but...
his entire goal is to take
information away from people.
If we don't publish this article,
we are no better than he is.
I just... this is...
I think it's too risky.
I know that's how you feel...
and I really want us
to be on the same page.
So... it's your decision.
- Iris...
- I just want you to remember
that The Flash is a beacon of hope
that the people have
always put their faith in.
And now it's time for The Flash
to put his faith in the people.
Ah, there you are.
I couldn't help but notice
your anger and hostility.
Thought your color was blue, not red.
Yes, I'm angry. I've
been angry for weeks
and still no Killer Frost.
And now Norvock's ruined everything.
Oh, Caitie.
I hate to see you so torn up like this.
So I'm going to tell you something
that will cheer you up.
That splicer...
did not cure you.
- What?
- Well, you...
You had come to me so broken...
so needy.
And so I put that piece
of tech on your head, and,
poof, nothing!
It did not work on you.
So you decided to lie to
me rather than tell me that?
Mm! But just because the splicer
didn't technically work doesn't mean
that the results were not the same.
How? That doesn't make any sense.
You're the doctor. You tell me.
It's a placebo.
You see?
It's been inside you the entire time.
Caitie, your power is unlike
anything I have ever seen before,
and no science kit or placebo
is going to explain why you...
Hmm.
A placebo...
A fake.
What are you talking about?
I know exactly where Norvock is.
We were surprised to get the call.
Shouldn't be. I'm running things now.
Amunet's gone.
But she did leave behind
something very valuable.
30 times stronger than steel.
You can assemble them
in any shape you like.
And best of all...
they're loaded with
enough potential energy
to flatten a city.
- We know where Norvock is.
- Just when I thought
I'd considered every option
for where Norvock might be skulking,
I remembered whenever the fuzz
used to be onto one of our deals,
I would plant a rumor
that it was going down
at a false location.
Ah, a fake-out to keep "the
fuzz" off your tracks.
- Mm!
- So that's where we think
Norvock is, in the abandoned
Reynolds substation.
Underground. That's
why the shards weren't
- registering on the satellite.
- All right, why don't
the three of us go get your shards?
Then we'll be armed and ready
to take out DeVoe's satellites.
I'm coming too. I'll get the cold gun.
Oh, goody, a group foray.
Dibs on cashing in Norvock's chips.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- No killing.
- That was not a stipulation
when I agreed to join this crew.
Okay, Amunet, look, I
know how you usually work,
but I can handle this fast
and without an casualties.
Okay. 'Tis a bit time-consuming
to remove blood from metal.
This deal's off. Those
shards belong to Amunet.
Well, if that decrepit hag
didn't want them stolen,
she shouldn't have told me
- where she hid them.
- Decrepit?
That's a big word for such a small man.
Amunet, I've got this.
There are some things that a woman
just cannot delegate.
We agreed, no killing.
That'll make this next part easy.
Joe, the shards are in there.
We can't let them get away.
Barry, what's going on?
Your vitals are going through the roof.
- Venom!
- Like the venom
on Amunet's locker. I'm on it.
You are just as vile as
that thing in your head.
Took a while to get this made.
Now you can't use those
things against me anymore.
You always underestimated me.
Caitlin, get back! Over here!
- Iris...
- Barry, there is no antidote
for meta-human venom that potent.
You're gonna have to
phase through it now
before it gets to your heart.
I'm running out of ammo.
They'll hit me before
I hit them with this.
Damn.
We've been looking at this
from the wrong direction.
What... what are you doing?
Nice!
Hmph!
I've never understood your superpower.
Are you a man with a snake
or a snake with a man?
Amunet! Don't kill him.
He's more than earned it.
It's not about him. It's about you.
Caitlin.
Amunet, there is a good part of you.
I truly believe that.
Fine.
But the snake has got to go.
Like Norvock, I must be on my way.
Amunet, no! Hey!
You leave, there's no way we
can stop DeVoe's satellites.
She was never gonna help us.
She just wanted her metal.
Oh... truthfully, I did consider it.
I did. But a good player
knows when to fold.
And the professor certainly
has a better hand, so...
don't try to stop me.
After all, I am packing.
There is no where you can
go that DeVoe's satellites
won't reach you. If you leave now,
you'll be mind melted
just like the rest of us.
Good point.
Just for the record,
this is not me helping.
It is entirely self-preservation.
Filled with shrapnel and bound with
my meta-human je ne sais quoi.
Pull a shard, throw it, it will deliver
one savage concussive blow.
But you only get one shot.
I know you won't waste it.
Go save the world, my darling.
And she's gone.
At least she didn't
leave us empty-handed.
Eye snakes.
Why did it have to be eye snakes?
Trust me, man, it wasn't
as cool as it sounds.
Guy's, I'm sorry I got so
worked up with Amunet around.
- It's okay.
- Yeah, and Amunet did give us
the alnico metal projectile bomb.
I still think it's our
best bet at stopping DeVoe.
- We just need to figure out how to fire it.
- Yeah.
Cisco, can you breach that thing?
Me? No way.
My energy field can't
even reach outer space.
'Kay, well, we need to find
another solution, and we need to find it
before DeVoe launches those satellites.
Well, actually, thanks to Ramon
and the Council of
Harrisons, we may have an idea
about why DeVoe has not
yet launched his satellites.
He put himself in DeVoe's shoes.
And I thought, well, if
I was this ultra-genius
moving around in a floating
chair, how would I feel?
You'd feel nothing.
You'd be sociopathic.
- Mm.
- Right, but...
to me, I wouldn't consider
myself sociopathic, right?
No, all my actions would be driven
by the one thing that I
care most about, right?
- And...
- So if you're not acting...
If I'm not acting, then I don't have
the one thing that I care most about...
my wife.
You guys need me to walk
you through this? So this...
No, we... we get it, Harry.
It's kind of complicated, but okay,
I'll take you at your word.
Actually, that took a lot out of me.
I'm gonna go have a nap.
Well, we can work with that idea.
Yeah, I will fire up the satellite
and see if I can find Marlize.
And I'll start figuring
out how to launch
this psychic dark matter-infused
metal shrapnel bomb.
No big deal.
Joe, do you want to get
a cup of coffee with me
before you go back to CCPD?
I could use some caffeine after today.
I know you don't get tired
of hearing it, but...
- you were right.
- Well, not about Amunet.
She still betrayed us.
But she knew the truth
about DeVoe, and...
she ultimately made a selfless decision
to help us by giving us the projectile.
And I do have faith
in Central City, Iris.
Because I know that at
the core of every citizen
of this city is... something good.
And I know they'll feel the same way
when they read your article.
Let's tell the team.
Are you sure you want to do this?
You want me to publish my article?
Without a doubt.
We're always stronger, better together.
Kiss me.
Thank you.
Ah-ah, this one's on me. I insist.
Nice. What'd I do to deserve that?
That's for giving me the advice I needed
even when I didn't want to hear it.
Well, when you raise kids,
you get used to giving advice.
So I was convinced
that that splicer technology was the key
to getting Killer Frost back.
But I was wrong.
The splicer was just a placebo,
and it tricked me into manifesting
those somatic results that I wanted.
- You learned that from Amunet?
- Mm-hmm.
I thought the answer was in science,
but it was never gonna be there.
- So what now?
- I'm gonna take your advice.
I'm gonna look in a
completely different direction.
The key to finding Killer
Frost is not out there.
It's in here.
Mm.
- Iris, what's happening?
- Barry?
- What?
- It's the city.
- I posted my article,
and they're responding.
What do you mean? They believed you?
More than that. They want to help. Look.
This guy says he saw DeVoe
on 5th and Knoll two days ago.
Yeah, and another guy
on Crescent and 10th.
This is great.
Iris, this means DeVoe
can't hide from us anymore.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --