My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously, on The Flash...
Why are you here?
Because I wanna go faster,
and you're the only one who can teach me.
Everything you need is on this drive.
It means a lot. You looking after Barry.
Barry's not the only person here
I want to keep safe.
We found Barry's double,
so where the hell am I?
Reverb.
You don't even know how powerful you are.
His name is Hunter Zolomon.
I thought that if I could
find my doppelganger on this earth,
I could replace my damaged cells
with some of his healthy ones.
I've been vibing Zoom.
And every time it's happened,
I've been near that thing.
I saw Jay.
He's Zoom.
Sometimes, terrible things
happen to us when we 're children.
Things that can define who we become,
whether we want them to or not.
Mom!
Run, Barry, run!
Some of us become stronger.
The people who took me in helped me heal,
and move past everything that happened.
They're responsible
for who I've become today.
But I know that I'm one of the lucky ones.
Come on, Barry.
Not everyone gets
that kind of support.
Without it, ldon't know
where I would've ended up.
Or what I could have become.
James.
Who do you think you are?
Do you know
what I went through over there?
Do you know the sacrifices I made for you?
I come back after years of fighting
for this country
and this is my welcome home?
You think you can walk out on me?
I'm your husband!
You're not my husband.
I don't know what you are right now.
I am a hero, Ashley!
No, you're a monster.
Run, Hunter. Run!
Stay, boy!
Hey, it's okay.
Come on.
- Please. Please don't do this...
- Shut up!
No, please! No, please! No, no...
You're gonna wanna see this, son.
No... No. James!
Please. No, James.
No.
No. James!
ASHLEYI No!
Name?
Hunter Zolomon.
Father killed the mother.
Kid saw the whole thing.
Next of kin?
No relatives wanted him.
He is all alone.
Follow me.
And don't dawdle.
Okay, you guys, I'm here.
You got my location?
You good? You don't need to,
like, stretch or somethin?
No, no, no, I'm good, I'm good.
Let's take this tachyon enhancer
out for test drive.
All right.
Ooh, yeah, I feel that.
That is the tachyon device
powering up the Speed Force in your cells
like a quick-charge battery.
- How do you feel?
- Different.
Let's see how long it takes for you
to get back here. On my count.
Three, two, one. Go!
Dang. This thing got you cruisin'.
How fast does he normally go?
Not this fast.
Not even close. Are his vitals okay?
Yeah, they're perfect.
Cool. It's like having a pit-stop
attached to your chest.
Guys. I can go faster.
Do it.
I'm... I'm back. I'm back.
What if... How long was I gone?
Let's put it this way.
You just annihilated your old record.
Yeah, you went four times faster
than you have ever been.
"Four times"?
- That's as...
- As fast as Zoom.
Well, faster. Actually.
Hey, uh, do we think that
we can get this thing smaller?
It kind of sucks.
If it sucks, then yeah.
All right, so now all we have to do
is figure out how to get back to Zoom.
Yes, uh, just a minor issue.
We closed all the breaches
and have no idea how to reopen them.
We're... Wells?
Yeah, I have an idea, Allen.
Let's keep the breaches closed forever.
Forget about the breaches,
forget about Zoom.
Wait, I'm sorry, lthought that
you were on board with this.
No. No.
I said I would help you get faster.
I did not say I would help you
give the man who kidnapped my daughter
and tortured her a chance to do it again.
Hey, we are not gonna let that happen.
Oh, you're not gonna let that happen.
Gosh, lwish I'd known that
the first time.
You don't understand.
Zoom is different than us.
Zoom is not tied to anything.
Zoom does not care for anyone.
I do.
My daughter's out here on
this earth somewhere, I have to find her.
We all have people that we care about.
Zoom will use that against us. Believe me.
Maybe we should just leave it be.
No, no. Look, no, look we're...
We're not turning our backs
on another earth.
We're not gonna let Zoom get away
with everything that he's done.
Right now, there is no way
to another earth, Allen.
Let's keep it that way.
We're getting back to Earth-2.
With or without his help.
Let's go to work.
Hey, where you goin?
We could use your help.
Uh, yeah, I would, it'sjust,
I have a date with Scott.
That's the editor?
Yeah. Yeah.
That's good. No, I'm glad that
you're finding a way to move on
without anything holding you back.
You deserve that.
Yeah, I... Well, lwouldn't have been
able to do it without your support.
- Means a lot to me, so...
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- Yes, for sure.
Well, hey, I mean, if you don't get
this breach problem fixed by tonight,
pencil me in for tomorrow.
I can do that.
Okay.
Man, I love it when you train
- in Keystone City.
- Mmm-hmm.
Hey, you sticking around after dinner?
Me and Wally are gonna watch Formula One.
Mmm.
No, I can't.
I gotta get back to the lab.
I'm still trying to find
a way back to Earth-2.
Can't you just stick Wells on it?
No, he refused.
Doesn't want me or anybody
opening the breaches again.
Well, I can't believe I'm saying this
about a man I shot at
and punched in the face,
but I think you should listen to him.
Why?
Barry, it worries the hell out of me,
the thought that you wanna
go back to Earth-2.
I'm faster now,
I'm faster than I've ever been.
Faster than Zoom.
I can take him down.
All I'm saying is, you already
escaped the hornet's nest once.
Why go back and kick it again?
Hey.
Wally. We got some pizza here
all the way from Keystone City.
Hope it's cool, I brought my laundry over.
Of course. Barry used to
do his laundry here all the time
when he was in college.
That's 'cause those machines in the dorm
always eat your quarters, right?
Actually, I'm not
livin' on campus anymore.
What? Since when?
Since room and board
became way more expensive than I thought.
Man, I can help you out with that.
I mean, I figured your money
must be tight after payin'
all your mother's medical bills.
How much more is it?
No, it's, uh... It's cool.
Come on, Wally, let me help you out.
Plus I got that mini-fridge in the garage.
You can use that, too, if you want.
Joe, I'm good, really.
All right.
Uh, let me just put these in real quick.
Man, I can't figure
that kid out sometimes.
I wonder if his doppelganger's
that complicated.
Hey.
Wow. Um...
Any ideas?
Well, the best plan
we've come up with so far
is to set off a nuclear warhead
next to the city's electrical grid. So...
We're not gonna do that. Um...
I think I thought of something, though.
Tell me everything that you know
about Cisco's doppelganger.
Reverb?
What were Reverb's powers on your earth?
Well, he could tap into the
multi-dimensional energies between earths.
He could see through dimensions,
find breachers.
Like Ramon.
I mean, we saw Reverb
do more than that, though, right?
I mean, we saw him
shoot vibrational bursts out of his hands.
Really painful ones.
What do you mean?
I... I mean, Reverb had the ability
to somehow manipulate
that multi-dimensional energy.
What's your point, Allen?
My point is, if his powers are linked
to the energy
that ties together the multi-verse
and he can manipulate it?
Then he can open a breach
- to any earth he wants.
- Exactly.
And if Reverb could do it,
I could do it, too.
Cisco, lthink that
the way back to Earth-2, is you.
I got nothin'.
Try again. okay?
Barry, what if he can't do it
because he thinks he can't do it?
He can do it, though. You can do it.
You... It's gonna work, okay? And it...
Maybe we're just not in the right place.
Or maybe I'm just not
the right man for the job, right?
Let's go.
Cisco.
I'm sorry, Barry.
It's gonna work.
Detective.
Um...
I need to ask you a...
You've got company.
- Um...
- No, it's cool.
I should be studying anyway.
You know, you kind of look like that guy.
I'm not him.
Okay.
Later, Joe.
Well.
Thank you. Uh, look, I apologize
for droppin' by unannounced.
I just...
Have you had any luck
locating my daughter?
Not yet.
But I've circulated her picture
through every department in the region.
And I've reached out
to some friends in Keystone.
She's smart.
She's gonna know
how to stay hidden. She's...
We'll find her.
Right.
There's another thing also, Detective.
A favor.
I would ask you to talk Barry out of
reopening the breaches to my earth.
I can't do that.
No, you can find a way to change his mind.
For both our children's sakes.
Look, I think it's just as dumb as you do,
but I learned a long time ago,
I can't talk Barry out of anything
once he sets his mind to it.
Zoom is terrorizing
this other world, your world.
He can't let it go.
But look, why don't you do me a favor?
Go with Barry.
Help him.
Help him?
Why would I do that?
Because he's got a much better chance
of defeating Zoom if you're involved.
This area has the highest levels
of residual trans-dimensional energy.
You should be able to
open the breach that used to be here.
It's right here. This is it.
For real?
In this Patch Adams nightmare, right here?
- Yeah.
- Love it.
All right.
Look, dude, if this doesn't work,
I'll stop asking you
to do this, all right?
Okay.
Yeah.
What?
I can't do it.
That's right.
You can't.
What are you doing here? You said...
I know what I said.
But you're not gonna stop, are you?
No.
Okay, Barry Allen,
then I'm gonna do what I can
to make sure you don't get killed.
I recalibrated these to the
electromagnetic frequency of this earth.
It should help you access enough
of the trans-dimensional energy
to manipulate it.
Just like Reverb,
all I'm missing is the guyliner
and the transformation's complete.
Take 'em out for a spin.
It's working.
Keep coming, Cisco. Keep comin'.
Hey, what happened? You were doin' it.
- No, no, no, no. I can't do this.
- What?
I can't. Don't.
Please. Don't ask me to do this.
Please.
Hey, what do we got?
It's your tachyon absorption
enhancer upgrade.
Retrofitted for when it was used
to steal your speed
to now give you more of it.
Almost done.
That's amazing, thank you.
You're welcome.
Hey, is Cisco back yet?
- Have we seen him?
- I haven't seen him.
Check his workshop.
Yeah, all right.
- Hey.
We just came by to see if you guys
needed some help.
- Uh, sure.
- Oh. Yeah.
We can always use an extra set of hands.
- Do you want to help me in the med bay?
- Yeah.
- Some advice?
- Huh.
- This whole Wally thing?
- Uh-huh?
He's not letting me help him.
It's probably 'cause you're not offering
the right kind of help.
Wally doesn't want your help
payin' for a place to live.
He wants you to offer him a place to live.
- Why didn't he just say that?
- I don't know.
- So he does wanna live in our house?
- Yeah, man.
Look, Wally's never
lived with his father before,
and trust me, that is a big deal.
- You're good with it?
- Mmm-hmm.
I mean, you know it's been you and me
for so long, and I love that.
But having Wally around will be cool, too.
Just, we won't get
to have as much pizza from Keystone.
Yeah, it kind of sucks. I'm sorry.
I better get used to that.
They really have a special bond,
don't they?
Yeah, they sure do.
Are you okay?
I don't know what I am.
Last night I was supposed to go on a date.
My first real date since Eddie died.
But at the last second, I just...
I couldn't do it.
Is that because of Eddie
or because of Barry?
I've noticed the way
you've been looking at him recently.
Is it that obvious?
Only to a woman who's been through
the same thing.
Everything seems to be telling me
that Barry and I are meant to be together.
I mean, on Earth-2 we're married.
In the future, we're supposedly married.
And now that I'm finally ready to move on,
I Just wonder
if that should be with Barry.
Everything seems to be
pointing in that direction.
D0 you believe in destiny, Caitlin?
Maybe for you.
Hello?
Joe?
Wally, I'm up here.
- Hey.
- What are you doin?
It's not done, yet.
I mean, you can decorate it how you like.
Make it your own.
Wait, wait, Joe, what is this?
Wally, forgive me.
When Barry and Iris went to college,
they couldn't get away fast enough.
They wanted nothing to do
with their old man.
It didn't even occur to me
that you might feel differently.
It's embarrassing,
but it took Barry to help me see that.
So if you still haven't found
a place to live, live here.
Imean, it's yours. If you want to.
You're serious?
Look, I'm not gonna do your laundry,
and I'm not washing dishes after you...
and this bed is gonna be made
every morning before you leave,
and there will be no beer in that fridge,
but, yeah.
It's yours.
When can I move in?
Whenever you want.
All right.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, man.
Look, um...
I know what it's like.
Zoom, getting in your head.
How scary that can be.
It's not Zoom.
It's me.
What do you mean, it's you?
It's like, right now I'm Anakin Skywalker.
I've got the midi-chlorians,
I've got the goods,
the Force is strong with me.
That is something I can feel.
But if I start opening breaches
into other worlds,
doing all this other crazy stuff
Reverb was doing, then,
what if this is how I become Vader?
Dude, you're never gonna become Vader.
But you don't know that.
That is what happened to Reverb.
He learned how to use his abilities,
and when he felt that...
When he felt that power,
he succumbed to the dark side.
Look, I get it. I... I really do.
Every time I've learned a new ability,
I've been terrified about
what it might mean for me,
what it could do to me, you know?
But you were there with me
when I learned how to run on water.
When I ran up a building
or traveled through time.
Just like I'm going to be there
every step of the way with you.
You got something that Reverb never had,
and that's Caitlin and Joe
and Iris and Wells and me.
Friends who are gonna look out for you.
And we're more than just friends.
We're your family.
So what do you say?
Ready to put those things on again,
go another round?
Let's do it.
All right.
You're all set.
You won't even know it's there.
Because whoever said
aesthetics aren't important?
Not me.
Let's go.
Hey, Cait.
I know how hard this is gonna be for you,
but we have to stop him.
I know, and I wanna be supportive.
I Just...
I can't face Jay.
Whatever his real name is.
What does that mean?
Well, you remember when I was
looking for his doppelganger, right?
Yeah, I mean, you couldn't find him.
Because there is no Jay Garrick
on this earth.
His doppelganger's name is Hunter Zolomon.
Hunter Zolomon?
Are... Are you sure?
Yeah, why?
Well, because on my earth,
Hunter Zolomon
was a convicted serial killer.
That's Jay?
No, that is Hunter.
Last public photo of Hunter Zolomon.
Instantly recognizable to people
from my earth.
On my earth, serial killers are
an anomaly, so a lot of media attention
to this... There was a podcast.
When Hunter was 11, his father
killed his mother right in front of him.
Father sent to prison,
Hunter grew up in the foster care system.
Years later, he was convicted
on 23 counts of murder?
23?
That's, like, some real
Hannibal Lecter-type level.
After the trial,
Hunter was sent to the St. Perez
Mental Asylum for the Criminally Insane.
Given daily electroshock therapy
to cure him of his urges,
and then faded from view.
Until the night your
particle accelerator exploded.
That's right.
The dark matter crept into
the mental asylum.
I'd thought piping the explosion
underground would limit exposure.
I was wrong, all it did was create
an unstoppable monster.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
He's not unstoppable.
Jay doesn't know
that we know who he really is.
He thinks that his past is a secret.
So?
I think I have an idea
of how we can stop him.
Are you sure Jay can't get in here?
Pretty sure. Butjust in case...
How do you use this?
All right, so you aim it
and then you pull the trigger.
Smart-ass.
Barry and Cisco are in position.
Let's hope this thing works.
You ready, buddy?
Yeah.
You've always believed in me.
Thank you.
You got this.
Reverb's doppelganger
has increased his powers.
Hatred is a strong motivator.
You were unwise to reopen the breach.
I'm not gonna let you terrorize
another world anymore.
Without your speed,
you won't be able to stop me.
Let's see.
- Zoom's gaining on Barry.
- He can't catch him.
Better not.
That was close.
Too close.
The tachyon device is working.
Yeah. Here they come.
They're here.
Ah.
You've gotten faster. Good.
There'll be more for rne to take.
You want my speed?
Catch me.
You're gonna wanna see this, son.
- Get him, Barry.
- Lt's working.
No!
How did you figure out who I was?
You made a mistake.
You told Caitlin
who your doppelganger was.
I had to do something to get her
to stop trying to fix me.
She's a smart girl.
And that I was Zoom?
The Velocity-Nine.
When you run fast enough,
it turns a speedster's lightning blue.
We would have helped you.
We would have done anything we could
to save your life.
Not everything.
Caitlin found you a cure!
A temporary one!
I'm dying, Barry!
There's only one thing
that can give me what I need.
And you just don't care how many lives
you destroy tryin' to get it?
How many people you kill?
No, I don't!
That feeling was taken from me
a long time ago.
We're not so different, you know.
What happened to us when we were kids?
You could have just as easily become me.
No.
I'd never become like you.
I got to say...
that was smart
using my parents against me.
Family.
Such a weakness.
Not for all of us.
Well, that's where you're wrong.
It's time I get what I came for.
You're not getting anything from me.
You're not getting anything
from anybody ever again.
On any earth.
You can't lock up the darkness.
What did you just say?
No!
He was right there.
I know.
I mean, we had him.
We had him, I can't believe it.
Wally!
Up here!
Hey, hey, hey.
Where are we? Where are we?
Well, help! Somebody please help!
There's only one person
who can help you now.
The Flash.
The Flash?
Why would he help me?
He doesn't even know who I am.
Someone he cares about
cares about you.
Dad.
Dad, coffee?
We're gonna get him back.
What if we could stop Zoom
through a vibe somehow?
We can weaponize the goggles...
Not enough time to weaponize, Ramon.
Okay, what if we modify the pulse rifle
to emit a low-level EMF?
We don't have the equipment
to modify the pulse levels now.
Then we do another
snatch-and-grab mission.
By the time we
scale those cliffs, Zoom could already...
I need a minute.
Barry, I know you can't
give up your speed to that monster,
but I also know that I wanna get
my son back, and I don't know what to do.
I do.
Wally, I mean, he's...
He's part of the family.
He's a part of our family.
And we do whatever we have to
to keep the ones we care about safe.
No, you... You can't give up your speed.
That's not your decision.
This is the only way, Joe.
Barry, are you sure?
I'm sure.
I mean, we don't even know
if he'll be able to hear me.
He'll hear you.
Isee him.
Wally's alive.
Thank God.
Do you see Jay?
Isee him.
He can sense me.
Jay.
Vibe.
He'll do it.
Barry will give you his speed.
Hey.
Dad!
Wally, hold on. Let him go.
We had a deal.
My speed for Wally's life.
Hand him over and it's yours.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You need to get out of here now.
- I can't.
- Go fast.
- Cisco.
Let's go.
Let's get this over with.
This thing is how I stole
the Flash's speed the first time.
Now all he needs to do is run
and his Speed Force
will transfer into this vial.
But only as long as I calibrate it.
Get to work.
Wells.
One day, I'm gonna knock
that smug expression clean off your face.
So this was your plan all along, huh?
Ever since the skies parted and showed me
another world with another speedster.
Once I saw you, I came here,
figured out what I had to do.
How are you still alive?
We saw you die.
You did.
So what was that? Speed mirage?
Speed mirage?
Uh, no.
Even I'm not that fast.
I knew that I couldn't be
on two earths at the same time.
So I went back in time
and I met another version of myself.
You're a time remnant.
Like the Reverse-Flash.
I also knew that the only way
to make Barry become faster
was if you all witnessed
your old pal, Jay, die.
When did you decide to do that?
Oh, once you closed all the breaches,
went to Earth-2.
Believe me, getting my time remnant
to agree to me murdering him...
Took a bit of convincing,
but once he saw the...
Well, the genius in my plan,
he was all for it.
Who's the man in the iron mask?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Why the charade?
Running around dressed like the Flash?
To give people a hope, Detective.
H0pe?
So I can rip it away from them.
It's so fun pretending to be a hero.
You are no hero.
You're nothing but a monster.
You're a monster.
No!
Barry?
It's all right, Joe.
He's slowing down.
The Speed Force is leaving his body.
He's becoming human again.
Barry, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thank you, Flash!
Jay, stop!
Please.
If anything you ever said to me was true,
or anything we ever shared was real,
then please just let him go.
Please. I know some piece of you
did care for me,
so if you have any humanity left,
then please, let him go.
Caitlin!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::