My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends'
power to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Twelve markers, twelve metas.
Your body's deteriorating
faster than the chair can handle.
I didn't just take Dominic's body,
I took his ability.
Sylbert Rundine
can shrink objects
and return them to original size.
Deacon controls technology.
Becky Sharpe can manipulate luck.
There was nothing keeping him
from going in the meta-wing
and absorbing the powers.
You should be able to change
into anyone you can think of.
How's this?
- I believe you're looking for me.
- It's Ralph.
Barry Allen is hereby
released immediately.
He only wants the bus metas,
he wants their powers.
Why is everyone looking at me
like I'm a dead man?
Addie, hey, what's going on?
- I think you should talk to Cap.
- About what?
Just go see him, Allen.
Okay.
...will no longer tolerate
the behavior that the previous
administration practiced.
Addie said you wanted to see me.
- Yeah. Shut the door.
- I promise you.
We will root out all corruption
at all levels...
...and restore your faith
in public servants.
The name Van Buren is a name
that has always stood for integrity.
I may be the mayor...
We've got a problem
that I'm not sure how to fix.
All right.
Some people don't think
you should be back on the force.
- Because of DeVoe?
- Hmm.
I was cleared of all charges.
I didn't do anything.
I mean, he is alive.
I know, and he's been cooperating.
Coming in, answering questions.
So, what's the problem?
Look, people nowadays
will believe anything.
Fake news, social media.
Allegations are treated as facts.
But DeVoe being alive,
showing up in the courtroom
at your appeal hearing?
Some people in Central City
don't buy it's actually him.
- Who do they think it was?
- Who the hell knows?
But we live in a city
full of meta-humans.
It's a conspiracy theorist's dream.
So, what does this mean?
Are you firing me?
Not firing.
But I have been asked to request
that you take a leave of absence.
By whom?
Thinks it will be easier for everyone.
Restoring the faith and all that.
For how long?
Indefinitely.
Look, Barry.
If you want me to fight
this thing, I'll do what I can,
but this new mayor, she's got a lot
to prove since the Bellows' debacle.
When do you think I can come back?
When everyone believes DeVoe
is really alive and well.
It's not permanent, is it?
Well, he said it was indefinite.
They wouldn't have given you
your ID back if it was for good.
I mean, maybe this is
for the best, Barry.
I mean, you need to prove
that DeVoe is still alive
and you can do that now as the Flash.
Yeah, maybe.
How are we doing with him by the way?
We know that we still have
four bus-metas left to find.
And that DeVoe has absorbed the powers
of Kilg%re, Hazard, Black Bison,
Brainstorm and Dwarfstar.
Fallout is safe with Tracy.
But the Weeper is MIA.
DeVoe must have him.
Well, that just leaves Ralph.
Ralph is safe with us,
but the other four metas aren't.
DeVoe will absolutely kill them
and take their powers.
But why does he need their powers?
I can't figure out his endgame.
I don't know. I just know that
these last four metas are the key.
- That's why we need to find them.
- Find them we will.
Where have you guys been?
A little home away from home,
otherwise known as the bus depot.
Thought I'd show Cisco here
an old PI trick I learned
from my mentor, Columbo.
Lost and found box from meta bus 405.
Question for the room.
How did I get stuck doing
the buddy-system thing with Ralph?
It's the best way
to keep Ralph safe, Cisco.
Yeah, it's the best way
Oh, clearly, you've never had
to stay over at an apartment
that uses neon beer signs for lamps
and a kitchen sink for a shower.
Ralph, I love you,
but you sleep on a futon.
Futon is not that bad.
It is when it's damp.
Why is it damp?
I sweat a lot when I sleep.
You're nasty.
Huh.
Hey, my retainer.
I've been looking for this.
Retainer.
Okay. You've made your point.
Not that the point needed to be made.
I'll take the next shift.
You're a good man, Barry Allen.
Really, who uses CDs anymore?
A musician trying to catch their break.
Izzy Bowin.
Ugh.
Country. Music's tone-deaf step-child.
All right. You remember anyone
on the bus with a fiddle?
There was a guy with a cowboy hat on
sitting behind me.
Maybe it was him?
Boy, I sure wish we had
a way of finding out.
Izzy Bowin.
Izzy, you wanna give us
a little mic check?
Check one. Check, check one, two.
Okay, well, it's a her, not a him.
And she's playing
a gig at The Busted Saddle.
All right. Ralph, let's go.
No, no way. I hate country music.
Well, buddy system.
It's my turn. Come on.
If you insist.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
She's good.
She's improving,
but she lacks refinement.
So you're not impressed by her at all?
The resting face of my current visage
may be more pleasant
than the one I used to display.
But I assure you,
this is not the look of a man
awed by symphonic greatness.
Clifford. Clifford.
This body, it's deteriorating.
Rapidly.
The additional dark matter
in your system
from each of your new powers
is wearing down your host.
It's draining too much
of this body's new energy.
Then I must move into the next one.
But you said that
Izzy Bowin wasn't ready,
that we needed to find another.
We don't have time.
We must act now.
We may be too late.
- Izzy Bowin?
- That's me.
My name is Barry Allen.
I'm with C.C.P.D...
Is that a label?
- Um...
- Maybe on another Earth.
Okay. Well, you want an autograph
or a phone number or something?
Uh... No, no, nothing like that.
Okay. If it ain't business,
and it ain't pleasure,
then we got nothin' left
to talk about now, do we?
Oh.
- Do it again next week. Great work.
- Thank you.
Okay, I'm sorry. Let me explain. Um...
Uh...
Someone very smart
and very dangerous is coming after you.
Me?
Yeah.
Okay, now, why in the name of God
would anybody dangerous
be coming after me?
Because you have powers.
Four months ago, you were
on Central City bus 405.
That bus got showered with dark matter
and made everyone on it a meta-human.
Now the person responsible for doing
that wants those powers for themself.
Okay, and let me guess.
You boys are here to protect me?
Something like that.
Look, we can explain more later,
but now, we just need you
to come with us.
Oh, no. That's not necessary.
My daddy bailed,
Mama bailed not long after.
I have been looking out
for myself my entire life.
This time, it's different. You can't.
Please, we need to go.
I ain't going anywhere
with either of you.
I think you should reconsider that.
I don't give a damn what you think.
I guess now we know what her power is.
- What?
- Yeah.
You two are lucky.
Barry, your ear's almost healed.
And Dibny, yours just stretched.
I still can't hear all that great.
Consider that a blessing in disguise.
Less twang in your future.
Give it an hour, you'll be fine.
So, Izzy Bowin can control music.
More like sound waves.
Soundwave. That's a great name.
It would be, if it wasn't already
taken by a Transformer.
Mmm.
Okay, well, it looks like billions
of tiny shrapnel ripped through this.
Exactly. Sound is just the force
of billions of tiny gas molecules
colliding into one another.
So if you can harness
an amplified kinetic energy, you get...
Molecular shrapnel.
Okay. We've got to keep searching.
If we can't track her down soon,
she's gonna fall right
into DeVoe's hands.
Speaking of tracking people down,
when is Harry getting back from Earth-2?
DA Cecile Horton.
Harry, hey. When did you
get back from your Earth?
Just got back. I'm getting
myself a little pick-me-up.
You and me both, kid.
- Okay. Good talk.
- Yeah.
Actually, I don't think
that pregnant people
are supposed to consume caffeine.
Uh, yeah. Doctor says
one cup a day is fine.
And Lord knows I need it...
I need it more than
you can possibly imagine.
Apparently. Must be exhausting.
It is. He's keeping me up all night.
He? I thought Allen said
you're having a girl.
Yeah. I'm not talking about the baby.
I'm talking about Joe.
Joe is keeping me up.
Harry, come here.
My newfound ability
to hear people's thoughts.
- Yeah. I can hear...
- Oh. I thought...
Joe, his thoughts. I can hear them
while he's asleep, all night long.
- You hear his dreams.
- Yup.
And they're crazy and fast
and, oh, so very loud.
It is like living in the middle
of an action movie, Harry.
I love Joe West with all my heart,
but I'm telling you I just can't...
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
Yeah, that sucks to hear, Cecile Horton.
- Yes, it does.
- Okay.
Actually, I might be able
to build something
that could help you with that.
- Yeah.
- Oh, Harry, thank you.
Satellite's been running all day,
but it's still not picking up
any irregular sound variances.
I checked the city. I can't find her.
- Babe, you checked the whole city?
- Yeah.
Look, we have to find her
before DeVoe. Her life's on the line.
She had another gig this week.
I doubt she'd skip town.
How would Dibny PI suggest we find her?
Well, since you asked.
Has anyone checked her website?
"Has anyone
checked her website?"
Dibs, of course,
we've checked her website.
No one has checked her website? Iris!
Yeah, I'm on it. I'm looking now. Um...
Guys, she's still in town.
"I just picked up
the first run of my next single.
Love the geniuses at Saloon Sounds."
All right, Ralph. Take two.
- Cisco, we might need Vibe's help.
- Giddy up.
Come on. Let's go, we're in a hurry.
Izzy Bowin?
We need you to come with us.
Flash?
You're in danger.
I know. Everybody keeps telling me that.
You're gonna keep hearing it
until it sinks in.
You just have to trust us.
We're not gonna hurt you,
but we know someone who will.
Who is gonna hurt me?
I am.
You all came to warn me about her?
DeVoe.
Hello, Flash.
You're gonna leave Izzy alone.
You know, you really don't learn
from our past encounters, do you?
You're not smart enough to stop me
from getting what I want.
And what I want now is her.
That's not gonna happen.
It's three against one, genius.
Check your math, Vibe.
It's three against six.
Though, I doubt I'll need to use
all of my powers against you.
You stay away from me!
You just hurt DeVoe.
Who the hell is DeVoe?
So you're telling me
that this three-foot tall chick
that tried to kill me is actually this
Clifford DeVoe?
Yeah, 100% dude.
Mmm-hmm. DeVoe is transferring his
consciousness to the other bodies
of all the other people
who were on the bus
and got their powers with you.
Wait. This little girl wants my body?
It's why we were trying to protect you.
DeVoe has already taken
most of his targets.
No. This ain't happening. Not now.
I only got my powers recently.
And now it's like
I've got a deeper connection
to my music than I've ever had.
I'm about to record
the rest of my new album...
Izzy, your album can wait.
This threat is real.
So is my big break.
Do you have any idea
how hard I've had to work for this?
I left my home.
I lost friends and good men.
And I have put up with more crap
than you could imagine,
so that one day I'd get my dream.
And now you're telling me
that some pint-sized lunatic
is just gonna take it all away?
Which is exactly why we want you
to stay here at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Why? You're all gonna
protect me or something?
We're gonna train you.
- We are?
Guys, her powers weakened DeVoe.
Izzy, that makes you
our best shot at stopping him.
No, no. This is all too much.
I don't even know who you people are.
We don't have time for this.
Flash!
You're that guy from before.
Yeah. Barry Allen.
And so are you, aren't you?
Yeah. Ralph. Ralph Dibny.
I'm Cisco. Cisco Ramon.
It's nice to meet you.
Okay, thank you.
Look, look, I don't need training.
Especially from you.
All I need is my life back.
I don't know, guys.
I kinda feel like if I just
followed her into that hallway
and just gave her one of those
"hey, look" inspirational talks,
I could probably get her to stay.
Then what are you still doing here?
Sorry, I don't know if you drew
straws for this stuff or something.
- No, go!
- Okay.
I'd watch out if I were you.
Sometimes, killer robots
come out of there.
Keep walking, Stretch.
I don't talk to creeps in dark hallways
dressed in purple leather.
It's actually more of a mauve.
And I'm not a creep.
Look, Izzy, I know how you're feeling.
The day you got your powers,
I was on the same bus.
So that evil chipmunk,
she wants to kill me, too.
Please. I think I'd remember
seeing you on my bus.
Actually, I was kind of
big-boned back then.
I was on a strict diet of gin,
doughnuts, and regret,
but I got another shot at it.
And I worked my tight butt off,
and now I'm the hottest
superhero in town.
Please.
My life, it's never been better.
Kinda like yours.
Yeah, but aren't you
afraid of losing it all?
Yeah, I am.
Which is why I'm a part of this team.
You said that your family bailed on you,
so I can understand why you wouldn't
trust someone to look out for you,
but, Izzy, I can tell you firsthand
that these amazing weirdos,
they won't bail.
They created a buddy system for me.
And if you'll stay,
they'll keep you safe.
I promise.
So, who's gonna be my buddy then?
I may have to pull some strings,
but I will see if I'm available.
Subject 9's sonic powers
accelerated the deterioration
of your internal organs.
She merely disrupted
my atrial flutter and bradycardia.
This body is nearly drained anyway.
Its palliation is a waste of time.
I need these biometric scans
to fully assess your ailments.
Then you should have
built this to work faster.
I'm doing all I can.
Yet, you achieved precisely
the opposite!
I couldn't idly stand by
and watch you be injured.
Your plan was failing.
Is it possible that
the repeated transference
has affected your cognitive functioning?
There is nothing wrong with my mind.
Next time, I will keep a level head.
Izzy, this will help
focus your powers.
Well, this ain't much help in a fight
unless you're dueling the devil.
Don't think of it like a weapon.
Just do what you've
always been dreaming to do.
Make your own sound.
You my new target, Stretch?
Yeah, 'cause I don't break so easy.
Please.
You're built like a twig.
DA Cecile Horton, you look tired.
Yeah. That's 'cause I am tired.
This thing, it doesn't work.
It works because I built it,
and "this thing," as you
so inelegantly put it,
happens to be a mental activity dampener
that is 10 pounds of cerebellum-proof,
anti-telepathy somno-steel.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's the problem.
It is 10 pounds of that stuff.
- So?
- Okay.
Okay.
And?
I can't sleep like this,
Harry, does this look
comfortable to you?
I was pulling state-of-the-art
technology out of my ass
to help you with your problem.
I forgot to make things
"comfortable" for you.
Are you kidding me?
You know what else I forgot?
I guess I also forgot,
while I was coming up
with generational breakthrough
in vibrational brainwave theory,
that I was working
for the Princess and the Pea.
Stop it! Stop. Put it down.
Harry, put it down.
Okay, just...
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm frustrated.
- You're frustrated?
- Yes.
You start yelling at me
and throwing things.
It's like every awful thought
that you have
just comes pouring out of your mouth.
Totally unfiltered. I don't even...
Is this normal behavior for you?
Sometimes behavior.
Okay. If I wanna hear
a grown man scream like a child,
I will go home
and listen to Joe's stress dreams
about showing up naked to math class.
- Ew.
- Just take your thing, Harry.
- See you later.
- It's heavy.
You missed. Again.
Well, what do you expect, Ralph?
I've been doing this all day.
I need a water break.
- Maybe we should call it a night.
- Not yet.
She's barely landed
another shot on Ralph.
She needs more time, Bar.
She held her own against DeVoe.
Totally on raw instinct.
Beginner's luck?
I mean, it took months to train Ralph.
We don't have months.
Look, this is our chance
to get ahead for once.
If DeVoe shows up again,
we have to be ready.
All right, Ralph. I'm taking over.
Uh, thanks, Bar, but we kinda
got this covered over here.
Gotta push her, Ralph.
All right, Izzy. I wanna see
if you can hit a moving target.
- Okay.
- You're ready?
Nice.
Take it up a few notches.
Ow!
Barry!
Whoa.
How's Izzy?
She just needs a couple stitches,
and she'll be okay.
Ralph won't leave her side.
I think he might really like her.
Ralph shouldn't be bothering her at all.
I mean, she needs to stay focused.
Izzy might be scrappy,
but, you know,
it's her first day training
with powers
she's had for a little while.
I know.
Barry, don't you think
you're being a little hard on her?
No. I'm trying to teach her
how to protect herself.
No. It seems like you're trying
to turn her into a hero.
And that path just
isn't meant for everyone, Barry.
I mean, Izzy's just trying to survive.
Well, she's not going to,
if I don't push her.
You think this is the only way
to fight DeVoe?
It's not just about that.
Iris, you weren't at Iron Heights.
I saw up close what DeVoe did
to Becky. To all of them.
They...
And I couldn't do anything except
just stand and watch it happen.
DeVoe is ruthless.
He is not gonna stop until he's
taken her powers and her life.
He's not gonna go easy on her,
so neither can I.
I'm so sorry that
you had to experience that,
but Barry, we can't be
ruthless like DeVoe.
He is willing to sacrifice
anyone and anything.
Just remember that the next time
you're pushing too hard, okay?
You, of all people, know that
heroes aren't made overnight.
Joe's not here.
Why would I want to talk to Joe?
I kinda figured after
our last conversation
you would never want
to speak to me again.
That's fine.
You do know
I can hear your thoughts, right?
Right.
No, Harry, I'm not gonna
yell at you again.
Okay. Good.
Here.
- That's a...
- Mental activity dampener.
Sorry version 2.0.
You have to adhere it
to your supraorbital ridge.
It will block West out.
Look, I'm sorry about...
You know, I just recently
can't seem to stop DeVoe.
Can't stop my daughter Jesse
from hating me.
Can't seem to stop blowing it
when I'm trying to befriend
someone who's my own age.
Did you just say "befriend"?
That's what you've been trying to do?
You've been trying to befriend me?
Well, yes, through transitive property.
I respect West, West respects you, so.
Harry, that was borderline sweet.
Thank you.
- Okay, we'll talk.
- When?
- Now.
- Okay.
Okay.
- I'm not much...
- Come on, Harry.
Okay.
What do you wanna talk about?
Oh, okay. I'll start. Um...
You wanna tell me how this thing works?
Does it keep Joe's brainwaves
blocked out?
Does it keep my mind
reading waves locked in?
Mostly disrupts
the inbound brain activity,
but I suppose actually,
if you were to reverse the polarity.
Wow. That is interesting.
- Also...
- Yes. Harry, you have to do that.
- Right.
- Right now.
- Okay, good chat.
- Okay.
Should be good to go.
Might leave a little scar though.
Wouldn't be my first, doc.
Probably won't be my last.
It will be
if I had anything to do with it.
Why would you have
anything to do with it?
I am gonna go.
What are you doing?
The way I see it,
I've got more hurt here
than I ever did fighting DeVoe.
So I'm not going to spend
another second training.
Okay, that is a really bad idea.
I've already hurt Devoe
by myself without y'all.
I can do it again.
Izzy, the only way for you to
stay safe is for you to stay with us.
It's the buddy system, right?
You're not my buddy, Ralph.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't do this.
Sorry, Ralphy.
Initially, I envisioned
the mental activity dampener
as just disrupting
inbound brainwave broadcast,
but I talked to DA Cecile Horton,
and we had the idea
to invert the polarity,
allowing this to disrupt
outbound brainwave
broadcast as well. So we...
- We could use this against DeVoe.
- "We could use this against DeVoe."
That's brilliant.
I'm totally on board
except mental activity dampener.
Ramon, the name's no good.
Which is why, drum roll please,
I've decided to rename
this the cerebral inhibitor.
This is where we came up
with the cerebral inhibitor
to use against DeVoe.
What's that? What are you guys doing?
What are those faces?
When Savitar came to S.T.A.R. Labs,
he said that we would build
a device to use against DeVoe.
The cerebral inhibitor.
I wish I had known that
before I spent all this time
trying to come up with a second name.
Naming is hard.
Okay. So we can use this on DeVoe
to keep him from projecting
his consciousness into new bodies?
- Precisely.
- How does it work?
Just fix it to his forehead,
it activates. Simple as that.
I'll make a few adjustments,
you'll be good to go.
All right.
Okay, when Harry's done,
we go after DeVoe.
I mean we have Izzy's powers,
the cerebral inhibitor.
We have everything that
we need to stop him.
Except that we don't. Izzy's gone.
What? What happened?
What did you say to her?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Rookie, homeslice
hit the road because of you.
She's convinced she can
take on DeVoe by herself.
That's what she's gone to do.
You kept pushing and pushing.
You pushed her right out that door, man.
Okay, that's not fair.
No, it's all right. I did.
I pushed her too hard.
It's my fault she's out there, but
if DeVoe gets to her before we do...
That cannot happen.
Cisco, you gotta use your E.S.P.N.
and find out where she is.
Give me that.
Hey, blondie.
You want trouble? Here I am.
Well.
Look who finally decided
to show her sorry face.
Nobody likes a Peeping Tom.
Goodbye, Mr. Ramon.
Cisco, are you okay? Can you hear me?
She's at the warehouse district.
DeVoe is there.
I can't go with you guys.
I gotta take care of Cisco.
Okay, Ralph, it's just me and you.
Come on.
Bravo, Miss Bowin.
Of all my subjects, you're the only one
to mount a credible defense against me.
Darlin', you talk too much.
A modicum of bad luck
at a time like this.
How unfortunate.
You're quite the fiddler.
The Fiddler.
Mr. Ramon might say, "Nailed it in one."
Ralph?
You came after me.
We all did.
All right, Ralph, I'll keep DeVoe busy.
You just get the inhibitor on.
Hello, Mr. Allen.
DeVoe, you're not getting her.
Flash!
Poor Dominic.
He didn't know he could
affect minds as well as read them.
Now I have taught you
what a brain aneurysm feels like.
Get out of here.
Aw, crap!
Thank you, Mr. Rundine.
That will teach you
to mess with a country girl.
Cerebral inhibitor is attached.
- Is it working?
- It's working.
How did Mr. Deacon put it?
Ah, yes.
Call me Kilg%re.
What the hell?
Did she hack the inhibitor?
No, that's impossible.
There's a kill-switch microchip that
prevents the patch from networking.
I can hear your radio signal, Mr. Wells.
You told me once
I wasn't as smart as I thought.
Wrong again.
Izzy!
- Ralph?
- Hey.
Get her out of there!
Ralph, we can't.
Get her out!
We can't.
Izzy, just look at me.
Izzy, keep looking at me.
Much better.
Please inform Mr. Ramon
that while I had no need for all
six of my powers,
I now have a seventh.
I'm afraid I'm gonna be busy
with my wife this weekend, Ralphy.
No.
- How's Ralph?
- Not great.
This shouldn't have happened.
DeVoe wasn't supposed
to walk away from this.
Yeah, well, he did. Because of me.
We all tried to protect her.
I built the inhibitor, Snow.
If it failed, it's my fault.
I don't even know why.
Maybe I overestimated
the microcombustion infrastructure.
Maybe I underestimated
the amount of time
between each synapse router.
Or maybe it didn't malfunction at all.
Guys, Savitar said that we would use
the cerebral inhibitor against DeVoe.
Yeah. He didn't say it was gonna work.
Or it didn't work because...
I'm not smart enough to make it work.
- Harry, where are you going?
- Out.
- Guys, we have to find DeVoe again.
- How?
Cisco tracked down DeVoe in his Vibe
state and almost got himself killed.
Actually,
we might have a different
way of pinpointing him.
Check this out.
Space.
The final frontier.
Now you see it.
Now you don't.
That's exactly what it looks like
when DeVoe disappears.
That is the warping signature
of someone moving into
a pocket dimension.
Does someone wanna explain
what that means?
Einstein postulated
that it was theoretically possible
for a region specific fold
in the space-time to exist between
the four dimensions
that we typically think of.
Yeah, that doesn't help.
It's another dimension.
One that you can enter or exit
at any location in the world.
Like how DeVoe captured me
in that alley,
but then he brought me back out
just somewhere above the city.
Are you saying that DeVoe's lair
is in a pocket dimension?
- Cisco, that is great.
- Can we track him?
That I'm still working on.
Okay. Work faster.
Just do your best, all right?
Let's find him.
All right.
- I'm gonna go check on Ralph.
- All right.
You were right.
As much as I want to get DeVoe,
and get back to our lives,
I can't rush this.
It's gonna be
a little hard for a speedster.
Especially an unemployed speedster.
Don't worry.
You're gonna find something.
And until then?
You can start by kissing your wife.
- Someone looks busy.
- Yeah.
I have a little bit of work.
Why don't you have it, okay?
- Harry.
- Yes.
- I wanted to say thank you.
- For what?
The M.A.D. 2.0, it worked like a charm.
I am rested.
If you could just do something
about these swollen
pregnant ankles of mine.
Edema is a normal thing.
You drink lots of water.
Don't cross your legs when you sit.
Okay. Thank you for the info.
It's the least
I could do after all the...
Mmm.
Rage. I have a problem with rage.
Apparently, it tends to crop up
when I make mistakes.
Makes it tough to be human.
The humans are a tricky species.
Anyway, I apologize.
Apology accepted.
- You just needed somebody to talk to.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I guess you're...
Are you doing that thing
where you're reading my mind?
You're reading my mind, aren't you?
Maybe. Yeah.
Yeah, I am. You should call her Harry.
Jesse's on a different planet,
DA Cecile Horton.
But this problem
isn't gonna just go away.
What if she...
What if she doesn't come?
You're not gonna know
unless you invite her.
That was beautiful.
And a welcome change
from the derivative pablum
this body subjected us to before.
Our plan is back on schedule.
Indeed, it is.
Only a few more subjects left to locate.
Hey, man.
- I can come back.
- No, it's okay.
Look, um, I totally understand
if you need some time
away from the team.
I mean, to lose someone
right in front of you.
Especially
someone you care about.
Izzy was very special.
Yes, she was.
But, now,
DeVoe is still out there.
And until that threat's over,
you gotta keep this buddy system going.
I thought
you might say that, Allen,
which is why I got you this.
You want me to be your partner?
Oh, hey, come on.
This Turner don't need no Hooch.
But I do know what it's like
to get fired from C.C.P.D.
when you didn't even
really break the law.
You absolutely broke the law.
And I remember after I lost my job,
I felt like I lost
a piece of my identity.
And now, you won't have
to deal with that problem.
So the next time we're out in the field
and somebody asks you who you work for,
you won't have to get all stammery.
You like me.
You really like me.
Don't go getting
all soft on me now, rookie.
You and I, we gotta stand up
and we gotta fight back.
- Just like Izzy would want it.
- That's right.
There's three more people
out there who need our help.
And we need to find them
before DeVoe does.
And after we do that,
I'm gonna take DeVoe down.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::