- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back.
And in doing so, our world
was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
- 12 markers,
12 metas.
- Why would anyone
wanna create metas?
- What's happening to me?
- Clearly, this guy
is a bus meta.
- Stretch these cells.
- Like silly putty.
- I'm silly putty?
- Let my team and I train you.
What made you look
into Mayor Bellows?
- Oh, it was a client.
Last name, DeVoe.
- You do what Amunet says
for as long as she tells you.
[glass shattering]
[yelps]
- Tell Amunet I'm done.
- Joe, I'm pregnant.
[playful music]
- Hey, you guys wanna see
something really cool?
- Uh, sure, go for it.
- Stretch, Ralph.
Stretch.
[stretching noises]
- That is pretty cool.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, look, a-are you sure
we can't find this DeVoe guy?
I mean, we were warned.
We had a heads-up that someday,
someone named DeVoe would
be one of my greatest foes.
- And the other thing
to think about is,
do you know how many
people there are
in this state alone
with the name DeVoe?
- No.
- Thousands.
And we still don't have an age.
- Unless one of your greatest
foes is the three-month-old
William DeVoe who lives
four blocks from here.
- I don't think one of my
greatest enemies is a baby.
- Evil killer baby.
- Ehh, could happen.
- You're right.
[knocking]
- Hey.
- Ho!
- Yo, Felicity!
- [giggles]
- How'd you get in here?
- I literally walked in here.
You have...you have no security,
you have no alarms,
you have nothing on your door.
You guys might wanna consider
something, anything at all.
- You came prepared.
- Well, yeah, Team Arrow
to Team Bride, you know,
very excited for that
bachelorette party.
- Yep, getting inebriated
with same gender
to celebrate
an archaic institution?
- Priceless.
- I mean, you only
get married once, so...
Well, actually,
pretty much everyone
gets divorced these days.
55% to be exact, I mean,
that's just statistics.
But not...not you and Iris.
That would just...
That would never happen
to you guys...
[stretching noises]
Whose feet are those?
- That's Ralph Dibny.
- I'm gonna...I'm gonna
go meet up with the ladies.
[whispering] That...
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- Well, here you are.
Okay, are you ready
for the ladies' nights
to end all ladies' nights?
- And by that, she means
a quiet, low-key dinner
at a very classy restaurant.
- Yeah.
That's exactly what I mean.
Super low-key, super quiet...
do you want a pink
or a blue feather boa?
- Actually, Iris, if it's okay,
I don't think
I'm gonna make it tonight.
I'm just not feeling up to it.
- What?
- Aww.
- Are you feeling okay?
- No, I'm fine, I just...
Sometimes life catches up
with you, you know?
- It's 'cause you're
not wearing the tiara.
Put on the tiara.
Everything will change. Oh!
- Wearing the tiara, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Caitlin, please, come on,
we work together every day
and we never get to do
a dinner just us girls.
You have to come.
- She's right.
Just one dinner, please?
- Wouldn't miss it.
♪ ♪
- This is so insane.
I can't believe you're
gonna be a mom again.
- I know, well,
you always wanted a sibling.
[doorbell rings]
- And seven Doctor Whos later,
you totally came through.
- You're a Doctor Who fan,
Joanie?
- Well, ever since
he became a lady, I am.
#Feminism.
- Bachelor party!
Girls, get out.
- Oh, that's our cue.
- Hey, Barry,
congrats on getting hitched.
- Thank you! I didn't
realize you were in town.
- Well, I just stopped by
for the weekend.
- Awesome.
Good to see you.
- You too.
- Ah.
- Have a great time.
[smooches]
Don't get too crazy.
No drinking.
- Mm-mm.
No, Iris promised me
a totally chill night
that even my pregnant
little booty can handle.
[laughter]
You should come with us,
sweetie.
You know, I'm sure
Iris wouldn't mind.
- Uh, no, it's okay.
I, um, I actually have plans.
But I will drop you off.
- Okay.
Have fun.
- Later, guys.
- Bye!
- Okay, I'll get the lights.
Harry will get the brandy.
Hey, Harry,
before you pour the brandy,
make sure you warm the glasses.
- What?
- For real?
- It's cool.
[screen rattling]
- Okay.
[with English accent]
Barry Allen.
Are you ready
to have your mind blown?
[with dramatic voice]
Meet Barry Allen.
Before he met Iris West,
before he became an
interdimensional time-traveling
speedster, he was an adorable
baby boy with Ewok-level chub.
- [chuckles]
Ugh, those cheeks.
- Cisco, this is great, but
where did you get these videos?
- Man, I'm a ninja.
Watch this part.
♪ ♪
- Ah, I forgot
you two got married.
- [laughs softly]
- Ah, you two were so young.
Damn. I was so young.
♪ ♪
- Gentlemen, I have arrived.
- Ralph.
- Dibny.
- Wasn't expecting you.
- You said see you later.
I assumed this was a superhero
hangout and this was a test
for my highly attuned
detective abilities, which,
for the record, nailed it.
- Okay, or...
- You weren't invited.
- Wow, this house is, uh...
- Bitchin'?
- No.
Small. Looks much bigger
from the street.
What's all this crap?
- This is my bachelor party.
- [laughs]
[playful music]
Oh, dear God, you're serious.
This weinerfest
is your bachelor party.
- This weinerfest is about
to indulge in some
very fine cigars and a very
nice steak dinner at The Oak...
- Okay. Stop.
You're gonna pay $50
for a steak dinner?
- Why not?
- I know a place...
Where you can get
all-you-can-eat steak
and chicken for $4.99
and they even throw in napkins.
Come on, ladies.
- No, really, Ralph.
We're gonna stay here,
we're gonna go have...
- No, Slim Jim.
I insist.
You can thank me later.
- [slurps]
- That was meant to be enjoyed.
- I enjoyed it.
- Cisco, don't worry.
Where we're going, the drinks
flow freely and the view is...
Ugh. Spectacular.
♪ ♪
[lounge music playing]
- So fancy.
- Yeah. A toast
to the future Mrs. Allen.
- West-Allen.
Although your life with Barry
may be fast-paced,
I hope you guys take the time
to enjoy the special moments.
- Aww,
thank you guys for coming.
It really means a lot.
- Cheers.
- Well, all right,
who wants my champagne?
Craziest thing I get to do
tonight is order two desserts.
- I'll take it.
- That's right.
Iris told me you were pregnant.
How's that going?
- Yeah, it's g...it's good.
I mean, it wasn't exactly
part of my plan,
but I just could not
be happier.
- I know exactly what you mean.
- Oh, yeah, how is everything
with Oliver and William?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Do I hear wedding bells
ringing in your future?
- Oh, no, the last time
we did anything that
resembled a wedding, Oliver
got shot with an arrow, so...
♪ ♪
- Uh, did you girls
order a stripper?
- Why didn't you tell me?
I would've brought
all my singles.
- No, I...
- Girl,
you into some freaky stuff.
- Amunet wants you.
- Uh, Caitlin, do you know him?
♪ ♪
- You need to come with me.
- I'm not going
anywhere with you.
♪ ♪
- Please tell me that this
is just part of his act.
- If it is,
it's taking too long.
Take it off!
♪ ♪
Gross!
I meant take off your pants,
not your eye!
♪ ♪
[shrieks]
Oh, my God.
- [hissing]
[dishes clattering]
[women shrieking]
[crowd yelling]
- Stand back,
baby mama, we got this.
[dramatic music]
[screams]
♪ ♪
- [hissing]
- [yelps]
♪ ♪
- Holy...
- Please don't do this.
- Didn't have to be this way.
- What?
♪ ♪
- I was hoping
to see you again.
- [distorted voice]
Really?
So I could give you
another scar?
♪ ♪
- [hisses]
[glass shattering]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Ugh. I hate pink.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[club music playing]
- Doesn't it just
take your breath away?
[cheering and whistling]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
that is Jade.
- Gentlemen, I welcome you
to The Golden Booty.
- There ain't nothing golden
about any of this.
- Nope.
- Came through for you.
Right, man?
What do you think?
- I think I should've brought
some hand sanitizer.
- Always come prepared.
- Ohh, yes.
- Ralph, this isn't
really my speed.
- Speed jokes? You're better
than that, Allen.
- I wasn't...
- Hey, Ralphy.
- Uh, Disney,
you're a regular in this joint?
- Oh.
[rock music playing]
So much more than that.
The girls may not
be bottomless,
but for yours truly,
the French fries always are.
- Golden Booty policy.
Out of respect for the ladies...
no touching, no pictures,
no video,
and no cell phones.
- What?
- [clears throat]
♪ ♪
- I need a drink.
- God, I wish I could
have a drink.
- Bro, do you really think
I'd let you down like that?
Your special concoction.
Guaranteed to give you
that gentle, pleasant buzz
all night long.
- What if we need the Flash?
- I volunteer to be
designated superhero.
- Go for it, Bar,
you deserve it.
- [sniffs, sighs]
- To Barry and Iris.
all:
To Barry and Iris.
[glasses clinking]
♪ ♪
[cell phone buzzes]
- They're not picking up.
- What the hell just happened?
Who was that Medusa man?
- You know that is not
a Cisco-approved name.
- Don't worry
about who that was.
[tense music]
Caitlin's taste in clothes
is matched only by
her taste in men...
both terrible.
- Wait, how are you you?
I thought Caitlin was cured.
- Caitlin shouldn't be keeping
secrets from her friend.
You are friends, right?
- Yeah, of course we are.
- Your friend was going
out of town tonight.
- What? Why?
- Because she got herself into
something she couldn't handle.
- Where are you going?
- To find Norvock's boss
and to kill her.
- And you need a change
of clothes for that because...
Whoa!
Whoa, okay, apparently somebody
doesn't have boundary issues.
- Uh, okay, girls,
can I talk to you
in the Cortex?
- Can we take it back
for a minute?
Since when did her superpowers
make her a supervillain?
- [whispering]
She is not a villain, okay?
- I remember being kidnapped
by her last year.
- What?
- Okay, yes, but that
is because she was
being manipulated by Savitar,
and in the end,
we wouldn't have been able
to stop him without her.
- [sighs]
- Look,
I know that there
is some good in there.
- I get it.
Technically,
Caitlin is underneath
all of that somewhere,
but she is still dangerous.
- And she is also
our friend, okay?
I am not just gonna
abandon our teammate.
- Fine.
I'm coming with you.
- No, Cecile,
you're pregnant.
- And your father will kill me
if you get killed
at your own
bachelorette party.
- That is some crazy logic
and that means I'm in too.
- Oh, great,
happy bachelorette.
- What are you all
talking about?
- Oh, nothing, you know,
just talking about how cool
it is to kill people and such.
No pun intended.
- It's been real, ladies.
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna use
the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
to track her cold signature.
- Great, I'm gonna try
and call for backup again.
- And I'll remember that
it's Caitlin under there.
[rock music playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
- You gotta stop doing that.
- I'm just getting change
for a five.
What?
Did you think I was stealing?
♪ ♪
- It's not about your
sticky fingers, Ralph,
it's about your stretchy arm
outwardly displayed.
- Oh, so I should be more like
Captain Discreet over there.
- I'm the Flash!
[strangers cheering]
Yeah! Whoo!
- I have slightly
miscalculated
his bachelor elixir.
- I got this one.
Hey, buddy.
- Hey!
- How you feeling?
- I feel good.
- [laughs] You're gonna
need to walk this off.
- Or run it off.
Because I'm the Flash.
[laughter]
- Let's get you back
to the table.
- Hmm.
[grunts]
[whooshes]
- Barry?
What did you just do?
- [slurred]
I just went
and got peanuts from the bar.
- You didn't even move.
- Or did I?
- Drink up.
- Oh, I'm good.
- Ah, it's cranberry juice,
buttercup.
So I was talking to Charity...
not her real name...
she tells me the dancers
here make more in a month
than an average teacher...
- Blah, blah, blah.
Less talky, more dancey.
- Next dancer...it's Jasmine!
- Whoo!
[electronic music playing]
Whoo! Oh, yeah.
Whoo!
♪ ♪
- Oh, hell no.
- Hey, she looks like
Cecile's daughter.
[laughs]
Oh.
[muffled club music playing]
[siren wailing]
♪ ♪
- Ugh!
- I'm sorry.
I thought touching without
permission is what you wanted.
♪ ♪
I'd let me pass.
Unless you wanna know
what it feels like
when the liquid in
your eyeballs crystallizes.
♪ ♪
- Darling, you're here!
Let her in!
[claps]
Let her in, let her in.
- Amunet.
Next time you wanna talk,
come yourself.
Don't send your
eye-hole to attack me.
- Did you start a fight?
Honestly, Norvock.
That's why you're
my third favorite henchman.
I mean,
what do I always say?
- Never start a fight
you can't finish.
- Hmm?
And that, my dear,
is why you are my favorite.
You listen.
- Well, apparently, you don't.
I'm out, Amunet.
- Out?
Out of what?
Out of options?
Out of your mind?
Out of the closet?
There's just so many outs
for the lady in blue.
- Are you asking me to dance?
- You should know by now
I don't ask for anything.
I tell, and I take.
Now, come along.
I want to show you
something that could
make us both very rich.
- ♪ Came to party
and beat will go on ♪
- All right, do you think
they're gonna be able to tell
that we don't exactly
fit in here?
- Well, it was your idea
to wear boas, so no.
- Have we heard
from the guys yet?
- No. Look.
Ladies, okay,
we are on our own, okay?
- How about a little love?
- No!
No, no, no, no, no.
No. No love.
- Engaged. Okay, bye.
- No love.
♪ ♪
- Is it just me,
or does it seem like
everybody here already bought
what that guy is selling?
♪ ♪
Uh, ladies, stay here, okay?
I think I know where Frost is.
- You got a pet.
Congratulations.
- I call him The Weeper.
I love naming metas.
- I know someone else
like that.
- Three weeks ago, this
young man became a meta-human
and I acquired my new favorite
product to sell in my network.
Did you notice?
Love...
is quite literally in the air.
[giggles]
Do you know why?
Oh.
[grunts]
- [coughing, sniveling]
[sniffing, panting]
[gasping shakily]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Pure.
[exhales shakily]
- His tears are a drug?
- His tears, my dear...
[sighs]
Are a gold mine.
One taste and Central City
will be hooked.
[tense music]
- Then why do you need me?
- Really?
Well, if I'm going
to be selling something
quite valuable,
I'm going to need protection.
- That's what you've got
good old snake-eye for.
- A deal like this
requires a lady's touch.
I-in your case, strength,
and I'll cut you in for 10%.
15%, and I throw in
not killing you right now
for your misguided rebellion.
And that is only because
I've got forgiveness
in my kidneys, right?
- I think you meant heart.
- No, there's no beat beat
in this chest, sister.
- As much fun it is to play
"I'm the bigger badass,"
I'm bored.
And like I said...
I'm done.
- Do you know what everyone's
mistake in business is?
Hmm?
Not realizing who has
the power in the room.
[low rumbling,
metal clinking]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey.
[laughs]
Ladies, ladies, let's put
the meta-abilities down.
- I'm sorry, who is this chick?
- Oh, uh, this chick...
Oh. [laughs]
Is trying to stop a meta-fight
from destroying your
very enchanting club.
Let's go.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Frost.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
- Should I stop her?
- No.
Let her think
she can walk away.
- You're lucky she
didn't kill you, West.
- Who was that?
- That was Amunet Black.
- Of the underground market?
- Oh, I'm guessing this chick
has a criminal record.
- Yeah, she's been linked
to the meta-human black market
selling stolen technology,
but we've never been able
to nail her down.
- And how do you know her?
- Through Caitlin.
Six months ago,
Caitlin thought she had
everything under control.
- Can't keep a good bad side
down for long, am I right?
- She felt me
becoming much stronger.
She found out that
Amunet had some tech
that would let her
stay in charge.
She got desperate,
so she decided to use it.
But it came with a price tag.
- Which...which was?
- Being her muscle.
- Did you kill anyone?
- Some people lost their
fingers and their toes, but...
no, no one died.
- And how are you here now?
- While Caitlin sleeps,
I am awake.
- Oh, my God! You're like
The Incredible Hulk! That's...
I said that with
too much chutzpah.
- Yeah.
- Dialing it back.
- Look, what are
Amunet's plans for The Weeper?
- Not my problem.
- Look, he was on that bus.
We helped create him.
We need to save him.
- No. I need to leave
and escape Amunet.
- And you're just
gonna run away?
- Listen, there's a reason
the CCPD has not caught her.
And that you idiots
just realized
there's a major
crime lord living
under your noses
for the past three years.
She's too powerful.
We can't stop her.
- Guys,
we have a responsibility
to The Weeper
and to the city.
- What do you suggest we do?
- We need to rescue
him before Amunet
does whatever
she's planning, okay?
Cecile, you need to gather
information on Amunet,
and, Felicity, you need to pull
up the blueprint to the club.
We got this.
We're strong women.
- Yeah.
#Feminism.
- #Feminism.
[electronic music playing]
- This isn't what
you think, Joe.
- Good, 'cause I thought
I saw you dancing
on that stage in
a gold sequin bikini.
- No, I'm writing a book
on the female experience.
- I'd buy that book.
[wolf whistle]
Shake it, baby!
- Why does your
female experience
include you dancing
at The Golden Booty?
- Because we live in a society
that's dictated
by the male gaze.
I wanna control the narrative
of feminism, okay?
I wanna show the world that
a powerful, strong woman...
she can wear anything,
be it a bikini or a pantsuit.
- Or nothing.
Feminism.
- That's not how
feminism works.
Will you cut it out?
Joanie's practically
his daughter.
Hey.
Sad Flash, why the face?
- Nothing, I just...
[crying] I just love
chicken wings so much.
- Where are you gonna go?
- I know a guy who can
breach me to another Earth.
Start over.
Escape Amunet.
Be who I wanna be.
- And that's Killer Frost,
right?
- Don't be cute, West.
You can't stop me.
- I wasn't planning on it.
Look, I know you could kill me.
Just like you could've
killed Amunet tonight
or Cisco six months ago.
But you didn't.
There is a part of you
that is good.
And decent.
You just don't know
how to accept it.
- You think you know me now?
- No.
But I do know what Caitlin
looks like when she's scared.
And you have that same look
in your eyes right now.
You're just as afraid
of being Caitlin
as Caitlin is
of being Killer Frost.
[gentle music]
- If you still
wanna have a hand
for Barry
to put a ring on,
I suggest you move it.
♪ ♪
- There's a strong,
powerful woman
that we both love and fear
and her name is your mother.
Does she know you work here?
- Of course not.
She would just jump to all the
same conclusions that you are.
- Joanie, your mother and I
just want you to be happy.
But I think you need
to ask yourself
why you're keeping this
a secret from her.
- Joe?
[crying]
Why didn't...
Rose make room for Jack
on the door?
There was plenty of room
for both of them.
- Uh, Cisco, when does this
gift of yours stop giving?
- Man, I don't know.
I thought we'd be watching
home movies right now.
- Again, you are welcome.
- You steal $20 from me,
Ralphy?
- When? I mean...
[laughs] No.
- Yeah, you did.
I saw it.
I've been waiting
a long time for this, Dibs.
[glass shattering]
- Oh!
- [screams]
You monster!
- [grunts]
[energetic music]
[grunting, yelling]
♪ ♪
- Everybody, stop! I'm a cop!
[yelps]
- [slurred]
I'm the Flash!
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- You're late.
♪ ♪
- I'm right on time.
What, were you expecting
a different meta?
Nobody walks away from me,
Frost.
[metal clinking]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [pants]
Did you really think
I was going to let you
just breach into the sunset?
You owe me your life.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[siren wailing]
- [sighs]
[tires screeching]
And I always take
what I'm owed.
- Hands over your head, ma'am.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Is there any part
of the way that I'm dressed
that leads you to believe
I want to be called ma'am?
Hmm?
[metal buzzes]
♪ ♪
Ugh.
Blood.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Kill you later, Caity.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- Let me help you.
Please.
- [sighs]
Okay.
It's already knotted,
you just have to pull it tight.
Thanks.
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- You don't remember?
- When she's in control,
I don't remember
much of what happens.
Did she...I hurt anyone?
- Just that snake-eyed scumbag.
Didn't kill him, though.
So the cure, it...
- Didn't work.
Not all the way.
- Which is why you wanted
to leave tonight?
- [sighs]
- And why it took you
six months to come back?
- When Cisco said
he was gonna get Barry back
from the Speed Force,
I thought that maybe
I could come back
and make up for some
of the pain that I caused,
but she's getting stronger.
[scoffs]
I never should've come back.
- That's not true, Caitlin.
You can always come back
to your friends.
Why didn't you tell any of us?
- I didn't know who to talk to.
- Could've talked to me.
I'm your friend, Caitlin.
- Work friend.
I mean, it's not like
you and I have become besties
over the last few years.
- Yeah, I guess we haven't.
♪ ♪
[siren wailing]
- [laughing]
Hey!
Jerry, buddy,
we gonna get
that phone call or what?
Hey! Come on, man.
[singsongy]
I know you can hear me.
I'm right here.
Hello!
[normal voice]
Okay, great.
- You just know everybody,
don't you?
- I've been in here
a few times.
You know, I could wiggle
through these bars
and get us out of here.
Maybe make my finger into
a key, that'd be pretty sweet.
A lot of pressure put
on the index finger, though.
Iron versus flesh.
What do you think?
- I think you should
stop talking immediately.
- [coughing]
Oh.
Ugh.
I don't ever have
to drink again.
- Words uttered by everybody
who's ever had too many.
Here.
- Ugh.
This was a bust, huh?
- Bachelor party.
Happens.
- What's up with you?
All night, you've
seemed preoccupied.
[breathes deeply]
- I'm worried.
- About what?
- Being a dad again.
I'm almost 50, Bar.
- Mm-hmm.
- When I saw that video
Cisco made of you and Iris
when you were kids, I...
Hit me like a ton of bricks.
I was...I was young
the first time I did this.
- Mm-hmm.
- And seeing Joanie?
Ugh.
It's hard raising humans,
Bar.
- You'll be fine.
- I barely get enough
sleep as it is
worrying about you three.
Especially with
Wally being gone.
Add to that
a crazy baby schedule.
Feeding, the crying...
I'm honestly
scared to death.
- Joe, when you raised Iris,
you were alone.
When you took me in,
And, you know, when Wally
showed up, you were alone.
You did all that
by yourself.
Single parent.
No one could've done
a better job, no one.
Now you've got a partner.
You've got family.
You've always been there
for us when we've needed you,
and now it's just our turn
to do that for you.
[breathes deeply]
We will.
♪ ♪
- I know you will.
[playful music]
- I'll take those three.
- [clears throat]
- Four.
♪ ♪
[metal door rattling]
- These tears are more
than just water.
When ingested,
the dark matter inside it
alters the brain function like
that of a psychoactive drug.
- So it's like,
what, an opioid?
- It's like a love drug.
From tears.
- If this spreads, Central
City's gonna have a massive
drug problem on its hands.
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay, well,
we need to stop Amunet
and save The Weeper
before that happens.
- How do we find her?
- I don't know. She's smart.
Off the grid, always on
the move, never leaves a trail.
- Okay, well,
what about her powers?
The metal that she controls.
Do you know what it is?
- Some kind of alnico alloy.
- Do you think you could use
our satellites to track it?
- You mean run a geological
scan of the city for
small-scale signatures of
aluminum, nickel, and cobalt?
Girl, please.
[tense music]
- There. She's headed
to Lawrence Hills.
That's...that's all
industrial out there.
That's steel mills,
docks, warehouses.
- Okay, we need to stop her.
- Okay.
- Guys, I can't go with you.
If I lose control,
I could become a liability.
I'm sorry, Iris, I can't go.
- You don't have to.
We got this.
Okay?
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- [speaking Japanese]
- [giggles]
♪ ♪
- Ladies, what's your status?
- We're in position.
- [singsongy]
I think you'll be pleased.
♪ ♪
- This is him?
- Mm.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
Good boy.
Sample?
- [speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply]
- I'll take him.
- [chuckles softly]
- On my count, we move.
- Okay.
- One, two...
- Three.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- I remember you.
You are the chick
from the bar, hmm?
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
- Hey, Amunet.
♪ ♪
This is between you and me.
Let my friends go and I'll
come back and work for you.
- Oh.
It's...it's too late
for that, Caity.
Do you know why
no one has ever testified
against me over the years, hmm?
Well, it's because
they're not alive to.
♪ ♪
Sorry.
Take care of them.
♪ ♪
- No!
[men grunt]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Well, hello, Chilly.
- We gotta get out of here.
♪ ♪
- And I thought I wasn't going
to be able
to kill anyone today.
♪ ♪
Kill them!
[gunfire]
- I don't think this
is gonna hold much longer.
- Well,
this is a steel factory.
And you move
steel plates with...
- Magnets.
Really, really big magnets.
[gunfire, ice crackling]
- Cecile, turn the crane on.
- What? How?
- Uh, should be in
the schematics, just...
just highlight it
and turn it on.
- Okay, um...
♪ ♪
[ice crackling]
[shattering, crashes]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
Ohh.
♪ ♪
You and I
could have been gods.
- I used to work with a god.
Over it.
♪ ♪
- Cecile, now!
[metal clinking]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Not so scary without
your bling now, are ya, sister?
♪ ♪
- Stop!
Caitlin, stop.
- I'm not Caitlin.
And I'll never be free
unless she dies.
- No, it's the opposite.
You are free right now.
But if you do this,
you will always be a killer.
Killer Frost, Caitlin...
you don't have to be
one or the other.
You get to decide who you are.
♪ ♪
[ice shatters]
- Get out of here.
- You've ruined this
for me today.
And one day soon, I promise you
I will ruin something for you.
♪ ♪
- Hold on.
It's okay, okay?
We're gonna help you.
- Get away from me.
- Wha...
♪ ♪
- The police are on their way.
- We did it, guys.
We really did it.
- Actually, it's girls.
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna have a headache
now until my wedding day.
- Worth it.
- Agree to never speak about
what happened tonight?
- Agreed.
- If I have to.
- What?
Hey.
- Hey.
I saw you called 17 times,
everything okay?
- Oh, yeah, everything is fine.
How was your night?
- Ummm, good.
Quiet.
- Uneventful.
- Yours?
- Uh, yeah, yeah,
not much happened.
- You know what?
We actually had a few scrapes.
- Honestly, so did we.
- [sighs]
- Some tears were involved.
- Yeah, us too.
- More crying.
Then puking.
- Aww.
- Lost access to
the happiest place on Earth.
- Pretty sure nothing could've
made tonight any worse.
[sighs]
I'm so tired.
I'm so tired, can we
just do this tomorrow, please?
- Aw, chicks with white hair.
Hot.
- Why is Killer Frost here?
- Guys...
she has something
that she wants to tell you,
and you all should listen.
[crystal chimes]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Aww.
It's just Caitlin.
♪ ♪
- I can explain everything.
- [sighs heavily]
- Hey, Joe.
- Hey.
- [laughs]
Uh, when you got arrested,
I figured you'd be okay
'cause you're a cop,
but still.
- Yeah, we're all fine.
How was the rest
of your night?
- It was fine.
Joe, I'm gonna do what I want.
- I know. You're an adult.
I was not trying
to tell you what to do.
- But if I'm being honest,
I know that I took it
too far tonight.
- And what about
your feminist research?
- I still believe
everything I was saying.
But after we talked,
I realized
that's not why
I'm working there.
So I'm gonna quit.
♪ ♪
Are you gonna tell Mom?
- That's not my secret to tell.
But your mom loves you.
And she'll always listen
if you let her.
[door clicks]
- Just got my first craving.
[sighs]
Hi, you two.
How was your night?
- Uh, it was fine.
Nothing happened. You?
- Oh.
Same.
Super chill.
- Mm.
- I'm gonna head
to bed, but, um,
do you wanna do breakfast
in the morning and just talk?
- Yeah, sweetie, I'd like that.
- Okay.
- Good night, guys.
- Good night.
[sighs heavily]
I gotta tell you something.
- Mm.
- This kid of ours?
Definitely not a vegetarian.
- This kid of ours.
Cecile, I gotta tell you.
I never thought I'd even have
a second chance at love,
and here you are.
You're my everything.
To top that miracle,
we're having this baby.
It's exciting.
Is it okay to say
that I'm scared?
- I'm so glad that
you told me that.
'Cause I am terrified.
- Really?
- Yes. Really.
I-I thought that
I'd finally hit this groove
in my life and my career
and with you,
and now this
changes everything.
- The last thing I thought at
our age, we'd be having a baby.
- [laughs]
I know.
It's scary.
But I figure pretty much
all we gotta do
is love this baby
as much as we love each other.
♪ ♪
- That's a lot of love.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
♪ ♪
- So much for quiet
and classy, right?
- Not exactly the bachelorette
party you had in mind.
- Well, saving the city wasn't
a bad way to spend the night.
But the best part
of the night was spending it
with the ladies
of Team Flash.
- It was.
When we weren't
almost getting killed.
- Yeah, we should
do it more often.
- We should.
- The hanging out part,
not the almost
getting killed part.
- I'd like that.
- Actually, I wanted to ask you
a favor about the wedding.
- Oh, you want
a custom ice sculpture?
- [laughs]
No.
Um...
I wanted to know if you
wanted to be my maid of honor.
- Me?
- Yeah,
we're more than work friends,
and we've been through
a lot together.
Weddings are all about
new beginnings, right?
So what do you say?
You wanna stand up for me?
- I do.
I guess that's your line,
though, right?
- [laughs]
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- I'm so excited.
- I know.
- Do I have
a bridesmaid's dress?
- Of course.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[aircraft rumbling]
- I went
to a lot of trouble...
creating you.
♪ ♪
I can't have you running away.
Not until you've completed
the task
for which you were born.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.