- Last season,
on "The Flash"...
- Hey, Mom and Dad.
If you're watching this,
it means that
something went wrong.
What's happening?
- A new timeline is setting in.
- Thank you for everything.
- I love you.
- [sobs]
[both gasp]
- Look, Kamilla, I don't want
to keep this from you anymore.
- If being Vibe is a part
of the life you want,
I would never get
in the way of that.
- I wanna take the cure.
- Killer Frost and I
are really gonna miss Vibe.
- Me, too.
- Dad...
- I would like my replacement
to be you, Joe.
- As captain?
- Captain Joe West.
- None of you can stop
what's been set into motion
because nothing you can do
can alter
what's about to happen.
[dramatic music]
[alarm ringing]
- It's a system-wide
power surge.
♪ ♪
[computer whirring, chirping]
- It's coming
from the Time Vault.
[computers power down]
Are we under attack?
- I don't know.
Whatever's going on
started the moment we left.
[air whooshing]
- I wasn't perfect.
Please remember
that I love you both...
and I always will.
And I always will.
And I always will...
always...always...
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- [hisses, grunts]
- Barry, Nora's message.
♪ ♪
- Why is it
every time I come to visit
there's always a crisis?
- Comes with
the meta-territory.
750 mph.
He's getting faster.
- Who is this guy, anyway?
- An old family friend.
♪ ♪
His name's Godspeed,
and he's from the future.
♪ ♪
He's like a fake speedster.
- What's that?
[computer beeping]
- The real deal.
♪ ♪
- Kick his butt, Barry!
- Done and doner.
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[growls]
- Who are you and what
are you doing in Central City?
- [electronic beeping,
warbling]
[electronic noises stop]
- He's just like the others:
no language skills, just noise.
- Lovely.
- What was that?
- The fourth Godspeed
we've caught this summer
and still no sign
of Mr. August Heart.
Just another dummy
who can't communicate anything
beyond modem speak.
All right, I'm clocking out.
Why don't you drop off G4
at Iron Heights, Barry?
I don't think we're figuring
out this mystery today.
[pleasant jazz music]
- This is nice, Dad.
We should do this
way more often.
- Agreed.
Hey, before I forget,
congratulations
on "The Citizen."
- Yeah, well, you know,
there's millions of people
in Central City
and I've only got a couple
hundred thousand subscribers.
You know, I'm no CCPN.
- Well, not yet,
but in about ten years
it'll be a
Pulitzer Prize-winning empire.
- Baby steps, Dad.
[both laughing]
- Mm, damn, this is good.
- You know
you can't get drunk.
- I don't even care,
that's how good this is.
- Never fear, the party's here!
[imitating air horn]
- [laughing]
- We brought
my famous ambrosia salad
and veggie dogs for Ralph.
- Guys, Ralph's still in Peru.
- Or Monaco...or Texas?
- All that
for a missing person's case?
That's dedication.
- Guys, guys,
what are we doing?
Baby Jenna is napping
like a little angel
and I have creamed corn,
I have candied yams,
I have collard greens.
Baby, let's eat.
- Yum!
- Yeah!
[all laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[all laughing]
- How's the MAC coming?
- There's mac and cheese too?
[all laugh]
- No, the
Mental Augmentation Chamber.
Basically, it allows us
to tap into the Speed Force
to boost Barry's
cognitive abilities.
It would allow him to see every
possible outcome to a scenario
at the same time.
- So speed-thinking.
- Which means we'll be able
to catch all
the bad guys faster.
- With all the ones that
you brought in this summer,
Barry, the DA's office
can barely keep up with you.
- Hey, since the MAC's done,
we should take it
for a test run.
- Absolutely not.
You know we're still
working out diagnostics.
- We could put in
a few hours tonight,
get a head start.
- Barry...
[laughs]
If there's anything
I've learned
since leaving Vibe behind,
it's that we all have
a work-life balance to protect,
and right now, mine is tipping
towards more beer.
[impish music]
Besides, I still gotta
tweak the mainframe
and I can't do that without...
- [huffs]
- Uh...
- Every time.
- My tablet.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
[all laughing]
I'm gonna go get that beer.
[clears throat]
♪ ♪
- Hey, so the last time
I talked to you guys,
you seemed good.
You guys good?
- Um...
we were devastated at first,
but Nora's only gone
for right now.
We're gonna have kids someday
and then we'll have
another Nora.
- Yeah, I think knowing
that we have a second chance
makes all the difference.
[phone ringing, buzzing]
- I gotta go, a break-in
at Eastside Industrial.
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
Dad, um, I meant to ask you,
what did you do
with those boxes
that were in the back
of the garage?
- Oh, he finally
threw them away.
Thank you very much.
- Okay, I gotta make a call.
- Guys, I'm sorry, I actually
have to sneak out too.
A friend of mine from
med school needs my support.
Thanks for having me,
it was delicious.
- Bye, Caitlin.
You notice ain't nobody
help clean up?
[somber music]
- My name is Ramsey Rosso,
and my mother,
Dr. Rachel Rosso,
was everything to me.
When I was seven,
I skidded out pretty badly
on a bike she bought me
for my birthday.
Imagine a scared kid
with two scraped knees
and a bloody nose.
When Mum found me,
she picked me right up,
she brushed me off,
and told me to get back
on my bike and ride.
♪ ♪
I tried, but I couldn't.
It was almost like
I was paralyzed,
it hurt so bad.
That's when she told me
that I would heal.
That I must never
let a little pain stop me
from getting to where I needed
to go in life,
and she was right.
I did heal.
♪ ♪
Enough to grow up
and follow in her footsteps.
♪ ♪
And even though a beautiful
life was cut short
when she lost her battle
to heal herself...
♪ ♪
She is still helping me to get
to where I need to go today.
♪ ♪
And for that,
I will always be grateful.
♪ ♪
Thank you, Jonathan.
- Ramsey, hi.
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Your mother was
an incredible woman.
I'm gonna miss her.
- It means so much
that you came.
Mum actually saw something
of herself in you.
Probably because
you're both overachievers.
- [laughs]
- Your hands are so cold.
- [sighs]
- Are you all right?
[tense music]
- Yeah, sorry, I'm fine.
Um, probably just
coming down with something.
- Well, I hope not.
Doctors make rubbish patients.
- Mm.
It was nice to see you.
- Eh, Caitlin?
Things have been
a bit, um, crazy.
♪ ♪
Do you fancy coming around
for a cuppa sometime?
You know, for a proper
catch-up.
I could really use someone
to talk to right now.
- Of course, any time.
Just give me a call.
♪ ♪
- Well, my log says that
your father's stuff
should have ended up
somewhere around here.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
There it is.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
- Must be pretty important.
- [sighs]
Yeah, it is.
Thanks.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [screaming]
- H-hang on!
I've got you!
[grunts]
♪ ♪
Hang on!
[gasps]
[both panting]
You okay?
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
- I missed you last night.
Are you sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
- What were you doing
out here anyway?
- I was following up
on a lead.
"The Citizen" got a tip
that there were a series
of junkyard robberies.
- People file police reports
for stolen trash?
- Yeah, well, you know,
not everything that's here
is garbage.
[garbage crashing, clattering]
[lighthearted music]
- Everything here is garbage!
I hate garbage.
- Okay, have fun
with Ghostbusters.
I'll see you at home.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
- What do you got?
- This site is littered...
no pun intended...
with gamma rays
and magnetar fields.
- What are you saying?
Iris was attacked by a...
- Yeah, a frakkin' black hole.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
[computer beeping rapidly]
That is a whole lot
of information to disseminate.
- No one's ever extrapolated
this much data
from a black hole before.
- We can be the first.
Come on, we're Team Flash!
- What did you put
in his coffee?
- Okay, a black hole
just showed up
and nearly swallowed Iris.
- So let's crunch the numbers,
find out where it went.
- I'm sorry, are we looking
at the same screen?
Creating a search algorithm
for this is gonna be like
deciphering a mystery
wrapped up in an enigma.
- Then it's a good thing
that "mystery"
is my middle name.
[snazzy jazz music]
The name's Dibny...
Ralph Dibny.
- Welcome back, Ralph.
- It's good to see you, man.
- Nice threads.
Where'd you get them?
- Picked this up in the Opal.
- A missing person's case
sent you all the way
to Opal City?
- And beyond, my friend.
A summer spent undercover
rubbing Rolexes
with the wealthy elite.
[stammers] Did you guys know
it's pronounced "yacht"
and not "yah-kt"?
- Yep.
- God, I missed you.
- Anyway, just following
any leads that might help
explain the disappearance
of Sue Dearbon.
- I don't think I've ever seen
you this devoted to a case.
- Me neither, but this one
is a real tragedy.
Maybe it was the look
of desperation
in her parents' eyes
when they begged me
to find their daughter.
So, uh, what's new
in Central City?
- We are trying
to track a black hole.
- Of course you are.
- We were just about to start
decoding this data stream.
[computer chirping]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Ugh, I'm sorry, sorry.
Been having these
random frost-outs lately.
- For how long?
- All summer.
It's happened twice
in the last couple of days.
- Cait, you're probably
overworked.
Maybe take a time out?
- A friend of mine did want
to meet for coffee.
- Ramsey?
- Yeah.
- It's never easy
losing a parent.
Maybe you should
take him up on it.
- I'll give him a call.
[mellow music]
- Ah, found it.
Theft report for Leawood
and New Brighton junkyard.
See, I have a system.
- You're a hoarder,
but I love you.
- Iris.
♪ ♪
Huh, these don't seem
to have anything to do
with the black hole.
They're just
run-of-the-mill human thefts.
Well, you have a list
of persons of interest,
in any case.
- Yeah, thank you.
Um, I'll get right on this.
- Iris?
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I...I don't know, maybe I'm
still a little shaken up
from the black hole.
I'll be fine, thank you.
♪ ♪
- You remembered
how I like my lattes.
- With a bit of cinnamon,
just like Mum.
You know, of all her
CC Hospital residents,
she really took
a special liking to you.
- She was the first person
to realize that
I was into cutting-edge tech.
It was her letter
of recommendation
that started my career
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
[melancholy music]
- I couldn't save her, Cait.
Had to watch
as her body betrayed her.
♪ ♪
Do you know how HLH works?
Then you know the cancer
literally boils you
from the inside out.
♪ ♪
Can you imagine
what that must have felt like?
Watching her suffer...
♪ ♪
That's my last memory of her.
- Don't let it be.
What you said at the funeral
about how brave she was?
Remember that.
- I lied.
Truth is, she was a coward.
- What do you mean?
- As a doctor, she knew her
chances of surviving were slim,
so she just started ticking
things off her bucket list.
- Isn't that a good thing?
- She should have
gone down fighting.
Instead, she ran away.
I didn't.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
In HLH,
white blood cells attack
the body's immune system.
A median survival rate
after diagnosis
was two to six months.
Not anymore.
[tablet chirps]
- Oh, my God,
this is a potential cure.
But what's the bonding agent
strengthening
the body's defenses?
- Dark matter.
I know what
you're thinking, Cait.
I thought the same thing, too...
at first.
But I have been running
simulations for months,
and they all show
the same results.
My cure will work.
- Or turn them into meta-humans
against their will.
- But I can save lives.
I just need
the dark matter
to start human trials.
- And that's why you wanted
to get coffee with me.
- S.T.A.R. Labs
has the dark matter I need
to take the next step;
you have access to it.
- Ramsey, your research,
it's groundbreaking,
but using dark matter?
That's a deal-breaker.
- It wasn't when you made
the meta-human cure.
- That was different.
We were trying to protect them.
- Well, what about
the rest of us?
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
I really am.
♪ ♪
But my answer is still no.
- She didn't have to die, Cait.
No one with HLH does,
because you could help me
stop it.
♪ ♪
[door closes]
[atmospheric thrumming]
[metal, glass rattling]
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
[wind howling]
♪ ♪
[all screaming]
- [yelps]
♪ ♪
Frost, where are you?
[screams]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[both thud]
[both panting]
♪ ♪
[melancholy music]
- How you feeling?
- Like I should be dead.
- That's not gonna happen.
We're Team Flash.
We always watch
each other's backs.
We always
keep each other safe.
- Meanwhile, over here
in the real world,
our black hole
keeps growing up.
Only next time it pops up,
it won't just be Jitters.
The whole city
could be in danger.
- Why did this thing show up
outside Jitters, anyway?
What does a coffee shop have
in common with a junkyard?
- I think I know
who can tell us.
[folder slaps]
Okay, so I followed up
with CCPD's list
of junkyard robberies.
Ten of them
were persons of interest,
nine were career criminals,
but this one guy,
a scientist, was let go
with a warning
after being caught
stealing old lab equipment.
Team Flash,
meet Chester P. Runk.
- Hey, what up, party people?
Welcome to a world
where all are welcome
and anything, including
the scientifically impossible,
can and probably will happen.
I'm your boy
Chugga-Chugga-Chugga-Chugga
Chester...
- I really like him.
[all laugh]
- With knowledge from
the bleeding edge of physics
and beyond-beyond-beyond.
[laughs]
I've been working
on that echo.
And...and yes, as usual,
I am fueled by some...
mm, damn fine coffee
from everyone's
favorite beanery.
Poured, of course,
to, uh, perfection
by a certain special someone.
Huh, huh, huh?
[laughs]
Uh, no, WookieLover77, I...
[sniffs]
I have not asked her out yet,
but I got my punch card, okay?
Three more Vibe-achinos
and I'm making my move, baby.
I'm making my move, baby.
I'm making my move, baby!
- Okay, he talks about Natalie
for a while, so...
[laughs]
There we go.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Is he building
what I think he's building?
- Behold, believers:
a gravitational wave emitter
powered by a modulated
neutrino charger.
In other words,
"Time to call some aliens."
[laughs]
- He built this in his garage?
- Using nothing but trash.
What a legend.
Oh, he's turning it on.
- Uh...uh, no.
No, no, no, that's not
supposed to do that.
Oh, crap.
Uh, hold on.
[stammering]
[screams]
[foreboding music]
- Okay, not exactly getting
the supervillain vibe
from our boy Chester here.
- He opened a black hole
by accident.
- And what about Chester?
Is he okay?
- Well, police reports show
that EMTs took him to the ER,
but then after that
the trail goes cold.
- Just a tiny question here:
how do we destroy a black hole?
♪ ♪
[computer chirping]
- Well, I am not a doctor,
but I'm gonna assume
in this case
that "negative"
means a positive.
- Not if it means
being clueless
about why my powers won't work.
- Did anything out of the
ordinary happen recently?
- I went to my friend Ramsey's
mom's funeral yesterday.
- Anything unusual
about the service?
- No, it was a lovely service
for an inspiring woman.
Then, today, I nearly got
sucked into oblivion.
- Has our frosty femme fatale
ever refused to come out
like this before?
- The last time I can think of
is right after my dad died.
- Right.
- So you think funeral
plus nearly getting sucked
into a black hole
equals Killer Frost is afraid
of dying?
- Maybe...
but I know we're gonna
figure this out.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- This place creeps me out.
- Will this sort you out?
♪ ♪
- Nice doing business with you.
[case rattles]
[latches click]
♪ ♪
Whoever pissed you off
won't be a problem anymore.
♪ ♪
[case snaps]
- Chester P. Runk is here?
[somber music]
- Ward nurses say he's been
catatonic since he arrived.
Just involuntary muscle spasms.
[approaching footsteps]
♪ ♪
- Chester?
[sighs]
My name is Iris West-Allen,
I'm a reporter.
♪ ♪
Chester, can you hear me?
[soft tapping]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
He was our only lead.
♪ ♪
- Iris.
You lost something of Nora's
last night, didn't you?
Something that Joe
accidentally threw away,
it ended up at that junkyard.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
I just miss her so much.
♪ ♪
Every day, every minute.
And I know
that is selfish because...
one day I may get
to see Nora again.
♪ ♪
But it won't be our Nora,
you know?
The one that we knew, the one
that we have pictures of,
the one that we grew to love,
you know...
[stammers]
That Nora is gone forever.
♪ ♪
And I guess because of that
you know, I just...
I don't know
how I'm supposed to feel.
- Iris, you do not get
to cheat the grieving process
just because you know you're
gonna see Nora again someday.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, you're right.
I guess I just
haven't been able
to put into words
how I've been feeling.
♪ ♪
- Iris?
[revelatory music]
What is it?
♪ ♪
[tapping in time with pulsing]
- It's Chester.
[tapping continues]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
- You're looking at
the world's first
inverse mass
angular momentum disruptor,
but we can just call it
a stellar grenade.
- Cool.
So this will
destroy the black hole?
- As long as it doesn't
get much bigger,
this will reverse the hole's
mass-collecting properties,
causing it to...
[sucks air]
Implode.
Just toss it
in the event horizon;
hasta lasagna,
don't get any on you.
- We can't.
If we destroy it,
we're gonna kill Chester too.
[dramatic music]
- You sure about this?
- Yeah, the corona's flair
matched the exact cadence
of Chester's fingers.
- So the black hole and Chester
are connected?
- Actually, I think
Chester is the black hole.
Watch this: so normally,
stimuli enters the brain
through the sensory area,
goes up to the temporal lobe,
and then back around,
but watch what happens
in Chester's brain.
It starts in the right area,
but halfway through
its rotation, it disappears.
[computer beeping]
- I think I know
where it's going.
[keys tapping]
You're looking at a map
of the negative ionic energy
inside the black hole.
Watch what happens
when an energy pulse travels
along its tendrils.
See how it stops halfway?
[dramatic music]
- The black hole is the other
half of Chester's mind.
It's his consciousness.
- Maybe it's been showing up
in places that hold an
emotional attachment for him,
like the junkyard where he
stole stuff for his projects.
- He's got a crush
on a girl at Jitters.
Okay, so all we have to do
is get Chester's mind
out of the black hole,
reunite it with his body,
and once his
condition stabilizes,
the black hole
should just collapse.
- Right, but they don't exactly
teach that in med school.
- Okay, but we can't
just let Chester die.
We have to do something.
[suspenseful music]
- Look, I don't like saying it,
but I think we need
to consider it.
- Cisco, I know
where you're going.
- And you know
we already have a way
of beating this
before it gets any bigger.
- We're not discussing this.
- You think I like saying this?
I don't, but if we don't find
a solution for this
and find one now, we're gonna
have to make a choice
down the line, and it's either
gonna be Chester
or it's gonna be everyone
in Central City.
- I'm not losing anyone else!
♪ ♪
I'm...let's find another way.
[phone chirps]
♪ ♪
[frost crackling]
- Where's the meltdown?
- We gotta talk.
- What is your problem?
- My problem is, we needed you,
and you were holed up
in your Snow-tress of Solitude.
I mean, you even refused
to come out at Jitters.
- Flash was there, so spare me
the little hallway chat...
and I'm not afraid of dying.
- I know that,
but you are afraid of living.
Thomas' death, the funeral,
what happened at Jitters:
all those things happened
to Caitlin.
She also led
her high school debate team
to back-to-back championships.
She went to med school.
She married Ronnie.
Those are her memories.
- Yes, I know.
I was there.
What's your point?
- Having Caitlin's memories
isn't the same
as having your own.
- Like you'd know anything
about that.
- I know it sucked
sitting courtside
for the Thinker show
when he hijacked my body,
and I think that you've been
going through something similar
since Thomas died.
And after being
at that funeral,
seeing that woman live
the last days of her life
to the fullest,
I think that made you want
want to start living
your best life right now.
- That's not my gig, okay?
I fight the bad guys,
keep Caiti safe,
and then go back in my cage.
[melancholy music]
I just have to deal with it.
- Have you thought
to ask Caitlin how she feels?
- What's she gonna say?
"Go ahead, Frost,
take the wheel."
- [chuckles] There's only
one way to find out.
♪ ♪
[retreating footsteps]
- You know, Barry, I think
it's time we faced the truth.
- I can't give up on Chester.
- No, I meant...
[sighs]
About Nora.
Look, I know we keep saying
that we're fine,
but I still miss the Nora
that was, Barry,
not the Nora that will be,
and I think that you do too.
♪ ♪
I think that's why you've been
working so hard all summer.
♪ ♪
- I thought if I could
keep people safe,
that it would make up
for how much I miss her.
♪ ♪
Think all the work this summer
and the long hours,
pushing myself,
pushing the team...
♪ ♪
It's so I could avoid
what scares me the most...
♪ ♪
That I'll never get over this.
- There is no support group
for what we're experiencing.
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
You know why
I was at that junkyard?
♪ ♪
I lost my purple jacket.
And I was obsessed
with getting it back because...
♪ ♪
You know, in my mind...
Nora needs it.
You know, she needs it
to become XS.
[sniffles]
And when that thing
swallowed it, just...
just for, like, a tiny second,
I wanted it to swallow me too.
♪ ♪
You know, the only way
we're gonna get through this
is if we carry
this burden together.
It's the only way, Barry.
♪ ♪
[alarm blaring]
[dramatic music]
- We just ran out of time.
[all screaming]
♪ ♪
- Okay, so how do we get
Chester's consciousness
out of the black hole?
- Well, the electrical impulses
that make up Chester's mind
are just past
the black hole's threshold,
but since his synaptic energy
has a negative charge...
- I could use my lightning's
positive charge
to attract his energy.
- Like a magnet.
- Exactly.
- Then what? I mean,
how are you gonna
survive inside of there?
- Well, your...
your Speed Force aura
should protect you, right?
- What if it doesn't?
- The gravimetric forces
will crush you
to a subatomic size
within seconds.
- That's not gonna happen.
The Speed Force
is a billion times stronger
than any gravimetric force.
- Even if you do survive
the entry, we don't have a way
of keeping Chester's mind
intact on the way out.
We'd need
superconductive wiring
from a quantum computer
to do that,
and last time I checked,
those only exist in the future.
[dramatic music]
- Nora.
Our Nora,
she can still help us.
- Oh, my God,
her back-up gauntlet.
Cisco, it's still here.
- That gauntlet's gonna have
the filament we need.
I'll strip it out
and thread it into your suit.
- Okay, in the meantime, Ralph,
can you and Frost help CCPD
evacuate downtown?
- Frost is ready to come out
and to use Cisco's present.
[all screaming, shouting]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Captain, you shouldn't be
out here!
- It's my city too.
Help these people
get out of here.
- Yes, sir!
♪ ♪
- No!
[screaming]
♪ ♪
[hollering]
[grunts]
[panting]
- Run, dude.
[all screaming]
[ice shattering]
♪ ♪
- You're welcome.
- Suit's finished.
- Okay, great, so when Barry
gets Chester's consciousness
out of there,
what is he supposed to do
with that energy?
- You remember the MAC?
- Yeah, but it's not working.
- No, but the
structural integrity
is strong enough
to contain synaptic energy.
Besides, we already moved
Chester into it, so...
- I'm sorry, what?
"We" moved Chester?
- That's right.
I may be small,
but I can bench my body weight.
♪ ♪
[lightning crackling]
- That's it.
♪ ♪
Queen: ♪ Flash ♪
- I've been saving this
for the right moment
since day one.
- Really, Cisco?
Queen: ♪ Savior of
the universe ♪
- The guy is running in
and out of a black hole.
[Queen's "Flash" playing]
- Good point.
- Yeah.
- [hollering]
[Queen's "Flash" continues]
Queen: ♪ Flash!
Ah-ah ♪
♪ He's a miracle ♪
♪ ♪
- That's your window, go!
Queen: ♪ Flash!
Ah-ah ♪
♪ King of the impossible ♪
♪ ♪
♪ He's for every one of us ♪
♪ Stand for every one of us ♪
- ♪ He saves
with a mighty hand ♪
♪ Every man, every woman,
every child ♪
♪ It's the mighty Flash ♪
- How long before he comes out?
- Seconds.
I think.
- "You think"?
- I think.
- Barry?
Barry, can you hear me?
Barry.
Barry...Barry,
please, say something.
Babe, please.
[breathing heavily]
Please, Barry,
I can't lose you too.
♪ ♪
Queen: ♪ Flash!
Ah-ah ♪
♪ King of the impossible ♪
♪ ♪
♪ He's for every one of us ♪
- [laughing]
- Oh, my God.
- Come on, let's go.
- ♪ Every man, every woman,
every child ♪
♪ It's the mighty Flash ♪
[dramatic music]
[electricity humming]
♪ ♪
- The black hole imploded.
- Chester?
Can you hear me?
Come back here, to us,
to this body, to yourself.
♪ ♪
- What up, party people?
[gasps]
Hey...hey, you're the Flash.
- [laughs]
- With the speeding around
and the lightning and all that.
Hey, big fan, man, big fan.
[laughs]
Also, where am I?
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
[no audible dialogue]
- [sighs]
Chester is doing
so much better.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
he's still, you know, glowing
in the eyes
with orange dark energy,
but he's in
really good spirits.
- How long until he gets out?
- Caitlin said his
molecules need to restabilize
at the subatomic level.
My guess is he'll need
to cook in the MAC
for another four
to six weeks, maybe more,
until he's back to normal.
- Well, believe me, he is
more than happy to chill here
at S.T.A.R. Labs
in the meantime.
And when he does get out,
that boy knows
exactly what he wants to do.
- Mm, definitely gonna
ask Natalie out.
- Speaking of going out,
Kamilla and I
are doing shawarma Tuesday,
so I'm gonna mosey.
Of course, moseying is a lot
harder these days post-Vibe.
Showing up to a date
in a S.T.A.R. Lab van,
not a good look.
- Mm, no.
I'll give you a ride.
- And risk looking like
my mom just dropped me off?
- Ooh, even better,
you can walk.
- Okay, I'm coming.
[mellow music]
- It never occurred to me
that you might want
to live a life.
That's why I never offered
to let you drive,
not because I think
you're only good in a fight.
- [Frost]You sure?
I know it's a really big ask,
and I don't want you
feeling obligated or whatever.
- Frost, you have always
been there for me,
protecting me.
Now I get to do something
for you.
Besides, even though
it's always felt
like you were a part of me,
for the first time, it feels
like I'm a part of you.
- Thank you.
- Any time.
[tender music]
[frost crackling]
♪ ♪
- Guess everything's
coming up frosty, huh?
- Yeah, I guess.
Where do I start?
How do you, you know,
live a life?
- With a life coach,
of course.
[lighthearted music]
So, first thing's first:
the name "Killer,"
it's a little bit too much
for some folks.
Have you thought about
changing it?
My mom's middle name is Anne.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- [groans]
♪ ♪
[device whirrs, chirps]
I will never accept death,
not like you did.
♪ ♪
[computer chirping]
[gasping]
[groans nervously]
[screaming]
♪ ♪
- So, what made you believe
that you could carry Chester
out of that place?
- You made me believe
I could do it.
I realized we could be
each other's support group,
even though it's gonna
take some time.
If we can carry a memory
like this together
in our hearts, carrying
somebody's consciousness
out of a black hole?
It's a piece of cake.
- [laughs]
- Besides, how else
could I get this back for you?
[panel chirps]
[tender, melancholy music]
[laughs softly]
♪ ♪
I know it's not as good
as Nora's video...
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
It's better.
Now we have something
that we can honor Nora with.
- She was pretty "schway."
[electricity thrumming]
[electricity powering up]
[sinister music]
♪ ♪
What do you want?
- For your universe to survive.
- The plinth...
you destroyed it.
You destroyed Nora's message.
- An unfortunate side effect.
But I needed to discourage you.
- From doing what?
- Hoping.
Your determination
is boundless, Flash...
it is one
of your greatest qualities...
but you cannot avoid
the coming Crisis.
- Barry has five years
before he vanishes.
- No longer.
December 10, 2019.
On that day,
he will answer the call
and make
the ultimate sacrifice.
Soon...
this world will fight
for the fate
of all the known universes.
- I'm not gonna leave
my family.
There has to be a way
to stop what's coming.
- I am sorry,
but events have been set
into motion
that you cannot
possibly comprehend.
- I don't need
to understand them!
Just tell me what I can do.
- To survive?
You can't.
In order
for billions to survive
this coming Crisis,
the Flash must die.
♪ ♪