Barry:
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created
the alternate timeline,
Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline
to how it was,
only to find
things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats
to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- They don't see
your potential.
I do.
You want to train?
I'll train you.
- You're Allen's friend,
Dr. Snow.
- I'm begging you,
don't turn her in.
I will do anything you want.
- Tender your resignation,
effective immediately.
- It's a story...it used to be
written by Iris West-Allen.
Something's changed
with our future.
God, what did I do?
- My brother's dead.
Now I'll never make another
memory with Dante again.
- You're only a man, Flash.
But I am a god.
I am Savitar.
- Now we know Alchemy's
just a lackey.
- Julian, become my servant
once more.
Become Alchemy.
[mystical music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- It's been six months since
I arrived here in India.
Though I have faith
it's out there,
the voice that once drove me
has waned.
And I fear my quest
may be for naught.
- Julian, come quick.
I think we found it.
[mystical music]
♪ ♪
- This is it.
Here, hold this.
♪ ♪
This is it.
I can feel it.
- I think we should wait
before we open it.
- No.
It needs to be set free.
[screams]
- ♪ Oh the weather outside
is frightful ♪
♪ But the fire
is so delightful ♪
- Holy winter wonderland.
- Took the words
right out of my mouth.
- Well, I guess Earth-19's
Christmas is just like ours.
- Some traditions
are multi-versal.
- So, um...
any more info on Savitar?
- Nope, all the we know
is that he's a speed god
and you're the only one
who can see him.
- All right, well, Alchemy is
Savitar's high priest
and he gets his power
from the stone
that he uses to create meta,
so I was thinking
if we can find out
what that thing is,
maybe we can figure out
how to stop him.
- I want to see
if I can dig something up.
- Okay.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
I know this is our first
Christmas together as a couple
and I want everything
to be perfect, but...
- You need to get to this.
Yes...no, I totally get it.
- Hey, uh, I got a dissertation
here from Oxford University
about the myth of an ancient
Hindu weapon
called the Brahmastra.
- Mm-hmm.
- Legendary artifact with
incredible powers,
capable of...wait for it...
- Creating metas.
- Creating meta-humans.
- Guys, that looks just like
Alchemy's stone.
- More importantly...
look who wrote this paper.
♪ ♪
- Julian?
[chuckles]
Love what you've done
with the place.
- Ah, Allen.
Thought we had a deal.
I keep your
frosty friend's secret,
and you never darken
these doors again, remember?
- I just need some
information from you
about that stone
that Alchemy uses.
- And you've come
to me because?
- Apparently, you
know a lot about it.
Well, why don't you tell me
everything you know?
And you'll never
hear from me again.
- Fine.
Many years ago,
I heard about the Brahmastra,
or as it's
colloquially called,
the Philosopher's Stone.
It is said
to be the first object
to give human beings powers.
- Like the Particle Accelerator.
- Over the years, it got lost.
I became quite obsessed
with trying to find it.
Did every piece of
available research I could
and much to my parents' dismay,
I used my future inheritance
and funded an expedition
to try and find it.
But we never found it.
Pretty soon after that,
I came here.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
- In your research,
have you ever come across
the name Savitar?
♪ ♪
- How do you know that name?
- I've done some research
of my own.
- As far as I know, Savitar
is the first meta with speed.
That's all I know, Allen.
And I suggest that you don't
waste your time on this.
♪ ♪
Move on.
- Alright..
- Julian.
♪ ♪
- Here you go.
- [chuckles]
- One whiff of aliens
and all the crazies come out.
- I'm gonna be buried under
these alien files
until next Christmas.
- Well, if by
some Christmas miracle
you dig yourself out sooner,
we do it up at the West house
on Christmas Eve.
Turkey, tree,
Grandma Esther's eggnog,
the whole shebang...and we would
love for you to come.
- One condition:
I bring the nog.
My Grandma Millie's recipe, it
is gonna knock your socks off.
- Oh, wait a minute.
- Hmm?
- We gonna have
a little nog-off.
- Really?
- Grandma Esther
versus Grandma Millie.
- Oh, you know I love
a challenge, Joe West.
- May the best grandma win.
- I am so sorry
for your grandma.
- We'll see.
- [giggles]
- Fine.
- Oh, yeah.
- I'll pick you up, all right?
- Christmas miracle.
[dramatic music]
[alarm blaring]
♪ ♪
- I told everyone inside
I'd let them live
if they followed instructions.
But I tricked them.
Which is so me.
[laughs]
- Give it up, Trickster!
- Hiya, Swiftie.
Will you do me the honor
of allowing me to kill you?
[machine gun blaring]
- You're out of ammo.
[handcuffs click]
- But I'm not out of bombs.
[laughs]
What do you say we take in
the afterlife, big boy?
[clock chirping]
[whooshing]
- Nice timing.
- You're welcome.
- There's something wrong
with my eyes.
I'm seeing double.
The Flash hit me
too hard!
I'm gonna sue you,
saucer-head!
One day,
I'll own that helmet,
and I'll use it as an ashtray
or a candy dish.
No, wait, a hubcap!
- I had that, kid.
- That's what I always say.
Especially when
I didn't have it.
- So I'm assuming you didn't
come all the way to Earth-3
to stop my Trickster.
- I have something I need to
talk to you about.
A speedster.
Calls himself Savitar.
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
- So... Savitar.
- Yeah.
- Apparently, you've grown
powerful enough
to challenge him.
- Who is he?
- Don't know,
never seen him.
You're the first speedster
I know of who has.
But every story I ever heard
about Savitar
is basically the same.
Savitar was the first man
ever granted speed.
[lightning crashing]
And over time,
he became the god of motion,
the fastest of us all.
♪ ♪
Before Savitar graces an Earth
with his presence...
- [growls]
- He sends a predecessor to
prepare for his arrival.
- Alchemy.
- Mm.
- What's he preparing for?
- A battle with you.
- Why me?
- You're threatening
his power.
- How do you know all this?
- Speed Force myths,
legends, rumors.
If Savitar's
come for you once,
he'll be back.
- Then I'll be ready.
- We'll be ready.
♪ ♪
- Run!
Wallace, run!
You got to torque to the left!
- [panting]
How'd I do?
- How'd you do?
Oh, I don't know, why
don't you see for yourself.
[device beeping]
- Hold up, are you saying
I'm faster than Barry?
- I'm saying that at this point
in his training,
you're faster than Barry.
You're faster than Barry,
you're faster than Barry,
you're faster than Barry!
- We got to tell everyone.
- Not a good idea.
- Why not?
- Self-preservation, basically.
Look, Wallace, you have
tremendous potential.
Yes, clearly, but one
thing I've learned
since coming to this Earth
is you do not trifle
with the West household.
No, you know... no,
say you're with me.
- Yeah, I'm with you.
- Yeah!
Now, we're gonna work on
your...your...yeah, your dodging
and your weaving.
[lively music]
- [sighs]
I've read every Hindu textbook
there is on mythology
and spirits and demigods
and nothing.
No mention of Savitar,
not once.
- In my experience, the answers
usually tend to come in time.
- Yeah, I can't just sit back
and wait for Savitar
or Alchemy to attack.
- You can't worry about what
may or may not lie ahead.
Besides...
it's Christmas.
A time to be with
the ones you care about.
- You know, it's just,
Savitar's still out there.
- Yeah, but not right now.
And your beautiful
girlfriend is.
Get your head
out of the books
and back into your life
with your loved ones
while you have them.
[sentimental music]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, Jay thinks he figured out
a way to find the stone.
♪ ♪
You okay?
- I don't know.
I keep seeing my brother.
Everywhere... here,
in the cortex...
- Well, this is your first
Christmas since Dante died.
Maybe your mind's
playing tricks on you.
- Yeah.
Probably.
[chuckles]
There was this one Christmas,
big family affair.
and Dante and I,
you know,
we used to fight
all the time as kids,
but that one Christmas,
we didn't fight.
We just sat and we talked
and we drank
a whole bottle of
whiskey, and...
that whole night,
we were laughing.
[laughs]
It's...
And that one night...
that one night, it was like
we felt like brothers.
- The last Christmas
before my dad died,
it snowed and snowed.
He and I just sat inside,
watching old movies
while the whole world
turned white.
It was magical.
- Hmm.
Are we about to be
the Grinches this year?
- [laughs]
- ♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
[door opens]
- Nice use of restraint.
- Yeah, well, I shopped,
and I shopped,
and now,
I am ready to drop
into your arms.
- I'm sorry I missed
Christmas shopping with you.
- It's okay.
I have everything I need.
So are you as excited
to give me my present
as I am to give you yours?
- Yeah, of course.
Definitely.
Yeah.
- You did get me
something, right?
- I did get you
something, yeah.
I just...I haven't
wrapped it yet, is all.
- ♪ Strike the harp
and join the chorus ♪
- Okay.
- Okay, um, by the way,
after you told me about
Julian's archeological dig,
I started doing some
digging of my own.
- Uh-huh.
- Turns out,
a few years ago,
four scientists were killed
in an excavation in India
and Julian was
the point person.
- He didn't mention that.
- You said he was obsessed
with that stone for years.
What if he was
covering something up?
Or someone?
- You think this is
about Alchemy?
- There's only one way
to find out.
[dramatic music]
- Julian lied about the
Philosopher's Stone.
I think he found it back
on that archeological dig.
- You think he's working with
Doctor Alchemy?
- He's not answering my calls.
- Hey, everyone.
Gang's all here,
what's going on?
- I think that Julian is
connected to Doctor Alchemy.
[device beeping]
- Jay, we got a hit.
There's energy coming from the
top of the Schults building.
That's the stone.
- Are you ready?
- Ready.
- All right.
- I'm coming, too.
- No you're not.
- No.
- Dad, I'm ready.
You...just tell them about
how fast I am.
Tell them about
the training.
- Training?
Oh, training.
The vocal training.
Because we're thinking of
going caroling.
- We're gonna
talk about this later.
[whooshing]
- We're definitely
gonna talk about it.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chanting]
- With energy form this stone,
and this building
as a refractor,
I shall restore the powers
of all the metas
from Flashpoint.
They will become the servants
of Savitar.
- It's over, Alchemy!
♪ ♪
[lightning crashing]
Please tell me
you're seeing him.
- [growls]
- Oh, I see him.
- We have to take him together.
- No, I'll cover Savitar,
you just get that stone!
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- This is not your fight,
Garrick.
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
- Julian.
♪ ♪
- Where am I?
What's going on?
♪ ♪
- [voice distorted]
Let's just say you're gonna be
our guest for a while.
- You.
I always suspected you had
your own private facility
for holding enemies.
You care to explain
what I'm doing in it?
- I know you're Alchemy, Julian.
- What?
- Turning innocent people
into meta-humans,
worshipping this Savitar?
- Sorry, um,
I'm still not following.
You think that I'm Alchemy?
That's the most absurd thing
I've ever heard.
Is that a mask?
I've never seen that
before in my life.
- I caught you!
I caught you wearing
this mask.
- You're trying to
set me up.
You're framing me,
aren't you?
The Flash, of all the people,
you're setting me up.
The hero.
- You're insane.
- The great hero!
I want my phone call,
when do I get my phone call?
- Hey.
- How you feeling?
- Not too bad for a guy
that got beat up by a myth.
- Yeah?
- You stopped him.
Well done, Barry.
- It was nice,
having you out there with me.
- Yeah, I never had
a sidekick.
- Oh, I'm your sidekick?
- Well, as a senior partner.
- Senior citizen
is more like it.
[both chuckling]
- I'll bet your dad
would've been proud of you.
Right?
[groans]
- Hey, why don't you just
take it easy, all right?
I'll see you in a little bit.
- Yeah.
[door opens]
- What do you think about
what Julian was saying?
- I know that every bad guy
we've ever had
has pretended to be our best
friend, while really being
an evil, murderous
bastard, but...
- I think if he's lying,
he sure believes
the hell out of his own lie.
- Okay, well what do we think
about this box?
- It's creepy.
Like, "Indiana Jones"
melt your face creepy.
- Have you guys figured out
anything about it yet?
♪ ♪
- It's nothing.
- Mm, it's something.
- No, I mean the box
is literally nothing.
I've run it through every
possible test I can think of...
MRI, x-ray, mass spectrometer,
the photon shifter.
Not a single reading.
Nothing.
It's like the box
doesn't even exist.
- Two weeks ago,
I almost lost you to Alchemy,
then last week aliens.
My heart can't take it, Wally.
- Dad, he gets it.
- Iris, does he?
- I think so, yeah.
- And you...
A couple weeks ago.
you were telling me
how you believed in me
and my instincts,
and now you're encouraging Wally
to do exactly the opposite?
- I don't know how much
encouraging he needed.
- What's the deal with you?
- Hmm?
- You have some psychotic need
to make other people like you
no matter what?
- I wouldn't call it psychotic.
No, my deal is,
I find people's
true talents,
and I just
marshal them along.
- Do you even have
your own opinions?
- Stop.
Stop banging on H.R.
This was all me, okay?
I pushed him to train me.
I pushed him to help me.
Wasn't like anyone else
was lining up to do it.
- Hey.
What's up?
- It's Wally.
I don't get it, Bar, it's like
his brain goes to sleep
and somebody else
is at the wheel.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Have you been losing time?
Blacking out?
Hours passing,
waking up somewhere different?
Not being sure of
how you got there.
- No.
- No?
- No!
I've had enough of these
baseless accusations
and ridiculous theories
of yours.
- Julian,
I'm trying to help you!
But you need to trust me.
- Says the man in a mask.
♪ ♪
- No, you're right.
- [chuckles]
I should've known.
I should've guessed it.
Ah!
The unexplained absences,
your passion for metas.
Your general thumbing your nose
at authority.
I'm sure you had a good laugh
behind my back.
- I actually wished
I could've told you before.
- So why tell me now?
- Because I need you
to trust me, Julian.
You are Alchemy.
I just don't think
you're aware of it.
Now, have you been
blacking out?
- Yes.
- When did it start?
♪ ♪
- My sister, Emma,
died when I was 20.
And it really broke the family
up, you know?
Mom and Dad
weren't speaking,
they wouldn't even
stay at the house.
One night,
I was there alone,
and she came back to me.
She stood
right in front of me,
clear as day...a ghost
or a vision, I don't know,
but...
she was real.
- What happened?
- She told me
about the stone.
She told me where to find it,
she told me that if I got it,
then it would
bring us back together again.
And at that point, mate,
I would've done anything
to have her back.
That's what I did.
I mounted
an expedition to India.
Days we searched, weeks.
Nothing.
And then we found it.
[screams]
And the next thing I remember,
I woke up in the hotel room.
I...
didn't remember anything,
and that's when the blackouts
started happening.
There was a news report
saying that
every other member of my team
had been found...
dead at the site.
I panicked, I thought they were
gonna blame me for their deaths,
so I ran.
I ran to America.
- What happens when you
black out, Julian?
How does it start?
- I hear the voice.
- Cisco.
- [gasps]
You're losing it, man,
you're losing it.
[yelps]
Stop scaring me!
Whatever you are,
it's not cool, okay?
Oh, I know exactly
what you are.
You are a figment
of my grief.
Please just leave.
- I can't do that, Cisco.
- This is not real.
Okay, I need an anti-psychotic.
Caitlin!
- If you leave,
I'm gonna have to
leave, too.
- So you're telling me that...
that every time
I'm blacking out...
- You've become Alchemy.
- That's impossible.
Alchemy is a monster,
he's been terrorizing people
for years.
- Look, it's not you.
Just like it wasn't you
back on that dig.
I know that this
is hard to believe,
but you have to start accepting
what's happening to you.
- Don't you want us
to be together again?
The stone.
It's the key
to everything.
It can transform people.
Open it and
I can be reborn.
We can be together again.
[sentimental music]
We can have that bottle
of whiskey.
After all, it is Christmas,
hermano.
It's the time of miracles.
♪ ♪
- I just want this
to be real.
♪ ♪
- Just open the box.
[dramatic music]
I love you, Cisco.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
Dante.
Dante?
[device beeping]
- What's that?
- Guys, what's going on?
- Cisco's workshop.
Barry, he opened the box.
- Wait...
[whooshing]
- Cisco?
- Bow to your god.
[lightning crashes]
[whooshing]
- What is happening?
- We can't see it,
just like at Alchemy's lair.
- Savitar's loose.
- Hey, Jay, Jay,
you're still too badly hurt.
- Remember: dodge and weave.
[whooshing]
- Wally, no!
[lightning crashing]
- I can see him.
- Great.
Get his attention.
- Uh, yo, metal mouth.
- [growls]
- Clearly, nobody taught you how
to place nice with others.
[whooshing]
- Cisco? Cisco, you have to
close the box!
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna save Dante.
- It's...that's not Dante,
it's Savitar.
Please, he's using
your memories against you!
- You're a good brother,
Cisco.
- Cisco, we're running
out of time.
Please,
just hand me the box.
- I won't lose him again.
I will not lose
my brother again!
- Cisco, Dante is gone.
I'm so sorry, but there is
nothing you can do about it.
But there are people
you can save right now.
If you don't close that box,
Barry and Wally will die.
[lightning crashing]
- If you do,
we can't be together.
- Cisco, listen to me!
♪ ♪
- Don't.
[metallic scraping]
-Lo siento, hermano.
[lightning crashes]
[sentimental music]
- Thanks.
- You kidding?
That was awesome.
♪ ♪
- Are you sure you're okay?
- Still in one piece.
- I don't know
what happened.
- So now that the box
is closed,
Savitar's, what,
gone for good?
- I don't know,
but we need to find out.
Cisco?
If we can't use this box,
Julian,
he may be our only link to
Savitar now, right?
- I think we can
use both of them.
If Caitlin's right and this
thing messes with brainwaves,
then I have a plan.
- Hey.
You put my son's life
in danger again.
- And he saved Barry's life.
Joe, why...
why do you think
I help Wally?
'Cause I'm selfish,
I get something...
I don't get
anything out of it.
I help Wally
'cause the kid is special.
He's extraordinary.
His powers are extraordinary
and...look, I get it.
I'm...I'm not his dad
and I don't have the same
safety concerns as you,
of course not,
but Joe,
one thing I do know,
the longer you deny someone
their potential,
the more they're gonna
look for it elsewhere.
- So what am I doing here?
- Okay, Julian, today
when I was fighting Savitar,
it...he and Alchemy,
they had the same voice.
- All right,
what does that mean?
- I don't think
there is an Alchemy,
I think it's Savitar
speaking through you.
- Savitar clearly possesses
someone who rallies worshippers.
- But he's like a poltergeist,
he needs a medium
to manifest himself.
- You.
- Right,
but what does that mean?
- We think we figured out a way
to sync your brain
to the stone.
- And it'll allow us
to speak directly to Savitar.
- I thought...
- If you want to try
to be free of this,
you need to trust us.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
I've never liked you, Allen.
- Yeah.
- Having a little séance
with your friends now
is not gonna help change
that fact.
You do know that.
♪ ♪
Fine, I'll try it.
- Deep breaths.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- You're gonna count
backwards from ten.
- [sighs]
Te...
♪ ♪
(snaps fingers)
- That was quick.
- Okay, so, um,
how long till this works?
- Not really sure, it may take
a minute for his brain waves...
- [screams]
♪ ♪
Hello, Barry.
It's been a while.
♪ ♪
[sinister music]
- Savitar?
♪ ♪
- None of you
are on your knees.
It's a smart move
to bow before a deity.
- You're not God.
- To be a god,
you just have to make people
believe you are.
- No one believes in you.
- You should, Iris.
I hold the power of life
and death over all of you.
- How do you know
so much about us?
- I know you, Caitlin.
Cisco, Joe, Wally.
The fake Wells.
I know your fears
and I know your weaknesses.
I know you better
than you know yourselves.
I know your destinies.
One shall betray you.
One shall fall.
One will suffer a fate
far worse than death.
This is the knowledge
I have for you.
About your everlasting
damnation.
- Who are you?
- I am the future, Flash.
- What do you want
from us?
- Everything!
Everything you took from me,
I want it back.
And I'm gonna
take it back.
Then, I will destroy you.
- Then why haven't you already?
If you're all-powerful,
then why don't you just
go ahead and kill us all now,
be done with it?
Because you can't.
- You did this to me.
You trapped me in eternity.
Your future self...
you did this to me, Barry.
And now the age
of my revenge rises.
My freedom is at hand.
You will feel my wrath.
The wrath of Savitar!
- [panting]
Did it work?
- That was so scary.
I mean, that was...
was it not truly frightening,
what the voice and the
prophesies and the...
oh, it was...I mean,
that a scare-a-thon, wasn't it?
I'm gonna have a mint tea
and a coffee and a lay down.
- Do you think the things
that he said about
one of us betraying him
and one of us dying
could really be true?
- I mean, if it really was
future Barry
that pissed him off and
locked him up somewhere,
then maybe he knows
what happens to future us.
- He doesn't.
He's never getting out of
wherever he's trapped.
- So how are we
supposed to stop him?
- The stone.
- Jay's right, the stone has
been the key to everything.
It's...it's how he
controlled Julian,
it's how he's created
more metas.
- So we destroy the stone
and Savitar is gone for good.
- It's impossible to destroy.
It's been around forever,
there's a reason for that.
- Why don't we just
bury it again,
put it back in the ground
where you found it?
- Mm-mm.
"Jumanji."
- Someone would just find it
and we'd be right back
where we started.
- We need to make that box
disappear forever.
There's only one thing
we can do with it.
Throw it into the Speed Force.
- Wait, you can do that?
- Oh, yeah.
The Speed Force
is eternity itself,
an endless void of time
and energy.
- It'd be like trying to find it
after it got lost in space.
- But that stone is loaded
with gravimetric force.
I mean, I don't think
you could run fast enough
to reach the Speed Force and
carry that at the same time.
- He can with my help.
We run as fast as we can.
You trail behind me,
siphon off some of my speed,
combine it with your own,
and when you have enough,
throw that thing
deep into the Speed Force.
♪ ♪
- And that would work?
- We need to find out.
♪ ♪
- Sure you're up for this,
Flash?
- You got it, Flash.
- I'll let you know
when you reach optimal speed.
Ready...go!
[whooshing]
♪ ♪
- Jay's moving really fast,
this might actually work.
♪ ♪
- Now, Barry!
[suspenseful music]
- In other legal news,
the highly publicized trial
of Jared Morillo, AKA
"Plunder," comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty of
grand theft
and aggravated assault after he
was caught by the Flash
robbing the Central City Museum
earlier this year.
- Don't!
♪ ♪
Please don't!
Don't do this.
- Now, finally,
I am free of you.
- Barry, I love you.
- No, don't say that,
all right?
You're gonna be all right.
I'm begging you, just...
- Barry!
- You lose, Barry.
- No!
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
Hey, hey, Iris.
Iris, hey...
♪ ♪
No.
Iris.
Iris, Iris...
[sobs]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
Jay?
What the hell was that?
Where was I?
- The future.
- I've never run
to the future.
I've traveled to the past,
but I always came back
to the present.
I saw myself.
And Iris.
And Savitar, what...
he killed her.
That's five months from now.
Is that actually
gonna happen?
- I don't know.
- You don't...
- You shouldn't have
seen that.
♪ ♪
- This doesn't
make sense, we...
we just got rid of the
Philosopher's Stone.
I mean, Savitar shouldn't have
even been there!
Oh, my God.
This is where the newspaper
in the time vault changed.
The byline, this is why
it's not Iris, this...
Iris didn't write
that story anymore
eight years from now,
because...
She's dead.
- Barry...
- I just watched her die.
I saw myself try to save her,
but I wasn't fast enough.
Jay, tell me that
this isn't my destiny.
- What you saw was one
possibility of the future.
What may be,
or may not.
- Okay, then I can stop this
from happening.
I can run back there...
- You can't go back there.
Not again, not ever.
- All right, then I'll figure
out exactly how it happened,
how we wind up on that street,
and I'll just make sure
that we don't go there.
And if we don't go there...
- Barry!
This is why speedsters
don't travel to the future.
Nobody should know this much
about their own.
Just as their are infinite
Earths in the multiverse,
there are infinite possibilities
to the future.
It's always bending,
always changing.
Every decision you make
creates another alternative.
- I won't let Iris die.
- The future isn't written yet.
And it might not even turn out
to be what you saw.
You need to focus
on the here and now.
You have to live your life.
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
You and Jay disappeared, and...
- Naw, I'm okay.
I'm just glad to see you.
- So where's Jay?
- Jay, uh, decided to
go ahead and go back to Earth-3.
But he wanted to wish everybody
a Merry Christmas.
- So, it worked?
The stone...
- It's gone.
It's lost in the Speed Force.
- Good, good.
- I don't know about you guys,
but being mind-punked
by a speed god that we
piss off in the future,
it's...it's enough to kill
your Christmas spirit.
- Guys,
Christmastime is here.
We need a little Christmas.
Right this very minute.
Who's with me?
BA.
- Well, he's right.
It's Christmas,
we should be together.
Let's have it.
- I'm still in
if everybody else is.
- Yes!
- Okay, we'll be there.
- Yeah!
- Julian...
- Where's he going?
- Hey, where ya going?
Do you have Christmas plans?
The West's are having
a Christmas get-together.
After what you've been through,
you shouldn't be alone.
- [clears throat]
I actually prefer to
be alone at Christmas.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Sleigh bells ring ♪
♪ Are you listening? ♪
- Rain on Christmas.
That's neither
holly nor jolly.
Hey, listen, um...
about Dante.
Thank you for
talking me off the ledge.
- Of course,
you'd do the same for me.
In fact,
you did the same for me.
- I was gonna say.
- [chuckles]
- Caitlo...Caitlo, Ciscan...
okay...whoo...
you got to try the eggnog
a holiday concoction
done by Joe
and his hot girlfriend...
- Babe.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- You seem a little weird.
No?
You do know
we won, right?
We defeated the bad guy.
- Yeah, I know.
- Okay.
- Grandma Esther.
- Grandma Millie.
- Let's see.
Mm.
Damn, that's strong.
- Oh!
[laughing] So is that,
my God!
- Our grandmothers are
alcoholics.
- Yes.
[giggles]
You know, technically,
we don't have to be standing
under the mistletoe to... mm.
- ♪ Sleigh bells ring ♪
- Finally.
- No comments from
the peanut gallery.
- No, but really,
it's about time.
- Mm-hmm.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Hold on.
And it's my daughter.
Yeah, just give me
a quick minute,
and then we can...yeah.
Hey, kiddo...
- Joe.
I saw you kiss her, good job.
[both shushing]
We're...oh,
that's right, the thing.
BA, hey.
- How many of those
have you had?
- B...where'd you go? Here.
- I'm right here.
- Oh, I see ya.
- Now that Cecelia's away,
this is from
all of us to you.
Merry Christmas, son.
[lively music]
[laughter]
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, man, it's time.
- You're ready, Wallace.
- Welcome to the team.
Kid Flash.
- Are we really calling me
"Kid Flash"?
- Yeah, I think we are.
- Kid Flash!
- Shh!
[knocking]
- Police!
- I got it.
It's not the police.
We're the police.
- You're the police!
- Calm down.
Hey, Julian.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
Here, let me get that.
- Thanks.
Uh, after everything
that happened,
being alone felt
a bit lonely, so...
- Yeah.
- This is for you.
- What's this?
- I spoke to Captain Singh,
and he hadn't put through
your resignation
paperwork yet, so...
well, if you'd, uh, you know,
like your old lab back,
or you'd like to
share it again.
- Thanks, Julian.
Merry Christmas, man.
- Cheers, mate.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Merry Christmas.
- Can I offer you some eggnog?
- I'd love some, yeah.
Happy Christmas, everyone.
- I'm glad you came.
- Thank you, yeah.
- ♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
- Whoa.
Do you hear that?
- It's outside.
- ♪ Oh come ye oh come ye ♪
- Carolers.
- ♪ To Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come and behold him ♪
- Caroling in the rain.
That sucks.
- ♪ Sing, choirs of angels ♪
- Hey.
What're you doing?
- It's okay, I got this.
We may not be able to have
a perfect Christmas,
but we can have a white one.
- ♪ All ye citizens
of heaven above ♪
- So.
When are we gonna
exchange presents?
- How 'bout right now?
- Okay.
- Follow me.
- Let's get out of here.
Okay, going through a door,
be careful.
Okay, right here.
Okay, are you ready?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Open your eyes...
now.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
- I...I don't understand,
where are we?
- Home.
♪ ♪
- What?
- I couldn't sleep on
Cisco's couch anymore,
and your place is sort
of small for two,
so I signed a lease
and I put both of
our names on it.
- I got you a wallet.
- I'm sure I'll love it.
- Barry,
this is a big step.
- Not for me.
♪ ♪
I don't know what's
gonna happen in the future.
All I know is,
right here, right now,
I want to spend every moment
I can with you.
You're the first thing I
want to see when I wake up.
And the last thing...
♪ ♪
- I love you, Barry Allen.
- I love you, Iris West.
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.