My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything in my friends' power
to bring me back, and in doing so
our world was opened up to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
This is where I came
out of the Speed Force.
And a wave of dark matter
washed out with you.
DeVoe orchestrated
everything to get the people
he wanted on the bus.
But why does he need their powers?
I can't figure out his end game.
We got a planner, just like Thawne.
I hereby deem Barry
Allen's appeal deni...
Wait!
- DeVoe?
- Not DeVoe.
It's Ralph.
Barry Allen is hereby
ordered release immediately.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Some people don't think you
should be back on the force.
When do you think I can come back?
When everyone believes DeVoe
is really alive and well.
I call this my thinking cap.
[SCREAMS]
He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers. All of them.
We know a bus meta.
There's three more people
out there who need our help,
and we need to find
them before DeVoe does.
♪ ♪
What if...
What if I just, like, breach all three
of the bus metas to, like, Earth-2?
How about this?
We alter each bus meta's DNA
by performing intercellular surgery.
And what? And turn them into chickens?
Yeah.
We're not Frankensteining
innocent people.
Listen, Ramon, DeVoe wants these bodies.
All right? Maybe if
we change the bodies,
we keep these people safe.
I'm sorry, don't you
have, like, six PhDs?
- Seven.
- Yeah, which one of them
is in mad science?
Mad science is just an area of study.
It's not a degree, okay?
And by the way, I
don't see you coming up
with any other ideas.
You know why?
'Cause it's bed time
over here on Earth-1.
Do you know what bed time is?
- Do they have that on Earth-2?
- Bed... Bed time.
All right, it's this thing
where we just shut down
to recharge our batteries.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I highly recommend it.
[BEEPING]
- Harry.
- You're still here? What?
No matter what you think,
DeVoe's already thought of it.
So why don't you just go home,
recharge, start again in
the morning, all right?
I'm gonna keep going.
[SIGHS] Goodnight.
♪ ♪
Maybe you have thought of everything.
Just like Thawne.
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What is all this?
This is gonna give us
the edge we finally need
to be smarter than DeVoe.
Or me to be smarter
than DeVoe, actually.
Take a look at this.
♪ ♪
What is that?
This is an intelligence booster.
You put this thing on Dibny here,
and even he would be able to understand
the point source construction.
You put it on a real genius,
I'll finally be able
to outthink the Thinker.
You know what, I'm not
sure this thinking cap
is the best idea you've ever had.
It's an intelligence booster.
It looks like a thinking cap.
You don't like it, blame yourself.
- You gave me the idea.
- What?
You're the one that said
DeVoe planned all this
just like Thawne in order to stop Barry.
And you said that DeVoe became
the Thinker the same night
you became the Flash,
and so I hacked into
security footage of that
night to see how he did it.
♪ ♪
This is why he's so smart.
DeVoe boosted his intelligence
with neurochemical engineering
powered by the dark energy
from the particle accelerator explosion.
And if we build our own,
we can do the exact same.
Wait, you wanna blast your
brain with 10 billion joules
of dark energy?
I've harnessed energy from
the particle accelerator
explosion before,
and I can do it again.
Yeah, but Harry,
reengineering your brain's
neurochemistry, that's...
DeVoe did it.
So can I.
How many more metas have to die
before we finally stop DeVoe?
Uh... not... Not me. I mean...
I say we go for it. Right?
Right, guys?
What do you think?
I say we explore it.
Yeah, I agree.
Ramon.
No, this is way too risky.
Of course it's risky, but if we succeed,
we will save the lives of
the four remaining bus metas,
including a member of our team.
You're talking about intense
amounts of dark energy
going right into your brain,
right into that cap,
that turned a mac and
cheese loving pacifist
into a homicidal maniac.
You put that cap on,
what's it gonna do to you?
I've run the numbers dozens of times.
The math and the chemistry check out.
I can do this.
I don't think you can.
I can with your help.
Not this time.
All right, let's keep coming
up with more ways to solve this.
♪ ♪
Just so I'm clear on this,
someone finally came up
with a way to stop this
La-Z-Boy riding lunatic
and we just might not do it?
♪ ♪
That's really cool, guys.
- I got this one.
- Yeah, thanks.
[SIGHS]
This is the only way.
I'm gonna do it with
or without his help.
Hey, Ralph.
Look, don't worry, okay?
We're gonna figure this out.
Yeah, everybody keeps saying that,
and each time we almost
get DeVoe, he gets away.
Every time he gets away,
he's one step closer to getting me.
Hey, that is not going to happen.
Well, I can't take that
chance anymore, Iris.
So if anyone needs me,
I will be downstairs
in my tiny guest quarters
until this is over.
There are still three
bus metas out there,
and we're gonna need your help
to find them and protect them.
Iris, the only person I
need to protect from now on
is good old Ralphie boy.
You are part of this team.
Yeah, and I'm the only
one with a body that DeVoe
is trying to snatch.
You don't have any concept
of how dangerous it is
for me out there.
Yes, I do.
How could you?
Because I'm the leader of this team.
Yeah, that's right, you are.
But you're always back
there hiding safe and sound.
While the rest of us
are out in the field
putting our lives on the line.
♪ ♪
♪ Just take me to your paradise ♪
♪ I wanna see the body skies ♪
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Some drama in the Cortex.
Thanks for the coffee.
It's all good.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm, you know...
Cecile's in her third trimester,
so it's definitely getting serious.
You guys have any names picked out yet?
Uh, yeah. A few.
Come on, I'm not gonna tell anybody.
No, you're not, because
you're not gonna know
until Cecile tells you.
- All right.
- Anyway.
I talked to Singh about
getting you back in the lab.
Yeah, and?
It's gonna be a while.
Why? I thought Judge Hankerson
and Singh had everything they needed.
We thought so, too, but
the mayor wants to sit down
with the DeVoes herself.
Seriously?
Look, we can't find Marlize,
so the only chance we
got is to get Ralph to use
his nauseating powers to
impersonate DeVoe again.
All right, I'll ask him,
but right now he'll barely
leave S.T.A.R. Labs.
What happened to that
whole buddy system thing
you had going on?
It's not enough for him, I guess.
Then I don't know, Barry.
I should be out there.
Helping people. Putting bad guys away.
Right now, we should
be trying to stop DeVoe
and finding those last few bus metas.
'Cause I got a bad feeling one
of them's gonna show up soon.
♪ ♪
[SCREAMS]
[SIZZLING]
Next time, it'll be your hand.
Now, everybody on the floor.
♪ ♪
Dude, you got a death wish?
Do what he says.
Stealing is a sin.
You shouldn't be using the powers
you've been given this way.
I'll use them any way I see fit.
Including frying you to a crisp
if you move any closer.
Oh, I don't think you will.
You don't wanna hurt me
or anyone in this bank.
You can still walk away from this.
♪ ♪
But the moment you touch that money,
your life changes forever.
Now, you don't really want that, do you?
Maybe you're right.
Or maybe you've got a death wish!
What the hell?
My powers!
They're gone!
- [GRUNTS]
- No, no, no!
[CHATTER]
Hey, buddy, you're a real...
♪ ♪
Hero.
[BEEPING]
- Cisco.
- Hmm?
What do you got?
Oh, you know, the usual.
Just loads and loads of dark matter.
Makes sense. Eye witnesses said this guy
melted this vault door
with fire from his hands.
Hmm, figures. But not just any fire.
This fire melted through ten
inches of reinforced steel.
I mean, that would take over
6,000 degrees Fahrenheit.
Ten times the thermal
output of Rory's heat gun.
Well, here's where it gets weirder.
Apparently shortly after,
his powers stopped working.
Stopped working?
Yeah, so if he was one of our bus metas,
I guess we have one less to worry about.
Nobody's powers stop working.
Eric Fry, six months ago,
were you on the 405 bus?
Please.
Do I look like someone
who takes public transit?
All right, then, Mr. Fry.
How long have you had your powers?
- A few years.
- Oh.
You're an OG meta.
And you just started using them now?
Here, yeah.
Once Flash showed up, I
took this act on the road.
Doesn't matter anymore, though.
Right, you don't have
your powers anymore.
'Cause they just disappeared? Vanished?
Into thin air? Huh?
All right, Cisco.
He's clear.
You have any idea how this happened?
One minute I had powers. The next...
Nothing.
Will you get him out of here?
That's right. Get him out of here.
- All right.
- Yeah, get him out of here.
I can't believe his powers
disappeared like that.
How does someone lose their powers?
So, I can think of a couple of ways
this might have happened.
If this Eric Fry
metastasizes solar radiation
to create heat, we
could put him in the dark
to de-power him.
But it was still broad daylight.
Okay, maybe his internal biochemistry
has been altered to create its
own internal thermal combustion
and he just ran out of fuel.
Okay, so if this guy's
not one of the bus metas,
then that met s that there's
still three more out there
before DeVoe gets to me.
So, I'm safe. Safer, I'm safer.
Those are innocent people, Ralph.
I'm innocent. I'm still
gonna get terminated.
Oh, my God.
- I'm Sarah Connor.
- No.
I'm gonna go back to my room.
Get some comfort food.
Ralph...
The way I see it, Fry
walks into the bank
with his fire powers,
meets this other guy,
and then his powers are gone.
Coincidence? I think not.
So you think this guy
did something to Fry?
I think we can ask him some questions.
I interviewed every eye
witness in that bank.
Nobody knew who he was.
Cisco, why don't you
crosscheck the deposits
from today with dad's witness list?
Way ahead of you.
Everyone on the list checks
out except Matthew Kim...
An EMT out of Central City General.
Barry, let's go ask some questions.
Oh, I'll go.
Barry, you can stay here.
Um, okay.
Well, you know, I never
go out into the field,
so I thought, you know...
Yeah, I mean, you're the boss.
Okay. Uh, Caitlin,
why don't you see how this
power stealing thing works,
and Cisco, why don't you
use the satellite's tracking
perimeters to scan the
city for dark matter?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
I'll just come running if you need me.
Okay. Thanks.
♪ ♪
[CLEARS THROAT] Can I hang out in here?
[SIGHS]
Can you... Do you mind...
Can you save the eating till later?
We're actually trying
to save lives here.
This is really good, though.
[SIGHS] Is it?
Yeah.
You put this together pretty quick, huh?
Yes, I did, for a test run.
[WHIRRING]
Ooh.
I can feel my neurons firing.
Firing at a rate 20
times their normal rate.
And that's without the
addition of dark matter.
I can feel my brain's
processing systems evolving.
There's a 67% chance you're
gonna spill that mustard
on the floor. Oh!
Okay, how did you do that?
Well, I simply analyzed
your eating habits
and extrapolated them at
a predictive behavior model
all within four seconds.
The cap is working.
Eh, cool, but I'm not quite convinced.
No?
Really? You're not convinced?
All right, then.
The answer is none.
And have a little more respect
for your body, will you?
This is a veggie dog, man.
I'm not talking about
the veggie dog, man.
I'm talking about the wiping
the mustard on the pants
causes the pant movement which
indicates a lack of clothing
to bodily friction, which
can mean only one thing.
Right, what kind of
underwear am I wearing?
And the answer...
is none.
You got all that from
your fancy metal cap?
- Yes, I did.
- It's impressive, Harry.
Except for one very small thing.
Which is?
Your head is on fire.
[LAUGHS] It's no...
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTS]
♪ ♪
[DISTANT SIRENS]
When I mentioned spending
more time together,
I meant family
barbecues, not questioning
people of interest.
I know, I just want people
to know that I'm not afraid
to go out in the field
every once in a while.
Who says you are?
- Ralph.
- Ralph?
He should talk. He won't even
leave the building.
I know, but it made me wonder, you know?
What kind of leader constantly
puts everyone else's life
on the line except their own?
Oh, baby.
We all know you're fearless.
Whenever you've been
needed on the field,
you've gone.
So don't let Ralph get in your head.
Excuse me. CCPD.
We're looking for an
EMT named Matthew Kim.
Yes, he's right through there.
There? Thank you.
[KNOCKING]
Matthew Kim?
Detective Joe West, CCPD.
We'd like to ask you some
questions about the attack
at Central City Bank this morning.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I wouldn't know anything about that.
Really? 'Cause I have a dozen witnesses
that saw you stand up to the
man that melted the vault.
♪ ♪
He was going to hurt people.
It was my duty to help them.
Any reason you left
without making a statement?
♪ ♪
I need to finish restocking my inventory
before another call comes in.
I can't help you.
Look, Matthew, we know
you had something to do
with that guy at the
bank losing his powers.
We need to know. What did you do to him?
Why? So you can steal mine?
No, no!
- Let her go.
- Put the gun down.
I said put it down.
♪ ♪
He didn't deserve those powers.
He was hurting people.
Flash!
You're not the only one that's
been blessed with powers.
I'm helping people, too.
Not like this.
You did this, not me.
I got him.
♪ ♪
I lost my speed.
What do you mean you lost your speed?
Uh, guys, I think I found it.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[WHOOSHING]
[GIGGLES] This is amazing.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, it is.
Well, I've run every
test I can think of.
EKG, cellular regression synthesis,
brain chemistry, and
dark matter confirms it.
Iris is a speedster.
So, what about Barry?
Um...
Everything that was a part of you...
Your speed, connection
to the Speed Force,
the dark matter...
It's all a part of Iris now.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
- Can you...
- Reverse it?
I don't know. I can try.
So, Matthew Kim isn't just removing DNA.
He's transferring it
to anybody he touches.
He's not getting rid of metas.
He's creating new ones.
Well, that's not the only thing.
Guess who's got an
apartment just a block away
from the 405 bus line and rides
it every day to get to work?
So Matthew is our bus meta, not Fry.
Which means that DeVoe is gonna
come after him sooner or later.
And if DeVoe gets Matthew's abilities,
he could take away all our powers.
Unless we get him on our side first.
Then he can remove the
meta DNA from DeVoe.
- Could that work?
- I mean, yeah.
It could. As best I can tell,
Matthew's abilities work by melting down
the highly concentrated
bonds between DNA.
That makes them totally
pliable so he can extract them
and infuse somebody else
with the exact same meta DNA.
Melting highly concentrated bonds.
Melting Point.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I gotta write that down.
Okay, great, so you guys
figure out how to get
this Mr. Melting Point
in the same room as DeVoe
and not get his brains sucked out.
I'm gonna go get a couple of bear claws
and go back to my room.
It's not Mr. Melting Point.
Look, it's just Melting Point.
You know, somebody out there
has Fry's fire powers right now.
We need to find them as much
as we need to find Matthew.
I'm on it.
And I'll see if there's
a way to reverse this.
♪ ♪
Well...
Until then, what do we do?
We train.
Okay.
[BEEPING]
Ramon! Where...
There you are. What are you doing?
Updating some software.
Oh, good. So nothing.
Great, I need your help.
Try Ralph.
Ralph's useless.
All he does is eat.
What do you want?
Do you have a microfilament
compression wrench
with cobalt retrieving clamp?
Yeah.
Yeah, where is it?
Why, so you can work on your death cap?
- It's not a death cap.
- It's a death cap.
- No, it isn't.
- I hear there's plenty
- of tools on Earth-2.
- Yeah, well I'm on Earth1.
Oh, you need a lift?
TOGETHER: I'll breach you there right now!
TOGETHER: That's not what I sound like!
Fine.
Cisco, why can't you just help him?
Why am I the only one who
thinks putting a rageoholic
and dark matter together is a bad idea?
He's trying to stop DeVoe.
That's not a bad idea.
He's trying to match his
intellect with a mad man
whose innovations are warping his brain.
Have you not seen "Spider-Man 2"?
- No.
- How can you live with yourself?
It might be dangerous,
but it also might work.
And we're kind of running out of ideas.
Besides, Harry's gonna do this
whether you help him or not.
So maybe there's some way
to make this thinking cap
and to keep him safe.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
She can move.
[BEEPING]
Uh-oh.
Hey, Iris, you might just wanna...
- I can't slow down.
- That's okay.
All right, just gradually
ramp your speed down,
otherwise you're gonna...
[GLASS BREAKING]
[GRUNTS]
- Do that?
- Whoa.
[GROANS]
Hey, you okay?
Come here. You good?
Yep, I'm straight. I'm straight.
Thank God for speed healing, huh?
[GASPS]
- Yeah.
- [SIGHS]
Hey, I know this isn't easy on you.
I... I'm fine.
Barry...
I am. It...
♪ ♪
I lost my speed.
I lost my job at the CCPD.
Just feels like DeVoe is slowly
taking everything away from me.
♪ ♪
He hasn't taken everything away.
What if I never get it back?
Hey.
Caitlin is gonna find something, okay?
Mm-hmm.
[SIGHS]
Until then, you just have to
watch me like I've watched you
these last three years.
Yeah, I guess so.
[ALARMS BLARING]
[WHOOSHING]
Wow, that's super annoying.
What's happening?
Baldwin Tower's on
fire. CCFD's responding,
but there's people on the
top floor they can't reach.
Okay, Caitlin, Killer
Frost is on fire duty.
Ralph, Cisco, suit up.
- Yeah.
- Not a chance.
This could just be a trap
for DeVoe to get us out
- in the open.
- Hey, I think we got
a bigger problem.
We don't have a Flash anymore.
Yeah, we do.
I don't think she's ready for all that.
I mean, she just got her...
You just got your powers.
Um...
No. I wanna do this.
Okay. Okay, all right.
We'll monitor from here, then.
Okay, well, you can't go
out there wearing that.
Oh. Right.
Sorry, Cait.
Mask?
Right.
Thank you, Jesse Quick.
♪ ♪
Nice.
Please, be careful.
[WHOOSHING]
♪ ♪
Guess you're on comms.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, how do I... How do I...
- Other monitor.
- Wrong monitor.
[GRUNTS]
[CHAIR HISSES]
♪ ♪
I'm here. Oh, boy.
Okay, Iris, there are
five people trapped
on the 14th floor.
Just get them out of
there as fast as you can.
♪ ♪
- I did it.
- Great work, okay?
Now you gotta get back in there
and put out the fire.
Right.
Guys, I'm here. What do I do?
You know what to do. Use your arms.
Create wind funnels.
Suck all the oxygen out of the room.
And the fire will go out.
Just like he's done a thousand times.
You got this, girl.
♪ ♪
It's making it worse.
[BEEPING]
Is she rotating her
arms the wrong way or...?
Just go the opposite direction, okay?
♪ ♪
- [RUMBLING]
- [SCREAMS]
Iris, what was that?
Iris!
My leg is pinned. I can't move.
♪ ♪
Okay, you have to phase through it.
What? I don't know how.
You have to vibrate
your whole body, okay?
You just... you have to feel it.
I can't. I can't move. I can't do it.
We're running out of time, Barry.
The integrity of the room is failing.
The ceiling's gonna collapse.
Barry! The whole place is going up.
♪ ♪
[WHIRRING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
There's still a little bit
of irritation in your lungs
from all the smoke
you inhaled last night,
but you should be good to go soon.
And your leg's already healed.
Shouldn't have let her go out there.
You weren't ready.
I saved a lot of people
last night, Ralph.
Yeah, and Cisco had to save you.
All right, look, we
just need to make sure
this doesn't happen again.
We have to find Matthew Kim
and whoever he transferred
Eric Fry's powers to.
How close are you to reversing this?
- I don't know that I can.
- What?
I was up all night trying
every conceivable solution.
Dark matter splicing,
pattern DNA cloning,
even regrowing meta
enhanced stem material
on a cellular level.
Nothing will work.
I cannot replicate
Melting Point's powers.
So unless we find him and get
him to reverse what he's done...
Iris is Team Speedster
on a permanent basis.
Great, that's, uh... That's great.
I'm gonna go work on my will.
Ralph...
♪ ♪
Harry. Harry, I know you hear me.
Another team member hurt
by one of DeVoe's metas.
- I know.
- And we can fix it,
but, no, no. I know!
And you know what else?
Snow wasn't the only one
who was up all night working.
I was up all night
working. I'm almost done.
I'm almost finished, but
you won't help me finish!
I'm gonna help you finish!
- Finish...
- The thinking cap.
I'm gonna help you
finish the thinking cap.
It's an intelligence booster, actually.
It's called an intelligence booster.
- Two conditions.
- What are your conditions?
One, we stimulate your synapses
without using dark matter.
Fine, no dark matter. And two?
The minute you start acting
like Locutus of Borg and start
assimilating everybody
with your Borg chair...
You can vibe me back to my Earth. Okay?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
Take it easy.
It's just day two.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, man.
You were right about running.
[SIGHS]
It's so peaceful.
So calming.
Actually makes it easy to think.
Look, I mean, you just got your speed.
You know that, right?
I don't think anyone
would hold it against you
if you took a minute and maybe
just let Cisco and Caitlin
handle this meta, just
run point like always.
Just stay here like I always do?
No, I... You know I didn't mean that.
No, I know you didn't. I did.
Iris, I...
You think that... what, that
you need to prove to the team
that you're not afraid?
No, not to all of you. To me.
Barry, when I was a reporter,
I was always in the field
putting myself in danger for a story.
And after last year,
for some reason that just stopped.
Maybe it was because of Savitar.
Maybe because you were
gone into the Speed Force.
I don't know, but...
I quit my job.
I joined this team, and
now for the most part,
I just stay here while
all of you are out there
putting your lives on the line.
Because of our powers.
No, it's not just that, Barry.
And it took me getting
these powers to realize it.
But now that I'm the one that has it,
it's my turn to do what
all of you have been doing.
To prove to myself that
that fearlessness that I had
is still in me.
[ALARMS BLARING]
Guys, I think we found
Fry's missing powers.
♪ ♪
Then go get them.
Satellite is tracking
temperature at the same
intensity as the bank robbery, so...
- That's him.
- Yeah.
So who's that?
Matthew Kim.
Kim's gonna try and steal his powers.
All right, let's go.
No. You guys are on point.
♪ ♪
I can do this.
You sure about this?
I have to, Barry.
All right, but remember,
he can't touch you.
Or he'll take your powers away, too.
Right.
Also I'm not sure my clothes
are gonna work this time.
I have a fix for that.
It's the best I could do on
such short notice, though.
Thanks, Cisco.
I got hangers.
All right, here we go.
Don't make us shoot you! Stand down!
Oh, I don't think so, copper.
Not until I get my money!
- This is a mistake!
- Down! Down! Take him down!
Hold your fire!
You need to stop this.
Oh, I just got going, pal.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Wait, you're that hero
from the bank, aren't you?
I am.
And I need you to stop this.
So you can take my
powers like you did his?
I don't think so!
You just gave them to me.
What are you talking about?
You didn't know that?
When you took powers from him,
you gave them to me.
[THWACKS]
♪ ♪
And now I'm gonna get what he couldn't.
Money!
I think you've done
enough saving for today.
I'll take it from here.
♪ ♪
How about we just end this right now?
That sounds fun.
'Cause I was just warming up.
[FIRE CRACKLES]
What's wrong? Can't stand the heat?
All right, Iris, we need
you to run around him.
Create a vortex.
The lack of oxygen should
extinguish the flames.
Can't get close to him!
Temperature's at 800 degrees.
Like, how hot is that?
As hot as lava.
Guys, we need a plan!
Oh, I got a plan, lady.
And it's called give me my
money before I unleash hell!
Yeah.
What the hell is that?
That is a thermo cyclone.
That fire's gonna get too
close to those apartments.
And thousands of people will die.
What do we do?
We turn this thing on.
- Harry, no, don't.
- Iris needs answers.
- Hey, we haven't...
- She needs answers!
Come on, guys! What do I do?
Do it.
[WHIRRING]
Barry, come on, I need an answer!
Hang on, Iris. Hang on.
There are 4,827 ways this could go,
and all of those ways
will fail except one.
If Iris uses her speed
to draw enough water
from Central City Bay into her wake,
she could extinguish that blaze.
You want her to create a tidal wave?
♪ ♪
It's our only hope.
Iris, I need you to
run as fast as you can.
- On the water.
- On the water? What?
Make sure when you run
you dig your heels in
and you move back and
forth in a tight formation.
- Why?
- So you drag as much
water ashore as possible.
Put out the cyclone.
You want me to create
a 100-foot tidal wave?
Are you crazy? I can't do that.
Yes you can. You told me that you used
to be fearless. I know
that you still are.
You're the bravest person that I know.
You can do this.
I know you can. We all do.
Now run, Iris. Run.
♪ ♪
Yeah, that's it. Yeah, that's it.
And then tight formations,
okay? Tight formations.
♪ ♪
That's it, Iris. Keep going.
Keep going.
♪ ♪
Everybody back!
Move, move, move, now!
♪ ♪
Long live rock and roll!
[SHOUTS]
Yes!
♪ ♪
Nice work.
She did it.
Nice work, Flash.
I'm so sorry I did this to you.
I thought I was cleaning up the city,
but I was just making it worse.
Well, we stopped him.
He's in Iron Heights, and
that's all that matters now.
You sure you both wanna do this?
It's your call.
I have to say running
on water is really fun.
But, if you guys will have me back,
I would love to get back
behind the console again.
- Of course.
- Please, and thank you.
All ready?
TOGETHER: Yeah.
- Okay.
- Here?
♪ ♪
Okay.
[WHOOSHES]
♪ ♪
That's it?
You okay, baby girl?
I think so.
What about you, Flash?
♪ ♪
[SPARKING]
[WHOOSHING]
I feel great.
[LAUGHS] My boy's back.
Well, that's the last
time I'm using this power.
The city was almost
destroyed because of me.
But you had no idea that would happen.
Yeah, don't be so hard on yourself, pal.
I thought I was chosen
for a higher purpose.
This can't be the plan for me.
But maybe you were
chosen for a bigger one.
What do you mean?
The guy we mentioned, Clifford DeVoe,
he isn't gonna stop until
he gets all the bus metas.
Which means we have to stop him.
We could use all the help we could get.
Are you sure I can make a difference?
Absolutely.
DeVoe's shown weakness against
other bus metas in the past.
With your help, we might
actually have a chance.
How do we start?
♪ ♪
- I'll give you the tour.
- All right.
[CHUCKLES]
No offense. I like my powers, so...
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
So, Bare...
You never made your
own tidal wave before.
No, I haven't.
You go, girl.
♪ ♪
So, what do you say, you
wanna teach an old dog
a new trick?
All right.
Training. 6:00 a.m.
Ooh, don't be late.
- You got it, boss.
- Welcome back.
♪ ♪
Hey, Ralph.
Hey.
You know, Matthew is
gonna need a buddy, too.
Well, that's, uh...
That's assuming he stays.
After he finds out that
DeVoe has gotten everyone
he's come after, he'll be terrified.
Just like I am.
Look, Ralph,
I know what you're going through.
No, Iris, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Last year when I thought that
Savitar was going to kill me,
I was...
Scared out of my mind.
How did you deal with it?
It was really hard.
But then I realized
that if I hid from him,
if I hid from the world, then...
Savitar had already won.
So I made the decision
to not give into the fear.
♪ ♪
I chose to keep living.
Look, uh...
What I said before about
you never putting your life
on the line...
I was wrong.
You make one hell of a Flash.
In or out of the costume.
♪ ♪
Thanks.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Are you going up?
- Yeah.
I think maybe it's time that
Clifford DeVoe paid the Mayor
another visit.
Hmm.
♪ ♪
I thought you were
never leaving S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well, I think maybe it's time
I started living again, too.
Plus, we're definitely
out of veggie dogs.
[LAUGHS]
Hey, thanks, Iris.
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
Fresh from this little place in Keystone
that Cecile recommended.
Wow.
Those cravings of hers are
getting really intense, huh?
Yeah, tell me about it.
It's a good thing I'm a speedster again.
[CHUCKLES]
You know you didn't have to
give up your speed, right?
I mean, I would have never asked you to.
I know.
Why'd you do it?
You know what makes a great speedster?
[GENTLE MUSIC]
It isn't their speed.
♪ ♪
It's being the light that everyone needs
when the world grows dark.
It's the kind of person they are.
The kind of person that
always wants to help.
That's why being the
Flash is your destiny.
It's your way of helping others.
♪ ♪
But it isn't mine.
This is.
♪ ♪
I'll leave you to it.
_
All right, take it off!
Take it off, Harry. That's enough.
We're already 20% over your
suggested safety limits.
You've gotta give it a little more time.
No, that's it. I'm shutting it down.
No, no, we're almost
there. We're almost there!
You're not "Breaking Bad," Locutus!
All right, I'm disengaging
the photon flow.
[BEEPING]
Fine.
♪ ♪
I don't need it anymore.
You got the names?
The last two remaining bus metas.
♪ ♪
Janet Petty and Edwin Goss.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --