HARRISON: Hello.
For those of you who don't know me,
my name is Harrison Wells.
(APPLAUDING)
Today, the future has arrived.
Our city has seen incredible,
impossible things.
Meta-humans, men and women
with extraordinary abilities.
The ability to soar above buildings,
to run faster than the speed of light.
Unfortunately, most of these meta-humans
have chosen the wrong path
with these powers. A dark path.
My team and I at S.T.A.R. Labs
are committed to keeping up
with these perilous times.
And so, may I present to you our new line
of "Meta-Human Awareness" apps.
(APPLAUSE CONTINUES)
(CHUCKLES)
This technology will allow you
to instantly detect the presence
of a meta-human.
You'll be instantly alerted to an
approaching speedster like Zoom or like...
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
Flash.
Welcome, Flash.
Tell them the truth, Dr. Wells.
Everything that has happened to this city,
the past two years, is because of you.
You created all of us metas.
You created Zoom.
-(CROWD GASPS)
-I created Zoom?
Eleven hours
before the first meta-sighting,
enormous blasts of dark matter radiation,
were silently expelled beneath this lab.
I'm sorry, Flash. I believe all this fast
running may have scrambled your brain.
You take no responsibility for
the wreckage your mistakes have caused.
Admit it, Wells. And then maybe, you can
truly help me do something about it.
Help you? Because I'm the greatest
tech entrepreneur of all time.
You're the superhero.
And we would all be safe,
if you would just do your job
and stop Zoom.
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
(DEVICE BEEPS)
Well, I guess it's safe to say
the speedster sensors work.
(CROWD LAUGHS)
-Are you okay, Dad?
-I'm fine, sweetie.
Now, where was I?
Oh, that's right. The future.
Very strange to be holding
your autobiography.
Especially when you didn't write it.
And it's not about you.
Dr. Caitlin Snow, Cisco Ramon,
meet Dr. Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
-Hi.
So, let me get this straight.
You're the doppelganger
of the man who murdered his mom
and is responsible for both
Ronnie and Eddie's deaths.
Yeah, but he's not even the doppelganger
of the Dr. Wells that we knew,
because that Dr. Wells' body
had been taken over by the Reverse-Flash
who was really Eobard Thawne, and
Eddie's distant relative from the future.
Yeah, I didn't follow any of that.
I'm my own man.
I had nothing to do with the murder
of your mother, or your friend Ricky.
-His name was Ronnie.
-Him either.
You told me you have proof
of your identity.
This almost hit me
when I went through the portal.
Your stabilized breach downstairs connects
directly to the S.T.A.R. Labs on my Earth.
Technically, this could be mine.
But I want to run some tests on you.
I'll be genetically indistinguishable
from my Earth-1 counterpart.
Your tests will reveal nothing.
-Great! Still gonna run 'em.
-Be my guest.
Why are we even listening to him?
How do we know he's not evil,
like the other guy?
He saved my life last night.
The question is why.
I'm guessing you didn't travel between
dimensions just to meet the Flash.
That's exactly what I did.
I came here to help you, Barry.
To stop your greatest enemy.
-He already did that.
-I'm not talking about Reverse-Flash.
I'm talking about Zoom.
I see you've already heard of him.
Yeah, Zoom has been sending
meta-humans from your world
through the breaches to fight me.
Well, they're the symptoms.
Zoom's the plague.
One that's infected my world
and now he's coming for yours.
-What do you know about Zoom?
-Everything.
I created Zoom.
I'm responsible for all
the Earth-2 meta-humans.
A fact I've ignored for far too long.
But now,
I'm doing something about it.
Yeah, well, we're batting a thousand
against these breachers.
You're batting a thousand, Crisco?
What's your sample size? Ten?
Less? Zoom is obsessed with speed.
He will never allow there to be
another speedster in the multi-verse.
And he's gonna keep
sending these metas here,
one after the next,
all with the same goal.
To kill the Flash.
Unless we stop him. Together.
Last time I listened to a guy with your
face, some bad things went down.
We lost people we cared about.
Everyone loses
someone they care about, Snow.
The real test of character
is what you do once they're gone.
Joe! Put the gun down!
How is he still alive?
How are you still alive?
Well, I don't know. Because you missed?
Hey, I'm trying to keep him from
shooting you. You're not helping.
Let's take a walk, all right?
It's all good.
We know someone who can verify
everything that this guy just said.
Be careful.
I don't suppose you have a
Big Belly Burger in this universe, do you?
This isn't happening
I know that this is lot to take in,
but that guy, back in that room,
that's not Wells.
Dr. McGee swore she saw Wells.
He broke into Mercury Labs.
What? Why didn't you tell me this?
Because I didn't believe her. I didn't
even want to consider Wells was alive.
Eddie erased that Wells from existence.
This guy is...
He's someone else. And he says
he's here to help us stop Zoom.
-How can you even look at him?
-You think this is easy for me?
The guy in there looks, moves, sounds
exactly like the guy that drove a knife
through my mother's heart.
I have to resist the urge to kill him.
I'm trying my best to get past that, okay?
You shooting him, that's not helping.
After all our losses,
I thought at least we were free of Wells.
I just want one week where we're
not surprised by somebody from our past.
I better go fill in Iris.
Good luck.
I hope you're happy, Linda. Tanner's
lawyers are threatening to sue us.
I'm sorry, Chief, I don't care
how many touchdowns Tanner throws,
I'm not interviewing
some 'roided out jerk who hit his wife.
Unless it's to hold him accountable
for domestic violence.
All right. (SIGHS) Run your story, Park.
The sports page
used to be a lot less complicated.
She shoots... (EXHALES)
She scores.
Larkin's the best editor
I've ever worked for.
It's just every once in a while,
you have to remind him
it's the 21st century.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
But that's not really him?
The Wells who Eddie gave his life to stop.
Apparently not.
(IRIS SIGHS)
That's life in Central City these days,
right?
-You sure?
-Dad, I'm fine. Really.
Good.
I wanna keep you that way.
-Dad.
-Take it.
I taught you how to use it for a reason.
And I'm praying that Barry's right
and this Wells means us no harm.
Last year you had Eddie
to look out for you, but now,
you can't murder somebody
that everybody thinks is dead, right?
Put it away.
You do realize that when I said I wanted
a drink, I didn't mean a latte, right?
I was talking about alcohol.
Like, mind-numbing alcohol.
All right, look,
you got to give him a chance, okay?
He's not a speedster.
He's just a regular, normal guy.
From another universe.
I never thought I'd miss time travel.
Time travel, huh?
-Hey! Are you kidding?
-Hi. (CHUCKLES)
Is there, uh,
a meta-human who can time travel?
Time... No. Time travel's not real.
'Cause that would be pretty cool.
(CHUCKLES)
Not so sure about that.
Patty, you know Cisco Ramon, right?
Yeah, you're the scientific advisor
on meta-humans to the C.C.P.D., right?
-Yeah, that's me.
-Nice.
Hey, Barr, did you hear?
I was right about King Shark.
-"King Shark"? Nice name.
-Yeah.
-I like her.
-Yeah, King Shark almost ate the Flash.
No. I'm sure the Flash had it handled.
Oh, no. I was there. I saw it all.
Some hooded guy saved his life.
Wait, and you're not, like,
traumatized or anything?
I just watched a half-man half-shark
take on the fastest man alive.
-I love this city.
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Let's see. Sorry.
Oh, uh, Captain just texted me.
He wants me to write my police report.
Uh, you maybe want to write it with me?
(STUTTERS) Uh, I can't. Tonight, I'm busy.
I'm... Yeah, sorry.
-Oh, yeah. Okay.
-I've just got science stuff.
Stuff I gotta science the stuff out of.
Maybe next time, though...
Yeah. Coolio.
-Yeah.
-Uh...
But I'm gonna actually skip the coffee
and go get a head start. So.
-Good to see you guys.
-Oh. Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah. For real?
-Stop, all right?
I was gonna ask her out,
and then a man-shark tried to eat me.
And then Dr. Wells, the sequel, showed up.
Okay. Can we not use the name "Dr. Wells"?
I'm just gonna call him "Harry."
Okay, Harry. Yeah.
Listen, there's always
going to be Harrys out there.
But you can't let the Harrys of the world
get in the way of you living your life.
Ask Patty out. You gotta be bold.
That's tough talk. When was the last time
you asked a girl for her number?
Watch and learn.
I'm watching. (CHUCKLES)
Hi. What can I get you?
-Hi, there.
-Hi. Again.
Uh...
-Do you want some coffee?
-Yeah, I'll get some...
No, uh... No I don't want coffee.
You know what I do want, though?
I wanna ask you this.
Do you wanna go out with me?
Oh.
Do... Wait, I mean, we could, we could go
get coffee, or we could, like...
No.
That's a no.
It's totally cool. It's cool.
Respect.
(WOMAN SOBS)
MAN: (WHISPERS) Stay back.
(WOMAN CONTINUES SOBBING)
(GASPS)
Yo, dude, you good? It's her loss.
-(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-Hey, what's up?
-We have another breacher.
-What? How do you know?
Central City Bank. You gotta go now.
All right.
You got my attention.
Flash?
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
Her name is Dr. Light. (SIGHS)
Small-time thief on my Earth
until exposed to the dark matter
from the particle accelerator.
Became a meta-human with the ability
to derive power from starlight.
Whoa, very cool.
Stars having a temperature
of 5,300 degrees Kelvin
and a blinding luminosity.
I would say not very cool. At all.
You know, our Dr. Wells may have been evil
but you're just a dick.
Okay, so, obviously, Zoom brought her
here from your Earth, like the others.
Mmm-hmm. Now that we know that,
we can use that to gain advantage.
What do you mean?
We capture Dr. Light.
Then use her to lure Zoom here.
You are insane. Okay?
We are not luring Zoom anywhere.
Apparently, they know each other.
And Jay is not a fan.
Well, well, well. Like everyone else,
I assumed our Earth-2 Flash was dead.
Why am I not surprised
to find Jay Garrick here? Still alive.
And in hiding,
a full universe away from Zoom.
I'm not in hiding.
Zoom nearly killed me and stole my speed
before the Singularity pulled me here.
-Is that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
Well, whatever the case, in your absence,
Zoom has only
gotten more powerful, faster.
Barry, you have to defeat Zoom now,
while you still can.
No. This isn't the time to be reckless.
We don't even know
why Zoom sent Dr. Light here.
She's a thief, not a killer.
Zoom can make people do things
out of character.
Thief or not, she'll kill you.
All right. Look, hey,
we can decide what to do with Light later.
First, we have to find her. Okay?
-(SLURPS LOUDLY)
-(BARRY SIGHS)
Hey, how did you know
that she was breaking into the bank?
(STUTTERS) I got an alert on my phone.
It's a little ring-a-ding... (VOCALIZING)
Every time there's a robbery at a bank.
-What?
-But you know what?
I think I can get
the S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite
to scan for any irregular
solar radiation emissions,
and we can find Dr. Light's light.
Okay. I'm gonna also, um, call Joe.
See if C.C.P.D. has any leads.
Why don't we
keep them apart until I get back.
I'm sure that won't be a problem.
(EXHALES)
-(ELEVATOR DINGS)
-(SIGHS)
-Hey.
How's your science stuff?
I finished it.
Um, did you get your report done?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
It wasn't as much fun
writing it by myself, but... (CHUCKLES)
-I'll see you.
-Yeah.
Hey, do you ever feel
completely overwhelmed
by everything that
you have to do in a day,
and it feels like the one thing
that you actually want to do
is the thing that gets lost?
I'm confused. What?
I've been thinking,
for a while now, actually,
would you want to get
dinner with me sometime?
Yeah. This isn't gonna be
one of those things
where I get really excited and then
more "science stuff" comes up, right?
No, no. That's not, uh... Tomorrow?
We can grab an early dinner.
I don't want to wait anymore.
-Okay.
Looking forward to it.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Harry. Hey, over here! Hey!
Come inside, use my work room,
use my computer, I don't care.
Thanks.
You and Wells Prime have very different
musical tastes. His were better.
This Harrison Wells and I are very
different, but similar in some respects.
I see he made almost the same mistake
I did with the particle accelerator.
He did a lot of terrible things,
but none of them were by mistake.
What did he do to you?
I know he caused the Singularity, murdered
Barry's mother, blah-blah-blah-blah.
What did he do to you?
You can barely look me in the eye.
Why is that? What did he do to you?
He shoved his hand through my chest.
He stopped my heart.
(CHUCKLES)
Ouch. Okay, that would do it.
But you survived that?
Only because Barry erased that timeline.
I see. Barry traveled in time.
-Twice.
-Hmm.
Here's how it is.
-What's the deal?
-You don't have to like me.
I don't like you.
But you have to work with me
to stop Zoom and Dr. Light.
Can you do that?
I guess we'll see, won't we?
I guess we will. One more thing...
You said you're gonna
re-task S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite?
To scan for solar emissions, yeah.
We're up and running.
I'd like to examine your program.
I wanna see if it works.
Don't worry. It'll work.
Harry's starting to get on my nerves.
The silent alarm just went off
at the Bank of Central City.
That's gotta be Dr. Light.
Could be a trap.
Barry, trust me, Dr. Light
is not a killer. You can talk to her.
Okay.
Looking for this?
I know Zoom sent you here to kill me.
Good news. You don't have to do that.
Not if I can get out of town
with that cash.
And then what? Zoom's not gonna like
that you ditched him, right?
My friends and I can help you.
Nobody can protect me from Zoom.
All right. Why don't we
take it down a lumen,
have a normal conversation, all right?
Thank you.
Linda? Linda Park?
How do you know my name?
I don't understand.
This was a mistake.
(BARRY GROANS)
CAITLIN: Barry, what's happening?
I can't see.
Guys, I can't see.
BARRY: I still can't see.
How long is this gonna last?
You're suffering from solar retinopathy.
Your retinas are severely damaged.
You're lucky you're not permanently blind.
But with your rapid regeneration
abilities, your sight should return soon.
HARRISON: 6.25 hours,
by my estimation.
All this could have been avoided
if you'd just stopped Light
instead of chit-chatting with her.
She caught Barry off guard.
Always an excuse with you, right?
He's the fastest man alive.
How could she possibly do that?
Because Light looks exactly
like my ex-girlfriend. Linda Park.
That's why Zoom sent her.
Because he knew you'd hesitate.
Well, that means Zoom had to have known,
somehow, that Linda was your ex?
Which is why Barry has to act now,
before Zoom sends another double
from Barry's life.
All right. Right now,
I'm more worried about Linda.
When I saw who was under the mask,
I said her name.
What if Light didn't even realize
that she had a doppelganger here
until I accidentally told her?
The first thing that Atom Smasher did
when he crossed the breach
was to kill his doppelganger.
Yeah, but Light's not like Atom Smasher.
We should keep an eye on your Linda.
All right. I'll go.
-Sorry.
-Bro.
-Barry.
-What?
Okay, okay. You can't do anything, uh,
until your sight returns.
No, no, no. Come on.
Here's the little rail here. I'll do it.
-BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
-I'll go with you.
-Hey, Barry! I came as soon as I...
-Hey.
You look just like him.
I'm guessing my counterpart
did something to offend her as well?
Her fiancé died because of him.
Oh.
Iris, I know it's weird seeing him.
Yes. It's just a lot to process lately.
Wells, my mother...
How are you doing with that, by the way?
I mean, now that she's gone, okay.
Yeah. Iris, um...
-Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
-Look, thanks.
You know you can talk to me about it.
Yeah, I know, but...
But really, I'm fine, okay?
I should be asking how you're doing.
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
-That's me. I got it.
-Barry, let me help you.
-I got it. All right.
Uh... "Running a little late. P." Who's P?
-Oh, P. That's Patty.
-My dad's partner, Patty?
-Mmm-hmm.
-What is she running late for?
Um...
Our first date.
-That's so great. She's great.
-Uh...
Yeah, no, Patty is great.
I just, you know,
I doubt she's gonna give me another shot
when I have to cancel on her.
Don't cancel.
I'm blind, Iris. A literal "blind date."
That's not gonna work.
Hey, we are in S.T.A.R. Labs. Come on.
There's got to be something here
that can help you get through the night.
Yeah.
Or someone.
Cisco. Hey.
To your left. Other left.
Cisco.
I'm sorry.
Oh. Sorry.
Okay. She's two steps in front of you.
-Nice glasses. (CHUCKLES)
-Hey. Hey.
-BARRY: I'm so, so sorry I'm late.
-Touchdown.
No, don't be. Uh, you know,
I actually judge my dates
on whether or not they stand me up.
So you are off to a great start.
What do you mean?
I mean, who would stand you up?
Oh, I have a reputation.
Not that kind of reputation.
That's not what I meant.
(LAUGHS) That's embarrassing.
You know, I actually, um,
I arrested a boyfriend once.
A very ex-boyfriend,
while we were at dinner.
He got really wasted
and decided to insult the waitress.
So I cited him for public intoxication.
-That is hilarious.
-Yeah. (LAUGHS) Special.
So...
Dude, she looks amazing. You have
to tell her how amazing she looks.
You look amazing, Patty.
Uh, thanks. I actually
had a really hard time
trying to figure out what to wear.
Like, if I should wear a dress or this
color was a little weird. I couldn't...
No, you look great. It's, um... Yeah, no,
what would you call that color?
Um, uh...
-I don't know.
-I can't tell. The feed's black and white!
Yeah, whatever it is, that color
should thank you for wearing it.
(CHUCKLES) My man!
-It's smooth.
-Not smooth.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, wine list! Here we go.
Uh...
Yes, oh, got it. Thank you.
Um...
-You know, why, why don't you... Sorry.
-Oh! That's okay.
The guy always picks.
Why don't you choose?
Yeah. What do you want? Red or white?
Whatever you'd like. Uh...
You've got this. Why do you even need me?
-Here you go.
-JAY: Thank you.
-Classic stakeout fuel.
-Yeah.
You have coffee on your Earth, right?
I think coffee is the one constant
in the multi-verse.
(CHUCKLES)
So, I don't mean to pry,
but when Wells keeps referring
to you and Zoom, what's he talking about?
I've fought Zoom many times,
each time barely escaping with my life.
(SIGHS) So, yeah. Maybe I didn't always
confront him when I should have.
The truth is, Zoom scared me.
He stole the most precious thing from me,
my speed.
I didn't want Barry
to suffer the same fate.
Well, maybe if you just sat down
with Wells, talk to him about it?
No, no, no. Do not trust Wells, Caitlin.
The guy was more than happy to make money
off the meta-human problem
with his tech apps.
So now he's obsessed with Zoom.
Something has changed,
and not just because I disappeared.
Well, I don't trust Wells. I trust you.
(CHUCKLES)
(PATTY LAUGHS)
So I've actually been dying to ask you.
What was it like
to be struck by lightning?
Um... Life changing, to be honest.
Did it hurt?
I mean, all I really remember is feeling
electricity surging through my body.
It was an intensity I'd never felt.
Like I was instantly connected
to everything around me.
Then I woke up from a coma
nine months later.
Waking up in the future like that,
it's like time travel.
-BARRY: Sort of, yeah.
-Yeah.
Yeah. When I was, um, nine,
I actually drowned.
I hit my head on the diving board
and fell into the swimming pool.
Uh, my heart stopped for,
I think, two minutes
until my dad rescued me
and saved my life. Yeah.
So I guess we've both cheated death.
(CHUCKLES)
I've been through a few things in my life
that taught me
not to be afraid of anything.
I think fear is what holds people back
from being who they should be.
Oh, preach!
Uh...
Yeah. I'm still here.
Creepin' and peepin'.
-You okay?
-Sorry. Yeah, I really agree with that.
-Really?
-Mmm-hmm.
I think, I think, uh, another thing too,
I think you can't see me.
Abort.
What? What do you mean? I...
I think you can't see me.
Come on. I would not be a good detective
if I couldn't have figured this one out.
-(CHUCKLES)
-So, I don't know...
Uh...
-Yeah.
I'm really sorry and embarrassed,
I didn't say anything.
-I had my pupils dilated earlier.
-Oh, my gosh!
I really didn't want to cancel.
CISCO: Barry! I lost my eyes!
You know, you have a great smile.
Really? How do you know I'm smiling?
(CHUCKLING)
Just a hunch.
Okay, so what else
is different about our worlds?
Do you have Tahiti?
Never been, but I do love Atlantis.
As in the lost city,
submerged in the ocean somewhere?
Well, it's actually above water
on my Earth.
One of my best friends is from there.
I would love to see it.
It's special.
It's the kind of place
you never want to leave.
(CAITLIN SCREAMS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hello, gorgeous. Everybody out. Now!
Go! Go, go, go. Go. Move! Quick.
-Except you.
-I don't think so.
No, no. She's leaving with us.
-Not today.
-What do you want from me?
Your life.
(GROANS)
Dr. Light.
-Oh, no. Go!
-(GRUNTING)
DR. LIGHT: I've never killed
anyone before.
But it's not murder
if it's your double, right?
Why are you doing this?
It's the only way that I can stay alive.
To become you. I'm sorry, Linda.
(GRUNTS)
No!
(GASPS)
-How is this possible?
-You couldn't understand.
Light!
Flash. I thought
I took care of you outside.
(IRIS GROANS)
(PANTING)
Please don't let go. I may trip.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, I won't. I promise. Two more steps.
-All right. Missed one.
-There you go. (LAUGHS)
It's funny how we skipped
straight to the hand-holding part.
Yes.
Um... We've arrived at my car.
Ah.
Well, do you think we've reached
the goodnight-kiss stage?
Um...
(CHUCKLES)
(PATTY GIGGLING)
Um...
This is burgundy, by the way,
and you look great in it.
Now, you can see?
Yeah, I can.
Well, that must have been some kiss.
I guess so.
(CELL PHONES VIBRATING)
-Sorry. Uh...
-No, it's mine, too.
Oh... Weird.
Cisco, hey.
Sir?
I saw myself.
How is that even possible?
It sounds like you have an evil meta-twin.
(SIGHS)
And now Larkin's dead,
because someone who looks like me
wanted to kill me?
Linda, none of this is your fault.
We're gonna figure it all out. I promise.
How you doing?
I'm alive. Thanks to Iris.
Turns out she's as badass with a gun
as she is with a pen.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, she is.
I'm just happy that you're safe.
I've arranged a security detail.
Round the clock, just to be sure.
I can take you to them if you're ready.
Yeah.
This is because of me.
I should have been here.
Barry, you were blind. There was
nothing that you could have done.
You think this mask
can help us find that woman?
Any evidence on this
is just gonna match Linda.
I'll think of something else.
Light's not gonna kill again.
-Caitlin, are you guys okay?
-Yeah.
Barry, I'm sorry.
Dr. Light's never killed before.
I thought we could reason with her.
You cannot reason
with someone under Zoom's influence.
And now a man is dead
because of you, Garrick.
This whole thing is because of you.
He doubts himself.
Because of you. But believe me,
Barry can do what you could not.
Barry can stop Zoom!
I spent two years hunting Zoom.
Wrong! Zoom hunted you.
You spent the last two years of your life
running, running, running from Zoom.
Look, Zoom would have killed me,
just like he will kill Barry
if you lead him down this path.
No, because he is not like you.
Barry runs towards danger, not from it.
Because Barry's not a coward.
(GRUNTING)
Enough!
(JAY SNIFFLES)
BARRY: You were pretty hard
on Jay in there.
Maybe you should be hard on Jay, too.
I've seen what you can do, Barry.
I've calculated how fast you can run.
And you should be teaching Jay.
Not the other way around.
You know, before I learned
that the other Wells
was the man who murdered my mom,
I looked up to him.
He was my mentor, actually.
So, my doppelganger,
a man who looks exactly like me,
betrayed you.
Hmm.
I'm sorry. I'm not him.
So you need to listen to me when I say
you can take care of Zoom.
And all we have to do
is capture Dr. Light.
I thought about testing the mask
for Light's DNA,
but it would only have Linda's.
The mask? What mask?
Light's mask.
How did you get this?
Iris shot it off Dr. Light
when she attacked Linda.
You know how to use the mask
to find Light?
Yes, I do.
All we have to do is give it to him.
-Why me?
-Because you have powers.
(SCOFFS)
What are you talking about?
I developed this watch
to detect meta-humans.
(BEEPING)
You never got an alert on your phone.
You never reprogrammed
the S.T.A.R. Labs' satellite.
And this is why.
He's a meta-human.
Cisco, have you known about this?
And you didn't say anything to us?
Yeah, I was going to tell you.
Thanks a lot, Harry.
I swear. I was, but I didn't.
I was just... I was afraid.
Afraid of what?
Dr. Wells said
the dark matter gave me this, this gift.
He said that one day I'd thank him for it.
What if I become like him?
Cisco, I don't think any of us
would become evil
if we all of a sudden got powers.
Even if they were from Dr. Wells.
Yeah. Maybe you're right.
I should have said something.
That's my fault. I'm sorry.
Well, you can be sorry later.
Because right now, we have to use
your powers to find Dr. Light.
Cisco, your abilities, how do they work?
Uh, I get these feelings sometimes.
These vibes.
Visions of the breachers when
they come to this Earth.
I just... I'm not sure what triggers it.
And sometimes it just happens.
Sometimes, it's when
I'm touching something of theirs.
Touch the mask.
You want to find Dr. Light, do it.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
Hmm... (GRUNTS)
I don't think it's working.
Try again.
-Try again!
-Yo.
-I'm sorry. It's not...
-HARRISON: Again!
-I can't control it.
-Because you're afraid!
I'm telling you, I don't know how it
works! I can't just make it happen!
I'm telling you, yes, you can!
(GASPS)
(FEMALE ANNOUNCER
SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
South Plaza Train Station, Platform 15.
What are you waiting for?
Oh, guys, the platform's crowded.
Are you sure she's here?
She should be wearing a black trench coat.
Black trench coat. Found her.
Everybody, get out of here! Go! Go, hurry!
(INDISTINCT SCREAMING)
Why won't you just let me leave?
I can't let you leave.
You killed an innocent man.
That was an accident.
Trying to kill Linda Park wasn't.
It's the only way that I can be free
from Zoom. Unless I kill you.
Can't let you do that, either.
So, we've got a problem.
We'll see.
Guys? Should've talked about this
before I left, but how should I stop her?
Keep trying different angles, Barry.
Find her blind spot.
(GROANS)
I can't get close enough.
What should I do?
I don't know.
BARRY: Oh, I gotta tell you, that's not
exactly the answer I was looking for.
You need to confuse her.
Give her more than one target
so she does not know who to fire at.
All right. How do I do that?
By running so fast, you create
multiple afterimages of yourself.
You create a speed mirage.
Oh, speed... I've never run that fast!
Well, from what I've been told,
you've traveled through time.
You'll be more than fast enough.
Okay.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Barry?
BARRY: I can't do it!
Yes, you can, Barry.
Hey, Dr. Wells is right. You are fast.
Faster than I ever was,
and better than I ever will be.
Don't let fear and doubt hold you back,
like it did to me.
You're the Flash, Barry.
Show Light what that means.
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTS)
Where are you?
(GROANS)
I'm right here.
Dr. Light
is safely locked in the pipeline.
-Nicely done.
-(CHUCKLES)
Wells. Thank you for helping Barry
put away Dr. Light.
So. What now?
(SIGHS)
We do what Dr. Wells said.
We use her to lure Zoom here.
End this, once and for all.
You can't be serious.
More breachers are gonna come.
More innocent people may die.
I can't let this happen anymore.
Well, you're making a mistake, okay?
Zoom is a nightmare
you can't wake up from.
I've already had my worst nightmare.
His name was Reverse-Flash.
I spent a long time being afraid of him.
I'm not gonna be afraid anymore.
(CHUCKLES) Okay, Barry,
you may be faster than me,
but you're not ready
to fight Zoom by yourself.
That's just it, Jay.
I'm not gonna fight him by myself.
I've got all of them to help me.
I've got Dr. Wells,
I've got you.
No. I can't in good conscience
help you when I know
it'll only lead to you losing your speed
or even worse,
your death.
Optimism must be an Earth-1 thing.
You all need to ask yourself
why this man, for years,
wouldn't admit that he was responsible
for the particle accelerator
exploding underground.
He may not be
Harrison Wells from your Earth,
but he has just as many secrets
as the one you knew.
Jay, please don't go.
I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
Have a nice day. What can I get you.
Yeah, I know, this is supes awkward.
Probably, more for me than for you.
But I just want coffee. Okay?
Just three Flashes.
One of them decaf. That's it.
(SIGHS)
Are you sure that's all you want?
Oh, that's funny. You just want to
shoot me down again, huh?
No. No, no, no. (CHUCKLES)
What I mean is,
I just moved to Central City.
And it's a pretty big change
from where I come from.
Everything here's so big and new,
and filled with meta-humans.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. Well, when you factor in
the size of the city,
the chances of running into a meta-human
are actually pretty low.
I guess what I'm trying to say is,
you kinda caught me
off guard the other day.
But now, I'm a little more prepared.
So I just want to make sure,
is coffee all you want?
(CHUCKLES)
Hi. I'm Cisco Ramon.
Kendra Saunders. It's nice to meet you.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. I just...
I was getting used to Jay
being part of the team.
Well, look, Jay is a hero.
They always seem to show up
just when you need 'em.
-Yo.
-(CLEARS THROAT)
Peep that.
-That's how it's done, young Padawan.
-Wow. Nice.
We're going on a date next week.
Things are looking up for Cisco Ramon.
I guess so.
Still stuck with these powers, though.
I just don't know how to feel about them.
Hey, look, you don't gotta
go through it alone.
And now you need a cool name.
Oh, snap. You're totally right.
Oh, I gotta think about this one.
Well, you know me. It's gotta be perfect.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Something that really sings, you know.
Something like...
"Vibe"?
Vibe.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Your father has abandoned you.
You're lying.
My father's the smartest man alive.
He'll find me. He'll save me.
And then he'll kill you.
I will not die.
What happens to you and your father
is still to be decided.
(GRUNTS)