- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans
like me.
But I became lost in time.
It took everything
in my friends' power
to bring me back,
and in doing so
our world was opened up
to new threats.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- His tears are
more than just water.
It's like a love drug.
[whooshing]
- I think I can read minds.
- Cecile's a telepath.
That's way more important
than getting Allen
out of prison.
- Cecile filed
an appeal last week.
- We have no new evidence,
so that doesn't matter.
- Did you know
the oscillating cameras
aren't the only ones
in this wing?
You're The Flash.
You said to call you when
I was ready to do business.
- Do you have another fish
to sell me?
[keypad beeping]
[door whooshes]
- Welcome to my own
personal meta-block,
built on the ruins
of the first Iron Heights...
completely off the books
and camera-free.
- Yes, yes, less history
lesson, more window shopping.
- Mina Chaytan...
her powers bring
effigies to life.
- Now, that is a nifty trick.
Can she animate anything else,
hm?
- How about my finger?
- Oh, I like her, she's feisty.
- You are going to love me,
and I'll come willingly,
gorgeous.
- Sylbert Rundine...
he can shrink objects
and return them
to original size.
- I know a drug smuggler
who'd pay
a pretty pence
for that man.
- Ramsey Deacon...
controls technology.
And Becky Sharpe...
can manipulate luck
on the quantum level.
- I smell a bidding war.
[giggles]
And who might this be?
- Something you've been
wanting for a long time...
a speedster.
- C'est pièce de résistance.
- Terms are the same as always.
Any metas you sell,
we split the profits evenly.
So, who would you like?
- Oh, well,
eenie, meenie,
miney,
all of them.
[laughs]
- [whistling]
[sniffing]
Drakkar Noir,
onions,
and liverwurst?
[squeaking]
Oh, no.
[soft, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[door closes]
Earl Cox.
Earl!
[whispers]
It's the cops.
- [Scottish accent]
It wasn't me!
I'll fight every one of you,
ha-ya, ha-ya!
Oh, hello, Ralphy.
- How'd you get in here, Earl?
- Door was unlocked.
- No, it wasn't.
- Was after I picked it.
[cackles]
Ow, oh, look at you.
You went all Zac Efron on me.
You drank so many six packs
you'd have grown one.
[cackles]
- Nice suit, Earl.
- Ah, thank you kindly...
Armani knockoff, I love it.
- Listen,
it's always great seeing you,
but if you'll excuse me,
I got a very busy day.
- Clear your calendar, slim,
'cause I've got a score that'll
knock your honey glazed holiday
ham into next Christmas.
- Yeah, I don't think
any of those words
mean what you think they do.
- How about
these words for you?
A rich, old heiress hires me
to find her other boyfriend,
the pool boy, as a gold digger.
Turns out, he is.
But pool boy is willing
to share said gold
with someone who can
help him keep up appearances,
so to speak,
and that, my friend,
is your specialty.
Are you in?
- I don't do that
kind of stuff anymore.
Ralph Dibny's
gone straight.
- You serious?
- I got friends now.
They're good people.
They helped me, uh,
turn over a new leaf.
- Are they, now?
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- We'll see.
- Meaning?
- Meaning,
I love you,
Ralphy, I really do.
But you let people down,
especially the good ones.
They get close to you,
place their trust in you,
and then, bam,
you screw up,
every single time.
So, when you let
your new friends down,
give your old one a call.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
- Thanks for coming, Cecile.
I know Barry
isn't too optimistic
about the appeal hearing.
- Don't lose hope, Iris,
we still have
a few days to prepare.
- I know,
but it's not like
we've come up
with any new ideas
for clearing Barry's name.
- [sighs]
A bigger issue is
we don't seem to have Barry.
- Mrs. West-Allen?
- Warden Wolfe.
- Unfortunately, you won't be
able to see your husband today.
He was in an altercation.
- What...
an altercation?
- A prison yard fight.
- What?
Is he okay?
- Oh, he's fine, he's fine,
he wasn't harmed
and he wasn't at fault,
but per Iron Heights protocol,
everyone involved is
in isolation for the week.
- And is he safe there?
- Oh, he couldn't be more safe.
Actually, it's a pretty
common occurrence.
[whooshing]
Safe until midnight...
and then Allen and the others
belong to Amunet.
The important thing to know is,
he's in good hands.
You can rest easy at night.
- Thank you, Warden.
- Yes, thank you.
♪ ♪
- What's wrong?
Joe:Wolfe is trafficking
meta-humans?
Is everybody crooked
in this town?
- Ah, he always did look smug
in those Italian wool suits.
Oh, my God, he's literally
a wolf in sheep's clothing.
- It's kind of the perfect
partnership, I mean,
Amunet deals in metas,
and Wolfe has a prison
full of them.
- And him being the Warden,
he can make some
inmates disappear
without raising any eyebrows.
I'm gonna go talk to Singh.
- And say what?
Your pregnant girlfriend
with gestational
psychic powers told you?
- Yeah Joe, Singh's
just gonna think that
you're a father desperate
to get his son out of prison.
- Well, if we don't figure out
something before midnight,
that's exactly
what I'm gonna say.
Hey, where's Harry?
He can help.
- He went to Earth Two,
he's checking in on Jesse,
so...
[clicks tongue]
- Great.
- Okay, well,
we're out of legal options,
and Cisco can't breach
Barry out of the meta-wing,
so, how do we stop this?
- Hey, guys,
got your alert, sorry I'm late.
- It's okay, Ralph.
- No, it's not okay.
I ran into this old
business partner of mine.
This guy...
he's just a big, fat creep.
[flesh stretching]
He's always sticking his nose
in my business.
Cecile: Oh, my.
And he's so shady.
He's got these beady eyes
and this crooked smile.
[voice distorting]
Just a real two-faced rat
from head to toe.
- Well...
- Freaky.
- What?
[Scottish accent]
He's a two-faced rat, he is.
♪ ♪
What's wrong with my voice?
Do you hear that?
- Um...
[computer chimes]
♪ ♪
- That's him right there.
That's him, do you see him?
That's him.
That's him,
that's him, that's him,
Right there, there he...
there...
♪ ♪
That's me, that's me.
What is happening?
- You somehow willed your body
to shape shift
into Earl's appearance.
Seems like your cells can do
a lot more than just elongate.
- Ugh, brilliant.
How do you undo it?
Undo this? That? This?
- Control Z?
- Control...
[grunting]
[lips trill]
[soft laughs]
- Guys, I think I just figured
out how to stop Warden Wolfe.
If Ralph could shape shift
into Braveheart here,
then he could easily
shape shift into Wolfe
and meet Amunet
before midnight.
- And call off the whole deal
before it ever even happens.
- Right.
- Angala what now?
[banging continues]
- If he doesn't stop soon,
I'm gonna ask to be sold early.
- Being a meta-prisoner
or a meta-pet...
what's the difference?
- Difference is Amunet Black.
She captures metas,
sells them to
the highest bidder.
Mob bosses,
drug traffickers, gangs...
just imagine how our powers
could be used
in the wrong hands.
- I ain't gonna be
nobody's weapon.
We gotta get outta here.
- Agreed, but how?
[soft, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Wolfe and Amunet's
latest criminal undertaking
throws an annoying wrench
in our plans.
What shall we do?
- I don't know.
- You,
you don't know?
- My mind is consumed
by a near infinite
web of variables,
more plentiful
than there are atoms
in an exploding star,
so for the moment,
I do not know.
- I fail to see
the humor in this.
[faint screeching, whooshing]
- I heard that in your mind...
a flash of stimuli
racing through
your ventromedial
prefrontal cortex,
where belief is formed...
and doubt.
- I don't have any doubt.
And if you had asked,
instead of reading my mind,
then you would know.
- I do know.
As for your earlier inquiry,
it's not about what
we are going to do.
It's about what Barry Allen
is going to do.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[toilet flushes]
[toilet gurgles]
[toilet gurgling]
Man:Sitter, how goes it?
- Hold your horses,
almost done.
[soft, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Looks like the trap got
clogged with a bunch of hair.
I'll head underneath,
make sure the stack is clear.
♪ ♪
Good to go.
- Thank you.
[door beeping]
[door clicks shut]
♪ ♪
[flesh stretching]
- [grunts softly]
♪ ♪
Okay, how's this?
- You know
that painting in "It,"
the one that comes to life?
It's like that.
- [sighs]
[lips trill]
This is impossible.
We might as well
just gift wrap Barry,
hand him to Amunet,
and call it a day.
- No, Ralph,
this is not impossible.
Your polymerized cells
are linked to your thoughts.
You should be able to change
into anyone you can think of,
just like when you squeezed
your belly into abs.
- Okay, uh, first off,
I have been working out,
so this is au naturel now.
And second,
that was just some abs.
This is an entire person.
- Look,
when I first learned
how to vibe,
I had to learn
how to clear my mind
of all other thoughts.
You think you can do that?
- Okay, uh,
all right, I'll try.
- Do better than try.
Barry's life is in your hands,
and we're all counting on you.
- [nervous laugh]
I think what you meant
to say was,
"No pressure, Ralphy."
- Here we go.
- All right, focus.
Be Wolfe.
- Be Wolfe.
Big, bad Wolfe.
[dramatic music]
[flesh stretching]
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Oh, wow, sweet, chiseled
cheekbones, I did it.
Wow, maybe I can save Barry.
Oh, uh-oh.
[groans]
Uh, a little help?
- Next, we need to work
on his motor skills.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[hissing, fizzing continue]
- Well done, boy.
And hey, for the record,
I was already
planning on making
that stuff that you used, so...
- Sure, right after your
lunch tray crowbar method.
- Can we continue on with the
breaking and exiting, please?
- You want us to follow
a cop on a prison break?
- I'm not a cop in here.
I'm a prisoner.
And I'm not about
to let Amunet turn me
into a weaponized slave,
are you?
- Okay, you convinced me,
let's go.
- I'm staying.
- What?
Why?
- Because I don't wanna
hurt anyone else.
Last time I was out there,
I almost destroyed
the whole city.
- Yeah, she can stay.
- No, we're all leaving.
Becky, if Amunet sells you,
your powers will be used
to hurt a lot of people.
The only way to prevent that
is to escape with us.
Please, trust me.
- Yay, one big happy.
Now what?
- Wolfe said that this wing
was built on top
of the old prison.
I also heard
the plumber talking about
piping underneath us.
[hissing, fizzing]
Once we're far enough
away from the meta-wing,
we'll get our powers back.
That's how we get our freedom.
♪ ♪
[soft, dramatic music]
- [gasps]
Ew...
[gasps]
- Aw, my bad, tiny.
Hey, as soon as we get out,
I'll steal you a brand
new pair of Timmy Choos.
- It's Jimmy.
I'm a size six.
You're so sweet.
[giggles]
- If you wanna use your powers
for something useful,
you could help me steal back
some native artifacts.
- If you two plan
on going back to crime,
you might as well
just turn around.
The Flash will just
run you back here.
Same goes for all of you.
- Don't look at me,
I'm reformed.
From now on,
I only commit legal crime.
- Legal crime?
- The stock market.
- Come on,
we have a long way to go.
[device chirping]
- Augmentation is complete.
Your chair will serve
its purpose.
- You have outdone yourself
once again.
[whooshing]
- ♪ Well, I think ♪
♪ I'm going out of my head ♪
- That melody in your head.
- ♪ Hmm hmm hmm ♪
You don't recognize it?
It was playing...
- The first time we danced,
yes.
- So, you do remember?
- June 27th, 1997,
at 8:13 p.m.,
in the countryside in
the small hamlet of Boars Hill.
It was also the
first time we kissed.
- And the first time I realized
I wanted to spend the rest
of my life by your side.
- Marlize,
I forget nothing.
Perhaps our song was once
at the forefront
of my consciousness,
but now...
- ♪ Hmm hmm ♪
♪ Think I'm going
out of my head ♪
- That song playing
in your head
makes it difficult
to read your thoughts.
Quite difficult.
Perhaps that's on purpose.
- Of course not.
[soft, dramatic music]
I know this unforeseen change
concerns you.
But fear not.
Once this next phase
is complete,
I will erase every doubt
from your head.
♪ ♪
[blues music playing]
- Wolfe-man to S.T.A.R. base,
I'm here.
- Ralph,
to help you stay as Wolfe,
I'm gonna hand you over to Joe,
okay?
He's gonna quarterback.
- Ralph, you copy?
- Yep.
So, what's the next move?
Preferably something
without a lot of moving.
- Okay,
Amunet's point man is Norvok,
so you're gonna have
to talk to him first.
- Grab a drink,
act like a hard-ass.
- Barkeep,
something cold and frosty,
if you please.
- Jeez.
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
- That's on you, bro.
♪ ♪
Snake's on the brain, 5:00.
- Stay focused, Ralph,
no distracting thoughts.
- Gingold on the rocks.
Hand it to me, please.
- The hell you doing here?
- I'd like to talk to Amunet,
please, about the deal.
- You could talk to Amunet
at the deal.
- Damn it, Ralph,
nobody talks
to Wolfe like that.
He's the Warden of the most
dangerous prison
in the Midwest.
Demand some respect.
[tense music]
- Listen, you lapdog.
Set the meeting
with your boss now,
or I'll pull on your eye snake
and strangle you with it,
understood?
- All right, all right.
Let me see what I can do.
♪ ♪
[flesh stretching]
- Oh, God.
♪ ♪
[nervous laugh]
'Sup?
- Ralph, you okay?
- Yeah, fine, yeah.
No problem here.
I'm definitely
holding it together.
- Yeah, that doesn't sound
too convincing.
- I have complete control
of the situation.
[laughs nervously]
Ol' Dibny won't
let his friends down.
♪ ♪
- Wolfe.
Amunet's ready.
- Then let's not
keep her waiting.
[water trickling]
- Are you sure
this is the right way?
- Do you hear the water
in this sewer drain?
It's moving in this direction.
We keep going this way,
we'll head away
from the prison,
find our exit.
- Wow, good catch.
You must've been
a really smart CSI.
- [laughing]
A CSI who killed a teacher
in his own apartment
and left evidence everywhere.
Yeah,
doesn't sound so smart to me.
Hey, speaking of,
maybe we shouldn't be...
[metal tool clatters]
- Crap.
- Hey, easy, easy.
Rundine, easy.
- We let him go,
he will out us.
- We can't do that, can we?
- Deacon.
- What are you doing?
No, we can't hurt him.
- We have to do more than hurt
him...we don't have a choice.
- No, hey,
we do not have to kill him.
- Yes, we do.
- [grunts]
- No, we don't, all right?
Just duct tape him.
Come on, let's move.
♪ ♪
- [giggling]
Looked like it hurt.
[men grunting]
Ding, ding!
Boys, have some orange slices.
Mommy needs to work, okay?
♪ Warden ♪
I'm going to assume
this is not one
of those good
emergency meetings...
a few hours before a major
criminal undertaking, hm?
- We have to delay the deal.
- What?
- My ears outside tell me
the police have been tipped.
I don't know how.
Maybe CCPD
hacked into the cameras.
- You said
there were no cameras.
- I did?
- Mmm.
- Yes, I did say that.
But then, afterwards,
I installed a few.
[tense music]
- Did you?
- Mm.
- Hmm,
something seems off
with the big, bad Wolfe,
if you even are Wolfe.
- Stay in it,
she's testing you.
- What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
I'm the same man
you've always dealt with.
- Okay, and who would that be?
- The one who gives you
your merchandise.
And trust me,
you need me a lot more
than I need you.
So, when I say the deal
has to be delayed,
it's because the deal
has to be delayed.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
[flesh stretching]
[clears throat]
- What the hell?
- What?
- You know, sometimes I hate
being right all the time.
- Ralph, get out of there.
- Uh...
[nervous laugh]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Damn it.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Get me Wolfe, yeah?
- I understand your concern,
Amunet,
but you have my word.
Your metas are exactly
where they're supposed to be...
locked up tight
and in their cells,
waiting for you
to claim them, heh.
Very good, I'll see you then.
♪ ♪
Find them!
- I mean,
there has to be another way.
- There isn't.
There is one card
left to play:
go to Iron Heights,
and stop the deal
before it happens.
- You're talking
about finding Amunet,
plus a prison full
of armed meta-guards
on their turf.
- This is the only option
we have left.
You guys can do this.
- Let's go.
Ralph.
- Yeah, uh,
maybe not this time.
- What?
Why?
- Look, you...
you're gonna have
a better chance
saving Barry without me.
- Ralph,
you know that isn't true.
- I just screwed everything up.
You know what could happen
if I screw it up again?
- You won't.
- Okay, you know what?
Maybe we just need
to talk this out,
let's go visit with
Dr. Hallway, come on.
- Look, look.
Talk's not gonna fix my head.
[soft, dramatic music]
I just can't do it this time,
guys.
Sorry I let you down.
- Hey.
Hey, Ralph.
♪ ♪
- Looks like we're
finally in the old prison.
We must be close.
- Getting closer than we think.
Hey, I know this lock.
It's the same kind they use
in the general population wing,
which means there
are no meta dampeners
on the other side of this door.
We get through,
we get our powers back.
- Well, that's
all I needed to hear.
Out of the way.
[loud bang]
- You good?
- No brains, no brawn.
- Allow me.
I may not have my powers...
[loud clank]
But I don't need them
to hack my way out of trouble.
Give me a few minutes.
- Come here.
- What, no, I'm fine,
it doesn't really hurt.
- Are you sure?
- [gasps]
- Yeah.
- I mean, it hurts a little.
- Yeah, come here.
There.
- [sighs]
Thanks.
Guess I forgot
what it feels like
to punch someone in the face
without my powers.
- [soft laugh]
Judging by the swelling,
I'd say you have a fracture
on either the fourth
or fifth metacarpal.
- How...
- I used to fall down a lot.
Super klutz.
- [soft laugh]
So, what are you gonna do
when you're free?
I hope it's not more
of what you did
to get you in here.
- Oh, no, trust me,
I am so over prison jumpsuits.
Orange is not the new anything.
Neither is gray,
neither is gray, so...
- [soft laugh]
So, what then?
- I don't know.
Using my powers just
hurt those around me.
My good luck just
jinxed everyone else.
You know, you seem to
really care about people...
not like the type
of person who'd
take someone's life.
- I didn't kill that teacher.
I wouldn't take a life.
♪ ♪
You know, not every meta uses
their powers to hurt people.
Some use them to help others,
to protect people.
Our powers don't
decide who we are.
We do.
- [snoring]
- Ralph?
Hey, Ralph, you in here?
- [snoring]
Ick, the light!
It burns!
- All right,
come on, time to get up.
- I can't, I'm dead.
- Okay, I don't know
what's going on with you,
but I'm betting it has
something to do with the reason
you literally
fell apart at the bar.
- I told Cisco that a talk
from him's not gonna help.
So, a talk from you
is not gonna help either,
Caitlin.
- Okay.
I'll get somebody else.
- Hey...
- [winces]
[soft, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[whooshing]
Hello, Stretch.
- They call me a man
who elongates now.
- Hm, they should call you
pathetic.
So, you screwed up,
get over it.
- You are a mean lady.
- I am just telling you
what you need to hear.
- Yeah, well, I'm not gonna
miss you when you leave.
- [scoffs]
Leave?
Is that what this is about?
- Well, yeah.
Everybody leaves
Ralph Dibny eventually,
that's how this
whole thing works.
I screw up big time,
and, tch, they take off.
♪ ♪
This time,
the people who are gonna leave
are actually my friends.
- [sighs]
- They're the first ones
that I've had
in a really long time.
- That's stupid.
- Yeah, well, I wouldn't
expect you to understand,
you kidnap and stab
all your friends.
- Right, I'm the queen
of letting these people down.
But you know what?
They're still here.
No matter how much
I disappoint them,
they still show up for me.
I don't really understand it,
but I think that's part
of this whole friends thing.
So, unless you do
something worse
than kidnap and stab them,
I think you're
gonna be just fine.
- You really think so?
- Yes, I do.
- Huh.
You know, that actually
wasn't a bad pep talk.
- Well, it's
your turn next time.
If I ever decide to
go full villain again,
you can give me
the lame heart to heart.
- Full villain?
Wait...
[laughs]
Wait.
I know how to fix this.
I gotta see
a girl about a guy.
Thank you, Frosty Oprah.
♪ ♪
[device chirping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Presto.
[door clicks]
♪ ♪
- Everyone's powers work?
- Yep.
- Ah,
I can smell all the tech
within five miles of here.
- Thank you, Barry,
you saved us.
- You did good, boy.
[metallic whoosh]
- Not good enough, it seems.
♪ ♪
- Everyone back inside,
and you'll live
to see another day.
- I think the only one
who should be worried
about surviving
right now is you.
[chants softly]
[eagle screeches]
[dramatic music]
[electricity crackling]
- There's no cavalry.
No one's gonna see
what happened here.
It's just you and us, Wolfe.
- You want revenge?
Understandable.
Just one thing...
if you're thirsty
for vengeance,
you might wanna start
with The Flash.
♪ ♪
Barry Allen is The Flash...
the same man
who put you behind bars
and who will, no doubt,
recapture you
after your escape.
That was probably
his plan all along...
[chuckles]
- Is all that true?
- I'm gonna squash you
so quick,
you won't even know
what hit you.
- No, not quick.
- [grunts painfully]
- Let's take our time.
- [gasps]
- The Flash on his knees.
Suppose there is justice,
after all.
- Let's see how fast he can run
when he's the size of a flea.
- Stop!
Stop.
- What are you doing, runt?
- Deciding who I am.
You're not gonna hurt him.
- Join us,
or get out of the way.
Either way, we're taking him.
♪ ♪
- Good luck with that.
[bird screeching]
♪ ♪
- Oh.
[bird screeches]
- [grunts]
[weights crashing]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Toldja.
♪ ♪
- Shoot to wound.
They're no good to me dead.
- They most certainly are not.
- Amunet, you're early.
- And you are exactly
as I suspected,
a liar,
who's obviously
in way over his head.
But no matter,
I will clean up
your mess for you.
Step aside, boys.
Mommy needs to work.
♪ ♪
Oh,
you've got to be kidding me.
[all coughing]
Not again.
♪ ♪
- Oh.
[electric blast]
- [gasps]
DeVoe.
[ominous music]
- Oh,
I don't pay me enough for this.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- [panting]
♪ ♪
- Powers won't work.
- Mine neither.
He must have blasted us
with something.
- Who the hell are you?
- I am your destiny.
[metallic whooshing]
[all gasping]
[electricity crackling]
♪ ♪
- No!
- Help me.
Too late, Mr. Allen.
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- Oh,
what an inconspicuous body.
This will be quite useful.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
Devoe:Not so fast, Warden.
- [grunts painfully]
♪ ♪
- You won't take my body.
- I don't want your body.
I want your life.
[machine whooshes]
- [screams]
♪ ♪
[thud]
- Good-bye for now, Mr. Allen.
[machine whooshes]
♪ ♪
[portal whooshes]
- [sniffs]
- What happened?
-  DeVoe.
- Well, party's over.
♪ ♪
Let's get the hell out of here.
- I'm staying.
- What?
Barry...
- I was only
willing to do this...
try to break everybody out
because Wolfe
was gonna sell us,
but that's not
gonna happen now.
[scoffs]
I'm staying
till you find a way to
get me out of here legally.
It's the only way
I'd ever really feel free,
you know that.
- This could be our
only chance to save you.
- We all have
to decide who we are.
This is who I am.
[alarms blaring faintly]
♪ ♪
[portal whooshing]
Man:Breakout in progress.
Engage lockdown.
Code X prison breach.
Repeat, we have a Code X.
- Move, move, move!
- Get against the wall.
Cell block secure.
[doors clanking, shutting]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- New evidence, Ms. Horton...
that's what you
told this court
had come into your possession,
only I haven't
heard it or seen it,
nor have the circumstances
changed in any way
that would convince me
to move for a retrial.
So, unless you have
something more to add,
this appeal hearing is over.
- [stammers]
I understand, your honor, I do,
if we could just wait
a few more minutes,
I am sure that...
- I am tired of waiting.
Either you have
something new to add,
or you don't.
Which is it?
[solemn music]
- We have nothing further,
your honor.
- Then I hereby deem
Barry Allen's appeal den...
- Wait.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- DeVoe?
- Nope, not DeVoe.
[whispers]
It's Ralph.
- I believe
you are looking for me,
Your Honor.
Devoe:I don't know how
any of this happened.
- You were found
in Barry Allen's loft.
You were dead.
- I was stabbed.
I heard a voice
saying something about
framing someone,
then I blacked out.
- It's gonna work.
- And this morning,
I woke up in my own home.
Mrs. DeVoe, does any of this
make any sense to you?
- No,
I am just as surprised
by all of this as everyone.
- Your Honor,
the city has had
reports in the past
of people
who have appeared dead,
only to later emerge
very much alive.
- That's impossible.
- Impossible, Your Honor,
is it as impossible
as a man
who can run faster
than the speed of sound?
I submit that
Central City is home
to the impossible.
- I have as many questions
as you have, Your Honor,
and I am looking forward to
working with the authorities
to solve this mystery.
- Yes, I'm sure that CCPD
will be very
interested in this.
As for Barry Allen's appeal...
[tense music]
I guess the court
must deem that
Clifford DeVoe
is alive and well.
Barry Allen is hereby
cleared of all charges
and ordered release from
Iron Heights Penitentiary
immediately.
[soft, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[all laughing]
- You're home.
- You're my home.
- Aww.
- [laughs, grunts]
- Oh,
he couldn't wait to do that.
- How you feeling,
Barry, you okay?
- I'm feeling great, yeah.
- Well, you look like
you could use a good meal,
and don't you worry,
I made a fresh batch
of Grandma Esther's meat loaf.
- Oh, yeah.
- Just like you like it.
- Meat loaf?
Gross.
I just meant, meat loaf is
a grossly undervalued menu item
in most restaurants, I think.
- You guys,
now that I'm free,
I don't care what I do.
I'm just so happy to be back
with all of you again.
- Team Flash.
[uplifting music]
- Today, we celebrate Barry.
Tomorrow,
we go back to stopping
the man that framed you.
- I'll drink to that.
- Here, here.
♪ ♪
You okay, Barry?
- Yeah, it's DeVoe.
- Barry, we're gonna stop him,
I know we will.
- No, that's not it, he...
♪ ♪
There was nothing keeping him
from going inside the meta-wing
and absorbing the powers
of every meta in Iron Heights...
Peek-a-Boo, Top, Weather Wizard.
Yeah, I mean, he could've
stolen their powers and more,
but he didn't.
He only wants the bus metas.
He wants their powers
for something...
all of them.
- We know a bus meta.
[door clicks]
- Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm late.
Just couldn't get
this left glute
to shape shift back
to its normal, perky...
Why is everyone looking
at me like I'm a dead man?
♪ ♪
- What's all this?
- Well,
after last night's success,
I thought a toast was in order.
- Success?
Is that what you call
last night?
- Yes,
how would you describe it?
- Barry Allen was...
supposed to remain
in the meta-human wing
at Iron Heights,
but he's now free.
- Even Team Flash
has good luck sometimes.
- And the bus metas?
We were supposed to wait
till all of them were captured.
But you only got four.
- I said I would retrieve
them from confinement.
I never said when or where.
[soft laugh]
[whooshing]
There is something else
on your mind,
isn't there?
- Warden Wolfe's death.
- He needed to die.
- I just don't recall it
being necessary for our plan.
[foreboding music]
[singing softly]
♪ ♪
♪ Hmm hmm hmm ♪
- The chair
can wait till morning.
For now,
to the enlightenment.
♪ ♪
- To the enlightenment.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[slurred]
I love you, Clifford.
- Yes, and I, you.
♪ ♪
♪ I think
I'm going out of my head ♪
♪ Yes, I think
- ♪ 'Cause I can't explain
the tears that I shed ♪
♪ Over you ♪
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.