BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so,
I opened up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Zoom wants me dead.
The meta-humans
that he's sending from Earth-2,
they don't care how many
innocent people get in the way.
I have to go.
I need you to tell me
that it's okay.
(GRUNTS)
Barry!
Is this the face of your
hero, Central City?
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
Seriously. You got your ass kicked.
I can't feel my legs.
- JOE: All right, I got you.
- Okay.
All right, I got you.
(GRUNTS)
I can't do it right now all right?
- Oh, yes you can, Barry.
- No, no, no.
(GRUNTS)
We were making so much progress.
Yep, six whole steps.
Someone get me a Bozo button.
Hey, give yourself some credit.
You just broke your back.
Yeah. A normal person would've been
paralyzed the rest of his life.
Hmm. How long until I'm fully healed?
The initial MRI I took a week ago
showed a complete dislocation
at the T-twelve to L-one interspace
of the thoracolumbar junction.
But this is the MRI I took this morning.
It's remarkable,
but you're almost completely healed.
I'm still having trouble breathing.
That's totally normal
with a spinal injury.
It should clear up soon.
JOE: We're gonna get you back
in that suit, Barr.
Real quick. Trust me.
What are we gonna do about Zoom?
No sign of him since Cisco nailed him
with that tranq dart.
And I haven't vibed since then.
Maybe Zoom's not coming back.
I highly doubt that.
Which is why
I'm gonna go do something about it.
What do you mean go do something about it?
I need access to your breach room
and your speed cannon.
Why is that?
Because, Barry, it's time to go home.
So, you show up on our Earth,
you screw everything up,
and now you want to go home.
Sounds very familiar.
Again, that wasn't me.
I need to go take care of Zoom
once and for all
before anyone else gets killed.
How do you plan on doing that?
I'll think of something.
Ramon, if you'll escort me
to the speed cannon.
No, no. You can't go through the breach.
Yeah, he can.
Jay taught us how to send people.
That's not what I mean.
Look, if you can figure out
how to stop Zoom on your Earth,
you can figure out how to do it here.
We need you to stay here
until we defeat Zoom, Dr. Wells.
What I need, Dr. Snow, is to return home.
I'm gonna do that,
with or without your assistance.
What are you doing?
If Harry wants to go, bye.
Look, like it or not, Cisco,
we need his help.
I'm not sure another plan
from Wells is what we need.
Yeah. I mean, the last bright idea he had
nearly got Barry killed.
I know. But Jay's gone.
And Dr. Wells knows Zoom
better than anyone.
So, until Barry is back on his feet again,
we need to keep Wells around
in case Zoom returns.
Caitlin, if he doesn't want to be here,
then we're better off without him.
Let him go.
I can't do that. Not yet.
(BEEPING)
Oh, snap, meta-human attack.
Nope. Nope. My bad.
That is just an alert for me.
For what?
Oh, it's just a reminder.
Oh, with who?
With the lovely Kendra Saunders,
the barista at Jitters.
Oh, she makes a mean latte.
I think we're gonna go out
for dinner and a movie.
And then, I don't know,
maybe some breakfast.
(LAUGHS)
Wait, breakfast? Why breakfast? I don't...
Yeah.
'Cause you go home and...
Mmm, Cisco. He's messing with you.
Oh.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(SIGHS) Patty-
Patty, hey-
Hey. I hear you're still sick.
Yeah, yeah. It's a nasty bug.
Well, I make a mean chicken noodle soup
from scratch.
I could bring some by later,
if you'd like.
No, that's sweet.
I'd feel terrible
if you caught any of this.
Besides, I love the canned stuff.
Okay, well, try to stay off your feet.
Oh, yeah. Believe me, I am.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you sure you're okay?
You sound like something's up.
(STUTTERS) No, no, no. I'm fine.
I'm just not myself right now.
Okay.
I hope to see you soon and...
feel better.
Thanks.
- Bye.
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
CAITLIN: You should stay away
from the cheese curds.
- They're addicting.
- (CHUCKLES)
I'm going to take a wild stab
and guess that you are here
without the consent
of the rest of your fabulous team.
It's been difficult having you here.
For all of us.
You don't have to worry about that anymore,
because I'm leaving.
We can help you save your daughter.
I know that's why you want to go home.
Look, I made a big mistake coming here.
My plan
was to get The Flash's help
and use that help to stop Zoom.
And my plan failed.
I don't have another plan.
Except to go back home
and face Zoom myself.
So, let's say you go back to your Earth
and you fight Zoom.
He will kill you.
And then how does that help your daughter?
Look, the best way to save Jesse
is for you to stay here.
And work with us. As a team.
No.
Now, please leave me alone
while I discover which one
of these breaches is gonna get me home.
You know, you're lucky Cisco
and Professor Stein never figured out
how to close all the breaches.
Then, you'd be stuck here.
Wait.
We close the breaches.
All of them except one.
So Zoom only has one way
to get to this world.
- The breach at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Exactly.
And then we set a trap.
CISCO: It's got fencing,
fighting, torture, revenge,
giants, monsters, chases, escapes,
true love,
miracles.
And, it's ranked as one of the best
date movies of all time.
Well, let's see if that's true.
KENDRA: Cisco?
Are you okay?
I gotta go.
What? Why?
I am so sorry that this
is happening right now.
Iam SO, SO sorry. Uh...
I have to go.
I'll call you, okay?
I'll call you. I swear.
(SIGHS)
Okay, Brian, let that sit overnight.
And then we'll assay in the morning.
Dr. Shore?
Are you okay?
(SHATTERING)
What are you doing?
You can't take that out of here.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
What happened to me?
(GROWLING)
(SHUDDERING) What are you?
(SCREAMING)
Foolish human.
I am Grodd.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
JOE: Patty!
What'd you find?
Found these weird looking hairs
all over the street.
I'm gonna run them against the database,
and see what I can find.
Uh, here. Our victim.
His name's Dr. Jeffrey Shore.
He's a biochemistry engineer here
at Vaughan Pharmaceuticals.
This is the second dead
lab tech in two weeks.
That ain't a coincidence.
Yeah, and like the other tech,
he had just stolen a serum
from their storage cooler.
Really? What kind of serum?
It's called Cortexin.
It's used to treat encephalopathy.
Uh, blood disease in the brain.
The serum's missing,
but his colleagues found him here,
a couple of minutes later, dead.
He didn't get far.
He died from blunt force trauma
- to the head.
- Ugh.
And apparently, a lot of it.
Yeah, check this out.
- Is that his blood?
- Point of impact.
Okay.
Can you run through
what you told me to her,
and see if you can get anything else
and if the cases are linked?
Sure thing.
Hi.
Some of the evidence.
I'll be right with you.
Uh, Detective?
How's Barry feeling?
Oh, I'm heading to see him right now.
He asked me to bring him
some of my homemade chicken noodle soup.
He hates that canned stuff.
Don't we all.
(PANTING)
JOE: Faster, Barry!
There you go.
Push yourself!
(GRUNTS)
Barry!
- Are you okay?
- (BARRY GROANS)
Oh, yeah, you know?
I'm not great right now.
(GRUNTS)
JOE: What happened?
I just... Nothing. I'm good, all right?
Just forget it.
Barry, talk to us. We can help you.
No, you can't help me.
Not this time. I'm sorry.
You wouldn't understand.
(SIGHS AND INHALES DEEPLY)
- What up, Barr?
- (SIGHS)
Zoom destroyed me.
He showed everyone in Central City
what he could do,
and that I'm powerless to stop him.
They gave me a key to this city, Joe.
I'm supposed to be their hero.
I'm supposed to be the guy
that can protect them
from something as evil as that.
And I failed
in front of all of them.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
When they think of The Flash,
all they see now
is someone not strong enough
to protect them.
- Hey.
- I'm good.
Oh, hey, I know I keep asking,
but have you read any reports
or anything recently
about a Birdman attacking anywhere?
There's no such thing as a Birdman, Cisco.
Okay, like that's a stretch, in this city?
Look, I know what I vibed. lt was a man,
- with these big, wide wings.
- (BEEPING)
It was crazy.
What if it was an angel?
(LAUGHS)
lt was an angel.
Caitlin.
Okay, come on. Like that's a crazy idea.
(GRUNTS)
What is wrong with you?
JOE: I just don't know
what to do about Barry.
I mean, all the test results say
he's fine, but it's like
there's something holding him back.
I keep trying to talk to him,
but I can't get through.
Then maybe we should
get the person who can.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
We can talk about that
when I see you at home.
- I gotta take this, okay?
- Okay.
- Bye, baby.
- Bye.
Patty, what's up?
Turns out our dead scientist
cases are linked.
Okay. Hit me.
Well, the other scientist
stole a large quantity
of a racetam drug,
typically used to treat
patients with Vertigo.
Okay. So, we got two stolen drugs,
one for blood disorders of the brain
and the other one for vertigo.
What's the connection?
Well, they are both nootropic drugs,
used to enhance intelligence.
Hey, did you get results
from the hairs you found?
Yes. (SIGHS) um.
Apparently, they were all over
the other crime scene, too.
The weird thing is,
they're not human hairs...
Uh, they're hairs from a...
From a gorilla.
How did you know?
Patty, I gotta go.
Did Caitlin come through here?
No.
She just hit me in the face and ran away.
JOE: Yo!
Grodd!
- What?
- Grodd's back!
Caitlin.
That must be why she was acting like that.
She was being mind-controlled!
(SIGHS)
I'm continually amazed by the similarities
between our two worlds.
You got talking gorillas on your Earth,
too?
Oh, yeah.
Remind me to never go there.
Ramon, why would this
Grodd abduct Dr. Snow?
I don't know. It doesn't make any sense.
She was always so nice to him.
He mind-controlled two lab technicians
to steal chemicals
that enhance intelligence.
He wants her for something.
Well, it looks like he left his
bachelor pad in the sewers. (SIGHS)
Grodd's a big-ass gorilla.
He can't just waltz through downtown
without anybody noticing.
Right, and if there's been sightings,
then we might be able to
approximate his location.
JOE: I can call C.C.P.D.
They can access the tip hotline,
send over files of Grodd's recent attacks.
Good.
We got to get her back.
We will.
Barry?
- Barry?
- Yeah?
You can't blame yourself for this.
There's nothing you could've done.
I still don't have my speed.
How are we supposed
to save her from Grodd?
You may not have your legs just yet,
but you still got that brain. Use it.
Help us figure that out.
Where are you?
(GASPS)
GRODD: Caitlin.
Grodd?
(GROWLS)
You remember me?
Caitlin always kind.
Why did you bring me here?
Need help.
I don't understand.
How did I become Grodd?
Oh.
That's a long story, Grodd. Um...
The dark matter
from the particle accelerator explosion,
that's how this happened.
Repeat.
Repeat?
(ROARS)
(ECHOING) Need to repeat Grodd!
You want me to make more like you?
I don't know how to do that.
(ECHOING) Learn.
(PANTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (BEEPS)
(PANTS)
Keep that chin down, slugger.
Dad.
(CHUCKLES)
That was a hell of an idea you had,
bringing Henry here.
Well, he may not have his mother,
but he's got two amazing fathers.
- Seemed like he needed both.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
- My girl.
- Mmm.
So, how did Grodd become sentient?
A few years ago, S.T.A.R. Labs
had this contract
with the military to research and awaken
latent mind reading capabilities
for interrogation purposes.
And I'm guessing Grodd
was one of the test subjects.
Right. But then,
Dr. Wells shut down the program.
And we all thought it was to save Grodd
from all the crazy
mind control experiments.
But it was really so that Dr. Wells
could use the accelerator explosion
to create a 1,500 pound
mind-controlling gorilla
that he could manipulate.
- Hmm.
- (COMPUTER WHIRRS)
What kind of algorithm is that?
It's an algorithm meant
to extrapolate Grodd's location
from places we know he's already been.
HARRISON: Hello.
And there we have it.
No spinal cord edema,
I don't see any subacute hemorrhaging,
bone fused beautifully.
You're all good, Barry.
I'd give you some physical therapy,
but you don't need it.
I'm really glad you're here, Dad.
Me too.
I tried to call, but you can't get a cell
in Granite Peak National Park. So...
Granite Peak?
What, you went camping by yourself?
Yeah, yeah. I got a tent.
I went fishing every day.
(LAUGHS) I have had my fill
of largemouth bass for a while.
(CHUCKLES)
Sometimes, you just have to slow down,
to get back to where you want to be.
Yeah.
- Dad...
- CISCO: Hey, guys!
Ithink we found them.
Yeah?
Grodd has to be in one of these
three bell towers.
The only reason
we couldn't find them on any cameras
underneath the city before is
'cause he upgraded from a bachelor pad
to a penthouse, like a baller.
Okay. So, we know where he is,
we still don't know how to get her.
We got a plan for you.
What's the plan?
We use me.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
That's Harry! That's the other Wells!
Barry.
Let him go. Let him go.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I found another suit in the Time Vault.
I thought he was dead.
He's dead. This is...
this is Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
Earth-2?
- I'll explain later.
- If we can
get Harry to convince Grodd
that he's his father,
maybe we can convince
him to let Caitlin go.
I'm not gonna be able to help
if anything goes wrong.
That's a chance I'm willing to take.
Looks like we're oh-for-two
in the bell towers, huh?
I like to think of it more as now,
we know exactly where they are.
Okay, let's do this again.
Give me your best Wells. (SIGHS)
I'm not doing the Wells again, Ramon.
I told you...
Look, I Just made these
anti-mind control ear buds.
They could fail, and if they do,
you're toast.
So, you're gonna need to nail it,
if you wanna live.
(SIGHS)
Ramon...
- Cisco.
"In many ways, you've shown me
what it's like to have a son."
What?
Okay, let's... Let's just try it again.
This time, up the creep factor,
like, a lot more.
And,
make it a little more sincere.
Like you really love me,
but you're gonna have to kill me anyway.
"Cisco,"
"in many ways,"
"you've shown me what it's like
to have a son."
Yep. That's the one.
- Here you go.
- (CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Yo. Yeah.
We're moving on to the third location.
Copy that.
Now, we wait.
So, this is what it's like.
Every time you go after
one of those meta-humans?
Uh... (SIGHS) pretty much.
Only Cisco and Caitlin
are normally the ones in here,
and I'm the one out there.
Well, there's no reason you shouldn't be.
Iris showed me what happened with Zoom.
That was hard to watch.
I can only imagine
what that must've been like for you.
He showed everyone in Central City that
their hero wasn't good enough to stop him.
Well, that's certainly
what it looked like.
Was he right?
(CHUCKLES)
Your body's healed, Barry.
And yet, here you are,
feeling the shame of losing.
I can't stop him.
I know it, he knows it.
And now,
everyone in this city knows it, too.
They don't believe in me anymore, Dad.
At my trial for your mother's death,
a lot of our family and friends
were in the courtroom.
They heard awful things about
what I had done to your mother.
It didn't matter that it wasn't true.
Every day, I could see it on their faces,
the moment
when I lost them,
until everybody had
stopped believing in me.
Well, that was my reality, you know?
I was gonna serve a life sentence
for a crime I didn't commit.
But worse than that, every time I looked
at someone in the eye,
from that moment forward,
they were gonna believe
that I had killed the woman I loved
in front of our son.
So, yeah. I do know
what's it's like being destroyed.
How did you get past that?
I embraced it.
Accepting it was the only way
that I could move forward.
But I knew that if I could survive that,
and learn to believe in myself again,
then I could survive anything.
You know what lit that belief in me,
Barry?
You. (CHUCKLES)
Eleven-year-old you running around,
believing in me, gave me that hope.
And now, I'm giving it back to you, Son.
No more monsters can take that from us.
So, one of the main differences
between ape and human brains
is the white matter and connectivity
in the brain cells.
The chemicals that
you were treated with as an infant
were meant to overcome those differences
and cause an explosive growth of both,
similar to what humans experience
in their first few years of life.
Maybe, these chemicals can be used
to duplicate that growth,
then we won't need
a particle accelerator explosion.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (GROWLS)
Hey, buddy.
HARRISON: Easy, buddy.
It's me.
I'm back.
Father? You died.
No.
No, buddy. I didn't die.
I just went away for a while.
All right, that's great, Wells.
Keep talking.
But now that I'm back,
we don't need Caitlin anymore,
do we, buddy?
So, you can let her go.
(GROWLS)
Come on, buddy.
Let me get her out of here.
Please.
GRODD: Father never ask.
Father take.
Run.
Who are you?
(GRUNTS)
Cisco, you gotta get in there, man.
Oh, Cisco, thank God.
Okay, you guys gotta get out of there!
Harry's trapped. We can't leave
him here. What do we do?
(STUTTERS) The drugs,
the drugs that Grodd stole.
Wells... an overdose of those
drugs will shock his brain.
Okay, just hit him with as much as you can.
You are not him. You are not father!
I am Father.
And you hit Father.
Grodd.
Look at me.
- Look at me!
- (ROARS)
(PANTS)
I would never leave you here alone, Grodd.
I made you a promise.
I have bigger plans for you.
Remember?
One day.
This city will be yours.
I promised you.
I intend to honor that promise.
(ROARS)
Go!
Come on.
Thank you.
Thank you for rescuing me.
Well...
We're a team, right?
I'm impressed.
Ithink we all are.
Yeah. We need to do something about Grodd.
- (GRUNTS)
- Like what?
Like, get rid of him for good.
You want to kill him?
Considering how many people he's killed?
Yeah.
This isn't Grodd's fault.
He's only like this because
Wells made him this way.
Yes, but Cait,
he kidnapped you and you could have died.
You didn't see what I saw.
Grodd's getting smarter.
He's lonely and sad.
He wants more apes like him.
What are you saying? He wants kids?
'Cause I'm pretty sure one telepathic
Grape Ape is more than
enough for this city.
I know somewhere we could send him.
What are you talking about?
When the singularity exploded
I discovered the breach in S.T.A.R. Labs,
I ran a similar test,
and discovered the same thing.
51 additional breaches.
The difference being,
the breaches in Central City
are scattered all throughout the city,
whereas their counterparts in my world,
most definitely are not.
And you know where they lead?
Well, I was in the process
of figuring all that out.
When Dr. Snow
so gallantly convinced me to stay.
But if I am correct,
this breach is gonna get Grodd
as close to home
as he's ever likely to get.
JOE: Okay.
Even if you're right,
how do we bait Grodd to go through it?
HENRY: My son will do it.
Won't you, Flash?
Grodd!
Caitlin.
(ROARS)
(GROWLS)
Flash.
You want Caitlin, Grodd,
you're gonna have to catch me first.
So, Barry's gonna lure Grodd
in front of the breach.
Yep.
And once he gets him to the right spot,
Cisco's gonna blast him into Earth-2
with his thingamajig.
Speed cannon.
Exactly.
Well, things have gotten a lot
more complicated
since I got out of prison.
- Mm-hmm.
- Man, you have no idea.
THE FLASH: Cisco?
Almost there, are you ready?
I'm in position.
Now, once you turn on the speed cannon,
the quark matter will stabilize,
stretching the breach about so big. So...
Anywhere within this circle will suffice.
Right on time.
(PANTS)
Okay, come on.
THE FLASH: I don't have eyes on Grodd,
does anyone see him?
(GRODD GROWLS)
(ROARING)
That is a big gorilla.
Where is Caitlin?
(THUDDING)
- Oh, my God.
- Get up, Barry.
(GROANS)
Where is Caitlin, Flash?
(GROANS AND PANTS)
CAITLIN: Right here.
(STRAINING) No. No, no, no.
You need to let him go, Grodd.
Flash is my enemy. Now, you too.
No.
He was trying to save me from you.
We didn't understand what you wanted.
But now, we do.
I can give you what you want.
I can give you a home.
You just have to trust me.
(THE FLASH GASPING)
(COUGHING)
All right, here he comes.
(GRUNTING)
Get ready to flip the switch.
Now, Barry!
(GROWLING)
- Full power!
- It is!
Barry.
You can't let Grodd get free.
Conquer your fears, son.
Believe in yourself.
(YELLS)
Come on.
Come on, come on.
(GROWLS)
(CHUCKLES)
(PANTING)
(LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Welcome back, Flash.
(SIGHS)
Thanks, bro.
I can't believe something good finally
came from that suit.
The first and the last time.
That thing still gives me the creeps.
We should destroy it.
Let's do that,
but see if you can figure out
how to get it back on this ring first.
Might be nice to have something like that
instead of carrying around
a bag all the time.
I can help you with that.
What?
I know a thing or two
about microtechnology.
Yeah. You know a thing or two
about a lot of things.
Well, as long as what he knows
keeps my son and these good people safe.
The more you know, the better.
Pleasure to meet you, Harrison.
Again.
Dr. Allen.
Good to see you.
Cisco.
- Let's go.
- Take care.
So, Dr. Wells, this place on your Earth
that we've sent Grodd,
what is it, exactly?
It's a refuge where gorillas subjected
to lab experiments, like Grodd,
(WHIRRS)
can roam freely.
I know it's for the best,
but I still feel like I betrayed him.
No, don't say that. You didn't betray him.
You gave him a better life.
I still don't understand, though. I...
Why do the breaches on our Earth
lead to different places on yours?
I don't know yet,
Ramon.
But I do know we have to close them all.
And I don't know how to do that.
You don't have to do it alone anymore.
Any of it.
Together, we defeated Grodd.
And if we stay that way,
we will figure out how to close
the breaches, get Zoom,
and get you your daughter back.
Thank you.
Oh, this one is definitely a keeper.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah.
He could've done just the standard
baking-soda-and-vinegar volcano,
but no.
Barry wanted to do
a molecular structure
- of chocolate and nougat.
- (CHUCKLES)
- It's my favorite candy bar.
- (LAUGHS)
Who does that in the sixth grade?
Why, a true science nerd.
- Like father, like son, I suppose.
- (IRIS WEST CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
All right, Dad. We should get going.
Yeah. Uh, Joe? Can I?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Iris.
Thank you so much
for reaching out to me.
I am so glad you did.
- Me, too.
- Mmm.
Joe,
there are no words, man.
Thanks.
All right. Um, I'm gonna swing by my lab
before I come home.
Which reminds me,
Patty, she's a smart girl.
She's not buying your whole sick story.
All right.
Patty? Would this be a new girlfriend?
Uh, yeah.
Something like that, yeah.
We'll talk about it on the way
to the bus station.
Come on.
- Bye.
- HENRY: See you.
You okay?
(SIGHS)
It's embarrassing. I... I love Barry
like he's my own son, but
when I'm reminded that he isn't,
I start to wonder
what it would've been like if, you know...
Dad, you would've been just as amazing
with your own son,
just like you were with me and Barry.
I hear you've been spending
a lot of time up here.
Well, you know what they say.
When the CSI's away...
It's good to see you on your feet again.
It must have been
all that canned soup you had.
Or maybe the homemade stuff
Joe brought you.
(STUTTERS) Yeah.
I wasn't actually sick, Patty.
Yeah, I figured that out. (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Why did you lie to me?
My dad was in town.
I needed to spend some time with him.
You couldn't just tell me that?
You gotta understand, Patty.
My dad was convicted of murder.
When someone's image
has been tarnished like that,
it's hard for some people to see past it.
And you seriously think
I'm one of those people?
No, I know.
I should've given you more credit.
No, you should've given yourself
more credit.
This isn't about your father, Barry.
This is about you.
I need to know that I can trust you,
if we're gonna do this.
Okay.
I'm serious.
- (CHUCKLES)
- I can tell.
You cannot always be a smart ass.
- Hi.
I didn't know if you liked
flowers or chocolate. So...
I got you both.
Well, I'm allergic to chocolate
and I think that flowers
are a waste of money.
Um...
I have lollipops in my car?
Cisco, I'm joking.
- Oh, God.
- (LAUGHS)
This is great. Thank you.
Listen, I wanted to come over here
and say I'm sorry
for bailing the other night.
I'm a liaison with the C.C.P.D.,
and there was an emergency
and I had to be there.
- The C.C.P.D.?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLES) Wow, that's really cool.
And very brave.
Thank you.
And this is very, very sweet, Cisco.
Um...
What is this?
- Oh, see, that right there?
- Mmm-hmm.
That's a digital movie projector.
I loaded all of Princess Bride on there.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Mmm-hmm. That's right.
So, all we need is a wall or, you know,
someplace where we can
pick up our date where we left off.
Well, if we're going to pick up
right where we left it...
(CHUCKLES)
Whoa.
Whoa. What? What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're just a really amazing kisser.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Let's go watch Princess Bride.
- Let's.
- There's a great wall up on the roof.
(GROWLS)
(SNIFFING)
(ROARS)