Previously on "The Flash"...
The Flash is back!
How did you get your powers?
Oh, you're not gonna believe it.
And do you two want
to know the best part?
I wasn't the only one.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes.
- This isn't good-bye.
- No.
More like, "See you later."
He's right where you wanted him.
What do we do now?
We find the others.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Begin recording.
Observations on subject number two.
Name, Rebecca Sharpe.
Or as she prefers,
the plebeian sobriquet Becky.
It's Becky with a Y, not, um, an I-E,
or an E-E, just Y.
And you heard me say
"no milk," right?
'Cause I am severely
lactose intolerant, like...
Subject was born in Sarasota, Florida,
the first indignity in a life
full of unfortunate circumstances.
Mmm, mmm.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[GASPS]
Oh, that is definitely not soy.
Oof.
Subject lives with her boyfriend.
Almost there, almost
there, almost there.
Oh!
[MOANING]
Kenny!
[GASPS] We are going
to deal with this...
[GROANS] In five... five to ten minutes.
- Correction...
- [DOOR CLOSES]
Subject previously lived
with her boyfriend.
- Oh, I don't know.
- Subject's occupation...
- Should I stay?
- Blackjack dealer.
Or should I hit?
- Subject's temperament...
- I... I don't know, man.
I think you should just
hit. Why don't you hit?
- Defeatist.
- Okay, I'll hit.
Great, perfect. And...
Got 21! [LAUGHS]
There it is. Here, ahh.
- Oh, ahh.
- [LAUGHING]
Here you go, sir. Congratulations.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Sure.
- There you go.
- Oh, that's... that's nice.
Thank you.
Looks like I found
my good luck charm.
[GASPS] Hey!
- [SCREAMS]
- [GASPS]
My appletini.
Oh, no, no, no.
Can I... can I maybe just...
Can I get a reference, you think?
No?
Subject believes no
matter what she does,
the universe will conspire to punish her.
Another job. Ow! Okay.
Or as she writes on her Myspace page,
"I am jinxed."
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
Great! There goes another car.
It's fine. I'm fine.
Subject's low self-esteem suggests
she will be easily manipulated.
Wait, wait!
Wait... ow!
Oh, jeez. Come on.
Wait, wait, wait!
Ow! Oh, come on.
I'm here! Hey, oh, yes!
Thank you, universe!
Finally, some good luck.
Hi. Okay.
Ow, ow, ow. Hey.
[PANTING] Hi.
Hey.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CLEARS THROAT]
[RUMBLING]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- [TENSE MUSIC]
- _
♪ ♪
[SLO-MO] Barry!
Where are you?
I don't know. I lost Caitlin.
There's too many of them, man.
No, you can take
them. Just listen to me.
You just need to do one thing.
Run, Barry. Run!
[SCREAMS]
Oh, come on.
[LASERS FIRING, ALARM BLARING]
They got me.
Oh, you have failed this city.
[SCREAMS]
[ALARM BLARING]
[EXHALES]
For real, Chad? In the back?
Suck it, old man.
[TOGETHER] Oh!
Wait, did you guys die already?
Well, Chad...
He just told us...
Come on. Come on.
I don't know what's
wrong with kids these days.
Churlish.
[LASER FIRING]
You better watch yourself, Chad.
Come at me at the
paintball field next time.
I'll kick your little... [LAUGHS]
Hey! Mrs. McConnell.
How you doing? Chad's a treasure.
- He really is.
- Pretzel for Caitlin.
Corn dog for Iris,
two franks for Cisco...
Yes, thank you.
Three burgers, five churros,
and six funnel cakes for Barry.
Look at all of this junk.
Guys, I'm really sorry.
If the pipes in the house weren't making
this weird, annoying sound,
I would have just actually
had you all over for dinner.
Squeaky pipes at the West house.
- What a surprise.
- Mmhmm.
Really? You're
familiar with this sound?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Oh, yeah.
You mean the... [MIMICS CREAKING NOISES]
- Yeah.
- It's been doing that for...
- 18 years?
- Yeah.
Every house has a personality, Iris.
- Just likes to be heard.
- Hmm.
[PHONE BUZZES]
Oh, my gosh. They broke up.
The Wexler-Waclawiks broke up.
- For real?
- Yes.
- Hell yeah.
- Yes!
Uh, who are the Wexler-Wa-claws-wilix,
and why are we happy
that their love is dead?
They're a couple that
were getting married
at the Propizio the weekend of the 2nd.
Which means now the venue is open.
That's amazing. What good luck.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So now we just have
to put a deposit down.
- I'll run it over.
- Nope, already covered, babe.
- Oh.
- [PHONES BUZZING AND BEEPING]
Oh, God. Breach alert, guys.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
[EXCITING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Uh...
♪ ♪
Hey, Harry, um, is Jesse not coming?
[SIGHS]
So, um...
I thought Jesse and I
were having date night.
Yeah, that's what you thought.
Let me just... Okay.
[QUIRKY MUSIC]
[CHUCKLES]
♪ ♪
Just let me...
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Okay, so...
Hey, Wally. It's me.
Good to see you.
So, I've, um... I've been doing some thinking.
- And...
- [STATIC INTERFERENCE]
You know, we've both been so busy...
- You and Earth...
- [STATIC INTERFERENCE]
Stupid hologram.
You know, it's that
darn Atlantean plastic.
It's really shoddy workmanship.
- Sorry about this.
- What is... what is this thing?
Break... Breakup cube.
You don't have breakup
cubes on your Earth?
Oh, that's not good. Okay.
Okay.
A breakup cube is, uh...
Kind of what it sounds like.
You know, you record a message
for the person you want to...
The person, and you,
uh, pick a music setting,
and then there's a tissue
that pops out if you need that.
You know, a breakup cube.
Jesse's breaking up
with me with a cube?
Seems like a really convenient
way to break somebody's heart.
Exactly.
What did she say in the message?
You know, you heard.
You... you're a great guy...
I don't remember.
Don't you have total recall?
Yeah... no, no. Don't... I did.
I don't. I did, but I don't.
♪ ♪
Come on, don't make me...
She... you heard.
She said that you're a great, great guy
and that she was busy on our Earth,
and that you're busy
here filling in for...
You know... [MIMICS WHOOSHING SOUND]
On this Earth, and she
just felt that you guys
were a little out of sync.
You know, and that
she thought she needed
some time, you know,
to work on her stuff.
You know, it's not you, it's me.
Not me. Her, me.
Her, not me. Her.
And... and she said, you
know, "I'll never forget you,
Wally West, because you're amazing,"
and then, uh, that you were her...
[CLEARS THROAT] First.
♪ ♪
And a bunch of other
stuff. Not important.
So... but he's tough. You
don't need that, right?
You're a tough guy. Right, West?
- Yeah.
Yeah, um...
♪ ♪
He doesn't want the
cube. I don't blame him.
[ALARM BEEPING]
211s at First National
and O'Sullivan Bank.
Could be a spree.
Central City Bank's
on that avenue, too.
I'll check it out.
We're not done.
What?
[FRANK SINATRA'S "LUCK BE A LADY"]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, I don't
know why the app crashed.
But, uh, this one's on the house.
♪ Luck be a lady tonight ♪
Oh.
Find a penny, pick it up,
then all day you'll have good luck.
So true.
Ah, afternoon, ma'am.
It is a good afternoon, Mr. Security Man.
[CHOKING]
[SCREAMS]
♪ Luck let a gentleman see ♪
♪ ♪
♪ How nice a dame you can be ♪
[ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
Please, don't touch the oven, Mom.
♪ I know the way you've treated ♪
♪ Other guys you've been with ♪
♪ Luck be a lady with me ♪
♪ ♪
Aww, you waited for me.
[GASPS]
- I see her.
- She's getting away in a Prius.
Last time I checked,
the Flash is faster than a Prius.
♪ ♪
♪ Luck be a lady ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
What the hell?
That's the least
secure security footage
I've ever seen.
Yeah, that's not even the
strangest thing she made happen.
I mean, I slipped on
a barrel of marbles.
It was like I was in a cartoon.
That's some seriously bad luck.
Yeah, there's no such thing as luck.
Yeah? Tell that to my cousin Hector.
He got jinxed by an ex.
Hasn't been able to find a mall
parking spot for three years.
Hey, so we ran the
sketches you made us
through the CCP database, and...
Her name's Becky Sharpe.
She's 24 years old, no priors.
No priors? Then why
is she in the database?
Because in the last three years
she's lived in Central City,
she's been rear-ended four times,
her identity stolen twice...
A cat burglar literally burgled her cat.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Okay, you see, Harry?
That is bad juju.
Okay, Ramon, what you call juju,
I call quantum entanglement.
Discrete quantum particles are connected,
and when triggered, they
simulate a synchronicity
that, to the untrained
eye... To the common eye...
Could seem like luck.
So if Becky can affect
the particles around her
in a positive way, then
their connected particles
start spinning negatively.
So when good things happen to her,
bad things happen all around her.
Great, she's got a good luck field.
- She's a meta.
- Well, except she can't be.
I mean, she's only been in
Central City for three years.
Yeah, so there's no
way she was affected
by the particle accelerator explosion.
Well, neither was Kilgore.
We saw firsthand what he could do.
Not to sound like a broken record,
but where the hell are all
these new metas coming from?
You know what? Maybe the scanners
in the suit picked something up.
You said you took all the tech out.
Okay, well, I left something in.
Okay? Sue me.
Wow.
Cecile needs me at the house.
You guys let me know what
you find out, all right?
All right.
- There.
- Yeah, I-I see it, okay?
Yeah, the suit definitely
registered trace amounts
of dark matter on Becky.
So if there was another
dark matter incident...
We need to figure out how
and where it happened, ASAP.
I'll calibrate your satellite
to scan for the same dark
matter found in the suit.
- Uh, no, you won't.
- Yeah, I will.
Don't touch the sat...
Don't touch the satellite!
- I'll be touching it.
- Don't!
- [PHONE BUZZES]
- Oh!
Um, something just
arrived for me at the loft.
I gotta go.
♪ ♪
What?
You called the plumber.
Joe West, I cannot keep
living with that sound.
You know, this house is, uh...
- Bitchin'?
- No.
It's in need of some work.
In my certified opinion,
you need all new piping.
Now, it'll set you back 15 thou.
- Hmm.
- Oh!
O-okay.
Thank you... so much.
You've, uh... you've given
us a lot to think about.
And I mean a whole lot.
[SIGHS]
15 thou.
My great uncle paid less
for this whole place.
I guess I'm gonna have to
break open the piggybank.
Or, you know, we could take that 15.
We could put it towards a
down payment on something new.
Ooh.
You're suggesting that
we sell my house?
Babe, I'm just saying,
you know, this is...
This is a really big place for a couple
of empty nesters like
us, and there's always
gonna be something that's
gonna need replacing.
Let me think about it, okay?
Mm-hmm. Think about it.
[SOFTLY] Think about it.
- I'll think about it.
- Mm-hmm, think about it.
♪ ♪
- [WHOOSHING]
- Barry!
Oh, my God. Turn around!
- I did!
- Did you see?
- No, I didn't see.
- You saw!
I did... see. But just for a second.
Which is like an
eternity for a speedster.
You know it's bad luck to
see a bride in her dress
before the wedding day.
Too late.
What happened?
Um, the Propizio called.
We're not gonna be able
to have our wedding there.
What? Why?
Well, um, the villa burned down.
I guess a crème brûlée competition
got a little heated.
Okay, well, thankfully
we have our backup.
No, another couple
booked it this morning.
[SIGHS]
It's okay, though. It's okay.
If we can stop evil
time-traveling speedsters
from destroying the planet,
we can find a wedding venue.
Barry, our wedding is in six weeks.
It'll work out. Okay?
I would marry you anytime, anywhere.
[SOFT MUSIC]
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
Ah, Kobe beef. My favorite.
[GIGGLES]
Becky.
What are the chances I'd run into you?
Is this your secretary?
Funny, you said she was haggard.
- No, I... I never said...
- I'll get that for you.
Whoa, whoa! [GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
I don't understand.
Your plan revolves around this dolt?
What's wrong with all of you?
Who makes soup so hot?
[BEEPING]
As lusterless as Rebecca is,
she may be the most
formidable of them all.
Then why don't we get her now?
The capricious nature of her powers
warrants further observation.
[SIGHS]
[BEEPING]
[SCREAMING]
Oh, man, are those live lobsters?
- Give me that. You're not...
- Stop hovering, okay?
- You're not holding it right.
- I know how to read
- a dark matter scan, Harry.
- Well, not from where I sit,
- you don't.
- Oh yeah, good one.
Don't you have somewhere else to be,
like breaking another speedster's heart?
Sorry I'm late. Iris and I just lost
two wedding venues
in less than 24 hours.
- Ah, bad juju.
- Give me that, okay?
Test, all right. Here we go.
And adjust.
[SCANNER BEEPING]
- Sorry.
- Ah, sorry.
Here, here. Right here.
This is where Becky Sharpe
was exposed to Dark Matter.
- Here?
- Yes.
It can't be. This is
the middle of the street.
It's not even an interesting one.
My scans are accurate.
- Your scans are accurate?
- My scans are accurate!
Explain how there's
nothing within miles of here
capable of even creating dark matter.
There was three weeks ago.
[RUMBLING]
This is where I came
out of the Speed Force.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
No, it isn't. You
came out in Ivy City.
No, I ran there after.
But I remember now.
This is where I came out.
This is where the portal opened.
And a wave of dark
matter washed out with you.
I can only imagine how many
meta-humans you created.
[ENGINE RUMBLES]
My best guess?
A busload.
We did it?
We brought dark matter
into Central City?
When you pulled me out
of the Speed Force, yeah.
All the people on that bus,
we turned them into metas.
Every time we try
to do something right,
- it goes horribly wrong.
- We're cursed.
Maybe we should burn some sage.
- Guys, we're not cursed.
- You're not cursed.
- You should be cursed at.
- Okay, why should we
- be "cursed at"?
- You should be cursed at
because you opened the Speed Force
- without consulting me.
- Okay, I don't think
- we need to rehash...
- [ALL EXCLAIMING]
- All right.
- Okay, I did consult you,
and you're the one who
gave me the calculations
- in the first place.
- Yeah, I told you not to use
them without consulting
me. I said, "Ramon,
don't use the calculations
without consulting me."
- Guys.
- Yeah, yeah, I heard you.
- I didn't see the need for that.
- And that's why
- you should be cursed at.
- What does that even mean?
What does it mean?
It means you're a...
Okay, you know what?
This is exactly why
we didn't contact you,
'cause the last thing we need
around here is more of
your salty-ass attitude.
If you don't need my salty attitude,
then maybe you should
carry on without me.
I'll let myself out.
Oh, are you going back to your Earth?
I'll breach you there right now.
"I'll breach you there right now!"
- That's not what I sound like.
- That was really high.
Listen, Cisco, I know Harry could stand
to work on his bedside manner, but...
You know what? We don't need him.
What we need is to focus
on catching this meta.
- Am I right?
- Yeah, you're right.
But Becky doesn't seem like
one of our typical villains.
I think if we could track her down,
maybe we could get through to her.
- [PHONE BUZZING]
- Hey, Cecile.
What? I'm on my way.
I need you to run me to the house.
You said you never wanted...
Yes, sir.
[WHOOSHING]
[WATER DRIPPING]
- Oh.
- What happened?
[SIGHS] The ceiling went
from clanking to howling,
and then it just started
pouring all this stuff down.
- Yeah.
- We need to turn the water off, stat.
Yeah.
So, the water valve
is in the crawl space.
Um, don't ever go into the crawl space.
I hear you, loud and clear.
Barry, thank you
very much for your help.
I'm gonna go check upstairs.
Man, why is this happening?
That girl jinx us?
No, no. Nobody jinxed us.
This house is just...
what's another word for "old"?
- Vintage.
Cecile thinks I should sell it.
Yeah? What do you think?
I think she's got a point.
Life would be a hell of a lot
easier in a brand-new house.
- Sounds like an easy decision.
- It should be.
But this house has got one thing
no other house will ever have.
[CHUCKLES]
Remember I'd measure
you kids at every birthday?
Yeah. I outgrew Iris at 12.
She kept saying she'd catch up.
All my memories of you kids
are tied into these walls.
How can I give that up?
Well, you don't have
to give that up, Joe.
We'll always have those memories,
no matter where you live.
Trust me.
When I came to live here
after my mom died, I learned that
it doesn't matter where you live.
Only matters that you
have people that love you.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hold on. What's up?
Great. Okay, I'll go there now.
Thank you. We're not jinxed.
If we were, Cisco
wouldn't have found Becky.
She is at Jitters. I'm going there now.
[WHOOSHING]
Winner, winner! Another winner.
Becky? Hi, you mind if I sit here?
Oh, today's my lucky day,
but you're not my type at all.
- Can I sit?
- Um...
Um, Becky,
well, you're probably wondering
how I know your name.
Mm, it's written on my cup.
Right, um, yeah, but that's not how I...
You see, I work for the CCPD as a CSI.
I investigate very special people.
- Celebrities?
- No, not celebrities.
- Um, meta-humans.
- Oh.
Which is what I think you are.
[SCOFFS]
See, I think you were exposed
to dark matter on a city bus
- three weeks ago.
- [SCOFFS]
I think I would know if I
was exposed to dark matter.
That's weird.
Becky, I know you've been
having a lot of luck lately.
- [EXHALES]
- And that you took some money
from a Central City bank
that doesn't belong to you.
- How do you know all that?
- I just do.
Look, getting powers is overwhelming.
I'm sure you don't know how they work
or what you should do with them.
I have some idea.
Uh-uh-uh.
Do you really want to test your luck?
Bad things happen to
people that get in my way.
[STEAM WHISTLING]
[INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Listen, CSI guy.
My entire life has been
one piece of crummy luck after the next.
Look, we all have ups and downs in life.
Oh, not Becky Sharpe.
I have only ever been dealt bad hands.
But I knew one day
the universe would
see it made a mistake.
And then I'd have the run of the table.
I got on that bus, and
Lady Luck smiled on me.
Becky, this isn't some higher
power fixing a miscalculation.
You have powers, and they're affecting
everyone around you,
making them feel as awful
as you used to feel.
I'm sorry about that, but...
maybe it's just their turn.
Maybe for once, everyone else can feel
for a second how bad
I felt my entire life.
Anyway, there is nothing you can do
to stop me.
[STEAM HISSING]
♪ ♪
[BABY CRYING]
[TOOL CLICKING]
Toodles.
So what are we gonna do?
I don't know. I
mean, I'm not sure yet.
I can't get close enough to
her without triggering bad luck.
Seriously, that girl's a hazard.
- Hazard, that's the one.
- [GASPS]
Maybe that means the jinx is gone.
Her powers only work
in her immediate vicinity.
She didn't jinx us.
And the house is still falling to pieces.
It's been falling apart for years,
just, like, really slowly.
Well, plus, Jesse dumped me, too.
I... I know, dude.
And, you know, that sucks.
And we're up against a
meta we can't even touch.
And we're the ones who
made her in the first place.
Guys, do you have any idea
how ridiculous you all sound?
We have not been jinxed.
Or cursed, all right?
We make our own luck, right?
So what do you say we focus
and we figure this out?
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hey, Iris.
You're where?
[ORGAN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Oh, come on.
- Hey.
Why did you want me to put on a shirt
- and meet you at a funeral?
- No, no, no.
I wanted you to meet me at this church.
- What?
- We're getting married.
- Here, put this on.
- Excuse me?
Barry, we've had the worst luck, okay?
From the Dominators
to Savitar to gorillas
and now these bus metas.
And on top of everything
else, now we're cursed.
- Iris, we're not cursed.
- Barry, look.
You said that you would
marry me anytime, anyplace.
- Well, this is...
- Right?
And I just feel like if
we don't get married now,
- it's never gonna happen.
- That's not true, okay?
- I mean...
- Oh, it's our turn.
Our turn. Go, go, go, go, go.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Sorry, excuse me.
Beautiful service.
- So sorry.
- I love this coffin.
- Is that cedar?
- Hey, let's... come on.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Can I help you?
- Uh, yes.
Uh, we would like to get married.
- Yes, we would.
- Oh.
- Right now.
Well, would you give us a moment
to, uh, reset the altar?
Oh, no, no, that won't be necessary.
Look, we'll just... watch. Watch.
- Okay.
- We'll just...
Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
She's excited. Sorry.
Flip that around.
Yeah, probably
shouldn't have done that.
I know, it's fine.
Okay. We are here
today to join, um...
- That's you.
- Me?
Bartholomew Henry Allen.
- And...
- Iris Ann West.
In holy matrimony. [COUGHS]
- Excuse me.
- You okay?
Thank you. [COUGHS]
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God.
- Jameson! Oh!
- [HACKING COUGH]
Kevin, did you use
the cinnamon incense?
You know he's allergic to it.
Shame on you.
I don't know if we need to
shame the little boy, but...
No, you're fine.
You're fine. Walk it off.
- Father...
- [COUGHING]
- It's fine.
- That did not just happen.
You know, it was a...
very nice funeral.
Really, Barry?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC]
Ahh! Ow!
[LAUGHING]
That was golden.
Don't shoot, okay?
I'm here to apologize.
I know you're trying to help us
fix our own colossal screw up.
- Yeah, like always.
- Yeah, I know.
I mean, I actually thought
you'd be at home by now,
but here you are working away.
Well...
things are a little
complicated on Earth-2.
Oh. Everything okay with Jesse?
Yes. I mean, yes.
If you must know, I spent the summer
assembling a support
staff for her, so...
Oh, like a Team Quick?
- No.
- Team Jesse.
- Jesse and the Quicksters.
- They're not called that.
- Well, they should be.
That sounds like an awesome team.
It is an awesome team,
because I assembled it.
But then, Jesse goes and kicks
me off the team, all right?
Apparently I'm too much
like me, whatever that means.
I push too hard. You
know, too many tests.
Too many training sessions.
You know, I don't allow
the team enough time
for their personal bonding.
I don't understand millennials.
Anyway. They took a vote. I'm out.
I don't even have a
home to return to now.
I can't even go back to my own Earth.
I'm sure you can
empathize, right, Ramon?
Because you know what I'm
like. Well, you know what?
We'll handle Sharpe,
and then I'll be out of your hair.
[SIGHS]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Guys, there are low
probability events happening
- all over the city.
- Becky's quantum field
- is expanding.
- Okay, that's not possiblsi
Yeah, no, her powers are localized.
Not anymore.
♪ ♪
Babe, you in there? The door's jammed.
One sec.
[SIGHS]
[WATER DRIPPING]
[SCREAMS]
Guys, the quantum
field is getting higher.
♪ ♪
My pals said you were bad luck, sir,
but I figure, what are the odds
a pilot has a goose fly
into his engine twice?
♪ ♪
[GOOSE HONKING]
- Bird strike.
- [ALARMS BLARING]
Mayday, this is Flight 512 to tower.
Lost an engine and are coming down.
When did Hazard get so powerful?
Every action has an equal
and opposite reaction, so...
The more good luck she experiences,
the more bad luck she spreads.
She must be experiencing
an extreme level of good luck
for her quantum field to
be expanding like this.
- Where is she now?
- She went back to work.
[TOGETHER] Snake eyes!
- For the 37th time.
- [CHEERING]
Bringing your winnings to 1.2...
BOTH: Million.
[LAUGHS] Give me those babies.
Hi. Okay.
Here we go. Oh, come on, Mama.
Guys, if Becky keeps winning,
then bad luck will keep spreading.
This could destroy the whole city.
- Okay, keep calm, all right?
- Keep calm.
Nothing's going wrong here.
[LOUD WHIRRING]
Guys, the particle
accelerator turned back on.
It's gonna explode.
Four minutes to particle
accelerator activation.
Harry, Cisco, status report.
The generators turned themselves on.
We got to shut 'em down.
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Flight 512 to tower,
we are attempting a water landing.
Cecile!
[HANDLE CLATTERS TO GROUND]
Damn it.
[INTENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[COINS CLINKING]
Barry, you've got to find Hazard.
I'm almost at the casino.
Hazard's quantum field is increasing.
- How much worse can it get?
- Hello, my old friend.
Let's keep this winning
streak going, shall we?
♪ ♪
[CHEERY ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
Yes. Okay, Cherry.
Here we go, cherry.
Cherry, cherry, cherry.
Cherry, cherry, cherry, Cherry. Cherry.
Cherry! Cherry.
It's a cherry. Give it
to me, give it to me.
Cherry, cherry, cherry, cherry, cherry.
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
How is that even possible?
- Wait, no!
- [ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
[GROANS]
Starboard fan blades
just disintegrated.
We're not gonna make it to the water.
- Barry, what happened?
- Well, she's playing
the slots, and, um, I cuffed myself.
[LAUGHS] Oh, honey.
Yeah, no, I know.
We need to get 'em off.
They're dampening my powers.
[ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
Yes, yes, yes. I'm trying.
The hydrogen particle
hatch. We need to seal it.
♪ ♪
There you go.
Cherry bang bang.
Cherry bang bang, cherry.
- [CHEERY JINGLE]
- Cherry bang bang!
- That's two cherries.
- Come on.
Hey, look. It's the Flash.
- [GRUNTS]
- [ALARM BLARES]
No, no, hey. There's no fire.
There's not a fire!
Someone set off the alarm.
Calm down!
♪ ♪
- Babe, you okay?
- I think so.
- [SCREAMS]
- Damn it, out back.
- Out back, out back. Be careful.
- Okay, okay.
One minute to activation.
Got it.
- Nope.
- BOTH: Don't got it.
That just opened up the electron hatch.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Yes, I am on fire. I know.
- [SCREAMS]
- There's no fire!
[GRUNTS]
Come on. Come on, cherry pop.
Cherry pop, cherry. Cherry pop, cherry.
[BOTH SCREAM]
Damn!
[SCREAMS]
[ELECTRICITY SPARKING]
♪ ♪
Barry, I can't get the cuffs off.
Now we got a sign
to get off of me, too.
Cherry number three, pop cherry, pop.
Brace, brace, brace!
- 30 seconds to activation.
- Nope, nope.
♪ ♪
What are you doing? Come on.
No, wait. Wait.
Let it go.
What?
- Let the accelerator turn on.
- Harry...
Let the accelerator
turn on. Trust me.
- Ten seconds to activation.
- This is it.
Last one.
Five, four, three, two...
Here we go.
[EXPLOSION]
♪ ♪
Cherry pop, cherry. Ah!
[RUMBLING]
[DULL BEEP]
No. What?
Star? No, I... I don't understand.
I lost?
[ELECTRIC RUMBLING]
[ENGINE ROARING]
The starboard thrusts are alive.
- We're gonna make it.
- Good.
What just happened?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
The hydrogen electron
collision released a charge
that temporarily negated
Hazard's quantum field.
We did it.
You did it.
How did you know to do that?
Lucky guess.
[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[WHOOSHING]
[GASPS] Okay. Hi.
- Hi.
- Um, is there, like,
any chance that you're
not gonna arrest me?
No? I understand.
- Come on.
- Sure.
- Ow!
- Okay.
- Okay. Yep.
- Right this way.
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[KNOCKS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ramon...
I owe you an apology.
Okay.
- No, that was it.
- Okay, all right.
How about something like...
"I'm sorry for blaming
everything on you?"
Or, "I'm sorry for 'cursing at' you."
Yeah, that's good.
That's good, that... yeah.
Pretend I said that.
Guess I'll take it where I can get it.
All right. Good talk.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
You don't have to go back to Earth-2.
♪ ♪
- What?
- You saved the day.
That's your "Get out of
jackass jail free" card.
- Hmm.
- Plus, you're family.
You'll always have a home here.
♪ ♪
Thank you, I...
I appreciate the
sentiment. It's just that...
- This is not my world.
- Oh, and Earth-2 is?
Did you make a bunch of friends
there that I don't know about?
What, are they all tall, brooding dudes
with bad haircuts?
[SCOFFS] I have...
I have colleagues.
Work colleagues. And, uh...
- Some of them I don't dislike.
- Exactly my point.
You've spent so much
time worrying about Jesse
and talking to dead people
that you've never even stopped
to make a life for yourself.
What are you saying, Ramon?
Are you literally saying
I don't have a life?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
You don't have a life.
But you can make one.
With us, right here.
We'll help you.
'Cause God knows you're
gonna need that help.
♪ ♪
[CHUCKLES]
- I don't think so.
- I don't think so, either.
Becky is locked up in the
meta wing at Iron Heights.
Something tells me
our bad luck streak
- has come to an end.
- Good.
We can't afford to blow
this place up a third time.
So, look at these heat
scans taken from the satellite.
This is three weeks ago.
It's a Central City bus?
- That's the bus?
- That's the bus.
Each of these heat scans
indicates a human body.
12 markers, 12 metas.
Now that we know how many there are,
we won't have to wait
for them to come to us.
We can go right to them.
- Well, two down.
- Yep.
- We got this.
- Yeah, you do.
What's wrong, Wally?
You guys tell me. I mean...
the city was about to blow up.
No one realized I wasn't here.
- Where did you go, Wall?
- I went to Earth-2.
I had to talk to Jesse. Hear it from her.
She told me she needs to
focus on herself, and I get it.
And I think I have
to do the same, right?
So...
I'm leaving Central City.
Where... where are you going?
I'm gonna go stay with a friend
in Blue Valley for a while.
Every hero has their own journey.
If yours is taking you on a new path,
you owe it to yourself to go.
Yeah.
[MELANCHOLY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Good luck.
- Kid Flash.
- [LAUGHS]
♪ ♪
I don't want anything more
than for you to find
what you're looking for.
But I've...
I've spent so much time
without you in my life.
I don't want to lose you.
You'll never lose me, Dad.
Plus, I'm a speedster.
You need me, and I'll come running.
- Love you, son.
- Yeah. Love you.
♪ ♪
You sure?
Yeah.
Well, don't forget,
Central City will always
be the home of Kid Flash.
I won't.
- Don't be a stranger.
- I won't.
- I love you.
- I love you more.
♪ ♪
Okay.
West leaves,
Allen returns.
West leaves. Move, counter move.
What's your point?
Simply that...
a mysterious stranger comes to town,
seeks out the Flash...
Causes us to open the Speed Force.
Which causes the creation
of a dozen new metas.
- Right.
- Hold on.
You think the guy behind
the Samurai Robot...
- Samuroid.
- You think he wanted us
to create a busload of metas?
I think it's all connected.
Why would anyone want to create metas?
I don't know.
Whoever they are, they've got
a seriously warped way of thinking.
[ELECTRONIC HUMMING]
They identified the targets
sooner than we planned.
Perhaps they're smarter
than you gave them credit.
[WHIRRING]
Perhaps.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
But I'm smarter.
♪ ♪
Oh!
Just when I thought it was
safe to get back in the house.
Hi.
I may not be a Craftsman expert
such as yourself, but
I can handle plastering
a couple of holes in the wall.
Baby, you didn't have to...
You didn't have to do this.
Oh, this is our home,
and it is a disaster zone
right now, so I am doing my part
- to fix it up.
- Well, I appreciate that.
- Mm.
[LAUGHS]
But, little Cecile...
- you were right.
- Hmm?
It's time for me
to let this place go.
I... It took me a minute to get there.
I'm not good with change. You know that.
But once I did, I realized that
whatever house I'm in
with you, I'm gonna love.
So we might as well get
one with a dishwasher.
- [LAUGHS]
- And a Jacuzzi.
[GASPS] Jacuzzi.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- [LAUGHS]
- I love you.
I love you.
- Funny thing, babe.
- Hmm?
I've actually had a change of heart.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
You want to stay? Really?
- Yeah.
- [LAUGHS]
You told me that you couldn't
have asked for a better place
to raise your kids, and it made me
look at this house with new eyes.
Mm.
Especially after I found out...
[CLEARS THROAT]
Joe...
I'm pregnant.
Joe?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --