Katie!
Cora!
You love your sister?
You make any noise,
you know what happens.
Good morning, Estelle.
How am I looking, Paul?
That's better.
Morning, Mr. Edgecomb.
Some Danish this morning?
No, just two pieces of dry
toast, Hector. Thanks.
Leftover's fine.
Dry and cold, same as always.
Cold is better.
Hmm.
Especially on those long walks.
Am I right?
Don't let Nurse
Godzilla catch you.
She'll raise holy hell.
You know we're not supposed
to let you wander off.
Where do you go every day?
What do you do
up in those hills?
Just walk.
I like to walk.
You try not to
fall down, bust a hip.
I don't wanna be in
no damn search party.
What? Do you want
this man constantly in your life?
Explain the moral basis of that.
I admit
I've made mistakes.
Tony doesn't admit that
he's not a good father.
No, it's not...
She can't ask nothin', okay?
You can't ask nothin'.
I had six kids myself.
Why do we always
watch this stuff?
It's interesting.
Interesting?
Bunch of inbred trailer trash?
All they ever talk
about is fucking.
It ain't no way
in this God green earth
I'm gonna have
a father like that!
If what you say is true...
No,
I'm talking now!
What kind of a mother are you?
One that
causes people more than...
is going to let you
try the Body Strider...
You're dead!
You can't come back!
It's back.
The Popeil Pocket Fisherman.
All right, all right.
Take my husband, take my kids...
Are you all right?
Hmm?
You look tired.
You're not yourself.
No, I'm... I'm fine.
I promise.
You're wearing yourself out
with those walks every day,
that's what I think.
Not that you asked me.
I just didn't
sleep well, is all.
I had a few bad dreams.
It happens. Lt...
I'll be fine.
What do you think of that?
Oh, if Madge
doesn't care, I certainly don't.
Neither do I.
All I know is...
Now, this here is worth a look.
Paul, what is it?
My God.
I've got to get out of here.
I guess sometimes the past
just catches up with you
whether you want it to
or not. It's silly.
Was it the film?
It was, wasn't it?
I haven't spoken of these
things for a long time, Ellie.
Over 60 years.
Paul, I'm your friend.
I ever tell you that I was a prison
guard during the Depression?
Uh, you've mentioned it.
Did I mention that I was
in charge of death row,
that I supervised
all the executions?
Usually, death row is
called "The Last Mile."
We called ours
"The Green Mile."
The floor was
the color of faded limes.
We had the electric chair.
"Old Sparky," we called it.
Oh, I've lived
a lot of years, Ellie.
But,  1935,
that takes the prize.
That year, I had
the worst urinary
infection of my life and...
It was...
It was also the year
of John Coffey and...
the two dead girls.
Old Alabama
J'ines the state of Floridy
At Mobile, lordy, at Mobile
Old Alabama is
a hog killing country
Every fall, lordy, every fall
All right,
now, hold on!
Up on the tower!
New prisoners coming in!
You men down in the yard, step
off the fence! Clear that gate!
Put me through to E Block.
E Block.
Yeah.
Right.
Oh.
Paul? Prisoner.
Christ, give me a minute.
You all right in there?
For a man pissing razorblades,
yeah.
Ah!
Oh.
You should've took the day
off, gone to see the doctor.
With a new arrival?
You know better.
Besides...
It's not as bad as it was.
I think it's clearing up.
All right. Let's look alive, Dean.
Yes, sir.
Damn.
They're riding on the axle.
What'd they do?
They bust the springs?
Holy...
Dead man!
Dead man walking!
Who...
We got
a dead man walking here!
Jesus, please us,
what is he yelling about?
Paul,
you might wanna reconsider getting
in the cell with this guy.
He's enormous.
Can't be bigger than you.
Dead man walking.
Dead man!
Dead man walking!
Dead man walking here!
Dead man!
We got a dead man walking here!
Dead man walking!
Percy.
That's enough.
Am I gonna have any trouble
with you, big boy?
Can you talk?
Yes, sir, boss.
I can talk.
Move your ass. Let's go.
Come on.
Percy,
they're moving house
down in the infirmary.
Why don't you go see
if they could use some help?
No. They got all
the men they need.
Why don't you just
go and make sure?
Uh-uh.
I don't care
where you go, Percy,
just as long as it's not here
at this very moment.
All right.
Ow!
God, you bust my finger.
I wiped that grin off your
shit-poked face, didn't I?
Goddamn it, Percy,
get the hell off my block!
Uh-huh.
Fuck you, Percy.
We're gonna get
that looked at, Del.
In the meantime,
you just stay quiet.
Yeah. Yeah.
I let Harry take
those chains off you.
You gonna be nice?
Your name is John Coffey.
Yes, sir, boss.
Like the drink,
only not spelt the same.
Oh, you can spell, can you?
Just my name, boss.
J-O-...
My name is Paul Edgecomb.
If I'm not here, you can ask for Mr.
Terwilliger,
Mr. Howell or Mr. Stanton,
these gentlemen right there.
Questions?
Do you leave
the light on after bedtime?
'Cause I get a little scared
in the dark sometime,
if it's a strange place.
It stays pretty bright
around here all night long.
We always keep a few lights
burning out in the corridor.
The corridor?
Right out there.
You can sit.
I couldn't help it, boss.
I tried to take it back,
but it was too late.
Dean, pull Delacroix's card,
take him down to the infirmary,
see if those fingers are broken.
Yes, sir.
Of course they're broken.
I heard the bones crack.
Did you hear what he was yelling
when we brought
the big dummy in?
How could I miss it, Harry?
The whole prison heard.
Goddamn Percy.
You'll probably have to answer
for sending him off the Mile.
Hmm. I'll chew that
food when I have to.
Right now I wanna hear
about this new inmate.
Aside from how big he is, okay?
Monstrous big.
Damn.
Oh, he seems meek enough.
Is he retarded, you figure?
Mmm-hmm.
Looks like they sent us
an imbecile to execute.
Imbecile or not, he deserves
to fry for what he done.
Make your blood curdle.
What? For God's sake, what?
The girls!
The girls are gone!
Papa! Papa, look!
There's blood.
Oh, my God.
Goddamn it, woman! Get on that phone now!
You tell them we headed west.
You mind what I'm saying!
We headed west!
Central! Are you on the line?
Oh, God, please! Somebody
took my little girls!
Katie!
Cora!
Jesus.
I'll kill you!
I... I couldn't help it.
I tried to take it back,
but it was too late.
Boy, you under arrest
for murder.
I interrupt?
Well, I'm just about done.
Hey,
how's that pretty gal of yours?
Melinda's not so well, Paul.
Not so well at all.
More headaches?
Got laid up with
another one yesterday.
Worst one yet.
I'll be taking her over to Vicksburg
next day or so for some tests.
Head X-rays and
who knows what else.
She is scared to death.
Truth to tell, so am I.
If it's something they
can see on the X-ray,
maybe it's
something they can fix.
Maybe.
This just came in.
DOE on Bitterbuck.
You didn't come all the way down
here just to hand me a DOE.
I had an angry call from the state
capitol about 20 minutes ago.
Is it true you ordered
Percy Wetmore off the block?
It is.
Now, I'm sure
you had reason, Paul,
but like it or not,
the wife of the governor of
this state has only one nephew,
and his name happens
to be Percy Wetmore.
Little Percy calls his aunt,
and squeals like
a schoolroom sissy.
He also mention
he assaulted a prisoner
this morning out
of sheer petulance?
Broke three fingers on Eduard
Delacroix's left hand?
I didn't hear that part.
I'm sure she didn't either.
The man is mean
and careless and stupid,
and that's a bad combination
in a place like this.
Sooner or later, he's gonna
get somebody hurt or worse.
Stick with it, Paul.
It may not be much longer.
I have it on good authority
that Percy has an application
in at Briar Ridge.
Briar Ridge?
The mental hospital.
Administration job.
Better pay.
Hmm.
Then why is he still here?
He can get that
application pushed through.
Hmm.
Hell, with his connections,
he could have
any state job he wants.
You know what I think?
I think he just wants
to see one cook up close.
Well, he'll get his chance,
then, won't he?
Maybe then he'll be
satisfied and move on.
In the meantime,
you'll keep the peace?
Of course.
Thank you, Paul.
Hal,
you give Melinda my love, okay?
I'm sure that X-ray will
turn out to be nothing at all.
You bet.
Paul.
Hey, you.
Hey.
The music too loud?
There's just this big,
empty spot in the bed
where my husband usually sleeps.
He said to tell you he's having a little
trouble with that tonight.
Worried about Melinda and Hal?
Is that what's got you up?
Yeah, that...
and things.
Things.
We got a new inmate today.
Simple-minded fella.
Do I wanna know what he did?
No.
Mmm.
Things that
happen in this world.
It's a wonder God allows it.
Why don't you come to bed?
I think I have something
to help you sleep.
Mmm.
Mmm. You can
have all you want.
I still got something wrong
with my waterworks.
I don't wanna pass it on to you.
Have you seen Doc Bishop yet?
No.
Paul.
Because he's just gonna
want me to take sulfa tablets,
and I'll spend
the rest of the week
puking in every
corner in my office.
It will run its
course all by itself.
Thank you very much
for your concern.
Poor old guy.
Oh.
Paul. Dean.
Yeah?
Come here. Go on.
I guess the legislature loosened
up the purse strings enough
to hire on a new guard.
Look again.
He's right...
there.
It ain't normal for a mouse
to come up on people this way.
Maybe it's rabid.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my Christ.
Yeah, it could be.
Oh, the big mouse expert.
The Mouse Man.
What, you see him foaming
at the mouth, Mouse Man?
I don't see its mouth at all.
Oh, Brutal, no.
We'll be hip-deep in mice.
I just wanna see what he'll do.
In the interest
of science, like.
He's in the damn restraint room.
And you just know he's chewing
the padding out of the walls,
making himself
a nice little nest.
All right.
Let's go get the damn mouse.
Boss.
Saw me a mouse go by.
Can't put anything over on you.
All right. Just watch your toes.
Watch your toes.
Yeah. All right.
Here we go.
You let him get past you.
No, I did not. I've
been here all the time.
Then where the hell is he?
Well, I don't know.
Three grown men
outsmarted by a mouse.
Well,
bright side is,
all this commotion
probably scared
him off for good.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's
the last we'll see of him.
You little son of a bitch.
Well, I'll be damned.
There he is,
big as Billy-be-frigged.
I thought Brutal
was pulling my leg.
And that's a goddamn mouse.
Yeah.
Brute said he was
in here last night,
begging for food.
He comes right on
up to the desk.
Give him some room, Percy.
Huh?
Yeah, see what he does.
All right.
He's a brave little bastard.
Gotta give him that.
Damn!
You little scurvy!
Percy, are you crazy,
you little son of a bitch?
I'm gonna kill you!
Percy!
I'm gonna take you out!
Percy! Percy!
You little vermin!
I'm gonna stomp your life out!
It's just a little mouse,
dumb merde.
You ugly little piece of...
Are you listening to me?
Fuck!
Percy!
I'm gonna rip your
diseased head off,
you little piece of shit!
Get on out of there!
I want you to stop this!
Pipe down.
I'm talking to you.
Percy.
Hey, boss!
Hey, Captain, what's going on?
Percy met your mouse.
It's in here somewhere. I'm gonna
squish the little son of a bitch.
Percy, we already tried that.
Huh?
What'd you say?
I said that we...
Knock yourself out.
Hope you nail the bastard.
Oh, yeah.
Gosh. He ain't
in there, huh?
Don't that beat the mousy band?
Percy,
you wanna think about
what you were doing just now?
I was trying to get the mouse.
Are you blind?
You also scared the living
crap out of me and Bill,
not to mention the inmates.
So what?
They aren't in cradle school,
in case you didn't notice.
Although you treat 'em
that way half the time.
We don't scare them any more
than we have to, Percy.
They're under
enough strain as it is.
Men under strain can snap.
Hurt themselves and hurt others.
That's why our job is...
talking,
not yelling.
You'd do better
to think of this place
like it's an intensive
care ward of a hospital.
I think of it as a bucket
of piss to drown rats in.
That's all.
Anybody doesn't like it? Hmm?
You can kiss my ass.
Don't.
Yeah, you try it. Go on.
Try it.
You'll be on the bread lines
before the week is out.
Okay, Brutal.
We all know who your
connections are, Percy.
You ever threaten
a man on this block again,
we all gonna have a go.
Job be damned.
You done?
Get all this shit back
in the restraining room.
You are cluttering up my Mile.
Arlen,
your daughter
and her family are here.
Let's move. I want at least two
rehearsals before he gets back.
Uh, settle down, settle down!
Rehearsing now.
Everybody settle!
Arlen Bitterbuck, step forward.
Stepping forward, stepping
forward, stepping forward.
Is his head properly shaved?
Nope. it's all dandruffy,
and it smells.
I will take that as a yes.
Let's go, Arlen.
Walking the Mile,
walking the Mile,
walking the Mile.
I'm getting to my knees.
I'm praying, praying.
Lord is my shepherd
and so forth and so on.
I'm sorry for all
the bad shit I've done
and people I've tramped on
and everything.
And I hope they forgive me,
and I'll never do it again,
that's for sure.
Paul, we're not gonna have some
Cherokee medicine man in here,
hooping, hollering
and shaking his dick, are we?
Well, actually...
Still praying, still praying.
Getting right with Jesus.
Do it quietly, you old gink!
As I was saying, I don't believe
they actually shake
their dicks, Harry.
Be that as it may,
Mr. Bitterbuck is a Christian,
so we've got
Reverend Schuster coming in.
Oh, he's good. He's fast, too.
Doesn't get 'em all worked up.
On your feet. Come on, Toot.
You prayed enough for one day.
Getting to my feet.
Walking the Mile,
walking the Mile,
walking the Green Mile.
Walking the Mile.
Walking in the Mile.
Sitting down now.
Sitting down.
I'm taking a seat in Old Sparky.
What do I do?
Watch and learn.
Getting strapped.
Getting clamped.
Gettin' wired.
All right.
Getting all electrode.
Roll on one.
"Roll on one" means
I turn the generator up full.
You see the lights go
brighter in half the prison.
Arlen Bitterbuck,
you've been condemned to die
by a jury of your peers
sentence imposed by a judge in
good standing in this state.
You have anything to say before
your sentence is carried out?
Yeah.
I want a fried chicken dinner
with gravy on the taters,
and I want to shit in your hat.
I got to have Mae West
sit on my face
'cause I'm one
horny motherfucker.
You bastard.
That's a good one.
Quiet.
Quiet! Shut up!
Shut up!
Sorry, boss.
Toot, one more remark like that,
I'll have Van Hay
roll on two for real.
And I'll have one less crazy
old trusty in the world.
It was pretty funny.
That's why I don't like it.
We'll be doing this
for real tomorrow night.
I don't want anybody
remembering some
stupid joke like that
and getting going again.
You ever try not
to laugh in church
when something funny
gets stuck in your head?
It's the same goddamn thing.
I'm sorry, Paul.
You're right.
Let's keep going.
Harry.
Soak the sponge.
Putting on the black hood.
And I'm putting on my cap.
Why's he putting
that sponge on his head?
Conducts electricity directly to
the brain, fast like a bullet.
You don't ever throw the
switch on a man without that.
Hush up there, Toot.
Getting screwed.
I'm getting the cap.
Arlen Bitterbuck,
the electricity
shall now be passed
through your body
until you are dead
in accordance with state law.
God have mercy on your soul.
Amen.
Roll on two.
And that's that.
I'm frying! I'm frying!
I'm a done tom turkey!
This is a shocking experience!
One of the witnesses
showed up a day early.
Goodbye.
All right.
Let's do it again,
and let's get it
right this time.
Get that idiot out of the chair.
Do you think if a man sincerely
repents on what he done wrong,
that he might get to go back to the
time that was happiest for him,
and live there forever?
Could that
be what heaven's like?
I just about believe
that very thing.
Hmm.
Had me a young wife
when I was 18.
Spent our first
summer in the mountains.
Made love every night.
And she'd lie there after,
bare-breasted
in the firelight.
And we'd talk sometimes
till the sun come up.
That was my best time.
it'll be fine.
You'll do fine.
Arlen Bitterbuck,
electricity shall now be
passed through your body
until you are dead,
in accordance with state law.
God have mercy on your soul.
Roll on two.
Again.
Adiós, chief.
Drop us a card from hell.
Let us know if it's hot enough.
He's paid what he owed.
He's square with
the house again.
So keep your
goddamn hands off him.
What's up his ass?
You.
Always. You, Percy.
On account I hate the new boy?
That the way it is around here?
Why don't you just move on?
Take that job at Briar Ridge?
Hmm? Oh, yeah.
I know all about it.
Sounds to me like
a pretty good job.
Yeah, I might just take it, too,
soon as you put me out front.
Yeah, you heard me.
I want Brutal's spot
for the next execution.
Seeing a man die,
now that's not enough.
You gotta be close enough
to smell his nuts cook.
I just wanna be
out front, is all.
Come on. One time.
And then you know what?
You'll be rid of me. I swear.
And if I say no?
Well, I might just
stick around for good.
Make me a career of this...
Boss.
You are not gonna believe this.
Look.
I done tame me that mouse.
We see that.
Oh, oh. Watch this.
Watch what he do.
Ain't he something now?
He's smart, Mr. Jingles.
Mr. Jingles?
That his name.
He whispered in my ear.
Hey, captain...
Could I have a box for my mouse
so he can sleep in here with me?
I notice your English gets
better when you want something.
Wanna see what else he can do?
Hmm? Watch, watch, watch.
Mr. Jingle?
Mr. Jingle, wanna play fetch?
Wanna play fetch?
Play fetch.
Watch, watch, watch.
He fetch it every time.
Every time.
That's some smart mouse, Del.
Like he a circus mouse
or somethin'.
Correct.
That just what he is, too.
He's a circus mouse.
When I get out of here,
he's gonna make me rich.
You just watch and
see if he don't do that.
Play fetch?
We play fetch again?
Well, well, well.
Looks like you found yourself
a new friend there, Del.
Don't hurt him.
Okay?
Is that the one I chased?
Yeah, that's the one.
Only Del says his name
is Mr. Jingles.
Is that so?
Del's been asking for a box.
Thinks the mouse will
sleep in it, I guess.
Might keep it for a pet.
What do you think?
You know what?
We ought to find a cigar box,
and, uh, get some cotton batting
from the dispensary
to line it with.
Yeah.
That should do real nice.
Man said get a cigar box.
Morning.
Hal, you wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Close the door.
So you know...
You got a new prisoner
coming in here tomorrow.
William Wharton.
He's what you call
a problem child.
Got "Billy the Kid"
tattooed on his left arm.
Been rambling all over the
state last few years,
causing all kinds of trouble.
Finally hit the big time.
Killed three people in a holdup.
One of them a pregnant woman.
Bad news all around.
Hal?
It's a tumor, Paul.
A brain tumor.
They got...
X-ray pictures of it.
It's the size of a lemon,
they said.
And...
Way down...
Deep inside,
where they can't operate.
I haven't told her.
I can't think how.
For the life of me, Paul...
I can't think how
to tell my wife
she's going to die.
Oh.
Ah.
Aah.
Oh... Oh, God.
Oh, God.
I'm going.
What?
To see Dr. Bishop.
I'm going.
Today.
Soon as we get that new
inmate squared away.
That bad?
Oh, yeah.
The boy is doped to the gills.
Hmm?
Dean, hand me them clothes.
William Wharton?
Hey! You put on these
clothes now, you hear?
We're gonna have to do this.
Hellraiser, huh?
Look more
like a limp noodle to me.
Hey.
You've been
declared competent, son.
You know what that means?
It means you're gonna
ride the lightning. Yeah.
Percy, could you shut up,
give us a hand here?
Hellraiser.
Boss,
you don't look so good.
Look like you're
running you a fever.
Boss Edgecomb?
I needs to see you
down here, boss.
I got things to tend to just
now, John Coffey. You just...
You just stay still
in your cell.
E Block.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Look alive, big boy.
Careful.
- Careful.
- Step up. Step up.
Where you going?
Ain't this a party now?
Is it or what?
Let him go.
Shoot him.
Shoot! See who you hit.
Shoot the son of a bitch.
Come on, shoot me!
Shoot him!
Hit him, Percy!
God damn it! Hit him.
Hit me, you limp noodle.
Hit him, Percy!
God damn it, hit him!
Come on, Percy. Hit me.
Wharton, I'm warning you.
You warning me?
Warn me now.
I'm warning you!
- You're warning me?
- Shoot him!
Well, come on...
You're a big fucker.
Where'd you come from?
Come on, Dean.
Come on, boy, get up.
All right. Now, just breathe.
That's it.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
Breathe. Breathe, boy.
Didn't see it coming.
Come on, boy, breathe.
Come on. Just breathe.
We thought he was doped.
Didn't we? Didn't we all
of us think he was doped?
You didn't ask?
Well, I guess
that's not a mistake...
you'll be needing to make
again anytime soon, is it?
You go get Dean and Harry looked at.
Make sure they're all right.
Percy, you make the report
to the warden for me.
Start out by saying the
situation's under control.
It's not a story.
He will not appreciate you
drawing out the suspense.
Well, what about you? You're
about ready to collapse.
Ah, I've got the Mile
till you all come back.
Go on, now. Go.
Come on, boy.
Let's get you looked at.
Boss,
I needs to see you down here.
This is not a good time,
John Coffey...
Not a good time at all.
But I needs to see you, boss.
I needs to talk to you.
Closer.
Boss, you know you ain't
supposed to do that.
Mind your business, Del.
What do you want, John Coffey?
Just to help it.
Don't be afraid.
Help!
Help! John Coffey's
killing Boss Edgecomb!
Help!
What are you doing?
Boss Howell! Help!
Boss Stanton!
Somebody, come!
Help!
Help! Boss Howell!
Boss Stanton!
Somebody, come! John Coffey's
killing Boss Edgecomb!
Del, for Christ sakes, shut up!
What did you just do to me?
I helped it.
Didn't I help it?
I just took it back, is all.
Awful tired now, boss.
Dog-tired.
Boss,
what that man do to you?
Hey, honey.
How you feeling?
Oh, not too bad.
What did the doctor say?
Oh, you know doctors.
Gobbledygook, mostly.
Gobbledygook.
Having stew tonight.
What are you doing?
What does it feel like?
Well, I know what it feels like.
It feels great.
Mmm.
Paul.
Yeah?
Not that I'm complaining...
Uh-huh.
But we haven't gone four times
in one night since we were 19.
Yeah, we did,
at your mom's, yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
Wanna tell me what's going on?
Well...
See, the thing is...
I never actually made it in
to Dr. Bishop's yesterday.
Brutal, Paul. Listen.
I'm thinking of taking
the morning off sick.
You cover the fort for me?
That's swell. Thanks.
Yeah, no.
I'm sure I'll feel better.
Okay. Okay.
You're sure
you ought to do this?
I'm not sure what I'm sure of.
Burt, you got some company.
Can I offer you a cold drink?
Oh, yes, ma'am. A cold drink
would be fine. Thank you.
Mr. Hammersmith,
your office said
I might find you at home today.
Hope I'm not troubling you.
Well, that depends, Mr...
Paul Edgecomb. I'm E Block
supervisor up on Cold Mountain.
The Green Mile.
Yeah, I've heard of it.
Lost a few clients your way.
I'd like to ask you
about one of 'em.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Which client?
Now you got my
curiosity aroused.
John Coffey.
Ah.
Coffey.
He causing you problems?
No. No, can't say he is.
He doesn't like the dark
and cries on occasion,
but other than that...
He cries, does he? Well, got
a lot to cry about, I'd say.
You know what he did.
I read the court transcript.
Thank you, missus.
My pleasure.
Kids! Lunch is about ready.
Y'all come on up.
Coming, Mama!
What exactly are you
trying to find out?
I've wondered if he ever did
anything like that before.
Why? Has he said anything?
No, but a man who
does a thing like that
has often developed
a taste for it over time.
It occurred to me
that it might be easy enough
to follow his back trail.
Find out.
A man his size, and colored to
boot, can't be that hard to trace.
You'd think so,
but you'd be wrong.
Believe me, we tried.
Like he'd dropped
out of the sky.
How can that be?
We're in a depression.
A third of the country's
out of work.
People are drifting
by the thousands,
looking for jobs,
for greener grass.
Even a giant like Coffey wouldn't
get noticed everywhere he goes.
Not until he kills
a couple of little girls.
He is, uh...
strange, I admit.
But there doesn't seem to be
any real violence in him.
I know violent men,
Mr. Hammersmith.
I deal with them
day in and day out.
You didn't come
up here to ask me
whether he might
have killed before.
You came up here to see
if I think he did it at all.
Do you?
One seldom sees
a less ambiguous case.
He was found with
the victims in his arms.
And yet you defended him.
Everyone is entitled
to a defense.
Kids! Lunch!
Y'all listen to your mama now!
I'll tell you something.
And you listen close, too,
because it might be something
you need to know.
I'm listening.
We had us a dog.
Just a sweet mongrel.
You know the kind.
Well, in many ways, a good
mongrel dog is like a Negro.
You get to know it.
Often, you get to love it.
It is of no particular use,
but you keep it around because
you think it loves you.
if you're lucky,
Mr. Edgecomb,
you never have to
find out any different.
My wife and I were not so lucky.
Caleb, come here for a second.
Come here.
Please, Son.
He still has the one good eye.
I suppose he's lucky
not to be completely blind.
We get down on our knees and thank
God for that much at least.
Right, Caleb?
Okay, go on in now.
That dog attacked
my boy for no reason.
Just got it in his mind one day.
The same with John Coffey.
He was sorry afterwards.
Of that I have no doubt.
But those little girls...
stayed raped and murdered.
Maybe he'd never done it before.
My dog never bit before.
But I didn't concern
myself with that.
I went out there with my rifle
and grabbed his collar
and blew his brains out.
Is Coffey guilty?
Yes, he is.
Don't you doubt it.
And don't you turn
your back on him.
You may get away with it once
or even a hundred times.
But in the end,
you'll get bit.
Oh, me! Oh, my!
John.
I'm smelling me some corn bread.
It's from my missus.
She wanted to thank you.
Thank me for what?
Well, you know.
For helping me.
Helping you with what?
You know.
Oh...
Was your missus pleased?
Several times.
Oh, John, I can smell that from over here.
I surely can.
Can I give Del
and Mr. Jingles some?
Well, it's yours, John.
You can do with it
as you please.
Here. This for Del
and Mr. Jingles.
Hey! What about me? I'm gonna
get some, too, ain't I?
It's yours, John.
As you please.
I think I'll
just keep the rest, then.
Courtesy of the gentleman
across the way.
Oh, John, that's so very fine of you.
I thank you.
Mr. Jingle thank you.
My mama would thank you,
too, but she dead.
Welcome.
Hey! What about me?
Don't you hold out on me,
you big dummy nigger.
Ooh, here come the boss man.
You'll keep a civil
tongue on my block.
You get that one for free.
But that's the last one.
That's it?
Just that little
itty-bitty one?
I guess I'm gonna have to pay
you out for the rest, huh?
Yee-haw!
Good shot, weren't it?
The look on your face!
Do you believe this?
That son of a bitch
pissed on me.
Did y'all like that?
I'm currently cooking up
some turds to go with it.
Nice soft ones.
Have 'em out
to y'all tomorrow.
We've been meaning
to clean out that room
for a while, haven't we?
Oh, yeah.
Hey! Hey! Be careful with that.
That's fragile.
Hey. Hey! What is it now?
What's it now? Moving day?
Y'all wanna come on in
here and dust a little?
You can shine my knob for me
while you're at it.
You can come in here
on your legs,
but you'll go out on your backs.
Billy the Kid gonna
guarantee you that.
Come on, fuck-stick. No
sneaking up on me this time.
We'll go man-to-man.
Piss on me?
Come on, Wild Bill.
Little walky-walky.
Don't you call me that!
Wild Bill Hickok
wasn't no range rider!
He was just some
bushwhacking John Law!
Dumb son of a bitch sat
with his back to the door,
killed by a drunk.
Oh, my suds and body.
A history lesson.
Oh, you just never know
what you're gonna get
when you come to work every
day on the Green Mile.
Thank you, Wild Bill.
Not in there. Not in there. I'll be good.
Fellas, I'll be good.
Honest Injun,
I will. I will.
Christ, he's pitching a fit.
He'll be fine, boys.
Trust me on this one.
One, two, three.
Hey. Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, hey!
Hey, fellers.
Hey, it's not funny.
You won't leave...
All I wanted me was a little
corn bread, you motherfuckers!
All I wanted me was
a little corn bread!
I... I learned my lesson.
I'll be good.
Psst.
Hey, Toot.
Give you a nickel
for that MoonPie.
Ooh, ooh.
Little Black Sambo! Yo!
Yes, sir, yes, sir.
How do you do?
Hope your bags are packed.
My bags are packed!
I'm ready to go!
Where are we going? Let's go!
No! No! No!
Let me out of here!
That MoonPie thing was pretty original.
Gotta give him that.
Oh, yeah.
Del, grab up your things. it's a
big day for you and Mr. Jingles.
What you talking about?
Important folks heard about your mouse.
Wanna see him perform.
Not just
prison guards either.
One's a politician all the way
from the state capitol I believe.
You fellas coming?
No, we got other fish
to fry just now, Del,
but you knock 'em
for a loop, yeah.
You knock 'em for a loop, Del.
Just like Mr. Harry says.
All right. Let's move briskly, folks.
There's not much time.
All right, rehearsing now!
Gotta move our ass.
Ain't got much time.
I been fixing the plumbing
here for 10 years.
Ain't never had to wear
no damn tie before.
Well, you're the VIP today,
Earl, so just shut up.
All right, everybody,
have a seat.
This is great.
All right.
Eduard Delacroix,
electricity shall now be
passed through your body
until you are dead,
in accordance with state law.
God have mercy on your soul.
Roll on two.
That's that.
Very good.
Very professional.
Let's do it again.
You got all the words right.
It sounded just fine.
Thank you.
Yep.
It's hard to keep a straight face
when Toot's acting the goat.
You got that chin
strap good and tight
because his head
is gonna buck...
All right, break it up.
So?
Oh, they love Mr. Jingles.
They laugh over there,
they cheer,
they clap their hands.
Well, that's just aces.
Isn't that something?
You done good, old-timer.
We're happy for you.
Yeah, we are.
Boo!
Percy, you shit.
Come on. Del, get up.
Del, you numb-wit.
I didn't mean nothing by it.
I was just playing.
Come on, now.
I was just having...
- Ain't you sweet?
- Wharton.
- Soft like a girl.
- Let him go.
I'd rather fuck your asshole,
than your sister's
pussy, I think.
Wharton!
I let him go. I was just playing.
I let him go.
I'd never hurt a hair
on his pretty little head.
Your noodle ain't
limp at all, lover boy.
I think you sweet
on old Billy the Kid.
Ooh, but smell you.
Look.
He done piss his pants.
Oh, my God.
Look what
the big man done.
He bust other people with a stick.
Come on, get in.
Somebody touch him,
he make water in his pants
like a little baby.
Del!
Learn when to shut up.
All right, now.
Don't touch me.
You...
You talk about this to anyone...
I'll get you all fired.
I swear that to God.
What happens on the Mile stays
on the Mile. Always has.
Yeah, you keep laughing,
you French-fried faggot!
You just keep on laughin'!
Wetmore a good name for you!
Percy Wetmore do a dance.
Listen to him
squishing in his pant.
Well,
what about Dean?
He's got a little boy.
He'd love to have
a pet mouse, I bet.
How could a boy be
trusted with Mr. Jingle?
Maybe forget to feed him.
How he keep up
with his training?
I mean,
he just a boy, n'est-Ce pas?
Hmm.
All right.
I'll take him, then.
Me.
Thank you kindly, but...
You live out in the woods.
Mr. Jingle, he be...
He be scared to live
out in the big woods.
How about Mouseville?
Mouseville?
Tourist attraction
down in Florida.
Tallahassee, I think.
Is that right, Paul? Tallahassee?
Yeah, yeah.
Tallahassee.
It's just down the road a-piece
from the dog university.
You think, uh... You think
they'd take Mr. Jingles?
You think he's got the stuff?
Well, he is pretty smart.
What is Mouseville?
Tourist attraction, I said.
They got this big
tent you go into.
You have to pay?
What, are you shitting me?
Of course you pay.
Dime apiece.
Two cents for the kids.
For the kids.
Inside the tent
they got this, uh...
Mouse city,
made out of
old boxes and
toilet paper rolls,
little windows
so you can look in.
Plus, they got the Mouseville
All-Star Circus.
Yeah, there's mice
that swing on trapeze.
Mice that roll barrels.
Mice that stack coins.
Yeah, that's it.
That's the place
for Mr. Jingles.
Oh!
You gonna be
a circus mouse after all.
You're gonna live in a mouse
city down in Florida.
Oh, there he goes.
No!
Mr. Jingles!
No! No! No!
You kill my mouse.
I knew I'd get him
sooner or later.
It was just a matter
of time, really.
You fucking
cruel bastard!
Give him to me.
Might still be time.
What are you doing?
Paul?
What the hell?
Please, John.
Help him.
Please, Johnny, help him.
Oh, dear Jesus.
The tail.
Look at the tail.
You're back.
What did you do?
I helped Del's mouse...
He's a circus mouse.
Gonna live in
a mouse city down in...
Florida.
Boss, Percy bad.
He mean.
He step on Del's mouse.
I took it back, though.
Merci.
Brute...
You come along with me.
You fellas go on back
to your cribbage game.
Now, don't start in on me.
It was just a mouse.
Never belonged here
in the first place.
The mouse is fine.
Just fine.
You're no better at mouse-killing
than you are at...
Hell, at anything
else around here.
Yeah, you expect me
to believe that? Huh?
I heard the goddamn
thing crunch.
Aren't you glad
Mr. Jingles is okay?
After all those
talks we had about...
keeping the prisoners calm?
Aren't you relieved?
What kind of game is this?
It's no game.
See for yourself.
Go on.
Don't let nothing
happen to Mr. Jingle.
You switched him.
You switched him somehow,
you bastards.
I always keep a spare mouse in my
wallet for occasions such as this.
Oh, yeah, you playing with me, huh?
Both of you.
Just who the hell
you think you are, huh?
Ah!
We're the people
you work with, Percy.
But not for long.
Percy, I want your word.
My word?
I put you out front for Del...
you put in your transfer to
Briar Ridge the very next day.
Well, what if I just
call up certain people
and tell 'em
you're harassing me?
Bullying me.
Go ahead.
I promise you'll leave your
share of blood on the floor.
Over a mouse?
No!
But four men will
swear you stood by...
while Wild Bill tried
to strangle Dean to death.
About that, people will care.
Even your uncle, the governor...
will care about that.
Thing like that goes
on your work record.
Work record can follow a man
around for a long, long time.
I put you out front,
you put in for that transfer.
That's the deal.
All right.
You make a promise to a man,
you shake his hand.
Hey, boys.
No, now, say,
"Hey," Mr. Jingles.
Eduard Delacroix,
will you step forward?
Boss Edgecomb?
Yes, Del?
Don't let nothing
happen to Mr. Jingle, okay?
Here. You take him.
Del...
I can't have a mouse
on my shoulder while...
You know.
I'll take him, boss.
Just for now, if Del don't mind.
Yeah.
Yeah, you take him, John.
You take him till
this foolishment be done.
You gonna take him to Florida,
to that Mouseville?
We'll do it together,
most likely.
Maybe take
a little vacation time.
Yeah.
People pay a dime
apiece to see him.
Two cents for the kids.
Ain't that right, Boss Howell?
That's right, Del.
You're a good man, Boss Howell.
You, too, Boss Edgecomb.
I sure wish I could've met
you guys somewheres else.
Hope he's good and scared.
Hope he knows
the fires are stoked
and that Satan's
imps are waiting.
Del, it's all right.
Roll on one.
You be still,
Mr. Jingles.
You be so quiet and so still.
Eduard Delacroix,
you've been condemned to die
by a jury of your peers,
sentence imposed by a judge in
good standing in this state.
You have anything to say before
sentence is carried out?
I sorry for what I...
I sorry for what I do.
I give anything to take it back.
But I can't.
God have mercy on me.
Amen.
Don't forget about Mouseville.
Hey,
there's no such place.
That's just a fairytale these
guys told you to keep you quiet.
Just thought
you should know, faggot.
Eduard Delacroix,
electricity shall now be
passed through your body
until you are dead
in accordance with state law.
God have mercy on your soul.
Roll on two!
The sponge is dry.
What?
Jack, the goddamn sponge is dry!
Well, don't you stop it!
Don't you do it!
It's too late for that.
Is this normal?
God, the smell.
Oh.
He's cooking now!
They cooking him good!
They're about done, I reckon!
Yeah!
We're gonna have a hoedown!
He's cooking now!
We gonna have a hoedown!
'Cution gumbo.
Give me some!
I'm smelling gumbo!
I'm smelling...
I said, give me some!
I smell it!
Should I kill the juice?
No!
Roll, for chrisssake, roll!
He's frying now!
Why don't you shut it down?
He's still alive.
You want me to shut down
while he's still alive?
You watch, you son of a bitch!
It's all right, folks!
It's all under control!
Everybody stay calm!
Please, stay calm!
Kill it!
You do it!
You're running
this show, ain't you?
I didn't know the sponge
is supposed to be wet.
Brutal!
Brutal, no!
No! No!
What do you mean, "No"?
How can you say no?
You saw what he did!
Delacroix's dead!
Now, there's nothing can change
that and Percy is not worth it!
So he just gets away with it?
Is that how it works?
What in the blue fuck was that?
Jesus Christ.
There's puke all over
the floor up there.
And the smell.
I got Van Hay
to open both doors,
but that smell won't go out
for five damn years.
That's what I'm betting.
And that asshole Wharton
is singing about it!
You can hear him up there!
Can he carry a tune, Hal?
Okay, boys, okay.
Now, what in the hell happened?
An execution.
A successful one.
How in the name of Christ
can you call that a success?
Eduard Delacroix is dead...
isn't he?
Percy?
Yeah.
Something to say?
I didn't know the sponge
is supposed to be wet.
How many years you spend
pissing on a toilet seat
before someone
told you to put it up?
Percy fucked up, Hal.
Pure and simple.
That's your official position?
Don't you think it should be?
He's putting in for a transfer
request to Briar Ridge tomorrow.
Moving on to bigger
and better things.
Isn't that right, Percy?
Yeah. Yeah.
Barbecue, me and you
Stinky, pinky Phew, phew, phew
Weren't Billy,
Jilly, Hilly or Pa
it was a French-fried
Cajun named Delacroix
Whoo!
Barbecue, me and you
Stinky, pinky Phew, phew, phew
Weren't Billy, Jilly...
You're about 10 seconds
away from spending
the rest of your life
in the padded room.
Poor old Del.
Yeah.
John?
You okay?
I could feel it from here.
What do you mean?
You could hear it.
Is that what you mean?
He out of it now, though.
He the lucky one.
No matter how it happened,
Del the lucky one.
Where's Mr. Jingles?
He run away under that door.
Don't think he'll be back.
He felt it too, through me.
Didn't mean to hurt him none.
All that hurt just spill out.
Awful tired now, boss.
Dog-tired.
Me too, John.
Me, too.
I hate this.
I know.
Melinda, hi.
I am so happy to see you.
Oh.
Look at you.
Well, we missed you at church.
Oh!
Ah, my hair...
You look fine.
I'm just a mess.
She's having one
of her good days.
I thank God for that.
What's a bad day?
Sometimes she's...
She's not herself anymore.
She swears.
She swears?
It just pops out.
Most awful language
you can imagine.
She doesn't even
know she's doing it.
I didn't know she'd
ever heard words like that.
To hear her say them
in her sweet voice.
I'm glad she's
having a good day, Paul.
I'm glad for you and Jan.
Honey,
if you don't tell me
what's on your mind,
I'm afraid I'll have to
smother you with a pillow.
I'm thinking I love you.
I'm thinking I don't know what
I would do if you were gone.
Oh.
I'm also thinking I'm gonna
have the boys over tomorrow.
Well, you sure do know
how to cook chicken.
Well, thank you.
This is one delicious treat,
ma'am, before I go to work.
Well, I'm glad
you're enjoying it.
Hey, Brutal.
Hmm.
You gonna hog all them taters?
Yes, I am.
Harry, you want some taters?
Come on, now.
What?
Very soon we'll just see your
feet sticking out of there, Brutus.
Y'all saw what
he did to the mouse.
I could've gone the rest of the
day without you bringing that up.
I could've gone
the rest of the year.
He did the same thing to me.
He put his hands on me.
He took my
bladder infection away.
It's true. When he came
home that day, he was...
all better.
Oh, now, wait.
You're talking about...
an authentic healing?
A praise-Jesus miracle?
I am.
Oh, yeah.
Well, if you say it,
I accept it.
What's it got to do with us?
You're thinking about Melinda.
Melinda?
Melinda Moores?
Yeah. So, Paul,
you really think
you can help her?
It's not a bladder infection
or even a busted mouse,
but I think there
might be a chance.
Hold on now.
You're talking about our jobs.
Sneak a sick woman
into a cellblock?
Oh, no. No, no. Hal would
never stand for that.
You know him. He wouldn't believe
anything if it fell on him.
So you're talking about
taking John Coffey to her.
That's more than
just our jobs, Paul.
That's prison time,
we get caught.
You're dang right, it is.
No,
not for you, Dean.
See now, the way I figure it,
you stay back on the Mile.
That way,
you can deny everything.
Why do I have to stay behind?
Well, our boy's grown up,
gone off to school.
Harry's girls,
they're all married now.
Brutal's a single man.
You're the only one here with two
children, another one on the way.
Let's not discuss this as if
we're thinking of doing it.
Brutal, help me out here.
I'm sure she's a fine woman.
The finest.
What is happening to her
is an offense, Brutal...
To the eye and the ear
and to the heart.
I have no doubt.
But we don't know her
like you and Jan do, do we?
And let's not forget,
John Coffey is a murderer.
Now, what if he escapes?
I'd hate to lose my job
or go to prison,
but I'd hate worse to have
a dead child on my conscience.
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
In fact,
I don't think he did it at all.
I do not see God
putting a gift like that in the
hands of a man who'd kill a child.
Well, that's a very
tender notion,
but the man is on
death row for the crime.
And plus,
he's huge.
If he tried to get away,
it'd take a lot of
bullets to stop him.
Oh, we'd all have shotguns,
in addition to side arms.
I'd insist on that.
If he tried anything,
anything at all,
we'd have to take him down.
You understand?
So...
Tell us what you had in mind.
- Oh, there it is.
- Oh, I see it.
You think this is enough?
I don't know.
You fellas thirsty?
Fresh out of the icebox.
You bet. That's swell,
Brutal. Thanks.
Oh, yeah.
Hot in here.
Boy, howdy.
Hey, hey. I'm gonna
get some, too, ain't I?
My ass, you get some, too.
What makes you think
you deserve any?
Because I got a big pecker.
Well, the day report
says he's been okay.
Hell, yeah, I been behaved.
Come on, now.
Don't be stingy hogs.
Come on.
Come on now, fellers.
Come on, boss.
I been good all day.
It's hot in here.
It's hot in this cell, and I'm
dogged to drink. I'm thirsty.
Why don't you give me some?
Come on.
You gonna stay behaved?
Come on, you clunk,
give me that.
You promise me,
or I'll drink this myself
right here in front of you.
Don't, don't, don't... Come on, now.
Don't be that way.
I'll be good.
Cup.
Anybody wants out,
now's the time.
After this,
there's no turning back.
So?
We gonna do this?
Sure.
That'd be just fine.
I'd like to take a ride.
Guess we're all in.
What is this?
Payback.
That's right.
No, you let me go!
Let go of me!
Settle down.
Let go!
What are you doing?
Settle down.
Oh!
"Miss Lotta Leadpipe."
Oh, Percy.
What would your mother say?
You let go of me, you ignoramus.
I know people. Big people!
Percy, stick out your
arms like a good lad.
No, I won't do it.
You can't make me.
Oh, you're dead wrong
about that, you know.
You gonna put your arms up, huh?
A big man is ripping
your ears off, Percy.
I'd do as he says.
There you go.
Please, Paul.
Please don't put me
in with Wild Bill.
Please don't.
You would think that.
No, no, no,
you can't do this to me.
You can't do this to me.
You can't.
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret, Percy.
We can and we are.
We'll give you a few hours
of quiet time, Percy,
so you can reflect
on what you did to Del.
And if you get lonely, just
think about Miss Leadpipe.
All right, let's go
over it one more time.
What do you say
if somebody stops by?
Coffey got upset
just after lights out,
so we put the coat on him, locked
him in the restraint room.
They hear any kicking and
fussing, they'll think it's him.
What about me?
You're down in Admin
pulling Del's file,
going over the witnesses
on account of
how big a screw up
the execution was.
We going for the ride now?
That's right.
We going for the ride.
What about us, Dean?
You, Harry, Percy, all down in
the laundry doing your wash.
Take you'll a few hours
before you're back.
Where you think you going?
You a bad man.
That's right, nigger.
Bad as you'd want.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Whole room...
Whole room's spinning.
It's like
I'm shitty-ass drunk.
Had me some shine or...
Or what?
Niggers ought to have
their own electric chair.
White man...
ought not to have to sit in
no nigger electric chair.
No, sir.
He a bad man.
Look, boss.
It's Cassie, the lady
in the rocking chair.
Shh!  John,
we have to be quiet now.
You see her?
You see the lady?
Yeah, we see her,
John. Come on.
Let's go. Go, go!
Now!
All right, big boy.
Let's get moving. Come on.
Upsy-daisy.
John,
do you know where
we're taking you tonight?
Help a lady?
That's right.
But how do you know?
Don't know.
Tell the truth, boss,
I don't know much of anything.
I never have.
We can still turn back.
Boss, look.
Someone's up.
This was a mistake.
Oh, Christ, Paul,
what were we thinking?
It's too late now.
John, you stay.
Harry, you keep John
here till we call you.
Who the hell goes there at
2:30 in the goddamn morning?
Hal, it's us.
It's Paul and Brutal.
It's us.
Jesus.
It isn't a lockdown, is it?
Or a riot?
No.
Hal, for God's sakes,
just take your finger
off the trigger.
Are you hostages?
Who's out there?
Who's by that truck?
Harry, the lights!
John Coffey.
- Halt!
- Hal.
You stay
right where you are!
Relax, now.
Take it easy, now.
Don't you move!
Wait!
I'm warning you.
John, wait!
Hal, listen! Halt
right there or I'll shoot!
I said, halt!
Hal, put the gun down!
Halt!
Hal.
Hal!
Who you talking to down there?
God damn it!
Hal, now, nobody is hurt.
And we are here to help.
Help what?
I don't understand.
You're just gonna have to trust me.
What do you want?
Hal!
Make them go away!
I don't want no salesmen
in the middle of the night.
Tell them to take
a flying fuck at a rolling...
Just to help.
Just to help, boss.
That's all.
You can't.
No one can.
Stay out of here!
Don't you go in there!
- Whoever you are, just stay out!
- Don't you do it!
I'm not
dressed for visitors.
You stop now.
You hear me?
Paul, I don't want him up there.
Boss, you just be quiet now.
it's all right, Hal.
It's all right.
Hal, watch.
Just watch him.
Don't come near me, pig fucker.
Why do you have so many scars?
Who hurt you so badly, huh?
Don't hardly remember, ma'am.
What's your name, huh?
John Coffey, ma'am.
Like the drink.
Only not spelt the same.
Ma'am?
Yes, John Coffey?
I see it.
What's happening?
Shh, you be still now.
You be so quiet and so still.
Come on, John.
Sick it up.
Come on. Cough it
out like you done before.
He's choking. Whatever
he sucked out of her,
he's choking on it.
John.
I'll be fine.
Just let me be.
How did I get here?
We... We were going
to the hospital in Vicksburg.
Remember?
Shh...  Melly.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Did I have the X-ray?
Did I?
Yes.
Yes. it was clear.
There was no tumor.
Oh.
Hal.
John, can you stand up?
Can you turn around
and see this lady?
What's your name?
John Coffey, ma'am.
Like the drink.
Only not spelt the same.
No, ma'am,
not spelt the same at all.
Melly. No, you can't.
I dreamed of you.
I dreamed you were
wandering in the dark.
And so was I.
And we found each other.
We found each other in the dark.
Take it, John.
It's a present.
It's St. Christopher.
I want you to have it,
Mr. Coffey.
And wear it.
He'll keep you safe.
Please. Wear it for me.
Thank you, ma'am.
Thank you, John.
Christ, he goes down,
it'll take three mules and a
crane to pick him up again.
Take it easy, John.
Come on, now.
You gotta stay on your feet.
He'll never sit in Old Sparky.
You know that, don't you?
He swallowed that
stuff for a reason.
I give him a few days.
One of us will be doing a cell
check, and there he'll be,
dead on his bunk.
Well, if that's his choice,
he's earned it.
Let's just get him
back on the Mile.
Oh, boy, am I happy
to see you fellows.
You were gone so long, Wild Bill's
making noise like he's gonna wake up.
What the hell happened to him?
He's hurting, Dean.
He's hurting bad.
Okay, John.
We gonna set you
down on your bed now.
Here we go.
Well?
What about Mrs. Moores?
Was it like the mouse?
Was it...
You know, a miracle?
Yes.
Yes, it was.
Damn.
Now,
I want to talk, not shout.
I take that tape off,
you gonna be calm?
Mmm-hmm.
My mother always says you do it
fast, it won't hurt so much.
Guess she was wrong.
Let me out of this nut-coat.
In a minute.
Now! Right now!
I want out now...
Shut up and listen.
Now you deserved to be punished
for what you did to Del.
You accept it like a man.
Or else we'll make you sorry
you were ever born.
We'll tell people how you
sabotaged Del's execution...
Sabotaged?
How you pissed yourself
like a frightened little girl.
Ooh, yes. Yeah, we will talk.
But, Percy,
you mind me, now.
We'll also see you beaten
within an inch of your life.
We know people, too.
Are you so foolish
you don't realize that?
Let bygones be bygones, hmm?
Nothing's hurt so far
but your pride.
No one ever need
know about that,
except the people
in this little room.
What happens on the Mile
stays on the Mile.
Always has.
Hmm.
May I be let out
of this coat now?
My things?
Think it over, Percy.
Oh, I intend to.
I intend to think
it over very hard.
Starting right now.
He'll talk.
Sooner or later.
Hmm.
Hey, let him go!
John, let go!
Let go, John!
John, God damn it! Let him go!
Let go, John! No!
Back off!
John, stop it!
Stop it, John!
Let him go! Back off!
John, let him go!
Easy, now. Easy.
Easy. Hey.
Hey.
Percy.
Are you all right?
Boy, what you looking at?
What you looking at?
You limp noodle.
You wanna kiss my ass?
You wanna suck my dick?
No!
Grab the gun!
Dean, grab the gun!
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
I punished them bad men.
I punished them both.
Why?
Why Wild Bill?
I saw in his heart
when he grabbed my arm.
I saw what Wild Billy done.
Saw it plain as day.
You can't hide
what's in your heart.
What?
You saw what?
Take my hand, boss.
You see for yourself.
Paul, no.
Please.
No, no, no.
I gots to, boss.
I gots to give you
a little bit of myself.
A gift.
A gift of what's inside of me
so you can see for yourself.
Hot cross buns with warm milk.
Klaus!
Suppertime!
Bring the girls.
Girls! You heard your mama!
Yes, Papa!
We're coming!
Come on, Billy. I worked
you enough for one day.
Come get you some supper.
God is great, God is
good, and we thank you...
You love your sister?
You make any noise,
you know what happens?
I'm gonna kill her
instead of you.
You make any noise,
I'm gonna kill her.
You understand?
Shh...
He killed them with they love,
they love for each other.
Now you see how it is.
That's the way it is every day.
That's the way it is
all over the world.
- Percy.
- Percy Wetmore.
Percy.
Son?
Percy. Percy Wetmore.
Son, can you hear me?
Speak up if you can hear us.
I think this boy's cheese
slid off his cracker.
Percy, I got to
ask you a few questions.
That's right. One minute, he
was fine, and the next, blammo.
Dirty bastard grabbed him
through the bars few days back.
Scared the boy so bad,
he wet hisself.
See, we didn't even...
We didn't see it happen.
I'll cover for you as much as I
can, even if it means my job.
But I have to know,
does this have anything to do
with what happened at my house?
Does it, Paul?
No.
Does Hal know?
That Coffey's innocent, I mean.
Well, can he help?
Does he have the influence
to do something about this?
Stop the execution?
No.
Then don't tell him.
If it can't help,
don't tell him.
Ever.
I won't.
There's no way out of
this for you, is there?
No.
And I've been thinking
about it, believe me.
I've been running it through
my head any number of ways.
No.
I'll tell you the truth, honey.
I've done some things in my
life that I am not proud of,
but this is the first time I've
ever felt real danger of hell.
Hell?
Oh, Paul.
Talk to him.
Talk to John.
Find out what he wants.
Hello, boss.
Hello, John.
I guess you know
we're coming down to it now.
Another couple of days.
Is there anything special you
wanna eat for dinner that night?
We can rustle you up
most anything.
Meat loaf be nice.
Mashed taters, gravy. Okra.
Maybe some of that fine
corn bread your missus make...
if she don't mind.
Now, uh...
What about a preacher?
Someone to say
a little prayer with.
Don't want no preacher.
You can say a prayer,
if you like.
Me?
Suppose I could,
if it came to that.
John,
I have to ask you
something very important now.
I know what you gonna say.
You don't have to say it.
No, I do. I do.
I have to say it.
John,
tell me what you want me to do.
You want me to
take you out of here?
Just let you run away?
See how far you could get?
Why would you do
such a foolish thing?
On the day of my judgment,
when I stand before God
and he asks me why did I...
did I kill one
of his true miracles,
what am I going to say?
That it was my job?
It's my job.
You tell God the Father
it was a kindness you done.
I know you're
hurting and worrying.
I can feel it on you.
But you ought to quit on it now.
I want it to be
over and done with.
I do.
I'm tired, boss.
I'm tired of being on the road,
lonely as a sparrow in the rain.
I'm tired of never having me
a buddy to be with,
to tell me where we's going
to, coming from, or why.
Mostly, I'm tired of people
being ugly to each other.
I'm tired of all the pain
I feel and hear in the world,
every day.
There's too much of it.
It's like pieces
of glass in my head,
all the time.
Can you understand?
Yes, John, I think I can.
Well, there must be
something we can do for you, John.
There must be
something that you want.
I ain't never seen
me a flicker show.
Why, they's angels.
Angels, just like up in heaven.
it be all right, fellas.
This here's the hard part.
I'll be all right in a while.
John, I should have
this just for now.
I'll give it back after.
You know, I fell asleep this
afternoon and had me a dream.
I dreamed about Del's mouse.
Did you, John?
I dreamed Mr. Jingles got down to
that place Boss Howell talked about.
That Mouseville place.
I dreamed there's kids.
And how they laughed at his tricks.
My!
I dreamed that those two little
blond-headed girls was there.
They's laughing, too.
I put my arms around them
and set 'em on my knees.
And there's no blood
coming out of they hair,
and they's just fine.
We all watched
Mr. Jingles roll that spool.
How we did laugh.
Fit to bust, we was!
John.
They's lots of
folks here that hate me. Lots!
I can feel it.
It's like bees stinging me.
Well, feel how we feel, then.
We don't hate you.
Can you feel that?
Kill him twice, you boys!
You go on and kill that
raping baby killer twice!
That'd be fine!
Wipe your face before
you stand up, Dean.
Yes, sir.
Roll on one.
Does it hurt yet?
I hope it does.
I hope it hurts like hell.
John Coffey,
you've been condemned to die
in the electric chair
by a jury of your peers.
Sentence imposed by a judge in
good standing in this state.
Do you have anything to say
before sentence is carried out?
I'm sorry for what I am.
Please, boss,
don't put that thing
over my face.
Don't put me in the dark.
I's afraid of the dark.
All right, John.
Heaven,
I'm in heaven
Heaven, heaven
Heaven
Heaven, I'm in heaven
I'm in heaven
Heaven
John Coffey,
electricity shall now be passed
through your body
until you are dead
in accordance with state law.
May God have mercy on your soul.
Paul.
You have to say it.
You have to give the order.
He killed 'em
with they love.
That's how it is every day
all over the world.
Roll on two.
It was the last
execution I ever took part in.
I just couldn't do it
anymore after that.
Brutal either.
We both transferred out,
took jobs with
Boys' Correctional.
It was all right.
"Catch them young"
became my motto.
You don't believe me.
I don't imagine
you'd lie to me, Paul.
It's just that...
it's quite a story.
It's quite a story.
One thing I don't understand.
You said you and Jan
had a grown son in 1935.
Is that right?
The math doesn't work, does it?
Do you feel up to taking a walk?
Watch your step.
Now let your eyes adjust.
There.
Hey. Wake up,
old fella. Wake up.
Paul, it isn't. it can't be.
Come over here, boy.
Come on over here
and see this lady.
That can't be Mr. Jingles.
Go on, you can do it.
This isn't exactly the Mouseville
we had in mind, is it?
But we make do.
Don't we, old fella?
I think Mr. Jingles
happened by accident.
I think when we electrocuted
Del, and it all went so badly...
Well, John could
feel that, you know.
And I think a part of
whatever magic was inside of him
just leapt into
my tiny friend here.
As for me,
John had to give me
a part of himself,
a gift, the way he saw it,
so that I could see for myself
what Wild Bill had done.
When John did that,
when he took my hand,
a part of the power
that worked through him
spilled into me.
He what?
He infected you with life?
It's as good a word as any.
He infected us both, didn't he, Mr.
Jingles? With life.
I'm 108 years old, Elaine.
I was 44 the year that John
Coffey walked the Green Mile.
You mustn't blame John.
He couldn't help what happened.
He was...
He's just a force of nature.
Oh, I've lived to see
some amazing things, Ellie.
Another century come to pass.
But I've...
I've had to see my friends and loved
ones die off through the years.
Hal and Melinda,
Brutus Howell,
my wife, my boy.
And you, Elaine.
You'll die, too.
And my curse is knowing
that I'll be there to see it.
It's my atonement, you see.
It's my punishment
for letting John Coffey
ride the lightning,
for killing a miracle of God.
Almighty,
everlasting God,
the source of all
being and life...
You'll be gone like all the others.
I'll have to stay.
Oh, I'll die eventually.
Of that I'm sure.
I have no illusions
of immortality.
But I will have wished for death
long before death finds me.
In truth, I wish for it already.
Mr. Jingles?
Where you been, hmm?
Been worried about you, boy.
You hungry, hmm?
Let's go see if we can't
find you something to eat.
A few crumbs anyway.
I know you'd like that.
Look at you. Mr. Jingles.
I lie in bed most nights
thinking about it.
And I wait.
I think about all
the people I've loved,
now long gone.
I think about my beautiful Jan,
how I lost her
so many years ago.
And I think about all of us
walking our own Green Mile,
each in our own time.
But one thought
more than any other
keeps me awake most nights.
If he could make
a mouse live so long,
how much longer do I have?
We each owe a death.
There are no exceptions.
But, oh, God,
sometimes,
the Green Mile seems so long.