BARRY: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime
and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop
the evil speedster, Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him
murder the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything
in my power to change the future.
And I'm the only one
fast enough to keep her alive.
I am the Flash.
H.R.: Previously on The Flash...
I'm free!
- Who are you?
- I am the future, Flash.
I can't spend
the rest of my life wondering
if I'm gonna become Killer Frost.
I understand the real reason
that you invited me on this team.
You just want
your own meta-human specialist
to try and find you a cure.
That's not the only reason.
I wish I could believe that.
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must be Gypsy.
- You're into me.
- GYPSY: Even if I was...
You couldn't handle me.
I'm marrying that woman.
- Iris West, will you marry me?
- Yes.
GUARD: Looks like we may need
to find a new job.
Heard Stagg Industries
may be getting bought out.
By Who?
Doesn't really matter now, does it?
All I know is,
we got millions of dollars of tech,
like whatever that thing is,
that no one's using.
Then, surely, you gentlemen won't mind
if I abscond with some of it.
This piece, in particular.
How did you get in here?
Believe me,
that's the least impressive of my tricks.
Hands up, pal.
Do it now, or I'll shoot. Stop!
How the hell did he do that?
Maybe you can figure out how I did it,
but I doubt you'll have time.
It's just beautiful. You know what?
- It matches the sparkle in your eyes.
- Thank you.
Barry, your grandfather
had really good taste in jewelry.
- BARRY: Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah, he did.
Okay, so break it down. How did it happen?
Um...
We were at the apartment,
and Barry sang to me,
and then he proposed.
My God, that's so romantic! You sing?
Not as good as Joe.
Shut up, Barry.
Well, okay, that reminds me,
my sister has four tickets
that she can't use, to Hamilton.
- Hamilton?
- On the house.
I thought that maybe we could make it
a double if you guys were interested.
Yeah, we're interested. When?
First weekend of July.
July.
Yeah, does that not work for you guys?
No, that works great. We'll be there.
All of us.
Don't! Don't do this.
Please, I'm begging you, just...
Barry.
You lose, Barry.
No!
Well, everything's the same.
The future has not changed.
All right, well, we have two months
to make sure that it does.
CAITLIN: Okay, well,
we should approach this
the same way
we approach any other problem.
Start with what we know.
Problem can't be solved
if it's not understood.
Therein lies the rub.
I feel like we can't understand
any of this till it actually happens,
just like Savitar's prophecies.
Precisely, and just like
the newspaper headlines.
Well, all bar one.
It's a crime scene. We've got to go.
- Stagg Industries?
- All right.
Julian, before you go,
there was an envelope delivered for you
from the Central City Opera.
Yes, you'd mentioned
that you'd never gone before, so...
Well, I got them for us a while back,
but now...
Just go with whoever you'd like.
Huh.
Looks like things between you and Julian
are a little frosty, huh?
- It's too soon for the cold puns, yeah.
- Yeah.
Thought so.
He still doesn't trust me after I lied
about taking a piece
of the Philosopher's Stone.
You did what you felt you needed to do
to get rid of your powers.
I know that, and you know that, but he...
He'll come around. Watch.
I don't know that he will, Cisco.
Hey, Barr. Anything?
Nothing yet.
How the hell did this thing
get filled with water
and those poor dudes get trapped in here?
Beats me.
There's no water access
in the entire wing.
Instead of sprinklers,
every floor uses a halon gas system
that absorbs all the oxygen
if there's a fire.
What about the security cams?
None of them, either.
Apparently, the Stagg geniuses don't want
- any of their "secrets" to get out.
- Yeah.
Julian, please tell me
you found something.
Nothing yet, Detective.
No fingerprints, no DNA,
just two rather plump-looking corpses.
What about the stolen tech?
Nothing. No one's saying a thing.
Everyone is incredibly
tight-lipped about it.
Of course they are.
Look, I'll make some phone calls, see if
I can pry those lips open, all right?
Okay. I'll keep working on it.
This is the last thing
we need to be dealing with right now.
Yeah, I feel the same way,
but we can't just do nothing.
Iris ain't gonna let us
get away with that.
I know, Joe,
but we're running out of time.
Yeah, that's why you and me
need to solve this case fast.
Yeah.
Sometimes, I wish you hadn't told me
what was gonna happen.
Yeah, I know.
Hold on. What's up?
Looks like we got a robbery in progress
over at Kord Industries.
Great. Thanks. Now Kord Industries.
That's two in one day.
That's two in under 12 hours.
Yeah, I'm gonna make sure
it's the last one.
I don't think that's yours, pal.
Flash.
You didn't think I'd wanna come meet
the newest resident of Iron Heights?
No, I assumed that you'd show.
I just didn't expect you to be so young,
Barry Allen.
Now, how do you know who I am?
I'm from the future.
You don't believe me?
Let's see. 2017. Hmm.
How are things going
with your doomed love, Iris West?
Or your greatest foe, Savitar?
You know Savitar.
I know everything about him
and you.
What the hell?
Gypsy. Still seeking revenge, I see.
I'm gonna get it this time.
We'll see.
No!
He calls himself Abra Kadabra.
CAITLIN: As in "hocus pocus"?
Well, he's certainly got a lot of tricks.
Yeah, we think he has some sort
of nanotechnology built into his body.
Allows him to do some extraordinary feats.
Teleportation, telekinesis, you name it.
And believe me, I have seen it all.
So that card trick he played on Barry,
the water tank at Stagg,
that's all some futuristic tech
that he's masking as magic?
CAITLIN:
Well, it's Arthur C. Clarke's third law.
"Any sufficiently advanced technology is
"indistinguishable from magic."
Before you showed up,
he said he was from the future.
The future?
He is. 64th century.
Great. Another criminal from the future.
Haven't we had our fill of those guys?
Sixty-fourth century.
What exactly are you after him for?
He's at the top
of the collectors' most-wanted list.
Showed up on my Earth a few years back,
did a string of robberies that ended
with a lot of people losing their lives.
Showed up again a couple weeks ago,
looted some tech companies, came here.
To do the same thing? Why?
He must have needed
our Earth's tech for something.
Well, whatever it is,
we can definitely help you figure it out
'cause I don't know about you guys,
but ever since last time you were here,
I've been looking forward
to some Gypsy-Vibe action!
- That's way too much.
- Embarrassing.
Yeah, I just wanna catch him,
so I can bring his ass back to Earth-19
and put him down.
Don't worry. We can help you do that.
We should check and see
if Julian's gotten anything.
I'll go ask him.
In the meantime, we can figure out
where this guy disappeared off to.
- Lend me a hand?
- Stupid.
I know that look.
What is going on
inside that head of yours?
This guy knew what was going on
with you and me, and Savitar.
If he knows something
about Savitar, then...
He might be the key to saving you.
This is the first real lead we've gotten.
But, guys, what about Gypsy?
I mean, if she gets a hold of him,
she's gonna take him back to Earth-19.
We can figure that out later.
Right now, we just need to find him.
I got nothing.
Why can't I find you?
I told you, this guy is smart.
You can't just vibe Kadabra's location.
Whatever he's doing,
it renders him invisible to us.
Okay, well, if we can't vibe him,
then I guess
we'll have to find him another way, right?
What are you doing?
I'm putting some search parameters
into the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
to see if anybody
vibrates at a different frequency
than Earth-1 folk.
Wish we had a satellite
that could do that on my Earth.
Wish I had a bunch of this stuff.
Oh.
I could hook you up, girl.
How about this?
I spend a few days on Earth-19.
I'll set you up
with something state-of-the-art.
You know, the only thing is,
I would need a place to crash, so...
- Cisco...
- Gypsy.
That kiss,
that wasn't "I'll see you around."
That was like,
"That needs to happen again, real soon."
Or did I misread that?
I've been preoccupied.
Is that the only reason?
Great timing!
Looks like David Copperfield's
not too far from us.
He's at one of Mercury Labs'
satellite offices.
- Another tech company?
- The techiest.
Let's grab the speedsters and go.
Man, you just can't help yourself,
can you?
- You brought the whole team this time?
- Mmm-hmm.
ABRA KADABRA: Well, that wasn't
very smart, was it?
Oh. This guy sucks.
I can see
why you wanna bring him down so badly.
Do yourself a favor. Give it up.
There's nowhere for you to go.
You can't out-trick all of us, Kadabra.
Really? I think I just did.
It's a hologram.
Upon further inspection, there was
some rather odd particulate residue
found at Stagg Industries.
Yeah, that's the nanotechnology
that Gypsy was talking about.
But what's it made out of?
Not exactly sure. It's definitely organic,
but it seems to have some sort
of metallic hydrogen properties.
Frankly, it's...
Beyond your understanding.
You make a move, you'll regret it.
Do you know how many times
I've heard that, Detective?
Told you.
Damn it.
Go, go, go!
Guys, move to the side.
Now I can get what I came for.
Everybody okay?
Magic or tech, doesn't matter.
You're not getting out of these.
Maybe not.
You let me go,
I will tell you Savitar's greatest secret.
It's the key to defeating him,
the key to stopping him.
What secret?
I know who he is. I know his name.
Hand him over.
GYPSY: Why'd you lock him up?
I'm taking him right back to my Earth.
Okay, but I need to talk to him first.
Fine. Get what you need from him,
but when you're done, he's mine.
You are gonna die
for all the things you've done.
I cannot wait to see you be put to death.
I'm gonna talk to her.
GYPSY, darling.
You said you knew who Savitar is.
I know everything about the God of Speed.
Hallowed be his name.
Like what?
That he's unstoppable,
that he was the first speedster,
and that you defeat him,
but not until after he takes
what matters the most to you,
Iris West.
Tell us who he is, now.
I don't think so.
It's frustrating, isn't it?
Knowing that you're going to die
unless I give the Flash what he wants.
All that power, all that speed,
and yet you're still too slow.
This isn't a game or a trick.
This is about my daughter's life.
And it's my life
if you hand me over to that collector.
It's simple.
Let me out,
and I'll tell you who Savitar is.
Give me to Gypsy, and Iris dies.
The decision lies with you, Barry.
Guys, we can't let Gypsy take him
before we find out who Savitar is.
No, we cannot.
Then what are we supposed to do?
I don't know.
What is it with you and this guy?
It's like you're hell-bent
on taking him back with you.
He killed a lot of people on Earth-19.
He's killed people here, too.
No one you know or care about.
Did he take somebody from you?
Is that what this is about?
What this is about, Cisco,
is he needs to be brought to justice,
and I am not gonna let anything
or anyone prevent me from doing that.
CAITLIN: You're lucky.
This could've been a lot worse.
I'm fine, really.
"It's merely a flesh wound,"
as the Monty Python boys would say.
Anyway, thanks for patching me up.
Of course.
Listen, I've been trying to find
the right time to say this,
and now seems to be as good a time as any.
I was so focused
on not hurting you as Killer Frost
that I forgot
that I could hurt you as Caitlin Snow,
and, for that, I'm very sorry.
So I understand
if you don't trust me anymore,
but maybe you can find it in your heart
to forgive me?
You're good to go.
Thank you.
We're gonna figure this out, Barry.
I mean, a guy like Kadabra,
he should have no say
whether you live or die.
How do we even know
that he's telling the truth?
I mean, he's done nothing but tricks
since he got here.
I mean, maybe this is one of them.
It's not, Iris.
So, what, you wanna let him go?
I mean, it just feels like our only move.
He's a murderer.
I know he's a murderer, but, I mean,
how many murderers have we put in prison?
How many bad guys have we taken down?
I mean, don't we deserve one win
after everything that we've done?
Life doesn't keep score, Barry.
You should know that better than anyone.
Look, even if Kadabra hadn't shown up,
we'd still be in the same place
we are right now.
But he did, and if he knows
who Savitar is, he's gonna tell us.
- Barry.
- Iris, he can save your life.
No, you can save my life.
Not him.
Trust me, I wanna find out who Savitar is
just as badly as you do,
but I don't wanna let someone
who has caused so much pain
walk free just to save my life.
And, you know, deep down,
I don't think you want that either.
I knew you'd come.
'Cause you're the only person
who's willing to do anything.
What do you want?
To be set free.
Murdering people, stealing smart tech.
You came here for something.
Told you before, Detective,
it is beyond your understanding.
This is about my daughter's life.
It's as simple as that for me.
You tell me who Savitar is,
and I will let you go.
You don't, you're going with Gypsy.
A leap of faith for us both, then.
Open the door.
If you take one step before you tell me,
I will blow you away.
Understood?
But you do not know this guy.
Great timing!
What is that?
No.
Gypsy-
Give me the name.
The name! Now!
Savitar is...
No! What the hell are you doing?
- He was about to tell me who Savitar is.
- Damn it.
Kadabra's on the loose.
He's somewhere in the building.
There we are.
Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Joe, he's headed for the elevator!
We had a deal.
Your freedom for Savitar's identity.
I've altered the terms of our agreement.
It appears that you have as well.
Move!
Caitlin. Caitlin, are you all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Okay. Okay, okay. Easy. Easy.
- Come on.
- Gentle, gentle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The hand-ray X-ray machine,
grab it for us, would you, please?
BARRY: Yeah.
- Here.
- Okay, good. Remove it.
- How bad is it?
- JULIAN: It's bad.
It's bad. There's quite a few pieces
of shrapnel inside you,
and they look deep enough
to pierce your kidney
if they're not removed immediately.
Guys, we have to get her to a hospital.
We can't. They're gonna ID her as a meta.
Yeah, and not just any meta.
Yeah, one that we have a file on
for attacking CCPD.
IRIS: Then what are we going to do?
None of us are doctors,
and she can't operate on herself.
We do have another option.
Well, what is it?
When Caitlin goes meta,
her metabolic rate
offsets cold-tissue destruction.
She can regenerate?
No, we're not gonna take off my necklace.
I don't need a hospital.
All I need is a mirror
and a steady set of hands.
You were a field medic
in the Royal Army, right?
What? No, I've never operated
on anyone before.
That's okay. I'll walk you through it.
Caitlin, you're talking about staying
awake during your own surgery.
I'm putting my life in your hands.
I trust you, Julian.
What the hell were you thinking?
Now is not the time, Gypsy.
You know, you got a really
messed up sense of justice for a cop.
Watch yourself.
I took two oaths in my life.
One, to uphold the law.
The other, to protect my family.
Guess which one takes priority.
That was my prisoner.
He was my prisoner, too,
and you're on my Earth.
He has information
that can save Iris' life,
so I don't give a damn.
It's because of you he's on the loose.
Because of me? No, no, because of you.
You opened that door!
You let him out!
That is on you, Detective!
How much of that did you hear?
I heard enough.
This is my friend.
It's the man's daughter.
I mean, wouldn't you do that
for someone you cared about?
I am doing that, you idiot.
Okay, what does that mean?
For who? Who are you talking about?
I used to have a partner.
Like a partner, or like a "partner"?
Both.
It was a long time ago, Cisco.
It's not like I'm burning a candle
for the guy,
but he did mean something to me.
It's been three years
since Abra Kadabra shot him dead.
I'm sorry.
I have been searching for him ever since,
and he finally showed back up.
Ten minutes ago, I had him dead to rights,
and then your friend messed it all up.
So, yes, I do know what it is like
to care about someone so much
that you break the rules.
That's why I have to find this guy,
no matter what.
And when I do,
he is gonna pay for what he did.
No more delays.
CAITLIN: Ready?
JULIAN: Ready as I'll ever be.
Okay, let's start with
the shrapnel on the surface.
Okie-dokie.
Just let me know
if I do anything wrong, okay?
Yeah.
Okay, that's the first bit. Well done.
Okay.
Is there supposed to be this much blood?
It's normal for the shrapnel
to cavitate and displace tissue,
but if I lose too much blood,
I'll start hemorrhaging.
Okay.
- IRIS: My God.
- Okay.
All right, nearly done. Nearly done.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
Okay, well done. Well done.
That's all the pieces of shrapnel
from the surface gone.
Okay, great.
Now it's time for the hard one.
But you're doing great.
- You got this, okay, Julian?
- Yes.
It's wedged between my kidney
and my inferior vena cava,
and it's surrounded
by some major blood vessels.
If you hit them,
there's a good chance I'll go into shock.
- Shock?
- But it's okay. You've got this.
Okay. All right.
Heart rate's increasing.
JULIAN: Okay, I think I've got it.
Great, pull it out.
I can't, Caitlin. It's stuck.
CAITLIN: Then turn it.
Guys, it's getting up there.
- It might be a tendon in the way.
- What if it's not a tendon?
Then I will rip this necklace off.
No! I would rather die.
Caitlin, this is going to hurt.
Can you please stitch me up
because I think I need to pass out.
Yes, yes. Of course, of course.
Well done, well done.
- She's gonna be all right.
- Thank God.
That really was amazing, Julian.
Seriously. Julian Albert, MD.
I think I know why Abra Kadabra's
been stealing all that tech.
- Why?
- Build a time machine.
He's trying to get back to the future.
Presto.
What is that thing in his hands?
Everything Kadabra's been stealing,
these are the exact components I used
to build Evil Wells' time sphere
two years ago,
but I could never figure out
what he used for a power source.
I think this is it.
So that's what he took
from the time vault, its power source?
Last thing he needs
to return to the 64th century.
Well, we need to find his ass
before he pulls another disappearing act.
If Kadabra's plan is to Marty McFly
himself back to the future...
He's gonna have
to open a temporal wormhole first.
- And when he does...
- We can nail him.
- Mmm-hmm.
- No, he's mine.
I look forward to showing him
the same mercy he showed my partner.
Hey, Gypsy, you can't go after him alone.
Sure, I can.
You want justice
for all those people that he's hurt,
for your partner, right?
Right now, we're trying to prevent
someone we love from getting hurt,
but we can't do that without your help.
I don't trust you guys anymore.
Kadabra's already given
both of us the slip.
If he does it again through time,
I don't think
we get this opportunity back.
Only way we catch him is together.
Guys, Abra Kadabra's
heading south on Ninth.
He opened up a Wormhole.
What do you say?
We can't let him get past us.
We're not gonna do that.
Catch me if you can.
- BARRY: Where's he at?
- He's on State and Main!
CISCO: We're on it!
You shall not pass!
Okay, now he's on Thurlow and Eighth.
We're gonna lose him.
No, we're not.
He's on Seventh, and he's moving fast!
You've got to stop this guy.
Time to go home.
Barr, he opened up another wormhole.
Yes. He did it. He got him.
Thank God.
- So much for your disappearing act.
- No.
By the laws of Earth-19, I hereby collect
you for the crime of mass murder.
Let her take me.
You'll never find out what I know,
and Iris dies.
You've come to see me off.
I'm really touched.
What are we gonna do here?
You're going with her.
I'm not gonna stop her.
Then you'll never find out
what you want to know.
I have nothing to offer you.
No reprieve,
no escape from what you're facing.
You've done some terrible things,
but you are still a man.
You have a family, friends,
people that you care about.
Somewhere inside of you,
there must be a glimmer of light,
of hope.
It's that part of you that I'm asking.
I'm begging.
Help me save her.
Flash.
Begging.
See, here it is. In the future,
you and I have been enemies for years.
There have been others, of course.
There's Thawne, Zoom, DeVoe,
but none of them hurt you like Savitar.
He truly broke you.
I have to be honest.
I was always a little bit jealous.
But now it's like I get to kill her, too.
If you'll excuse me,
I have my execution to attend.
Where does this leave us?
I don't know.
Cisco, I'm...
I'm still here.
Yeah.
Well, I wasn't gonna let you go that easy.
Kadabra?
He's gone. He's gone for good, apparently.
Sorry, my palms are sweaty.
It's quite all right.
Honestly, my stitch work may leave
quite a lot to be desired, so...
It's okay.
I was never much of a two-piece
bathing suit kind of gal anyway.
I cannot believe what you did, Caitlin.
I mean, staying awake
during your own surgery, that's one thing,
but talking my clumsy hands through it,
that's quite the other.
You are immensely brave.
You fought through the pain
like I've never seen anyone before.
You did all the hard work.
Hardly.
You going soft on me, Julian?
Yes.
Absolutely.
I'm so terribly sorry.
That's most clumsy of me.
Some bedside manner you got there.
I'm working on it.
Just rest.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Easy.
Sorry.
I should've been stronger.
You think you should've shot Kadabra?
Dad, I think you showed true strength
by letting him go.
I try to be strong for you guys.
For you, and Wally, and Barry.
Dad, you have been,
and it makes me stronger, too.
When you were a baby, I was terrified
that you might die
in the middle of the night.
I just didn't sleep.
I would just sit in your room
and watch you sleep.
I put my hand on your chest
just to make sure
you were breathing in and out.
I would just sit there praying that
you'd just keep breathing.
That's how I feel right now.
I don't know what I can do to save you.
I know how to save her.
What?
Kadabra, Savitar, Thawne,
you know, they're...
They're always one step ahead of us.
For one reason.
They know what's gonna happen.
So, every move we make,
every trap we try and set,
it's all just history to them.
They're armed with the future.
Well, not anymore.
What does that mean?
If the answers that we need
to stop Savitar and save you
are in the future,
then that's where I need to go.
I'm gonna run to the future.
No more strawberry.
What do you mean,
there's no more strawberry?
I just bought some, like, a week ago.
Yeah, well, I may have eaten some/all.
Cisco.
Do you want me to go out and get you more
strawberry Jell-O? I will get you more.
No, it's fine.
But next time I operate on you,
you're getting bupkis, mister.
Next time you operate on me,
maybe you can fix my broken heart.
I'm sorry it didn't work out
with you and Gypsy.
If two metas from two different universes
with the same vibrational powers
can't make it work,
then what hope is there?
H.R.: There you guys are.
I've been looking all over for...
What are you doing in bed?
- It's a long story, H.R.
- I have a long story.
Yeah, how about you tell us
where you've been?
Her name is Rhonda,
and she's into new positions.
- We had the...
- Okay. My God, stop talking.
You've got to let somebody know next time
you decide to go on a two-day love romp.
Who was worried about me?
He was. I'm touched.
You'll be touched in the face
with a hammer
the next time
you pull something like that.
Guys, stop it. Don't make me laugh,
or I'll bust my stitches.
Is that lime Jell-O?
It's all you, H.R.
Are you serious?
I love the lime.
I love the lime!
You were really worried about him,
weren't you?
Just promise me
that you'll never ever tell him.
Cross my heart and hope to...
Caitlin?
Hey.
Caitlin? Caitlin? Somebody help!
- What happened? What happened?
- I don't know. She just started seizing.
Hold her down. Hold her down!
H.R., grab her legs. Hold her down!
What's happening?
She's not breathing.
We have to get an ambulance
in here right now.
H.R., grab the crash cart.
Cisco, grab the oxygen.
Wheel it over here!
Slow and steady, over her mouth.
Okay, go. Come on, slow and steady.
That's it. That's it.
What's happening?
She may have thrown a blood clot.
I don't know.
H.R.: Julian!
JULIAN: Charge the paddles!
- Give me the paddles!
- Charging, you're good.
Okay, give it here. Give it here. Clear.
All the way. Turn it up to the top.
All the way up.
- Okay, you're ready.
- Clear!
Clear, clear, clear.
Charge... Go.
Go. Keep going.
Come on, Caitlin. Come on!
Just keep going. Just keep going.
Here, take this.
Here we go. She's coming back.
She's coming back.
Yes, she is.
Come on. Please, come on.
Don't stop. Please!
Please don't stop.
Don't...
She's gone.
- Stop! That's not what she wanted!
- I don't care!
I'm not gonna sit here
and watch her die, okay?
Okay?
It's all right, mate. It's okay.
It's okay.
Caitlin?
Caitlin.