Help me! Help me. Help me.
My cake is ready.
Time for the show. Everybody on stage.
Ruby?
Is that you?
Goddamn it.
Ruby?
If that's you, Jupiter,
I got some buckshot for you.
Ya hear me?
I told you, it's over!
I'm out! Ya hear me?
You're on your own now!
I-
I'm sorry,
I can't do this anymore.
Oh.
Huh?
Hello!
Hey!
- Ah! It's hot out here.
- Honey, you ought to stay
in the car out of the wind.
- Well, honey, I have to stretch my legs.
- Where the hell is everybody?
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Get up, jackass.
- Bobby!
Oh. Hey.
- Fill her up and check the fluids, my friend.
- Oh, yeah. Right away, sir.
Hey!
- Beauty, Beast, stop it!
- Ah! Ah! Damn it!
You okay?
Tell me again why we couldn't fly
like normal people? Oh, that's right.
- They wouldn't let your dad drive the plane.
- Doug, relax, please.
It's their silver anniversary,
and they're so happy you came.
- Your parents can't stand me.
- Nope, you're wrong. They love you.
I could have taken them
on a cruise.
Hey, you know what?
Stop. I never ask you for anything, okay?
Just think how happy you'll be when
Catherine comes along on our 25th, huh?
Huh?
Aw, it's okay.
It's not gonna be
in a fucking trailer home.
Don't see too many travelers around here.
Where y'all headed?
- San Diego.
- California?
- Uh-huh.
- Sure didn't take the fastest road.
Oh, no. We absolutely
had to see the desert.
- Didn't we, Bob?
- Absolutely.
There ain't nothin'
to see in the desert.
Really?
Did you hear that, honey?
Yeah.
Don't you know it's illegal
to smoke around a gas pump?
Yeah.
Come here. Come on.
He's a good little piggy.
Little baby piggy.
Hey, Bobby, come over here.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
That's so random.
You two make a perfect pair.
Hey.
You're sweet.
Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't pee there.
What the hell do you care?
Just turn around for a second.
Uh, hello.
Don't you see that?
Geez.
She's so uncomfortable
in this heat. I told you to use cloth diapers.
- Mom, the doctor said these were fine.
- Look at those little cheeks.
- I know, sweetheart.
- Yes, she is. It's okay.
I think she's getting hungry again.
Uh, excuse me. Do you have a phone I can use?
I can't get a signal out here.
No, I don't.
Hey, Bukowski.
Give the cell phone a rest.
Sorry, Bob. Duty calls.
Honey, you've been on the phone
since we left, really.
Well, sweetheart,
I've been gone two days.
I have to make sure that
my store's not burning to the ground.
Oh, God.
Thanks, Brenda.
What the hell, Brenda?
Damn it!
Got it all over my hand.
How far are we from l-88?
- Freaking perv.
- What?
- You're at least five or six hours.
- You hungry, sweetie?
- Why couldn't we
have gone through Santa Fe?
- It's nasty out here.
- Honey, could you put a cork in it for a minute?
- Well, if I do say so myself...
ma'am, your husband here's
quite right.
This is the only southbound road
going to l-88. From there...
you can take the 40 to California,
but it's a long, old drive.
That doesn't bother me a bit.
I like to drive at night.
I used to work the night patrol
for 15 years.
Is that right? You a cop?
- Well, detective.
- Not anymore, thank God.
- I'm starting my own, uh, security firm.
- Uh-huh.
You a cop too, mister?
No. I'm in telecommunications.
I sell cell phones.
- You won't find any customers around here.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- Everything's fine. Oil's okay.
Beauty, come back here!
Hey, buddy.
What do I owe you?
Uh, $46 even.
Oh, hey, Bob, here.
Let me take care of that.
I can still afford the gas, Bukowski.
Keep the change, my friend.
That's not what I meant.
Beauty?
Beauty? Come on, girl.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Beauty!
Beauty, what are you doing?
- Can I help you, miss?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just our dog. She just-
She got out, and she won't stay put.
- Lynn, we're leaving!
- Come on, girl. Let's go.
- Bobby, she keeps getting out.
- It's all right. I got her.
- Okay.
Oh, honey? Honey?
Could you, uh, tell him to take it easy?
- The heat's making me nauseous.
- Let's go!
Do you need something?
No, thanks.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go!
Honey, we're on vacation.
Yeah?
You know, uh...
it's not on the map,
but if you...
take a left at the dirt road,
couple miles from here...
- Uh-huh.
- It'll lead you through the hills.
Probably save you
a couple of hours.
Can't miss it.
Uh, there's an old fence right in front.
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Old fence, dirt road,
two miles.
Mm-hmm.
You have a safe trip.
Thank you.
Dad, I hate your singing.
Guys, no.
- Stop!
- Imagine the first people
to cross this desert.
They didn't know
where they were.
- Yeah, I can, because neither do we.
- Brenda, the road is here.
It exists.
It's got to go somewhere.
Besides, look how beautiful it is.
Look at the light on the rocks.
It's gorgeous.
- This is so fucked!
- Excuse me?
Watch your language, young lady.
I would like
a little backup here.
- This is such bullshit.
- Hey, watch your fucking mouth!
Can we just calm down here?
We're all a little tired, okay?
Yeah, Mom. Didn't you grow up in the '60s?
Why are you so uptight?
Your mom didn't
used to be uptight.
- She was a little hippie chick.
- No.
You should have seen her when she was
your age. She was a little hottie.
- Dad. - Stop that.
Driving through the New Mexico desert
in the middle of summer...
with a broken air conditioner.
Great vacation.
I'm glad you came because
I would have been so fucking bored otherwise.
Yeah. So bored.
Oh. Give up on that, man.
I tried for an hour and a half.
Thing's ancient.
Wiring's medieval.
Needs to be replaced.
There.
It's just the, uh, thermostat.
It's disconnected.
Anyway, at least
we can breathe now.
Hey, I thought you quit smoking.
- Does my sister know?
- Hey, man.
Fuck your sister.
You know, uh, Big Bob'd
get pretty pissed off...
if he found out you were smoking
in his newly renovated '88 Airstream.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, fuck Big Bob too.
Here. Want one?
Go ahead.
Uh-uh.
Your sister would cut my nuts off
if you start smoking.
I think she did that
a long time ago.
I think you're right.
I think we're somewhere
on this blue road.
Mom, we're not on the blue road
or any other road.
The guy said it wasn't
on the map, remember?
Oh, my God!
Jesus! Hang on!
Watch the baby!
Honey? Where's the baby?
- She's right here.
- Is she okay?
- She's fine. She's fine.
- What the hell happened?
- The heat must have caused a blowout.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm just a little scared.
Where's Bobby? Bobby.
Are you all right, honey? Are you okay?
He's all right.
I knew this wasn't going
to be safe for the baby.
- You okay?
- Yeah, we're okay. We're fine.
Son of a bitch!
- Okay, okay, we're all right.
- Oh, my God. The whole trailer.
Come here, guys.
Come here.
- Beauty!
Beast!
We are so fucked.
- Did you find a signal?
- No. Nothing.
Ninety-seven percent nationwide coverage,
and we find ourselves in that three percent.
- Yeah.
- Well, your dad wanted to see the desert.
I hope he's enjoying himself.
Doug, don't start.
- Maybe somebody will need
a rent-a-cop around here.
- Doug!
- What? - Come on.
Every chance the guy gets, he takes me
down a peg. Can't snap back at him?
- Yeah, well, don't stoop to his level.
- It's my fault?
200 degrees out here!
It's everybody's fault.
- Don't listen to him.
- Get off my back.
General, what's the damage?
The axle is broken,
and it's... totaled.
Can we fix it?
What?
No, the frame is twisted to hell.
We can't-
- With what? I mean-
- There she is.
Give me your damn cell phone.
I'm gonna call a tow truck.
No signal. I tried.
- Well, we can use the C.B.
- You can try it, but I doubt
you're gonna get anybody.
The freeway's way the hell on the other side
of those hills. You won't get a signal.
So, what are we gonna do?
Excuse me.
Bob? What are we doing?
We walk.
- We walk?
- Yep. You and me.
We're in the middle of the desert.
We're miles from anywhere.
It's either that, or we sit here
and wait for somebody to drive by.
Have you seen anybody drive by
since we got off the freeway?
I haven't seen anyone drive by since
you decided to take the shortcut.
- Honey. Honey, let's go for a walk. Okay?
- Okay.
There's nothing there,
you shitheads.
There you go. Ah, good boy.
I'm sure this desert is full of rattlesnakes.
Is that locked?
- Bobby, come here.
- I think that's locked.
- Come here.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks, honey.
- You're welcome.
- You know, I saw- Mom?
- What?
- Safety's on, boy.
- Yes, sir.
- I saw a documentary on desert snakes-
- Uh-huh.
On the Discovery Channel-
And there's some species...
if you get bit, you can die
within like 25 minutes.
Really? I'd like to see
how they stack up against this one.
I thought those were gonna
stay locked up, honey.
- I thought you weren't talking to me, honey.
- You're right.
Relax, honey. I'm a licensed professional.
Besides, I'd take my bullets
over your prayers any day.
Well, some things never change.
So, what about, like, uh, scorpions
and coyotes and stuff?
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition.
Hey, Doug. You wanna try?
- Hey, don't point that at me!
- Don't worry, man. The safety's on.
- Hey, Bobby?
- Yeah?
Leave Doug alone. He's a Democrat.
He doesn't believe in guns.
Oh. Come on, Dougy.
Come here. Just one shot.
It makes you feel kind of powerful.
You might like it.
I don't think so, Bobby.
I'd probably just shoot my foot off.
You know, he's right.
He'd probably shoot his foot off.
- Hey, "B." - Hey.
How you holding up?
I am thrilled.
Yeah. This is a total drag.
Yeah, well, you know,
I really don't care what they say.
Next year, I am going
to Cancún with my friends.
Not going on any more
of these little family trips.
Well, we're not gonna have
many more of them, you know?
And if you want to go to Cancún,
you know you're gonna have to get a job.
Oh, yeah. What, you mean
like your job?
Brenda, I help Doug out
at the store, okay?
Oh, yeah.
Honey? Can you bring me my jacket?
I'll be right there, honey.
Bobby!
Fucker!
- Could you get me a Twinkie?
- No!
Aw.
- Just keep walking this direction.
- Yeah, fine.
You find out where the road leads,
and I'll head back the way we came.
- Stay away from me.
- All right.
It's gotta lead somewhere.
Maybe back to the freeway.
- Are you taking a gun too?
- No, honey, I'm not.
I don't need a gun
to find help.
- I don't want this.
- You need the hat.
- It gives me hat head. I don't like it.
- Who cares?
- It's not about fashion.
- All right. Thank you.
Hey, listen. Uh, if you don't find help
within five or six miles, just come back.
All right?
- Here, honey.
- I'm gonna go to the gas station.
You're just never gonna make it back
by sunset is the only problem.
Honey, it's only about eight miles.
I'll borrow the old man's car.
Use his phone, if he's got one. I'll be back
with a tow truck before nightfall.
- Can I go with Doug?
- No. Nope.
You stay here with your mother
and your sisters. Now, hey, uh, Brenda?
Listen up. Your brother is
in charge, all right?
- So don't tease him.
- I think we should pray before you go.
- Oh, Mom!
- Brenda, is it really so much to ask?
- Yes.
- Come on.
Damn it.
We're waiting.
Thank God no one's watching us.
- Bobby.
- Stop it, Bobby.
- Stop. - Thanks.
Please bless us at this time...
and send your guardian angels...
to help us to walk through
this valley in our faith...
this, yeah, with the help
of thy dear Lord.
- Amen. - Amen.
- Okay.
- Bye, Doug. Be careful.
- See you later.
- See you guys in a few hours.
Honey? Keep the hat on, okay?
- Am I wearing it?
- Don't give me that look.
- Do you see it on my head?
- I love you.
I love you too. Bye.
Hi.
Hi, sweetness. Hello.
Who doesn't want
to sleep anymore?
Are you hungry?
Please take your feet
off the table. Honestly.
Just because we're camping
doesn't mean you get to act like a pig.
You know, honey, really...
you shouldn't go
from the breast to the bottle.
At her age, she should
get used to one or the other.
Mom, thanks for the advice,
but she's my baby.
I can't believe that we're stranded
in the middle of nowhere on your anniversary.
- Hmm.
- You know, if we just stayed on the main road...
we'd be in California right now.
What I'd give for a hot shower
and a cold margarita.
- The beach.
- A massage.
- I'll take a real bed.
- Yeah.
- The chronic.
- The what?
Brenda!
What?
The chronic.
It's pot, Mom.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Who smokes pot?
- Yes, exactly.
- Who smokes pot?
- Hey, has anybody seen my red sweatshirt?
You know, the hoodie thing
in the backseat? Brenda?
- Weren't you sleeping on it?
- I haven't touched your smelly sweatshirt, okay?
- Why are the dogs so excited?
- There's probably some
rattlesnakes somewhere around.
- Ew.
You know how Freud would have interpreted
your obsession with rattlesnakes, Mom?
Bobby!
So bad.
- Bobby Carter! Stop that!
- That's gross!
- That's so wrong.
- That was a little gross. I'm sorry.
- I apologize to the entire table.
- Well, thank you.
I'm really glad that
we all came on this trip together.
Ah, well, that makes one of us.
- Where is the, uh, fruit?
- Does anyone need anything?
No.
- Hey. Hey. Brenda!
- Wonderful.
- Are you kidding me? Do you know how long-
- Bobby.
- Bobby? - Sorry.
Bobby, it's dinnertime.
- I'll get him, Mom. Bobby!
- This always happens.
- Bobby, I don't want you going
away from the trailer right now.
Beauty!
Fuck!
What the hell?
Look at that. Huh.
Hello?
Hey, buddy.
Hello!
Hey, uh, I had a bit of a wreck
out on your, uh, shortcut.
Yo!
I grabbed some water, all right?
Uh-
It's dead. Damn it.
Yo, my friend! Hey!
You here?
You home?
Hello?
Weird son of a bitch.
Yeah.
Jupiter!
I got buckshot, ya hear?
Hey, mister.
You don't understand
what's going on here.
Hey!
The kids...
grew up in the mines
like wild animals.
Open the door, slowly!
What kind of place
is that for children?
What kind of a place is that?
Okay. Put the weapon down.
Put it down, easy. Put it down.
I did the best I could.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Daddy.
Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy. Oh, Daddy.
- Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy.
Would you give me that gun, Pluto!
- Give me the gosh darn gun!
- Get on over here!
That's right. Come on.
You oughtn't have a gun.
Brenda?
Brenda!
Hey, I'm here!
I'll be back in a minute!
Bobby!
- Bobby!
Okay, let me just-
Oh, honey, the hair.
It's just-
You know, you really are so lucky
that Brenda found you.
I mean, what if you'd had to spend
the whole night out there in the cold?
Hey, Bobby. Don't worry. Beauty will
come back when she's hungry, okay?
- Did you- Did you try the radio?
- It doesn't work.
But we heard something.
Some sort of breathing.
What breathing?
It was weird.
Right, Mom? I-
I'm sure it was just static.
Mom! It sounded like
a perverted call.
Only Mom would get
an obscene phone call out here.
Bobby! What-
- Honey?
- No, no, no, no! I want you guys to stay here.
What is wrong with him?
What's he doing?
Shit.
Beast! Beast!
- Hey, Bobby.
- Jesus Christ!
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
Stop pointing the gun at me! Please!
- Jesus, Bobby!
- Doug, I'm sorry, man.
It's me! You okay?
- Yeah. - God!
- Didn't mean to startle you, man.
- Yeah, I know. I just-
Look, I found this place out here.
You wouldn't believe it. It's like the Twilight Zone.
- Hey.
- Is that Bob?
- It's Doug. It's okay.
- Ta-da!
Honey! Oh, my God! Thank God you're okay.
I was so worried about you.
- No, I'm fine. Just exhausted. Look.
- Yeah.
Look at all this stuff
I found.
There's a huge crater out there.
People must use it as a dump site.
I've never seen anything like it in my life.
- What are-
- Look at this stuff. It's brand new.
What are we gonna do with
a fishing pole in the desert?
- I thought you went to go find somebody.
- Road dead-ends in five miles.
That's where the crater is.
It's not a shortcut. It's just desert.
- It dead-ends?
- Dead end.
- I knew that old man was full of shit.
- Hope your dad did better.
Maybe we just missed a turn.
- Honey, did you guys cook
any dinner? I'm starving.
- Yeah. Come on inside.
- Great. Thanks. Brenda?
- Yeah?
Do you have that lip balm?
My lips are really dry.
Are you serious? That's gross.
I'm not letting you use my lip balm.
Do you use it
without telling me?
Wait. Bobby. Don't close that door.
We're leaving in a second.
- What?
- Get some rest for Daddy.
You guys aren't gonna wait
till Dad gets back?
No, Bobby, I'm exhausted.
I need to get some sleep.
No, no, no. It's fine.
You'll be more comfortable here.
I'll sleep on the floor, and Mom and Brenda
are gonna be up front.
And you and Lynn can take the back.
We got extra sleeping bags.
Bobby, you got six people sleeping
in a three-person trailer.
It's not comfortable.
It's a little bit weird. Okay?
- Honey, you gonna bring the water?
- Yeah.
- Hey, hey, hey. Doug, Doug. Can I talk to you?
- What's up?
- Baby, you coming?
- I'm almost ready.
- See, uh-
- What's going on?
- Uh, when I-
- Bobby.
- No, no, no, no. It's-
- Bobby, hey.
I'm sure your dad's gonna
be back soon. Okay?
I mean, come on.
He's Big Bob, all right?
I'm sure it's gonna take more than snakes
and scorpions in the night to stop him.
- Okay?
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- Did you get pillows?
They're in the S.U.V.
Hey, hey, listen.
If he's not back by midnight,
we'll both go looking for him. Deal?
- Yeah. Deal.
- Okay.
- Get some rest, man.
- Good night, Bobby.
Good night.
What are you doing?
There's no mosquitoes in the desert.
Honey, there's
mosquitoes everywhere.
Hi.
Beast.
Beast?
- Beast?
Beasty? Come here, boy.
Beast?
Hey. Guys! Guys!
- Oh, good God. What-
- Jesus!
- Bobby.
- What is it, Bobby?
- Guys, something- something
is going on around here, okay?
- What is it?
There-There are, like, people
or something living in those hills.
- People? Bobby.
- No, no, no, no. Doug.
- Doug. Doug. Please.
- Bobby. Bobby, listen to me!
We're in the middle of nowhere, okay?
Nobody lives in those hills.
- Beauty's dead.
- What?
I found her,
and, uh, she was, like-
- It looked like somebody cut her open, you know?
- Cut her open?
Yeah, and I-I didn't want
to say anything...
because I didn't want to scare everyone
and I didn't want to get Mom upset.
But I'm telling you, there is something
going on, okay? And Dad's not even back yet.
Okay. All right. Stay right there.
I'll come check this out.
- We're not alone.
- All right, Lynn.
You stay here,
you lock the car, okay?
Calm down, man. We're gonna check this out.
Now where did you see this?
Now!
It's Bob.
- Wait. We don't know what that is.
- It's Bob!
- We don't know what that is!
- Bob!
Dad? Dad!
Brenda. Watch the baby!
No!
Hey, little birdie.
Get off! Get your mother out of here!
Get your mother out of here!
Doug! Do something!
Move! You gotta be
a man to do that!
I told you to move!
So, move!
Now, get! Get!
Whoo!
What you got under there?
That's it. Give it to me. Whoo! Whoo!
Fuck off!
Come on. Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo.
It's not my Bob!
Come on, Mom. No! Let's go.
No, just come on.
It's not my Bob.
What was that?
Mom, just stay here, okay?
- Help! Help! Help!
Oh, you fat.
Oh. Big, fat...
and juicy.
No. No, please!
Bobby!
Bobby, where you going?
Fucking kill those motherfuckers!
Get back here! Don't do something stupid!
No. No.
Get back to the trailer!
Come on!
Get out the door!
Help! Shoot him! Shoot him!
- Brenda! - Bobby!
Come on, now.
Look at me. Look at me.
That's it. Look at me.
Shit! I'll come back for ya.
Brenda!
Bitch stuck me like a pig!
Are you okay?
No.
Oh, God!
Don't move! Don't move, honey. Don't move.
Okay. Okay. All right.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay. S-Sweetheart?
Okay.
Honey? Sweetheart?
Lynn, come on!
Lynn!
Come on!
Oh!
Hmm.
Okay.
What are we gonna do? Huh?
What are we-
What are we gonna do
if they come back, Doug?
This trailer is so small.
I clean and clean.
- It's still a mess.
- Shh.
It's a mess.
- Is Big Bob home?
- Not yet.
Every- Everybody went to bed?
- Yes? - Yeah.
Brenda's right here,
and Bobby's in the back.
Is Lynny sleeping? Hmm?
You need anything?
- A blanket.
- Okay.
- It's cold.
- Shh. Shh. Nice and warm, huh? Nice and warm.
You're so sweet, Doug.
I understand why Lynny
loves you so much.
So-
I'm not gonna take this shit.
- Hey, we're not going anywhere!
You wanna die too?
- I don't fucking care!
You wanna die, huh?
Look what they did to your mother!
Look what they did to your sister!
Huh? You stop and think!
You're not a fucking child anymore!
You won't make it three feet out there.
We need a plan.
We need to think.
- We need-We need to think.
- Think about what?
Think about what, Doug?
They have Catherine!
They have your daughter.
And you're just gonna sit here and do nothing?
That's 'cause you're a fucking pussy
just like my dad said!
- Shut the fuck up! You shut up! Shut your mouth!
- Fuck you.
No! Turn the lights on.
Turn the lights on.
- He said he's coming back!
- Shh! Quiet!
He said he's coming back
for me. Please.
It's them! It's them!
It's them!
Goggle? Goggle?
Goggle? You copy, Goggle?
Where's Goggle?
He stayed back there.
He's keeping an eye on them.
- I told you.
- What?
I told you,
you've gotta kill them all!
Beast! Beast! You're alive!
Oh, good boy.
Good boy. Good boy.
- Good boy.
- Oh, my God.
Jupiter's going to finish them off.
Why are you doing this to us?
Why are you doing this?
You hear me?
Give me back my baby!
What the fuck
do you want from us?
What do you want?
You give me back my little girl.
You hear me?
- Bobby?
- Hmm?
How many bullets
do you have left?
A clip and a half.
What are we doing?
Which way, Beast? Which way?
Come on. Follow the trail.
Come on, big guy.
I hope you're not afraid of the dark.
Where are they, boy?
Which way, Beast?
Good boy.
Bobby?
Bobby, I followed the blood trail.
It leads to a town or something
out here. Bobby?
Who knows?
Maybe someone heard our calls.
Nobody's gonna hear
the fucking calls, Brenda!
Nobody's gonna see the goddamn smoke
in this goddamn desert!
We're in the middle of freakin'-
Ah, shit!
- God!
I'm sorry.
I'm so scared.
Who are these people?
Good dog. Stay.
- Did you push her?
- Yes.
- Did you destroy the furniture?
- No.
Did you call her
trailer park trash?
- So, now, you're saying you still-
- I'm still in love with her.
Okay, but-So, you said
you treasured the marriage...
and you wanted to end it
two weeks after you got into it?
I wanted to end it
because I have-
I had a feeling that things
weren't gonna work together.
She wasn't working as a team player
with me, and I tried coaching her-
- What were you doing coaching her?
- Well, I tried to show-
- Is she your child?
- No, she's not my child, but she-
Shh, shh, shh.
She wanted me
to eat dinner-spaghetti-
and I wanted to do it
before it got cold.
Watch her head, Bobby.
Come on.
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
Answer me!
I don't know where she is.
I never leave this place.
Your people asked our families...
to leave their town...
and you destroyed our homes.
We went into the mines.
You set off your bombs...
and turned everything to ashes.
You made us what we've become.
Boom. Boom. Boom!
Where's my baby?
What's so funny?
It's breakfast time!
Please don't kill me.
"Please don't kill me."
- Please don't kill me.
- "Please don't kill me."
Lizard.
Kill the baby.
Baby. Baby.
Get out of the way, Ruby.
I said get. Now, get!
Mister, would you play with us?
Ruby!
Catherine!
It's okay.
We'll be all right.
No. No.
- Come on. Come on.
- No!
- Come on, Brenda.
- Bobby!
Stay with me. Stay with me.
Stay with me.
Come on. Come on.
It's gonna be all right.
It'll be all right.
Careful. Please? Please?
Oh, shit.
Come on out,
you motherfucker.
Look. Look. It's just a tumbleweed.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go back
to the trailer. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- She's gone.
She's fucking gone! She's gone!
Brenda! Brenda! Go get the trailer ready.
- Brenda, go get the-
- Where's Mom?
- Go get the trailer ready. Okay?
- Listen to me. I need you to go get the trailer.
Just go in,
do what we talked about.
Let's go! Get the window!
Get the window!
It's stuck!
Bob! Help me! Bob!
Go! Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get out!
Here.
Ruby!
Ruby! Come back here!
You little bitch!
Give me that baby!
Fuck!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Oh, my God.
Look! Bobby!