1
00:00:09,100 --> 00:00:10,420
Now! I know what you're thinking 

2
00:00:12,128 --> 00:00:13,200
How did this happen?

3
00:00:16,023 --> 00:00:17,630
Well... it's a long story

5
00:00:34,120 --> 00:00:36,500
Asgard is dead

6
00:00:43,023 --> 00:00:44,500
Hi, there!!!

7
00:00:56,231 --> 00:00:58,600
What have you brought today, Tell me 

8
00:00:58,800 --> 00:00:59,800
A Contender ...

10
00:01:08,200 --> 00:01:11,480
Its main event time

11
00:01:32,020 --> 00:01:33,180
Yess

12
00:01:35,800 --> 00:01:37,900
We know each other 

13
00:01:38,023 --> 00:01:39,500
he's a friend from work

14
00:01:40,600 --> 00:01:41,800
Come On!!!

15
00:01:45,230 --> 00:01:50,450
mmtv95