(MUSIC PLAYING)
THOR: Now, I know
what you're thinking.
"Oh, no! Thor's in a cage.
How did this happen?"
Well, sometimes
you have to get captured
just to get a straight answer
out of somebody.
It's a long story,
but basically,
I'm a bit of a hero.
See, I spent some time
on Earth...
fought some robots,
saved the planet
a couple of times.
Then I went searching
through the cosmos
for some magic, colorful
Infinity Stone things.
Didn't find any.
That's when I came across
a path of death
and destruction...
which led me all the way here
into this cage...
where I met you.
Hmm.
How much longer do you think
we'll be here?
(CHAIN RATTLING)
(GRUNTS)
(SURTUR CHUCKLING)
Thor, son of Odin.
Surtur, son of a bitch.
You're still alive.
I thought my father killed you
a half a million years ago.
I cannot die.
Not until
I fulfill my destiny...
and lay waste to your home.
It's funny
you should mention that.
Because I've been having these
terrible dreams of late.
Asgard up in flames,
falling to ruins.
And you, Surtur,
are at the center
of all of them.
Then you have seen Ragnarok,
the fall of Asgard.
-The great prophecy...
-Hang on.
-(CHAIN CREAKING)
I'll be back around shortly.
I really feel like we were
connecting there.
(GRUNTS)
Okay, so Ragnarok.
Tell me about that.
Walk me through it.
My time has come.
When my crown is reunited
with the Eternal Flame...
I shall be restored
to my full might.
I will tower
over the mountains...
and bury my sword
deep in Asgard's...
THOR: Oh, hang on.
Give it a second.
I swear I'm not even moving.
It's just doing this
on its own.
-I'm really sorry.
-(SIGHS)
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
You're going to put your crown
into the Eternal Flame...
and then you'll suddenly grow
as big as a house?
A mountain!
The Eternal Flame that Odin
keeps locked away on Asgard?
Odin is not on Asgard.
And your absence has left
the throne defenseless.
Okay, so where is it?
This crown?
This is my crown,
the source of my power.
Oh, that's a crown.
I thought it was
a big eyebrow.
It's a crown.
Anyway, it sounds like all I
have to do to stop Ragnarok...
is rip that thing
off your head.
(LAUGHS) But Ragnarok
has already begun.
You cannot stop it.
(METAL SCRAPING)
I am Asgard's doom,
and so are you.
All will suffer,
all will burn.
Oh, that's intense.
To be honest,
seeing you grow really big...
and set fire to a planet
would be quite the spectacle.
But it looks like I'm gonna
have to choose option B...
where I bust
out of these chains...
knock that tiara
off your head,
and stash it away
in Asgard's vault.
You cannot stop Ragnarok.
Why fight it?
Because that's what heroes do.
(THOR SIGHS) Hmm.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I didn't time that right.
-(DISTANT THUDDING)
-Hmm?
And, now!
(GRUNTS)
(IMMIGRANT SONG BY LED ZEPPELIN PLAYING)
You have made
a grave mistake, Odinson.
I make grave mistakes
all the time.
(GROWLING)
Everything seems to work out.
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(CREATURES ROARING)
(ROARS)
(YELLING)
(SURTUR LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
Huh?
(CREATURES SNARLING)
Heimdall, I know
it's been a while,
but I could really use
a fast exit.
Heimdall?
SKURGE: Heimdall was an idiot.
This job should have
made him rich.
Now, the job ain't easy...
but it does have its benefits.
The Bifrost gives me
access to everything
the Nine Realms has to offer.
I mean it's all mine
for the taking.
Behold...
my stuff.
Ooh.
I'm particularly fond
of these.
I pulled them out of a place
on Midgard called Texas.
I even named them.
Des and Troy.
You see,
when you put them together...
they destroy.
(ROARING)
Heimdall, come on.
(RUMBLING)
(ROARING)
Stay!
Heimdall?
I'm running short on options.
-Heimdall?
-(RATTLING)
Um... Skurge?
(RATTLING)
Is that important?
SKURGE: You girls
are in for a treat.
(ROARING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(SQUEAKING)
(CREATURE EXHALES)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Girls!
Well, well, well.
Look who decided to pop in.
Thanks for scaring away
my company
and drenching my workplace
in brains.
Who are you?
Don't you remember?
I'm Skurge.
We fought together
on Vanaheim.
Right. Where is Heimdall?
That traitor. No one knows.
He's a fugitive of the throne.
Traitor?
Yeah. Well, you see,
Odin charged Heimdall
with negligence of duty...
but he disappeared
before the trial.
Hard to catch a guy
who can see
everything in the universe.
Sure.
Hold on. I'm supposed
to announce your arrival.
(WHOOSHES)
(SIGHS)
(ALL GASP)
What the hell is that?
(CHOIR VOCALIZING)
MAN 1: Oh, brother.
This is it.
I take my leave.
MAN 2: You fool,
you didn't listen!
MAN 1: I'm sorry.
Lady Sif, get help!
Somebody, help!
MAN 1: Sorry
for all I've done.
Shh. It's all right. Hold on.
I'm sorry
I tried to rule Earth.
They'd be lucky to have you.
I'm sorry about that thing
with the Tesseract.
-I just couldn't help myself.
-I know.
I'm a trickster.
So mischievous.
Sorry about that time
I turned you into a frog.
It was a wonderful joke.
'Twas indeed hilarious.
(CHUCKLES)
MAN 2: You are the savior
of Asgard.
-Tell my story.
-I will.
Build a statue for me.
We will build
a big statue for you.
With my helmet on,
with the big bendy horns.
I will tell Father
what you did here today.
I didn't do it for him.
(GROANS)
(VOCALIZING)
No!
(SOBBING)
And so,
Loki died of his wounds...
giving his life for ours.
He fought back
those disgusting elves...
he brought peace to the realm.
Loki, my boy...
'twas many moons ago
I found you
on that
frostbitten battlefield.
On that day,
I did not yet see in you...
Asgard's savior. No.
You were merely
a little blue baby icicle...
that melted
this old fool's heart.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING)
Bravo! Bravo!
Well done. Bravo.
Father.
Oh, shit.
Uh, my son, Thor,
has returned!
-Greetings, my boy.
-(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
It's an interesting play.
What's it called?
The Tragedy of Loki of Asgard.
The people wanted
to commemorate him.
THOR: Ah, indeed they should.
I like the statue.
A lot better looking than he
was when he was alive, though.
A little less weaselly,
less greasy, maybe.
Do you know what this is?
The skull of Surtur.
That's a formidable weapon!
Do me a favor.
Lock this away in a vault...
so it doesn't turn
into a giant monster
and destroy the whole planet.
Thank you, dear. Um...
So it's back to Midgard
for you, is it?
Nope.
I've been having this
reoccurring dream lately.
Every night,
I see Asgard fall into ruins.
ODIN: That's just
a silly dream...
signs of an overactive
imagination.
THOR: Possibly.
But then I decide to go
out there and investigate.
And what do I find,
but the Nine Realms
completely in chaos.
Enemies of Asgard assembling,
plotting our demise...
all while you, Odin,
the protector
of those Nine Realms...
are sitting here
in your bathrobe,
eating grapes.
Yes, it is best to respect
our neighbors' freedom.
Yes, of course,
the freedom to be massacred.
Yes, besides I've been
rather busy myself.
Watching theater.
Board meetings, and security
council meetings...
You're really gonna
make me do it?
Do what?
(ALL GASP)
You know that
nothing will stop Mjolnir
as it returns to my hand.
Not even your face.
You've gone quite mad.
You'll be executed for this.
Then I'll see you
on the other side, brother.
All right, I yield.
(ALL GASP)
Behold!
Thor...
-Odinson.
-No.
You had one job. Just the one.
Where's Odin?
You just couldn't stay away,
could you?
Everything was fine
without you.
Asgard was prospering.
You've ruined everything.
-Ask them.
-Where's Father?
-Did you kill him?
-You had what you wanted.
You had the independence
you asked for.
(GRUNTS) Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay. I know exactly
where he is.
(SIRENS BLARING IN DISTANCE)
I swear I left him right here.
THOR: Right here
on the sidewalk,
or right there where the
building is being demolished?
Great planning.
How was I supposed to know?
Can't see into the future.
I'm not a witch.
No? Then why do you dress
like one?
-Hey.
-I can't believe you're alive.
I saw you die.
I mourned you,
I cried for you.
I'm honored.
GIRL: Ask him.
Hi. Would you mind taking
a picture with us?
-Oh, sure.
-(GIRLS GIGGLING)
Start figuring out
where he is.
-(CAMERA CLICKS)
-GIRL: Oh, my God.
Sorry to hear
that Jane dumped you.
She didn't dump me, you know.
I dumped her.
It was a mutual dumping.
What's this?
What are you doing?
This isn't me.
(YELPS)
THOR: (WHISPERS) Loki.
(HORN HONKS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Thor Odinson.
God of Thunder.
You can put down the umbrella.
(THUDS)
So, Earth has, uh,
wizards now?
-(CHUCKLING)
-(CLATTERING)
The preferred term is
"Master of the Mystic Arts."
You can leave that now.
All right, wizard.
Who are you?
Why should I care?
My name
is Doctor Stephen Strange,
and I have some questions
for you.
Take a seat.
Tea?
I don't drink tea.
What do you drink?
Not tea.
So, I keep a watch list
of individuals and beings
from other realms...
that may be a threat
to this world.
Your adopted brother, Loki,
is one of those beings.
He's a worthy inclusion. Hmm.
Then why bring him here?
We're looking for my father.
So, if I were to tell you
where Odin was...
all parties concerned would
promptly return to Asgard?
Promptly.
Great! Then I'll help you.
If you knew where he was,
why didn't you call me?
I have to tell you,
he was adamant
that he not be disturbed.
Your father said he had chosen
to remain in exile.
-Hmm.
-And you don't have a phone.
No, I don't have a phone...
but you could have sent
an electronic letter.
It's called an email.
-Yeah, do you have a computer?
-No. What for?
-Uh-huh.
-Anyway,
my father
is no longer in exile.
So if you could
tell me where he is,
I can take him home.
Gladly. He's in Norway.
I'm just seeing
whether this incantation
requires any Asgardian
modifications.
Nope.
Oh, we don't need that.
(SIGHS)
Will you stop doing that?
(STAMMERS)
I need just one strand
of your hair.
Let me explain something.
My hair is not to be
meddled with. (WINCES)
We could have just walked.
He's waiting for you.
All right.
Don't forget your umbrella.
Oh, yes.
(DISTANT CRASHING)
(CRASHING CONTINUES)
Sorry.
There we go.
I suppose I'll need
my brother back.
Oh, yeah. Right.
(LOKI SCREAMING)
(LOKI GRUNTING)
I have been falling
for 30 minutes!
You can handle him from here.
Yes. Of course.
Thank you very much
for your help.
Good luck.
Handle me? Who are you?
Loki.
LOKI: You think you're
some kind of sorcerer?
Don't think for one minute,
you second-rate...
Bye-bye.
(LOKI GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Father?
Look at this place.
It's beautiful.
Father, it's us.
My sons.
I've been waiting for you.
I know. We've come
to take you home.
Home, yes.
Your mother, she calls me.
Do you hear it?
Loki, lift your magic.
(CHUCKLES)
Took me quite a while
to break free from your spell.
Frigga would have been proud.
Come and sit with me.
I don't have much time.
(ODIN SIGHS)
I know that we failed you.
But we can make this right.
I failed you.
It is upon us. Ragnarok.
No, I've stopped Ragnarok.
I put an end to Surtur.
No.
It has already begun.
She's coming.
My life was all that
held her back.
But my time has come.
I cannot keep her away
any longer.
Father, who are you
talking about?
Goddess of Death. Hela.
My firstborn.
Your sister.
Your what?
Her violent appetites
grew beyond my control.
I couldn't stop her,
so I imprisoned her.
Locked her away.
She draws her strength
from Asgard...
and once she gets there,
her powers will be limitless.
Whatever she is,
we can stop her together.
We can face her together.
No, we won't.
I'm on a different path now.
This you must face alone.
I love you, my sons.
Look at that.
Remember this place.
Home.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
Brother.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
This was your doing.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
So he's gone.
That's a shame. I would've
liked to have seen that.
You must be Hela.
I'm Thor, son of Odin.
Really?
You don't look like him.
Perhaps we can come
to an arrangement.
You sound like him.
Kneel.
Beg your pardon?
Before your queen.
I don't think so.
(GRUNTS)
(VIBRATING)
It's not possible.
Darling, you have no idea
what's possible.
(BOTH GROANING)
(BOTH PANTING)
Bring us back!
No!
Loki!
(LOKI SCREAMING)
(THOR GRUNTS)
Who are you?
What have you done with Thor?
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
I'm Hela.
I'm just a janitor.
You look like a smart boy
with good survival instincts.
How would you like a job?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(DISTANT THUDDING)
(THUNDER CRACKS)
(ALARM BLARING)
Are you a fighter?
Or are you food?
I'm just passing through.
It is food.
On your knees.
(COCKS GUN)
-(SCRAPPER SCREAMS)
-(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(ALL EXCLAIM)
-(GLASS SHATTERS)
-He's mine.
Wait!
(SQUELCHES)
He's mine.
So if you want him,
you go through me.
But we've already got him.
All right, then.
I guess I go through you.
-(COCKS GUN)
-More food.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(POWERING UP)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCRAPPER SCREAMS)
-(DISTANT CRASH)
-Thank you.
(GROANS)
Scrapper 142. I need clearance
and an audience with the boss.
I've got something special.
Hey! Where are you taking me?
Answer me!
Hey!
I am Thor, son of Odin.
I need to get back to Asgard.
-Many apologies, your majesty.
-(DEVICE BEEPING)
(GROANING)
It's come to my attention
that you don't know who I am.
I am Hela,
Odin's firstborn...
the commander
of the Legions of Asgard...
the rightful heir
to the throne,
and the Goddess of Death.
My father is dead.
As are the princes.
You're welcome.
We were once the seat
of absolute power
in the cosmos.
Our supremacy
was unchallenged.
Yet Odin stopped
at Nine Realms.
Our destiny is to rule over
all others.
And I am here
to restore that power.
Kneel before me...
and rise into the ranks
of my great conquest.
Whoever you are...
whatever you've done,
surrender now!
Or we will show you no mercy.
Whoever I am?
Did you listen
to a word I said?
This is your last warning!
I thought you'd be happy
to see me.
(SIGHS)
Fine.
(GRUNTING)
SOLDIER: Charge!
(ALL YELLING)
(MEN GROANING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(BONES CRUNCHING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, I've missed this.
Still, it's a shame.
Good soldiers dying
for nothing...
all because
they couldn't see the future.
Sad.
-(HOGUN GROANING)
-Oh, look, still alive.
(GROANING)
Change of heart?
Go back to whatever cave
you crept out of.
You evil demoness!
(GROANS)
HELA: Let's go see my palace.
(DOOR OPENS)
(MACHINERY POWERING UP)
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
Fear not, for you are found.
You are home,
and there is no going back.
(STRAINS)
No one leaves this place.
But what is this place?
The answer is Sakaar.
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
Surrounded
by cosmic gateways...
Sakaar lives on the edge
of the known and unknown.
It is the collection point
for all lost
and unloved things...
like you.
But here on Sakaar,
you are significant.
You are valuable.
Here you are loved.
What the hell?
And no one loves you more
than the Grandmaster.
He is the original,
the first lost
and the first found...
the creator of Sakaar...
and father
of the Contest of Champions.
Where once you were nothing,
now you are something.
You are the property
of the Grandmaster.
Congratulations!
You will meet the Grandmaster
in 5 seconds.
Prepare yourself.
You are now meeting
the Grandmaster.
(SCREAMING)
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
(STRAINING)
He's wonderful.
It is a he?
It is a he.
Yeah.
I love when you come
to visit, 142.
You bring me the best stuff.
Whenever we get
to talking, Topaz,
about Scrapper 142...
what do I always say?
"She is the..."
And it starts with a "B."
Trash.
No, not trash.
Were you waiting
just to call her that?
It doesn't start with a "B."
Booze hag.
Uh, I'm so sorry. No, "best."
I was thinking about "best."
'Cause I always say
you're the best.
She brought me my beloved
champion, you know.
You say that every time
she's here.
What have you brought today?
Tell me.
A contender.
A what?
I need to go closer.
I want a closer look at this.
Can you take us closer?
Thank you.
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
Pay this lady.
Just wait a damn minute.
(STRAINING) I'm not for sale.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLES)
Man, he's a fighter.
I take 10 million.
Tell her she's dreaming.
Oh, for heaven's sakes,
transfer the units.
(DEVICE BEEPS)
(WEAKLY) You'll pay for this.
No, I got paid for this.
-Here's what I wanna know.
-(DEVICE BEEPS)
Who are you?
I am the God of Thunder.
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
-Wow.
I didn't hear any thunder,
but out of your fingers,
was that sparkles?
We've located your cousin.
Uh, oh, good!
Yeah, come on. I think
you're gonna like this.
There he is.
Hey, cuz.
We almost couldn't find you.
What, you been hiding?
Hi.
-(GROANS)
-GRANDMASTER: Hmm.
So...
Please.
(GROANS) I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Carlo...
I pardon you.
(SIGHS) Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
You're officially pardoned.
From life.
-(SCREAMING)
-(SIZZLING)
(GROANS) Help me.
Oh, my God!
I'm stepping in it.
I'm stepping in it. Look!
Wow.
Oh, the smell.
What does it smell like?
-Burnt toast.
-(CHUCKLES)
What happened to my manners?
I haven't
properly introduced myself.
Come on. Uh, follow me.
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
-My name is Grandmaster.
I preside over
a little harlequinade
called
the Contest of Champions.
People come from far and wide
to unwillingly
participate in it.
And you, my friend,
might just be part
of the new cast.
What do you say to that?
We're not friends and I don't
give a shit about your games.
I'm going back to Asgard.
-Ass-gard.
-(MUSIC CONTINUES)
One, two, three, four.
LOKI: There was a wormhole
in space and time beneath me.
At that moment,
I let go. (LAUGHS)
Loki?
Loki! Loki!
-Over here. Over here.
-(LAUGHING)
-Excuse me one second.
-Loki!
-(SHUSHING)
-(BOTH WHISPERING)
-What?
-You're alive?
-Yes, of course I'm alive.
-What are you doing here?
What do you mean,
what am I doing?
I'm stuck
in this stupid chair.
-Where's your chair?
-I didn't get a chair.
-Get me out of this one.
-I can't.
-Get me out. What?
I've made friends
with this man.
He's called the Grandmaster.
-Oh, he's crazy!
-I've gained his favor.
The Bifrost brought me
out here weeks ago.
-Weeks ago?
-Yes.
I just got here.
(WHISPERS) What are you
whispering about?
(YELPS)
Time works real different
around these parts.
On any other world, I'd be,
like, millions of years old.
But here on Sakaar...
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
In any case,
you know this, uh...
You call yourself
Lord of Thunder?
God of Thunder.
Tell him.
I've never met this man
in my life.
-He's my brother.
-Adopted.
Is he any kind of a fighter?
(LAUGHS) You take this thing
out of my neck
and I'll show you.
Now, listen to that.
He's threatening me.
Hey, Sparkles,
here's the deal.
If you wanna get back
to Ass-place, Assberg...
Asgard.
Any contender who defeats
my champion...
their freedom they shall win.
Fine. Then point me
in the direction
of whoever's ass
I have to kick!
That's what I call, contender.
Direction would be
this way, Lord.
Ah! Loki!
(GRUNTING)
Hey, hey, hey.
Take it easy, man.
-(PANTING)
-Over here.
The pile of rocks
waving at you. Here.
Yeah, I'm actually a thing.
I'm a being.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Korg.
I'm kind of like
the leader in here.
I'm made of rocks,
as you can see.
But don't let that
intimidate you.
You don't need to be afraid
unless you're
made of scissors. (CHUCKLES)
Just a little
rock-paper-scissor
joke for you.
This is my very good friend
over here, Miek.
He's an insect
and has knives for hands.
You're a Kronan, aren't you?
-That I am.
-How'd you end up in here?
Ah, well, I tried to start
a revolution,
but didn't print
enough pamphlets.
So hardly anyone turned up,
except for my mum
and her boyfriend, who I hate.
As punishment, I was forced
to be in here
and become a gladiator.
Bit of a promotional disaster,
that one.
But I'm actually organizing
another revolution.
I don't know
if you'd be interested
in something like that.
Do you reckon
you'd be interested?
How did you...
Ah, yeah, no.
This whole thing is a circle.
But not a real circle,
more like a freaky circle.
This doesn't make any sense.
No, nothing makes sense
here, man.
The only thing
that does make sense
is that nothing makes sense.
Has anyone here fought
the Grandmaster's champion?
Doug has.
Doug!
Our luck, Doug's dead.
That's right.
Everyone who fights
the Grandmaster's champion
perishes.
What about you?
You're made of rocks.
Perishable rock. There you go.
Another one gone.
Yeah, no, I just do
the smaller fights,
warm up the crowd and whatnot.
Wait. You're not gonna
face him, are you?
Yes, I am.
Gonna fight him, win,
and get the hell out
of this place.
That's exactly
what Doug used to say.
See you later, new Doug.
Does no one remember me?
Has no one been taught
our history?
Look at these lies.
Goblets and garden parties?
Peace treaties?
Odin...
proud to have it...
ashamed of how he got it.
(GRUNTING)
We were unstoppable.
I was his weapon
in the conquest
that built Asgard's empire.
One by one,
the realms became ours.
But then, simply because
my ambition outgrew his...
he banished me, caged me,
locked me away like an animal.
Before that, Asgard's warriors
were honored...
their bodies buried as heroes
beneath this very palace.
-Odin's treasures.
-Fake.
(CLATTERS)
Most of the stuff in here
is fake.
Or weak.
Smaller than I thought
it would be.
That's not bad.
(GASPS) But this...
The Eternal Flame.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Want to see what true power
really looks like?
(THUDS)
Fenris, my darling,
what have they done to you?
With the Eternal Flame,
you are reborn.
(GROWLING)
I've missed you.
I've missed you all.
THOR: Odin...
I bid you take your place
in the halls of Valhalla...
where the brave
shall live forever.
Nor shall we mourn
but rejoice...
for those that have died...
THOR AND LOKI:
...the glorious death.
Hurts, doesn't it?
Being lied to.
Being told you're one thing
and then learning
it's all a fiction.
You didn't think I'd really
come and see you, did you?
This place is disgusting.
(ROCK CLATTERS)
Does this mean
you don't want my help?
Look, I couldn't jeopardize my
position with the Grandmaster.
It took me time
to win his trust.
He's a lunatic,
but he can be amenable.
What I'm telling you is,
you could join me
at the Grandmaster's side.
Perhaps, in time,
an accident befalls
the Grandmaster, and then...
(MOUTHING WORDS)
(ROCK CLATTERS)
You're not seriously thinking
of going back, are you?
Our sister destroyed
your hammer
like a piece of glass.
She's stronger than both of
us. She's stronger than you.
You don't stand a chance.
Do you understand
what I'm saying to you?
(SCOFFS)
Fine.
I guess
I'll just have to go it alone.
Like I've always done.
Would you say something?
Say something!
What would you like me to say?
You faked your own death...
you stole the throne,
stripped Odin of his power...
stranded him on Earth to die,
releasing
the Goddess of Death.
Have I said enough or would
you like me to go back
further than the past
two days?
You know, I haven't seen this
beloved champion
he talks of...
but I've heard
he is astonishingly savage.
I've placed a large wager
against you tomorrow.
Don't let me down.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
KORG: Piss off, ghost!
He's freaking gone.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
KORG: Oh, yuck!
There's still someone's hair
and blood all over this.
Guys, can you clean up
the weapons
once you finish your fight?
Disgusting slobs.
Oh, Thor...
wanna use a big wooden fork?
No.
Yeah, not really useful.
Unless you're fighting off
three vampires
that were huddled together.
I really wish I had my hammer.
Hammer?
Quite unique.
It was made from this
special metal from the heart
of a dying star.
And when I spun it really,
really fast,
it gave me the ability to fly.
You rode a hammer?
No, I didn't ride the hammer.
The hammer rode you
on your back?
No. I used to spin it
really fast,
and it would pull me
off the...
Oh, my God.
A hammer pulled you off?
The ground. It would pull me
off the ground,
up into the air,
and I would fly.
Every time I threw it,
it would always
come back to me.
Sounds like you had
a pretty special
and intimate relationship
with this hammer...
and that losing it
was almost comparable
to losing a loved one.
That's a nice way
of putting it.
I said they're mine.
See her, that's the one
that put me in here.
Oh, yeah. Scrapper 142.
Gotta watch out
for those Asgardians, man.
They are hard to perish.
Asgardian?
Hey.
Do not zap me with that thing.
I just wanna talk.
Asgard is in danger.
My God, you're a Valkyrie.
I used to wanna be a Valkyrie
when I was younger...
until I found out that
you were all women.
There's nothing wrong
with women, of course.
I love women.
Sometimes a little too much.
Not in a creepy way,
just more
of a respectful appreciation.
I think it's great
that there is
an elite force
of women warriors.
It's about time.
Are you done?
WARDEN: Lord of Thunder,
you're up.
Please, help me.
I need your help.
Bye.
Fine, then you must be
a traitor or a coward.
Because the Valkyrie is sworn
to protect the throne.
Listen closely, your majesty.
This is Sakaar, not Asgard.
And I'm a Scrapper,
not a Valkyrie.
-(DEVICE BEEPS)
-(GROANING)
Bring him in for processing.
And no one escapes this place.
So you're gonna die anyway.
BARBER: Now, don't you move.
My hands ain't as steady
as they used to be.
By Odin's beard,
you shall not cut my hair...
lest you feel the wrath
of the mighty Thor.
(WHIRRING)
Please. Please, kind sir,
do not cut my hair.
(BARBER LAUGHS)
Please! No!
No!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Wow! Look at
all of you. (LAUGHS)
What a show! What a night!
Who's having fun?
Please, I'm your host.
Big round of applause
for all of our
undercard competitors...
who today died so gruesomely.
Good sports.
What a show! What a night!
This is what you've come for,
and so have I.
And now,
without further ado...
it's main event time.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Making his first appearance,
though he looks
quite promising...
got a couple of tricks
up his sleeve.
I'll say no more,
see what you think.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you...
Lord of Thunder.
(AUDIENCE BOOING AND SHOUTING)
Watch out for his fingers.
They make sparks.
Okay, this is it.
Let's get ready to welcome
this guy. Here he comes.
-(FIREWORKS BURSTING)
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(RUMBLING)
GRANDMASTER: He is a creature.
What can we say about him?
Well, he's unique.
There's none like him.
I feel a special connection
with him.
He's undefeated.
He's the reigning.
He's the defending.
Ladies and gentlemen...
I give you...
Uh-oh.
...your Incredible...
(ROARING)
Hulk!
Yes!
(CHEERING DIES DOWN)
I have to get off this planet.
Hey, hey, hey.
Where you going?
-(YELLING)
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(AUDIENCE CHANTING)
Hey!
We know each other.
He's a friend from work.
(LOKI CLEARS THROAT)
Where have you been?
Everybody thought
you were dead.
But so much has happened
since I last saw you.
I lost my hammer.
Like, yesterday,
so that's still pretty fresh.
Loki. Loki's alive.
Can you believe it?
He's up there.
Loki! Look who it is!
Banner, I never thought
I would say this...
but I'm happy to see you.
AUDIENCE: (CHANTING)
Hulk! Hulk! Hulk!
THOR: Banner.
Hey, Banner!
No Banner. Only Hulk.
What are you doing?
-It's me. It's Thor!
-(GROWLS)
(YELLING)
(ROARS)
Banner, we're friends.
This is crazy.
I don't want to hurt you!
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
-Here we go.
(HULK GRUNTS)
What?
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
Hey, big guy.
The sun's getting real low.
(GRUNTING)
(SHUSHING)
That's it.
The sun's going down.
I won't hurt you anymore.
No one will.
(YELPS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(ROARING)
Yes! That's how it feels!
(LOKI CHUCKLES)
I'm just a huge fan
of the sport.
(LAUGHING)
(AUDIENCE CHANTING)
(ROARS)
All right. Screw it.
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
AUDIENCE: Oh!
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
I know
you're in there, Banner.
I'll get you out!
(AUDIENCE CLAMORING)
(ROARS)
What's the matter with you?
You're embarrassing me!
I told them we were friends!
(THOR YELLING)
(YELLS)
(CLAMORING STOPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(THOR GRUNTS)
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(LAUGHS)
(THOR GRUNTING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(GROANING)
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
AUDIENCE: (CHANTING)
Thunder! Thunder! Thunder!
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(DEVICE BEEPS)
(AUDIENCE BOOING)
(ROARING)
(SIGHS)
Another day, another Doug.
(ROARS)
(THUDDING)
HELA: What is that noise?
The common folk aren't exactly
falling in line.
There's a resistance trying
to knock down the front gates.
(CREATURES GROWLING)
Tell me about yourself,
Skurge.
Well, me dad was a stonemason.
Me mum was...
Right, yeah,
I'll just stop you there.
What I meant was...
what's your ambition?
I just want a chance
to prove myself.
Recognition.
When I was young...
every great king
had an executioner.
Not just to execute people...
but also
to execute their vision.
But mainly to execute people.
Still, it was a great honor.
I was Odin's executioner.
And you shall be
my executioner.
Let's begin our conquest.
(SWEEPING MUSIC PLAYING)
Skurge, where's the sword?
That sword is the key
to opening the Bifrost.
Those people you mentioned,
the ones who aren't
falling into line...
round them up.
(CREATURE SNARLS)
(PANTING)
(SNARLS)
Excuse me.
(CREATURE SNARLS)
Sorry about that.
These bloody things
are everywhere.
Come on.
(RUMBLING)
You'll be safe here.
-(YELLS)
-(ALL GASP)
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WATER SPLASHES)
Are we cool?
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
It's Hulk in a hot tub.
So how long
have you been like that?
Like what?
Like this. Big, and green,
and stupid.
Hulk always Hulk.
How'd you get here?
Winning.
You mean cheating, huh?
Were they wearing one of these
when you won?
How'd you arrive here?
(IMITATING WHOOSHING)
Quinjet.
Yes. Now,
where is the Quinjet now?
That's naked.
-He's very naked. Hmm.
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
It's in my brain now.
Quinjet.
Yes!
I'm getting us out of here.
This is a terrible,
awful place.
You're gonna love Asgard.
It's big. It's golden. Shiny.
Hulk stay.
No, no, no. My people need me
to get back to Asgard.
We must prevent Ragnarok.
Ragnarok?
The prophesied death
of my home world.
The end of days,
it's the end of...
(YAWNING)
If you help me
get back to Asgard...
I can help you
get back to Earth. Huh?
Earth hate Hulk.
Earth loves Hulk.
They love you.
You're one of the Avengers.
One of the team,
one of our friends.
This is what friends do.
They support each other.
You're Banner's friend.
I'm not Banner's friend.
I prefer you.
Banner's friend.
-I don't even like Banner.
-(SPITS)
"I'm into numbers and science
and stuff."
Thor go. Hulk stay.
Fine.
Stay here.
Stupid place.
It's hideous, by the way.
The red, the white.
Just pick a color. Ridiculous.
Smash you.
You didn't smash anything.
I won that fight.
-I smashed you.
-Yeah, sure, sure.
-Baby arms.
-What?
Baby.
Moron! You big child.
Thor go!
-I am going.
-(ALARM BEEPS)
-(GROANING)
-(LAUGHING)
Thor go again.
(HULK LAUGHS)
Thor home.
Hulk trains.
That's great. Have fun.
-Hey, big guy.
-Angry girl.
What have you been up to?
HULK: Winning.
(VALKYRIE LAUGHS)
(THOR SIGHS)
Heimdall, I know
you can see me.
I need you to help me.
Help me see.
I see you,
but you're far away.
What's going on here?
Come see for yourself.
I'm providing refuge
in a stronghold
built by our ancestors.
But if the garrison falls,
our only escape is Bifrost.
You're talking
about evacuating Asgard?
(CREATURE SNARLS)
We won't last long if we stay.
She draws her power
from Asgard
and grows stronger every day.
Come on.
Hela is ravenous.
If I let her leave,
she'll consume Nine Realms
and all the cosmos.
We need you.
I'm working on it.
But I don't even know
where the hell I am.
You're on a planet surrounded
by doorways. Go through one.
-Which one?
-The big one.
(CREATURE SNARLS)
(GASPING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Thor sad.
Shut up.
I'm not sad, you idiot.
-I'm pissed off!
-Oh.
Angry. I lost my father.
-I lost my hammer.
-(SCOFFS)
-You're not even listening.
-Whining and crying.
Cry like baby.
Don't kick stuff.
You're being
a really bad friend.
You bad friend!
-You know what we call you?
-No.
We call you
the stupid Avenger.
You're tiny Avenger! (GRUNTS)
What, are you crazy?
Yes.
You know what?
Earth does hate you.
(WEAPON THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
No. Mmm-mmm.
I'm sorry I said those things.
You're not the stupid Avenger.
Nobody calls you
the stupid Avenger.
It's okay.
You just can't go around
throwing shields
at people.
Could have killed me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I just get so angry
all the time.
Hulk always, always angry.
I know.
We're the same, you and I.
We're just
a couple of hot-headed fools.
Yeah, same. Hulk like fire,
Thor like water.
We're kind of both like fire.
But Hulk like real fire.
Hulk like raging fire.
Thor like smoldering fire.
(CHUCKLES)
Hulk, I need you
to do something for me.
Hmm?
(CHUCKLING)
Angry girl.
(LAUGHS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
What's going on?
What are you...
(HULK GROANS)
You're so thick-headed
that you can't tell...
when someone's hiding
all the way across
the universe and wants
to be left alone.
-We need to talk.
-No, you wanna talk to me.
I need her to stay.
Stay?
Block.
Stay.
-Please.
All right.
-Here's the deal.
-(BALL BOUNCING)
I'll listen to you...
till this is empty.
Asgard is in danger and
people are dying.
We need to get back there.
I need your help.
Wow.
-Finished. Bye.
-(GLASS SHATTERS)
Odin is dead.
Hela, the Goddess of Death,
has invaded Asgard.
If Hela's back,
then Asgard's already lost.
I'm going to stop her.
-Alone?
-Nope.
I'm putting together a team.
It's me, you, and the big guy.
No. No team. Only Hulk.
It's me and you.
I think it's only you.
Wait. Just listen.
The Valkyrie are legend.
Elite warriors of Asgard
sworn to defend the throne.
I'm not getting dragged into
another one of Odin's
family squabbles.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Your sister.
Her power comes from Asgard,
same as yours.
When it grew
beyond Odin's control
she massacred everyone
in the palace...
and tried to seize the throne.
When she tried
to escape her banishment...
he sent the Valkyrie in
to fight her back.
I only survived because...
Look, I already faced her once
back when I believed
in the throne...
and it cost me everything.
That's what's wrong
with Asgard.
The throne, the secrets,
the whole golden sham.
I agree.
Don't get familiar.
(SIGHS) I agree.
That's why I turned down
the throne.
But this isn't
about the crown.
This is about the people.
They're dying
and they're your people, too.
Forget it.
I have.
-Okay.
-Good. Great.
-Great.
Thank you.
-For what?
-For this.
(CHUCKLES) Didn't see that,
did you?
(SIGHS)
-(DEVICE POWERS DOWN)
-There... That's better.
You know, go ahead.
Stay here and enslave people
for that lunatic.
Keep drinking, keep hiding.
But me...
I choose to run
toward my problems
and not away from them.
Because that's what...
Because that's what heroes do.
(UPBEAT ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING)
Friend stay!
Yes!
(GRUNTS)
All right.
(BEEPING)
Come on.
COMPUTER: Welcome.
Voice activation required.
-Thor.
-(BEEPS)
Access denied.
Uh... Thor, son of Odin.
-(BEEPS)
-Access denied.
God of Thunder.
-(BEEPS)
-Access denied.
Strongest Avenger.
-(BEEPS)
-Access denied.
(IN DEEP VOICE)
Strongest Avenger.
-(BEEPS)
-Access denied.
(SIGHS) Damn you, Stark.
Point Break.
-Welcome, Point Break.
-(CHUCKLES)
-(POWERING UP)
-(LAUGHS)
-(RUMBLING)
-Friend stay!
No, no, no! Stop!
-Stay!
-(QUINJET POWERS DOWN)
Stop!
Stop breaking everything!
Don't go!
Nice work, big guy.
We don't know
where Ultron's headed,
but you're going very high,
very fast.
So, I need you to turn
this bird around, okay?
We can't track you
in stealth mode...
so I need you
to help me out. Okay?
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
(DISTORTED) I need you to...
(GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
No! No, Banner!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Oh, jeez.
Banner.
-Hey, hey, hey.
-(GROANING)
-You all right, Banner?
-(GASPS)
-(GASPING)
-(SHUSHING)
Sun's going down.
That's it, breathe.
(EXHALES) I won't hurt you.
-Sun's going down.
-(GROANS)
-Thor.
-Yeah.
What happened to your hair?
Some creepy old man
cut it off.
-It looks good.
-Oh, thanks.
Where are we? Oh, how's Nat?
-Uh, Nat is good, I'm sure.
-Is she okay?
-And what about Sokovia?
-Sokovia?
The city, Sokovia.
Did we save it?
-Banner, listen.
-What?
Sokovia. Ultron.
That was two years ago.
-What are you saying?
-Well...
What?
I've been Hulk for two years?
I'm afraid so.
(CLATTERS)
What the hell happened?
Banner, there's something
you should know.
(BEEPING)
COMPUTER:
Voice activation required.
Banner.
Welcome, strongest Avenger.
Uh, what?
Ship's log.
(CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Thor, where are we?
Yeah, about that.
GRANDMASTER: (ON SPEAKERS)
Sakaar, hear ye.
Attention please.
I have some bad news.
My beloved exalted champion
has turned up missing.
Take to the streets.
Celebrate my champion.
BANNER: Who's that?
He kind of runs the place.
You actually lived
at his house for awhile.
-I did?
-Yeah.
Quite a lot's happened. You
and I had a fight recently.
-Did I win?
-No, I won. Easily.
Doesn't sound right.
Well, it's true.
It seems that that
criminally seductive
Lord of Thunder
has stolen him away.
Seductive God of Thunder.
We need to move.
Oh, no.
(GRANDMASTER CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
This is bad.
This is really, really bad.
Thor, I think
I'm freaking out.
No, no, no.
Don't freak out. You're okay.
Put these on.
These are Tony's clothes.
-I know, come on.
-Is he here?
No, he's not here. But listen.
Just stay calm, okay?
The sun's going down.
The sun's getting really low.
Sun's going down.
GRANDMASTER: I'm upset!
I'm very upset.
You know what I like about
being upset? The blame.
Right now, that's
the mindset that I'm in.
And you know who I'm blaming?
-Grandmaster, I can...
-Hey!
Don't interrupt me!
Here you go.
Why are you handing me
the melt stick?
He was interrupting.
That's not
a capital violation.
Where was I?
My precious champion
has come up missing...
and it's all because
of that Lord of Thunder.
It's all because of him.
Your brother.
Whatever the story is.
Adopted, or complicated.
I'm sure
there's a big history.
And your contender...
LOKI: My dear friend...
if you were to give me
12 hours,
I could bring them both
back to you. Alive.
I could do it in two.
I could do it in one.
Let's stop there.
You know what?
I woke up this morning
thinking about
a public execution.
But for now, I'll settle
for this sweet little...
(EXCLAIMS)
"Who's gonna get him first?"
So, you're on the clock.
What have you done?
I don't answer to you, lackey.
It's Loki.
And you will answer
to the Grandmaster.
-(GRUNTS)
-Hmm.
Why would you help my brother
escape with that green fool?
I don't help anyone.
You're a Valkyrie.
I thought the Valkyrie had
all died gruesome deaths.
Choose your next words wisely.
I'm terribly sorry.
Must be a very painful memory.
(GRUNTS)
THOR: The sun's going down.
It's getting really low.
The sun's going down.
-It's getting real low.
-Oh, shoot.
-Sun's getting low.
-Would you stop saying that?
I just need you to stay calm.
Calm? I'm on an alien planet!
It's just a planet. You've
been on a planet before.
Yeah. One.
Now you've been on two.
That's a good thing.
It's a new experience.
My neurons,
they're firing faster
than my brain can handle
the information.
The whole thing is totally
different this time.
In the past, I always felt
like Hulk and I
each had a hand on the wheel.
But this time, it's like
he had the keys
to the car and I was
locked in the trunk.
All right, well, you're back
now. That's all that matters.
No, it's not what matters.
What I'm trying
to tell you, is that
if I turn into
the Hulk again...
Banner may never come back.
And we're stranded on a planet
that is designed
to stress me out.
We're not stranded.
I'm gonna figure out a way
to get us home.
Thank you.
Not your home, though. Asgard.
My home.
What?
Listen, my people
are in great danger.
You and I, we have to fight
this really powerful being...
who also happens
to be my sister.
Okay, that is so wrong
on so many...
I don't wanna
fight your sister.
That's a family issue.
No, she's an evil being.
I don't care what she is.
I'm not fighting any
more beings. I'm sick of it.
-What?
-I just told you.
If I turn into the Hulk,
I am never gonna
come back again.
And you don't care.
No, no. I'm putting together
the team.
The Hulk is the fire.
Wait, you're just using me
to get to the Hulk.
-What? No!
-It's gross.
You don't care about me.
You're not my friend.
No! I don't even
like the Hulk.
He's all like...
"Smash, smash, smash."
I prefer you.
Thanks.
But if I'm being honest,
when it comes
to fighting evil beings...
he is very powerful
and useful.
Yeah, Banner's powerful
and useful, too.
Is he though?
How many PhDs
does Hulk have? Zero.
How many PhDs does
Banner have? Seven.
Fine, you don't have
to fight anyone.
But we're in danger here,
so we have to move.
What are you doing with that?
I need a disguise.
I'm a fugitive.
-I need a disguise.
-You are the disguise.
-I'll be Tony Stark.
-What?
Yeah. Tony and the gypsy.
No, no, you're not Tony.
You're Bruce. Bruce Banner.
Then why did you dress me up
like Tony?
Because you were naked.
Okay, I'll give you that.
What are you doing?
Stop doing that!
Tony wears his pants
super tight.
-Stop it!
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you being so weird?
-I don't know.
Maybe the fact that I was
trapped for two years...
inside of a monster
made me a little weird.
Hey. Shh. It's okay.
You're good. Calm down.
Come on.
Listen, we're gonna
go to Asgard...
and you're not gonna
have to think about
the Hulk ever again.
-All right?
-All right.
-(PEOPLE CHEERING)
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
ALL: (CHANTING) Hulk!
Oh. This is bad.
Banner! Banner!
Banner!
(FIREWORKS BURSTING)
Thor!
(SNARLS)
Hi.
I was gonna do that.
Yeah, well, I did it first.
That's good.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were leaving.
I got sidetracked.
What's with the...
It's my disguise.
But I can see your face.
Not when I do this, you can't.
Your hair looks nice.
I like what you did with it.
Change it? Washed it maybe?
BANNER: What are those things
on her eyes?
Are those the people
that she's killed?
She's so beautiful and strong
and courageous.
Who is this guy?
-He's a friend.
-Who? Me?
-I'm Bruce.
-I feel like I know you.
I feel like I know you, too.
(DISTANT CHATTERING)
Look, I've spent years
in a haze,
-trying to forget my past.
-THOR: Mmm.
Sakaar seemed like
the best place
to drink and forget,
and to die one day.
I was thinking
that you drink too much,
and that probably
was gonna kill you.
I don't plan to stop drinking.
-Oh.
-But I don't wanna forget.
I can't turn away anymore...
so if I'm gonna die...
well, it may as well be
driving my sword
through the heart
of that murderous hag.
-Good.
-BANNER: Yeah.
So, I'm saying
that I wanna be on the team.
Has it got a name?
Yeah, it's called
the Revengers.
Revengers?
Because I'm getting revenge.
You're getting revenge.
(STAMMERS)
Do you want revenge?
(STAMMERS) I'm undecided.
Okay.
Also, I've got
a peace offering.
Surprise.
(CLATTERS)
Ow.
Just had to be sure.
Hello, Bruce.
So, last time I saw you,
you were trying
to kill everybody.
Where are you at these days?
It varies
from moment to moment.
THOR: Is that a Dragonfang?
It is.
THOR: My God.
This is the famed sword
of the Valkyrie.
Sakaar and Asgard
are about as far apart
as any two known systems.
Our best bet is a wormhole
just outside of city limits.
Refuel on Xandar, and
we can be back in Asgard
in 18 months.
Nope. We are going through
the big one.
The Devil's Anus?
Anus?
Wait, wait, wait. Whose anus?
For the record, I didn't know
it was called that
when I picked it.
That looks like
a collapsing neutron star...
inside of an
Einstein-Rosen Bridge.
We need another ship.
That would tear
mine to pieces.
THOR: She's right. We need one
that can withstand
the geodetic strain
from the singularity.
And has an offline
power steering system...
that could also function
without the on-board computer.
And we need one
with cup holders,
because we're gonna die.
So, drinks!
Do I know you?
I feel like I know you.
I feel like I know you, too.
It's weird.
THOR: What do you say?
Uncharted metagalactic travel
through a volatile
cosmic gateway.
Talk about an adventure.
-We need a ship.
-Need a ship.
There are one or two ships.
Absolute top of the line
models...
I don't mean to impose...
(GLASS SHATTERS)
But the Grandmaster
has a great many ships.
I may even have stolen
the access codes
to his security system.
And suddenly you're overcome
with an urge
to do the right thing.
Heavens, no.
I've run out of favor
with the Grandmaster...
and in exchange for codes
and access to a ship...
I'm asking for safe passage
through the Anus.
You're telling us
that you can get us
access into the garage...
without setting off
any alarms?
Yes, brother. I can.
Okay, can I just... (WHISTLES)
A quick FYI.
I was just talking to him
just a couple minutes ago...
and he was totally ready
to kill any of us.
He did try to kill me.
Yes, me too.
On many, many occasions.
There was one time
when we were children...
he transformed himself
into a snake,
and he knows
that I love snakes.
So, I went to pick up
the snake to admire it...
and he transformed back
into himself
and he was like,
"Yeah, it's me!"
And he stabbed me.
We were eight at the time.
VALKYRIE: If we're
boosting a ship...
we're gonna need to draw some
guards away from the palace.
Why not set the beast loose?
Shut up.
You guys have a beast?
No, there's no beast.
He's just being stupid.
We're going to start
a revolution.
-Revolution?
-I'll explain later.
-Who's this guy again?
Is that
some sort of protoplasm,
all the stuff
that's coming out of you...
or are they eggs?
Looks like eggs.
-Oh!
-(CLATTERING)
I'm looking for Korg.
Who's asking?
I know you're asking.
Is anyone else asking,
or is it just you?
The Lord of Thunder
sends his best.
(GUN POWERING UP)
The revolution has begun.
Revolution?
How did this happen?
Don't know.
But the arena's mainframe
for the Obedience Disks
have been deactivated...
and the slaves
have armed themselves.
Oh. I don't like that word.
Which? Mainframe?
No. Why would I not like
"mainframe"?
No, the "S" word.
Sorry, the prisoners with jobs
have armed themselves.
Okay, that's better.
(BEEPING)
Hey, so, listen.
We should talk.
I disagree.
Open communication
was never our family's forte.
You have no idea.
Been quite the revelation
since we last spoke.
Hello.
Hi.
Odin brought us together.
It's almost poetic that his
death should split us apart.
We might as well be
strangers now.
Two sons of the crown,
set adrift.
-Oh.
-(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Thought you didn't
wanna talk about it.
Here's the thing.
I'm probably better off
staying here on Sakaar.
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
Did you just agree with me?
Come on, this place
is perfect for you.
It's savage,
chaotic, lawless...
Brother, you're gonna do
great here.
Do you truly think
so little of me?
Loki, I thought
the world of you.
I thought we were gonna fight
side by side forever.
But at the end of the day,
you're you and I'm me.
I don't know, maybe
there's still good in you.
But let's be honest,
our paths diverged
a long time ago.
Yeah.
It's probably for the best
that we never
see each other again.
That's what you always wanted.
(PATS ON THE BACK)
Hey, let's do "Get Help."
-What?
-"Get Help."
No.
-Come on, you love it.
-I hate it.
It's great.
It works every time.
-It's humiliating.
-Do you have a better plan?
-No.
-We're doing it.
We are not doing "Get Help."
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
-Get help! Please!
My brother, he's dying.
Get help! Help him!
Classic.
(GROANS) Still hate it.
-It's humiliating.
-Not for me, it's not.
Now, which one's the ship
she told us to get?
The Commodore.
THOR: Right.
Though I feel it won't make
much of a difference.
Oh, Loki.
I know I've betrayed you
many times before...
but this time
it's truly nothing personal.
The reward for your capture
-will set me up nicely.
-(ALARM BLARING)
Never one for sentiment,
were you?
Easier to let it burn.
I agree.
(GROANING)
Oh, that looks painful.
Oh, dear brother,
you're becoming predictable.
I trust you, you betray me.
Round and round
in circles we go.
See, Loki, life is about,
it's about growth.
It's about change.
But you seem to
just wanna stay the same.
I guess
what I'm trying to say...
is that you'll always be
the God of Mischief...
but you could be more.
I'll just put this over here
for you.
Anyway, all got places to be,
so good luck.
All right,
I can figure this out.
It's just another spaceship.
(POWERING UP)
GRANDMASTER: (ON SPEAKERS)
Loyal Sakaarians...
Lord of Thunder
has stolen my ship
and my favorite champion.
Sakaarians, take to the skies.
Bring him down.
Do not let him
leave this planet.
-Good shot!
-Thanks.
VALKYRIE: (ON RADIO)
Open the doors.
Okay.
I hope that you're tougher
than you look.
Why?
(SCREAMING)
-(GROANING)
-(LAUGHS)
Shouldn't we be shooting back
or something?
Yes, we should.
Where are the guns
on this ship?
VALKYRIE: There aren't any.
-It's a leisure vessel.
-BANNER: What?
Grandmaster uses it
for his good times,
orgies and stuff.
Did she just say
the Grandmaster
uses it for orgies?
Yeah.
Don't touch anything.
(ALARM BEEPING)
No!
(LAUGHING)
-No!
(YELLS)
Get inside!
In a minute.
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
I should probably go and help.
Here, take the wheel.
No. I don't know
how to fly one of these.
You're a scientist.
Use one of your PhDs.
None of them are for flying
alien spaceships!
Okay, come on.
There's gotta be a gun
on this thing.
That looks like a gun.
GRANDMASTER: (SINGING)
It's my birthday
(FIREWORKS BURSTING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Yeah!
-(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
-(GRUNTS)
Guys, we're coming up
on the Devil's Anus!
There she is.
Our ticket out of here.
Hey, what's this?
-(DEVICE POWERS DOWN)
-(LOKI GROANS)
Thank you.
Hey, man. We're about to jump
on that ginormous spaceship.
You wanna come?
You do seem like
you're in desperate need
of leadership.
Why, thank you.
Here we go.
Shit.
(EXPLOSIONS)
(BANNER GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
SKURGE: Asgardians...
some misguided soul...
has stolen the Bifrost sword.
Tell us where it is...
or there will be consequences.
Bad ones.
Well?
You.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(MAN PROTESTING)
(WOMAN BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SOBBING)
Well? Executioner?
-(ALL GASP)
-MAN: Wait!
Wait!
I know where the sword is.
I never thought
I'd be back here.
BANNER: I thought
it'd be a lot nicer.
I mean,
not that it's not nice.
It's just, it's on fire.
Here, up here
in the mountains.
Heat signatures.
People clustered together.
She's coming for them.
Okay, drop me off
at the palace
-and I'll draw her away.
-And get yourself killed?
The people trapped down there
are all that matters.
While I'm dealing with Hela,
I need you two
to help get
everyone off Asgard.
How the hell are we supposed
to do that?
I have a man on the ground.
(LOW INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Asgard.
She's here.
Now the ship has a gun.
I'll take it from here.
I found this in the armory.
Good luck.
Your Majesty...
don't die.
You know what I mean.
HEIMDALL: We must keep moving!
Go to the Bifrost!
(STAFF THUDDING)
Sister.
You're still alive.
I love what you've done
with the place.
Redecorating, I see.
It seems our father's solution
to every problem
was to cover it up.
Or to cast it out.
He told you you were worthy.
He said the same thing to me.
You see?
You never knew him.
Not at his best.
Odin and I drowned
entire civilizations
in blood and tears.
Where do you think
all this gold came from?
And then, one day...
he decided to become
a benevolent king.
To foster peace,
to protect life...
to have you.
I understand why you're angry.
And you are my sister,
and technically
have a claim to the throne.
And believe me, I would love
for someone else to rule.
But it can't be you.
You're just... (SIGHS)
The worst.
Okay, get up.
You're in my seat.
You know,
Father once told me...
that a wise king
never seeks out war.
But must always
be ready for it.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(FENRIS GROWLS)
(GROWLING)
Go back!
(ALL CLAMORING)
(SNARLS)
HEIMDALL: Go!
To be honest, I expected more.
Heimdall!
The sword!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
Here's the difference
between us.
I'm Odin's firstborn...
the rightful heir,
the savior of Asgard.
-And you're nothing.
-(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
So simple,
even a blind man could see it.
(YELLS)
Oh.
Now you remind me of Dad.
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(ROARING)
The stupid dog won't die!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Everything's gonna be
all right now. I got this.
You wanted to know who I am?
What the hell
are you talking about?
You'll see!
(FENRIS SNIFFING)
(GROWLS)
(SNARLS)
(ALL WHIMPERING)
(ROARING)
(ROARS)
(GROANS)
You see?
No one's going anywhere.
I'll get that sword...
even if I have to kill every
single one of them to do it.
Hey, man.
I'm Korg. This is Miek.
We're gonna jump
on that spaceship
and get out of here.
Wanna come?
(SHIP APPROACHING)
Your savior is here.
(CHUCKLING)
(SCREAMS)
Did you miss me?
Everyone, on that ship now.
Welcome home.
I saw you coming.
Of course you did.
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(KORG YELLING)
It's a valiant effort,
but you never stood a chance.
You see...
I'm not a queen or a monster.
I'm the Goddess of Death.
What were you
the god of, again?
(PANTING)
Even when you had two eyes...
you'd see
only half the picture.
She's too strong.
Without my hammer, I can't.
Are you Thor,
the God of Hammers? Hmm?
(PANTING)
That hammer was to help you
control your power,
to focus it.
It was never your source
of strength.
It's too late.
She's already taken Asgard.
Asgard is not a place.
Never was.
This could be Asgard.
Asgard is where
our people stand.
Even now, right now,
those people need your help.
I'm not as strong as you.
No...
you're stronger.
Tell me, brother.
What were you
the god of again?
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
-(THOR YELLING)
(IMMIGRANT SONG BY LED ZEPPELIN PLAYING)
(FIREWORKS BURSTING)
(GROWLS)
(ROARS)
(YELLING)
-You're late.
-You're missing an eye.
VALKYRIE: This isn't over.
(ALL PANTING)
I think we should
disband the Revengers.
Hit her
with a lightning blast.
I just hit her with
the biggest lightning blast
in the history of lightning.
It did nothing.
We just need to hold her off
until everyone's on board.
It won't end there.
The longer Hela's on Asgard,
the more powerful she grows.
She'll hunt us down.
We need to stop her
here and now.
So what do we do?
I'm not doing "Get Help."
Asgard's not a place,
it's a people.
Loki...
this was never about
stopping Ragnarok.
This was about
causing Ragnarok.
Surtur's crown, the vault.
It's the only way.
Bold move, brother.
Even for me.
Shall we?
After you.
(GRUNTING)
This is madness.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Go! Go, now!
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(GUN FIRING)
For Asgard.
SKURGE: Hela!
(GUN CLICKS)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
With the Eternal Flame,
you are reborn.
(GASPING)
Hela, enough!
You want Asgard, it's yours.
Whatever game you're playing,
it won't work.
You can't defeat me.
No, I know.
But he can.
(ROARING)
No.
(HELA GRUNTS)
Tremble before me, Asgard!
I am your reckoning!
The people are safe.
That's all that matters.
THOR: We're fulfilling
the prophecy.
I hate this prophecy.
So do I,
but we have no choice.
Surtur destroys Asgard...
he destroys Hela,
so that our people may live.
But we need to let him
finish the job,
-otherwise...
-(HULK ROARING)
No!
(HULK ROARING)
Hulk, stop, you moron!
(HULK GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
(SCREAMING)
THOR: Hulk, stop.
Just for once in your life,
don't smash.
Big monster!
Let's go!
(GROWLS)
Fine.
(HULK GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
SURTUR: I am Asgard's doom!
(LAUGHING)
The damage is not too bad.
As long as the foundations
are still strong...
we can rebuild this place.
It will become a haven...
for all peoples and aliens
of the universe.
Now those foundations
are gone. Sorry.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
What have I done?
You saved us from extinction.
Asgard is not a place...
it's a people.
It suits you.
Maybe you're not so bad
after all, brother.
Maybe not.
Thank you.
If you were here,
I might even give you a hug.
I'm here.
Your throne.
So. King of Asgard.
Where to?
I'm not sure.
Any suggestions?
Miek, where are you from?
Oh, Miek's dead.
Yeah, no, I accidentally
stomped on him on the bridge.
I've just felt so guilty,
I've been carrying him around
all day.
-(CHITTERING)
-(GASPS) Miek, you're alive!
He's alive, guys.
What was
your question again, bro?
Earth it is.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Do you really think
it's a good idea
to go back to Earth?
Yes, of course.
The people of Earth love me.
I'm very popular.
Let me rephrase that.
Do you really think
it's a good idea
to bring me back to Earth?
Probably not, to be honest.
I wouldn't worry, brother.
I feel like everything's
gonna work out fine.
(LOW RUMBLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANING)
Oh, boy.
(SCRAPPERS EXCLAIMING)
(GROANS) Oh.
I just gotta say,
I'm proud of you all.
This revolution has been
a huge success. Yay, us!
Pat on the back.
Come on. No?
Me too. 'Cause I've been
a big part of it.
Can't have a revolution
without somebody to overthrow.
So, you're welcome.
And, uh, it's a tie.