Malekith
Asgard's forces are upon us.
Send in the Kursed!
Their deaths will mean our survival.
This war is far from over.
The Aether awakens us.
The Convergence returns.
Look upon my legacy, Algrim.
I can barely remember a time
before the light.
Our survival will be your legacy.
The Asgardians will suffer
as we have suffered.
I will reclaim the Aether.
I will restore our world.
And I will put an end
to this poisoned universe.
The worlds are nearly aligned.
You will be the last of the Kursed.
Let my life be sacrificed.
It is no less than our people did,
or you have done.
You will become darkness,
cursed to this existence
until it consumes you.
Until then, no power our enemies
possess can stop you.
I will tear down their defenses and
ensure your return to a universe reborn.
We must strike now.
No.
Asgard is meaningless.
The Aether has found its way home.
He is an enemy of Asgard.
He was a prisoner in their dungeons.