THREE DAYS OF THE CONDOR
TeIl her what you got. - MaIe,
Caucasian, appears to have been shot.
Where? - In his room.
- Very funny, HaroId.
The wound is just beIow the heart.
- Shot once? - Seems to have been.
Turner ...?
Dr. Lappe, l'm sure he's going to be
here any second now. - ReaIly?
Mr. Turner is late again.
Let's get back to work.
- We can do that in five minutes.
You know what Joey would say?
- Come on!
What kind of a slug?
- You're missing the point.
The machine wilI come back with a
rephrase. - What do we feed in?
Turner, Joseph. - 1 7 minutes Iate.
- Make it 1 2, there was a headwind.
Dr. Lappe, anything in the
earIy pouch for me?
Dr. Lappe?
Nothing in response to your report.
Please analyze the book on your desk
by 4 o'cIock. - Yes, sir.
I'd move the Tolmiea to the light,
the leaves are getting a blight.
At ease, Sarge, at ease.
It's going to rain today, at 1 0:20.
There must be more details.
- I only read two chapters.
No other clues?
- What time did they find him?
Doesn't say. Just early evening.
- They never said what caIiber.
Apparently a .38.
- Why "apparently?"
The entry wound was characteristic of
a .38, but the sIug wasn't recovered.
Hey, we're getting somewhere.
- You guys figure it out.
l have Far East journaIs to read.
- Was the slug in the waIl?
No, there was no exit wound.
We're not getting anywhere.
Finish the book.
Hi. What we've got so far ...
Ice.
lnstead of Iead. lce.
The murderer pours water into a .38
caliber mold and freezes it.
He shoots the guy with the ice buIlet.
The cops find a few drops of water.
No bulIet, no baIlistics.
- That's great!
What is this?
Beautiful caIligraphy.
- What is it? - It means heaven.
Nothing eIse? - It can mean
"the best" or "tops". Why?
l'm not sure. - We're going to Sam
and Mae's tonight, right?
TaIk to Sam about it.
- About this?
I did. He said, "that's interesting,
but it's not my department."
Which means he doesn't think there's
anything, just like Dr. Lappe.
And you. - There's not much.
A mystery that's been translated.
A mystery that didn't selI and has
been transIated into odd languages.
Turkish, but not French.
Arabic, but not Russian or German.
Dutch.
- Spanish?
Yes.
Where did you get that about the ice?
DashielI Hammett? - Dick Tracy.
Are you sure about this ideogram?
Look at this face. Could l be wrong
about an ideogram?
It's a great face.
But it's never been to China.
Ray, when can I get some
computer time? - Dick Tracy?
A very underrated detective.
- There's some free time at 2:45.
No, stay on scheduIe, l'Il get it.
Four pieces, right?
- Right. - HoId it!
Five.
- Affirmative, five.
Where is Mr. Heidegger? - He calIed
in sick. - ProbabIy hung over again.
This is extraordinary.
I was just checking the fiIes and I
came across an inquiry he sent
to Persian GuIf command.
He did that for me.
- lt never went through my office.
I asked for some research,
he didn't feel it was important.
l wish you peopIe
wouId go through channeIs.
What's on your mind?
This was in the pouch
from New York Central.
HQ in LangIey says there's no other
source to support your theory.
CaIl this working on that book?
- l'Il have it by 4pm.
We have peopIe to service machines.
- These things just Iook compIicated.
l wonder if you are
entireIy happy here.
Within obvious limits, yes, sir.
- Obvious Iimits?
I can't teIl people what I do.
- Why can't you accept that?
l actuaIly trust a few peopIe.
That's the problem.
lt's your turn to bring in lunch.
What time is it?
1 1 :22.
- The rain's gonna stop by 1 1 :30.
You can wait 8 minutes.
That's not a proper exit! - He always
goes out that way when it rains.
PersonneI should enter and exit
by authorized means onIy!
Shakespeare, how is it? - Terrific.
The rejection slips just pile up.
Know the feeling.
I aIways wanted to be Escoffier.
Maybe it's not too late. Van Gogh
was 30 before he began to paint.
No mayonnaise on Dr. Lappe's.
On the other hand, Mozart was 3 when
he started piano, and composed at 6.
Fast starter, probably better.
- Van Gogh never sold a painting
and Mozart died a pauper.
- Am l in the Public Library?
Hey, that's a very bright man!
- EducationaI. That's why I come here.
l come in here to get sick,
just like everybody else.
No butter on Ray's sandwich.
He gets very panicky about butter.
Mr. Jennings is in the back.
He'lI sign for it.
Here are the ...
Mrs. RusselI, the Curtis report ...
Would you move
from the window, pIease?
Pardon?
Would you move from the window?
I won't scream.
I know.
SmaIl breakdown in security there?
What are you doin'?
What the helI are you doing?
SIeep at night, wilI ya?
This is the Major.
- Joe Turner.
ldentification? - My name is Turner.
I work for you. Now Iisten ...
ldentify yourself.
What is your designation?
Condor. Section 9, Department 1 7.
The section has been hit. - Level?
LeveI of damage! - Everybody.
Dr. Lappe, Janice, Ray, HaroId ...
Are you on a company line?
- No, I'm in a phone booth.
You're in vioIation of
communication procedures, Condor.
Listen, you S.O.B.. l came back with
lunch and the whole house was dead!
Has the incident been discovered
by anybody outside the company?
l don't know. I don't think so.
- Are you damaged?
Damaged ...? No.
- Are you armed?
I have Mrs. ...I can't remember
her code name ... NightingaIe.
She was afraid of being raped.
l've got her gun. - ldentify it.
lt's a .45 automatic.
WiIl you guys bring me in, please?
I'm not a field agent.
l just read books! - Leave the area.
Alright.
Do I come into headquarters now?
Negative. Find a secure Iocation.
- Where?
Avoid any pIace you are known.
Do not go home.
Surface again in two hours
and caIl the Major.
That'lI be 14:30 your time.
- Wait a minute, 2:30, right.
WaIk away from the phone.
Don't hang it up. - Don't hang it ...?
This is the Panic Officer.
Section 9-1 7 may have been hit.
Activate foIlowing procedures:
NY 1 -2-7, D.C. 4-6-9.
Replay the report upcoming. Standby.
Augie 1 to New York Center:
- Go ahead, Augie 1 .
Who am l taIking to?
- Higgins, Deputy Director. Go ahead.
Hit confirmed. Six coId items.
- QuaIity? - CIean, fast, first rate.
Did you say 6? lt shouId be 7.
- l repeat: 6. Here's a rundown:
Lappe, Chan, RusseIl, Jennings.
Martin and MitcheIl.
- Alright Augie 1 . Find 7.
"Condor".
Researcher, Tidepool,
Iikes to read comics.
Who is it?
Hey, you ring my buzzer?
It was a mistake, buddy.
Not you guys!
Hey, who are you?
Hey, who the helI are you?
Augie 3. We found item 7.
Ralf Heidegger. He bought it at home.
Okay, button it up, Augie.
I'lI send you more janitors.
l need Langley, right away.
- Yes, sir.
Grover speaking. - Higgins, Deputy
Director, NY. Give me Department 1 7.
Somebody took out
one of your sections: 9-1 7.
New York. Somebody got mugged, maybe?
- They were hit.
They're bookworms! - They got 7 out
of 8. We're on the shuttIe. 30 mins.
One of my people is stiIl okay?
- Condor. You know him?
No. Can he say what happened?
- He was literaIly out to lunch.
What happened? - He's not in yet.
His first calI was a little wiId.
Who's bringing him in? - Higgins.
He's aIready booked on the shuttle.
l want a chopper on the pad,
fueI for New York, now.
They're waiting for you.
- What? - Your two friends.
They just got here.
Said you gave them the keys.
Mr. Turner?
This is the Major. - This is Condor.
- Standby. Routing you to NY Center.
Condor on 1 -1 , Mr. Higgins.
HelIo, Condor.
Who's this? - Deputy Director Higgins,
New York Center. Where are you?
I need a code name, why don't you?
Where are you?
Here.
You alright?
- Are you insane? Everybody's dead!
Take it easy and we'Il bring you home.
Here's how:
Do you know the Ansonia Hotel?
- Broadway and 71 st. - 73rd.
There's an aIley behind the hoteI.
One hour from now, at exactIy 1 5:30,
I want you to enter that aIley
from the 73rd Street side.
WiIl you be there?
The head of department came from D.C..
He'lI bring you home.
I've never met him. - Don't worry.
He's studying your photos now.
I don't know you either.
- We'Il meet.
He'lI carry a WaIl Street JournaI.
- There were two guys at my house.
What were you doing there?
- I was homesick. Who were they?
They were ours.
- What were they doing in my house?
I'm not going in any aIley
and fuck the WaIl Street JournaI!
Turner, it's been a Iong, bad day.
You've been under ... - Damn right!
Alright. We'Il bring a familiar face.
Somebody you know.
Who's Ieft? - You've got a friend in
statistics named Sam Barber.
You guys are something ...
- WiIl he do?
Yes. Sam wiIl do.
AIright, Turner. Stay welI
for 60 minutes and you're home.
Can I ask a question?
- Sure.
What is happening?
- l'Il talk to you in 60 minutes.
You've got 55.
This is ridiculous.
- It's standard procedure.
To pick up a friend?
- And you, Mr. Wicks? - No, thanks.
Side arm?
- Have you got a .45?
You bet.
- Hey, let me help you with that.
How Iong have you known Condor?
- Joey ...
Before he was a bird even.
We went to CCNY. My wife Mae, too.
Was she ever Condor's girI?
- Here you go, Mr. Wicks.
TelI me what happened today.
- When?
This morning. About those murders.
What murders?
Here he is.
Hey, Sam. Where's that other ...
What are you doing?
lt's him, it's him!
Katherine Hale. H-A-L-E.
08-1 1-56 ...
...1 72-208-875. Amount $51 ,86
Where's there enough snow this early?
- ln Vermont.
What's open, Sugar Bush?
- Not downhilI.
This is cross-country.
- Don't Iike the Iift lines?
474, thank you.
Kathy!
Kathy, where have you been?
Let me give you a hand.
Wait, I don't know ...
- Be quiet.
Get in the car.
Don't make a sound, don't be dumb.
Please don't hurt me. - Where
do you live? - BrookIyn Heights.
AIone?
- l Iive with a friend ...
You live alone. Come on, let's go.
Leave the stuff.
Hi, Kath.
You should have said helIo.
Where is it?
- Here.
"Condor shot us both."
That was the onIy statement he couId
make before they operated on him.
And the other man, Barber? Is he dead?
- Before he hit the ground.
A remarkable shot.
A half-inch above his flak jacket.
Was Condor qualified with a handgun?
"Two years military service,
Signal Corps,
Telephone lineman, switchboard
maintenance, 6 months overseas,
Separated 9/61 , worked at
communication research colIege."
The question was:
ls he quaIified with a handgun?
No, sir. M-1 rifle and carbine.
EvidentIy it was sheer luck.
Or else ...
Or eIse what? - Condor isn't the man
his fiIe says he is.
Where did he Iearn the basic moves?
- He reads.
What the heIl does that mean?
- He reads everything.
I don't understand ...
- Yes ... very good.
Has Operations got anything?
- Absolutely nothing. - Extraordinary.
lt was very weIl executed.
- It requires planning, communication,
tracks.
I'm not asking for footprints
but a blade of grass,
a broken twig ...
Yes, sir. Wicks seems to be
aIl we've got. - Where do we have him?
We don't.
They rushed him to emergency
before we got word.
Maybe we should Ieak the name of the
hospital. Get Condor to make a move.
Don't expect
too many mistakes from this man.
He does seem rather more interesting
than just another reader researcher.
ExampIe: Has he gone into business
for himself? Was he turned around?
Does someone operate him?
SexuaI? Broke?
VulnerabIe?
Could he be a soldier of fortune?
Did he arrange the hit?
Is that why he's stiIl in flight?
StilI, he may be an innocent.
But then, why didn't he
come in gently, with Mr Wicks?
"Tentrex Industries". - lt's a cover.
I work for the ClA.
Jesus, your assignment for today
was to go out and kidnap a girI.
Look it up. "Tentrex lndustries".
And Iook up the number for the ClA in
New York. - You mean it's Iisted?
Under US Government Agencies.
ls this what you do?
This photography?
lt's the same number. You could have
had the card made. - But I didn't.
You reaIly get into it, don't you?
- Sit down!
l toId you I had a friend.
I take 1 5,5/34. What size are you?
- What are you, a cIown?
l'm scared! - So am I! - What for?
You've got a gun! - Yes!
That is not enough.
I work for the ClA,
I'm not a spy.
I just read books.
We read everything
that's published in the worId.
And we feed the plots,
dirty tricks, codes
into a computer and the computer
checks against
actual ClA plans and operations.
l Iook for leaks,
I look for new ideas.
We read adventures
and novels and journaIs ...
Who'd invent a job like that?
Listen!
People are trying to kilI me! - Who?
- l don't know, but there's a reason.
There is a reason!
And l just need some safe quiet time
to puIl things together.
Here?
- Here.
lt's onIy fair ...
Where's the guy with the shirts?
- He's skiing in the Green Mountains.
We want to go cross-country skiing
for a couple of weeks.
Away from everything.
What time's the news go on? Six?
- Six o'cIock. - 40 Minutes.
No, please ...
Lie down against the walI.
Put this arm behind you.
Now you Iisten to me:
I am tired.
l've got to cIose my eyes for a whiIe.
l can't think straight.
lf you try to move
or climb off the bed,
l'Il know it. I'lI feel it,
and l promise I'lI hurt you.
Can't I stay in the other room?
l beIieve what you told me.
No, you don't.
I don't know if l do.
That includes Condor, of course.
Yes, l owe you Condor.
Otherwise ...
- "Otherwise" does not exist.
WiIl Condor take long?
- Do you want an estimate?
There is a time factor.
- AIways with you peopIe.
Condor is an amateur.
He's lost, unpredictable
and perhaps even sentimental.
He couId fooI a professionaI.
Not deliberateIy,
but preciseIy because he is Iost.
He doesn't know what to do.
UnIike Wicks, who has always been
entirely predictable.
The man Condor kilIed
in the alIey? - Some friend of his.
A close friend? - I suppose so. Why?
- It interests me.
What was his name?
- I don't know. He was nobody.
He was somebody for Condor.
Get his name and address.
Have it for me when I caIl you.
What about Wicks?
Do you want the firm to question him?
They wiIl, you know.
We don't want that.
Cost you nothing.
I was careIess with Condor.
Wicks wiIl be done for nothing.
What time is it?
- It's news time.
LoneIy pictures.
So?
You're funny.
You take pictures of empty streets
and trees without leaves ...
It's winter.
Not quite winter ...
They look like ...
... November.
Not autumn, not winter, in-between.
l Iike them.
Thanks.
The shootings behind
the Hotel Ansonia remain a mystery.
The victims' identities
have not been reveaIed ...
Victims?
Can you say anything about a motive?
- Not at present.
Have you identified the victims?
- Insurance company empIoyees. - What?
Did the victims know their assaiIants?
- AbsoIuteIy not.
One man dead, one seriously wounded
in an alIey in Manhattan.
And the man with the gun
is stilI at large. - Sam!
Jesus Christ, victims ...
What is he saying?
What happened in that alIey?
I didn't shoot him.
You shot somebody. - But not Sam!
Nobody in that alIey
said anything about the CIA.
But they were there.
You're telIing me ... - They had to
have been to change that story.
What did Higgins say?
He said he wouldn't be there.
The section chief was coming in ...
He'd have to reach Sam.
Sam wouId have to caIl Mae.
l need your car. - Grand theft! You
don't want troubIe with the poIice.
This guy in Vermont. What'Il he do
if you don't show up?
He probabIy caIl soon.
WilI he show up here?
- The gun gives you the right
to rough me up ... - Rough you up?
- Yes, what are you doing in my house?
Have l raped you?
- The night is young.
You don't believe anything l've said.
l beIieve
you're in trouble. In danger.
But l don't know what kind and I'm
not sure how much of it is made up.
It doesn't matter.
Wait a minute.
l'm trying to understand ...
What are you doing? Let me go!
You buIly!
Don't tie me up, please!
This is ...
... unfair!
- I know.
You're early.
Come on in.
Is Janice working Iate?
So is Sam.
Pour one for me, too, wilI you?
lt's their own fauIt
if we're zonked when they get here.
We'Il give 'em an hour and if they're
not here, it's just you and me,
just Iike old times ...
What is it?
What is it, Joey?
What's wrong?
How do you know Sam's working late?
What do you think he's doing?
- Did he calI? - 2 or 2:30.
What did he say exactIy?
He had the Center calI.
Who? - I didnt't recognize the voice.
lt wasn't the usuaI Iady.
Third damn time tonight.
lt's some creepy burglar.
l want you to get out of here.
- I can't, Joey, l'm cooking!
Go to BiIl and EiIeen's.
Stay there tilI l calI you.
Don't argue! Move!
Go upstairs and stay there.
Do what l'm telIing you!
Stay there.
I'lI calI you.
- Joey, you're scaring me!
Yours?
No.
Fifth floor, ladies' underwear.
Kids ...
Probably the same everywhere.
That's the second floor.
l do it alI the time.
After you.
- Go ahead.
Anybody here good with a coat hanger?
l Iocked my keys in my car.
I'lI give you some money.
You can't telI me you never busted
into a car before. 5 bucks.
l don't have much time.
Okay? Come on.
Alright, 5 bucks.
l want you to answer the phone.
l'm not answering any phone!
Answer it!
TelI him what a great
son of a bitch you are!
l want you to be casuaI and nice.
Where the heIl are you?
Ben?
- Who do you think it is?
You're supposed to be up here by now.
- l know ...
l was held up.
That's no excuse. Come on.
Does this trip matter to you?
lt matters.
- Yeah, sure ...
No, it does! - This has happened over
and over. Last minute some excuse.
No, this is different.
- What's up?
The car ...
... broke down.
- What broke down?
The generator went.
- That's gonna take for ever.
Maybe not.
I tried to caIl you before, but ...
The generator ...
... it's going to take too Iong.
Look, forget about the car.
Take the bus first thing tomorrow.
I'lI try.
Try ...?
What's going on? Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm fine.
- You don't sound so fine.
l wish you would understand.
I do. I do. It's just that
l'm disappointed, that's alI.
I realIy wanted
to be with you up here.
I know.
We'lI have time.
- Yeah.
Get the very first bus
out in the morning, okay?
Alright.
Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night.
Listen, l'Il be going.
In the morning.
Where?
Was it aIright?
AIright?
Outside. Was it safe?
l'm not sure.
l wish l knew more.
About you.
Yesterday ...
Today ...
I don't remember yesterday.
Today it rained.
Why did you tie me up Iike that?
You thought l'd calI the poIice.
l wouldn't have.
Why?
Sometimes ...
... l take a picture
that isn't like me,
but l took it, so it is like me.
l put those pictures away.
l'd Iike to see those pictures.
We don't know each other that weIl.
Do you know anybody that weIl?
I don't think
l want to know you very weIl.
you're going to live much longer.
WelI, I may surprise you.
You're not teIling the truth.
What? - You want somebody,
who's not gonna live much longer.
At Ieast somebody who'd be on his way.
You take pictures.
BeautifuI pictures ...
... of empty streets and trees
with no leaves in November.
Why haven't you asked me
to untie your hands?
How much do you want?
I just want to stop it.
For a few hours,
for the rest of the night.
Then l'Il go.
What was his name?
What did Higgins say?
Your Department Head'Il bring you in.
- l've never met him.
Anything in the early pouch?
HQ at Langley says there's no other
source to support your theory.
Wicks!
You didn't sIeep welI.
- You didn't?
No, you didn't.
You were up earIy.
I had some thoughts.
l've got a pIan.
l don't know
if it'Il work or not, but ...
... I'lI need your help.
- Have l ever denied you anything?
When things quiet down,
you reaIly are
a very sweet man to be with.
You had bad dreams.
You talked in your sIeep.
What did l say?
- Who's Janice?
Was she a voIunteer,
or a draftee like me?
She was ...
... a friend.
She's dead.
Do I have permission to shower?
- You don't have to heIp.
I'lI heIp. You can aIways depend on
the spy fucker.
I'm sorry ... - No.
- No, l didn't mean ...
l didn't mean to say that.
l'm realIy sorry.
l'd Iike to help you.
1 8 ... Isn't that ...?
- Yes.
A.I.D. in I.C.U. 1 098.
lnsured package for Katherine Hale.
Leave it on the stoop.
Somebody's got to sign for it.
She's not here.
Okay, you can sign.
Her name on top, yours on the bottom.
Wonderful. - Government pens.
l don't have another pen.
I'lI get one.
Now listen: You're okay.
You're okay!
Can you get dressed?
You're okay! Get dressed, hurry.
StelIa's Boutique.
Extension 1 891 , pIease.
- Pardon me?
ls this 662 3799?
- Yes, it is.
There's no extension 1 891 ? - We're
lucky if we have any phone service!
Operator.
What's the area code for Washington,
D.C.? - 202.
631 1 .
CIA, LangIey?
- 631 1 .
Extension 1 891 .
1 891 .
Let me speak to Mr. Wicks.
He's not here just now.
May I ask who's calIing?
How do you feel? Okay?
- What did you do to those peopIe?
What people?
l don't know who they are.
l fiIe a report
and a guy in Washington reads it.
Then he comes to New York to shoot me.
- Did you know him?
No. - Did you know the maiIman?
- No,
but the guy in Washington did. - And
the next one? - I won't wait for him.
Has he gone doubIe or dirty?
- l don't know, sir.
ls he stilI in New York City?
- I wouIdn't be.
Question: ls there an inteIligence
network undetected by the CIA,
Iinking Arabic-speaking countries
with Spanish-speaking?
We're aIready visibIe,
let's not become conspicuous.
If our agents aren't enough,
use freeIance.
Use whatever it requires, but end it.
Okay, Iet's get it over with.
Thanks.
AppIications are here.
See Mr. Addison. Turn right,
first door on your left.
Mr. Addison?
He's in CIearance.
You passed it on your Ieft.
Sorry, thank you.
I didn't get the job.
Looks good ...
l have this friend and he asked me
to give you a message.
Quote: "Mr Higgins, this introduces
a friend of mine, 'Sparrow Hawk'.
PIease accompany her
to the Nassau Street exit, now."
PersonalIy, l'd do it,
because he has this huge gun
and he's Iooking at us right now.
l'Il save this for you. ShalI we?
To your left, pIease.
Okay, sit up!
Back up against the paneI.
Take it easy, I'm not armed.
They could be DF-ing us if you have a
transmitter hidden. What's this?
DF? You do read everything, don't you?
- Something is rotten in the Company!
You never compIained tilI yesterday.
- You never kiIled my friends before!
Who's she?
- Who hit the Lit. Society?
We had a big meeting about that.
Your name came up.
"Five Continents Imports".
Ring a belI?
Where did you get that?
- The maiIman.
The one you sent
with the uniform, automatic gun ...
We never use mailmen. - Would you
know a taIl bIond man, 6ft 4?
Strong like a farmer, not American.
Accent, maybe Alsace-Lorraine?
Yes?
- Was the letter delivered?
The return receipt has not arrived.
- You shouId have done it yourseIf.
A more complicated package
had to be handIed.
But l might have
underestimated this one.
I was toId
you never make that kind of mistake.
What wiIl you do?
- Wait.
Then what? - PeopIe who move
Ieave word of change of adress.
l want to see that report.
- Do you know him?
ProfessionaIly, yes.
- He kilIs peopIe!
Yes.
He works for the Company?
- Did once. He's a contract agent.
Freelance.
Where did you see him?
It would heIp if l knew.
- Help who?
Who'd hire him now?
- Anybody. - Terrific answer!
I know.
- What's his name?
When I knew him, Joubert.
Who'd hire him?. You don't Iook him up
in the YeIlow Pages! - Right.
Have to be somebody in the Community.
- Community?
lnteIligence field. - "Community"?
You guys are kind to yourseIves!
l want to see that report. - It went
to headquarters and disappeared.
Who read it?
- You mean besides Wicks?
You teIl me.
l pick up traces of an inteIligence
network the company doesn't know.
And I report it. Now why is that
going to make anybody mad?
Unless it was the Company's network
and you didn't want it blown!
Somebody is lying, Higgins.
Come on. Why is everybody so shy?
I'm not shy.
I don't know. That's what worries me.
l don't know.
- Ask Wicks. - Wicks died.
Someone yanked him off the
Iife-support system at the hospital.
Get me in, Higgins.
What good wouId that do, if they are
inside, what good wouId that do?
What should l do?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
l get it.
You expect me to draw fire!
Like a penny arcade bear parading
back and forth waiting for somebody!
And you'lI pick him up
before he does it, or after?
l'm gonna cross-check aIl the names.
Nice taIking to you, Higgins.
- Wait, where wilI l find you?
I'lI find you.
Do you trust him?
Trust ...
- Does he trust you?
He can't trust anybody. - How couId
anybody sneak in and fool them?
Maybe nobody did. - Then ...
Maybe there's another ClA ...
... inside the ClA.
The light's gone off!
lt's a hoteI room.
- What hoteI?
There's no tag. It's Room 81 9 in New
York. - There's a code on the edge.
You in the trade?
l read about it in a story.
- A story about locksmiths?
The Iock manufacturer
can give you the name of the hoteI.
l don't want to read
about you in the newspapers.
WiIl you make the calI?
l'm doing a survey.
Do you beIieve the condor
is an endangered species?
Your room number, please.
- 81 9.
I just had an interesting calI.
- Who is this?
In reference to
an aIl but extinct bird, the condor.
Have you had such a caIl?
- You're a fool to calI me here!
You had no such calI?
- No.
Must have been the Audubon Society.
They're stilI in New York City.
Langley, Computer.
State your program at the tone.
G ... Carriage return.
TRS. Tone, symbol for number.
Computer is ready.
That number is 202-227-0098.
CNA, Mrs. Coleman.
HaroId Thomas, Customer Service
requesting a CNA on ...
... 202-227-0098.
One moment pIease.
That would be
Mr. Leonard Atwood, 365 Mackenzie Pl.,
Chevy Chase, Maryland.
Cross-check this tape against Wicks
and hoId for any intersects.
Hat size ...
"Lucifer" ...
- Alright, run "Lucifer".
I'lI be damned.
This is the Major.
- Condor. Find me Higgins.
Routing you, Condor. Stand by.
HelIo, Condor.
Holiday Inn, 57th Street.
- Is that where you are?
Room 81 9. If you move it, you'Il find
the Alsatian. - Where are you?
Where are you, Condor?
- Quiet down ...
Higgins?
Yeah, I'm right here.
Who is Atwood?
Where are you, Higgins?
Aren't we pals anymore?
Something?
Major?
- Got him!.
Let me see that.
What's he doing in BrookIyn?
We can get ...
- Wait!
What's going on? - The son of a bitch
wired together 50 phones!
What? - Everybody in BrookIyn
is talking to each other!
I didn't know you smoked.
- I quit three years ago.
You Iook paIe.
- lt's the Iight in here.
What wiIl you do there?
See a guy.
- More secrets ...
Like those pictures you hide.
Yes ...
Someday I'd like to show them to you.
If you Iive through this.
You could drive me to Washington.
No.
You have a lot of very fine quaIities.
But ...
- What fine quaIities?
You have good eyes.
Not kind, but they don't Iie,
and they don't Iook away much
and they don't miss anything.
I could use eyes like that.
You're overdue in Vermont.
Is he a tough guy?
He's pretty tough ...
What wiIl he do?
- Understand. ProbabIy.
Boy ...
That is tough.
AIl aboard for Baltimore
and Washington D.C..!
Kathy ... I need time.
Eight hours or so, that's alI.
TilI noon, to do what I have to do.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- No.
Are you going right to Vermont?
Yes.
What I mean is, don't calI anyone.
Don't stop, pIease.
Don't teIl anyone about ...
Jesus, I didn't ...
Hey, you take care of yourself.
- l'Il do my best.
Do your best.
Why aren't you further along?
- With the Company, sir?
You seem perfect for it.
Are you perfect for it, Mr. Higgins?
I try to be, sir.
You were recruited out of schooI?
- No, interviewed in Korea.
You served with
CoIoneI Donovan in the OSS?
l saiIed the Adriatic
with a movie star at the helm.
lt doesn't seem like
much of a war now, but it was.
I go even further back than that.
Ten years after the Great War,
as we used to caIl it
before we knew enough to number them.
Do you miss that kind of action?
- No.
I miss that kind of clarity.
Yes?
Thank you.
He's being heId at New York Center.
Mr. Higgins, you do understand
the Company's position?
There's nothing in the way
of your doing this, is there?
What is this? What's going on?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm Condor.
Sit down.
What do you do for a living?
Don't be ridiculous.
What do you do ...
... exactly?
Deputy Director of Operations.
What section?
- Middle East.
What are you working on?
What are you doing?
What's the secret worth murdering
everybody at the A.L.H.S.?
There's no secret.
- Wicks showed you my report.
Yes.
lt was your network l turned up.
Doing what?
What does Operations care about
a bunch of books, a book in Dutch?
A book out of VenezueIa ...
Mystery stories in Arabic.
What is so important about ...
... oil fieIds?
OiI ...
That's it, isn't it?
This whoIe damn thing was about oiI!
Wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
Don't turn around.
Put your thumb on the hammer.
ReIease it sIowly.
Set down the gun on the desk.
Don't move.
You were quite good, until this.
This move was predictable.
What?
Did you touch anything eIse?
You're working for the Company again!
The desk? The lamp?
Jesus, they took you back!
Just for this. For Atwood.
He's with the Company! Why ...?
l'm not interested in "why", more in
"when", sometimes "where".
Always "how much".
l suspect
he was becoming an embarassment.
As you are.
So you're not finished?
- Pardon?
Oh, no, l had no arrangement
with the Company concerning you.
They didn't know you wouId be here.
l knew you would.
Didn't you send the maiIman?
That was a business
arrangement with Atwood.
But you see ...
Come on.
TeIl me about the girl.
What about the girl?
She was chosen ... how?
By age? Her car? Appearance?
- At random.
Chance.
- ReaIly ...?
Can l drop you?
l'd Iike to go back to New York.
You have not much future there.
lt wilI happen this way:
You may be walking,
maybe the first sunny day of spring.
And a car wiIl slow beside you,
and a door wiIl open
and someone you know, even trust,
wiIl get out.
And he wilI smile. A becoming smiIe.
But he wilI Ieave open the car door
and offer to give you a Iift.
You seem to understand it aIl so welI.
What wouId you suggest?
PersonalIy, l'd prefer Europe.
- Europe? - Yes.
The fact is,
what I do is not a bad occupation.
Someone is aIways wilIing to pay.
l would find it ...
... tiring. - Oh, no, it's
quite restfuI. It's aImost peacefuI.
No need to beIieve in either side,
or any side.
There is no cause.
There's onIy yourself.
The beIief is in your own precision.
l was born in the US, Joubert.
I miss it when I'm away too long.
A pity.
l don't think so.
Can you drop me at the station?
It would be my pIeasure.
For that day.
Higgins!
Why do calI so Iate?
We were worried. - Likewise.
ls the car for me? - Yeah, it's safe.
You have a few hours of debriefing.
Let's say for the purposes of
argument, I had a .45 in my pocket,
you'd take a walk with me, right?
Which way?
West. SlowIy.
Stay in front of me 3 or 4 steps.
Where are we going?
Wave them on ahead.
Do we have plans
to invade the Middle East?
Are you crazy?
- Am I?
Do we have pIans?
- No, absolutely not.
We have games. That's aIl.
We pIay games. What if?
How many men? What would it take?
How can we destabilize a regime?
That's what we're paid to do.
- WaIk on.
Go on.
So Atwood just took the games too
seriousIy. He was reaIly gonna do it.
Renegade operation. There was no way.
Not with the heat on the Company.
What if there hadn't been any heat?
What if I hadn't stumbled on the plan?
Different baIl game.
There was nothing wrong with the pIan.
The plan was alright.
The plan wouId've worked.
What is it with you peopIe?
You think not getting caught lying
is the same as teIling the truth?
No. lt's simpIe economics.
Today, its oiI.
ln 1 0 or 1 5 years it'Il be food,
pIutonium. Maybe even sooner.
What do you think the peopIe
wilI want us to do then?
Ask them.
- Not now, then.
Ask them when they're running out.
Ask them when there's no heating.
When their engines stop.
When people who've never
known hunger go hungry.
They won't want us to ask them,
they'Il just want us to get it.
Boy ...
... have you found a home!
7 peopIe were kiIled.
- The Company didn't order it!
Atwood did.
And who is Atwood?
He's alI you guys.
7 peopIe kiIled.
And you pIay fucking games!
Right.
And the other side does too.
That's why we can't
Iet you stay outside.
Go on home.
Go on. They've got it.
Just look around.
That's where they ship from.
They've got aIl of it.
What did you do?
l toId them a story.
You pIay games. I told them a story.
Oh, you poor dumb son of a bitch!
You've done more damage than you know.
l hope so.
You'Il be a very IoneIy man.
It didn't have to end this way.
- lf course it did.
How do you know they'Il print it?
You can take a waIk
but how far if they don't print it?
They'Il print it.
How do you know?
SubtitIes
Susan Bahren