Costgard Sector Command.
How I can take your call?
Sir.
- Do not have a new...
...baby to be home to?
I'll stay as you have a 456 line 4...
Captain Maine.
- What?
How big?
OK. On my way.
Problems sir? - Bring me to Snives
- Mr immediately...
'He called me sir?
- No, Snives...
But since no one else.
- Sorry sir, good morning.
I think this morning there is nothing good.
Watch where you walk.
I'd rather see someone die rather than
give mouth to mouth resuscitation...
Still not sure
- I am sure is coming.
You're a hopeless case.
Your boyfriend is here...
It's so great.
- The planes are great girl.
This is monumental.
Are we?
I changed my mind, your
dad has to come now.
Really, why?
Well, I think you have to know someone.
What?
I thought you had...
...it in your hands.
Besides does not like your dad?
No, I would hate if I met him, believe me.
Good is the boat owner.
Well to address.
How are you?
How are you, having a good time?
Enjoy, How are you? Hello, hello...
Look at this, hi.
- Can I have your...
...autograph please...
Sure, what's your name honey? - Tamy.
- I like that name...
Tamy Here.
- I also could have your...
...autograph please?
Sure, what's your name?
- Bruneo...
I like that name.
- Now make safer than old.
Only bad children for safety
are not permitted...
Hi, Dad. - Amy
- Let me guess, work.
There is a glacier that want to investigate.
Dad the boat is amazing there
is nothing to worry about.
Not that I worry about the outside.
We talked about this, how
much is in that boat?
We agreed that it was good for me.
Yes, but that was before I realized...
...the rush to put him on
the anniversary was...
Dad, the boat passed inspection?
- With the just...
We M.
- Baby I have to hang...
...up, then talk...
Bye.
- Te Quie...
What's wrong sir?
- No, that's fine...
Hi Glen. - Amy Maine, Good to see you.
- Ditto...
Welcome aboard the Titanic II.
- Thank you, you have good day.
You also.
Amy, that good that could come.
Yes, everything looks nice
you did a great job...
How is your dad?
- OK...
See ya.
- Bye.
Ladies and gentlemen I thank
you all for coming.
On this day come with me to
the history of this country.
And that he sees a good future
and establish a new path.
A day in which the loss of the lives
of the predecessor of this boat.
Will be replaced with the memory of the
larger boat, fast, and sophisticated...
...ever built, the Titanic II.
I want to introduce the man
who will guide this ship.
Will ship's Captain Howard.
I hope you all enjoy as we all.
And we enter the history book...
Will not you come to lunch?
- I had lunch 5 minutes ago...
How dull.
- Do not let them bite you...
All passengers are on board sir.
- Well...
Let's make history.
- Yes sir.
Control tower this is the
6565 Coast Guard change.
How will 6565 Copy Captain?
We will land in a couple
of minutes, during...
The Coast Guard will be on hold.
- Do you have another bad...
...presentimiendo Captain?
You could say...
There is the camp.
- Yes sir I see...
The Coast Guard is here.
- Really?
They should give a smaller...
It is very far
- I'll leave it on just in case...
Dr Kim Patterson.
- Nice.
Insurance will wonder why you asked to
come but his reputation precedes him.
And I need someone serious when I
say that we are on a time bomb.
I'm listening.
The wave of collapse yesterday
went to northern Canada.
The piece of ice that fell from collapse,
is the size of Manhattan.
I figured it would make a
piece of ice that size.
I guess we push to mid-Atlantic.
Across the Atlantic.
These measures are mass balance.
That when the temperature increases
the balance shifts.
The ice show.
These tests tell us that the
ice in which we are now.
Thickness has decreased
60 meters in a year...
It's awesome.
- Exactly.
I think there is anything you
would like to see follow me.
Of course there is global warming true...
Can you tell me what
the hell am I watching?
The collapse of yesterday.
God.
Have you ever thought of
Captain Armageddon?
If yesterday's collapse was only a trifle
the following will be colossal.
Now imagine the Atlantic Ocean.
Do you admire your masterpiece?
Yes, I did Do not be late for your party?
It's my boat, I think I will wait also
would like to enter with a girl...
You know, I called you.
- Yes.
If only be delayed six months.
Your dad gave me a punch
in the nose you expect.
I found driving his boat at
2 am without his consent...
I think he was right.
- You're still the Daddy's girl.
Look Who's Talking.
I did not speak, I feel what happened to
your dad, I know how much he wanted.
Do not mention it.
Looks like you left in charge.
COA industries.
I always thought you'd end as coastguard.
Yeah, well...
when you give the keys of an...
...empire is hard to refuse.
You still have the earrings that I gave you.
Yes, I have so many earrings.
Well, those like me.
You could have answered the call.
And then what...
pretend that all was as before?
Accept that you care more about your boat
and your money than you care about me.
Yeah well, your father did not need
controlling all my life paranoid.
Not talking about my father, talked to us.
You chose a different life
is fine, I understand.
And it seems that you are happy
with the decision you made.
You better back in does not
want to miss your party.
Good lord the Titanic time goes well.
Wait, hold it steady.
We are stable, naval
readings to 31 degrees...
Is it true?.
- How so?
The same reading as 100 years ago.
Well, only this time we
have enough lifeboats.
I also believe that this time
also avoid the icebergs.
Yes sir.
Lord, I have to remind.
We have not yet deployed the propellers...
Yes... we need to accelerate
- Relax.
May resemble its predecessor
but inside is much better.
Yes sir...
How long before we collapse?
- Hard to say.
But when you do the North Atlantic
will be devastated by the wave.
What was that?
Go back.
Upload.
Now Mr...
...is tracking the satellite.
But we do not have much time to report...
A tsunami alert.
- James I already did.
The warning is being given at this time.
We will need the navy, coast
guard, national guard...
...and all we can when this thing hit...
How long do we have
- I can see.
No time.
Hand me the alert center readers
are going to need SNA.
We have to find out how
fast this thing moves.
And send me all the information
we need to move fast.
Sir and vessels are at sea?
The boats are well, the
Tsunami is dangerous...
...only when it reaches the coast.
Ships at sea should not be affected.
That's not entirely true captain
of the surface ships maybe yes.
But everything below will
be affected particularly...
...throughout the north Atlantic...
Ice?
- Exactly.
There may be a layer of ice beneath the
surface in several feet produndidad.
So if the wave strikes, can push.
Okay.
Abo, listen.
We need to send a warning.
All the ships of the Atlantic tell them
not to come to any signs of ice.
Again tell them to stay away
from the ice blocks...
Consider it done James
- And one more thing...
Do you also have a view on the Titanic?.
- We are monitoring all James...
What you need
- check what is the...
...marina in the area...
Check your position
- Copying...
Sir, we have redirected.
- Where?
North Latitude 40 Ñ” 45
West Longitude 50 Ñ” 14.
We'll confirm it's okay.
Let's move.
Speak the Coast Guard is a Tsunami
alert in the North Atlantic.
Again there is a warning...
Captain.
Did you know that the Titanic was warned
six times on icebergs and did nothing?
Ignoring his position was true.
On hate...
Nursing.
- Ladies I need one...
...of you in the port...
We are in the midst of an
important conversation.
No matter.
I need one of you to get passengers.
We are on track.
Why are escorting passengers
to the lower chambers?
Yes sir.
Good evening ladies and gentlemen can
provide me your attention please.
All passengers of the Titanic please.
Come by my front door and
go to the elevators.
And go to the ground floor
this is a precaution.
No need to worry thanks...
How long?.
- Just M.
The Coast Guard gave the alert.
- Coast Guard...
What the hell caused it?
- An iceberg collapsed...
On the coast of Greenland
- We are ready for icebergs.
Not the lord but the Tsunami
iceberg coming fast sir.
How long?
We are waiting for the Coast Guard.
- Captain, that we...
...will pass under...
Do not even feel.
- Coast Guard Captain...
...communication...
Here the Captain Howard.
- Captain James Howard here on.
Maine Coast Guard Captain.
We listened...
Do you see any iceberg in your area?
- Mr Negative.
Lord I need to reverse the
direction of your boat.
Mr.
This wave is moving with
incredible strength.
Any ice on the way the wave moves.
I need you to contact the
West as soon as possible.
It is the only chance to avoid ice.
For God's sake James I know
this looks dangerous.
But I remind you that this is the Titanic II.
Equipped with radar ice that are activated
within a radius of 5 yards.
Hayden this wave travels
at 842 miles per hour.
Now 5 yards will not make a difference.
If any ice will reach you flip the boat.
Do what it says.
How long do we have?
How long for the impact?
- 15 minutes maximum.
They have 15 minutes maximum.
God...
What is our distance?
- 40 degrees and heading...
...northeast at 30 miles...
How long?.
- Mr Anytime...
Shoot. - Lord if you do...
- Do.
Mr. 2000... 5000 meters Lord strike us.
Prepare for impact...
Captain at 50 knots.
- We're in 40...
It's not fast enough.
- Mr Walsh, I can remember...
The engines are not well tested yet...
If the press...
- They have been built...
...to withstand speed...
Put them in 50.
- Yes sir...
Put in 50 knots
- Yes sir.
All to please the ground floor
there is no need to panic...
Madeleine.
- People are going crazy...
What?
- You think climate caution...
Is all this fuss about the weather?.
- That's all they told me.
If something is wrong.
We answer Amy.
Hello, just call Amy Maine leave
a message after the tone.
Amy talks to you about your dad, listen.
Something is happening, there is a tsunami
that will go through the North Atlantic.
Your boat will reach in a few minutes
I want you to pay attention.
Away from the ground floor.
There are chunks of ice in your direction.
Take as many people as possible
to higher levels.
Stay in the center of the boat.
And if something happens, permance
calm and get on a lifeboat...
Be careful honey.
- Is your daughter?
Yes, a nurse.
- Lord.
We have very little fuel M.
Where you can stock up?
- In the Canadian coast...
In the San Juan hub.
- Take us there faster.
Yes sir...
We are at 50 knots Captain.
- Very well...
Lord lost the first mover.
- Turn it off...
We can not.
- We can not lose the other.
We can not stop this ship...
This boat has three engines.
- Do you want to...
...fly the other 3?
We both know that the
engines have not been...
...properly installed, have to be cooled...
Turbines.
- The turbine will...
...consume more fuel.
We can not let go slow.
We are adrift.
We turn on the alarm being dragged.
Keep calm happens all the time.
Happens all the time make
it right and climb...
...the pattern is well.
Attention, Captain speaking.
All passengers please lifejackets.
This is not a drill I repeat, not a drill.
Attention, attention.
Your captain speaking.
All passengers please lifejackets.
This is not a drill,
I repeat not a drill.
I know the same thing I'm sorry
you'll find information.
Talk to them and let you know.
No, no panic stop.
Captain.
Everybody Moving...
A starboard now
- We hit.
Maidem, maidem this is the
Titanic II calling the U.S.
Coast Guard.
Maidem, maidem this is the
Titanic II calling the U.S.
Coast Guard.
Titanic II, Captain James
Maine speaks of the U.S.
Coast Guard...
What is your situation?
- Mr collided with an iceberg...
We need immediate assistance.
- Captain I think we...
...have another problem.
We filled it with water.
All the bow water is filling up fast.
That will cut the power
to lower the lifeboats...
How many?
- Of all...
We have a dinghy.
- And the boats tied?
They are small or even float...
The little pot.
- They were not designed...
...to withstand a collision...
Not anticipate being beaten by his side.
- What is he saying?
We must continue...
If we keep filling our water we will sink.
- How long?
2 hours, maybe three.
- What else?
We sink...
Prepare all is well and evacuate
all the boats that we have.
Women and children first.
It seems that history repeats itself.
Mr Walsh have to remove it.
Come on, we need him to safety.
Let...
Between sir.
- And the passengers?
We have to upload the fix.
Listen to me, goes to most people
as possible in the helicopter...
Mr Walsh is the procedure
- the procedure I do not care...
It's my boat, do it
- Yes sir.
Okay, you catch me out of here.
Arise.
I have received under the glacier activity.
Near the area of collapse.
If successful will mean that unstable ice.
What are you saying?
If collapses.
A greater mass of ice fall into the Atlantic.
Creating a mega tsunami toward
the Atlantic Coast.
How big?
Everything in its path will be devastated.
We have to get people out of the Titanic II.
James we have a rescue squad.
The marina is 40 miles west of them.
They will find the Titanic in an hour.
That boat does not have an hour.
We need planes and helicopters
in the area immediately.
Captain of the Titanic have enough boats.
We may not have seen the
end of this collapse...
...if there is another wave, these
boats will not change anything.
And my daughter is in that boat.
I understand.
Everyone calm.
No, please sir.
Let me let go...
Lord have to go back.
- Please Lord ago.
Come women we.
Sorry we have to go.
Madeline helps...
Amy.
- Come.
Let me help you.
Ladies first.
No, I'm staying here I'll stay.
One more go.
Only women...
How far?
- 30 minutes Mr.
We will supply us.
There's a boat on the way
if we do not reach.
It is good that we refuel
and go back to the boat.
Yes sir.
Patterson.
Gone.
I want to put them all aircraft
that we fly now...
Mr.
- What?
I think this has to do...
This is a pre-existing right.
- No, sir.
Is twice.
I need another group of
women going around here.
We girls have to take them out.
Put on lifejackets...
I have to go...
- Sign in...
Come on ladies.
- Madeline...
Where is Kelli?
- I have not seen, is in nursing.
I'll see...
Get off me.
- Amy...
Are you okay? - Yes I'm okay
- You have to go on a boat.
No I have to go to the nurse
I think Kelly is there.
It's in the basement will not get last time.
I will not go without it...
Okay I'll go with you.
- It's all your fault.
What is it, Get off me.
There are more important things like
wear a life jacket and board a boat...
Are you okay?
- Yes, we.
I know another way...
Kelly.
- God.
Kelly...
It hurts.
- Okay we will remove you.
Hence we will remove you'll be fine...
Only resists
- Put pressure...
Press the wound.
- Whatever it quick.
Okay.
- You'll be fine.
Hurry.
I need a card...
Cover the wound. - Yes
- Do.
Let's hurry.
Where is the tape?
'Where's the tape?
You have to relax Kelly, resists.
I have it.
Okay, I have...
You'll be fine.
- You have to hurry.
Breathe...
Kelly are you okay?.
- Stay here.
We need you out of here.
Put your arm around me You'll be fine.
We shall produce from here...
Are there any boats?
- We have to let go.
Help, please.
Carefully.
Chief Engineer Speaks Daniels if anyone
here I can hear the turbine hall.
Let's hurry up, we all come, come.
Sign in...
If someone else has to go with you
- Yes sir...
Are you okay?
- Yes.
Let's all please follow me...
Please.
- Are all inside?
Hold on strong.
What was that? Carefully...
Is there another way?
- Yes, we can use the elevators...
Elevators?
- We have no choice.
U.S. Coast Guard to Titanic II.
U.S.
Coast Guard to the.
Titanic II, change.
Again the U.S.
Coast Guard to Titanic II.
Change...
Captain Maine.
- Captain, talk.
We are sinking.
Captain has to get his people
from the lifeboats.
Half of the boats have been evacuated.
The lifeboats are traps.
Enter.
I understand Captain comes another wave.
God does not.
Are you there?
Captain.
Lord's time to resupply.
We must do this fast friends...
...6565's copy.
- Roger.
Mr.
My God...
We must go up.
- Climb, climb repeat...
Baby you okay?
- If...
Kelly are you okay?.
- If.
Take my shirt.
What happened?
I do not know, I think they flew turbines.
Everything will collapse...
You're bleeding. - I'm fine.
- I have to get points.
I'll tell you if we leave it alive.
I'll let me put all the points
you want, we have to go.
Put your foot in my hands, let...
On the count of three list.
- One. two... three...
Push it going, keep pushing.
- You are stuck.
It should have collapsed this is wrong.
My cell phone.
My dad, answer.
Dad
- Amy...
Are you in a lifeboat?
- No, we are caught.
The ship is sinking How do you catch?
Kelly Hayden and I are stuck in an elevator.
Hear, hear help is on the way.
I also.
I want them to stay away
from the lifeboats...
Do not get any.
- What do you mean?
CariÑ
This really is the worst.
- What?
When it wipe out everything
including lifeboats.
Not survive.
Your best bet is to stay in the boat.
You can flip but it is strong
and the wave drag is not.
James 'how long do we have?
As 30 minutes 'Hayden is another
diving equipment?
Sure...
Can you get there
- I think so.
Okay, we will resist until we get there.
Once I did think you were
an honorable man.
Let me think again my daughter is there...
Dad I'm so scared
- I know darling, it's okay.
Do as I say and you will be well...
If we do not?
- Not even mention it.
Okay we'll get there baby on the way.
Goodbye Dad.
James, if you do what
you say has a chance.
Yes.
Care...
Get out of here.
- We will remove you.
Give me your hands...
Kelly.
- Kelly let.
Take my hand Ready?
Let.
Come and.
Now you.
Take my hand.
I have you.
Let.
Follow up.
You have to hurry up.
Let.
Come up.
Follow me...
The door is locked.
- I thought he left open the...
Supposedly.
- Is to protect the boats.
Fast Pass.
Hurry.
Spend.
I can not spend too narrow.
Amy, we.
Let.
We will be closed.
I believe I can go, push...
Pasa. - Amy ax
- I know.
Return...
Kelly.
- No.
Kelly, no, no.
I'm sorry Kelly.
Amy, you did everything you could.
We must go, please.
If we have died for nothing.
Come on, get out of here.
Waiting.
Let.
The ship is falling apart.
We fry them, we must think
in a way we can not return...
We will have to go up
- What would you change that?
Until we touch the wires or the ground.
We do not electrocute a...
Do not know.
- You are a nurse.
I am not technical I do not know electricity.
There is only one way to find out.
Let's your turn.
I do not know if I can not
know if I can jump as high.
Amy can do it we have to hurry.
I can not and if I fall.
Let your dad come soon Amy...
Salta.
- Vale.
You can do jumps.
Well-done.
We'll come to me.
Come on, well done.
Still, almost.
We already have it.
You're almost there remains.
Continue.
I slip, I fall...
I fall.
- I'll come for you.
Hold on, I'll go for you hurry I slip.
I will not let you fall expected.
Hurry please.
Give me your hand.
Are you okay?
Follow me.
Let.
I have you, you did...
Are you okay? - Yes
- We're almost there.
Wait listen do you hear?
People trapped.
- We need to help.
I'll leave you where did your
father and come to aydudarles...
No, we do not have time for that.
- Vale.
Come with me...
Where next?
- Over there.
We are close...
Let's open the door.
- Help.
Is stuck.
Help me, I'm here...
Help.
- Hell's door is jammed.
Curse...
Damn, I can not.
- It is stifling.
Hear the door is stuck Can
you find another way out?
Are you there?
We will respond, are you there.
Bastard...
I killed him
- Hayden's not your fault...
It's my fault
- Listen Hayden.
I made a promise to my father.
Now come on, move.
Let.
Well I think I will have to go without me...
What now?
- We came here for you...
Quick put this on. - And you?
- Do not worry about me...
The water is frozen
- Put it Amy.
Hurry.
Let's hurry...
'Hurry?
Arms.
We have to go...
How much is missing?
- We are close to Mr.
Within 30 miles of the east side...
Think I'll make it
- We are near.
Amy you ok?
Yes What happened?
We headed the ship is upside down...
Can you move?
- Yes.
We have to go, stop...
Give me your hand.
- Is frozen.
We have to go give me your hand.
Are you okay?
- Yes...
Something is blocking the door.
- What can we do?
The water will rise faster
- Everything will be under...
...water in 5 minutes.
You have to get it.
Amy Turn around.
You have to leave...
Those are the planes?
- Yes if you came...
...to the room dive.
They will be there.
No good.
Each unit has a diving emergency tracker...
How it works
- have a tracking signal.
A low frequency we have.
Hayden is frozen water.
I'll keep you warm.
Do you?
I think the temperature is
the least of my concerns.
Lord I have a low frequency signal...
Seems to come from the Titanic II
- Mira.
How to get there?
Listen, I take off the suit.
Why? I use it not Forget.
Freeze to death.
First I'll drown.
We will share the oxygen
tank to keep breathing...
No. - Why?
- Freeze to death anyway.
So what's your plan?
Listen, this boat has air bags.
Caught.
Stop the sinking air that will give me.
Breathe deep and try to get...
Wait...
- Insurance and picked...
...up your signal...
Wait.
- You can find...
What about you?
- I'll drown.
If they can survive rapid...
No. - It is the only way
- No, Hayden.
Listen, be wise.
If we share the tank will die anyway.
And half of the air will.
I swear can relive.
You have more chance of survival.
But I do not like you...
This is my fault.
- No.
Come on, give me your arm...
What is your plan?
- I have to find...
How will you know where?
- No need to know...
James if the ship sinks,
the pressure will increase.
I know...
Everything that is below...
- Yes, you have to take care...
Here, take the end of it, and let me go
- What's this?
To find the way back there
you have 1000 feet.
Just let it go I'll be fine...
What if the string ends?
- I'll be dead...
Then cut the rope.
- M. Ready.
Now...
Hayden
- Sorry...
No holding out.
- No, no, no.
Amy, I did what did you
do what you gotta do...
Yes
- Then I wake up.
Put it.
Put the controller.
You'll have to jump.
There is a lifesaving equipment
you have to hurry back...
What about you?
- I will do my.
Go.
You have to hurry, jump.
Post it...
...1... 2...
Hayden Resist.
We breathe.
We Hayden.
Hayden breathes.
Damn.
Breathe.
We Hayden.
Hayden Breathe, breathe,
we breathe.
Hayden, no.
We Hayden.