(SONAR ECHOING)
(MUFFLED RADIO CHATTER)
MAN: 13 meters.
You should see it.
(MUFFLED RADIO CHATTER)
Okay, take her up
and over the bow rail.
MAN: (OVER RADIO) Mir2,
we're going over the bow.
Stay with us.
(SONAR ECHOING)
(VEHICLE WHIRRING)
(MUFFLED RADIO CHATTER)
MAN: Okay, quiet.
We're rolling.
Seeing her coming out of the
darkness like a ghost ship...
...still gets me every time.
To see the sad ruin of the
great ship sitting here...
...where she landed at
2:30 in the morning
of April 15, 1912...
...after her long fall...
...from the world above.
(SNORTS) You are so
full of shit, boss.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(CREAKING)
(SONAR ECHOING)
MAN: Dive 6. Here we are again
on the deck of Titanic.
2½ miles down.
3,821 meters.
The pressure outside is
3½ tons per square inch.
These windows are
9 inches thick.
If they go, it's sayonara
in to microseconds.
All right,
enough of that bullshit.
(VEHICLE WHIRRING)
Just put her
down on the roof of
the officers'
quarters like yesterday.
(OVER RADIO) Mir2,
we're landing right over
the Grand Staircase.
You guys set to launch?
Yeah, Brock.
Launching Dunkin now.
Go, Charlie.
(ROBOT WHIRRING)
TECHNICIAN: All right,
tether out.
Tether out.
TECHNICIAN: Okay,
Brock, we're dropping
down along the hull.
Yeah, roger that.
Okay, drop down and go
into the first
class gangway door.
I want you guys
working the D deck...
...reception area
and the dining saloon.
TECHNICIAN: Copy that.
BROCK: Tether out.
Okay, now left.
Left, left. Okay, coming left.
BROCK: Snoop Dog is
on the move.
We're headed
down the stairwell.
Okay Lewis,
drop down to B deck.
Okay, A deck.
BODINE: Give me
some rope, Captain.
B deck. Get in there.
Get in there.
(WHIRRING)
BROCK: Watch the door frame.
Watch it, watch it.
I see it. I got it.
(WHIRRING)
BROCK: We good?
Bring her down.
We're good. Just chill, boss.
BROCK: Okay, make your turn.
BODINE: Cable out, Captain.
BROCK: Make your turn.
Watch the wall.
Yeah Brock,
we're at the piano.
You copy?
BROCK: Okay, copy that.
BROCK: Okay, right
there. Right there.
Okay, that's it, that's it.
That's the bedroom door.
I see it. I see it.
We're in!
We're in, baby.
We're there.
(BROCK SIGHS)
That's Hockley's bed.
That's where the
son of a bitch slept.
(CHUCKLES)
BODINE: Oops.
Somebody left
the water running.
Hold it.
Hold it just a second.
Go back to the right.
(WHIRRING)
That wardrobe door.
Get closer.
You smelling something, boss?
I want to see what's under it.
BODINE: Give me
my hands, man.
(WHIRRING)
All right.
BROCK: Take it easy.
It might come apart.
Okay.
Go, go, go. Flip it over.
Flip it over. Go.
Turn her over.
Keep going.
Go, go, go.
Okay, drop it.
Oh, baby, baby.
Are you seeing this, boss?
It's payday, boys.
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN
RUSSIAN OVER PA)
(MEN CHEERING)
(APPLAUDING)
Cha-ching!
We did it, Bobby.
We brought it back, Baby.
Oh, yeah! Who's the best?
Who's the best, baby?
Say it. Say it. Say it.
You are, Lewis.
Bobby, my cigar.
Right here.
(CHEERING)
BROCK: Okay, crack her open.
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN
RUSSIAN OVER PA)
Shit.
No diamond.
You know boss, this same
thing happened to Geraldo
and his career
never recovered.
Turn the camera off.
MAN: Brock,
the partners would like
to know how it's going.
Hey, Dave, Barry, hi.
Look, I it wasn't
in the safe. But hey, hey...
...Don't worry about it.
There's still
plenty of places
it could be. Hell, yes.
The floor debris
in the suite,
the mother's room...
the purser's safe on C deck.
Jimmy Hoffa's briefcase.
BROCK: A dozen other places.
Guys, look, you're
just going to have
to trust my instincts.
I know we're close.
We've just got to
go through a little
process of elimination.
Hang on a second.
Let me see that.
BUELL: Ah, we may have
something here, guys.
Where's the photograph
of the necklace?
We'll call you right back.
I'll be goddamned.
REPORTER: (ON TV)
Treasure hunter Brock Lovett
is best known for
finding Spanish gold...
It's okay.
I'll feed you in a minute.
Now he has
chartered Russian subs
to reach the most famous
shipwreck of all, the Titanic.
He is with us
live via satellite
from
the research ship Keldysh...
...in the North Atlantic.
Hello, Brock.
BROCK: Hello, Tracy.
Of course, everyone knows
the familiar
stories of Titanic.
You know, the nobility of
the band playing to
the very end and all that.
But what I'm interested
in are the untold stories.
The secrets locked deep
inside the hull of Titanic.
And we're out here using
robot technology to go
further into the wreck...
...than anybody
has ever done before.
REPORTER: Your expedition
is at the center of a storm
of controversy...
...over salvage rights
and even ethics.
Many are calling you
a graverobber.
Well, nobody ever called the
recovery of the artifacts...
What is it?
Turn that up, dear.
I have museum-trained experts
sent out here making sure...
...that these relics
are preserved and
catalogued properly.
Take a look at this drawing
that we found just today.
A piece of paper
that's been underwater
for 84 years.
And my team are able to
preserve it intact.
Should this have
remained unseen
at the bottom of the
ocean for eternity...
...when we can see
and enjoy it now?
I'll be goddamned.
Brock!
There's a satellite
call for you.
Bobby, we're launching.
You see
these submersibles
going in the water?
Trust me, buddy.
You want to take this call.
This better be good.
Now, you gotta speak up.
She's kind of old.
Great.
This is Brock Lovett.
How can I help you, Mrs...?
Calvert. Rose Calvert.
Mrs. Calvert.
I was just wondering
if you had found...
...the "Heart of
the Ocean" yet, Mr. Lovett.
Told you you
wanted to take the call.
All right, you have
my attention, Rose.
Can you tell us who
the woman in the picture is?
Oh, yes. The woman
in the picture is me.
She's a goddamn liar!
Some nutcase seeking
money or publicity.
God only knows why.
Like that Russian babe,
Anesthesia.
They're inbound!
Rose De Witt Bukater
died on the Titanic
when she was 17, right?
BROCK: That's right.
If she had lived,
she'd be over 100 by now.
101 next month.
Okay, so she's a very
old goddamn liar.
Look, I've already done the
background on this woman...
...all the way
back to the 20s,
when she was working
as an actress.
An actress.
There's your first
clue, Sherlock.
Her name was
Rose Dawson back then.
Then she marries
this guy named Calvert.
They move to Cedar Rapids
and she punches out
a couple of kids.
Now Calvert's dead
and, from what I hear,
Cedar Rapids is dead.
And everybody
who knows about
the diamond is
supposed to be dead...
...or on this boat,
but she knows.
Doesn't exactly
travel light, does she?
Hurry up, give him a hand.
Mrs. Calvert,
I'm Brock Lovett.
Welcome to the Keldysh.
Okay, let's get
her inside there.
Hi, Miss Calvert.
Hi.
Welcome to the Keldysh.
Thanks.
PILOT: Hey!
(KNOCKING)
Are your staterooms
all right?
Oh, yes.
Very nice.
Have you met my
granddaughter, Lizzy?
She takes care of me.
We met just a few
minutes ago.
Remember, Nana?
Up on deck?
Oh, yes.
(BODINE TUTS)
There. That's nice.
Have to have my
pictures when I travel.
Can I get you anything?
Is there anything you'd like?
Yes.
I would like to
see my drawing.
BROCK: Louis XVI wore
a fabulous stone that was...
...called the Blue Diamond
of the Crown...
...which disappeared
in 1792...
...about the same time
old Louis lost everything
from the neck up.
The theory goes that
the crown diamond
was chopped, too.
Recut into a heart-like shape
that became known as...
...the Heart of the Ocean.
Today it would be worth
more than the Hope diamond.
(SCOFFS) It was a dreadful,
heavy thing.
I only wore it this once.
You actually think
this is you, Nana?
It is me, dear.
Wasn't I a dish?
(LAUGHS) I tracked it down
through insurance records.
An old claim that was
settled under terms
of absolute secrecy.
Can you tell me who the
claimant was, Rose?
I should imagine someone
named Hockley.
BROCK: Nathan Hockley,
that's right.
Pittsburgh steel tycoon.
The claim was for a
diamond necklace his son...
...Caledon,
bought his fiancée.
You.
A week before he
sailed on Titanic.
And it was filed right
after the sinking.
So the diamond had to have
gone down with the ship.
You see the date?
April 14, 1912.
Which means if
your grandmother
is who she says she is...
...she was wearing the diamond
the day the Titanic sank.
And that makes you
my new best friend.
These are some of the things
we recovered from
your stateroom.
This was mine.
(ROSE GASPS)
How extraordinary.
And it looks the same as it
did the last time I saw it.
(SIGHS)
Hmm.
The reflection has
changed a bit.
Are you ready to go
back to Titanic?
BODINE: Okay, here we go.
She hits the berg on
the starboard side, right?
She kind of bumps along...
...punching holes like
morse code...
...dit-dit-dit...
along the side...
...below the water line.
Then the forward compartments
start to flood.
Now, as the water
level rises...
...it spills over the
watertight bulkheads...
...which, unfortunately,
don't go any
higher than E deck.
So now as the
bow goes down...
...the stern rises up,
slow at first...
...then faster and faster...
...until finally,
she's got her whole ass
sticking up in the air.
And that's a big ass.
We're talking
20, 30,000 tons. Okay?
And the hull's not designed
to deal with that pressure.
So, what happens?
(CLICKING TONGUE)
She splits, right
down to the keel.
And the stern...
...falls back level.
Then as the bow sinks...
...it pulls
the stern vertical...
...and then finally detaches.
Now the stern section
just kind of bobs there
like a cork for
a couple of minutes...
...floods, and finally goes
under about 2:20 AM...
...2 hours and 40 minutes
after the collision.
The bow section
planes away...
...landing about a
half a mile away...
...going 20, 30 knots when
it hits the ocean floor.
(IMITATES EXPLOSIONS)
Pretty cool, huh?
Thank you for that fine
forensic analysis, Mr. Bodine.
Of course, the
experience of it was...
...somewhat different.
Will you share it with us?
(MUFFLED RADIO CHATTER)
(SONAR ECHOING)
(BAND PLAYING WALTZ)
(SIGHS)
Oh. (SOBBING)
I'm taking her to rest.
No.
Come on, Nana.
No!
Give me the
tape recorder.
Tell us, Rose.
It's been 84 years...
It's okay. Just try
to remember anything.
Anything at all.
Do you want to hear this
or not, Mr. Lovett?
It's been 84 years...
...and I can still smell
the fresh paint.
The china had
never been used.
The sheets had
never been slept in.
Titanic was called
the ship of dreams.
And it was.
It really was.
(CREWMEN SHOUTING)
(GULLS CRYING)
PORTER: All third-class
passengers...
...with a forward berth...
...this way please!
This queue!
It's a big boat, huh?
Daddy, it's a ship.
You're right.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
I don't see what all
the fuss is about.
It doesn't look any bigger
than the Mauretania.
You can be blasé
about some things, Rose...
...but not about Titanic.
It's over 100 feet longer
than Mauretania...
...and far more luxurious.
Your daughter is far too
difficult to impress, Ruth.
(LAUGHS) So this is the ship
they say is unsinkable.
It is unsinkable.
MAN: Sir, sir.
God Himself
could not sink this ship...
Sir!
What?!
You have to check
your baggage through
the main terminal.
It's round that
way, sir.
I put my faith in
you good sir.
Now kindly
see my man.
Yes sir. It's my
pleasure, sir.
If I can do
anything at all...
Yes, right.
All the trunks from
that car there.
12 from here.
And the safe,
to the parlor suite...
...rooms B-52, 54, 56.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Ladies...
...we better hurry.
Come along.
My coat?
MAID: I have it, miss.
PORTER: All third-class
passengers queue here
for health inspection.
Welcome aboard, ma'am.
Welcome to Titanic.
OLD ROSE:
It was the ship of dreams...
...to everyone else.
To me, it was a
slave ship...
...taking me back to
America in chains.
Outwardly, I was
everything a well brought
up girl should be.
Inside, I was screaming.
(SHIP'S HORN BLOWING)
(BOTH SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(ITALIAN ACCENT) Jack,
you are pazzo.
You bet everything
we have.
When you got nothing,
you got nothing to lose.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Sven?
(WATCH TICKING)
(TICKING CONTINUES)
All right,
moment of truth.
Someone's life is
about to change.
Fabrizio?
Niente.
Olaf?
Nothing.
Sven?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Uh-oh.
2 pair.
(TUTS) I'm sorry,
Fabrizio.
(SHOUTS IN ITALIAN)
I'm sorry...
...you're not gonna see
your mom again for a...
...long time...
...'cause we're
going to America.
Full house, boys! (WHOOPING)
(FABRIZIO LAUGHS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Oh!
(PATRONS LAUGHING)
Come on.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(KISSES) I'm going home!
(SHOUTING IN SWEDISH)
I'm going home. (LAUGHS)
I go to America!
No, mate.
Titanic go to America,
in 5 minutes.
Shit. Fabri.
Come on.
Come on,
here. Here.
We're riding in
high style now!
We're a couple of
regular swells.
We're practically
goddamn royalty...
...ragazzo mio.
You see?
Is my destino.
Like I told you...
I go to America to
be millionaire.
Whoa! Whoa!
(NEIGHING)
FABRIZIO: Bastardo.
JACK: Whoo!
You are pazzo.
Maybe, but I've
got the tickets.
Come on, I thought
you were fast.
Aspetta!
Whoa. Wait! Wait!
Hey, wait!
We're passengers!
Have you been through
the inspection queue?
Of course.
Anyway, we
don't have any lice.
We're Americans.
Both of us.
Right.
Come aboard.
We're the luckiest sons
of bitches in the world.
You know that?
(SHIP'S HORN BLOWING)
(SHOUTING)
(CHEERING)
JACK: Good-bye!
FABRIZIO: You know somebody?
Of course not.
That's not the point.
Good-bye!
I'll miss you!
I will never forget you!
(CHEERING)
(SHIP'S HORN BLOWING)
Come with me,
darling. Let's go.
G-60.
G-60. G-60.
Excuse me,
ma'am.
G-60.
Oh, right here.
Hey, how you doing?
Jack. Nice
to meet you.
Jack Dawson.
Nice to meet you.
How you doing?
Who says you get
top bunk, huh?
(FABRIZIO LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
This is your private
promenade deck, sir.
Will you be requiring
anything?
Mmm.
Excuse me.
GIRL: This one?
ROSE: No.
It had a lot of faces on it.
This is the one.
Would you like all of
them out, miss?
Yes. We need a little
color in this room.
Put in there.
In the wardrobe.
God, not those finger
paintings again.
They certainly were a
waste of money.
The difference between
Cal's taste in art...
...and mine is
that I have some.
They're fascinating.
Like being inside a dream
or something.
There's truth but no logic.
What's the artist's name?
Something Picasso.
He won't amount
to a thing.
He won't, trust me.
ROSE: Let's put the
Degas in the bedroom.
At least they were cheap.
Put it in the wardrobe.
OLD ROSE: At Cherbourg,
a woman came aboard
named Margaret Brown.
We all called her Molly.
History would call her
the Unsinkable Molly Brown.
Well, I wasn't about to
wait all day for you, sonny.
Here, if you think
you can manage.
OLD ROSE: Her husband
had struck gold
someplace out west.
And she was what Mother
called "new money."
By the next afternoon...
...we were steaming west
from the coast of Ireland...
...with nothing out ahead
of us but ocean.
Take her to sea,
Mr. Murdoch.
Let's stretch her legs.
Yes sir.
All ahead full, Mr. Moody.
Very good, sir.
(ENGINE TELEGRAPH RINGING)
(CHIMES)
All ahead full.
(RINGING)
All ahead full!
ENGINEER BELL: Come on lads,
step lively!
(ENGINEERS SHOUTING)
All right! Let's stoke
her right up!
We go full ahead!
Come on, put your
backs into it!
(WIND HOWLS)
21 knots, sir.
Hey, look,
look, look!
See it?
There's another
one! See him?
Look at that one!
Look at him jump!
(WHOOPING)
(STOKERS GRUNTING)
Whoo!
I can see the Statue
of Liberty already.
Very small,
of course.
I'm the king
of the world!
(WHOOPING)
(BOTH WHOOPING)
Yee-hah!
(HOWLING)
She is the largest
moving object
ever made by
the hand of man...
...in all history.
And our master shipbuilder,
Mr. Andrews here...
...designed her from the
keel plates up.
I may have knocked
her together, but...
...the idea was
Mr. Ismay's.
He envisioned a steamer
so grand in scale...
...and so luxurious in...
...its appointments...
...that its supremacy
would never be challenged.
And here she is.
Willed into solid reality.
CAL: Hear, hear.
I'll have the salmon.
You know I don't
like that, Rose.
She knows.
Hm. We'll both have
the lamb.
Rare, with very
little mint sauce.
Hm. You like lamb,
right sweet pea?
You gonna cut her meat
for her too there, Cal?
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, who thought of
the name Titanic?
Was it you,
Bruce?
Yes, actually.
I wanted to convey sheer size.
And size means stability...
...luxury, and above
all, strength.
Do you know of
Dr. Freud, Mr. Ismay?
His ideas about
the male preoccupation
with size might be of
particular interest to you.
(WHISPERS)
What's gotten into you?
Excuse me.
I do apologize.
She's a pistol, Cal.
Hope you can handle her.
Well, I may have to
start minding what she reads
from now on,
won't I, Mrs. Brown?
Freud? Who is he?
Is he a passenger?
FABRIZIO:
The ship is nice, huh?
MAN: (IRISH ACCENT)
Yeah. It's an Irish ship.
FABRIZIO: Is English, no?
No, it was built
in Ireland.
15,000 Irishmen
built this ship.
Solid as a rock.
Big Irish hands.
That's typical.
First-class dogs
come down here
to take a shite.
Lets us know where we rank
in the scheme of things.
Like we could forget?
(JACK LAUGHS)
I'm Tommy Ryan.
Jack Dawson.
Fabrizio.
Do you make any money
with your drawings?
Ah, forget it, boyo.
You'd as like have
angels fly out of your
arse as get next to...
...the likes of her.
(FABRIZIO LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT EXCHANGE)
OLD ROSE: I saw my whole life
as if I'd already lived it.
An endless parade
of parties and cotillions...
...yachts and polo matches.
Always the same narrow people,
the same mindless chatter.
I felt like I was standing
at a great precipice...
...with no one
to pull me back.
No one who cared...
...or even noticed.
(PANTING)
(ROSE SOBBING)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(ROSE PANTING)
(OCEAN ROARING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Don't do it.
Stay back.
Don't come any closer.
Come on.
Just give me your hand.
I'll pull you back over.
No!
Stay where you are.
I mean it.
I'll let go.
No, you won't.
What do you mean,
no I won't?
Don't presume to tell me
what I will and will not do.
You don't know me.
Well, you would
have done it already.
You're distracting me.
Go away.
I can't.
I'm involved now.
You let go,
and I'm going to have
to jump in there after you.
Don't be absurd.
You'll be killed.
I'm a good swimmer.
The fall alone
will kill you.
It would hurt. I'm not
saying it wouldn't.
Tell you the truth...
...I'm a lot more
concerned about that
water being so cold.
How cold?
Freezing.
Maybe a couple degrees over.
You ever, uh...
...ever been
to Wisconsin?
What?
Well, they have some of
the coldest winters around.
I grew up there,
near Chippewa Falls.
I remember when I was a kid,
me and my father,
we went ice fishing...
...out on Lake Wissota.
Ice fishing is,
you know, where you...
I know what ice fishing is!
Sorry.
You just seem like, you know,
kind of an indoor girl.
Anyway, I...
...fell through some thin ice.
And I'm telling you...
...water that cold,
like right down there...
...it hits you
like 1000 knives
stabbing you all
over your body.
You can't breathe.
You can't think.
Least not about
anything but the pain.
Which is why I'm not
looking forward to
jumping in there after you.
Like I said...
...I don't have a choice.
I guess I'm kind
of hoping you'll come
back over the rail and...
...and get me off
the hook here.
You're crazy.
That's what
everybody says but...
...with all due
respect, miss...
...I'm not the one hanging off
the back of a ship here.
Come on.
Come on,
give me your hand.
You don't want to do this.
Phew.
I'm Jack Dawson.
Rose De Witt Bukater.
I'll have to get you to
write that one down.
(ROSE LAUGHS)
Come on.
(ROSE SCREAMS)
(JACK GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
I got you.
Come on.
(SCREAMING)
Help, please!
(SCREAMING) Help!
Please, help me!
Listen. Listen to me.
I've got you.
I won't let go.
Now pull yourself up.
Come on!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Come on.
That's right.
You can do it.
(ROSE GRUNTS)
I got you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
What's all this?
(ROSE GASPING)
You stand back and...
...don't move an inch!
Fetch the Master at Arms.
This is completely
unacceptable!
What made you think
that you could put your
hands on my fiancée?!
Look at me, you filth!
Cal.
What do you think
you were doing?
Cal, stop.
It was an accident.
An accident?
It was.
Stupid, really.
I was leaning over
and I slipped.
I was leaning far over
to see the, uh...
...uh, uh, the uh...
Propellers?
Propellers, and I slipped.
And I would have
gone overboard
but Mr. Dawson here...
...saved me.
And almost went
over himself.
You wanted to see the...
She wanted to
see the propellers.
Like I said, women and
machinery do not mix.
Was that the way of it?
Yeah. Yeah, that
was pretty much it.
Well, the boy's a hero then.
Good for you, son.
Well done.
So, it's all's well and back
to our brandy, eh?
Look at you.
You must be freezing.
Let's get you inside.
Perhaps a little something
for the boy?
Of course.
Mr. Lovejoy,
I think a 20 should do it.
Is that the going rate
for saving the woman
you love?
Rose is displeased.
What to do?
I know.
Perhaps you could join us for
dinner tomorrow evening...
...to regale our group...
...with your heroic tale.
Sure.
Count me in.
Good.
It's settled then.
This should be interesting.
(WHISTLES)
Can I bum a smoke?
You'll want to tie those.
It's interesting...
...the young lady slipped
so suddenly...
...and you still had time
to remove your jacket
and your shoes.
(TUNE PLAYS ON MUSIC BOX)
(KNOCKING)
I know
you've been melancholy.
I don't pretend to know why.
I intended to save this...
...until the engagement
gala next week...
...but, I thought...
...tonight.
Good gracious.
(CHUCKLES)
Perhaps as a reminder
of my feelings for you.
Is it a...
Diamond. Yes. (LAUGHS)
56 carats to be exact.
It was worn by Louis XVI.
And they called
it Le Coeurde la Mer.
The Heart of the Ocean.
The Heart of
the Ocean. Yes. (LAUGHS)
It's overwhelming.
Well, it's for royalty.
We are royalty, Rose.
You know, there's
nothing I couldn't give you.
There's nothing
I'd deny you...
...if you would not deny me.
Open your heart to me, Rose.
JACK: Well, I've been on
my own since I was 15,
since my folks died.
And I had no brothers
or sisters or
close kin in that
part of the country...
...so I lit on out of
there and I haven't
been back since.
You could just call me
a tumbleweed
blowing in the wind.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Well, Rose,
we've walked about a mile
around this boat deck and...
...chewed over how
great the weather's
been and how I grew up...
...but I reckon that's
not why you came
to talk to me, is it?
(SIGHS) Mr. Dawson, I...
Jack.
I want to thank you
for what you did.
Not just for pulling me back,
but for your discretion.
You're welcome.
Look.
I know what you
must be thinking.
Poor little rich girl.
What does she know
about misery?
No.
No, that's not
what I was thinking.
What I was thinking was...
...what could have
happened to this girl
to make her think
she had no way out?
Well I...
It was everything.
It was my whole world and...
...all the people in it.
And the inertia of my life,
plunging ahead and me...
...powerless to stop it.
God,
look at that thing.
You would have gone
straight to the bottom.
500 invitations
have gone out.
All of Philadelphia
society will be there.
And all the while
I feel I'm...
...standing in the middle
of a crowded room...
...screaming at the
top of my lungs...
...and no one
even looks up.
Do you love him?
Pardon me?
You're being very rude. You
shouldn't be asking me this.
Well, it's a simple question.
Do you love the guy or not?
(SCOFFS)
This is not
a suitable conversation.
Why can't you just
answer the question?
(LAUGHS)
This is absurd.
You don't know me
and I don't know you...
...and we are not having
this conversation at all.
You are rude...
...and uncouth
and presumptuous and
I am leaving now...
...Jack. Mr. Dawson.
It's been a pleasure.
I sought you out to thank you
and now I have thanked you.
And you've insulted me.
Well, you deserved it.
Right.
I thought you were leaving.
I am.
You are so annoying.
(LAUGHS)
Wait.
I don't have to leave.
This is my part of
the ship. You leave.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Well, well, well.
Now who's being rude?
(ROSE LAUGHS)
What is this stupid thing
you're carrying around?
So, what are you,
an artist or something?
Well...
These are rather good.
They're very good, actually.
Jack, this is exquisite work.
Ah, they didn't think too
much of them in old Paree.
Paris?
You do get around
for a p...
Well, a... a
person of limited means.
Go on. A poor guy.
You can say it.
Well, well, well.
And these were
drawn from life?
Well, that's one of the
good things about Paris.
Lots of girls are willing
to take their clothes off.
(ROSE LAUGHS)
You liked this woman.
You used her several times.
Well.
She had beautiful
hands, you see?
I think you must have
had a love affair with her.
No, no, no.
Just with her hands.
She was a
one-legged prostitute.
See?
Oh.
(BOTH LAUGH)
She had a good
sense of humor though.
Oh, and this lady...
She used to sit at
this bar every night...
...wearing every piece
of jewelry she owned...
...just waiting for
her long, lost love.
We called her Madame Bijoux.
See, her clothes
are all moth-eaten.
Well,
you have a gift, Jack.
You do.
You see people.
I see you.
And?
You wouldn't have jumped.
But the purpose of university
is to find a suitable husband.
Rose has already done that.
Look, here comes that
vulgar Brown woman.
Quickly, get up before
she sits with us.
Hello, girls. I was hoping
I'd catch you at tea.
We're awfully sorry,
you missed it.
The Countess and I were
just off to take the air
on the boat deck.
What a lovely idea.
I need to catch up
on my gossip.
Countess.
So, you've not yet lit
the last four boilers?
No, I don't see
the need.
We are making
excellent time.
The press knows
the size of Titanic.
Now, I want them
to marvel at her speed.
We must give them
something new to print.
This maiden voyage
of Titanic must...
...make headlines.
Mr. Ismay, I would prefer
not to push the engines...
...until they've been
properly run in.
Of course
I'm just a passenger.
I leave it to
your good offices to
decide what's best.
But what a glorious end
to your final crossing...
...if we were to get
into New York
on Tuesday night...
...and surprise them all.
Make the morning papers.
Retire with a bang, eh, E.J.?
Good man.
...then I went
on a squid boat
in Monterey...
down to Los Angeles
to the pier in Santa Monica...
...and started doing portraits
there for 10 cents apiece.
Why can't I be
like you, Jack?
Just head out for
the horizon whenever I...
...feel like it.
Say we'll go there
sometime, to that pier...
...even if we only ever
just talk about it.
No, we'll do it.
We'll drink cheap beer.
We'll ride on the roller
coaster 'til we throw up.
(LAUGHS)
Then we'll ride
horses on the beach.
Right in the surf.
Now, but you'll have to
do it like a real cowboy.
None of that sidesaddle stuff.
You mean, one leg
on each side?
Yeah.
Can you show me?
Sure, if you like.
Teach me to ride like a man.
(WESTERN U.S. ACCENT)
And chew tobacco like a man.
And spit like a man.
What, they didn't teach you
that in finishing school?
No. (LAUGHS)
Come on,
I'll show you. Let's do it.
I'll show you how. Come on.
Aw, come on.
Jack! No, Jack, no!
Wait Jack!
Come on.
No Jack. I couldn't
possibly, Jack.
Watch closely.
(HAWKING PHLEGM)
That's disgusting.
All right, your turn.
(ROSE SNIFFS)
That was pitiful.
Come on, you
really got to hawk it back.
You know,
get some leverage to it.
And use your arms. (SNORTS)
Arc your neck.
(HAWKING)
(ROSE CLEARS THROAT)
You see the range
on that thing?
Mm-hm.
JACK: Okay, go.
That was better.
You got to work on it.
Really try and hawk it up
and get some body to it.
You know, you gotta...
(SNORTS)
(JACK GULPS)
Mother.
May I introduce
Jack Dawson.
Charmed, I'm sure.
OLD ROSE: The others
were gracious and curious
about the man
who'd saved my life.
But my mother looked at him
like an insect.
A dangerous insect...
...which must be
squashed quickly.
Well Jack, sounds like
you're a good man to have
around in a sticky spot.
(FANFARE PLAYING)
Why do they always
insist on announcing
dinner like
a damn cavalry charge?
(LAUGHS)
Shall we go dress, Mother?
See you at dinner, Jack.
Uh, son?
Son!
Do you have the slightest
comprehension of
what you're doing?
Not really.
Well, you're about to go
into the snake pit.
What are you
planning to wear?
(SCOFFS) I figured.
Come on.
I was right.
You and my son are
just about the same size.
Pretty close.
(WHISTLES)
You shine up
like a new penny.
(LAUGHS)
Good evening,
sir.
(ORCHESTRA PLAYS
THE BLUE DANUBE)
CAL: You know that
there are several
thousand tons of
Hockley steel...
...in this very ship?
RUTH: Which part?
CAL: All the right ones,
of course.
Then we'll know who
to hold accountable
if there's a problem.
Where's my daughter?
Oh, she'll be along.
There is the Countess.
Hello, my dear.
Good evening, Cal.
I saw that in
a nickelodeon once
and I always
wanted to do it.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Darling...
...surely you remember
Mr. Dawson.
(LAUGHS) It's amazing.
You could almost
pass for a gentleman.
Almost.
Extraordinary.
What a remarkable
voyage this is.
It's mad, isn't it?
There's the
Countess of Rothes.
And, that's
John Jacob Astor...
...the richest
man on the ship.
His little wifey there,
Madeleine, is my age...
...and in
a delicate condition.
See how she's
trying to hide it?
Quite the scandal.
Hmm.
And that's Benjamin Guggenheim
and his mistress,
Madame Aubert.
Mrs. Guggenheim is at home
with the children, of course.
And over here we have...
...Sir Cosmo and Lucile,
Lady Duff-Gordon.
She designs naughty lingerie,
among her many talents.
Very popular with the royals.
Congratulations, Hockley.
She's splendid.
Why,
thank you.
Care to escort
a lady to dinner?
Certainly.
(LAUGHS)
(RUTH LAUGHS)
Sweet pea?
Ain't nothing to it,
is there, Jack?
Remember,
they love money...
...so just
pretend like you own
a gold mine and
you're in the club.
Hey, Astor.
Well, hello, Molly.
Nice to see you.
J.J., Madeleine, I'd like
you to meet Jack Dawson.
How do you do?
Pleasure.
Well, Jack...
...are you of
the Boston Dawsons?
No, the Chippewa Falls
Dawsons, actually.
Oh, yes.
OLD ROSE:
He must have been nervous...
...but he never faltered.
They assumed
he was one of them.
Heir to a railroad fortune,
perhaps.
New money, obviously,
but still
a member of the club.
Mother, of course, could
always be counted upon.
Tell us of the accommodations
in steerage, Mr. Dawson.
I hear they're quite
good on this ship.
The best I've seen, ma'am.
Hardly any rats.
(LAUGHTER)
Mr. Dawson is joining us
from the third class.
He was of some assistance
to my fiancée last night.
It turns out that Mr. Dawson
is quite a fine artist.
He was kind enough to show me
some of his work today.
Rose and I differ somewhat in
our definition of fine art.
Not to impugn your work, sir.
(ROSE CLEARS THROAT)
(MOUTHS)
(HUSHED)
Are these all for me?
Just start from the outside
and work your way in.
He knows every rivet
in her, don't you Thomas?
Your ship is a wonder,
Mr. Andrews. Truly.
Thank you, Rose.
How do you take
your caviar, sir?
No caviar for me, thanks.
Never did like it much.
And where exactly
do you live, Mr. Dawson?
Well, right now, my address
is the RMS. Titanic.
After that,
I'm on God's good humor.
And how is it you have
means to travel?
I work my way from
place to place.
You know, tramp
steamers and such.
But I won my ticket on Titanic
here at a lucky hand at poker.
A very lucky hand.
All life is
a game of luck.
Hmm. A real man
makes his own luck, Archie.
Right, Dawson?
Mmm.
And you find that
sort of rootless existence
appealing, do you?
Yes, ma'am, I do.
I mean, I've got everything
I need right here with me.
I got air in my lungs and
a few blank sheets of paper.
I love waking up
in the morning
not knowing
what's gonna happen or...
...who I'm gonna meet...
...where I'm gonna wind up.
Just the other night
I was sleeping
under a bridge and now...
...here I am on the grandest
ship in the world...
...having Champagne
with you fine people.
I'll take some more of that.
I figure life's a gift and
I don't intend on wasting it.
You never know what hand
you're gonna get dealt next.
You learn to take life
as it comes at you.
Oh, here you go, Cal.
To make each day count.
Well said, Jack.
Hear, hear.
To making it count.
ALL: To making it count!
COL. ARCHIBALD: Bravo.
(MOLLY LAUGHING)
But Mr. Brown had no idea
I'd hidden the money
in the stove.
(LAUGHTER)
So, he comes home
drunk as a pig
celebrating and
he lights a fire.
(LAUGHTER)
(HUSHED) Next
it'll be brandies
in the smoking room.
Well, join me in
a brandy, gentlemen?
What a good idea.
(HUSHED) Now they retreat
into a cloud of smoke...
...and congratulate
each other on being
masters of the universe.
Ladies, thank you for
the pleasure of your company.
Rose, may I escort
you back to the cabin?
No, I'll stay here.
Here you go, Molly.
COL. ARCHIBALD:
Joining us, Dawson?
You don't want to
stay out here with
the women, do you? (CHUCKLES)
No, thanks.
I've got to be heading back.
COL. ARCHIBALD: Ah.
That's probably best.
It'll be all business
and politics,
that sort of thing.
Wouldn't interest you.
But Dawson,
good of you to come.
Jack, must you go?
Time for me to go row
with the other slaves.
Good night, Rose.
(CLOCK CHIMING)
(EXHALES)
So you want to go
to a real party?
(WHOOPING)
(PLAYING IRISH JIG)
(CLAPPING)
Is okay I put
my hand here? Okay.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
What?
I can't understand you.
(GLASS SMASHING)
(LAUGHS)
(FABRIZIO LAUGHING)
(MUSIC ENDS)
(CHEERING)
FABRIZIO: Bravo!
I'm going to dance
with her now, all right?
Come on.
What?
Come with me.
Jack, wait.
I can't do this.
We're gonna have to
get a little bit closer.
Like this.
(GASPS)
(IRISH JIG PLAYING)
You're still my best girl,
Cora.
I don't know the steps.
Neither do I.
Just go with it.
(LAUGHS)
Don't think.
(EXCLAIMS)
(LAUGHS)
(JACK WHOOPING)
(WHOOPING)
Wait! Jack, Jack!
Wait! Stop, Jack!
Bom, bom, bom.
(WHOOPING)
What? Wait!
JACK: Whoo-hoo!
(ROSE LAUGHING)
JACK: Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Jack, no.
Wow!
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
...beyond the jurisdiction
of the Sherman Act.
So my lawyers will argue.
That's what
Rockefeller said but the
Supreme Court is
not swallowing it.
(SHOUTS OF ENCOURAGEMENT)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
What? You think
a first-class girl
can't drink?
(LAUGHS)
ROSE: Oh!
(SCREAMS)
Get out of here.
You all right?
(LAUGHS)
I'm fine.
(BJORN ROARS)
Two out of three.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
So...
...you think
you're big tough men?
Let's see you do this.
Hold this for me, Jack.
Hold it up.
Ow! (LAUGHS)
Whoa!
Jesus,
Mary and Joseph!
Are you all right?
I haven't done that in years.
(ROSE LAUGHING)
(MUSIC ENDS)
Come on, lads. Give it
all you got. Let's go.
(WHOOPING)
Coffee, sir?
I had hoped you would
come to me last night.
I was tired.
Your exertions below decks
were no doubt exhausting.
I see you had
that undertaker of
a manservant follow me.
How typical.
You will never
behave like that again,
Rose. Do you understand?
I'm not a foreman in
one of your mills...
...that you can command.
I'm your fiancée.
(QUIETLY) My fiancée.
(SHOUTING) My fiancée!
Yes, you are!
And my wife!
My wife in practice...
...if not yet by law...
...so you will honor me!
You will honor me
the way a wife
is required to
honor her husband.
Because I will not be
made out a fool, Rose.
Is this in any way unclear?
No.
Good. Excuse me.
(ROSE GASPING)
Oh, Miss Rose.
(PANTING)
We had a little accident.
That's all right.
I'm sorry, Trudy.
Let me help you.
It's all right, miss.
(SOBS)
Tea, Trudy.
You're not to
see that boy again.
Do you understand me?
Rose, I forbid it.
Oh, stop it, Mother.
You'll give
yourself a nosebleed.
This is not a game.
Our situation is precarious.
You know the money's gone.
Of course I know it's gone.
You remind me every day.
Your father left us
nothing but a legacy
of bad debts
hidden by a good name.
That name is the only
card we have to play.
I don't
understand you.
It is a fine match
with Hockley. It will
ensure our survival.
How can you put
this on my shoulders?
Why are you being
so selfish?
I'm being selfish?
Do you want to see me
working as a seamstress?
Is that what you want?
To see our fine things
sold at auction?
Our memories scattered
to the wind?
(SIGHS) It's so unfair.
Of course it's unfair.
We're women.
Our choices are never easy.
Mmm?
ALL: Protect them
by Thy guiding hand
From every peril on the land
O, spirit whom the Father sent
To spread abroad the firmament
O, wind of heaven,
by Thy might
Save all who dare
the eagle's flight
And keep them by
Thy watchful care...
Hello, Mr. Andrews.
Hello, Jack.
(SINGING CONTINUES WITHIN)
I just need to talk to
somebody for a second.
You're not supposed
to be in here.
I just need to
speak to someone.
I was just here last night.
You don't remember me?
No, I'm afraid I don't.
Now you're gonna
have to turn around.
He'll tell you.
I just need to talk to...
Mr. Hockley and
Mrs. De Witt Bukater...
...continue to be appreciative
of your assistance.
They asked me
to give you this
in gratitude.
I don't want your
money. Please, I just...
Also to remind you that you
hold a third-class ticket...
...and that your
presence here...
...is no longer appropriate.
Please,
I just want to speak to
Rose for one second,
all right?
Gentlemen,
will you please see that
Mr. Dawson gets back
to where he belongs...
...and that
he stays there?
Yes, sir.
Come along, you.
Oh hear us when we cry to Thee
For those in peril
on the sea
RUTH: And why do you have
to steering wheels?
We really only
use this near shore.
Excuse me, sir.
Another ice warning.
This one's
from the Noordam.
CAPT. SMITH:
Thank you, Sparks.
Oh, not to worry.
Quite normal for
this time of year.
In fact,
we're speeding up.
I've just ordered
the last boilers lit.
(GRUNTING)
MAN: Okay, son, wind it up
tight like I showed you.
That's right.
Okay, now let it go.
It was good, wasn't it?
Quite nice.
That's excellent.
ROSE: Mr. Andrews...
Forgive me.
I did the sum
in my head...
...and with
the number of lifeboats
times the capacity
you mentioned...
Forgive me,
but it seems that there are
not enough for
everyone aboard.
About half, actually.
Rose, you miss nothing,
do you?
In fact, I put in
these new type davits...
...which can take
an extra row of boats
inside this one.
But it was thought,
by some...
...the deck would look
too cluttered.
So, I was overruled.
It's a waste of
deck space as it is
on an unsinkable ship.
Sleep soundly,
young Rose.
I have built you a good ship,
strong and true.
She's all the lifeboat
you need.
Just keep heading aft.
The next stop
will be the engine room.
Jack, this is impossible.
I can't see you.
I need to talk to you.
No, Jack. No.
Jack.
I'm engaged.
I'm marrying Cal.
I love Cal.
Rose...
...you're no picnic.
All right?
You're a spoiled
little brat even.
But under that, you're the
most amazingly, astounding...
...wonderful girl...
...woman,
that I've ever known.
Jack, I...
No, let me try and get
this out. You're ama...
(SIGHS)
I'm not an idiot.
I know how the world works.
I've got ten bucks
in my pocket.
I have nothing to offer
you and I know that.
I understand.
But I'm too involved now.
You jump, I jump.
Remember?
I can't turn away without
knowing you'll be all right.
That's all that I want.
Well, I'm fine.
I'll be fine. Really.
Really?
I don't think so.
They've got you
trapped, Rose.
And you're gonna die if you
don't break free.
Maybe not right away...
...because you're strong...
...but sooner or later
that fire that I love
about you, Rose...
...that fire is
gonna burn out.
It's not up to you
to save me, Jack.
You're right.
Only you can do that.
I'm going back.
Leave me alone.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Tell Lucile about
the disaster you had
with the stationers.
Well, of course
the invitations had to be
sent back, tice.
Oh, my dear.
And the dreadful
bridesmaids' gowns.
Let me tell you what
an odyssey that has been.
Rose decided
she wanted lavender.
She knows
I detest the color.
So, she did it
only to spite me.
LADY GORDON: If only
you'd come to me sooner.
Ruth saw some of my designs
in La Mode Illustrée.
They were for
the trousseau of
the Duchess of Marlborough's
youngest daughter.
They were quite charming.
But, I think you'll agree,
my dear, that together...
...we've created something
of a phoenix from the ashes.
(LAUGHTER)
Hello, Jack.
I changed my mind.
They said you
might be up here.
Give me your hand.
Now close your eyes.
Go on.
Now, step up.
Now, hold onto the railing.
Keep your eyes closed.
Don't peek.
I'm not.
Now, step up onto the rail.
Hold on. Hold on.
Keep your eyes closed.
(LAUGHS)
JACK: Do you trust me?
I trust you.
All right...
...open your eyes.
(ROSE GASPS)
I'm flying.
Jack.
(SINGS)
Come, Josephine, in my
flying machine. Going up...
...she goes. Up she goes.
(MUFFLED RADIO CHATTER)
That was the last time
Titanic ever saw daylight.
We're up to dusk
the night of the sinking.
6 hours to go.
Incredible. There's Smith
and he's standing
there and...
...he's got
the iceberg warning
in his fucking hand...
...excuse me... his hand,
and he's ordering more speed.
26 years of experience
working against him.
He figures anything big
enough to sink, the ship...
...they're gonna
see in time to turn.
But the ship's too big
with too small a rudder.
Doesn't corner
worth a damn.
Everything he knows
is wrong.
(LAUGHING) It's quite
proper, I assure you.
This is the sitting room.
Will this light do?
What?
Don't artists
need good light?
(FRENCH ACCENT) That is true,
but I'm not used
to working in...
...such horrible conditions.
Monet!
Do you know his work?
Of course.
JACK: Look at
his use of color here.
Isn't he great?
ROSE: I know.
It's extraordinary.
Cal insists on
carting this hideous
thing everywhere.
Should we be expecting him
any time soon?
Not as long as the cigars
and brandy hold out.
That's nice.
What is it,
a sapphire?
A diamond.
A very rare diamond.
Jack, I want you to
draw me like
one of your French girls.
Wearing this.
All right.
Wearing only this.
The last thing I need is
another picture of me looking
like a porcelain doll.
As a paying customer...
...I expect to get
what I want.
Over on the bed
...uh, the couch.
Come. Lie down.
Tell me when it looks right.
Keep that.
Put your arm back
the way it was.
Put that other arm up,
that hand right
by your face there.
Right.
Now, head down.
Eyes to me.
Keep them on me.
And try to stay still.
(ROSE CLEARS THROAT)
(EXHALES)
So serious.
I believe you are blushing,
Mr. Big Artiste.
I can't imagine
Monsieur Monet blushing.
He does landscapes.
Just relax your face.
Sorry.
No laughing.
(ROSE EXHALES)
My heart was pounding
the whole time.
It was the most erotic
moment of my life...
...up until then, at least.
So what happened next?
You mean,
did we do it?
Sorry to disappoint you,
Mr. Bodine.
Jack was very professional.
Thank you.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
What are you doing?
Will you put this
back in the safe for me?
JACK: Mmm-hmm.
Whew.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Gentlemen,
would you excuse me.
None of the stewards
have seen her.
This is absurd.
It's a ship.
There's only so many places
she could be.
Lovejoy, find her.
Clear.
Yes.
I don't think I've ever
seen such a flat calm.
Like a mill pond.
(CHUCKLES)
Not a breath of wind.
It will make the bergs
harder to see...
...with no breaking water
at the base.
CAPT. SMITH: Hm.
Well, I'm off.
Maintain speed and
heading, Mr. Lightoller.
Yes, sir.
(BLOWS)
It's getting cold.
You look nice.
(KNOCKING)
LOVEJOY: Miss Rose?
My drawings!
(DOOR LOCK CLICKS)
(ROSE LAUGHS)
Come on!
ROSE: (LAUGHS)
Wait, wait, wait!
JACK: Go. Go. Down, down.
Take us down,
quickly. Quickly!
(BOTH LAUGH)
Bye.
Sorry.
(LAUGHS)
Keep going.
Thank you, I've got it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Pretty tough for
a valet, this fella.
Seems more like a cop.
I think he was.
Oh, shit.
Go!
(SCREAMS)
No, over here!
ROSE: Quick!
(FANS ROARING)
(RUMBLING)
Now what?
What?
(LAUGHS)
MAN: More coal for
number one, mate.
Hold up? What are you to
doing down here?
You shouldn't be down here.
It could be dangerous!
Carry on!
Don't mind us. You're
doing a great job!
Keep up the good work!
JACK: Ah. Look at
what we have here, huh?
(JACK CHUCKLES)
(ROSE CLEARS THROAT)
(JACK CLEARS THROAT)
Thank you.
(HONKS HORN)
(LAUGHS)
Where to, miss?
To the stars.
(JACK LAUGHS)
You nervous?
(QUIETLY) No.
Put your hands on me, Jack.
It's bloody cold.
You know,
I can smell ice, you know.
When it's near.
Bollocks!
Well, I can, all right?
Did you ever find those
binoculars for the lookouts?
Haven't seen them
since Southampton.
Well, I'll be on
my rounds.
Cheerio.
(JACK BREATHING HEAVILY)
You're trembling.
Don't worry.
I'll be all right.
They ran down there.
Right.
LOVEJOY: Anything missing?
I've got a better idea.
(CLICKS FINGERS)
Gotcha!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Did you see
those guys' faces?
Did you see them?
When the ship docks...
...I'm getting off with you.
This is crazy.
I know. It doesn't
make any sense.
(SIGHS)
That's why I trust it.
Oh, yes.
Here, look at this.
Look at that,
would you?
They're a bit warmer
than we are.
Well, if that's
what it takes for us
to get warm...
I'd rather not
if it's all the same
to you, all right?
(CHUCKLES)
Bugger me!
(BELL RINGING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Pick up, you bastards!
(TELEPHONE CONTINUES RINGING)
FLEET: Is there
anyone there?!
Yes, what do you see?
Iceberg, right ahead!
Thank you.
Iceberg right ahead!
Hard to starboard!
Turn! Turn! Smartly!
(ENGINE TELEGRAPH RINGS)
Full astern!
Hard over.
MOODY: Helm's hard over, sir.
(ENGINE TELEGRAPH RINGING)
Go, lads,
go!
ENGINEER BELL:
Bring that steam down!
Bring it down!
Shut all the dampers!
Shut them!
(DOORS SLAMMING)
Hold it.
Hold it!
Now! Engage the
reversing engine!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Why ain't they turning?
Is it hard over?!
It is. Yes sir.
Hard over.
(QUIETLY) Come on,
come on, come on. Turn.
Yes.
It's gonna hit!
Jesus Christ!
(CREAKING)
(METALLIC SCRAPING)
(GLASS TINKLING)
Jesus!
Hard to port!
MOODY: Hard to port!
(SCREAMING)
JACK: Get back!
(MEN GRUNT)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(ALARM RINGING)
Come on. Let's go!
Get out of the doors.
They're closing the doors!
Get out!
Get out the door! Go!
Go! Come on, lads!
Go, lads, go!
Go! Go!
Out!
(ALARM RINGING)
Oh, my God.
That was a close shave,
wasn't it?
Smell ice, can you?
Bleedin' Christ!
Note the time and...
...enter it in the log.
What was that,
Mr. Murdoch?
An iceberg, sir.
I put her hard to
starboard and ran
the engines full astern
but it was too close.
I tried to port round it,
but she hit and I...
CAPT. SMITH:
Close the watertight doors.
The doors are closed, sir.
All stop.
Aye, sir.
(ENGINE TELEGRAPH RINGING)
Find the carpenter.
Get him to sound the ship.
Yes, sir.
(SPLASHING)
(EXCLAIMS IN ITALIAN)
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Come on, let's get
the hell out of here!
Come on, hurry up!
Excuse me,
why have the engines
stopped? I felt a shudder.
I shouldn't worry, madame.
We've likely
thrown a propeller blade.
That's the shudder you felt.
May I bring you anything?
No, thank you.
MAN 1: So, now there's
talk of an iceberg.
Did you see anything?
MAN 2: I don't see
anything now. Do you?
If this is
the direction the rats
are going,
that's good enough for me.
Please, everything
is under control.
There is nothing to
worry about at all.
You there.
Sir, there is
no emergency.
Yes there is.
I have been robbed.
Get the Master at Arms.
Now, you moron!
Yes, sir.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Hey, did I
miss the fun?
Did you see
what happened?
No, I missed it.
Apparently,
it hit over there.
Boiler room 6 is
flooded 8 feet above
the plate and
the mail hold is worse.
She's all buckled in
in the forward hull.
Can you shore up?
Not unless
the pumps get ahead.
Have you seen
the damage in mail hold?
HUTCHINSON: No,
she's already underwater.
This is bad.
We should tell
Mother and Cal.
I think
they're very good, sir.
Don't touch anything.
I want the entire
room photographed.
Just keep hold of my hand.
We've been looking
for you, miss.
ROSE: Here we go.
Something serious
has happened.
Yes, it has.
Indeed. Two things dear
to me have disappeared
this evening.
Now that one is back...
...I have a pretty good idea
where to find the other.
Search him.
Take your coat off, son.
Now what?
Come on.
Cal, what are you doing?
We're in the middle...
...of an emergency.
What's going on?
Is this it?
That's it.
This is horseshit!
Don't you believe it,
Rose. Don't.
He couldn't have.
Of course he could.
It's easy enough
for a professional.
But I was with him
the whole time.
This is absurd.
Perhaps he did it
while you were
putting your clothes
back on, dear.
Real slick, Cal. Rose,
they put it in my pocket.
Shut up.
LOVEJOY: It isn't
even your pocket, is it, son?
"Property of A.L. Ryerson."
That was reported
stolen today.
I just borrowed it.
I was going to return it.
Oh, an honest thief.
We have an honest
thief here, do we?
You know I didn't
do this, Rose.
You know it.
Don't you believe
them, Rose.
You know it.
You know I didn't do it.
Come on, let's go.
You know I didn't
do it, Rose!
Rose!
Come on.
There's a good lad.
Come on son.
You know I didn't do it!
You know me!
ISMAY: This is most
unfortunate, Captain.
Water 14 feet above the keel
in 10 minutes...
...in the forepeak,
in all 3 holds and
in boiler room 6.
That's right, sir.
When can we get
underway, damnit?
That's 5 compartments.
She can stay afloat
with the first 4
compartments breached,
but not 5.
Not 5.
As she goes down by the head,
the water will spill...
...over the tops
of the bulkheads
at E deck,
from one to the next...
...back and back.
There's no stopping it.
The pumps.
If we open the doors.
The pumps buy you time,
but minutes only.
From this moment,
no matter what we do...
...Titanic will founder.
But this ship can't sink.
She's made of iron, sir.
I assure you, she can.
And she will.
It is
a mathematical certainty.
How much time?
An hour.
Two, at most.
And how many aboard,
Mr. Murdoch?
2,200 souls on board, sir.
Well, I believe you may
get your headlines, Mr. Ismay.
(SIGHS)
Oh, it is a little slut,
isn't it?
You look at me when
I'm talking to you!
(KNOCKING)
Mr. Hockley?
Not now. We're busy.
Sir, I've been told
to ask you to please...
...put on your lifebelts and
come up to the boat deck.
I said, not now.
I'm sorry to
inconvenience you...
...Mr. Hockley,
but it's Captain's orders.
Now please, dress warmly.
It's quite cold out tonight.
Now, may I suggest
topcoats and hats?
This is ridiculous.
Not to worry, miss.
I'm sure
it's just a precaution.
Everybody up!
Lifebelts on!
What? What's
he on about?
Everybody up and put
your lifebelts on!
What's the ruckus?
Just put your lifebelts on.
C.Q.D.?
Sir?
That's right, C.Q.D.
The distress call.
That's our position.
(SIGHS)
Tell whoever responds
that we're going
down by the head...
...and need immediate
assistance.
Blimey.
Keep lowering!
(CREWMEN SHOUTING)
Steady! Make it taut!
And winch out!
Uncover this boat! Uncover
all the boats aft!
LIGHTOLLER:
Release those ties!
Roll back that cover!
Smartly now!
Mr. Wilde, where are
the passengers?
They've all gone back
inside. Too damn cold
and noisy for them.
You there! Get down here
and help with these lines!
(CHATTER)
Care for a drink, sir?
Hey Sonny,
what's doing?
You get us all trussed up
here and now we're
cooling our heels.
Sorry, ma'am. Let me
go and find out.
I don't think
anybody knows what
the hell's going
on around here.
It's the goddamned English,
doing everything by the book.
There's no need for
language, Mr. Hockley.
Go back and turn the
heaters on in our rooms.
I'd like a cup of tea
when I return.
Mr. Andrews.
I saw the iceberg.
And I see it in your eyes.
Please tell me the truth.
The ship will sink.
You're certain?
Yes, in an hour or so...
...all this will be at
the bottom of the Atlantic.
What?
Please,
tell only who you must.
I don't want to be
responsible for a panic.
And get to a boat.
Quickly. Don't wait.
You remember what I told
you about the boats?
Yes.
I understand.
Over here, son.
Sir, they need you
up in the Second Class
Purser's office.
There's a big mob
up there.
Go on.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Aye. Right.
Sir, Carpathia says
they're making 17 knots.
Full steam for them, sir.
She's the only one
who's responding?
The only one close, sir.
She says they can be
here in 4 hours.
4 hours?!
Thank you, Bride.
My God.
We are swung out
and ready, sir.
Hadn't we better get
the women and children
into the boats, sir?
(QUIETLY) Yes.
Sir?
Women and children
first, yes.
Yes, sir.
LIGHTOLLER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
attention, please!
Step this way, please.
That's right.
Come towards me.
Thank you.
Good.
For the time being...
...I shall require only
women and children.
MAN: Right here.
All right boys,
like the Captain said...
...nice and cheery,
so there's no panic.
"Wedding Dance."
Lifebelts on.
Put your lifebelts on.
Here, put your lifebelt on.
Here, come on.
Put that lifebelt on.
Turn that around.
There isn't
any reason to panic.
It isn't time to go
up to the boats yet!
Please, stay calm.
Make sure,
everybody, you've got
your lifebelts on.
And gentlemen, allow
the women and children
through to the front.
What are we doing, mommy?
We're just waiting, dear.
When they finish
putting first-class
people in the boats...
...they'll be
starting with us and
we'll want to be
all ready, won't we?
Don't push on the gate.
You won't get
you out any faster.
Go and get some help.
Lower away, left and
right together! Steady.
Both sides together! Steady!
Steady!
Stop, stop, stop!
Hold the left side!
Right side only!
Right side down!
Lower away together!
Steady, lads!
(FLARE EXPLODES)
(ALL GASP)
You know, I do believe
this ship may sink.
I've been asked to
give you this small token
of our appreciation.
Compliments of
Mr. Caledon Hockley.
(PANTING)
Come on, sister, you heard
the man. Into the boat.
Any room for a gentleman,
gentlemen?
HICHENS: Only women
at this time, sir.
Will the lifeboats be
seated according to class?
I hope they're
not too crowded.
Oh, Mother, shut up!
Don't you understand?
The water is freezing and
there aren't enough boats.
Not enough by half.
Half the people on this
ship are going to die.
Not the better half.
Come on, Ruth,
get in the boat.
First class seats
are right up here.
You know, it's a pity
I didn't keep that drawing.
It'll be worth
a lot more by morning.
(FLARE EXPLODING)
You unimaginable bastard.
MOLLY: Come on, Rose
darling. There's plenty
of room for you.
Come on, Rose.
You're next, darling.
Come into the boat, Rose.
CAL: Come.
Rose.
Get into the boat!
Good-bye, Mother.
(RUTH CALLING OUT)
Where are you going?
To him?!
To be a whore
to a gutter rat?
I'd rather be his whore
than your wife.
No!
(GRUNTING)
I said, no!
RUTH: Rose!
Please, stop!
LIGHTOLLER:
And, lower away!
No, Wait!
LIGHTOLLER: Lower away!
Rose!
LIGHTOLLER: Lower together!
Hold the left side!
Help!
Can anybody hear me?!
(CLANGING)
Hello! Help me!
JACK: (DISTANT) Help me!
Can you hear me?!
Can anybody hear me?!
Somebody help me!
ROSE: Mr. Andrews?!
(PANTING)
Steward, check the
starboard corridor.
Madame,
please put on a lifebelt.
Get to the boat
deck immediately.
Lucy, for God's sake
put on
your lifebelt and
set a good example.
Yes sir.
Anyone in here?
Mr. Andrews!
Thank God!
Where would
the Master at Arms take
someone under arrest?
What? You have to get
to a boat right away.
No!
I'm doing this with or
without your help, sir.
But without will take longer.
Take the elevator
to the very bottom.
Go to the left...
...down the crewmen's passage.
Then go right and left
again at the stairs.
You'll come
to a long corridor.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS) This could be bad.
(WATER RUNNING)
Oh, shit!
(GRUNTING)
Excuse me. Thank you.
I'm sorry, miss,
but the lifts are closed.
I'm through being polite,
goddamnit!
Now take me down!
E deck.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROSE SCREAMS)
I'm going back up.
No! No! No!
Come back!
I'm going back up!
Crew passage.
(WATER GURGLING)
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Jack!
Rose!
Rose, I'm in here!
(MUFFLED CLANGING)
JACK: I'm in here!
I'm in here!
Jack! Jack!
Rose!
Jack! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
That guy Lovejoy
put it in my pocket.
I know, I know, I know.
Listen Rose...
...you're gonna have to find
the spare key, all right?
Look in that
cabinet right there.
It's a little
silver one, Rose.
These are all
brass ones!
Check right here, Rose.
Rose.
How did you find out
I didn't do it?
I didn't.
I just realized
I already knew.
Keep looking.
No key.
There's no key!
All right, Rose, listen.
You're gonna have
to go find some help.
It'll be all right.
I'll be right back.
(MOANS)
I'll just wait here!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREAKING)
Hello?
Is there anyone here?
Is there anybody
down here?
We need help! Hello?
(WHIMPERS)
Damnit!
Can anybody hear me,
please?! Hello?! Hello?!
Oh, thank God.
Wait, please,
I need your help.
(GRUNTS)
There's a man back
here and he's...
(STUTTERS)
Wait!
(PANTING)
Hello?!
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
(BREATHING CALMS)
Hello?
Miss, you shouldn't
be here now.
I need your help.
There is a man down
here and he is trapped.
This way, yes. All right.
Please!
There's no need to panic.
No, I'm not panicking!
You're going
the wrong way!
Let go of me!
Listen!!!
To hell with you.
(MOANS)
(GRUNTING)
(CREWMAN SHOUTS IN DISTANCE)
(FLARE EXPLODES)
(CREAKING)
Oh, my God.
(GASPS)
(CREAKING)
Jack!
Rose!
Will this work?
I guess we'll
find out.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Try a couple practice
swings over there.
(GRUNTS)
Good.
Now try and hit the same mark
again, Rose. You can do it.
(GRUNTS)
Okay, that's enough practice.
Come on, Rose.
You can do it.
Listen,
just hit it really hard
and really fast.
Come on. Wait.
Open your hands up
a little more.
Like that?
Right.
Listen, Rose,
I trust you.
Go.
(CLANG)
(ROSE SCREAMS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You did it!
Come on. Let's go.
Oh shit, this is cold!
Oh, shit!
Shit! Shit!
ROSE: This is the way out.
We have to find
another way. Come on.
CREWMAN: Pull.
Put your backs into it.
(BAND PLAYING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Pull!
Now, there's something
you don't see every day.
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
What's this luggage
doing here? Get rid of it.
Get rid of it.
We need the room.
Get rid of that. Out.
This way.
Let go, sir. Get back.
Keep calm!
(ELDERLY WOMAN SOBBING)
(SOBS)
Lovejoy!
She's not on
the starboard side either.
We're running out of time.
This strutting
martinet isn't
letting any men on at all.
There's one on the other
side letting men on.
Well then,
that's our play.
We'll need some
insurance first. Come on.
This way, please.
All the way down here.
(THUD)
(ROARING)
Here!
What do you think
you're doing?
You'll have to pay
for that, you know.
That's White Star
Line property.
BOTH: Shut up!
Will you hold
the boat a moment?
I just have to run
back to my room...
(LIGHTOLLER ROARS)
Sit down!
She's the last.
Prepare to lower.
Mr. Lightoller.
Why are the boats being
launched half full?
Not now, Mr. Andrews.
There, look. 20 or so
in a boat built for 65?
And I saw one boat
with only 12.12!
Well, we weren't sure of
the weight, Mr. Andrews.
These boats may buckle.
Rubbish!
They were tested in Belfast
with the weight of 70 men.
Now, fill these boats,
Mr. Lightoller.
For God's sake man!
Please, I need more women
and children, please!
SEAMAN: Get back in there!
This is not an exit.
You can't keep us
locked in here.
Like animals.
The ship's bloody sinking.
Bring forward the women!
Unlock the gates.
Women only!
No men!
(PASSENGERS SHOUTING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Get back!
Lock the gates!
Get them back
from those gates!
Don't touch the gates!
(ALL SHOUTING)
For God's sake, man...
...there are women and
children down here!
Let us up so
we can have a chance!
STEWARD: Get back!
Jack!
JACK: Tommy!
Can we get out?
It's hopeless that way.
Whatever we do,
we've got to do it fast.
Jack!
Fabrizio!
The boats are all going.
This whole place is flooding.
We've gotta get out of here.
There is niente this way.
Let's go this way, all right?
Come on!
I make my own luck.
So do I.
(CHUCKLES)
Come on!
No, come on,
let's go this way.
(SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE)
This way!
Just go back to
the main stairwell.
And everything will be
sorted out there.
It will all get
sorted out back there.
Go back to
the main stairwell.
Open the gate!
Go back down
the main stairwell.
Open the gate right now!
Go back down the main
stairwell, like I told you.
(BOTH SIGHING)
Goddamn it! Son of a bitch!
STEWARD: Stop that!
JACK: Fabri, Tommy,
give me a hand here.
Move aside.
JACK: Come on, pull!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Pull!
Move aside.
Quickly, move aside!
STEWARD: Put that down!
Move aside!
Put that down!
One! Two!
Three!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Again!
(GRUNTING)
JACK: Now, let's go!
Let's go, Rose.
You can't go up there!
You can't do this!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
LIGHTOLLER: Keep order!
Keep order here!
Back! Back! Back!
(MAN GRUNTS)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
LIGHTOLLER: Hold on to her!
(SCREAMS)
SEAMAN: Pull her in!
Get back, I say,
or I'll...
...shoot you all
like dogs!
Keep order here!
Keep order, I say.
Mr. Lowe, man this boat.
LOWE: Right.
Is everybody all right?
Nobody panic.
(SHUTS GUN)
(SHOUTING)
MURDOCH: Stay back.
We're too late.
There are more boats
down the front. Stay with
this one. Murdoch.
He seems to be
quite practical.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
BARRETT: Don't lower it!
SEAMAN: Cut the falls!
LOWE: Sit down!
Stay back, you lot!
Just stay back, the
lot of you! Stay back!
(SCREAMING)
It's starting to fall apart.
We don't have much time.
Mr. Murdoch?
Mr. Hockley.
You to, with me, now!
I'm a businessman,
as you know...
...and I have a business
proposition for you.
(BAND CONTINUES TO PLAY)
JACK: Come on, Rose.
The boats are gone!
Colonel, are there
any boats on that side?
No, miss, but there
are a couple of boats
all the way forward.
This way,
I'll lead you.
What's the use?
Nobody's listening
to us anyway.
Well, they don't
listen to us
at dinner, either.
Come on, let's play.
Keep us warm.
"Orpheus."
Music to drown by.
Now I know
I'm in first class.
Where is everyone?
They're all still aft, sir.
We have an understanding
then, Mr. Murdoch.
Will the men please hold
back! Hold back, I say!
(GUNSHOT)
Women and children only!
Get back!
Come through, madame.
This way. Step back, sir!
You better check
the other side. Go!
I found her,
on the other side.
Waiting for a boat.
With him.
Any more women
and children?
They're all aboard,
Mr. Murdoch.
Anyone else then?
Anyone else?
Do hurry. Hurry along.
Goddamn it all to hell.
Shit.
SEAMAN: Fire!
Sir, sir, you can't
go through here.
That's it.
Splendid. Right.
MURDOCH: Prepare to lower.
Ready on the left.
Take them down.
Keep it steady.
Both sides together.
Steady. Keep it steady.
Give her to me.
Daddy.
FATHER:
It'll be fine, darling.
Don't you worry.
Daddy, get in the boat.
It's good-bye for
a little while.
Only for a little while.
There'll be another
boat for the daddies.
This boat is for the
mummies and the children.
You hold Mummy's hand
and be a good little girl.
I'm not going without you.
No, you have
to go, now.
No, Jack.
Get in the
boat, Rose.
No, Jack.
Yes.
Get on the boat!
Yes, get on
the boat, Rose.
Oh my God, look at you.
You look a fright.
Here.
Put this on. Come.
Go on. I'll get the next one.
No, not without you.
JACK: I'll be all right.
Listen, I'll be fine.
I'm a survivor, all right?
Don't worry about me.
Now, go on.
Get on.
I have an arrangement
with an officer on
the other side of the ship.
Jack and I can
get off safely.
Both of us.
See?
I got my own
boat to catch.
CAL: Go on, hurry.
They're almost full.
Step aboard, miss.
Go. Go.
Step aboard, please.
FATHER: You're daddy's
good girl, all right?
You're my little sailor.
(ROSE GRUNTS)
Clear the rail, please.
And, lower away!
(LIFEBOAT PASSENGERS EXCLAIM)
You're a good liar.
Almost as good as you.
There's no... there's no
arrangement, is there?
No, there is.
Not that you'll
benefit much from it.
I always win, Jack.
One way or another.
Rose!
(PASSENGERS EXCLAIM)
CAL: Stop her!
Rose, what
are you doing?!
(ROSE PANTING)
No!
(ROSE SOBS)
Rose! You're so stupid!
Why did you do that, huh?
You're so stupid, Rose.
Why did you
do that? Why?!
You jump,
I jump, right?
Right.
Oh God.
I couldn't go.
I couldn't
go, Jack.
JACK: It's all right.
We'll think of something.
ROSE: At least I'm with you.
JACK: We'll think
of something.
Come on! Move!
Come on!
Move.
(GRUNTS)
Come on!
(ROSE SCREAMS)
Move!
Come on!
Come on Rose.
Rose, come on!
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
Move Rose!
Go!
(CREAKING)
I hope you enjoy
your time together.
(CREAKING)
(LAUGHING)
What could
possibly be funny?
I put the diamond
in the coat.
And I put
the coat on her!
Come on!
(CHILD SCREAMING)
Dada!
We can't leave him.
All right, come on!
Dada!
(DOORS STRAINING)
(BOY SCREAMING)
(BOY SOBBING)
Go back!
(SHOUTING IN SLOVAKIAN)
JACK: It's the wrong way!
Come back!
ROSE: No, not that way!
Come back! Stop!
(DOORS STRAINING)
(SCREAMING)
JACK: Go!
Go! Run!
Jack!
Rose!
(ROSE GRUNTS)
(JACK GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
JACK: This way!
Give me your hand!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, God!
JACK: Help!
ROSE: Help!
JACK: Wait, sir!
Sir, open the gate, please!
Help us, please!
Help us!
Please!
Bloody hell!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Go, go!
Jesus.
ROSE: Please!
JACK: Come on!
Hurry!
I'm sorry,
I dropped the keys.
Wait, please!
Wait!
Don't leave! Please,
send for help!
(TAKES DEEP BREATH)
(GASPS) I got it!
Which one is it, Rose?
The short one.
Try the short one.
Hurry, Jack.
Oh no! It won't go in.
It's stuck! It's stuck!
Come on!
Hurry, Jack!
(SHRIEKING)
JACK: I got it! I got it!
Go! Go, Rose!
Go! Go!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
Jack!
Jack! Come on!
Move, move.
(SCREAMING)
WILDE:
Get those oars in place.
Get an oar under it.
Hold it! Hold it!
Hold it!
(SHOUTING)
Get these davits cranked in!
Let's get the falls hooked up!
CAL: Oh!
(BAND CONTINUES PLAYING)
GIRL: (WAILING) Mommy!
(CRYING)
Keep going up!
(SHIP GROANING)
MURDOCH:
Stop pushing!
(SCREAMING)
Stay back!
Will you give us a chance
to live, you limey bastard!
I'll shoot any man who tries
to get past me! Get back!
Bastard!
Get back!
We had a deal,
damn you!
Your money can't
save you any more
than it could save me.
Get back!
WILDE: Women
and children only!
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMING)
FABRIZIO: Tommy!
No, Tommy! Bastardo!
(FABRIZIO SPEAKING ITALIAN)
No, Will!
Now stand back,
damn you!
LIGHTOLLER: Gently, gently.
Hold it. Hold it.
(SCREAMING)
(GIRL CRYING)
CAL: I have a child!
I have a child!
Clear a path here!
Please, I have a child!
Please. I'm all
she has in the world.
Go on.
Step back!
Please?
Here, give her to me.
You're all right, dearie.
Give her here.
(GIRL WAILING)
There, there.
Wait, wait, wait!
Mr. Andrews!
Oh, Rose.
Won't you even
make a try for it?
I'm sorry that
I didn't build you
a stronger ship, young Rose.
It's going fast.
We have to move.
Wait.
Good luck to you, Rose.
And to you.
Mr. Guggenheim?
These are for you,
Mr. Guggenheim.
No, thank you.
We are dressed in
our best and are
prepared to go down
as gentlemen.
(CREAKING)
But we would
like a brandy.
LIGHTOLLER: Get the falls
over here now!
Let them drop.
Then we'll right it.
Capitán?
Capitán, where should I go?
Please.
Captain. Captain. Sir.
(BAND CONTINUES PLAYING)
Right.
That's it, then.
Good-bye, Wally.
Good luck.
Good-bye, Wallace.
So long, old chap.
(PLAYING NEARER
MY GOD TO THEE)
And so they lived happily
together for 300 years...
...in the land
of Tir na nog...
Land of eternal
youth and beauty.
(SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
There's no time!
Cut those falls!
Cut them!
Cut them if you have to!
I need a knife!
WILDE: Cut the falls now!
Cut them loose!
Cut those bloody falls!
(SCREAMING)
Gentlemen...
...it has been a privilege
playing with you tonight.
(CREAKING)
(SCREAMING)
We have to stay on the
ship as long as possible.
Come on!
(SCREAMING)
JACK: This way.
Through the rail.
Come on, Rose.
Jump.
Come on.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
JACK: I got you.
Jump.
(GRUNTS)
I've got you, miss.
Jack!
CAL: Back!
(SCREAMING)
No! You'll swamp us!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Yea, though I walk
through the valley of
the shadow of death...
You wanna walk
a little faster through
that valley there?
(SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING)
Holy Mary,
mother of God...
...pray for us sinners
now and at the hour
of our death. Amen.
Hail Mary,
full of grace...
JACK: This way.
(ROSE GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Come on!
And I saw a new heaven
and a new earth...
...for the first heaven
and the first earth
had passed away...
...and there was no more sea.
Ah!
It'll be over soon.
It'll all be over soon.
(SHIVERING)
FATHER BYLES:
And He shall dwell with them.
And they shall be His people
and God Himself
shall be with them...
...and be their God.
Jack...
...this is where
we first met.
And God shall wipe away
all the tears
from their eyes...
...and there shall be
no more death.
Neither shall there be
sorrow or crying.
Neither shall there
be any more pain...
...for the former world
has passed away.
(SMASHING)
Bloody pull faster!
And pull!
(SCREAMING)
MAN: Hang on,
miss Trudy!
(SCREAMING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SCREAMS)
JACK: Hold on real tight.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
God Almighty.
Keep those breakers in!
Keep them in!
(SCREAMS)
(SHIP GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(ROSE GASPS)
We have to move!
Give me your hand.
I'll pull you over.
ROSE: I can't.
Come on!
Give me your hand.
I've got you.
I won't let go.
Come on,
I've got you.
(ROSE GRUNTS)
What's happening, Jack?
I don't know.
JACK: Hold on.
Jack!
Rose.
(SCREAMING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
(SCREAMS)
(CREAKING)
This is it!
(SCREAMING)
Oh, my God, Jack!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Hold on!
The ship is
gonna suck us down.
Take a deep breath
when I say.
Kick for the surface
and keep kicking.
Do not let go
of my hand.
We're going to
make it, Rose.
Trust me.
I trust you.
JACK: Ready! Ready!
Now!
(BOTH INHALE)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
(MAN GRUNTING)
No!
Jack!
Rose!
Get off her!
Jack!
Swim, Rose!
I need you to swim!
Keep swimming.
ROSE: It's so cold.
Swim, Rose!
Come on.
Keep swimming.
Here...
...get on it.
Get on top.
(ROSE GRUNTING)
Come on, Rose.
(ROSE SCREAMS)
Stay on it.
Stay on, Rose.
Jack...
It'll be all right now.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Return...
...the boats!
(WHISTLE BLOWING CONTINUES)
The boats are coming
back for us Rose.
Hold on just
a little bit longer.
They had to row
away for the suction...
...but now they'll
be coming back.
WOMAN: For God's sake!
Please...
...help us!
You don't understand.
If we go back,
they'll swamp the boat.
They'll pull us right down,
I'm telling you.
Oh, knock it off.
You're scaring me.
Come on, girls,
grab an oar. Let's go.
HICHENS: Are you out of
your mind? We're in the
middle of the North Atlantic.
Now,
do you people want to live
or do you want to die?!
(DISTANT SHOUTING)
(WHISTLING)
I don't understand
a one of you.
What's the matter with you?
It's your men out there!
There's plenty
of room for more.
And there'll be one less
on this boat...
...if you don't shut
that hole in your face!
LOWE: Now, bring in
your oars over there.
And tie these boats
together as well.
Now, make sure that's
tied up nice and tight.
Right, listen to me, men.
We have to go back.
I want to transfer
all the women
from this boat into
that boat right now...
...as quick as
you can, please.
Let's create some
space over there.
Move forward and aft.
(SHIVERING)
It's getting quiet.
It's just going to take
a couple of minutes...
...to get the boats organized.
I don't know about you but...
...I intend to write
a strongly worded letter...
...to the White Star Line
about all this.
I love you, Jack.
Don't you do that.
Don't you say your
good-byes. Not yet.
Do you understand me?
I'm so cold.
Listen, Rose...
...you're gonna
get out of here.
You're gonna go on...
...and you're gonna
make lots of babies.
And you're gonna
watch them grow.
You're gonna die an old...
...an old lady.
...warm in her bed.
Not here.
Not this night.
Not like this.
Do you understand me?
I can't feel my body.
Winning that ticket, Rose...
...was the best thing that
ever happened to me.
It brought me to you.
And I'm thankful
for that, Rose.
I'm thankful.
You must...
...you must do me
this honor.
You must promise me
that you'll survive.
That you won't give up...
...no matter what happens.
No matter how hopeless.
Promise me now, Rose.
And never let go
of that promise.
I promise.
Never let go.
I'll never let go, Jack.
I'll never let go.
(KISSES)
SEAMAN: Right ahead, sir.
LOWE: Oars!
Do you see any moving?
No, sir.
None moving, sir.
Check them.
Bring that oar up here.
Make sure.
SEAMAN: These are dead, sir.
Now, give way.
Ahead easy.
Careful with your oars.
Don't hit them.
Is there anyone
alive out there?
Can anyone hear me?
Is there anyone
alive out there?
We waited too long.
Well, keep checking them!
Keep looking!
Is there anyone
alive out there?
Can anyone hear me?
(SINGING QUIETLY)
Come, Josephine...
...in my flying machine
And it's up she goes
Up she goes
Come, Josephine...
...in my flying...
(GASPING)
(DISTORTED VOICE ECHOING)
Jack.
There's a boat.
Jack!
(TEARFULLY)
There's a boat, Jack.
Jack.
(SOBBING)
Come back.
(CROAKING) Come back.
Come back!
(ECHOING) Hello!
Can anyone hear me?
SEAMAN: There's nothing
here, sir.
Come back.
(HOARSELY) Come back.
(GRUNTS)
I'll never let go.
I promise.
(KISSES)
(ROSE SOBBING)
(BLOWS)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Come about!
(GASPS)
(BLOWS)
Fifteen hundred people
went into the sea...
...when Titanic
sank from under us.
There were twenty boats
floating nearby...
...and only one came back.
One.
Six were saved
from the water...
...myself included.
Six...
...out of fifteen hundred.
Afterward...
...the seven hundred
people in the boats...
...had nothing to
do but wait.
Wait to die.
Wait to live.
Wait for an absolution...
...that would never come.
(INAUDIBLE)
Sir, I don't think
you'll find any of
your people down here.
It's all steerage.
WOMAN: His hair is
reddish brown, reddish
brown, reddish brown.
White beard.
Isn't there another
passenger list?
There is no other list.
Perhaps he's on
another ship.
We're doing all we can,
ma'am. I'm so sorry.
OLD ROSE:
That's the last time
I ever saw him.
He married, of course,
and inherited his millions.
But the Crash of '29
hit his interests hard...
...and he put a pistol
in his mouth that year.
Or so I read.
Can I take your name
please, love?
Dawson.
Rose Dawson.
Thank you.
We never found
anything on Jack.
There's no record
of him at all.
No, there wouldn't
be, would there?
And I've never spoken
of him until now.
Not to anyone.
Not even
your grandfather.
A woman's heart is
a deep ocean of secrets.
But now you know there was
a man named Jack Dawson...
...and that he saved me...
...in every way that
a person can be saved.
I don't even have
a picture of him.
He exists now only
in my memory.
PILOT: Keldysh, Mir2
on our way to the surface.
(ANNOUNCEMENT IN RUSSIAN
OVER SHIP'S PA)
BROCK:
I was saving this for
when I found the diamond.
(SNIFFS)
I'm sorry.
Three years...
...I've thought of
nothing except Titanic.
But I never got it.
I never let it in.
Ha!
(SINGING)
Every night in my dreams
I see you, I feel you
That is how I know you go on
Far across the distance
And spaces between us
You have come to
show you go on
Near, far
Wherever you are
I believe that
The heart does go on
Once more
You open the door
And you're here in my heart
And my heart will go on and on
Love can touch us one time
And last for a lifetime
And never let go
till we're gone
Love was when I loved you
One true time I hold to
In my life we'll always go on
Near, far
Wherever you are
I believe that
The heart does go on
Once more
You open the door
And you're here in my heart
And my heart will go on and on
You're here
There's nothing I fear
And I know
That my heart will go on
We'll stay
Forever this way
You are safe in my heart
And my heart will go on
And on
English - US - PSDH