[sonar pinging]
[muffled radio chatter]
[man] Thirteen meters. You should see it.
Okay, take her up and over the bow rail.
[man over radio] Okay, Mir Two,
we're going over the bow. Stay with us.
[switch clicks]
[sonar pinging]
[vehicle whirring]
[muffled radio chatter]
[man] Okay, quiet. We're rolling.
Seeing her coming out
of the darkness like a ghost ship
still gets me every time.
To see the sad ruin
of the great ship sitting here
where she landed at 2:30 in the morning
of April 15, 1912
after her long fall
from the world above.
[snorts] You are so full of shit, boss.
[both laugh]
[metal creaking]
[sonar pinging]
[Brock] Dive six. Here we are again
on the deck of Titanic.
Two and a half miles down. 3,821 meters.
The pressure outside
is three and a half tons per square inch.
These windows are nine inches thick,
and if they go,
it's sayonara in two microseconds.
All right, enough of that bullshit.
[vehicle whirring]
Put her down on the roof
of the officers' quarters
-like yesterday.
-[Anatoly] Sure.
[Brock over radio] Okay, Mir Two,
we're landing right over
the Grand Staircase.
You guys set to launch?
Yeah, Brock. Launching Dunkin now.
Go, Charlie.
[robot whirring]
-Running tether out.
-[technician] Tether out.
Tether out.
[technician 2] Okay, Brock,
we're dropping down along the hull.
Yeah, roger that. Okay, drop down
and go into the first-class gangway door.
I want you guys working the D deck,
reception area and the dining saloon.
[technician 2] Copy that.
-[Brock] Tether out.
-[technician 3] Tether out.
[Brock] Now left. Now left. Left. Left.
[technician] Okay.
Coming left. Coming left.
[Brock] Snoop Dog is on the move.
We're headed down the stairwell.
Okay, Lewis, drop down to B deck.
Okay, A deck?
[Bodine] Give me some rope, Captain.
-B deck. Get in there. Get in there.
-Okay.
[whirring]
[Brock] Watch the door frame.
Watch the door frame.
-Watch it, watch it.
-Yeah, I see it. I got it.
[whirring]
-We're good.
-Bring her down.
We're good. Just chill, boss.
[Brock] Okay. Okay, make your turn.
-Come around.
-[Bodine] Cable out, Captain.
[Brock] Make your turn. Watch the wall.
Yeah, Brock, we're at the piano. You copy?
[Brock] Okay, copy that.
[Brock] Okay, right there.
Right there. Right there.
Okay, that's it, that's it.
That's the bedroom door.
I see it. I see it.
We're in!
We're in, baby. We're there.
[Brock sighs]
That's Hockley's bed.
That's where the son of a bitch slept.
[chuckles]
[Bodine] Oops.
Somebody left the water running.
Wait, hold it. Hold it. Just a second.
Go back to the right.
[whirring]
That wardrobe door. Get closer.
You smelling something, boss?
I want to see what's under it.
[Bodine] Give me my hands, man.
[whirring]
All right.
[Brock] Take it easy.
-It might come apart.
-Okay.
Go, go, go. Flip it over.
Flip it over. Go.
Turn her over. Keep going. Go, go, go.
Okay, drop it.
Oh, baby, baby. Are you seeing this, boss?
It's payday, boys.
[announcement in Russian over PA]
[men cheering]
[applauding]
Cha-ching!
-We did it, Bobby.
-We brought it back, baby.
Oh, yeah! Who's the best?
Who's the best, baby?
Say it. Say it. Say it.
You are, Lewis.
-Bobby, my cigar.
-It's right here.
[cheering]
[Brock] Okay, crack her open.
[man 1] Get around. Hang on.
You getting it?
[man 2] Got it.
[announcement in Russian over PA]
Shit.
No diamond.
You know, boss,
this same thing happened to Geraldo
and his career never recovered.
Turn the camera off.
[Buell] Brock, the partners
would like to know how it's going.
Hey, Dave, Barry, hi.
Look, it wasn't in the safe.
But, hey, hey… Don't worry about it.
There's still plenty of places
it could be.
Hell yes.
The floor debris in the suite,
the mother's room,
the purser's safe on C deck.
Jimmy Hoffa's briefcase.
[Brock] A dozen other places.
Guys, look,
just got to trust my instincts.
I know we're close.
We've just got to go through
a little process of elimination.
Hang on a second.
Let me see that.
[Buell] Ah, we might
have something here, guys.
Where's the photograph of the necklace?
We'll call you right back.
Holy…
I'll be goddamned.
[reporter on TV]
Treasure hunter Brock Lovett
is best known for finding Spanish gold…
It's okay. I'll feed you in a minute.
Come on.
Now he has chartered Russian subs
to reach the most famous
shipwreck of all, the Titanic.
He is with us live via satellite
from the research ship Keldysh
in the North Atlantic. Hello, Brock.
[Brock] Hello, Tracy.
Of course, everyone knows
the familiar stories of Titanic.
You know, the nobility of the band
playing to the very end and all that.
But what I'm interested in
are the untold stories.
The secrets locked deep inside
the hull of Titanic.
And we're out here using robot technology
to go further into the wreck
than anybody's ever done before.
[Tracy] Your expedition
is at the center of a storm of controversy
over salvage rights and even ethics.
Many are calling you a grave robber.
Well, nobody ever called
the recovery of the artifacts…
What is it?
Turn that up, dear.
I have museum-trained experts
sent out here making sure
that these relics are preserved
and catalogued properly.
Take a look at this drawing
that we found just today.
A piece of paper
that's been underwater for 84 years.
And my team are able to
preserve it intact.
Should this have remained unseen
at the bottom of the ocean for eternity,
when we can see and enjoy it now?
I'll be goddamned.
Brock!
There's a satellite call for you.
Bobby, we're launching.
You see these submersibles
going in the water?
Trust me, buddy.
You want to take this call.
This better be good.
-And you gotta speak up.
-Yeah, standby.
She's kind of old.
Great.
This is Brock Lovett.
How can I help you, Mrs…
Calvert. Rose Calvert.
Mrs. Calvert.
I was just wondering if you had found
the "Heart of the Ocean" yet, Mr. Lovett?
Told you you wanted to take the call.
All right, you have my attention, Rose.
Can you tell us who
the woman in the picture is?
Oh, yes. The woman in the picture is me.
She's a goddamn liar!
Some nutcase seeking money or publicity.
God only knows what.
Like that Russian babe, Anesthesia.
They're inbound!
Rose DeWitt Bukater died on the Titanic
when she was 17, right?
[Brock] That's right.
If she had lived,
she'd be over 100 by now.
101 next month.
Okay, so she's a very old goddamn liar.
Look, I've already done
the background on this woman
all the way back to the 20s,
when she was working as an actress.
An actress.
There's your first clue, Sherlock.
Her name was Rose Dawson back then.
Then she marries this guy named Calvert.
They move to Cedar Rapids
and she punches out a couple of kids.
Now Calvert's dead
and, from what I hear,
Cedar Rapids is dead.
And everybody who knows about the diamond
is supposed to be dead
or on this boat, but she knows.
Copy that.
Doesn't exactly travel light, does she?
Hurry up, give him a hand.
Mrs. Calvert, I'm Brock Lovett.
Welcome to the Keldysh.
Okay, let's get her inside there.
Hi, Miss Calvert.
-Hi.
-Welcome to the Keldysh.
Thanks.
[pilot] Hey. Hey!
[knocking]
[old Rose] Yes?
Are your staterooms all right?
Oh, yes. Very nice.
Have you met my granddaughter, Lizzy?
She takes care of me.
We met just a few minutes ago.
Remember, Nana? Up on deck?
Oh, yes.
[Bodine tuts]
There. That's nice.
Have to have my pictures when I travel.
Can I get you anything?
Is there anything you'd like?
Yes.
I would like to see my drawing.
[Brock] Louis XVI wore
a fabulous stone that was
called the Blue Diamond of the Crown
which disappeared in 1792,
about the same time old Louis
lost everything from the neck up.
The theory goes that the crown diamond
was chopped too.
Recut into a heart-like shape
that became known as
the Heart of the Ocean.
Today it would be worth
more than the Hope Diamond.
[scoffs] It was a dreadful, heavy thing.
I only wore it this once.
You actually think this is you, Nana?
It is me, dear.
Wasn't I a dish?
[laughs] I tracked it down
through insurance records.
An old claim that was settled
under terms of absolute secrecy.
Can you tell me
who the claimant was, Rose?
I should imagine someone named Hockley.
[Brock] Nathan Hockley, that's right.
Pittsburgh steel tycoon.
The claim was for a diamond necklace
his son Caledon bought his fiancée.
You.
A week before he sailed on Titanic.
And it was filed right after the sinking.
So the diamond had to have
gone down with the ship.
You see the date?
April 14, 1912.
Which means if your grandmother
is who she says she is,
she was wearing the diamond
the day the Titanic sank.
And that makes you my new best friend.
These are some of the things
we recovered from your stateroom.
This was mine.
[gasps] How extraordinary.
And it looks the same as it did
the last time I saw it.
[sighs]
Hmm.
The reflection has changed a bit.
Are you ready to go back to Titanic?
[Bodine] Okay, here we go.
She hits the 'berg
on the starboard side, right?
She kind of bumps along,
punching holes like Morse code…
[mimicking Morse code beeps]
along the side, below the water line.
Then the forward compartments
start to flood.
Now, as the water level rises,
it spills over the watertight bulkheads
which, unfortunately,
don't go any higher than E deck.
So now as the bow goes down,
the stern rises up, slow at first,
then faster and faster
until finally, she's got her whole ass
sticking up in the air.
And that's a big ass.
We're talking 20, 30,000 tons. Okay?
And the hull's not designed
to deal with that pressure.
So, what happens?
[clicking tongue]
She splits, right down to the keel.
And the stern falls back level.
Then as the bow sinks,
it pulls the stern vertical
and then finally detaches.
Now the stern section
just kind of bobs there
like a cork for a couple of minutes,
floods, and finally goes
under about 2:20 a.m.
Two hours and 40 minutes
after the collision.
The bow section planes away,
landing about a half a mile away
going 20, 30 knots when
it hits the ocean floor.
[imitates explosions]
Pretty cool, huh?
Thank you for that fine
forensic analysis, Mr. Bodine.
Of course, the experience of it was…
somewhat different.
Will you share it with us?
[muffled radio chatter]
[sonar pinging]
[band playing waltz]
[sighs]
Oh. [sobbing]
I'm taking her to rest.
No.
Come on, Nana.
No!
Give me the tape recorder.
Tell us, Rose.
It's been 84 years…
It's okay. Just try to remember anything,
anything at all.
Do you want to hear this
or not, Mr. Lovett?
It's been 84 years…
and I can still smell the fresh paint.
The china had never been used.
The sheets had never been slept in.
Titanic was called the ship of dreams.
And it was.
It really was.
[crewmen shouting]
[gulls crying]
[porter] All third-class passengers
with a forward berth,
this way, please! This queue!
It's a big boat, huh?
Daddy, it's a ship.
You're right.
[car horn honking]
I don't see what all the fuss is about.
It doesn't look any bigger
than the Mauretania.
You can be blasé about some things, Rose,
but not about Titanic.
It's over 100 feet longer than Mauretania,
and far more luxurious.
Your daughter is far too
difficult to impress, Ruth.
[laughs] So this is the ship
they say is unsinkable.
-It is unsinkable.
-[man] Sir, sir.
God Himself could not sink this ship--
-Sir!
-What?
You have to check your baggage
through the main terminal.
It's round that way, sir.
I put my faith in you, good sir.
Now kindly see my man.
Oh, yes, sir. It's my pleasure, sir.
If I can do anything at all…
Yes, right.
All the trunks from that car there.
Twelve from here.
And the safe to the parlor suite,
rooms B-52, 54, 56.
[whistle blowing]
Ladies, we better hurry.
Come along.
-My coat?
-[maid] I have it, miss.
[porter] All third-class passengers
queue here for health inspection.
Welcome aboard, ma'am. Welcome to Titanic.
[old Rose] It was the ship of dreams
to everyone else.
To me, it was a slave ship
taking me back to America in chains.
Outwardly, I was everything
a well brought up girl should be.
Inside, I was screaming.
[ship's horn blowing]
[both speaking Swedish]
[in Italian accent] Jack, you are pazzo.
You bet everything we have.
When you got nothing,
you got nothing to lose.
[in Swedish] You moron.
I can't believe you bet our tickets.
[in English] Sven?
Bet.
[watch ticking]
All right, moment of truth.
Someone's life is about to change.
Fabrizio?
[speaking Italian]
Olaf?
[in English] Nothing.
Sven?
[inhales sharply]
Uh-oh. Two pair.
[tuts] I'm sorry, Fabrizio.
[shouts in Italian]
[in English] I'm sorry,
you're not gonna see your mom again
for a long time,
'cause we're going to America.
Full house, boys! [whooping]
[Fabrizio laughs]
Yeah.
[both laughing]
[speaking Swedish]
Oh!
[patrons laughing]
-[in English] Come on.
-[speaking Italian]
[kisses, in English] I'm going home!
[shouting in Swedish]
[in English] I'm going home. [laughs]
I go to America!
No, mate.
Titanic go to America, in five minutes.
Shit. Fabri. Come on.
Come on, here. Here.
We're riding in high style now!
We're a couple of regular swells.
We're practically goddamn royalty,
ragazzo mio.
You see? Is my destino.
Like I told you,
I go to America to be millionaire.
-Whoa! Whoa!
-[neighing]
-[Fabrizio] Bastardo.
-[Jack] Whoo!
You are pazzo.
Maybe, but I've got the tickets.
Come on, I thought you were fast.
Whoa. Wait! Wait! Hey, wait!
We're passengers! We're passengers!
Have you been through
the inspection queue?
Of course.
Anyway, we don't have any lice.
We're Americans. Both of us.
Right. Come aboard.
We're the luckiest sons of bitches
in the world. You know that?
[ship's horn blowing]
[shouting]
[cheering]
[Jack] Goodbye!
[Fabrizio] You know somebody?
Of course not. That's not the point.
Goodbye! I'll miss you!
Goodbye!
I will never forget you!
[cheering]
[ship's horn blowing]
Come with me, darling. Let's go.
G-60.
G-60. G-60.
Excuse me, ma'am.
G-60.
Oh, right here.
Hey, how you doing?
Jack. Nice to meet you.
Jack Dawson. Nice to meet you.
How you doing?
Who says you get top bunk, huh?
[Fabrizio laughs]
[in Swedish] Where's Sven?
[in English] This is your
private promenade deck, sir.
Would you be requiring anything?
-Mm.
-Excuse me.
-[girl] This one?
-[Rose] No.
It had a lot of faces on it.
This is the one.
Would you like all of them out, miss?
Yes. We need a little color in this room.
Put it in there. In the wardrobe.
God, not those finger paintings again.
They certainly were a waste of money.
[Rose] The difference between
Cal's taste in art
and mine is that I have some.
They're fascinating.
Like being inside a dream or something.
There's truth but no logic.
-What's the artist's name?
-Something Picasso.
Something Picasso.
He won't amount to a thing.
He won't, trust me.
[Rose] Let's put the Degas in the bedroom.
At least they were cheap.
Put it in the wardrobe.
[man] Passengers to the upper deck,
we're boarding please.
[old Rose] At Cherbourg,
a woman came aboard
named Margaret Brown.
We all called her Molly.
History would call her
the Unsinkable Molly Brown.
Well, I wasn't about to
wait all day for you, sonny.
Here, you think you can manage?
Yes, ma'am.
[old Rose] Her husband had struck gold
someplace out west.
And she was what Mother
called "new money."
By the next afternoon,
we were steaming west
from the coast of Ireland
with nothing out ahead of us but ocean.
Take her to sea, Mr. Murdoch.
Let's stretch her legs.
Yes, sir.
All ahead full, Mr. Moody.
Very good, sir.
[engine telegraph ringing]
[machine dings]
All ahead full.
[ringing]
All ahead full!
[Engineer Bell] Come on, lads.
Step lively!
[engineers shouting]
All right! Let's stoke her right up!
We go full ahead!
Come on, put your backs into it!
[wind howls]
Mummy!
Twenty-one knots, sir.
Hey, look, look, look!
See it?
There's another one! See him?
Look at that one! Look at him jump!
[whooping]
[stokers grunting]
Whoo!
I can see the Statue of Liberty already.
Very small, of course.
I'm the king of the world!
[whooping]
[both whooping]
Yee-hah!
[howling]
[Bruce] She is the largest moving object
ever made by the hand of man
in all history.
And our master shipbuilder,
Mr. Andrews here
designed her from the keel plates up.
I may have knocked her together,
but the idea was Mr. Ismay's.
He envisioned a steamer so grand in scale
and so luxurious in its appointments
that its supremacy
would never be challenged.
And here she is.
-Willed into solid reality.
-[Cal] Hear, hear.
I'll have the salmon.
You know I don't like that, Rose.
She knows.
Hmm. We'll both have the lamb.
Rare, with very little mint sauce.
Hmm. You like lamb, right, sweet pea?
You gonna cut her meat for her
too there, Cal? [chuckles]
Hey, who thought of the name Titanic?
Was it you, Bruce?
Yes, actually.
I wanted to convey sheer size.
And size means stability,
luxury, and above all, strength.
Do you know of Dr. Freud, Mr. Ismay?
His ideas about the male
preoccupation with size
might be of particular interest to you.
[whispers] What's gotten into you?
Excuse me.
I do apologize.
She's a pistol, Cal.
Hope you can handle her.
Well, I may have to start minding
what she reads from
now on, won't I, Mrs. Brown?
Freud? Who is he? Is he a passenger?
It's a great big shaft,
goes right through the middle of the boat.
It's known as a propeller.
And it goes right along there
and it makes these waves.
Makes them spin.
[Fabrizio] The ship is nice, huh?
[man in Irish accent]
Yeah. It's an Irish ship.
-[Fabrizio] Is English, no?
-No, it was built in Ireland.
Fifteen thousand Irish men
built this ship.
Solid as a rock. Big Irish hands.
That's typical.
First-class dogs come down
here to take a shite.
Lets us know where we rank
in the scheme of things.
Like we could forget?
[Jack laughs]
I'm Tommy Ryan.
-Jack Dawson.
-Hello.
-Fabrizio.
-Hi.
Do you make any money with your drawings?
Ah, forget it, boyo.
You'd as like have
angels fly out of your arse
as get next to the likes of her.
[Fabrizio laughs]
-Do you mind?
-I hope you're proud of yourself.
[old Rose] I saw my whole life
as if I'd already lived it.
An endless parade
of parties and cotillions,
yachts and polo matches.
Always the same narrow people,
the same mindless chatter.
I felt like I was standing
at a great precipice
with no one to pull me back.
No one who cared
or even noticed.
[panting]
Really, miss.
[Rose sobbing]
[running footsteps]
[Rose panting]
[ocean roaring]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
Don't do it.
Stay back.
Don't come any closer.
Come on.
Just give me your hand.
I'll pull you back over.
No! Stay where you are.
I mean it.
I'll let go.
No, you won't.
What do you mean, no, I won't?
Don't presume to tell me
what I will and will not do.
You don't know me.
Well, you would have done it already.
You're distracting me. Go away.
I can't.
I'm involved now.
You let go, and I'm going to have to
jump in there after you.
Don't be absurd.
-You'll be killed.
-I'm a good swimmer.
The fall alone will kill you.
It would hurt. I'm not saying it wouldn't.
Tell you the truth,
I'm a lot more concerned
about that water being so cold.
How cold?
Freezing. Maybe a couple degrees over.
You ever, uh, ever been to Wisconsin?
What?
Well, they have some of
the coldest winters around.
I grew up there, near Chippewa Falls.
I remember when I was a kid,
me and my father, we went ice fishing
out on Lake Wissota.
Ice fishing is, you know, where you--
I know what ice fishing is!
Sorry.
You just seem like, you know,
kind of an indoor girl.
Anyway, I…
I fell through some thin ice.
And I'm telling you
water that cold, like right down there,
it hits you like 1,000 knives
stabbing you all over your body.
You can't breathe. You can't think.
Least not about anything but the pain.
Which is why I'm not looking forward
to jumping in there after you.
Like I said…
I don't have a choice.
I guess I'm kind of hoping
you'll come back over the rail
and get me off the hook here.
You're crazy.
That's what everybody says, but…
with all due respect, miss,
I'm not the one hanging off
the back of a ship here.
Come on.
Come on, give me your hand.
You don't want to do this.
Phew.
I'm Jack Dawson.
Rose DeWitt Bukater.
I'll have to get you to
write that one down.
[Rose laughs]
Come on.
[Rose screams]
[Jack grunting]
-[screaming]
-I got you. Come on.
Come on.
[screaming]
Help, please!
[screaming] Help!
Please, help me!
Listen. Listen to me.
I've got you. I won't let go.
Now pull yourself up. Come on!
[both grunting]
Come on. That's right.
You can do it.
[Rose grunts]
I got you.
[both grunting]
What's all this?
[Rose gasping]
You stand back and don't move an inch!
Fetch the Master at Arms.
Care for a brandy?
This is completely unacceptable!
What made you think
that you could put your hands
on my fiancée?
-Look at me, you filth!
-Cal.
What do you think you were doing?
Cal, stop. It was an accident.
An accident?
It was.
Stupid, really.
I was leaning over and I slipped.
I was leaning far over to see the, uh,
uh, uh, the, uh…
-Propellers?
-Propellers, and I slipped.
And I would have gone overboard
but Mr. Dawson here saved me.
And almost went over himself.
You wanted to see the…
She wanted to see the propellers.
Like I said,
women and machinery do not mix.
Was that the way of it?
Yeah. Yeah, that was pretty much it.
Well, the boy's a hero, then.
Good for you, son. Well done.
So, it's all's well
and back to our brandy, eh?
Look at you. You must be freezing.
Let's get you inside.
Perhaps a little something for the boy?
Of course.
Mr. Lovejoy, I think a 20 should do it.
Is that the going rate
for saving the woman you love?
Rose is displeased.
What to do?
I know.
Perhaps you could join us
for dinner tomorrow evening
to regale our group with your heroic tale.
Sure. Count me in.
Good. It's settled then.
This should be interesting.
[whistles]
Can I, uh, bum a smoke?
You'll want to tie those.
It's interesting…
The young lady slipped so suddenly
and you still had time
to remove your jacket and your shoes.
[tune plays on music box]
[knocking]
I know you've been melancholy.
I don't pretend to know why.
I intended to save this
until the engagement gala next week
but I thought
tonight.
-Good gracious.
-[chuckles]
Perhaps as a reminder
of my feelings for you.
-Is it a--
-Diamond. Yes. [laughs]
Fifty-six carats to be exact.
It was worn by Louis XVI.
And they called it "Le Coeur de la Mer."
-"The Heart of the Ocean."
Yes. [laughs]
It's overwhelming.
Well, it's for royalty.
We are royalty, Rose.
You know, there's nothing
I couldn't give you.
There's nothing I'd deny you
if you would not deny me.
Open your heart to me, Rose.
[Jack] Well, I've been on my own
since I was 15, since my folks died.
And I had no brothers
or sisters or close kin
in that part of the country,
so I lit on out of there
and I haven't been back since.
You could just call me
a tumbleweed blowing in the wind.
[both chuckle]
Well, Rose, we've walked
about a mile around this boat deck
and chewed over
how great the weather's been
and how I grew up,
but I reckon that's not why
you came to talk to me, is it?
-[sighs] Mr. Dawson, I--
-Jack.
Jack.
I want to thank you for what you did.
Not just for pulling me back,
but for your discretion.
You're welcome.
Look.
I know what you must be thinking.
Poor little rich girl.
What does she know about misery?
No.
No, that's not what I was thinking.
What I was thinking was
what could have happened to this girl
to make her think she had no way out?
Well I…
It was everything. It was my whole world
and all the people in it.
And the inertia of my life,
plunging ahead, and me,
powerless to stop it.
God, look at that thing.
You would have gone
straight to the bottom.
Five hundred invitations have gone out.
All of Philadelphia society will be there.
And all the while, I feel I'm standing
in the middle of a crowded room,
screaming at the top of my lungs,
and no one even looks up.
Do you love him?
-Pardon me?
-Do you love him?
You're being very rude.
You shouldn't be asking me this.
Well, it's a simple question.
Do you love the guy or not?
[scoffs]
This is not a suitable conversation.
Why can't you just answer the question?
[laughs]
This is absurd.
You don't know me and I don't know you,
and we are not having
this conversation at all.
You are rude and uncouth and presumptuous
and I am leaving now,
Jack. Mr. Dawson. It's been a pleasure.
I sought you out to thank you
and now I have thanked you.
And you've insulted me.
Well, you deserved it.
-Right.
I thought you were leaving.
I am.
You are so annoying.
[laughs]
Wait. I don't have to leave.
This is my part of the ship. You leave.
Oh-ho-ho-ho. Well, well, well.
Now who's being rude?
[Rose laughs]
What is this stupid thing
you're carrying around?
So, what are you, an artist or something?
Well…
These are rather good.
They're, uh… They're very good, actually.
Jack, this is exquisite work.
Ah, they didn't think too
much of them in old Paris.
Paris?
You do get around for a p…
Well, uh, a person of limited means.
Go on. A poor guy. You can say it.
Well, well, well.
And these were drawn from life?
Well, that's one of
the good things about Paris.
Lots of girls are willing
to take their clothes off.
[Rose laughs]
You liked this woman.
You used her several times.
Well…
She had beautiful hands, you see?
I think you must have had
a love affair with her.
No, no, no. Just with her hands.
She was a one-legged prostitute.
See?
Oh.
[both laugh]
She had a good sense of humor, though.
Oh, and this lady…
She used to sit at this bar every night
wearing every piece of jewelry she owned,
just waiting for her long, lost love.
We called her Madame Bijoux.
See how her clothes are all moth eaten?
Well, you have a gift, Jack.
You do.
You see people.
I see you.
And?
You wouldn't have jumped.
But the purpose of university
is to find a suitable husband.
Rose has already done that.
Look, here comes that vulgar Brown woman.
Quickly, get up before she sits with us.
Hello, girls.
I was hoping I'd catch you at tea.
We're awfully sorry, you missed it.
The Countess and I were just off
to take the air on the boat deck.
What a lovely idea.
I need to catch up on my gossip.
Countess.
So, you've not yet lit
the last four boilers?
No, I don't see the need.
We are making excellent time.
The press knows the size of Titanic.
Now, I want them to marvel at her speed.
We must give them something new to print.
This maiden voyage of Titanic
must make headlines.
Mr. Ismay, I would prefer
not to push the engines
until they've been properly run in.
Of course I'm just a passenger.
I leave it to your good offices
to decide what's best.
But what a glorious end
to your final crossing
if we were to get
into New York on Tuesday night
and surprise them all.
Make the morning papers.
Retire with a bang, eh, E.J.?
Good man.
Well, after that,
I worked on a squid boat in Monterey,
then I went down to Los Angeles
to the pier in Santa Monica
and started doing portraits there
for ten cents apiece.
Why can't I be like you, Jack?
Just head out for the horizon
whenever I feel like it.
Say we'll go there sometime, to that pier,
even if we only ever just talk about it.
No, we'll do it.
We'll drink cheap beer.
We'll ride on the roller-coaster
till we throw up.
[laughs]
Then we'll ride horses on the beach,
right in the surf.
Now, but you'll have to do it
like a real cowboy.
None of that sidesaddle stuff.
You mean one leg on each side?
Yeah.
Can you show me?
Sure, if you like.
Teach me to ride like a man.
[in Western American accent]
And chew tobacco like a man.
And spit like a man.
What, they didn't teach you
that in finishing school?
No. [laughs]
Come on, I'll show you. Let's do it.
-What?
-I'll show you how. Come on.
-Jack, no! Jack, no!
-Oh, come on! Come on.
-Wait, Jack!
-Come on.
-No, Jack…
-Come on!
I couldn't possibly, Jack.
Watch closely.
[hawking phlegm]
That's disgusting!
All right, your turn.
[Rose sniffs]
That was pitiful.
Come on, you really gotta hawk
it back, you know.
Get some leverage to it. Use your arms.
[snorts] Arc your neck.
-[hawking]
-[Rose clears throat]
Now, you see the range on that thing?
Mm-hmm.
[Jack] Okay, go.
Oh, that was better.
-You gotta work on it.
-Really?
Really try to hawk it up
and get some body to it,
you know? You gotta…
[snorts]
[Jack gulps]
Mother.
May I introduce Jack Dawson?
Charmed, I'm sure.
[old Rose] The others
were gracious and curious
about the man who'd saved my life.
But my mother looked at him
like an insect.
A dangerous insect
which must be squashed quickly.
Well, Jack, sounds like you're a good man
to have around in a sticky spot.
[fanfare playing]
Why do they always insist
on announcing dinner
like a damn cavalry charge?
[laughs]
Shall we go dress, Mother?
See you at dinner, Jack.
Uh, son?
Son!
Do you have the slightest comprehension
what you're doing?
Not really.
Well, you're about to go
into the snake pit.
What are you planning to wear?
[scoffs] I figured. Come on.
I was right.
You and my son
are just about the same size.
Pretty close.
[whistles]
You shine up like a new penny.
[laughs]
Good evening, sir.
[orchestra plays "The Blue Danube"]
Hello.
[Cal] Do you know that there
are several thousand tons
of Hockley steel in this very ship?
[Ruth] Which part?
[Cal] All the right ones, of course.
Then we'll know who to hold accountable
if there's a problem. Where's my daughter?
Oh, she'll be along.
There is the Countess.
-Hello, my dear.
-Good evening, Cal.
It's so good to see you.
I saw that in a nickelodeon once
and I always wanted to do it.
[both laugh]
[Ruth] I'll see you at dinner.
Darling, surely you remember Mr. Dawson.
Dawson.
[laughs] Well, that's amazing.
You could almost pass for a gentleman.
Almost.
That's extraordinary.
[Lucile] My dear,
it's delightful to see you.
[Cal] Cosmo.
What a remarkable voyage this is.
It's mad, isn't it?
How lovely.
There's the Countess of Rothes.
And that's John Jacob Astor,
the richest man on the ship.
His little wifey there, Madeleine,
is my age and in a delicate condition.
See how she's trying to hide it.
-Quite the scandal.
-Hmm.
And that's Benjamin Guggenheim
and his mistress, Madame Aubert.
Mrs. Guggenheim is at home
with the children, of course.
And over here we have Sir Cosmo
and Lucile, Lady Duff-Gordon.
She designs naughty lingerie,
among her many talents.
Very popular with the royals.
Congratulations, Hockley. She's splendid.
Why, thank you.
Care to escort a lady to dinner?
-Certainly.
-[laughs]
-[Ruth laughs]
-Sweet pea, sweet pea.
Ain't nothing to it, is there, Jack?
Remember, they love money
so just pretend like you own a gold mine,
and you're in the club.
Hey, Astor.
Well, hello, Molly.
Nice to see you.
J.J., Madeleine, I'd like you
to meet Jack Dawson.
-How do you do?
-Pleasure.
Hello, Jack.
Are you of the Boston Dawsons?
No, the Chippewa Falls Dawsons, actually.
Oh, yes.
[old Rose] He must have been nervous,
but he never faltered.
They assumed he was one of them.
Heir to a railroad fortune, perhaps.
New money, obviously,
but still a member of the club.
Mother, of course,
could always be counted upon.
Tell us of the accommodations
in steerage, Mr. Dawson.
I hear they're quite good on this ship.
The best I've seen, ma'am.
Hardly any rats.
[laughter]
Mr. Dawson is joining us
from the third class.
He was of some assistance
to my fiancée last night.
It turns out that Mr. Dawson
is quite a fine artist.
He was kind enough to show me
some of his work today.
Rose and I differ somewhat
in our definition of fine art.
Not to impugn your work, sir.
[Rose clears throat]
[mouths]
[Ismay] She may be mine on paper,
in the eyes of God,
she belongs to Thomas Adlers.
Are these all for me?
Just start from the outside
and work your way in.
He knows every rivet in her,
don't you, Thomas?
-Indeed.
-Your ship
is a wonder, Mr. Andrews, truly.
Thank you, Rose.
How do you take your caviar, sir?
No caviar for me, thanks.
Never did like it much.
And where exactly do you live, Mr. Dawson?
Well, right now,
my address is the RMS Titanic.
After that, I'm on God's good humor.
And how is it you have means to travel?
I work my way from place to place.
You know, tramp steamers and such.
But I won my ticket on Titanic here
at a lucky hand at poker.
A very lucky hand.
All life is a game of luck.
A real man makes his own luck, Archie.
Right, Dawson?
Mm.
And you find that sort of
rootless existence appealing, do you?
Well, yes, ma'am, I do.
I mean, I've got everything
I need right here with me.
Got air in my lungs
and a few blank sheets of paper.
I mean, I love waking up in the morning,
not knowing what's gonna happen
or who I'm gonna meet.
Where I'm gonna wind up.
Just the other night
I was sleeping under a bridge,
and now, here I am,
on the grandest ship in the world,
having champagne with you fine people.
I'll take some of that.
I figure life's a gift,
and I don't intend on wasting it.
You never know what hand
you're gonna get dealt next.
You learn to take life as it comes at you.
Oh, here you go, Cal.
To make each day count.
Well said, Jack.
Hear, hear.
To making it count.
[all] To making it count.
Bravo.
[Molly laughing]
[Molly] But Mr. Brown had no idea
I'd hidden the money in the stove.
[laughter]
So, he comes home
drunk as a pig celebrating
and he lights a fire.
[laughter]
[Col. Gracie] Bravo.
Next it'll be brandies
in the smoking room.
Well, join me in a brandy, gentlemen?
-[Ismay] What a good idea!
-[Cal] Yes.
Now they'll retreat into a cloud of smoke
and congratulate each other
on being masters of the universe.
Ladies, thank you
for the pleasure of your company.
Rose, may I escort you back to the cabin?
No, I'll stay here.
Here you go, Molly.
[Col. Archibald] Joining us, Dawson?
Well, you don't want to stay out here
with the women, do you? [chuckles]
No, thanks. I've gotta be heading back.
[Col. Archibald] Ah.
Probably best.
It'll be all business and politics,
that sort of thing.
Wouldn't interest you.
But, Dawson, good of you to come.
Jack, must you go?
Time for me to go row
with the other slaves.
[laughs]
Good night, Rose.
[clock chiming]
[exhales]
So, you wanna go to a real party?
[whooping]
[playing Irish jig]
Is okay if put my hand here? Okay.
[speaking Swedish]
[in English] What?
[in English] I can't understand you.
[glass smashing]
[indiscernible chatter]
[laughs]
[Fabrizio laughing]
-[music ends]
-[cheering]
[Fabrizio] Bravo!
Let's go!
I'm gonna dance with her now, all right?
Come on.
-What?
-Come on.
-Come with me.
-What? Jack. Jack, wait.
I can't do this.
We're gonna have to get
a little bit closer.
Like this.
[Irish jig playing]
You're still my best girl, Cora.
I don't know the steps.
Neither do I. Just go with it.
[laughs]
-Don't think.
-[exclaims]
[laughs]
[Jack whooping]
[whooping]
Wait! Jack, Jack! Wait! Stop, Jack!
Bom, bom, bom.
[whooping]
Jack, what? Wait!
[Jack] Whoo-hoo!
[Rose laughing]
[Jack] Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Jack, no!
Wow!
[screams]
[laughs]
Beyond the jurisdiction
of the Sherman Act.
That's how my lawyers will argue.
That's what Rockefeller said,
but the Supreme Court
is not swallowing it.
[shouts of encouragement]
[speaking Swedish]
What?
You think a first-class girl can't drink?
[laughs]
-[Rose] Oh!
-[screams]
Hey, get out of here.
-You all right?
-[laughs]
-I'm fine.
-[Bjorn roars]
Two out of three. Two out of three.
Yeah, you the man. You the man-beast!
So…
you think you're big, tough men?
Let's see you do this.
Hold this for me, Jack. Hold it up.
-Ow! [laughs]
-Whoa!
-Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
-You all right?
I haven't done that in years.
-[Rose laughing]
-[music ends]
Go see Maggie, lads. Give her the holley!
Let's go.
[whooping]
Oh, here. Come on.
Coffee, sir?
I had hoped you would come
to me last night.
I was tired.
Your exertions below decks
were no doubt exhausting.
I see you had that undertaker
of a manservant follow me. How typical.
You will never behave
like that again, Rose.
Do you understand?
I'm not a foreman in one of your mills
that you can command.
I'm your fiancée.
[quietly] My fiancée.
[shouting] My fiancée!
Yes, you are! And my wife!
My wife in practice, if not yet by law,
so you will honor me!
You will honor me the way a wife
is required to honor a husband.
Because I will not be made out
a fool, Rose.
Is this in any way unclear?
-No.
-Good.
Excuse me.
[Rose gasping]
Oh, Miss Rose.
[panting] We had a little accident.
It's all right, Miss Rose. It's all right.
-I'm sorry, Trudy.
-It's all right.
Let me help you.
It's all right, miss.
[sobs]
Tea, Trudy.
Yes, ma'am.
You're not to see that boy again.
Do you understand me?
Rose, I forbid it.
Oh, stop it, Mother.
You'll give yourself a nosebleed.
This is not a game.
Our situation is precarious.
You know the money's gone.
Of course, I know it's gone.
You remind me every day.
Your father left us nothing
but a legacy of bad debts
hidden by a good name.
That name is the only card
we have to play.
I don't understand you.
It is a fine match with Hockley.
It will ensure our survival.
How can you put this on my shoulders?
Why are you being so selfish?
I'm being selfish?
Do you want to see me
working as a seamstress?
Is that what you want?
To see our fine things sold at auction?
Our memories scattered to the winds?
[sighs] It's so unfair.
Of course it's unfair.
We're women.
Our choices are never easy.
Mm?
[all] ♪ Wherever, Lord our brethren go ♪
♪ Protect them by Thy guiding hand ♪
♪ From every peril on the land ♪
♪ O, spirit whom the Father sent ♪
♪ To spread abroad the firmament ♪
♪ O, wind of heaven, by Thy might ♪
♪ Save all who dare the eagle's flight ♪
♪ And keep them by Thy watchful… ♪
-Hello, Mr. Andrews.
-Hello, Jack.
♪ O Trinity of love and power… ♪
Sir. Sir.
I just need to talk to somebody for a sec.
You're not supposed to be in here.
Just need to speak to someone.
♪ Fire, and foe ♪
♪ Protect them… ♪
I was just here last night.
You don't remember me?
No, I'm afraid I don't.
Now you're gonna have to turn around.
He'll tell you.
I just need to talk to…
Mr. Hockley and Mrs. DeWitt Bukater
continue to be appreciative
of your assistance.
They asked me
to give you this in gratitude.
I don't want your money, please, I just--
And also to remind you
that you hold a third-class ticket
and that your presence here is
no longer appropriate.
Please, I just wanna speak to Rose
for one second, all right? Please!
Gentlemen, please see that Mr. Dawson
gets back to where he belongs
and that he stays there?
Yes, sir. Come along, you.
♪ O hear us when we cry to Thee ♪
♪ For those in peril on the sea ♪
[Ruth] And why do you have
two steering wheels?
We really only use this near shore.
Excuse me, sir. Another ice warning.
This one's from the Noordam.
[Capt. Smith] Thank you, Sparks.
Oh, not to worry.
Quite normal for this time of year.
In fact, we're speeding up.
I've just ordered the last boilers lit.
[grunting]
[man] Okay, son, wind it up tight
like I showed you. That's right.
Okay, now, let it go.
-That's good, wasn't it?
-Quite nice.
That's excellent, son.
[Rose] Mr. Andrews, forgive me…
I did the sum in my head.
And with the number of lifeboats
times the capacity you mentioned,
forgive me, but it seems that
there are not enough for everyone aboard.
About half, actually.
Rose, you miss nothing, do you?
In fact, I put in these new type davits
which can take an extra row
of boats inside this one.
But it was thought, by some,
that the deck would look too cluttered.
So, I was overruled.
Waste of deck space as it is
on an unsinkable ship.
Sleep soundly, young Rose.
I have built you a good ship.
Strong and true.
She's all the lifeboat you need.
Just keep heading aft.
The next stop will be the engine room.
Come on.
Jack.
This is impossible.
-I can't see you.
-I need to talk to you.
No, Jack. No.
Jack, I'm engaged.
I'm marrying Cal.
I love Cal.
Rose, you're no picnic.
All right? You're a spoiled
little brat even.
But under that,
you're the most amazingly astounding,
wonderful girl…
woman that I've ever known.
-And…
-Jack, I…
No, let me try and get this out. You're…
I'm not an idiot.
I know how the world works.
I've got ten bucks in my pocket,
I have nothing to offer you,
and I know that.
I understand.
But I'm too involved now.
You jump, I jump, remember?
I can't turn away
without knowing you'll be all right.
That's all that I want.
Well, I'm fine.
I'll be fine. Really.
Really?
I don't think so.
They've got you trapped, Rose.
And you're gonna die
if you don't break free.
Maybe not right away
because you're strong, but…
sooner or later,
that fire that I love about you, Rose,
that fire is gonna burn out.
It's not up to you to save me, Jack.
You're right.
Only you can do that.
I'm going back. Leave me alone.
[door shuts]
Tell Lucile about the disaster you had
with the stationers.
Well, of course, the invitations
had to be sent back twice.
Oh, my dear.
And the dreadful bridesmaids gowns,
let me tell you what
an odyssey that has been.
Rose decided she wanted lavender.
She knows I detest the color.
So she did it only to spite me.
[Lady Gordon] If only
you'd come to me sooner.
Ruth saw some of my designs
in La Mode Illustrée.
They were for the trousseau of the Duchess
of Marlborough's youngest daughter.
They were quite charming.
But I think you'll agree, my dear,
that together we've created
something of a phoenix from the ashes.
[laughter]
Hello, Jack.
I changed my mind.
-They said you might be up here.
-Shh.
Give me your hand.
Now close your eyes.
Go on.
Now, step up.
Now, hold onto the railing.
Keep your eyes closed, don't peek.
I'm not.
Step up onto the rail.
Hold on. Hold on.
-Keep your eyes closed.
-[laughs]
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
All right. Open your eyes.
[Rose gasps]
I'm flying! Jack!
♪ Come, Josephine
In my flying machine ♪
♪ Going up, she goes ♪
♪ Up, she goes ♪
[muffled radio chatter]
That was the last time Titanic
ever saw daylight.
So we're up to dusk
the night of the sinking.
Six hours to go.
Incredible. There's Smith
and he's standing there,
and he's got the iceberg warning
in his fucking hand.
Excuse me. His hand,
and he's ordering more speed.
Twenty-six years of experience
working against him.
He figures anything big enough
to sink the ship,
they're gonna see in time to turn.
The ship's too big
with too small a rudder.
Doesn't corner worth a damn.
Everything he knows is wrong.
[laughing] It's quite proper,
I assure you.
This is the sitting room.
-Will this light do?
-What?
Don't artists need good light?
[in French accent] That is true,
but I'm not used to working
in such horrible conditions.
Monet.
Do you know his work?
Of course.
Look at his use of color here.
Isn't he great?
[Rose] I know. It's extraordinary.
Cal insists on carting
this hideous thing everywhere.
Should we be expecting him anytime soon?
Not as long as the cigars
and brandy hold out.
Whew. That's nice. What is it, a sapphire?
A diamond. A very rare diamond.
Jack, I want you to draw me
like one of your French girls.
Wearing this.
All right.
Wearing only this.
The last thing I need
is another picture of me
looking like a porcelain doll.
As a paying customer…
I expect to get what I want.
Over on the bed, uh, the couch.
Come. Lie down.
-Yeah, keep that…
-Tell me when it looks right.
Put your arm back the way it was.
Right.
Put that other arm up.
That hand right by your face, there.
Right.
Now, head down.
Eyes to me, keep them on me.
And try to stay still.
[Rose clears throat]
[exhales]
So serious.
I believe you are blushing,
Mr. Big Artiste.
Can't imagine Monsieur Monet blushing.
He does landscapes.
Just relax your face.
-Sorry.
-No laughing.
[Rose exhales]
My heart was pounding the whole time.
It was the most erotic moment of my life.
Up until then, at least.
So what happened next?
You mean, did we do it?
Sorry to disappoint you, Mr. Bodine.
Jack was very professional.
[blows]
Thank you.
[both laughing]
Whatcha doin'?
Will you put this back in the safe for me?
[Jack] Mm-hmm.
Whew.
[indistinct chatter]
Gentlemen, would you excuse me?
Of course.
None of the stewards have seen her.
This is absurd.
It's a ship. There's only
so many places she could be.
Lovejoy, find her.
-Clear.
-Yes.
I don't think I've ever seen
such a flat calm.
Like a mill pond. [chuckles]
Not a breath of wind.
It will make the 'bergs harder to see.
With no breaking water at the base.
[Capt. Smith] Hmm.
Well, I'm off. Maintain speed
and heading, Mr. Lightoller.
Yes, sir.
[blows]
It's getting cold. You look nice.
-[knocking]
-[Lovejoy] Miss Rose?
My drawings.
[door lock clicks]
[Rose laughs]
Come on!
[Rose laughs] No, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
[Jack] Go, go! Down, down, down!
Take us down! Quick! Quickly!
-Go, go, go!
-[Rose] Quickly, quickly!
[both laugh]
Bye!
Sorry. [laughs]
It's all right, sir. I've got it.
[both laughing]
Pretty tough for a valet, this fella.
Seems more like a cop.
I think he was.
-[Jack] Oh, shit!
-[Rose] Go!
Hold on!
-[Rose screams]
-No, over here!
[Rose] Quick!
[fans roaring]
-[rumbling]
-Now what?
-What?
-[laughs]
[man] Coal. More coal
for number one, mate.
Hold on. What are you two doing down here?
You shouldn't be down here.
It could be dangerous. Oi!
Carry on. Don't mind us.
You're doing a great job.
Keep up the good work.
[Jack] Ah. Look what we have here, huh?
[Jack chuckles]
[Rose clears throat]
[Jack clears throat]
Thank you.
-[honks horn]
-[laughs]
Where to, miss?
To the stars.
[jack laughs]
You nervous?
[quietly] No.
Put your hands on me, Jack.
Cold. It's bloody cold.
You know, I can smell ice, you know.
When it's near.
Bollocks!
Well, I can, all right.
Did you ever find those
binoculars for the lookouts?
Haven't seen them since Southampton.
Well, I'll be on my rounds. Cheerio.
[Jack breathing heavily]
You're trembling.
Don't worry. I'll be all right.
They ran down there.
Right.
[Lovejoy] Anything missing?
I've got a better idea.
[clicks fingers]
Got ya!
[both laughing]
Did you see those guys' faces?
Did you see them?
When the ship docks…
I'm getting off with you.
This is crazy.
I know. It doesn't make any sense.
That's why I trust it.
Oh, yes. Here, look at this.
Look at that, would ya?
They're a bit warmer than we are.
Well, if that's what it takes
for us to get warm,
I'd rather not, if it's all
the same to you, all right?
[chuckles]
-Bugger me!
-[bell ringing]
[phone ringing]
Pick up, you bastards.
[phone continues ringing]
[Fleet] Is there anyone there?
Yes. What do you see?
Iceberg right ahead.
Thank you.
Iceberg, right ahead.
-Hard to starboard.
Turn! Turn! Smartly!
-[engine telegraph rings]
-Hey, I'll have some of that.
-Hey.
-Full astern!
Hard over.
[Moody] Helm's hard over, sir.
[engine telegraph ringing]
-Go, lads, go.
-[engineer 1] Faster, faster!
[Engineer Bell] Bring that
steam down! Bring it down!
Shut all the dampers!
Shut them.
[doors slamming]
Hold it.
-Now! Engage the reversing engine.
-[engineer 2] Bring them down!
[indistinct shouting]
Why ain't they turning?
Is it hard over?
It is. Yes, sir. Hard over.
[quietly] Come on, come on.
Come on, turn.
[Engineer Bell] Go, lads, go!
Step lively, go!
Yes.
It's gonna hit!
Jesus Christ!
[creaking]
[metallic scraping]
[glass tinkling]
Jesus.
-Hard to port!
-[Moody] Hard to port!
[screaming]
[Jack] Get back!
[men grunt]
[screams]
[man 1] Come on!
[man 2] Get down!
[screaming]
[alarm ringing]
Come on, let's go! Get out the door!
They're closing the doors!
-Get out!
-[man 3] Get out!
Get out of here!
Get out of here! Get out!
Get out the door! Go!
Go! Come on, lads!
Go, lads, go!
Get out!
Go, go!
Go, come on.
[Barrett] Out! Out!
Oh, my God.
That was a close shave, wasn't it?
Smell ice, can you? Bleedin' Christ.
Is that hull leaking in?
Note the time. Enter it in the log.
What was that, Mr. Murdoch?
An iceberg, sir.
I put her hard to starboard
and ran the engines full astern,
but it was too close.
I tried to port around it but she hit and…
[Capt. Smith] Close the watertight doors.
[Murdoch] The doors are closed, sir.
All stop.
[quartermaster] Aye, sir.
[engine telegraph ringing]
Find the carpenter.
-Get him to sound the ship.
-Yes, sir.
-[splashing]
-[exclaims in Italian]
[speaking Swedish]
[in English] Come on,
let's get the hell out of here.
Come on, hurry up.
Excuse me, why have the engines stopped?
I felt a shudder.
I shouldn't worry, madam.
We've likely thrown a propeller blade.
That's the shudder you felt.
May I bring you anything?
No, thank you.
[man 1] Say, old man,
there's talk of an iceberg.
You see anything?
[man 2] Well, I don't see
anything now. Do you?
[man 3] Water!
If this is the direction
the rats are going,
that's good enough for me.
[steward 1] Please, sir. Please.
Everything's under control.
[steward 2] There's nothing
to worry about at all.
-You there.
-Sir, there is no emergency.
Yes, there is. I have been robbed.
Get the Master-at-Arms.
-Now, you moron.
-Yes, sir.
[men laughing]
Hey! Did I miss the fun?
-Did you see what happened?
-No, I missed it.
Apparently, it hit over there.
[Hutchinson] Boiler room six is flooded
eight feet above the plate
and the mail hold is worse.
She's all buckled in in the forward hold.
Can you shore up?
Not unless the pumps get ahead.
Have you seen the damage in the mail hold?
No, she's already under water.
This is bad.
We should tell Mother and Cal.
I think they're very good, sir.
Don't touch anything.
I want the entire room photographed.
[Rose] Just keep holding my hand.
[woman] Harold, do you know
what's going on?
[Harold] I heard it's just the engine.
We've been looking for you, miss.
[Rose] Here we go.
Something serious has happened.
Yes, it has.
Indeed. Two things dear to me
have disappeared this evening.
Now that one is back,
I have a pretty good idea
where to find the other.
Search him.
-Take your coat off, son.
-Now what?
Come on, now.
Cal, what are you doing?
We are in the middle of an emergency.
What's going on?
-Is this it?
-That's it.
This is horseshit!
Don't you believe it, Rose. Don't.
-He couldn't have.
-[Cal] Of course, he could.
-It's easy enough for a professional.
-Come on.
But I was with him the whole time.
This is absurd.
Perhaps he did it while you were
putting your clothes back on, dear.
Real slick, Cal.
Rose, they put it in my pocket.
Shut up.
[Lovejoy] It isn't even
your pocket, is it, son?
"Property of A.L. Ryerson."
That was reported stolen today.
No, I just borrowed it.
-I was going to return it.
-[Cal] Oh, an honest thief.
We have an honest thief here, do we?
You know I didn't do this, Rose.
You know it.
Don't you believe them, Rose.
You know it. You know I didn't do it.
Come on, son, let's go. Come on, let's go.
Rose, you know I didn't do it, Rose!
-Don't make a fuss.
-Rose!
Come on. There's a good lad.
Come on, son. There's a good lad. Come on.
You know I didn't do it! You know me!
[Ismay] This is most unfortunate, Captain.
Water 14 feet above the keel
in ten minutes,
in the forepeak, in all three holds
and in boiler room six.
That's right, sir.
When can we get underway, damn it?
That's five compartments.
She can stay afloat with
the first four compartments breached,
but not five.
Not five.
As she goes down by the head,
the water will spill over
the tops of the bulkheads
at E deck from one to the next.
Back and back. There's no stopping it.
The pumps, if we opened the doors--
The pumps buy you time. But minutes only.
From this moment, no matter what we do,
Titanic will founder.
But this ship can't sink.
She's made of iron, sir.
I assure you, she can.
And she will.
It is a mathematical certainty.
How much time?
An hour. Two at most.
And how many aboard, Mr. Murdoch?
2,200 souls on board, sir.
Well, I believe you may
get your headlines, Mr. Ismay.
[sighs]
Oh, it is a little slut, isn't it?
You look at me when I'm talking to you!
[knocking]
-[steward Barnes] Mr. Hockley?
-Not now, we're busy.
Sir, I've been told to ask you
to put on your lifebelts
-and come up to the boat deck.
-I said, not now.
I'm sorry to inconvenience you,
Mr. Hockley,
but it's Captain's orders.
Now, please, dress warmly.
It's quite cold out tonight.
Now may I suggest, top coats and hats.
This is ridiculous.
Not to worry, miss.
I'm sure it's just a precaution.
Everybody up, lifebelts on!
What? What's he on about?
Everybody up, put your lifebelts on.
What's the ruckus?
Just put your lifebelts on.
CQD? Sir?
That's right. CQD. The distress call.
That's our position.
[sighs]
Tell whoever responds
that we're going down by the head
and need immediate assistance.
Blimey.
[man 1] Hold her underway.
[Wilde] Keep lowering. Keep lowering.
-Aye, aye, sir.
-[Wilde] Pull.
[crewman] Easy now!
Steady! Make it taut! And winch it out!
Uncover this boat!
Uncover all the boats aft!
[Lightoller] Release those ties!
Roll back that cover!
Roll back that cover smartly, now!
[Andrews] Mr. Wilde.
[Wilde] Release the boat from…
Mr. Wilde. Where are the passengers?
They've all gone back inside.
Too damn cold and noisy for them.
You there. [whistle blows]
Get down here and help with these lines!
[lively music playing]
[chatter]
Care for a drink, sir?
-Please put your lifebelt on.
-Hey, sonny.
-Miss.
-What's doing?
You got us all trussed up here
and now we're cooling our heels.
Sorry, ma'am. Let me go and find out.
Make sure the straps are secure.
I don't think anybody knows
what the hell's going on around here.
It's just the goddamned English
doing everything by the book.
There's no need for language, Mr. Hockley.
Go back and turn the heaters on
in our rooms.
I'd like a cup of tea when I return.
-Yes, ma'am.
[steward] Will you put
your lifebelt on, please?
[woman] I don't understand
why didn't they know?
Mr. Andrews?
I saw the iceberg.
And I see it in your eyes.
Please tell me the truth.
[steward] Yes, madam.
Please, put it on immediately.
The ship will sink.
-You're certain?
-Yes.
In an hour or so.
All of this will be at
the bottom of the Atlantic.
What?
Please, tell only who you must.
I don't want to be responsible
for a panic.
And get to a boat, quickly. Don't wait.
You remember what I told you
about the boats?
Yes.
I understand.
[woman] Have I put this thing on right?
[steward] Yes, madam.
Please put it on immediately.
Over here, son.
Sir, they need you up in
the Second-Class Purser's office.
-There's a big mob up there.
-Go on.
I'll keep an eye on him.
Aye. Right.
[Bride] Sir.
Carpathia says they're making 17 knots.
Full steam for them, sir.
She's the only one who's responded?
The only one close, sir.
Says they can be here in four hours.
Four hours?
Thank you, Bride.
My God.
[Lightoller] I really
don't think so, Mr. Wilde.
Secure the falls aft.
Sir?
We are swung out and ready, sir.
Hadn't we better get the women
and children into the boats, sir?
[quietly] Yes.
Sir?
Women and children first. Yes.
Yes, sir.
[Lightoller] Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please!
Step this way, please! That's right!
Come towards me! Thank you!
Good.
For the time being,
I shall require only women and children.
Gentlemen, please stay where you are.
[Hartley] Right here.
All right, boys. Like the captain said.
Nice and cheery so there's no panic.
Gentlemen please stay
exactly where you are.
"Wedding Dance."
[lively music playing]
Lifebelts on. Here, put your lifebelts on.
Put your lifebelts on.
Here, put your lifebelt on.
Here, come on. Put your lifebelt on.
Turn that around.
[steward 2] Please, ladies and gentlemen,
there isn't any reason to panic.
It isn't time to go up to the boats yet.
Please, stay calm.
Look, please, make sure, everybody,
you've got your lifebelts on.
And gentlemen,
allow the women and children
through to the front.
-What are we doing, Mommy?
-We're just waiting, dear.
When they finish putting
first-class people in the boats,
they'll be starting with us,
and we'll want to be all ready, won't we?
[steward 1] Everybody, not just quite yet.
[steward 2] Don't push on the gates.
You won't get out any faster.
Go and get some help.
Lower it away.
Left and right together. Steady.
Both sides together. Steady.
Steady.
[crewman] All right, steady as she goes.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Hold the left side!
Right side only! Right side only!
Right side only! Hold the left side!
Right side down! Lower away together!
Steady, lads!
-[flare explodes]
-[all gasp]
[Wilde] I need two men each
to handle the fore and aft port. Now.
You know, I do believe this ship may sink.
I've been asked to give you
this small token of our appreciation.
Compliments of Mr. Caledon Hockley.
[panting]
[Lightoller] Step aboard, sir.
Come on, sister. You heard
the man. Into the boat.
[Lightoller] These gentlemen
will take care of you.
Any room for a gentleman, gentlemen?
[Hichens] Only women at this time, sir.
[Lightoller] Thank you.
This man here will take care of you.
Will the lifeboats be seated
according to class?
I hope they're not too crowded.
Oh, Mother. Shut up!
Don't you understand?
The water is freezing
and there aren't enough boats.
Not enough by half.
Half the people on this ship
are going to die.
Not the better half.
Come on, Ruth. Get in the boat.
First-class seats are right up here.
You know, it's a pity
I didn't keep that drawing.
It'll be worth a lot more by morning.
[Lightoller] Women and children
-towards the front beam.
-[flare exploding]
You unimaginable bastard.
[Molly] Come on, Rose, darlin'.
There's plenty of room for you.
[Lightoller] Right this way, miss.
Come on, Rose.
You're next, darlin'.
Come into the boat, Rose.
[Cal] Come.
Rose!
Get into the boat.
Rose.
Goodbye, Mother.
Rose?
Rose, come back here right now!
Where are you going?
What, to him?
What? To be a whore to a gutter rat?
[Ruth] No, wait!
I'd rather be his whore than your wife.
-No! No!
-[grunting]
I said, no!
[Ruth] Rose! Please, stop!
-[Lightoller] And lower away!
-No, Rose!
-[Lightoller] And together.
-No, wait!
Lower away!
-Rose!
-[Lightoller] Lower together!
Pull the left side in!
Help!
Can anybody hear me?
[clanging]
Hello, help me!
[in distance] Help me! Can you hear me?
Can anybody hear me?
Somebody help me!
[Rose] Mr. Andrews!
[panting]
Steward, check the starboard corridor.
Yes, Mr. Andrews.
Madam, please, put on a lifebelt,
get to the boat deck immediately.
Lucy, for God's sake,
put on your lifebelt.
-Set a good example.
-Yes, sir.
-Anyone in here?
-Mr. Andrews!
Mr. Andrews! Thank God!
Where would the Master-at-Arms
take someone under arrest?
What? You have to
get to a boat right away.
No! I'm doing this
with or without your help, sir.
But without will take longer.
Take the elevator to the very bottom,
go to the left.
Down the crewman's passage.
Then go right and left again
at the stairs,
you'll come to a long corridor.
[sighs]
[sighs] This could be bad.
[water running]
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
[grunting]
Excuse me. Thank you.
-[woman] I do not care what you think.
-The lifts are…
I'm sorry, miss, but the lifts are closed.
I'm through being polite, God damn it!
Now take me down!
E deck.
Come on!
Come on, come on!
[grunting]
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[Rose screams]
-I'm going back up!
-No!
No, no!
Miss!
Come back! I'm going back up!
I'm going back up!
Crew passage.
[water gurgling]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
Jack!
-Jack!
-Rose!
-Rose, I'm in here!
-I'm in here!
-Jack!
I'm in here!
-Rose!
Jack! Jack! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
That guy, Lovejoy, put it in my pocket.
I know! I know! I know! I know!
Listen, Rose,
you're gonna have to find
a spare key, all right?
All right.
Look in that cabinet right there.
It's a little silver one, Rose.
Silver one.
These are all brass ones!
Check right here, Rose.
Rose.
How did you find out I didn't do it?
I didn't. I just realized I already knew.
Keep looking!
No key.
-There's no key!
-All right, Rose, listen.
You're gonna have to go find some help.
It'll be all right.
I'll be right back.
[moans]
I'll just wait here!
[breathing heavily]
[creaking]
Hello, is there anyone here?
Hello!
Is there anybody down here?
We need help! Hello! [whimpers]
Damn it!
Can anybody hear me? Please! Hello!
Hello!
Oh, thank God! Wait, please!
I need your help!
There's a man back here and… [splutters]
Wait!
[panting]
Hello?
[breathing rapidly]
[breathing calms]
Hello?
Miss, you shouldn't be here now.
Wait. Please!
-I need your help.
-Come along.
This way, quickly.
There's a man down here and he is trapped.
-This way. Yes, all right.
-Please!
-There's no need to panic.
-No, I'm not panicking!
You're going the wrong way!
Let go of me! Listen!
To hell with you.
[moans]
[grunting]
[crewman shouts in distance]
[flare explodes]
[creaking]
Oh, my God.
[gasps]
[creaking]
Jack!
Rose!
Will this work?
I guess we'll find out. Come on!
Wait, wait, wait.
Try a couple of practice
swings over there.
All right.
-[grunts]
-Good.
Now try and hit the same mark
again, Rose. You can do it.
[grunts]
Okay, that's enough practice.
Come on, Rose. You can do it.
Listen, just hit it really
hard and really fast.
Come on. Wait!
Open your hands up a little more. Good.
-Like that?
-Right.
Listen, Rose. I trust you.
Go!
-[clang]
-[Rose screams]
[both laughing]
You did it!
Come on! Let's go!
Oh, shit, this is cold!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
This is the way out.
We have to find another way. Come on!
[crewman] Pull!
Pull!
Put your backs into it!
[band playing]
[people shouting]
Pull!
Now there's something you
don't see every day.
Pull!
[panicked shouting]
[whistle blowing]
[Lightoller] There's no room
for luggage in this boat!
What's this luggage
doing here? Get rid of it!
Get rid of it. We need the room.
Get rid of that. Out!
This way. Let go, sir! Get back!
-Keep calm. Sit down.
-[elderly woman sobbing]
-No!
-Move along now. Make more room.
That's right. Let's go!
-This way, please.
-Lovejoy!
She's not on the starboard side either.
We're running out of time.
And this strutting martinet
isn't letting any men on at all.
There's one on the other side
letting men on.
Well, then, that's our play.
We'll need some insurance, first. Come on!
Come on this way.
It's all the way down there.
[thud]
[roaring]
Here!
What do you think you're doin'?
You'll have to pay for that, you know.
That's White Star Line property.
[both] Shut up!
Will you hold the boat a moment?
I just have to run back to my room.
[Lightoller roars]
Sit down!
She's the last.
-Prepare to lower.
-Mr. Lightoller.
Why are the boats
being launched half full?
-Not now, Mr. Andrews.
-There, look.
Twenty or so in a boat built for 65?
And I saw one boat with only 12! 12!
Well, we weren't sure
of the weight, Mr. Andrews.
-These boats may buckle.
-Rubbish.
They were tested in Belfast
with the weight of 70 men.
Now, fill these boats, Mr. Lightoller,
for God's sake, man!
Please.
I need more women and children, please.
Get back in there.
-This is not an exit.
-Get back. Get back in there.
It's not an exit!
You can't keep us locked
in here like animals.
-The ship's bloody sinking.
-Stand back!
Bring forward the women!
Unlock the gates. Come on.
Women only!
-No men! Get back!
-[passengers shouting]
No men!
[man screaming]
Get back!
Lock the gates!
Get away from those gates!
Don't touch the gate!
[all shouting]
For God's sake, man,
there are women and children down here!
Let us out so we can have a chance!
[steward] Get back!
-Jack!
-[Jack] Tommy!
-Can we get out?
-It's hopeless that way.
Well, whatever we do,
we've gotta do it fast.
Jack!
Fabrizio!
The boats are all gone!
This whole place is flooding.
We've gotta get out of here.
There's niente this way.
All right.
Let's go this way, all right? Come on!
I make my own luck.
So do I.
[chuckles]
Come on!
No! Come on, let's go this way.
[speaking other language]
This way!
Just go back to the main stairwell
and everything will be sorted out there.
[man] The hell it will.
[steward] It will all get
sorted out back there.
Go back to the main stairwell!
Open the gate.
Go back down the main stairwell.
Open the gate right now!
Go back down the main
stairwell like I told you!
[Jack sighs]
God damn it! Son of a bitch!
Stop that!
[Tommy] Open the damn gate! Open it!
[Jack] Fabri, Tommy, give me a hand!
Move aside! Move aside!
Come on, pull!
Pull!
Move aside! Quickly! Move aside!
-[steward] Put that down!
-Move aside!
-Put that down! Stop it!
-One!
-Stop that!
-Two! Three!
[all grunting]
Again! [grunting]
Yeah, let's go!
Let's go Rose.
You can't go out there! You can't do this!
[people shouting]
[man] Move back as much as you can!
[Wilde] Keep order! Keep order here!
Back. Get back. Back.
-[man grunts]
-[woman screams]
Hold on to her!
[screams]
[seaman] Pull her in!
Get back, I say!
Or I'll shoot you all like dogs!
Keep order here!
Keep order, I say!
Mr. Lowe, man this boat.
[Lowe] Right. Is everybody all right?
-Nobody panic.
-[shuts gun]
[shouting]
[Murdoch] Stay back!
We're too late!
There are more boats down the front.
Stay with this one, Murdoch.
He seems to be quite practical.
[women screaming]
[Barrett] Don't lower it!
[seaman] Cut the falls!
[Lowe] Sit down! Hey!
Stay back, you lot! Just stay back!
Stay back, the lot of you. Stay back!
[screaming]
It's starting to fall apart.
We don't have much time.
Mr. Murdoch?
Mr. Hockley. You two, with me, now!
I'm a businessman, as you know.
And I have a business proposition for you.
[band continues to play]
[Jack] Come on, Rose.
The boats are gone!
Colonel, are there any boats on that side?
No, miss, but there are
a couple of boats all the way forward.
This way, I'll lead you.
What's the use?
Nobody's listening to us, anyway.
Well, they don't listen to us
at dinner either.
Come on, let's play. Keep us warm.
"Orpheus."
[lively music playing]
Music to drown by.
Now I know I'm in first class.
Keep along. Keep going.
Where is everyone?
They're all still aft, sir.
[Ismay] Come on, madam.
Don't cry. Come on.
Do we have an understanding,
then, Mr. Murdoch?
[Lightoller] Stand back!
Will the men please hold back?
Hold back, I say!
[gunshot]
Women and children only!
Stand back!
Step back, sir. Come through, madam.
This way. Step back, sir.
Let the women through!
You better check the other side.
-Stand back, sir.
-Go!
Stand back, sir.
[Murdoch] Any more women and children?
Any children?
I found her on the other side.
Waiting for a boat…
with him.
Any more women and children?
-They're all aboard, Mr. Murdoch.
-Anyone else then?
Hop on, sir. Hop on.
-Anyone else?
-Do hurry. Hurry along.
Stand by the falls.
-Quickly.
-God damn it all to hell.
[Ismay] That's it!
-Shit.
-Fire!
Sir!
Sir, you can't go through here.
Sir, you can't go through.
That's just splendid. Right.
Right.
[Murdoch] Prepare to lower!
Ready on the left.
Take them down.
Keep it steady.
Both sides together. Steady.
Give her to me.
-Daddy!
-[father] It'll be fine,
-darling.
-Take her.
-Don't you worry.
-Pull her up.
Daddy, get in the boat.
It's goodbye for a little while.
Only for a little while.
There'll be another boat for the daddies,
this boat's for the mummies
and the children.
You hold Mummy's hand
and be a good little girl.
I'm not going without you.
-No, you have to go, now.
-No, Jack.
Women and children only, please!
-Get in the boat, Rose.
-No, Jack.
Yes! Get on the boat!
Yes, get on the boat, Rose.
Oh, my God, look at you.
You look a fright.
Here.
Put this on. Come on.
[man] On the boat, please.
[woman] We'll pray for you.
[man 2] Get on the boat.
[woman] Yes, we'll pray for you, darling.
Go on. I'll get the next one.
No, not without you.
I'll be all right. Listen, I'll be fine.
I'm a survivor, all right?
Don't worry about me.
Now, go on. Get on.
I have an arrangement with an officer
on the other side of the ship.
Jack and I can get off safely.
Both of us.
See? I got my own boat to catch.
[Cal] Come on, hurry.
They're almost full.
-Step aboard, miss.
-Go, go.
Come on, hurry.
[Wilde] Step aboard, please.
[father] Be Daddy's good girl, all right?
-[Lightoller] Step lively!
-You're my little sailor.
[Lightoller] Keep back! Keep back, I say!
-[Rose grunts]
-Clear the rail.
Clear the rail, please.
And lower away!
-[lifeboat passengers exclaim]
-Lower away together!
Lower slowly!
Keep going! Keep going!
And lower away evenly, lads.
Easy! Lower away!
-You're a good liar.
-And even away!
Almost as good as you.
[Wilde] Easy now! And lower away!
Steady!
-There's no…
-Easy!
There's no arrangement, is there?
[Wilde] Lower away!
-No, there is.
-Even!
Not that you'll benefit much from it.
[Wilde] And even away!
-I always win, Jack.
-And lower away evenly, lads!
One way or another.
[Wilde] Watch that turn! Turn that boat!
Easy!
Even, lads!
Keep going! Keep going!
Steady!
And even away!
Lower away!
Steady!
Rose!
[passengers exclaim]
-[Cal] Stop her!
-Rose!
-What are you doing?
-[Cal] Stop her!
[Rose panting]
No!
-Rose!
-[Rose sobs]
You're so stupid!
Why'd you do that, huh?
You're so stupid, Rose.
Why did you do that? Why?
You jump, I jump, right?
All right.
Oh, God! I couldn't go.
I couldn't go, Jack.
[Jack] It's all right.
We'll think of something.
[Rose] At least I'm with you.
[Jack] We'll think of something.
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Move!
[grunts]
Come on!
[Rose screams]
Move!
Come on, come on, Rose!
Come on!
-Move! Come on!
-[screams]
[grunts]
Move, Rose!
Go!
[creaking]
I hope you enjoy your time together!
[laughing]
What could possibly be funny?
I put the diamond in the coat.
And I put the coat on her!
Come on!
[child screaming] Dada!
Dada!
-Dada!
-We can't leave him.
Dada!
All right, come on!
[doors straining]
[boy screaming]
[boy sobbing]
Go back!
-Dada! Dada!
-[shouting in Slovakian]
[Jack] It's the wrong way! Come back!
-[Rose] No! Not that way!
-You're going the wrong way!
-Come back!
-Come back! Stop!
[doors straining]
[screaming]
Go!
Run!
-Jack!
-Rose!
[Rose grunts]
[Jack groans]
[both grunting]
This way!
Come on!
Give me your hand!
[grunts]
Oh, God!
[Jack] Help!
[Rose] Help!
Wait, sir! Sir, open the gate, please!
-Help us, please!
-Please!
Help us!
Bloody hell!
Hurry!
-God, come on!
-Come on!
Go, go!
Oh, Jesus!
-[Rose] Please!
-[Jack] Come on!
Hurry!
[Jack] Come on!
I'm sorry, I dropped the keys.
-Wait, please!
-Wait!
Don't leave!
-Please! Send for help! No!
-[takes deep breath]
[gasps] I got it!
-Which one is it, Rose?
-All right!
The short one, try the short one.
Hurry, Jack.
Oh, no! It won't go in!
-It's stuck! It's stuck!
-Come on, Jack! Hurry.
-Jack! Hurry, Jack!
-Come on!
-Hurry, Jack!
-Go on!
[shrieking] Jack!
I got it! I got it! Go! Go, Rose!
Go! Go! Move!
[grunting] Jack!
[gasping] Jack!
Jack!
Come on!
Move, move.
[screaming]
-[Wilde] Keep on working!
-Get the oars in place.
[Lightoller] Get an oar under it!
Women and children only, damn you!
[Wilde] Hold it! Hold it!
Hold it!
[shouting]
Get these davits cranked in!
And get the falls hooked up!
[Cal] Oh!
[band continues playing]
[Wilde] Stay back!
[girl wailing] Mommy!
[crying]
[Wilde] Stay back, I say!
Keep going up!
[ship groaning]
[Murdoch] Stop pushing!
[screaming]
Stay back!
Will you give us a chance
to live, you limey bastard!
I'll shoot any man who tries
to get past me! Get back!
Bastard!
Get back!
We had a deal, damn you!
Any more women and children?
Your money can't save you
any more than it could me. Get back!
[Wilde] Women and children only!
[gunshot]
[screaming]
[Fabrizio] Tommy!
No, no! No, Tommy!
[exclaims in Italian]
[in English] Oh, no!
[Fabrizio speaking Italian]
[in English] No, Will!
Now stand back, damn you!
God damn you!
[Lightoller] Gently! Hold it.
Hold it, hold it!
[screaming]
[girl crying]
[Cal] I have a child!
-I have a child!
-Clear a path here!
Please, I have a child!
Please. I'm all she has in the world.
Go on.
-Step back! Step back, I say!
-Please?
[woman] Here. Give her to me.
You're all right, dearie.
Give her here.
[girl wailing]
There, there.
Wait, wait, wait!
Mr. Andrews!
Oh, Rose.
Won't you even make a try for it?
I'm sorry that I didn't build you
a stronger ship, young Rose.
It's going fast. We have to move.
Wait.
Good luck to you, Rose.
And to you.
Mr. Guggenheim?
These are for you, Mr. Guggenheim.
No, thank you.
We are dressed in our best
and are prepared to go down as gentlemen.
[creaking]
But we would like a brandy.
[Lightoller] Get the falls over here now!
Let them drop. Then we'll right it.
[woman speaking Spanish]
[in English] Where should I go? Please.
[man] Captain.
Captain. Sir.
[band continues playing]
Right. That's it, then.
Goodbye, Wally. Good luck.
-Goodbye, Wallace.
-So long, old chap.
["Nearer My God to Thee" playing]
And so they lived happily together
for 300 years
in the land of Tír na nÓg,
land of eternal youth and beauty.
[screaming]
[shouting]
[women screaming]
There's no time! Cut those falls!
Cut 'em! Cut 'em if you have to!
[man] I need a knife! I need a knife!
[Wilde] Bloody cut the falls now!
Cut 'em loose!
Cut the falls!
Cut those bloody falls!
[Cal] Here.
[screaming]
[Wilde] Now!
Gentlemen,
it has been a privilege
playing with you tonight.
[creaking]
[screaming]
We have to stay on the ship
as long as possible. Come on.
[screaming]
[Jack] This way. Through the rail.
Come on, Rose. Jump.
Come on, come on.
-[woman 1 screaming]
-[woman 2] Help! Help Us!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[Jack] I got you. Jump.
[grunts]
[Baker Joughin] I've got you, miss.
-Jack!
-Come on.
-[Cal] Back!
-[man] Help me!
[Lightoller] Give me your hand.
[screaming]
Hang on, sailor.
No! You'll swamp us.
[all screaming]
Move.
"Yea, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death, I will fear no--"
You wanna walk a little faster
through that valley there?
[screaming]
Row!
Pull together!
[man] Jump down, swim to the boats!
[shouting]
[screaming]
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners now
and at the hour of our death. Amen.
-Hail Mary, full of grace.
-This way.
The Lord is with thee. Blessed art thou…
[Rose grunting]
[screaming]
Come on. Come on.
"And I saw a new heaven and a new earth,
when the first heaven
and first earth had passed away
and there was no more sea."
[woman 1] Where are you?
-[woman 2] Help me!
-It'll be over soon.
It'll all be over soon.
"And I heard a voice suddenly…
Behold, the tabernacle of God is with man,
and He shall dwell with them
and they shall be His people
and God Himself shall be with them
and be their God."
Jack.
This is where we first met.
"And God shall wipe away
all the tears from their eyes
and there shall be no more death."
"Neither shall there be sorrow or crying."
"Neither shall there be any more pain,
for the former world has passed away."
[smashing]
Bloody pull faster and pull.
[woman screaming] Help me!
[screaming]
[man] Hang on, Miss Trudy!
[glass shattering]
[screams]
Help me. Please, save me.
-[woman] Help!
-[Jack] Hold on real tight.
[woman] Help me, please!
[woman sobbing]
[screaming in distance]
God Almighty.
Keep those breakers in. Keep them in!
[screams]
[ship groaning]
[screaming]
[Rose gasps]
We have to move.
-Give me your hand. I'll pull you over.
-I can't.
Come on. Give me your hand.
Give me your hand.
I've got you. I won't let go.
Come on, I've got you.
[Rose grunts]
What's happening, Jack?
[Jack] I don't know. I don't know.
-Hold on. Come on, Rose.
-Jack!
[man screaming] Help me, please!
Someone, help me, please!
[screaming]
[breathing rapidly]
[screams]
[woman] Help! Help, help! Help!
[creaking]
This is it.
[screaming]
Oh, my God, Jack. Oh, God.
-Oh, God.
-Hold on!
Oh, God. Oh.
The ship is gonna suck us down.
Take a deep breath when I say.
Kick for the surface and keep kicking.
Do not let go of my hand.
No!
We're gonna make it, Rose. Trust me.
[Rose] I trust you!
[Jack] Ready! Ready!
-Now!
-[both inhale deeply]
[screaming]
[gasps]
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
[woman] Help me! Help!
[all shouting]
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
[man grunting]
No!
Jack!
Rose!
Get off her! Get off her!
-Rose.
-Jack.
Swim, Rose. I need you to swim.
Keep swimming.
-[Rose] It's so cold.
-Swim, Rose.
Come on. Here.
Keep swimming.
Come on.
Here, get on it.
Get on top.
[Rose grunting]
Come on, Rose.
[Rose screams]
Stay on it. Stay on, Rose.
Jack.
No.
It'll be all right now.
[woman] Oh, God!
[whistle blowing]
Return the boats!
[whistle blowing continues]
The boats are coming back for us, Rose.
Hold on just a little bit longer.
Return the boats!
They had to row away for the suction,
but now they'll be coming back.
[woman 1] For God's sake!
-Help us!
-Please! Help us!
[woman 2] Come back!
You don't understand.
If we go back, they'll swamp the boat.
They'll pull us right down,
I'm telling you.
Knock it off. You're scaring me.
Come on, girls. Grab an oar. Let's go.
Are you out of your mind?
We're in the middle of the North Atlantic.
Now, do you people want
to live or do you want to die?
[shouting in distance]
[whistling]
I don't understand a one of you.
What's the matter with you?
It's your men out there.
There's plenty of room for more.
And there'll be one less on this boat
if you don't shut that hole in your face!
[man] Here, take this rope.
[Lowe] Now, bring in your oars over there.
And tie these two boats together as well.
Now make sure that's tied up
nice and tight.
Right, listen to me, men.
We have to go back.
I wanna transfer all the women
from this boat into that boat right now.
As quick as you can, please.
Let's create some space over there.
Move forward and aft.
[shivering]
It's getting quiet.
It's just gonna take a couple of minutes
to get the boats organized.
I don't know about you, but I intend to
write a strongly worded letter
to the White Star Line about all this.
I love you, Jack.
Don't you do that.
Don't you say your goodbyes.
Not yet. Do you understand me?
I'm so cold.
Listen, Rose.
You're gonna get out of here.
You're gonna go on
and you're gonna make lots of babies
and you're gonna watch them grow.
You're gonna die an old lady
warm in her bed.
Not here.
Not this night.
Not like this. Do you understand me?
I can't feel my body.
Winning that ticket, Rose,
was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
It brought me to you.
And I'm thankful for that, Rose.
I'm thankful.
You must do me this honor.
You must promise me that you'll survive.
That you won't give up…
no matter what happens.
No matter how hopeless.
Promise me, now, Rose.
And never let go of that promise.
I promise.
Never let go.
I will never let go, Jack.
I'll never let go.
[kisses]
[seaman] Right ahead, sir.
[Lowe] Oars!
Do you see any moving?
No, sir. None moving, sir.
Check them.
Bring that oar up here.
Check them. Make sure.
[seaman] These are dead, sir.
Now, give way. Ahead easy.
Careful with your oars. Don't hit them.
Is there anyone alive out there?
Can anyone hear me?
We waited too long.
Well, keep checking them! Keep looking!
Is there anyone alive out there?
Can anyone hear me?
[quietly] ♪ Come, Josephine ♪
♪ In my flying machine ♪
♪ And as up she goes ♪
♪ Up she goes ♪
♪ Come, Josephine ♪
♪ In my flying ♪
[distorted voice echoing]
[gasping]
Can anyone hear me?
Jack.
There's a boat.
Jack!
Jack.
[tearfully] there's a boat, Jack.
[melancholy music playing]
[sobbing]
Come back.
-Come back.
-Can anyone hear me?
[croaking] Come back.
Come back.
Come back. Come back.
[echoing] Hello!
Can anyone hear me?
[seaman] There's nothing here, sir.
-Come back.
-Can anyone hear me?
[hoarsely] Come back.
[grunts]
I'll never let go.
I promise. [kisses]
[Rose sobbing]
[blows]
[whistle blowing]
Come about!
[gasps]
[blows]
Fifteen hundred people went into the sea
when Titanic sank from under us.
There were 20 boats floating nearby
and only one came back.
One.
Six were saved from the water,
myself included.
Six…
out of 1,500.
Afterward…
the 700 people in the boats
had nothing to do but wait.
Wait to die,
wait to live.
Wait for an absolution…
that would never come.
[imperceptible]
Sir, I don't think you'll find
any of your people down here.
It's all steerage.
[woman] His hair is reddish brown,
reddish brown.
Reddish brown and a white beard.
Calm down, it's all right.
Isn't there another passenger list?
-There's no other list.
-Perhaps he's on another ship.
We're doing all we can, ma'am.
There's got to be another passenger list.
[old Rose] That's the last time
I ever saw him.
He married, of course,
and inherited his millions.
But the Crash of '29
hit his interests hard.
And he put a pistol
in his mouth that year.
Or so I read.
Can I take your name, please, love?
Dawson.
Rose Dawson.
Thank you.
We never found anything on Jack.
There's no record of him at all.
No, there wouldn't be, would there?
And I've never spoken of him until now.
Not to anyone.
Not even your grandfather.
A woman's heart
is a deep ocean of secrets.
But now you know there was
a man named Jack Dawson,
and that he saved me
in every way that a person can be saved.
I don't even have a picture of him.
He exists now only in my memory.
[pilot] Keldysh, Keldysh,
Mir Two on our way to the surface.
[announcement in Russian over PA]
[Brock] You know, I was saving this
for when I found the diamond.
[sniffs]
I'm sorry.
Three years…
I've thought of nothing except Titanic.
But I never got it.
I never let it in.
Ha!
["Titanic" theme music playing]
["My Heart Will Go On" playing]
♪ Every night in my dreams ♪
♪ I see you, I feel you ♪
♪ That is how I know you go on ♪
♪ Far across the distance ♪
♪ And spaces between us ♪
♪ You have come to show you go on ♪
♪ Near, far ♪
♪ Wherever you are ♪
♪ I believe that ♪
♪ The heart does go on ♪
♪ Once more ♪
♪ You open the door ♪
♪ And you're here in my heart ♪
♪ And my heart will go on and on ♪
♪ Love can touch us one time ♪
♪ And last for a lifetime ♪
♪ And never let go till we're gone ♪
♪ Love was when I loved you ♪
♪ One true time I hold to ♪
♪ In my life we'll always go on ♪
♪ Near, far ♪
♪ Wherever you are ♪
♪ I believe that ♪
♪ The heart does go on ♪
♪ Once more ♪
♪ You open the door ♪
♪ And you're here in my heart ♪
♪ And my heart will go on and on ♪
♪ You're here ♪
♪ There's nothing I fear ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ That my heart will go on ♪
♪ We'll stay ♪
♪ Forever this way ♪
♪ You are safe in my heart ♪
♪ And my heart will go on ♪
♪ And on ♪