Before time began...
There was The Cube.
We know not where it comes from.
Only that it holds
the power to create worlds,
and fill them with life.
That is how our race was born.
For a time we lived in harmony.
But like all great power...
Some wanted it for good...
Others for evil.
And so began The War.
A war that ravaged our planet
until it was consumed by death.
And The Cube was lost to
the far reaches of space.
We scattered across the galaxy,
hoping to find it and rebuild our home.
Searching every star, every world...
And just when all hope seemed lost...
Message of a new discovery
took us to an unknown planet called...
Earth.
But we were already too late...
Oh God, four months of this...
Can't wait to get a little taste of home.
Play with mama's alligators...
- You've been talking about barbecued
gators and crickets for the last 2 weeks.
I'm never going to your mama's house, Vic,
I promise.
Bobby, gators are known to have
the most secular meat.
I understand.
English, please.
English.
I mean how many times...
We don't speak Spanish. I told ya--
You ruin it for me, man.
That's my heritage...
Okay, fine. Go with the Spanish,
whatever.
Hey you guys remember weekends?
Sox and Filmway, cold hotdog
and flat beer?
Perfect day...
What about you captain?
You got a perfect day?
I just can't wait to hold
my baby girl for the first time.
Shut up.
Watch this crossover man,
like Jordan in his prime...
Step aside mates.
Danny!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Water?
Thank you.
Are you gonna help me with the gear?
Colonel Sharp, we have an inbound
unidentified infiltrator.
10 miles out.
Unidentified aircraft, you are in
restricted US military airspace.
Walk indent, and proceed East out of the area.
Raptors 1 and 2, snap to
heading 250 and intercept.
Bogey's in the weeds,
10 miles out, not squawking.
Unidentified aircraft, we will
escort you to US SOCCENT airbase.
If you do not comply,
we will use deadly force.
Copy on the bogey.
Tail, 4500 X-ray.
Sir, it says here 4500X
was shot down 3 months ago.
Afghanistan.
That's got to be a mistake,
check again and recheck.
I did, sir. Friend of mine
was on that chopper.
Unidentified aircraft, we will escort you
to US SOCCENT.
Radar, where's the inbound?
- Bogey's 5 miles out sir.
My wife phoned?
- Yes, captain.
Hi my ladies!
Oh my goodness, look at her,
she's getting so big.
Look at those cheeks,
I just want to chew on them.
Baby we've got a
good looking kid.
I know that people say
that all the time...
Wow, we made one good looking kid.
Nice work.
She has your laugh.
- She laughs?
Her first one, yeah.
You look--
Are you sure she
didn't just fart?
No, she's a lady.
She doesn't know you yet,
but she will.
4500X, something's not right.
Bogey's on the deck.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa..
Radar's jammed.
It's coming from the chopper.
Well--
- Sarah..
Hey.
Sarah, if you can hear me,
I love you and I'll be home soon.
Move out, move out!
Check fire! Get your field!
MH53 pilot, power down now.
Have your crew step out
or we will kill you.
Hold your fire! Stand by to engage!
My God...
They bombed that ten-oh-four!
We're under attack!
Go! Move, move!
They're going after the files!
- Cut the hard lines!
I need a key, it's locked!
Behind here!
Oh my god!
What the f...!
Epps, let's go!
Ok, Mr. Witwicky you're up.
Sorry, I got a lot of stuff.
Watch.
Okay.
For my family gen--
Who did--
Who did that?
People...
Responsibility.
So, for my family genealogy
report, I decided to do it
on my great great grandfather.
Who was a famous man.
Captain Archibald Witwicky.
Very famous explorer,
in fact, he was one of the first
to explore...
The arctic circle,
which is a big deal.
In 1897, he took 41 brave
sailors straight into the arctic shelf.
The ice is freezing faster
than it's melting!
Chop faster!
No sacrifice, no victory!
We'll get to the arctic circle, lads!
So that's the story, right?
And here we have some of
the basic instruments and tools
used by 19th century seamen.
This here is the quadrant,
which should be around $80 bucks.
It's all for sale by the way.
Like the sextant here.
$50 dollars for this,
this is a bargain.
These are pretty cool.
These are my grandfather's glasses.
I haven't quite gotten them appraised yet,
but they've seen many cool things.
Are you going to sell me
his liver?
Mr. Witwicky, this isn't show and sell.
It's the 11th grade, I don't
think your grandfather would be
particularly proud of what you're doing.
- I know, I'm sorry. I just--
You know, this all is going toward
my car fund.
You can tell your folks, it's on eBay.
I take PayPal, cold hard cash works too.
And the compass makes a great gift
for Columbus Day.
Sam!
- I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, my great great
grandfather, the genius that he was...
Wound up going blind
and crazy on a psycho ward.
Drawing these strange symbols,
and babbling on about some...
Giant ice man that he thought
he discovered...
OK, might be a pop quiz tomorrow,
might not!
Sleep in fear tonight.
$50? $40? $30?
- Sam..
Sorry.. Sorry.
Okay..
Pretty good right?
I'd say a solid B minus.
A B minus?
- You were hawking your great
grandfather's crap
in my classroom.
Look, can you do me a favor?
Can you look out the window
for a second and see my father?
He's the guy in the green car.
I'll tell you about a dream,
a boy's dream.
And a man's promise to that boy.
He looked him in the eyes and said:
"Son, I'm gonna buy you a car.
But I want you to bring me
$2,000 dollars and 3 A's."
I got the $2,000 and
I got the 2 A's.
Here's the dream.
Your B minus... dream gone.
Sir, just ask yourself...
What would Jesus do?
Yes!
Well?
- A minus. It's an A though.
Wait, wait, I can't see. It's an A.
So I'm good?
- You're good.
I got a little surprise
for you son.
What kind of surprise?
- Yeah, little surprise.
No...
No, no, no, no!
Dad!
Oh, you got to be kidding me!
- Yeah, I am.
You're not getting a Porsche.
You think that's funny?
Yeah, I think it's funny.
- What's wrong with you?
What, you think I'd really get you
a Porsche?
For your first car?
- I don't want to talk to you
for the rest of my life.
Come on, it's just a practical joke.
- It's not a funny joke.
Manny!
- What?
Get your cousin out of that damn clown suit,
he's having a heat stroke again.
Scaring away folks.
- I'm hot, makeup's melting, hurts my eyes.
Here? No, no, no,
what is this?
You said half of car,
not half of piece of crap, dad.
When I was your age, I'd be happy
with 4 wheels and an engine.
Let me explain something to you.
You ever seen '40 year old virgin'?
That's what this is,
and this is 50 year old virgin.
Okay.
- You want me to live that life?
No sacrifice...
- No victory, you know, I got it.
The old Witwicky motto.
Gentlemen.
Bobby Bolivia, like the country
except without the runts.
How can I help?
Well my son here, is looking
to buy his first car.
You come to see me?
- I had to.
That practically makes us family.
Uncle Bobby B baby.
Uncle Bobby B.
- Sam.
Sam. Let me talk to you.
Sam, your first enchilada
of freedom...
awaits underneath
one of those hoods.
Let me tell you something son.
A driver don't pick a car.
A car picks the driver.
Some mystical bond between
a man and a machine.
Son, I'm a lot of things,
liar is not one of them.
Especially not in front
of my mammy.
That's my mammy.
Hey, mammy!
Oh, don't be like that... If I had a rock,
I'd bust your ass bitch.
She's deaf, you know.
Over here...
Every piece of car man
might want or need.
So it's got racing stripes.
- Yeah, it's got racing...
What the heck is this?
I know nothing about this car.
Manny!
- What?
What is this?
This car, check it out.
I don't know boss.
I've never seen that.
That's loco!
Don't go Ricky Ricardo on me,
Manny. Find out!
Feels good.
How much?
- Well...
Considering the semi classic
nature of the vehicle...
With the slick wheel and a
custom paint job--
But the paint's faded.
Yeah, but it's custom.
- It's custom faded?
Well it's your first car,
I wouldn't expect you to understand.
$5 grand.
- No, I'm not paying over $4. Sorry.
Kid, come on get out of the car.
- No, you said cars pick their drivers.
Well, sometimes it picks a driver
with a cheap ass father, out of the car.
Now, this one's here $4 G is a beauty.
There's a Fiesta with racing stripes over there.
- No, I don't want a Fiesta racing stripes.
This is a classic engine right here.
I sold a car the other day...
Holy cow. Are you all right?
I guess slugs have might knock
this right out.
Hey, Manny!
Get your clown cousin and get some hammers
to come bang this stuff out baby!
That one's my favorite.
It drove all the way from Alabama.
$4,000.
Hello Mr. Secretary.
They're so young.
-They're the top subject matter experts, sir.
NSA is recruiting right out of
high schools these days.
Guys, that's the Secretary of Defense.
- I'm so underdressed.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Secretary of Defense.
Please be seated.
I'm John Keller.
Obviously you've wondered why
you're here, so these are the facts.
At 1900 local time yesterday,
SOCCENT forward operations
base in Qatar was attacked.
So far as we know,
there were no survivors.
The objective of the attack was
to hack our military network.
We're not sure exactly
what they were after,
but we do know, that they were
cut off during the assault.
Which would leads us to assume
that they're going to try it again.
No one has taken the
responsibility for the attack.
And the only real lead
we have so far...
Is this sound.
That's the signal
that hacked our network.
NSA is working at full capacity
to analyze it,
and intercept further
communications.
But we need your help
to find out who did this.
You've all shown considerable ability
in the area of signals analysis.
We're on a hair trigger here people.
The president has dispatched battle
groups to the Arabian Gulf
and the Yellow Sea. This is as real
as it ever gonna get.
I'm gonna leave you
to your officer in charge,
you break up into teams
and you start your work.
Good luck to us all.
Alright, Mojo. I got the car,
now I need a girl.
I need money to take out
the girls with what in here.
0 bids.
Great, broke.
Come on Mojo,
you want your pain pill?
It's like clockwork.
All right. I know you're wasting
these things,
but if you piss in my bed again,
you're sleeping outside.
That's it for today. No more.
Crack head.
Ron, this one is uneven.
- Yeah, probably.
This one is wobbling.
- Yeah, I'll take care of that.
Couldn't we have hired
a professional?
Oh, Sam.
- What?
I do not like footprints on my grass.
- There's no footprints.
That's why I built my path.
So why don't you go from
my grass on to my path, okay?
It's family grass dad.
When you own your own grass,
you'll understand.
This, I can't do it anymore.
You're putting girl jewellery
on a boy dog.
He's got enough self esteem
issues, he's a Chihuahua.
That's his bling.
I want you home by
11 o' clock.
Yeah, alright.
- 11 o' clock.
Please, for the love of God
drive safely.
Seatbelts, on.
Wow.
You are so cheap.
That's his first car.
It's supposed to be like that.
At this time, we can't confirm,
whether there were any survivors.
Our bases worldwide are as
of now DEFCON Delta.
Our highest readiness level.
We're dealing with a very effective
weapon system
that we have not come across before.
Both our prayers are
with the families
of the brave men and women...
- Daddy's going to be ok.
I've never seen a weapon
system like this.
Thermal shows this weird aura around
the exoskeleton like it's cloaked
by some kind of invisible force field.
That's impossible. There's no such thing
as invisible force fields
except in like comic books stuff,
right?
Man, I don't know.
My momma, she had a gift,
you know.
She saw things.
I got the gene too, and I--
That thing that attacked us...
I got a feeling it ain't over.
How about you use those magic voodoo
powers and get us the hell out of here.
When I took that picture,
I think it saw me.
It looked right at me.
We got to get this thing back
to the Pentagon right away,
they're gonna know what
we're dealing with here.
Our radio's fried.
I got no communication with Aerial.
How far do you live from here?
- Not far, just up that mountain.
Do you have a phone?
- Yes.
All right, let's hit it.
Dude, are you sure
we're invited to this party?
Of course Miles, it's a lake.
Public property.
Oh my God. Oh my God, dude.
Mikaela's here.
Just don't do anything weird,
all right?
I'm good right?
- Yeah, you're good.
Okay.
Hey guys, check it out.
Hey bro, that car...
It's nice.
Hey..
So what are you guys doing here?
We're here to climb this tree.
I see that, it looks fun.
I thought I recognized you,
you tried out for the football team
last year right?
Let's go call your mum.
Oh, no, no, no.
That? No.
That wasn't like a real try out.
I was researching a book I was writing.
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, what's it about?
Sucking at sports?
No, it's about the link between
brain damage and football.
I tell you, it's a good book,
your friends will love it.
It's got mazes in it, little coloring areas,
sections, pop up pictures...
A lot of fun.
- That's funny.
Okay, okay. You know what?
Stop.
You got to get off the tree right now.
Just, get off the tree right now, please.
What are you doing?
- You said it's fun.
All the chicks were watching...
- You're making me look like an idiot.
We both look like idiots.
How about you let me drive?
- Oh no, this is not a toy.
These 22's, I don't want you
grind them.
Why doesn't my little bunny
just hop in the back seat?
Oh God,
I can't even tell you how much
I'm not your little bunny.
Okay.
You'll call me.
Hey man, what's wrong
with your radio?
I'm driving her home tonight.
- What?
She's an evil jock concubine man,
let her hitchhike.
She lives 10 miles from here, okay?
It's my only chance.
You got to be understanding here, alright?
- Alright, we'll put her in the back, I'll be quiet.
Did you said put her in the back?
Miles, I'm not putting her in the back!
You got to get out of my car right now.
What rules?
Bros before hoes.
- Miles, I beg you to get out of my car.
You can't do this to me.
- You got to get out of my car right now.
Mikaela!
It's Sam...
Witwicky.
Hope you're not stranded
or anything...
You sure?
So listen, I was wondering if I
could ride you home...
I mean, give you a ride home,
in my car to your house.
Here you go.
Thanks.
So, uh..
I can't believe that I'm here right now.
You can drop down if you want,
it won't hurt my feelings.
Oh, no, no, no.
I didn't mean here with you,
I just mean here like,
in this situation.
Same situation that I'm always in.
I don't know, I guess I just have a
weakness for hot guys, for tight
abs and really big arms.
Big arms?
There's couple of new additions in the car.
Like, I've just put in that
light there...
And that disco ball, so the light
reflects off the disco ball.
Yeah.
Are you new to school this year?
Is this your first year?
No, we've been in the same
school since first grade.
Really?
- Yeah.
No.
- Yeah, long time.
Do we have any classes together?
- Yeah, History...
Language Arts, Math, Science...
- Sam...
Sam, yeah...
Sam Wilckeky...
Witwicky.
- I know, I'm so sorry.
I just--
- No, it's cool.
I just didn't recognize you.
- Yeah, well, that's understandable.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
What's going on?
Come on.
Just started working out the cakes,
you know..
This radio is like... you know,
it's an old radio..
Look this isn't something...
Look I wouldn't try this on you.
This is like a romantic thing
that I'm not trying to do.
You know, it's not that you're not worthy
of trying something like this on--
No, of course not.
I'm a friend of yours, I'm
not a romantic friend.
Romantic friends do this.
I mean, I'm not that friend.
I mean we...
I could be if--
Just pop the hood.
Shut up. Shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up!
Nice headers... You got a hi-res
double pump carburetor...
That's pretty impressive Sam.
Double pump?
It squirts the fuel in,
so you can go faster.
Oh.
I like to go faster.
It looks like your distributor cap
is a little loose.
Yeah? How did you know that?
My dad, he was a real grease monkey.
Taught me all about this.
I could take it all apart, clean it,
put it back together.
That's weird, I just wouldn't
pay you for mechanical.
Well you know,
I don't really broadcast it.
Guys don't like it when you know more
about cars than they do.
Especially not Trent.
He hates it.
I'm cool with females
working on my engine.
I prefer it actually.
Ok, you want to fire it up for me?
Oh, yeah. No problem.
I was thinking,
if Trent is such a jerk,
why do you hang out with him?
You know what, I'm gonna walk.
Good luck with your car.
All right.
Walking's healthy, right?
Oh no, no, no,
no, no.
Come on, please...
Please stay work for me now.
Don't let her walk away,
come on.
Please... Please...
Hey!
Wait a second!
There it is.
I had fun, so...
Thanks for listening.
Oh, yeah.
You think I'm shallow?
No. No, no, no.
I think... There's a lot
more than meets the eye...
With you.
Okay.
Alright, I'll see you at school.
Alright.
Stupid...
That was a stupid line.
"There's more than meets
the eye with you.."
Stupid.
Oh, God.
God, I love my car.
Guys, I think the other team
figured it out.
Iran.
Come on, man. This is way too smart
for Iranian scientists.
Think about it.
- What do you think, Kim?
Chinese?
No way, this is nothing like what
the Chinese are using.
Yes, Mr. President?
Yeah, can you rangle me up
some ding-dongs darling?
Join the Air Force to
serve him ding-dongs.
I'll be in storage.
Shoot...
Oh, gross.
Did you hear that?
Are you getting this?
I think they are hacking
the network again.
Oh my God, this is a direct match
to the signal in Qatar.
Are you running a diagnostic?
- Should I be?
Yes, you should.
- Slam.
Someone! They are hacking into
Air Force One.
We need a senior analysts.
I think they're planting a virus.
- A virus?
Streaming right now.
They are planting a virus,
and stealing a whole lot of data
from your system at the same time.
Code Red, we have a breach.
Air Force One, someone's aboard
have breached the military network.
I'm in the cargo hold.
Clear!
You got to cut the hard lines.
- What?!
Whatever they want,
they are getting it.
Sir, permission to take down
the defense network.
Cut all server hard lines now.
- Cut all server hard lines now.
Someone's tampered with
the POTUS mainframe.
What the...!
Shot fired in the inner deck.
Repeat, shot fired.
Crew, prepare for emergency
descend.
I want our president
in that bunker.
And I don't want to discuss
a damn thing other,
till that becomes reality.
That's our first priority,
that's our only priority right now.
Air Force One is on the ground.
No, no, no, no,
no, no!
Halt! That's my car!
No!
Dad call the cops!
Where are you going with
my car buddy?
Where are you going?
Hello? 911 emergency?!
My car's been stolen!
I'm in pursuit, I need all units,
the whole squadron!
Bring everyone!
No, don't ask me questions,
all right?
My father is the head of a
neighborhood watch.
Oh my God...
My name is Sam Witwicky.
Whoever finds this, my car is alive.
Okay?
You saw that?
These are my last words ever.
I just want to say mom, dad I love you.
And if you find "Busty Beauties"
under my bed
it wasn't mine,
I'm holding it for Miles.
Okay, that's not true, it's mine and
uncle Charles gave it to me, I'm sorry.
Mojo, I love you.
Good dog, good dog!
Oh my God.
Please don't kill me,
I'm sorry.
Take the keys, I don't want them.
The car's yours.
Listen, listen.
Good you're here.
Let me see your hands!
No, no, no..
- Let me see your hands!
It's not me, the guy's inside.
- Shut up!
Walk towards the car.
Put your head on the hood.
Whoever did this finally managed
to infiltrate our defense network
which is what they've tried to do
in Qatar, only this time it worked.
What did they get?
- We still don't know.
Talk to me about the virus.
It's a spider bug virus. We're not sure
what it's going to do
but it may cripple the system.
- Can we stop it?
Every time we try an antivirus
it adapts and speeds up.
It's like it's not a virus anymore,
it's become the system.
Obviously the first phase
of major attack against the US.
Only countries with this kind of capability
are Russia, North Korea, maybe China.
I'm sorry, that's not correct.
Excuse me young lady, I didn't
see you standing there
You would be who?
I'm just an analyst who
detected the hack.
Hold on, it was you?
You did it?
- Her team.
Sir, I was trying to say...
They hacked your firewall in 10 seconds.
Even a supercomputer with a brute force
attack would take 20 years to do that.
Maybe you can explain then,
how our latest satellite imagery
shows North Korea doubling
its naval activities?
Maybe it's a precaution, because
isn't that what we're doing?
The signal pattern is learning, it's evolving
on its own and you need to move past
fury air transfers and start
considering quantum mechanics.
There is nothing on Earth
that complex.
What about an organism?
A living organism, maybe some kind of
DNA based computer,
I know that that sounds crazy--
That's enough.
We have 6 floors of men who's
working on this thing.
Now if you can find proof,
to back up your theory
I'm going to be happy to
listen to you.
But if you don't put a filter
on that brain-mouth thing,
you're going to be off the team.
You understand?
Look, I can't be any clearer,
on how crystal clear I am being.
It just stood up.
- Just stood up?
Wow.
It's really neat.
Ok, time to fill her up.
And no drippy, drippy.
What you're rolling? Weapons? Goofballs?
Little wowie sauce with the--
No, I'm not on any drugs.
- What's this?
Found it in your pocket.
Mojo...
Is that what the kids
are doing now?
A little bit of Mojo?
Those are my dog's pain pills.
- Yeah, Chihuahua...
What was that?
- Huh?
You're eyeballing my peace
50 Cent?
You want to go?
Make something happen, do it.
Because I promise you,
I will bust you up.
Are you on drugs?
Let's hope this
telephone line works.
What the heck was that?
English dude, English.
Watch out!
Everybody quiet! Settle!
- Whoa, mother...!
What the hell was that?!
Go! Move it!
Vic, cover the rear ass!
Cover the rear doorway!
Come on!
Give me the map!
Where's your papa?!
- Papa!
Sir, I need a telephone...
- Telephone?
Yeah, telephone.
Yes.
Cell phone.
- All right, thank you.
This is an emergency Pentagon call...
I need you to..
Do you understand,
this is an emergency Pentagon...
I don't have a credit card!
Sir, the attitude is not going to
speed things up, any deed at all.
I'm going to ask you to speak
into the mouth piece very clearly...
I'm in a middle of a war!
Pretty ridiculous!
I need a credit card!
Epps, where's your wallet?!
- Pocket!
Which pocket?
- My back pocket!
You got 10 back pockets!
- Left jinks!
Keep shooting! Keep shooting!
- Okay, it's a Visa...
Also sir, have you heard about our
Premium Plus world service call package?
No, I don't want a premium package!
Epps, it's the Pentagon!
Give me a status.
Sir, we're tracking a Special Ops team
under fire in Qatar.
They say they're survivors of
the base attack.
Survivors?
I've never seen this in my life!
Need gunships on station ASAP!
Predators coming up in a minute.
- Link in the call to the nearest AWACS.
I don't know man... Man,
if you've seen this shit...
Predator ETA 2 minutes.
What is that?
- I don't know...
We need air support and
we need it now.
Roll in strike package Bravo
on unknown target.
I authenticate Tango, Whiskey,
and time 0300 Zulu.
Attention all aircraft, this will be a danger
close fire mission.
Weapons, I just got a call from Falcon Ops,
said us to clear kill box One Alpha,
Send the Hogs, sir.
Ok, send the Hogs over to kill box
One Alpha to danger...
...kill box One Alpha, 300 feet,
8 o'clock..
...friendlies in the area.
7 man team, north of
orange smoke!
Received kill box One Alpha,
engage hostile.
Attack to Rich and Weiss,
you're cleared hot!
Strike, tell me status--
Bravo 1, Dark Star, status?
Lennox, the heat's coming!
- Laser target!
We got to beam light it for incoming!
Light target!
The heat's coming!
- Come on, bring it!
Receiving radar's streaming
in the city of target.
No freaking way!
That thing is still not down!
Bookie 32, use .105 shells.
Bring the rain.
Be advised, ground team is
requesting .105 Sable rounds.
Did we lose it?
- Warthog 1, confirm visual on frendlies.
Where is Fig?
Fig.
Get a medic!
He's got a pulse. Hit in there.
Bring them home.
You get those men,
stateside right now.
I want them debriefed,
in 10 hours.
There's only one hacker in the world
who can break this code.
Wait! Taxi!
I'm sorry to bother you.
- Maggie...
I need your help.
- No, this is my private area...
my place of zen and peace.
Glenn, who is it?
- Shut up grandma!
What are you doing here?!
- Just give me a break will you?
Grandma, cut your prune juice!
What level are you on?
- Sixth...
Oh, here comes The Matrix,
here comes The Matrix!
Glenn, seriously, don't you want to
see something classified?
I need a moment... please.
- Sorry.
And save my game.
How classified?
Like, I will go to jail
for the rest of my life,
for showing you classified.
- Yes!
One quick peak.
Special Ops got a thermal snapshot
of whatever hit the base in Qatar.
I want to see it.
- All the imager was damaged, sir.
The Rangers are en route with the imager,
but we also have a security issue.
Server logs indicate one of the
analysts made a copy of the network
intrusion signal.
The signal strength is through the roof,
where did you say you got this?
Hacked the national military air guard
frequency in less than a minute.
No way...
Looks like there's a message
embedded in the signal.
Let me work my magic.
Project 'Iceman'?
- What's Sector-7?
Who is captain Witwicky?
Are you playing those
video games again?
Cops!
FBI! Clear right!
Mark them down!
I'm just a cousin!
Get off my grandmama's carpet!
She don't like nobody on her carpet!
Especially police!
It was an awesome spectacle here,
an hour ago,
when over 40 C-17s lifted off
at this very base.
We were not told where
they're going,
the government have been very
quiet about what's going on.
But, in our opinion, they were headed
directly towards North Korea.
Stop with the barking Mojo,
it's too early please.
Miles, listen to me.
My car, it stole itself ok?
What are you talking about man?
- Satan's Camaro in my yard.
It's stalking me.
Stop!!
Sam?
Hi...
That was really...
Awesome.
It felt awesome.
- Are you ok?
I'm not ok, I'm loosing
my mind a little bit.
Getting chased by my car
right now, I got to go.
You know what, I'm gonna catch up
with you guys later.
Oh, great, the cops.
Officer!
Listen...
Oh... that hurt.
Listen to me.
Thank God you're here.
I've had the worst day ever.
I've been--
I've been followed here,
on my mother's bike.
Right.
And my car is right there
and it has been following me here.
So get out of the car.
Stop! Oh God.
Okay, all right!
All right, I'm sorry!
Please!
Okay, what do you want
from me?!
Okay.
Oh, God. No!
No!
Oh shit, oh shit!
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit...!
This is a bad dream.
Are you username LadiesMan217?
I don't know what you're
talking about!
Are you username LadiesMan217?!
Yeah...
Where is the eBay item 21153?!
Where are the glasses?!
Get back!
Go!
What is your problem Sam?!
There's a monster right there,
it just attacked me!
Here it comes!
You have to run!
Sam what is that thing?
- You have to get in the car.
Get in the car.
Trust me, trust me!
Sam!
Get in!
Go, go, go, go,
go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
My God! We're gonna die!
- No, we're not gonna die!
Watch him.
He's a kick-ass driver!
We're gonna die!!
Oh, my God!
We're locked in.
The car won't start.
At least we've ditched
the monster, right?
Okay.
Now it's time...
Oh, he's got me!
He's got me!
He's gonna kill me!
Get off!
Get him, get him!
Not so tough without
a head, are you?!
Come on.
What is it?
It's a robot.
Like a... different... you know,
like a super advanced robot.
It's probably Japanese.
Yeah, it's definitely
Japanese.
What are you doing?
I don't think he wants to hurt us.
He would've done that already.
Really?
Well, do you speak robot?
Because they just had like a--
giant twin death match.
I think he wants something from me.
- What?
Because the other one was talking
about my eBay page.
You're the strangest boy
I have ever met.
Can you talk?
XM Satellite radio... the broadcast--
digital cable brings you--
...broadcasting system.
So you talk through the radio?
How do you do? You're wonderful,
you're wonderful.
So what was that last night?
What was that?
...message from stars reach up--
throughout the anonymous vessels of--
...bring down like a visitors
from heaven, hallelujah!
"Visitors from heaven"...
What?
What, are you like an alien
or something?
Any more questions
you want to ask?
He wants us to get in the car.
And go where?
50 years from now, when you're
looking back at your life,
don't you want to be able
to see here
the guts that get you in the car?
This car is a pretty
good driver.
Why don't you go sit
in that seat there?
I'm not gonna sit in his seat,
he's driving.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe you should sit
in my lap.
Why?
I have the only seatbelt here,
you know-- safety first.
Yeah, alright.
- Alright?
Yeah..
Thank you.
See, that's better.
You know, that seatbelt thing
was a pretty smooth move.
Thank you.
You know what I don't understand...
Why if he's supposed to be like
this super advanced robot,
does he transform back into
this piece of crap Camaro?
Oh, see.
No, that doesn't work.
See?
Move it you moron!
Great, now see?
Fantastic!
Now you've pissed him off!
That car is sensitive. I mean,
$4,000 dollars just drove off.
What?
It's the coolest thing
I've ever seen!
Explosives everywhere!
This is easily a hundred times
cooler than Armageddon,
I swear to God!
Sweet... Oh dude,
I hope this guy's got
ass-drilling insurance
coz he is so boned.
What is that?
Exactly in the tree.
- You got to get out of here!
There's got to be
something by the tree!
You guys! Could you
gave me a space slot?
Excuse me, are you the tooth fairy?
Hey sweetheart, what are you
doing out here by yourself?
Holy cow, what happened
to the pool?
Are you Samuel James Witwicky,
descendant of Archibald Witwicky?
They know your name.
Yeah...
My name is Optimus Prime.
We are autonomous robotic organisms
from the planet Cybertron.
But you can call us Autobots for short.
Autobots?
What's cracking' little bitches?
- My first lieutenant...
Designation Jazz...
- This looks like a cool place to kick it.
How did he learn to talk like that?
We've learned Earth's languages
through the World Wide Web.
My weapons specialist, Ironhide.
You feeling lucky punk?
- Easy Ironhide.
Just kidding, I just wanted
to show him my canons.
Our medical officer Ratchett.
The boy's pheromone levels suggest
he wants to mate with the female.
You already know your
guardian Bumblebee.
Bumblebee, right?
You're my guardian,
huh?
His vocal processor was damaged in battle.
We've been still working on him.
Why are you here?
- We are here looking for the Allspark.
And we must find it before Megatron.
Mega what?
Our planet was once
a powerful empire.
Peaceful and just.
Until we were betrayed by Megatron,
leader of the Decepticons.
All who defied them were destroyed.
Our war finally consumed the planet,
and the Allspark was lost to the stars.
Megatron followed it to Earth.
When Captain Witwicky found him.
My grandfather...
It was an accident that
intertwined our fates.
Come back!
I think the dogs have found
something.
The ice is cracking.
Captain! Grab the rope captain!
I'm alright lads!
Can we throw you a rope,
captain?
Megatron crash-landed before
he could retrieve The Cube.
Men, we've made a discovery!
He accidentally activated
his navigation system.
The coordinates to The Cube's
location on Earth
were imprinted on his glasses.
How did you know about
his glasses?
eBay.
- eBay.
If the Decepticons find the Allspark...
They will use its power to
transform Earth's machines
and build a new army.
- And the human race will be extinguished.
Sam Witwicky, you hold
the key to Earth's survival.
Please tell me that
you have those glasses.
It's like a self regenerating
molecular armor.
Look at the scorch mark
where the Sable round hit.
Melted right through.
Aren't Sables hot loaded for like a
6,000 degree magnesium burn?
Close to it,
it melts tank armor.
This metal skin must react
to extreme heat...
I thought you said
that thing was dead, man!
Strap it down!
Strap it!
This thing is wicked!
Alright, get on a horn of Northern Command,
tell them that our effective weapon
is high heat Sable rounds.
Recommend we load
them on all the gunships, go.
You want that piece?
Ok, Maggie, look.
Let me break your time,
tell you how's it gonna happen.
They're gonna come through
that door, play good cop, bad cop.
Don't fall for that, alright?
That's why I ate their food.
See, they put the plate of donuts
out here to test your guilt.
If you don't touch, it you're guilty.
I ate the whole plate.
The whole plate.
Okay?
It's me and you.
They walk through that door,
you don't say nothing.
She did it! She did it!
She's the one you want!
I was just sitting home
watching cartoons,
playing video games
with my cousin
and she came in there, alright?
- Glenn, you freak!
Hey, I am not going to jail
for you or anybody else.
I have done nothing bad
my entire life.
Hey man, I'm still a virgin.
Ok, so what, I've downloaded a couple
of thousand songs off the internet,
who hasn't?!
Glenn, shut up!
- No, you shut up!
Don't talk to me!
Don't talk to me, criminal!
Sugar rush.
- This is not his fault.
Can I go home now?
Just listen to me.
Whoever hacked into your
military system, downloaded a file.
It was something about
someone named Witwicky...
And some government group, right?
Named Sector-7.
You have to let me talk to
Defense Secretary Keller
before you go to war
with the wrong country.
Whatever fell out of the sky,
ended up right behind...
What did he say?
- What?
Did he hear it too?
Yeah, Jack heard it too.
- What does he think it is?
He thinks it's a military experiment.
Well I think it's a plane.
...still no official words
as to what happened...
Call Sam, he should be
home in 15 minutes.
Well, I'll call him in 15 minutes.
- If you wait 15 minutes, he'll be late
and you'll have to ground him.
- I can't ground him if he's not late, can I?
I need you to stay here, alright?
You have to stay here and watch them.
You hear what I'm saying?
5 minutes, alright?
Thanks for staying on my path.
Oh the path, I'm sorry I
forgot about the path.
I'm gonna sweep the whole thing
right now, how about that?
I buy half of your car,
I bail you out of jail,
and then I just decided to
do all your chores.
The chores...
- Yeah, life is great.
Well, life is fantastic,
that's how good it is.
The trash can, sorry dad,
I'm gonna do the trash cans, alright?
No, I don't want you
to strain yourself.
Dad, you'll hurt my feelings
if you do it.
I promise... No, no, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do the trash cans and I'm gonna
scrape the grill and I'm gonna...
Sweep up the whole house
right now.
Right now?
- Right now.
I love you.
God I love you.
Just so much right now.
- You know, your mom wanted
me to ground you.
You're 3 minutes late.
Just another thing you did
for me dad,
because you're such a swell guy.
Alright, I love you.
Sleep good, handsome man.
What are you doing?
Watch the path!
Please! Please!
No, wait!
No!
Sorry, my bad.
You couldn't wait for 5 minutes,
I told you to stay.
I told you...
- Ok, you know what?
They seem to be in a little bit
of a rush.
Well, this is bad.
Mojo no!
No! Stop!
Mojo, off the robot!
God.
No, no! Easy, easy,
hold on!
This is Mojo, he's a friend of mine,
he's a pet.
Okay? That's all.
Just put the guns away,
put them away.
You have a rodent infestation,
shall I terminate?
He's not a rodent, he is a Chihuahua.
This is my Chihuahua.
We love Chihuahuas, don't we?
- He's leaked lubricant's all over my foot.
He peed on you?
Bad Mojo!
- I'm sorry,
he's got a male dominance,
that's all there is.
It's gonna rust.
Okay, okay.
Just hurry.
Autobots, recon.
I hope he's okay.
He's in the kitchen,
got some ice on his nose,
I had to slap him around a little bit.
You did not.
You didn't even ground him.
- Almost, almost.
Where are you?
Come on.
What?
What is this?
Time is short.
- They really want those glasses.
Please hurry.
No, no, it's definitely gone.
- What do you mean?
My glasses were in the bag,
they were in the backpack,
and now the backpack
isn't here.
Well, they're gonna be pissed,
so what do you want to do?
What I think you should do,
you should check this whole--
--this whole section here.
Just give it a clean sweep.
And I'll get the corner here.
Not there, that's my private.
Sorry.
You just told me...
I didn't mean to look inside
of my treasure chest.
You should be way more specific,
so I don't, getting trouble over
your room, because I've had
just about enough.
What now?
No, no, no.
This isn't hiding. This isn't hiding.
This is my backyard, not a truck stop.
Oh, God. Oh!
I saw it. The UFO landed right here
and now it's gone.
My moped is under there man,
who's gonna pay for that?
Sam, Sam, Sam.
Sam, he's back.
- Ok, I'll deal with this.
What?! Oh no, no, no
these are my mother's flowers.
Listen, you got to listen to me.
If my parents come out here
and they see you,
they're gonna freak out.
My mom's got a temper,
okay?
We must have the glasses.
- I know you need the glasses.
I've been looking everywhere,
they're not here,
they're definitely not here.
Keep searching.
- I need you to be quiet for 5 minutes.
10 Minutes.
Okay?
Please, I'm begging you.
I can't concentrate.
You want me to look...
- Calm down.
You got to do something.
Autobots, fall back.
- Please, for 5 minutes.
Move!
- Give a way!
What's the matter with you,
can't you be quiet?
He wants us to be quiet...
Earthquake! Move, move,
move, earthquake!
Judy, get under the table,
move it!
Duck and cover right now!
- How did you get over there so fast?
Wow!
That was tingling.
Yeah, that looks fun.
Sam?
Sammy?
What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
Sam?
That's weird.
Sam!
Ratchett, point the light.
- Come on, hurry.
We've got a major issue here.
What's with the light?
You got to stop the light.
You got to tell him to shut it off.
Sam are you in there?
How come the door's locked?
You know the rules,
no doors locked in my house!
You know he'll start counting
if you don't open the door.
- One more chance.
5... 4...
- Oh dear.
Sam he's counting.
- It's coming of the hinge pal.
Sam just open the door.
- 3... 2...
Stand back.
What's up?
What's with the bat?
Who were you talking to?
I'm talking to you.
- Why are you so sweaty and filthy?
I'm a child, teenager.
- We heard voices and noises...
We thought maybe...
- It doesn't matter what we thought.
What was that light?
- What light?
There's no light, dad, you've
got 2 lights in your hand.
There was a light coming
underneath the door.
Look, you can't just bounce
into my room like that.
You got to knock,
you got to communicate.
We did, we knocked...
- We knocked!
You didn't knock, you were
screaming at me, okay?
This is repression,
what you're doing here.
You're ruining my youth, okay?
Oh, for Pete's sakes,
you are so defensive.
Were you masturbating?
Judy...
- Was I... No, mum!
No, I don't masturbate!
- That's not something for you to bring up.
That's a father and son thing.
- Father and son thing.
We don't have to call it that word
if that makes you uncomfortable.
You can call it...
"Sam's Happy Time".
Or "My Special Alone Time".
- Stop, Judy, stop.
I'm sorry, it's just been a weird night,
I had a little bit to drink.
Well, we saw a light.
Oh, parents.
Whatever it was, but we saw it.
Earthquake, another one!
Another earthquake! Get the doorway!
Okay!
- Aftershock, aftershock.
God, I hate these.
- Quick hide!
Oh no, look at the yard,
the yard is destroyed.
Judy, better call the city,
we've got a blown transformer.
Power pole's sparkling
all over the place...
Oh man, the yard's a waste.
Crashed, gone.
It's all gone. The whole yard.
- You kidding?
The parents are very irritating.
Can I take them out?
Ironhide, you know we don't
harm humans.
What is with you?
Well, I'm just saying we could.
It's an option.
We heard you talking to somebody
Sam, we want to know who.
Hi, I'm Mikaela.
I'm a friend of Sam's.
Gosh, you're gorgeous.
She can hear you talking mom.
- Thank you.
Oh my goodness, I'm sorry you had
to hear our little family discussion.
Where's my backpack mom?
- It's in the kitchen.
Your mom's so nice.
I want you to distract my parents,
while I sneak out these glasses, okay?
Ronald Wickedy?
- It's Witwicky, who are you?
We're the government, Sector-7.
Never heard of it.
- Never will.
Your son is the great grandson of
captain Archibald Wickedy, is he not?
It's Witwicky.
May I enter the premises sir?
Ron, there's guys all over
the front yard.
What the heck is going on here?
- Your son filed a stolen car report last night,
we think it's involved in a
national security matter.
National security?
- That's right, national security.
My God Ron, they're everywhere.
There's guys in suits all around
the house!
Look at this!
- Could you stay off the grass?!
Get me a sample and some
isotops readings.
Good lord!
They got to get their hands
off my bush.
Drop the bat ma'am,
I'm carrying a loaded weapon.
You better get those guys
out of my garden,
or I'm gonna beat the crap
out of them.
Are you experiencing any
flu-like symptoms?
Eating joints, fever?
- No!
What is this?
- How you doing son!
Is your name Sam?
- Yeah...
I need you to come with us...
- You're way out of line!
Sir, I am asking politely.
Back off.
You're not taking my son.
- Really?
You're gonna try to get rough with us?
- No, but I'm gonna call the cops.
Because there's something fishy
going on around here.
There's something a little fishy about you,
your son, your little Taco Bell dog
and this whole operation
you've got going on here.
What operation?
- That is what we are gonna find out.
I think, direct contact.
Son?
- Yeah?
Step forward please.
I'm just standing..
14 rads...
Bingo!
Tag 'em and bag 'em!
You hurt my dog,
I'll kick your ass!
Sam, do not say anything!
Not a word until we get a lawyer.
So...
LadiesMan217...
That is your eBay username right?
Yeah, but it was a typo,
then I ran with it.
What do you make of this?
My name is Sam Witwicky, okay.
And my--
Is that him?
- Yeah, that sounds like LadiesMan.
Last night at the station you told
the officer your car "transformed"...
Enlighten me.
- Here's what I said, okay?
'Cause this is a total misunderstanding
that my car had been stolen.
Really?
- From me, from my home
but it's fine now because
it's back, it came back.
Well, not by itself.
- Well, no.
Because cars don't do that,
because that would be crazy.
So, what do you kids know
about the aliens?
You mean like a martian?
Like what? ET?
It's an urban legend.
- You see this?
This is I-can-do-whatever-I-want
and-get-away-with-it badge.
Right.
I'm gonna lock you up, forever.
- Oh God, you know what?
Don't listen to him, he's just pissed
because he's got to get back
to guarding the mall.
You, in the training bra.
Do not test me.
Especially when your
daddy's parole coming up.
What?
Parole?
It's nothing...
- A grand theft auto, that ain't nothing?
You know those cars my dad
used to teach me to fix...
Well they weren't always his.
- You stole cars?
We couldn't always afford a babysitter,
so sometimes he had to take me along.
She's got her own juvie
record to prove it!
She's a criminal!
Criminals are hot.
It would be a real shame
if he had to rot in jail
for the rest of his natural life.
It is time to talk!
I can't see it!
Shift your weight towards the front!
You're loser in trouble now.
Gentlemen...
I want to introduce you
to my friend.
Optimus Prime.
Taking the children,
was a bad move.
Autobots, relieve them
of their weapons.
Freeze!
Whoa, whoa!
- Give me those!
Whoa..
Hi there...
You don't seem afraid.
Are you not surprised to see us?
There are S-7 protocols.
Okay?
I'm not authorized to communicate
with you except to tell you
I can't communicate with you.
- Get out of the car!
Me?
- Now!
I'm getting out, you see?
Very nifty how you put us down
without really killing us.
You're good with handcuffs too now?
You weren't supposed to
hear all that.
Yeah..
This is real.
Sam, I have a record because
I wouldn't turn my dad in...
When did you have to sacrifice
anything in your perfect little life?
Big guys, big guys with big guns.
What is Sector-7?
Answer me!
- I'm the one who asks
questions around here,
not you young man!
How did you know about the aliens?
- Where did you take my parents?
I am not at liberty to discuss...
- No?
Hey, you touch me,
that's a federal offense.
Do whatever you want,
get away with the badge, right?
Brave now all of a sudden with his big
alien friends standing over there.
Where is Sector-7?
- Wouldn't you like to know.
Bumblebee, stop lubricating
the man.
Get that thing to stop!
Alright, tough guy, take it off.
- What are you talking about?
Your clothes, all of it, off.
- For what?
For threatening my dad.
Little lady...
This is the beginning...
Of the end of your life.
You're a criminal.
Let's face facts,
it's in your gene pool.
Those are nice.
Now get behind the pole.
- All right.
This is such a felony,
what you're doing.
I will hunt you down.
- Hunt you down.
Without any remorse!
- No remorse.
Okay?
We've got to alert everyone.
- They already know.
Speaker.
Optimus, incoming!
Roll out!
Okay, I'm picking up rads signal
from radio down there.
Okay, we really need to get
that rad reading point higher.
Hop kick at.
Okay, we'll drop this.
That's it, right there.
Fog him, fog him.
Okay, I got 'em.
Got him going down the street.
Where'd he go guys?
I'm lost.
I got no IR signature.
Where'd he gone?
Okay, hold up, hold up.
We're coming around.
Easy, you two.
Hold on!
Alright, we got 'em again,
we got 'em again.
In the river.
I'm in for the shot.
Stop! Stop!
Wait! No!
Take the shot, Reef.
Give it a good shot.
No!!
Stop!
Get down on the ground!
Get down! Get down!
Look, he's not fighting back!
Somebody, help!
Happy to see me again?
Put him in the car with his
little criminal friend.
I want that thing frozen
and ready for transport!
Hang back,
let me check it out.
Optimus...
Are we just gonna
stand here and do nothing?
There's no way to free Bumblebee
without harming the humans.
But it's not right...
- Let them leave.
Chinese and the Russians
are nearing
our area of operations in
the western Pacific.
We feel like this could get
out of hand real fast.
At the next couple of hours,
they justified its presents here.
US and Chinese task forces are approaching
100 nautical miles of cruise missile range.
Tell the strike group commander that
he's not to engage, unless fired on first.
Yes, sir.
- Mr. Secretary...
Tom Banachek.
I'm with Sector-7,
advanced research division.
Never heard of it.
I'm a little busy Tom,
I think you can see that.
Siegfried!
Talk to me!
- The whole room's going down, sir.
I can see that.
- Virus was coded to shut us down.
General!
I'll take a seat.
What do you mean shut us down?
- They used our network to spread
out to the whole world.
The blackout's global.
We have no communication.
Satellite and land lines are dead.
You mean to tell me that I can not
pick up this telephone and call my family...
Mr. Secretary...
I'm here under direct order
from the president.
You really need to see
what I have in the case.
You'll have to accept that
there are certain things
you won't understand
right away.
Sector-7 is a special access division
of the government.
Conveined in secret under president
Hoover 80 years ago.
You might remember a NASA JPL
lost the Beagle 2 Mars rover?
We told them to report
the mission a complete failure.
It wasn't.
Beagle 2 transmitted 13 seconds.
This was classified above top secret.
ETA ended at 117 hours..
More than just a pile of Martian rocks.
This is the image from Mars.
Here's the image your Special Ops team
was able to retrieve from the base attack.
We believe they are of the
same exoskeletal type.
And obviously not Russian
or North Korean.
Are we talking about
an invasion?
We intercepted the message
from your Special Ops team.
These things can be hurt by our weapons,
and now they know it.
That's why the virus shut us down,
so we can't coordinate
against their next attack.
Which I would bet my ridiculous
government salary is coming.
Soon.
Get word to our fleet commanders
over national guard frequencies
short wave radio channel,
it might be still working.
Tell them to turn their ships around
and come home, ASAP.
And inform all commands,
to prepare for imminent attack.
Captain Lennox,
we need you and your team
to come with us right now!
Let's go!
She's in here.
What's going on?
You're coming with me.
You're gonna be my advisor.
Me too?
Who's this?
He's my advisor.
He comes too.
So..
What did they get you for?
I bought a car...
Turned out to be an
alien robot.
Who knew.
Please, let this work.
Fire it up Optimus.
The code...
The code on these glasses
indicates the Allspark is
230 miles from here.
I sense the Deceptions are getting
ready to mobilize.
They must know it's here as well.
- What about Bumblebee?
We can't just leave him to die.
He'll become some human experiments.
He'll die in vain if we
don't accomplish our mission.
Bumblebee is a brave soldier,
this is what he would want.
Why are we fighting
to save the humans?
They are primitive,
violent race.
Were we so different?
They are young species.
They have much to learn.
But I've seen goodness in them.
Freedom is the right
of all sentient beings.
You all know there's only
one way to end this war.
We must destroy The Cube.
If all else fails, I will unite it
with the spark in my chest.
That's suicide, The Cube is raw
power, it could destroy you both.
A necessary sacrifice to
bring peace to this planet.
We cannot let the humans
pay for our mistakes.
It's been an honor
serving with you all.
Autobots, roll out!
We roll!
At ease.
Captain, sergeant.
I got your intel, excellent work.
- Thank you sir, what about the gunships?
It's being retrofitted with Sable rounds now.
The heat skin will be ready for them.
But, it won't do us much good if we can't
get world communications back up.
Hey kid.
I think we got off to a bad start.
You must be hungry. You want a latte,
double vatte macchiato?
Where's my car?
- Son...
I need you to listen to me
very carefully.
People could die here.
We need to know everything you
know, we need to know it now.
Okay.
But first, I'll take my car, my parents...
Maybe you should write that down.
Oh, and her juvie record.
That's got to be gone.
Like, forever.
Come with me,
we'll talk about your car.
Thank you.
Man's an extortionist.
All right, here's the situation.
You've all had direct contact
with the NBEs.
NBEs?
Non Biological Extra-terrestrial.
Try and keep up with the acronyms.
What you are about to see,
is totally classified.
Dear God, what is this?
We think, when he made his approach
over the North Pole
our gravitational field
screwed up his telemetry.
He crashed in the ice,
probably a few thousand years ago.
We shipped him here to this
facility in 1934.
Call him NBE-1.
Sir, I don't mean to correct you on
everything you think you know, but...
That's Megatron.
He's the leader of the Decepticons.
He's been in cryostasis since 1935.
Your great great grandfather,
made one of the greatest discoveries
in the history of mankind.
Fact is, you're looking at the source
of the modern age.
Microchip, lasers, space flight,
cars, all reverse engineered
by studying him, NBE-1.
That's what we call it.
And you didn't think the United States
military might need to know
that you're keeping a hostile
alien robot frozen in the basement?
Until these events, we had no
credible threat to national security.
Well, you got one now.
So why Earth?
- It's the Allspark.
Allspark?
What is that?
They came here looking for
some sort of cube looking thing.
And Mr. NBE-1 here, aka Megatron,
That's what they called him.
Who's pretty much the harbinger of death
wants to use The Cube, to transform
human technology to take over the universe.
That's their plan.
- Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
You guys know where it is,
don't you?
Follow me.
You're about to see
our crown jewel.
Carbon dating puts the Cube here
around 10,000 B.C.
The First Seven didn't find it
until 1913.
They knew it was alien, because of the matching
hieroglyphics on the cube as well as NBE-1.
President Hoover had the dam
built around it.
4 football fields thick with concrete,
perfect way to hide its energy
from being detected by anyone
or any alien species on the outside.
Wait, back up, you said the dam hides
The Cube's energy...
What kind exactly?
- Good question.
Please step inside,
they have to lock us in.
Has Freddy Kruger have been
up here or something?
Oh, no man,
Freddy Kruger have 4 blades man.
That's only 3, that's Wolverine.
Right? That's Wolverine!
That's very funny.
Anybody have any mechanical devices,
Blackberries, cell phone?
I got a phone.
Nokia's are real nasty.
You got to respect the Japanese.
They know the way of the samurai.
Nokia's from Finland.
Yes, but he's, you know...
He's French.
He's a little strange.
We're able to take The Cube radiation...
Bundle it into that box.
Mean little sucker.
- That thing is freaky!
Kinda like the Energizer
bunny from hell.
Oh, he's breaking the box.
Gentlemen, they know
The Cube is here.
Banachek.
What's going on?
The NBE-1 hangar has lost power.
And backup generator, it's just not gonna cut!
Do you have an arms room?
Get everyone to the
NBE-1 chamber now!
Move it, move it!
Let's go!
They're popping our generators.
We're losing pressure.
We're losing pressure!
Cryogenic system is failing.
We're losing NBE-1.
40mm Sable rounds
on that table!
You got to take me to my car.
You have to take me to my car,
he's gonna know what to do
with The Cube.
Your car? It's confiscated.
- Unconfiscate it.
We do not know what will happen
if we let him near this thing.
Maybe you know, but I don't know.
- You just want to sit here,
and wait and see what happens?
- I have people lives
at stake here young man!
Drop it.
Drop your weapon soldier.
There's an alien war going on
and you're gonna shoot me?
No, we didn't asked to be here.
I'm ordering you under S-7
executive jurisdiction.
S-7 don't exist!
That's right. We don't take orders
from people that don't exist.
I'm gonna count to 5.
- I'm gonna count to 3.
Simmons?
- Yes, sir?
I'd do what he says.
Losing is really not an option
for these guys.
All right. Okay.
You want to lay the faith of the world
on the kids Camaro...
That's cool.
Stop! You got to stop!
Stop! Stop!
No, no. Stop! Stop!
Let him go!
You ok?
They didn't hurt you, right?
Listen to me, The Cube is here,
the Decepticons are coming.
Don't worry about them,
they're ok, right?
They're not gonna hurt you.
Just back up a little bit.
He's friendly, he's fine.
Okay, come on.
Put the guns down,
they're not gonna hurt you.
Come with me,
we'll take you to the Allspark.
Ok, here we go.
He's doing something.
Oh my God...
Message from Starfleet captain.
Let's get to it.
He's right, if we stay here we're screwed
with Megatron in the other hangar.
Mission City is 22 miles away.
We're gonna sneak that cube
out of here and we're gonna hide it
somewhere in the city.
Good. Right.
But we cannot make a stand
without the air force.
This place must have
some kind of radio link...
Yes.
Short waves...
- Right.
Sir, you got to figure out some way
to get word out in the open.
Let's move!
In the alien archives, sir.
There's an old army radio constant.
Will it work?
Anything's possible.
You just see that...
All right, Sam, get in the car!
Mr. Secretary, get our broods in the air
when we get to the city, we're gonna
find a radio on a F specter romero, ok?
Affirmative!
Warning! NBE-1,
cryo chamber failing.
Check that backup system!
Well, get out of here!
Set up perimeter around
the yellow sealed door!
This way, this way,
this way!
I am Megatron!
The Cube's okay?
- Yeah, it's fine.
Put its seatbelts on.
I live to serve you Lord Megatron.
- Where is The Cube?
The humans have taken it.
You fail me yet again, Starscream.
Get them!
Over here sir.
Give me a minute.
Come to me, now.
Come to me!
We're hot, we're alive!
- Where are the mics?
Mics?
This doesn't work without
the mics, Simmons!
No, no, no,
no!
Let's find them.
Get in the chair.
How do we get the signal out?
How do we call the air force?!
Glenn, can you hotwire this computer
to transmit a tone, through the radio?
What good is that?
Morse code, you can use this
to transmit it through that.
Ok, I'll do it!
Turn around.
Ok, let's see..
Simmons, I need a screwdriver!
It's Optimus.
Almost done.
What the hell was that?
Barricade the door.
Watch out!
It's 5-4-6-3...
Here, put some rounds in it.
I got it, we're transmitting!
- Send exactly what I say!
Get out of the way,
get out of the way!
Burn you, sucker!
Burn!!
It's the Defense Secretary Keller.
In the North Com commander.
What was that?!
Authenticate emergency action,
Blackbird 1195...
Sir, I have authenticated air strike
order from Sector.
No, no, no!
- What?
Same cop.
Block 'em, block 'em,
block 'em!
Oh, my God.
Cool mom!
This is so not good.
He's behind the pillar.
Shoot that mother...
Maggie, cover fire!
The air force!
They're responding!
Sucker, burn!!
Yes, they're sending F-22's
to the city!
Roger that. Scramble,
scramble, scramble!
Strike, Dark Star, roll call.
Is that looking up at a bright side?
Push to kill box One Alpha.
All right, let's go!
Moving out!
Here, I've got short wave radios.
What am I supposed to do with these?
- Use them, that's all we got.
This is like, radio shack,
dinosaur radio stuff, man.
I'm only gonna get 20-30 miles
out of this thing.
Are there any aircraft
orbiting the city?
F-22 12 o'clock.
I want planes for air cover
and get Black Hawks on station
to extract that cube, got it?
Air force has arrived, pop smoke!
Raptor, Raptor, do you copy?
We have you on visual.
Green smoke is the mark. Provide air cover,
and vector Black Hawks for extraction.
It's Starscream!
Please tell me you copy.
Back up! Take cover!
Bumblebee.
No, no, no, no,
move!!
Back up! Back up!
- Retreat! Fall back!
Incoming!
Anybody hurt?!
Everyone okay?!
Bumblebee...
Your legs...
Back, back, back,
back!
You all right?
Please, God...
Bumblebee, get up!
Ratchett!
What the hell was that?!
- What are you talking about?!
What do you mean what
I'm talking about?!
They shot at us!
- F-22 pilots will never fly
below buildings.
That's alien, that ain't friendly.
You got to get up.
You're ok.
Come on!
Army Black Hawk inbound
to your location, over.
Alpha 273, 10 miles.
November Victor, 1.2 clicks north.
Move out, let's go!
I'm not gonna leave you.
Come on, Decepticon punk!
Concentrate your fire!
Megatron.
It's Megatron, retreat!
Move! Fall back!
Fall back!
Move out!
- We need air cover down here, now!
Sam, help me with this.
Oh, you got me Megatron.
- Come here, you little creepner.
You want a piece of me?!
You want a piece?!
No, I want two!
What's going on?
Sir, that tank thing is
getting back up!
These things just don't die.
Now a second..
Wrap it around the head.
Sam!
Where's The Cube?
- Right there.
Okay, you got to wrap it around
the base and around his neck.
Epps, get those Black Hawks here!
That building...
Okay.
All right, I can't leave my guys
back there, so here, take this flare.
There's a tall white building
with statues on top
go to the roof, set the flare,
signal the chopper.
I can't do it!
- Listen to me, you're a soldier now!
All right?
I need you to take this Cube, get it into
military hands while we hold them off.
Or a lot of people are gonna die.
You got to go. You got to go.
You need to go.
No, I'm not leaving until I get
Bumblebee out of here, okay?
Army Black Hawk, requesting immediate evac,
a civilian boy with precious cargo,
Headed to rooftop marked by flare.
Sam, we will protect you.
- Ok.
Epps, where are those planes?
Sam...
No matter what happens, I'm
really glad I got in that car with you.
Sam, get to the building!
- Move!
Hit it!
Cover fire!
Watch out!
Girl, get that tow truck out of here!
- I'm going, I'm going!
Get out of here, now!
Megatron!
- Prime!
Humans don't deserve to live.
- They deserve to choose for themselves!
Then, you will die with them!
Join them in extinction!
Keep moving Sam.
Don't stop!
Sam, get to the building!
Give me that Cube, boy!
That jerk just damped my car.
You're not gonna get me,
you're not gonna get me!
Surprise!
I smell you, boy!
Maggots!
I'll drive, you shoot!
This isn't going well.
- Shoot! Shoot!
Nice shot.
Ok, he's definitely dead now.
- Let's go, we've got business.
Hey! I'm over here!
We got the boy.
Watch out!
Missile!
Hang on Sam!
Is it fear or courage that compels you,
fleshling?
Give me the Allspark and
you may live to be my pet.
I'm never giving you this Allspark!
Oh, so unwise.
I got you boy.
Hold on to The Cube.
Disgusting.
Sam...
You risked your life,
to protect The Cube.
No sacrifice...
No victory.
- If I cannot defeat Megatron,
You must push The Cube into my chest.
I will sacrifice myself
to destroy it.
Get behind me.
It's you and me, Megatron.
- No, it's just me, Prime.
At the end of this day,
one shall stand, one shall fall.
You still fight for the weak,
that is why you lose!
Fighter jets in 60 seconds.
We got friendlies mixed with bad guys,
targets will be marked.
Bring the rain.
Let's kill these things.
Move, move, move!
Remember, aim blow.
Armor's weak out in the chest.
Target marked, still waiting.
- Coming on target, 20 seconds.
That's F-22, so stay away.
Move out!
Incoming!
Weapon's armed.
Status green.
Roll out! Roll!
Second wave's on approach.
What is that?
Take it off!
...there are massive amount
of break around...
8 o'clock, on that guy!
I can see on him.
Keep him in your sight.
Take 'em out!
He's down!
Before I kill you...
Mine...
...Allspark!
Sam, put The Cube in my chest now!
Sam!
No, Sam!
Hold up.
You left me no choice, brother.
Sam, I owe you my life.
We are in your debt.
Prime, we couldn't save him.
- Oh Jazz...
We lost a great comrade.
But gained new ones, thank you,
all of you.
You honor us with your bravery.
Permission to speak, sir.
Permission granted, old friend.
- You speak now?
I wish to stay with the boy.
If that is his choice.
Yes.
Gentlemen, the president has
ordered Sector-7
be terminated, and the remains
of the dead aliens
disposed of.
The Laurencian Abyss, is 7 miles below
sea level, deepest place on our planet.
Massive depth and pressure there,
coupled with subfreezing temperatures
will crush them totally.
Leaving no evidence.
With the Allspark gone,
we cannot return life to our planet.
And faith has yielded it's reward.
A new world to call...
Home.
We live among it's people now,
hiding in plain sight.
But watching over them in secret.
Waiting...
Protecting...
I have witnessed their
capacity for courage.
And though we are worlds apart,
like us, there's more to them
than meets the eye.
I am Optimus Prime, and I send this message
to any surviving Autobots
taking refuge among the stars.
We are here...
We are waiting...
Subtitle provided by:
Rockstone@CS110
Can you shed any light on the
recent so called alien activity?
You know what... I think that...
If there was some sort of an alien...
..infestation..
- Yeah.
I think the government would be
the first to let you know. They...
The government would let us know.
- I mean, this is America...
You know that's how we know we live in
a free land because there's no secret.
They would say:
"Hey, duck and cover!"
Your head, is kind of different size
than it is on the television.