[Optimus] We were once
a peaceful race
of intelligent,
mechanical beings.
But then came the war...
...between the Autobots,
who fought for freedom...
and the Decepticons,
who dreamt of tyranny.
Overmatched and outnumbered, our defeat was all but certain.
But in the war's final days,
one Autobot ship
escaped the battle.
It was carrying a secret cargo,
which would have changed
our planet's fate.
A desperate mission.
Our final hope.
A hope that vanished.
[man] One up there.
One over there.
And one more down there.
What you got?
[man] Impact detected.
We have impact confirmed.
Contact at...
- ...2250 GMT.
- What?
Get me SecDef
on the phone right away.
[man] Mr. McNamara,
the president's expecting you.
- Get Bobby in here.
- Mr. President,
designation top secret:
We believe a UFO
has crashed into the moon.
We think the Russians
are onto it as well.
Well, then you tell NASA
to move heaven and earth.
We need to get to the moon.
[McNamara] We're going
to attempt a manned mission.
NASA said it would
take five years.
You get there
before the Russians.
[president on TV] I believe
that this nation should
commit itself...
- ...to achieving the goal...
- [man on radio]
Fifteen seconds.
[president] before
this decade is out,
of landing a man on the moon
and returning him
safely to the earth.
[man on radio] Ignition
sequence starts.
Five...Four...
Three... Two...
One... All engine running.
Liftoff. We have a liftoff,
32 minutes past the hour.
Liftoff onApollo 11.
Tower cleared.
[man] Neil Armstrong
reporting.Apollo 11
on proper heading.
Apollo 11 is on the way,
riding that pillar of
flame from theSaturn V,
out there, 250,000 miles away,
where the moon is waiting
for man's first arrival.
Houston, you're a go
for landing. Over.
[man] Forty feet, down two and
a half. Pickin' up some dust.
Thirty feet, two and
a half down. Faint shadow.
[man 2] CAPCOM, flight.
[man] Four forward. Drifting to the right a little.
[man 2] OK. Down a half.
Contact light.
OK, engine stop.
- [beeping]
- [Armstrong] Houston, uh...
...Tranquility Base here.
TheEagle has landed.
- [all cheering]-
[man] We copy you down,Eagle.
You got a bunch of guys
about to turn blue.
We're breathin' again.
Perhaps four hundred million
persons are watching
this broadcast today
of the greatest event
in our time
and one of the great events
of all recorded history.
[Armstrong] I'm at
the foot of the ladder.
I'm going to
step off the LEM now.
That's one
small step for man...
...one giant leap
for mankind.
- Are we good?
- Yes, sir.
[man] Unofficial time on the
first step, 1092...
[static]
[man]Apollo 11?
This is Houston, over.
Eagle,we're getting
a signal interference.
Do you copy?
We now have had confirmation
of loss of signal
from the Apollo 11.
TheApollo 11 is at the moment
on the far side of the moon.
Neil, you are dark on the rock.Mission is a go.
We have 21 minutes.
[man on radio] Three minutes,
45 seconds and counting.
[grunts]
My God.
It's some sort of giant,
metal face.
Jesus.
[man on radio] OK.
[breathing heavily] Control...
We are inside the ship.
Extensive damage.
Way too big to check
the entire ship.
Everything's dead
in here, Houston.
No signs of life anywhere.
These things are massive.
We copy. You've got seven
minutes on your oxygen.
[man on radio] We are not
alone after all, are we?
No, sir. We're not alone.
[man on radio] All right,
go ahead, Mr. President.
[president] Hello, Neil
and Buzz. I'm talking
to you by telephone
from the Oval Room
at the White House.
And this certainly has to be
the most historic telephone
call ever made.
I just can't tell you how proud we all are of what you...
For every American,
this has to be the
proudest day of our lives.
Because of what
you have done...
[man on radio]
We have splashdown.
[president] ...the heavens
have become a part
of man's world.
For one priceless moment...
...in the whole history
of man...
...all the people on this earth are truly one.
One in their pride
in what you have done.
It inspires us
to redouble our efforts
to bring peace and
tranquility to Earth.
[♪ U2: "North Star"]
[woman] My hero
needs to wake up.
- What is that?- This is your new lucky bunny.
It's a beautiful thought, Carly,but I don't think it's the
whole, uh, bunny that's lucky.
You see, it's just
this section here.
You see, it's just the
rabbit foot that's lucky.
Well, it's just
a good-luck charm.
Hmm? Help you think positive?
Today's important. [moans]
Come on, get up.
Hey, wear that nice tie.
- Yeah.- You need any money for lunch?
No, I don't need
any money for lunch.
I have money from
yesterday's lunch.
You love it, don't you?I'm just your American boy toy.
[chuckles] A lover boy toy.
You know how demoralizing it isto have saved the world twice
and still be
groveling for a job?
People don't know you
saved the world, Sam.
I mean, I do.
I believe you.
Government knows. I mean,
they could hook me up with
a job right here in DC.
I mean, I should be
workin' with the Autobots.
Otherwise, it's not fair.
Come on, they paid
for your college.
The president
gave you a hero medal.
- [snorts]
- [man] Thank you, man.
Great job.
That's the coolest thing
that ever happened to me.
- [president] All right guys...- [whispering] What the fuck!
Wow.
And as I recall, that wasn'teven the highlight of your day.
Mr. Ambassador, here.
British embassy, you're up next.
- [woman] No, you don't wear it.- It's not? Well...
You took it out of the box.
You're supposed to leave it
in the box, right?
You keep it in this.
What a gorgeous box.
Oh, yeah. My medal.
You know who gave that to me?
- Who?
- POTUS.
- Oh.
- President of
the United States.
- [lamp crashes]
- [gasps]
Babe, it's hard for
everybody to get a job.
I don't have time.
You see, my parents are
gonna be here in a week
on their road trip
party bus world tour.
If my dad gets here
and I don't have a job...
...he's gonna spank me.
You know? It's go time for me.
All right. Tonight,
I'll give you a job.
Romance me with a nice dinner
and, uh, maybe you can get
that bonus.
Mmm...
- [voice] Oh...
- [shrieks]
- Get lucky.
- [Carly] Get him out of here!
No, no, no...!
- [Carly] Ugh, he's gross!
- Oh, ow! She's good.
I'm sorry. But they'restranded here. Somebody's got towatch out for them, you know?
Yesterday, that one
was in my underwear drawer.
Did research. Lookin'
real good, too. [cackles]
Oh! Don't need to hit me, man.
You're so not
a normal boyfriend.
That's what you love
about me, isn't it?
- Bye, baby.
- We're not at
the love word yet.
Maybe a little bit closer
when you're covering your
half of the rent.
- [rapping at window]
- Good-bye.
- [chuckles]
- Frickin' shortin'
my circuits out here!
It's inhumane what it is!
Make us live in a box
on a balcony, right
next to a beast!
- Like a common animal!
- Stop, OK?
You and your creepy sidekick,
you can't be in here without
permission.
Accordin' to who,
Ms. Blondie Blonde?
Giddyup, little doggie. Hah!
[mimics whip]
- Yo, Brains, wassup?
- Doin' good.
Ah, shit,
I seen this one.
This is the one
where Spock goes nuts.
You know, Sam, I don't knowabout movin' in with this chick.
Uh, what if she dumps us,
like the last girl?
She was mean.
Didn't like her.
Us guys gotta
stick together.
♪ We are family
[singing unintelligibly]
No, we're not family.
You're a political refugee
and I have finally found someonewho appreciates me for me.
Well, you tell her
that we're not your pets.
And we're not your toys!
All right? We're an advanced,
genius alien race just lookin'
for a home.
- [woman] Maybe it
wasn't such a good idea.
- [man] Gonna have to stop.
Come on, what are they
gonna do, tow it?
- [door slams]
- [woman] Where is he?
[gasps] Sammy!
- Oh, come on, that's funny!
- Sam!
- Ha-ha!
- I missed you guys so much.
Sure, you did.
What do ya think?
- Look at that. Wow.
- Cute.
- You look old.
- Stop it.
- I feel like I can see the end.- I love your little tie.
Hey, where's my girl?
Where's my beautiful Carly?
She's at work, Ma.
She's got a new job.
You guys said you were
gonna be here in a week.
The 21st, not the 11th, Dad.
We just hauled ass
in this thing.
This thing,
the love tub, it flies.
Oh, are we keepin'
you from something?
Like, say, your job?
Well, it's about time.
You had us worried.
Uh, I... I have,
uh, job interviews.
Oh! That's good.
- That sucks.
- Stop it.
You don't have to be so
negative, Dad.
You're in DC. You're here
with your son and your family.
- This is good times.
- Sucks that you don't
have a job.
Yeah, but there's good things
to do here, too, right?
- Right? Museums
and monuments, OK?
- Don't take...
- I'll see you tonight.
- I'm baggin' the gift.
Sam, I think for an interview,
you should wear real pants.
I think for life
Oh, what happened
to Bumblebee?
He's off on his missions.
I had to get this for backup.
- [man] Oh, your car
has a job, huh?
- [woman] Stop.
- What does it change into?
- It doesn't change
into anything.
It's a collector's item, Ma.
I got it for a steal.
It just needs some work.
Trust me.
Oh. No, I think it's darling.
It reminds me
a lot of Bumblebee...
...if Bumblebee were
a sad piece of shit.
[engine sputtering]
Come on, we'll
give you a ride!
[Optimus] In the years
since our arrival,
our new home, Earth,
has seen much change.
Energon detectors guard
its cities now.
Long-range defense systems
watch the skies.
So now we assist our allies
in solving human conflicts.
To prevent mankind from
bringing harm to itself.
[speaking foreign language]
[shouting]
[grunting]
Ha-ha! On the ground,
per favore!And stay there!
[screams]
[Optimus] We work in secret
teams on various missions
around the globe.
And all the while,
we search for signs
of our true enemies' return.
[man] I am Voshkod,
General Counsel
with Ukrainian
Department of Energy.
My government
will officially deny
that we're having
this conversation.
At one of our
decommissioned facilities,
a discovery was made,
which I fear may be...
alien in nature.
The facility's
name is Chernobyl.
[man] Mr. Voshkod.
So, uninhabited since '86.
I hear it won't be livable againfor another 20,000 years?
At least. Ukraine was the most
fertile land. It's a tragedy.
This way.
[man] Gear up! We have
60 minutes on the ground.
Watch your radiation levels.
Mr. Voshkod, where's
your protective gear?
Hey, where's your
protective gear?
It would not matter. For me,
it's only matter of time.
Through the school.
Yuri will take you below.
And one other thing, colonel.
In private.
There were some
energy experiments...
Uh, it can wait.
[man on radio]
Keep movin', stay tight.
[breathing through mask]
OK, right here.
I think I found it.
[man 2] Optimus,
we got a visual.
Looks like the object's
clamped in some kind of
a metal harness.
What's this? Guys!
Hey, why does this thing
have Soviet space
program markings on it?
- Sputnik?- [man 2] Energon reading, sir.
- [rapid beeping]
- It's strong.
Below us.
It's coming fast.
Contact, contact!
[all shouting]
[man] Get topside now!
Move, move, move!
[grunting]
- Let's go, let's go!
- Heavy weapons up!
Stay behind me!
- Go, go!
- Optimus!
[shouting, screaming]
Go, go, go, go!
Fall back!
It's circling around us!
It's takin' our flank!
[man] Get the heavy weapon!
Optimus!
Yaahhh!
What the hell was that thing?
That... is Shockwave.
- Why was he after this?
- It's impossible.
This is an engine part...
from a long lost Autobot ship.
[gasping, panting]
[gasping]
Pleasure working with you.
Interviews.
This is so exciting.
Honey, do you
want some gum?
Your breath gets really
gnarly when you're nervous.
[♪ Aerosmith: "Sweet Emotion"]
- Mister Witwicky?
- Yeah. Search is over.
- I'm Mr. Whitley.
- Mr....
- Is anybody else joining?
- No.
No? You want me to move
right there? I'll...
- I'd prefer not.
- Sensei.
Ready? Begin.
Graduated this year.
Majored in geopolitics,
minored in tech studies.
Very interested in government
and technology,
how that's gonna
intersect and coexist.
Shape the future.
Why did we bother sending
him to an Ivy college for?
I mean, three months out ofschool and he can't find a job?
- Mister Masuhisu...
- Matsumoto.
- ...moto.
- Martha? Can I call you Martha?- No, you may not.
OK. Jack, there's two types
of people in this world.
- There's thinkers.
There's doers.
- Hmm.
There's winners, there's
dreamers and there's buddies.
- What about some weaknesses?
- [scoffs] I don't...
You have a very trustworthy
face. You remind me of,
like, a...
...an Asian Colonel Sanders.
A man I can trust.
[woman] He's a millennial.
That means they're the, you
know, like lost generation.
Why was the FBI
looking for you?
The what?
Yeah, FBI, good of you
to flag that.
It was during all that alien
craziness when you were 14.
I mean, they were very kind to
me. They found me in a jiffy.
And that's all been expunged.Obama gave me a medal, actually.
I'm just sayin', it's always
good to have a medal guy
in the office with a medal.
- From Obama?
- Yeah.
In this office, we're
mostly Republicans, so...
I'm not feeling too good.
No? Why don't you get
a little dipping tray
and dip the dog into Pepto?
That's a solution.
- Pow. I got another one.
We gotta go. Come on!
- Really?!
Sit.
Got myself a Mr. Sam Witwicky,
recent college graduate.
Previous experience
next to zero. Yet...
...he has a recommend
letter from our board?
WTF to that.
Do I know somebody
on your board?
Here's the deal.
You know who we are.
Accuretta Systems,
global leader in telecom,
aerospace, 17 billion
in profit last year.
We contract for DARPA,
NASA, JPL, you name it.
You perform here,
doors open for you anywhere.
First job out of college
is critical, kid.
You either take a step
down the correct career path
or you fall into
a life-sucking abyss.
- Hm.
- So it all depends
on how you respond
to my next two words:
Impress me.
- Now?
- Impress me.
- You catch me off guard.
I don't...
- Impress me.
I'm an open book.
Ask me any question you like.
So you're a go-getter,
ramrod, take-charge kinda guy?
I'm a killer.
A stone-cold killer.
- So take-charge...
- Take charge,
Viking, barbarian...
Of course. That's me.
Pow! I'm here.
We are not looking
for that here.
No brown-nosing. No suck-up.
No toolery. I...
- [phone beeps]
- [man] Yes, Mister Brazos.
Um, why is Shawntel using
what appears to be a red cup
from the red floor when
we are on the yellow floor?
- [man] I'm on it.
- It is a visual,
and, therefore,
a visceral betrayal.
- Stop it!
- Such a dumbass.
- [Brazos] Disgusting!
- [whimpers]
Thank you!
It's total
anarchy around here.
- [woman crying]
- The, uh...
...e-mail I, uh, read
said administrative aide?
Nope. Mailroom.
I'm gonna go.
Uh, do you have any idea
how many Ivy League
Phi Beta Kappas would kill...
Mister, I saved
your life twice. OK?
I can't tell you how or when,
or why, but I have done shit
that matters
and I'd just kind of like
a job where I matter again.
So thank you,
but no thank you, OK?
You know what I think?You want the job after this job.
But, son, this is the job
that's standing in your way.
And that's why you're gonna be
so very, very good at it.
'Cause when I look at you,
I see a younger me.
[man on PA] All arriving
Autobots... training and
debriefing in 15 minutes.
Dino, report to bay 23.
Sideswipe, bay 37
for weapons assessment.
Senator, I suggest you rememberthat when the NSA wants
funding, they call me.
When the CIA's gonna take
out a target, they ask
first for my permission.
And when the president wants toknow which members of Congress
are politically vulnerable
in terms of, oh, let's say,
undiscovered criminal conduct,
I'm the number he dials.
[man on TV] U.S. agencies say
they've been monitoring the
blast.
But if, in fact, this
was a covert military
strike no nation has...
CIA is up my ass about thismystery raid in the Middle East.
So it's time to come clean.
Was your unit involved?
Uh, I'm not sure, ma'am.
All right, guys, this is how youdo a Decepticon head kill shot.
As Director of National
Intelligence,
I'm a really big fan
of intelligent answers.
I can't really
tell you definitively.
These Autobots, they're
like teenage kids.
They like to sneak out ofthe house every once in a while.
Colonel Lennox, are you
in command or are you not?
- Yes, ma'am, I am...
- Stop with the "ma'am."
Enough with the "ma'am!"
Do I look like a ma'am?
No, ma'am. Yes, ma'am. Yes.
This gun is me perfect
invention, Ironhide.
- Right.
- Oh, good, you're here.
Me name's Que. I do hope
you have answers for him.
I've never
seen him so upset.
Optimus, you remember
Charlotte Mearing?
Our Director
of National Intelligence?
He's in a bad mood.
He's not talkin'
to anybody today.
What is this?
The silent treatment?
We've seen that
and this is not that.
- Definitely not.
- This is worse.
Prime! Make something
of yourself!
He's pissed.
You lied to us. Everything
humans know of our planet
we were told had
all been shared.
So why was this found
in human possession?
We were in the dark
on this also.
It was "Director Only" clearanceat Sector Seven until now.
- The bag.
- Which bag?
Hermes Birkin. Green ostrich!
My God.
This is a secret
few men knew.
And fewer still
remain alive.
Allow me to please
introduce to you
two of NASA's founding
mission directors,
and astronaut, Dr. Buzz Aldrin,
one of the first two men
to step foot on the moon.
Sir? Optimus Prime.
And from a fellow space
traveler, it's a true honor.
The honor is mine.
Our entire space race
of the 1960s, it appears,
was in response to an event.
Our astronauts investigated
a crashed alien ship.
No survivors onboard.
We were sworn to secrecy
by our Commander in Chief.
This was a mission
you will never speak of.
- I understand, sir.
- A total of 35 people
knew the real plan at NASA.
Soviets managed
to land unmanned probes.
Somehow, they must have
picked up that fuel rod.
We believe the Russians
deduced that the rod was a
fissionable fuel assembly,
believed they had it mastered,
and tried to harness it
at Chernobyl.
We landed six missions in all.
We took hundreds
of photos and samples.
We locked them away forever.
And the moon program
was shut down.
Well, did you search
the crash vault?
The ship's name was the Ark.
I watched it escape
Cybertron myself.
It was carrying an Autobot
technology which would have
won us the war...
- ...and its captain.
- Who was its captain?
The great Sentinel Prime,
the technology's inventor.
He was commander
of the Autobots before me.
It's imperative that I find it
before the Decepticons
learn of its location.
Our Autobot spacecraft
has the ability to get there.
And... you must pray
it's in time.
♪ Forty-five light years
from home ♪
♪ Is where you are
♪ And where I wanna be
Hi, I'm here
to see Carly Spencer.
[growling]
[Sam whispering] Carly!
[Carly] Sorry, excuse me.
- You got the job?
You really got it?
- This is crazy.
- Yes.
- See? What did I tell you?
It's the bunny.
[laughs] You are so welcome.
- Do you like me more?
- A little bit, yeah.
You said you were his assistantcurator. You didn't say the guyowns Space Mountain.
I know. Isn't it
beautiful in here?
And he's the coolest guy. Ever.
- [Sam] Yeah?
- [Carly] Yeah.
Sam.
Dylan Gould.
Hey. Pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure meeting you.Carly's told me a lot about you.
Well, vice versa. It's a...
beautiful building you got.
It's like the Starship
Enterprisein here.
[chuckles] Thank you very much.It leaks.
Before Carly came
to help run the collection,
it was just a complete mess.
But now the restorations
are back on track, we're going
to Pebble Beach this year
and we're gonna get a trophy
for that stand right there.
You know why? Because
this woman right here
is my secret weapon.
[laughs] Mister Gould,
please, you exaggerate.
All I've done
is get you organized.
Oh, you have done much more
than that, my Duchess.
- Nicknames, that's fun.
- Yeah.
- The Duchess. Hm.
- She's adorable.
You know, when I stole her
away from the British Embassy,
I said, "It's easy
to manage a country.
Try managing a priceless
collection of art."
Take a look at this
1939 Delahaye 165 Cabriolet.
Designed by a Frenchman.
Look at the curves.
Elegant, isn't it? Beautiful.
Sensual.
Built to evoke the body
of the ideal woman.
Come on. My dad had a ten-dollardesk and a dream,
and he built it into an empire.
[Sam chuckling] Oh, wow.
[Dylan] We're the largest
accounting firm in the US.
I started up the venture side
after he passed.
Invest in the future.
Try and bet on the winners.
See, collecting cars
helps me keep my sanity.
- You guys look great.
- Oh.
That was a great day, Mr. Gould.
- I haven't seen that one.
- No, me, neither.
- Jeans are tight.
- [Sam sighing]
Oh, here we go. Here we go.
You see that? Judgment.
Judge a man by his car?
And you're gonna wave
at him while he's judgin' me?
[Carly] What's with you?
He's my boss. This job
pays for our food. Our rent.
[Sam] No, I totally understand.I'm totally fine. I get it.
I'm well fed.
And guess what? I'm not your
boy toy anymore. I got my
big-boy pants on. You see 'em?
In the car.
Thank you, Duchess.
Oh, my God.
Are you threatened by him?
[forced laughter]
Threatened?! What am I
threatened by? His money?
His power? His good looks?
- None of the above. Check!
- God, your temper tantrums
are so sexy.
Get in the car, please.
Sam. He's hardly the first man
to ever smile at me.
I think I can handle it.
Hold on, hold on.
It's, it's the smiling back
part that gets me.
- OK?
- No more smiles.
- [engine turning over]
- Never again, I promise.
- You see, that works for me.
- Yeah?
[kicking engine]
Easy! Easy. You're not gonna
get it started that way.
Well, I'm just gettin' it ready.You know, I'm about 32 percent
done with my restoration.
Some chrome work, put a spoileron the back and done deal.
You know, Carly's been telling
me you've been struggling
job-wise.
Just so you know, I'm onthe board for Accuretta Systems,
and I put in a call for ya.
Let's keep it between us, OK?
She's so proud of you.
[chuckles]
You're a lucky man.
[Optimus]Xantium
approaching Tranquility Base.
[man on radio] Houston,
you're a go for landing.
[radio chatter]
Ratchet, let's roll!
[chatter continues]
[Optimus] We're
entering the Ark.
His levels are faint.
He locked himself away...
to guard the pillars.
Sentinel. You're
coming home, old friend.
[motor approaching]
[growling]
All hail Megatron!
My master! Yes, master! Yes!
Oh, don't be greedy,
my fragile ones.
Oh, my poor master!
How it pains me to see you
so wounded, so weak.
Spare me, you gaseous sycophant!
You know what you are told,
which is nothing.
Soundwave reporting,
Lord Megatron.
And what news from your
little assassin?
Autobots have taken the bait!
They've discovered the Ark
and returned with its cargo.
You did me great honor,tracking that ship to the moon.
Your human collaborators haveserved their purpose, Soundwave.
It's time to eliminate
loose ends.
[Megatron] Laserbeak...
kill them all.
[Laserbeak] With pleasure.
Is your daddy home?
- [girl] Then Madeline said
it's about time...
- [woman] Madeline!
Hello, Mom!
[screaming] Bob, get
out of the house!
- What are you doing
in my house?!
- [Laserbeak] Just visiting.
[♪ Goo Goo Dolls:
"All That You Are"]
♪ And I feel
♪ All the faint morning light
- What is this
hoochie-mama outfit?
- [speaking Spanish]
No, this is the aerospace
division, OK? We do not
allow that here!
New guy, you see that?
That's a Latin meltdown, OK?
You ever show up in my office
with a hoochie-mama outfit,you're fired. You got that? OK?
You're gonna be on this cart
for two and a half years, OK?
I want you to live it,
love it and name it.
There's no ladder climbing in myoffice. I run a tight ship, OK?
- Yes, sir.
- Move!
♪ Yeah, all the things
that you are ♪
♪ Beautifully broken
alive in my heart ♪
♪ And know that you
are everything ♪
♪ Let your heart sing
and tonight ♪
♪ We light up the stars
I found that paper
I was tellin' you about.
- What are we lookin' at?
- Shut up!
You do that to me again
and I'll kick your ass!
- Hi.
- Oh. Hi, angel.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
I had a meeting downtown.
Was it OK for me to stop by?
I don't know. My 500-page
employee conduct manual
isn't exactly a page turner.
- This is great.
- Yeah. Autobots are off
saving the world
and I've organized four binders.I'm livin' the dream. Come on.
Visitor violation.
- You OK?
- Absolutely.
- I'm next.
- Oh.
- Listen.
- Huh.
Saturday. Dylan's throwing
a party at his house.
It's a work thing,
but he's invited you, too.
- Oh, did he?
- I want you to come
and laugh at my bad jokes.
It would really
mean a lot to me, OK?
I'd love to go.
How'd you get over here?
- Car.
- You don't have a car.
Yes, I do.
What, did you
win it in a raffle?
- Uh, he gave me one.
- He gave you a car?
Yeah, I think it was
a work perk.
Huh. A work perk. What kind
of a car did he give you?
Um, a Mercedes SLS AMG.
- Mm-hm.
- Really throaty engine.
- [typing]
- [woman on computer]
The Mercedes Benz SLS
You drove this here? [exhales]
- That's a $200,000 car.
- [whispers] I know.
You know how long it would takeme to afford a car like this?
Long time?
- Yeah, like 53 years.- He said it was for both of us.
Then what we should do is weshould sell it and buy a house.
You're frustrated, I know.
I've been there.
It's called paying your dues.
Good things will happen.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I need some lunchtime
filing done, stat.
- He's coming.
- Who would like to score
some Bruce Brazos points?
- Bruce, you found your guy.
- [Carly clears throat]
Witwicky!
The man who makes
this company run!
Now who have we here?
Is it sister, Facebook friend,
Twitter tweeter?
- Carly, this is Bruce.
- Hi.
I'm his girlfriend.
Pleasure to meet you.
Sam was right. You really do
have a smashing head of hair.
- Well, thank you.
- Sam, I got to run.
- Yeah.
- Oh. Here. Your present.
Your favorite color.
- Nice to meet you,
Mister Brazos.
- And you.
See you, boys!
[elevator dings]
[♪ Debby Boone:
"You Light Up My Life"]
I'm still stewing about that
binder incident, Jerry.
May I finish my
Shuhua milk, Donny?
I don't care about your exotic
milk. I care about respect!
[groaning]
[slurping]
[sighs]
I know who you are!
- You mean...
- Witwicky! Witwicky!
I know you, I know you.
I'm talking to you!
Excuse me. Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
slow down, tiger.
You showed up in the backgroundof six different photos,
two continents, with aliens.
That was you
in Egypt, huh?
Right? Because you know
the aliens. See ya.
Give me my jacket!
[both grunting]
Hai! I'm Wang. Deep Wang.
Deep Wang. You're not
gettin' it. Deep Throat.
Watergate?
Talkin' code to you! Shh!
Damn it. Shhhh!
They watch and listen.
I can't go to the government.
But you, you can!Because shit's goin' down, son!
It is Code Pink as in Floyd!
Dark Side! Why do you
think no one's been
up there since 1972?
You're speaking English,
I just... It's a very
strange English.
That's why I'm not...
Oh, oh...
Don't. I'm gonna hit you.
I'm gonna hit you
right back, son.
Here's my manifesto.
They're whackin' us out.
Everyone who knows
what's on the dark...
- [door opens]
- [Brazos] I get it, I get it.
Your alien friends are indanger, you know, the good ones.
It's up to you.
- [stall rattling]
- [Sam] Calm down. Ow!
[Wang] Easy, Sam!
[zips pants]
What are you lookin' at?
Yo, dawg.
Are you up in my shit?!
Who you workin' for?
Staredown, you and me.
Guess I won.
Moon satellites.
The Russian space program.
Experts dead.
Space program ends.
Dark... dark side.
Dark side of the moon.
Look what I found outside the
bathroom, huh? Is it yours?
- Deal with this.
- Yes, sir.
I did everything you want!
I really think we should talk,
'cause some of this stuff...
Whoa! Knock first!
Can't you see I'm busy?
Who are you? Who are you?
You straddled me in the stall.
That's happened to me once inthis life. I wouldn't forget it.
In the bathroom stall.
You took your package out.
Whoa! Whoa!
We are not boyfriends, OK?
One phone call from me
and I'll have you fired!
Oh, yes I will, Gaylord!
- [Wang screeches]
- Are you OK?
Hemorrhoid!
Should I come back...?
When should I come back?
Come back when you
learn some manners!
[cries out] I don't know him!
I would never say anything!
Whoa... OK, OK! I sabotaged
the mapping satellite,
just like I promised.
I even put a blind spot
in the program as a bonus!
- What more do you want from me?- Jerry, you are my favorite.
I'll do whatever
you want me to do.
I know, but my superiors
need me to...
- Please. You don't
have to do this!
- ...suicide you.
What did you say
to Witwicky?
Oh, shit!
Huh? Who wants some chicken
dinner, now, bitch?!
'Cause somebody messed
with the wrong Wang today!
Come on! You want some of me?!
[grunts]
Oh, no, no, no...!
I don't need any more
didactic lectures from Chuck.
- [screaming]
- Jesus!
- [car alarm blaring]
- [panting]
Get legal.
That's Jerry!
Come on, people,
yes, a workmate died,
but looking out the window
is not gonna bring him back.
- The man was depressed.
- Don't take a picture!
You can keep watching him, but
he's not getting up. You all
read Humpty Dumpty.
OK? Witwicky...
I'm spearheading the press.
You clean up.
Wang is everywhere.
He is in the bistro.
He's in the bamboo.
He's on the balustrade.
You see the sidewalk down there?[laughing] Man!
Box up his personals. Get his
name off his parking space.
- One more thing...
- [Donny] Hey, when did we
get a new copier?
I'm not gonna say anything
about what I saw.
Who you share a toilet stall
with is totally your business.
This is exceedingly Japanese.
They never make it
easy, do they?
[screams]
[shrieks]
[all screaming]
[gasping]
- [Carly] What is with you?
- [Sam] This is
the real deal, Carly.
I need you to stay composed.
It's real life. I'll explain
it to you later.
We got an emergency. You gotta
get Colonel Lennox out here.
The Decepticons are back.
You gotta open that gate.
- Easy, sir, this is Health
and Human Services.
- Right, packing M4's?
What are you protecting,
colostomy bags? Bed pans?
Throat lozenges?
Where'd you get that hat from,
nursing school? You're nurses
and foot-powder protectors?
- I don't think we're
in the right place.
- We are in the right place.
We are in the right place
and I'm gonna talk to Optimus.
Sir, you got the wrong
building. I don't know
what you're talking about.
What part of "the Decepticonsare back" do you not understand?
Yo! You being a smartass?
[screaming] Do not hit my car!
It's a collector's item!
- I wouldn't do that.
- [Carly] You're crazy!
[both yelling]
We got an Energon reading!
- Got aliens in the vehicle!
- Whoa!!
You move, you're dead! Out! Out!
Got aliens in the vehicle!
- Freeze!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
We're freezin'!
Are you...
Are you kidding me?!
[Carly] Sam, they've got guns!
- I got him.
- Bee! Is Bee in there?!
[shouting] OK, all right!
This how you treat Autobots?
We're on the same team.
Yeah, enjoy your next job
at 7-Eleven, dickhead.
- That's right.
- A-hole.
How's your car now?
That's my car.
Come here.
- Come here!
- Come on. Sam.
What is your deal, huh?
I know your black ops stuff
is important.
I'm not trying to diminish it
or, you know, guilt-trip you,
I just never see you anymore.
You can't come to the garage
and just hang out one night?
Sam. That makes me
feel bad.
I hope you feel bad.
You should feel bad.
Look at the jalopy I'm
driving now. I feel bad
every single day.
Yo, let's go, both of you.
Lennox wants to see you.
We not good enough
for you anymore?
I'm sorry, babe.They were very rude, all right?
You're fixing my car.
You don't think so?
Raise your hand if you had
a flying psycho-ninja copier
try to kill you today!
- [detector beeping]
- Those are my brass knuckles.
That's my anklet. Do I
have to take that off, too?
- And my toe rings?
- [man on PA] All NEST
officials clear the floor.
We have ten minutes
until attempted contact.
[Mearing] We've taken possessionof the five devices
that were hidden in the ship
with Sentinel Prime.
They're some kind of prototype
Autobot technology.
They say Sentinel was the
Einstein of his civilization,
so we're gonna keep these
locked up until we know
what we're dealing with.
Right now, no one gets access.
- No one.- [Sam] This Wang guy recognizedme. He told me to warn you.
He was talking about
the dark side of the moon,
then they killed him.
- Wait a minute,
he mentioned the moon?
- Yeah, dark side of the moon.
But why would Decepticons
want to kill humans?
I thought their
war was with the Autobots.
And that is when he made
his first quick-look science
report. That's...
Who's the chick?
OK, excuse me! Colonel Lennox?
Director Mearing,
this is Sam Witwicky...
I know his name, colonel. I wantto know who gave him clearance?
How about Optimus Prime,
when he touched down in
suburbia looking for my house?
This is the National
Intelligence Director.
In case you...
- Hi.
- Disrespecting
a federal officer?
Huh. Maybe that'll get
you somewhere. Who's she?
- She's my girlfriend.
- What is this, like a date?
She knows all about the
Autobots, OK? She knows
Bumblebee.
She comes from a military
family. I can vouch for her.
Hey, I have an idea.
How about we get back
to the important topics,
like the fact that I almost hadmy face cut off by a Decepticon?
As a taxpayer, I'd like
to lodge a complaint,
as a matter of fact.
OK, listen, one of the
software engineers in Sam's
office was murdered today.
He was involved in NASA's
lunar mapping probe.
Here's the thing,
Colonel Lennox.
We cannot entrust national
security to teenagers,
unless I missed a policy paper.Are we doing that now?
No. Good.
I don't care who you are.
If you breathe a word of what
you see in here, you will do
time for treason.
Do you understand me?
I'll take my orders
from the Autobots.
I know them.
- I don't know you.
- You will.
[Lennox] Sentinel Prime.
These things run on Energon,
and he's out of it.
He's in a...
sort of a sleep mode.
[Optimus] Let us begin.
That's the great
Matrix of Leadership.
He holds the only thing
in the universe
that can repower a
Transformer's spark.
This is incredible.
Sentinel Prime...
...we bid you return.
Hold your fire!
Stop! Sentinel!
It is I, Optimus Prime!
It is all right. You are safe.
There is nothing to fear.
We are here.
You are home, Sentinel.
The war... the war!
The war was lost.
Cybertron is now
but a barren wasteland.
We have taken refuge here
on Planet Earth.
Its human race is our ally.
My ship! We came under fire!
The pillars.
Where are the pillars?
You saved five of them,
including the control pillar.
Only five?!
We once had hundreds!
Excuse me, gentlemen,
may I ask...
What is this technology
you're looking for?
It is the ability
to reshape the universe.
Together the pillars
form a space bridge.
I designed and,
I alone, can control it.
It defies your laws
of physics to transport
matter through time and space.
You're talking about
a teleportation device,
aren't you?
Yes, for resources,
for refugees.
Refugees, or troops of soldiers,weapons, maybe bombs!
A means of an instant strike!
That's its military function,
isn't it?
It is our technology
and it must be returned.
Yes, if humans say so.
You can't just bring weapons
of mass destruction
into our atmosphere!
You kinda have to clear
Customs first! A little
formality called "paperwork."
Kinda separates us
from the animals.
I will overlook your
condescending tone
if you heed
the gravity of mine.
The Decepticons must never knowthe space bridge is here.
For in their hands,
it would mean
the end of your world.
"Total Nightmare" file.
So the investigation is open.
We've sent agents to youroffice. And for the time being,
we're gonna send you home
with Autobot protection.
Who do I need to speak to
to get you guys to understand
that I can help?
- That I can contribute?
- Hey, we can all help.
Want me to tell you what
I know? I could tell you
about the solar system,
- all the fun planets
to hang out in.
- Get off my desk, please.
You pulling out guns? I can't
help you out now. She angry.
- Oh, my God.
- What do you envision for me?
I go home now? I go back
to work? I make copies?
This is a unit for veteran
intelligence officers
and Special Forces,
not for boys who
once owned special cars.
That's a bit harsh,
isn't it, ma'am?
Don't call me ma'am.
I'm not a ma'am.
You're a woman,
aren't you?
[clearing throat] So...
- ...are those yours?
- Yeah. CIA.
I only ask 'cause I also have
a medal, from the president.
Yeah. Great. So it's
not complicated, right?
No one gets to work
with the Autobots
unless I approve it.
You're breaking
my chain of command.
Come on, let's go.
You've done what you came for.
With all due respect, youngman, I appreciate what you did.
But you're not a soldier.
You're a messenger.
- You've always
been a messenger.
- He's a hero.
Bee, you take the freightelevator, I'll see you up there.
[Wheelie] Ah. this blows. That
lady officially kicked us out.
Yeah. Witness Protection
Program sucks.
Yeah, but we're a whole
lot safer with Big Yellow
and his cannons.
'Cause that dog
can't protect crap.
[Sam] Bee?
You miss hanging out?
Yeah, me, too.
That woman called me
a messenger. Can you
believe that?
After everything I've done,
I'm a messenger.
Oh, I believe it. I tell you,
Sammy, we feel the same way.
The disrespect
on this rock is criminal.
We should do something about it.
Bee...
...I need to know why
they're killing humans.
I say we call in the expert.
[man] My next guest is a former intelligence operative
who has dared to speak out
regarding our alleged
military alliance
with what many describe as
a group of extraterrestrial
mercenaries.
He is the author
of the bestselling book,
Code-Name Hero.
Former special agent,
Seymour Simmons.
Bill. Big fan. Great to be here.
Agent Simmons, you would
have us believe
that it is in our best interest
to formally take sides in this so-called alien civil war?
Well, the other side wanted
to spank us for breakfast,so I wouldn't call it a toss-up.
These Decepticons are lethal.
But polls show half
the world would feel safer
with the
Autobots completely gone.
Get them out of here!
We don't need them!
I feel safer when I sleep
with a hand grenade.
Doesn't mean
I'm always right.
Now, agent, here
atThe Factor,
we have obtained documents
that show you were fired...
- Chaz, I'm doing an interview.- Sorry, Mr. Simmons.
Downsized, Bill. Budget cuts.
Chaz, out.
...report "severe
delusional tendencies."
This is ambush journalism.
You want the truth about
the alien alliance?
Buy my book! Buy my book,
before it's too late, people!
You want a piece of me, Bill?
You want to get naked? I'm
ready! Interviewis over!
You sound like
a pinhead, agent.
I got a suggestion for you:
Damage control.
- Dutch!
- You have upset Mr. Simmons!
You have 23 seconds
to leave the property!
I have called the police!
You are peasants, people,
throwing rocks at a giant!
What's up next?
What do we got?
Book signing, midtown, noon.
Then we pitch your reality showto Discovery Channel.
Oh, and I have this...
"Vitvicky" who keeps
calling me five times today.
- Kid? What does he want?
- I called you because the
Decepticons are back.
- I want to know why
and need your help.
- They're back?
Well, that's good for business.
What if I told you I know
a 50-year-old alien secret
- that nobody ever told you?
- Do not tempt my addiction.
I have gone
through withdrawal, kid
- Dutch, is this line secure?
- No.
Don't take the risk.
I'm rich, why should I?
Do not relapse. I won't.
Do not let the demons win.
- [beeps]
- Got it.
What kind of... secret?
Apollo. Moon. Aliens. Cover-up.
Future tech. Assassinations.
That kind of stuff.
Oh, Apollo.
Dutch!
Tell Megatron, "Let's tango."
So majestic and peaceful,
this planet.
Unlike the final days
of Cybertron.
I've wondered what
might have been...
...if you had foughtthe final battle, instead of me.
Never mourn the past,
young warrior.
Thanks to you,
our race survives.
You were our
leader, Sentinel.
It is your right
to lead us again.
In a world I do not know...
...I am no longer
your teacher, Optimus.
You are mine.
We've got to break
this case down.
What we have here is
an astronaut epidemic.
MIA. Dead.
Died in a car accident.
Killed. DOA. Car death.
It's like these guys
can't drive.
They can fly into outer space,
but they can't drive a car.
- Procured your
information, Witwicky.
- Thank you, Bruce.
Now...
You let me see one
right now. One time.
- Quick.
- Very.
Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter.
Says NASA launched it in 2009.
Forensics show Wang may
have messed with the code,
preventing it from mapping
the far side of the moon,
which is also the dark side.
Fuckin' awesome.
They infiltrate us,
intimidate us,
coerce us to do their dirty
work. And once they're done...
Doosh! ...double-tap
to the cerebellum.
So humans are working
for the Decepticons.
I don't think this is about
the Decepticons looking
for something on the moon.
I think it's about something
they wanted to hide.
Come to Daddy.
Come on, throw down.
Did you eat a lot of paint chipswhen you were a kid?
- He's a freak.
- Ha! Like it?
[grunts, laughing]
I'm ticklish!
Sir! We are having a
pretty high-level alien
intel confab here,
that I don't think you're
cleared for, errand boy.
Yeah, you're right.
It's a bitchin' robot.
[Sam] I think it's
time to go, Bruce.
Thank you so much for this.
Got to go, Bruce.
Hey, I'm smokin' over here.
Downloading missing
Russian cosmonauts.
Turns out, the Soviets cancelleda manned mission to the moon.
The moon! In 1972.
Then two of the cosmonauts
went into hiding in America.
And I just found them alive.
[Wheelie] You're a genius,
Brains.
- [gasps]
- [Sam] Whoa!
[Brains] Oh, that was
smooth, Bumblebee.
Missed it by that much.
- Hi.
- Would somebody care to tell
me what the hell's going on?
- Who are you?
Who am I? Who is that?
Dutch! Frisk her!
- Certainly.
- No. Dutch. Um...
- Don't touch me.
- I'm not gonna touch her.
- Sam?
- Angel.
Uh... I was working.
I'm sorry about this.
- [Brains] Great,
we're homeless.
- She lives here? Wow.
You had your chance
to frisk her.
- I have a girlfriend.
- Really? What's her name?
India.
We're supposed to be
at Dylan's party, remember?
I do remember, but these are myfriends, they need me. I have tobe here right now.
The Autobots and the military,
they can't handle this
on their own?
You know what I liked
about your war stories, Sam,
is that they were stories.
They were in the past.
Look, I know you're thinking
about your brother, and you're
thinking about your family.
And it's not that situation.No? Why not? Why isn't it, Sam?
You think we'd
rather have his medals,
or we'd rather have him?
I hear you. I get it.
Where are you
taking my bunny? Stop!
Just stop for a second.
You think I could sleep last
night? And then it hit me:
No, Sam wants to be in danger.
- He doesn't know
who he is without it.
- I just want to matter.
You matter to me.
I know you're worried, but Ipromise you, I can handle this.
- Can you?
You can promise it?
- I promise.
Sam, I don't want to lose you,
and I know where this leads.
I'm not ready for this.
Are you coming with me?
I can't.
OK.
Hey...
Here's your foot.
The warrior's path
is a solitary one.
How the hell did
she afford that car?
- Her boss.
- Rich bastards!
I used to hate 'em.
Now, it's...
[Seymour] Goin' to a gig on ahunt for two Russian cosmonauts.
Nothin' like drivin'
in a Maybach, huh?
Germans know how to make cars,
let me tell ya.
My Dutchman, former NSA,
cybersleuth extraordinaire,
tracked 'em down here.
So these cosmonauts went
into hiding. Why?
Bingo. I got a match.
You're a German Shepherd, Dutch.
The thing about Russians
is, they never like to talk.
Gonna take a little of the
"international language."
- [speaking Russian]
- That means "goodbye."
[whispers] Watch this.
[speaking Russian]
[♪ Seryoga: "Discomalaria"]
[Seymour] Stay loose.
Dutch. Give me somethin' tough.
Uh... Baryshnikov.
- We do speak English.
- Dutch, you suck.
It's a Cyrillic alphabet!
It's like all the buttonsyou never push on a calculator!
- I don't suck.
- Agent Seymour Simmons,
Sector Eight, formerly Seven.
- We know who you are,
cosmonaut-chiks.
- So what?
You were supposed to travel
to the dark side of the moon.
Then, tsk...
it all got shut down.
The question is... why?
[speaking Russian]
Nostrovia!
"Can my child smoke in here?"
[speaking Russian]
[shouting]
- [yelps]
- Agh, OK, all right, OK.
- Go ahead, shoot me.
- [speaking Russian]
I'm willin' to die
for my country. Are you?
Really?
You are beautiful. Has anyoneever told you you're beautiful?
- She's a beautiful woman.
- [woman yelling]
Whoa! Hey!
Dutch! Back in the cage.
[yells]
Halt, Dutch! Halt!
Control your boy, please!
Control your boy!
Dutch! Stop!
[speaking foreign language]
I'm so sorry.
That is the old me.
OK, let's everybody
just calm down!
Let's lower the heat,
lower the guns. Let's relax.
World War Two is over.
You are about to see one
of the biggest Soviet secrets.
America, first to send
man to the Moon.
But USSR, first to send camera.
In 1959, our Luna 3...
...take picture of the dark,
the shadow side.
Sees nothing.
- But in 1963, Luna 4sees...
- Strange rocks.
- Yeah.
- Around the ship.
- Hundreds of them.
- Yeah, show picture, hm?
[Sam] With some... drag marks.
I've seen these. Thesearen't rocks. These are pillars.
Alien pillars
for a space bridge.
We know about them 'cause the
Autobots have five of these.
Decepticons must have
raided the ship
before Apollo 11ever got there,
took the pillars...
- ...and hid them.
- It doesn't make sense.
The Decepticons have the ship.
They have all those pillars.
Why would they leave Sentinel
when he's the only one that
can use them?
Unless....
He's the one thing
they still need.
We got to meet up with Sentinel.Rendezvous with him and
keep him safe.
Mearing, I just picked up
Sentinel.
Optimus is ten minutes behind.
We're comin' to NEST now.
Mr. Witwicky, I thought I made
it clear to you that I did not
want you calling this phone.
[Sam] Listen, the whole thing
has been a setup since
the beginning.
The Decepticons wanted Optimus
to find Sentinel because
only Optimus could revive him.
- But we have the space bridge.- Mearing, you have
five pillars.
I just learned that
they have hundreds.
You're doing exactly what
they wanted you to do. What
do you need me to say to you?
The Decepticons are coming
for Sentinel Prime!
We're going to NEST.
[man on PA] We have an Energon
alert. Energon readings
detected on the DC Parkway.
Currently tracking
three black Suburbans.
[sirens wailing]
Whoa! [screaming]
Bee, you got to get Sentinel outof here! You got to guard him!
Oh, mein Gott!I'm fired!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Got you!
Shoot him, shoot him!
Shoot him, Bee!
Bee, you got to move!
Faster, faster, Bee! Go!
Bee! Ohhh!
[yelling]
[shrieking]
All right, back to NEST!
Dino, I got him!
Ironhide!
[roaring]
- Get him!
- Is there a problem?
Whoa. A little Mexican
standoff we got here.
Weapons down.
And we'll let you escape
with your dignity.
Drop 'em.
That's good.
[Sideswipe] Ironhide! Watch out!
Yagh!
Ironhide! Catch!
Behind you!
[Ironhide] Decepticon punk!
Class dismissed.
- Get inside! Let's go!
- Move! Team's moving!
- Lennox!
- Go, go, go, go!
We got Decepticons everywhere.
I've got my whole team
deployed, lookin' for 'em.
Ironhide! Protect Sentinel!
- Get him locked up inside!
- Consider it done!
You gotta guard him 'cause he'sthe key to the whole thing.
Indeed, I am.
What you must realize,
my Autobot brothers,
is we were never
going to win the war.
For the sake of
our planet's survival,
a deal had to be
made... with Megatron.
[groans]
- Get back!
- What have you done?
I hereby discharge you
from duty.
Nooo!
[Lennox] Fall back, take cover!
- Bee!
- Get back!
Bee!
[screaming]
Rally all NEST forces
back to the base!
Come on! Come on!
[groaning]
- Get a medic down here!
- We don't have enough men!
Do not engage Sentinel!
[Mearing] Just go
to the back gate.
[man] Take cover!
Punch left, punch left!
Let's go! Follow me!
[shouting, screaming]
- Director...
- Stand down!
- Hey, Sentinel!
- Director!
What is going on?What do you think you're doing?
I am a Prime!
I do not take
orders from you.
Director Mearing, come on.
We can't fight him. Let's go.
- We have to go.- Now return what belongs to me!
Oh... my God!
- [man] You guys OK?
- [man 2] Everybody out!
Is everybody out?!
OK, buddy, stay calm.
You're gonna be fine,
just breathe slow.
Yeah, take a look, Optimus!
This is all on you!
Sentinel hit the vault!
Took the pillars.
Come on, let's go.
All right, notify
the 101st Airborne!
We need to hunt this thing down!
- [gasping]
- [sirens blaring]
[panting] Carly?!
Hot from our little campfire.
S'mores.
- Aw.
- Isn't that great?
We were really
livin' off the land.
Mom, Dad, have you guys seen
Carly come home yet?
Excuse me, can you knock,
please? This is our bedroom.
- Why wouldn't she be at home?
- We had a fight and...
...we might have broken up or beon a break. I don't really know.
- What?! No!
- Look, I can't talk
about it right now.
- You got to be kidding me!
- I can't go into the details.
I have to find her.
Sit down! We're havin' afamily meeting! Family meeting!
You may not know this,
but your father and I
were not always this perfectly
happy. You know, there was
a time in our marriage
- when I thought this
was not gonna work out.
- Can we please not?
- I'm just trying to understand.- She's damaging him.
You break up with one
world-class hottie...
No, stop, stop, OK?
She dumped me, I moved on to
somethin' better. That's it.
I'm a happier person.
Why don't you help me?
- They had an argument.
- [Sam] One fight.
You're not gonna get a third
one. I mean, unless you have,
like, a big...
What the f...?!
Ma! Mom, Mom...
...don't know
what you're doin'.
I don't want
to talk about this.
You need the book.
You're always wrong.
Get used to it.
OK, this, you got to read
this. She Comes First.
- There's some killer
shit in this.
- No, no, no...
- Oh, that's it, I'm goin'...
- No, no.
Sit down! Sit down!
Back me up!
- Happy wife, happy life.
- Fuck, yeah.
Unhappy wife, stone-coldmisery for the rest of your....
- Stop.
- It's true.
All I'm sayin' is,
do you love this girl?
- She's the one.
- Then you gotta go get her.
I mean, your dad and I,
when we had troubles, he...
...he moved heaven
and earth to find me.
Guess what he...
Say what you said. Say it.
"I will follow you
to the end of time."
Does that suck or what?
- I mean, it's like
a bad sci-fi film.
- No, it was so sweet.
I want you to get out of
the city. You get as far
away from here as you can.
You understand?
I love you.
[gibbering]
Ah, my master!
Such a brilliant scheme!
So, when Sentinel left
Cybertron, it was to defect.
He was meant to rendezvous
with me here on Earth
before fate waylaid us both.
The only way to revive him:
We needed Prime and his Matrix.
[Starscream] Excellent strategy.
Mine, mine!
So he is now
your partner, master?
He is my
greatest triumph.
So impressive.
Commencing transport.
- Stop! No! No, no, Sentinel!
- Forgive me.
Here we are.
Fight us now.
Autobots, retreat!
[yelling]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Why, Sentinel, why?!
For Cybertron! For our home!
What war destroyed,
we can rebuild!
But only if we join
with the Decepticons.
No, it's not the only way.
This is our home!
We must defend the humans!
So lost you are, Optimus.
On Cybertron,
we were gods.
And here, they
call us machines.
Let the humans
serve us or perish.
You're lucky I didn't kill you.
In time, you'll see.
It's not over.
[Dylan] Now if I were him,
I wouldn't let you out
of my sight for one second.
- [chuckles]
- Mmm.
It's funny. I was just thinkin'on the way over here,
I could really use some
advice from Dylan.
And there he is.
- Can I speak to you?
- Welcome. Please, sit down.
Have a drink.
You know what? I don't need
a drink. Or a car or a job.
I just need to speak to my
girlfriend alone. Is that OK
with you, Mr. Inappropriate?
Excuse me.
- What's going on?
- I'll tell you outside.
I really think
I could help you, Sam.
I remember a talk I had withmy dad once about tough choices.
[Sam] Yeah, now's not the time.We'll set somethin' up, though.
[Dylan] Of course, that was
way back when my dad's firm
was in charge of budget review
and accounting for NASA.
You see, the thing
that he taught me was,
when it's not your war,
you join the side
that's going to win.
- Move.
- [Dylan] Too direct?
- Or was it just me?
- Certainly not you, sir.
- You're mine!
- [screams]
No!
- Get help!
- Sam, I can't get out!
- Good night.
- Good night, Mr. Gould.
[Carly] Get me out of here!
[Sam] Help! Get help!
- He's young. He will learn.
- [Carly] Get me out!
- Good night.
- It was a fun night.
You really think
you're the first man
- ever asked to join
the noble alien cause?
- Who are you?!
Do you know why we've
not been back to the moon
since 1972?
Because these two... they came
to my dad and they told himto do some creative accounting.
Make it way too expensive
to ever go back.
So he and others shut down
the American and Russian
space programs,
- and they've been
our clients ever since.
- You help them kill people?
You think they give you
a choice? Besides, it's notlike I personally participated.
I am a liaison. I liaise.
[grunting]
It's hostile takeover time, Sam.
Sam!
- Sam!
- Let her go!
- [grunting]
- Sam!
[whimpering]
[Dylan] I've had my eye
on you for years, Sam.
The one spy I've never been
able to provide is someone
close to the Autobots.
Sam, don't do what he wants!
Yes, he will. They all do.
[grunts]
They will slaughter her,
do you understand me?
In the time it
takes you to blink,
they will do it to her
and they will do it to me.
So you show a little respect
when someone
offers you a job!
A wrist.
You are to track down
Optimus Prime, because
you're the one human he trusts
and you will
ask one question:
How does he intend
to fight back?
Strategies, tactics, everything!
- [screams]
- Has a nasty little bite,
doesn't it?
It's very high-tech.
It lets us see what you see,
hear what you hear and it
taps your nervous system.
So if you so much as
try and signal...
- [crackling]
- [groans]
I don't know what
to tell you, Sam.
Relationships have consequences.
I am here because of my father.
She is here because of you.
- [Carly yells]
- Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
Soundwave, would you please?
Sam? Do your job.
She'll be safe.
I give you my word.
I'll kill you.
You have my word.
[man] Combatant Commands
are now at DEFCON one.
Approximately two hundred
Decepticons are now in hiding.
Energon detectors have been
triggered as far away as
South America and China.
The UN has just received
an encrypted audio file.
They say it's from
the leader of the Autobots.
[Sentinel] Defenders of Earth.
We have come for your
natural resources
to rebuild our damaged planet.
When we have transported
all we need,
we will leave
your world in peace.
For such peace to exist,
you must immediately
exile the Autobot rebels
you have harbored.
Nonnegotiable.
Renounce the rebels.
We await your reply.
[Mearing] We'll debrief you
in transit.
I really don't see how
I can be of any help.
You guys seem pretty busy.
We could just do this
another time, I think.
[groans]
I have underestimated you
at every turn.
- What?
- You warned us that
they were using humans.
And you knew that
Sentinel was the key.
- Director!
- No, who am I?
Hey, you're the expert.
I'm just a walkin'
security risk.
[gasps]
[clattering]
- Are you all right?
- [groaning]
- [straining] Yes.
- No, you're not.
You're sweating.
I'm, I'm fine. I'm fine.I'm sweating 'cause I'm nervous.
I'm nervous because you
got me in here with
this information, OK?
I'm a Twitter junkie. I
blog everything. I can't keep
a secret to save my life.
- Oh, you wouldn't dare.
- Director, the Pentagon's
calling in 15.
- What are you doin'?
- Nothin', what are you doin'?
Get away from me.
It's been a remarkable series of events today at the Capitol.
And just moments ago,
legislation was passed
to exile the Autobots
from American shores.
The US military alliance
with them is officially over.
- Yeah?
- In the words of the House
Majority Leader,
the sponsor of
today's resolution,
- "We cannot in good
conscience...
- What?
They can't do this. You got to
tell 'em they can't do that.
OK, it's official.
It's a go, people!
These are our allies.
The Autobots fought for us,
they fought with us.
And where are we now?
Facing an enemy invasion
with an enemy that has the meansto deploy countless more.
[Mearing] If there
is any more you know,
anything at all about
the enemy's intentions...
...now is the time to tell.
Autobots have no way
of leavin' this planet.
And that is
where you're wrong.
Its name is theXantium.
It brought the second wave
of Autobots,
and it's been under NASA's
care and study ever since.
We linked it with a
decommissioned Shuttle,
to maintain military control
until they're gone.
Gonna be 10,000 pounds oftorque on that itsy bitsy bolt!
- Not nineteen!
- You're gonna risk
the lives of all me mates!
- I'll bottle ya!
- These guys are the Wreckers.
They take care of the Xantium.
We don't let 'em off the base
much, 'cause they're assholes.
- You're gonna pull that,
you nancy wanker!
- It's time to kill him!
I'm just tryin' to help, you
know? I'm just doin' my job!
Just calm down. Leave him alone.This is a human being.
- Epps!
- [Wrecker]
You are ridiculous!
- Is that you?
- Hey, what up, man?
- What are you doin' here?- I retired from the Air Force.
Can you let my hand go?
What the hell was that?
Now I just consult to run
interference for them.
[Wrecker] Well,
you're not helpin'!
No more combat and aliens
shootin' at my ass.
- I got a dream job.
- Time to get off this planet.
Kickin' the Autobots out.
Can you believe this
is happenin'?
Where do you
think it's taking 'em?
Any planet but here.
I want to talk to who's
ever in charge here.
Well, well, well.
Charlotte Mearing.
Agent Simmons.
Former Agent Simmons.
So, I see you
survived Washington.
Washington, Egypt, heartbreak.
I survive. I will survive.
They're bringin'
everybody in, kid.
Putting all the intel
on the table.
And if you think
deporting nine Autobots
is gonna solve a damn thing...
It's out of my hands.
Moving up in the world, huh?
Your booty looks excellent.
You ever say a word to anyone
about what happened that night
in Quantico,
I'll cut your heart out.
You already did.
Sammy, listen to me.
Don't let 'em exile us.
Don't let 'em take us, Sam.
It's a Decepticon trap.
Check the nitrogen levels.
We're bookin' out of here, eh?
- Optimus?- What your leaders say is true.
Aye, this was all my fault.
I told them whom to trust.
I was so wrong.
That doesn't make it
your fault. It just makes
you human for a change.
Remember this.
You may lose
your faith in us,
but never in yourselves.
[groaning]
I need to know how
you're gonna fight back.
I know there's a strategy. Iknow you're, you're comin' backwith reinforcements, somethin'.
I know there's a plan. I....
You can tell me.
No other human will ever know.
There is no plan.
If we just do what they want,
how are we gonna live with
ourselves?
You are my friend, Sam.
You always will be.
But your leaders have spoken.
From here...
the fight will be your own.
Make it short.
We're loading up.
[Wrecker] All right, hustle up!We're launchin' at dawn.
We're gonna do whatever we can.
Make it like it was.
You will always be
my friend, Sam.
I got to be goin' on.
[sobbing]
Years from now,
they're gonna ask us...
"Where were you when they
took over the planet?"
And we're gonna say...
"we just stood by and watched."
[Dylan] You should really look
at this as a partnership.
You have to stand on the side
of progress if you want
to be a part of history.
[radio chatter]
[man on PA] Seven, six, five...
Four, three, two, one, zero.
Go ahead and throttle up,
CAPCOM. Booster flight.
- [applause]
- Go ahead, flight.
[line ringing]
Well, you wanted an answer.
You got one.
[Dylan] I always get
what I want, Sam.
We just needed to be sure.
Sure of what?
That they would go
without a fight.
- [man on PA] Say again?
- [woman on PA] We're tracking
an incoming object.
[grunting]
We all work
for the Decepticons now.
I need your help to track
a phone call. There's a man
on this phone.
He's the head of their
human operations and
he has Carly hostage.
I want you to sit down.
Don't move, all right?
Follow me.
I'm watching him
drive up right now.
[Dutch] The call
was placed en route.
Wait, I'm hacking into
the phone's camera now.
There, that's it! That's a livestream from the camera.
Some place. Hold on,
I can triangulate this.
OK, it's Chicago cell sites.
There, I've got it.
Trump Tower, Chicago.
Lower penthouse.
We're on.
- I'm goin'.
- [Seymour] You sure?
She's done nothin' but try
to help me and I can be there
in 15 hours.
You're not goin' alone.
I still got my NEST
friends out there.
I'm gonna round 'em up,
we gonna find your girlfriend,
we gonna bring this guy in.
Why are you helpin' me?
'Cause that asshole
killed my friends, too.
They said they were here
for our resources.
- To rebuild their planet.
- Yes.
But really one resource
in particular.
One unique to our planet.
Us?
You're very smart.
You see, they can't rebuild
without a slave labor force.
How many rocks up there
in the universe offer
six billion workers?
What are you talking about?
We can't transport people.
They're not shipping people.
They're shipping their planet
here.
Oh, my God.
What's Sentinel doing here?
[Dylan] Watch. They're
spreading hundreds of pillars
around the globe right now.
In just a few hours, they're
gonna launch 'em into orbit
and bring Cybertron
into our atmosphere.
The red one there
controls the rest.
He triggers that,
it starts the whole thing.
Begone, insect operative.
Your work is done.
Your Excellency.
He's such a dick.
[people screaming, shouting]
- You want this to happen?
- I want to survive.
I want 40 more years.
You think I asked for this?
- I inherited a client.- Yeah and when Cybertron's here
and we're all their slaves,
I guess they'll still need
a human leader.
Don't jinx me. You want to
survive? You listen to me.
- [sirens blaring]
- [men shouting]
It is time for the slaves
of Earth to recognize
their masters.
Seal off the city.
[Dylan] Get the dogs
out of here now!
Get 'em in the back!
I guess they didn't tell you
about this part, did they?
You think I'm in every meeting?
Look, I'm safe.
They said I'm safe.
Let's roll!
[♪ Linkin Park: "Iridescent"]
We had a signal earlier.
It's not workin'.
♪ When you were standing
in the wake of devastation ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
♪ When you were waiting
on the edge of the unknown ♪
♪ With the cataclysm
raining down ♪
♪ Insides crying
"Save me now" ♪
♪ You were there
impossibly alone ♪
Wrong way!
[man] Get out of here!
Go back!
[man] There is a ring
of alien ships around Chicago.
Our high-range bombers were
just knocked out of the sky.
They can't get through enemy
air defenses over the city.
Our satellites have been
jammed. We have no way to
monitor the enemy's movement.
All NEST teams are on
stand-down, holding at
Grissom Air Force Base.
We're about ten minutes
from the battle zone.
We have Special Forces trying
to gain access to the city.
And infantry is staging
at the perimeter.
Excuse me, excuse me!
It just doesn't make sense!
Can't we get any eyes
in there at all?
- They keep shooting
down our drones.
- They want us blind.
But we do have a couple of
mini-drones we're gonna try.
Well, who's ever manning
these UAV drones,
can we try to redirect them
toward Trump Tower?
The kid, Witwickety,
was on his way to Chicago.
Said some point-man human op
is there, for the Decepticons!
Listen, if I know
anything, I know this:
That kid is an
alien-bad-news magnet!
My God.
We came here to find her
in the middle of all that?
Hey, we really
goin' out there, Epps?
- I'm not goin' in there.
- No one's goin' in.
I am.
With or without you,
I'll find her.
You're gonna get yourself
killed, Sam!
Is that what you want?
You came all the way out here
to get yourself killed? Huh?
- Listen to what I'm sayin'.
- She's here because of me.
Do you understand?
Listen. If you go
in this buildin',
that's if she's even
still alive,
there's no way you're gonna
be able to reach her!
What do you suggest I do?
It's over.
I'm sorry, but it's over.
No.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Incoming!
- [yells]
[all yelling]
[screaming]
We will kill them all.
Wreckers, kill him!
This is going to hurt!
A lot!
Ah, ha-ha!
Your leaders will
now understand.
Decepticons will never
leave your planet alone.
And we needed them
to believe we had gone.
For today, in the name
of freedom, we take
the battle to them!
I saw your ship blow up!
The ship? We were never
in the ship!
We designed the damn
thing, didn't we?!
We were hidden in the first
booster rocket to separate.
Splashed down back in the
Atlantic, just as planned.
[spits] We ain't goin' nowhere.
Yeah, no one's exilin' us.
The Autobots are
stayin' right here.
We're gonna help you
win this war.
They're surrounding the city
to make a fortress,
so that no one can see
what they're up to inside.
Our only chance is
the element of surprise.
I think I know where to look!
[man] Mini-drone is
on approach to Trump Tower.
You're tellin' me
Sam's headed into that?
Poor kid.
Probably never got close.
So you can fly
this thing, right?
What is that supposed...?
What is that? So-so?
So you so-so can fly this?
That feels terrible.
We're right behind you.
All right, we're goin' in!
The city is secure.
The humans cannot stop us.
As the afternoon falls,
the rest of the pillars will
reach their launch position.
This is the victory I promised
you so many years ago,
where we rebuild
Cybertron together!
I have deigned to work
with you that our planet
may survive!
I will never work for you!
And you would be wise to
remember the difference.
Ugh, I'm so sick of this.
I'm just sick of waiting.
Where is she?
Where is she?!
You've got some balls.
[yelling]
[gun fires]
No, Sam!
No! No! No!
Carly!
- Carly!
- [grunts]
Jump!
Bee! Fire!
Bee!
Whoa!
[yelling]
Autobots! They're alive!
- They're here, they're alive!
- Decepticons,
defend the pillar!
Raise the bridges!
Find them!
Oh, Sam.
Oh! You found me.
I'd have followed you anywhere.
- Form a perimeter!
- [man] Let's go, let's go!
- Oh, you're crazy.
- What is that? Is that us?
This thing's a military UAV.
Stone, check and see if
it's still workin'.
[Stone] Yeah, it's
still got power.
Flight Control, do you copy?
Can, can you rotate?
- Can you do somethin'?
- I think we got something.
- Epps, we got Epps!
- Can you rotate or somethin'?
Come on, man, work! Work!
All right, turn the volume
up on that!
- The kid!
- Can you rotate? somethin'!
Yes, yes! OK, OK, OK.
They can see us.
Chicago is ground zero.
Do you understand?
- Do you hear us?
You understand?
- Witwicky.
Please listen. Sentinel Prime
is here and he has the pillars
for his space bridge.
They're on top of a building onthe Chicago River. It's owned byHotchkiss Gould Investments.
Now the pillar that
controls everything is
in the southeast cupola.
You gotta destroy the pillar.
You have to shoot down
the pillar
or they're gonna
transport Cybertron here.
Do you understand?
- Do you understand?
- What?
Give me a GPS on the
building and on that drone!
Let's go!
Mensurate those coordinates.
Shorten the kill chain.
[Lennox] Guys on the tarmac,
five minutes.
All right.
We need to move before
the fighters spot us.
Wait here until we scout
a route ahead. Let's roll.
Ratchet, cover high.
Hey, you think we could
use that rocket to shoot
down the pillar?
We're eight blocks away. We gotto get closer to take a shot.
Not closer. Higher.
We need clear line of sight.
And it's across the river.
We're gonna have a hell of
a time tryin' to sneak up.
- We only got one shot.
- One shot's all we need.
We got to be able to see aroundthat building from the ground.
Get NSA to send server specs
for any cameras in that area.
Maybe some are working. Trafficlights. ATMs. Anything.
[Lennox] Listen up.
You want to hit back?
We're gonna have to wingsuit in.It's the only way to get close.
I can't promise anyone a ride
home, but if you're with me...
...the world needs you now.
I can find my own
ride home, sir.
Who else?!
[man] Right here, sir!
General Morshower,
requesting diversionary action
to the south of the city.
We're comin' north and low.You guys drive 'em to the east.
Autobot victory,
Autobot victory!
That is one scary-ass
Decepticon!
They got my trailer.
I need that flight tech.
Shockwave can't hunt
all of us at once.
Wreckers, we need a diversion.
- Let's get some!
- You got that right.
Listen, we're gonna circle
around to that glass buildin'.
And we'll get high enough
to make the rocket shot.
While you guys draw his fire!
Let's move!
Wait a minute! I'm not lettin'
ya go out there without my
urban combat prototypes.
- We gotta go, Que! Come on!
- Oh, please!
They're great inventions
for kicking ass!
- What are these?
- [Que] Those are boom-sticks.
Armed in 30 seconds.
Grapple gloves, for climbin'.
[Epps] Go, go, move your ass!
Move, move!
Move, move! Go, go, go!
- Move, move!
- Let's go!
- Agh!
- Ow, ow, ow!
Let's go! Run!
Hey, hey, hey, where you
goin'?
No, no, no! Stop, stop, stop!
Don't leave!
You never leave a 'bot behind!
Aw, Shockwave's comin'!
- [Epps] Go for the stairs!
- Epps, this way!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
[man] Breakin' right,
breakin' right.
[man 2] Bead. Rollin' in.
We got another one comin'
around, comin' around
the left side.
Comin' around on the right sideand lookin' around.
We're gonna use
Willis Tower for cover!
Once we make altitude, we jump!
There are a lot
of airplanes out here!
Mayday, I don't think
he's gonna make it.
[man 3] Heads up, heads up!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- [man] Tally on the left. - [man 2] Got 'em. Have visual.
[man 3] Time on target:
20 seconds.
All right, here we go!
Here we go!
- Keep it tight!
- Clear. Comin' around.
All right,
focus, focus, focus.
[man] Threat above!
Pop-up! Six o'clock!
Locusts!
Look out, look out!
Break right!
- [man] Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
- [man 2] Holy shit!
Look out, look out!
Get 'em out,
get 'em out, get 'em out!
- Everybody out, out, out!
- Go, go, jump, jump!
- Get out, get out!
- I'm stuck, I'm stuck!
[man] Tail, get 'em out now,
get 'em out now.
Help!
Get separation.
Track away, track away.
Hard left! Hard left!
Six hundred feet!
Check your six!
He's on our ass!
Watch out, watch out!
[screams]
Sharp right!
Building dead ahead!
Thread the needle!
- Whoa!
Pull, pull!
[Sam] All right, come on,
we're high enough!
This is a mother,
gettin' up here!
- Get your fat ass over here!
- I'm comin'.
Set up the rocket!
- They're comin'.
- All right, weapon status!
Twenty-nine Bot-busters.
Twenty piercing D-Bots.
There. The building
with the dome.
For our brothers.
Let's make this trip worth it.
- Oh, God.
- [building creaking]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- [man] Is this building...?
- Whoa, the building!
- Oh, shit!
- Whoa!
Whoaaa. They're shooting
at the building!
- This is not a good idea.
- What?
This is not a good idea.
The building's unstable.
Listen, stop for a second. If wedon't do what we came to do,
then it doesn't matter.
We all die.
Right? That's your target.
Come on, man!
I don't even care if the
building collapses.
I'm havin' a
heart attack anyway.
The building is goin' over!
- Hang on! Grab somethin'!
- Take cover!
[shouting]
Keep your hands up!
[all shouting]
- It's OK! It stopped!
- Guys, look!
- Incoming, incoming!
- Everybody hide!
- Don't move!
- [shrieks]
Don't... move.
[Epps whispering] Go, go.
- Run!
- Cover fire!
Shoot the glass!
Jump out the window!
- Jump!
- No!
[shrieking]
[man] We're gonna die!
[Carly] Sam, I can't stop!
Shoot the glass!
[Carly] Sam!
[all grunting]
Sam!
No! No! Oh, no, no!
[screams]
Is everyone OK?!
- [Sam] You OK?
- What the hell was that?!
[panting] This evil thing's
lookin' at me!
What?!
It's even got an uglier
Decepticon with it!
[Epps] Evac!
[metallic shriek]
Find a way out!
The stairs are blocked!
We're trapped!
Hey, how do we get
out of here? Hey!
- Come on!
- No, no, no. Oh, Lord Jesus,
let me just get out of this
alive. I'll be a good man.
Just let me get out of this.
- [Epps] Whoa!
- [exclaims]
Move! We got to move!
Why do the Decepticons
always get the good shit?!
- We got to move!- We about to be eaten, people!
[screaming]
- [Carly screams]
- [yells]
Agghhhh! Hold on!
Give me your hand, come on!
Swing that way!
- I got her!
- Oh, my God!
I'm droppin' you
on the fire escape!
- Sam!
- Whoa! We got to move!
I'm coming for you!
[yells]
- [Wrecker] Optimus!
- Wreckers!
We're comin'!
Decepticons
around the world...
...launch the pillars.
[Wheelie] Agh, we are so lost!
[Brains] Always left out.
Ooh, ka-ching!
It's time to lay
down the law.
About to bring some hurt now.
[Sam] It's starting!
You see it?
Whoa! Look out!
Where are Sam and Carly?
Um....
We'll go this way.
I give you one thing to do.
One thing to do! And you drop
the ball on that?!
I ain't signed up for all this!
Got aliens blastin' at me,
runnin' around, chasin' me!
I'm duckin' through churches
and buildings and all that
kind of crap, man!
This is bullshit! I ain't
signed up for this, Epps!
I'm tryin' to keep it together.
Ooh, what a treat!
You and me alone!
Carly!
Come on, come on! Run!
OK, he's after me,
not you.
Wait, run! Run!
You can't hide, boy!
Come on, come on, run!
Oh, I just love it when your
little insect feet try to run!
- Sam!
- Run!
[yells]
Thought you were
working for us, boy?!
No! Sam!
My eye!
- [yelling]
- [cackling]
My eye! Agh! My eye!
Target the Decepticon!
Sam!
Lennox, you've got to save Sam!
- You've got to save him!
- What the hell's he doin'?
This better work!
[man] D-Bots! D-Bots!
[yelling]
[shrieking] I can't see!
I can't see!
- Sam!
- It's on my hand!
Grab the knife!
- I'm tryin'!
- Knife, knife,
knife, knife, knife!
Oh, God! The bomb's gonna...
You human scum!
- We got 20 seconds
on that bomb!
- What bomb?
See that bomb?
Go on, cut it, cut it!
I got it! How long do we have?!
I'm gonna kick you!
I'm gonna kill y...!
[both yelling]
- Well, he's dead.
- Uh-huh.
Hey, Bee's gonna run with the
rest of the Autobots
- and meet us
at the edge of the river.
- All right.
[Wheelie] Hey, it sucked me in!There was nothin' I could do!
- Uh-oh.
- Ugh.
This is a total clusterf...!
We gotta get across the river.
See that? Now she said
the control pillar was
in that first cupola.
- All right.
- Let's go! Move! Let's move!
[man on radio] Tomahawks are
inbound. ETA 20 minutes.
- I'm in the traffic cameras.
- [man] Four Autobots
are captured.
Oh, my God.
We're helpless.
Whatever's set to happen, with
those pulses getting faster,
- it's gonna happen soon.
- [man] No sign of Optimus.
How do we get
these bridges down?
Spread out.
Check in there.
Epps! Epps, been lookin' for
your ass. How you doin'?
Retirement is wack. Even worse,
we can't get across the river tothat building and the Autobots
are upstairs, surrounded.
Just pan the camera around,
all right?
All right, pan...
pan right. That's you.
All right, try getting
into the bridge control room.
[Mearing] What are they doing?
They are just standing there.
Hang on. Dutch see if you can
hack into the bridge.
Sir! SEALs are here.
Uh, it's a good days, boys!
What do you got?
Got a ten-man SEAL element,
sir, tasked with vectoring
in Tomahawks.
- How long?
- Fifteen.
You're my prisoners!
[Sideswipe] Take it easy.
We surrender.
[Ratchet] Get off me.
Get off me!
All right, you're gonna need
your 40 mic mics and your
frags. Go full auto.
The vibrations jack up
their circuits! Snipers,
shoot for the eyes.
All right, your target's
up on top of that building,
that cupola.
How doomed you are, Autobots.
You simply fail to understand
that the needs of the many
outweigh the needs of the few.
Activating the bridge.
[all howling]
They're happy
about somethin'.
We're in the heart
of their ship.
Let's give 'em a little ride.
Ho-ho! We gonna
screw this ship up!
It's a 128K
binary encryption code.
It's difficult.
But not for me.
I'm in. Bridge down.
The bridge is comin' down!
Someone's watchin' over us!
Come on, let's go!
"Pleasure working
with you, Seymour"...
...I believe you're
supposed to say.
- Good job, Dutch.
- Danke schoen.
Get off me!
Hurry! They're
triggering the pillars!
Prisoners?
You're keeping prisoners?
Yes.
You need to teach them
about respect.
This was all business,
but now it's personal.
Do you understand me?
[Chuckles] I understand.
No prisoners. Only trophies.
Bee... I think they're
going to kill us.
- You. Your time is up.
- Wait, wait, wait!
We surrendered!
We're your prisoners.
- Move it!
- Can't we talk this out?
We're all a bunch of good chaps!I mean, you know...
[grunts]
Why did you...? Agh!
[cackling]
Goodbye, my old friend.
You're mine now.
- Get off me!
- I gotta help him.
What? What are you doing?
- Sam, you can't help him.
Sam!
Turn around!
We gave 'em a hell of a run.
[Wheelie] We did it,
Brains, we did it!
Rip this ship apart!
- We had a nice run,
Brains, you and me.
- Yeah, we gonna die.
Come on. Whoa, whoa, whoa!OK, baby! You all come with us!
Go! You guys, follow
that ground team! Go!
- Move, move, move!
- Epps, third floor!
We're goin' to 45!
All right, give me
two snipers right here!
All right, dock up!
We jump in three minutes!
Set up shop right here.
All right, set up.
I'm downstairs. And we got
five targets and Shockwave
right below us.
Stand by to jump!
All right, let's go!
Get ready, get ready.
Go!
Snipers, take out their eyes.
All right, demo team,
let's crank steel.
Turning steel!
[yelling]
Don't fire till I tell you!
Go!
All right, good job, kid!
Fire!
- We got him!
- Yeah!
He's on the run!
Autobots, attack!
Mortar that bridge!
It's our world now!
Commence transport!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[both yelling]
Optimus!
You die! Yah!
No!
Get down here, Sentinel!
Optimus...
you forget your place!
I bring you Cybertron.
Your home.
And still you choose humanity.
You were the one who taught me
freedom is everyone's right.
[yelling]
I will retrigger
that pillar!
Then you'll have to
go through me!
OK, I got to try to help.
- Don't, don't, don't...
- I have to. You're gonna
stay here. Stop.
- You're gonna be fine.
OK? I promise.
- Promise? Promise?
OK? I got to get
to that pillar.
[Sentinel] Charge the pillar!
We got Autobots!
Reinforcements! Decepticon
ships, fire at Optimus!
We're takin' effective fire!
I need those Tomahawks
on scene now!
[man] First wave inbound.
We got to cover for Optimus!
Decepticons!
Trigger the pillar!
Restart that pillar!
Trigger the pillars.
I can't hold them!
The ships have us pinned!
No!
[man] Inbound, ten seconds!
Danger close!
Mark, Lima,
Echo, Echo, 14250!
- Positive surface contact.
- [man] Target ID.
Target acquired.
Dylan! Wait!
- No!
- [grunts]
Shit! Dylan!
Stop! Stop!
No! You can't do this! OK?
There's only one future for me.
Cybertron...
You are saved. At last.
Oh, have you come
to surrender?
- Was it all worth it?
- Obviously.
All your work
to bring Sentinel back
and now, clearly,
he has all the power.
It's actually almost tragic.
You dare lecture me, slave?
Your Decepticons finally
conquering this planet,
and yet their leader
won't be you!
It will be me!
It will always be me.
And any minute now...
...you'll be nothing...
...but Sentinel's bitch.
Rocket!
Yeah!
You chose sides?
You chose wrong!
Always the bravest of us!
But you could never
make the hard decisions!
Our planet will survive! Ha!
No!
[Sentinel] We were gods once.
All of us! But here...
Please!
...there will
only be one!
This is my planet!
I just saved
a whole other world.
You think you're a hero? Huh?
You think you're a hero?!
No. I'm just a messenger.
[shouts]
[Lennox] The pillar's
still connected!
[Epps] Guys, bring it up!
- Bee!
- Get through, get through!
- Let's do this!
- Pillar's still connected!
[Wrecker] Rip that pillar down!
Now...
we need a truce.
All I want is
to be back in charge.
Besides...
who would you be
without me, Prime?
Time to find out.
Optimus, all I ever wanted
was the survival of our race.
You must see why
I had to betray you.
You didn't betray me.
You betrayed yourself.
No, Optimus!
Sam.
I love you.
You're the only thing I need inthis world and I'll do anythingto make it up to you, I promise.
I'm gonna hold you
to that.
- Just never let me go.
- Promise.
[Carly] Ooh, rings.
[Bee hums wedding march]
I love this car.
Yeah, but you gotta
slow it down.
You got to slow
way down, OK?
Well, I'm just tryin'
to help out.
[Optimus] In any war...
...there are calms
between storms.
You fought bravely.
[Optimus] There will be
days when we lose faith.
Days when our allies
turn against us.
But the day will never come
that we forsake this planet...
...and its people.
[♪ Linkin Park: "Iridescent"]
♪ Do you feel cold
and lost in desperation ♪
♪ You build up
all the failures ♪
♪ All you've known
Oh!
That's what I call the start
of a beautiful future.
- [laughs]
- Arrest him.
- It was worth it!
- Get him out of here!
I'll go to jail for love!
I don't care!
Go ahead, take me in!
I want to go in! Let's go in!
- I have the best lawyer.
- Come on, Charlotte,
take me in right now!
♪ Do you feel cold
♪ And lost in desperation
♪ You build up
all the failures ♪
♪ All you've known
♪ Remember all the sadness
♪ and frustration
♪ And let it go
♪ Let it go
[♪ Paramore: "Monster"]
♪ You were my conscience
♪ So solid
now you're like water ♪
♪ And we started drowning
♪ Not like we'd
sink any farther ♪
♪ But I let my heart go
♪ It's somewhere down
at the bottom ♪
♪ But I'll get a new one
♪ And come back for the hope
that you've stolen ♪
♪ I'll stop the whole world
♪ From turning into a monster
♪ And eating us alive
♪ Don't you ever wonder
♪ How we survive
♪ Well now that you're gone
♪ The world is ours
♪ I'm only human
♪ I've got a skeleton in me
♪ But I'm not the villain
♪ Despite what you're
always preaching ♪
♪ Call me a traitor
♪ I'm just collecting
your victims ♪
♪ And they're
getting stronger ♪
♪ I hear them calling.
♪ Calling
♪ I'll stop the whole world
♪ From turning into a monster
♪ And eating us alive
♪ Don't you ever wonder
♪ How we survive
♪ Well now that you're gone
♪ The world
♪ I'll stop the whole world
♪ From turning into a monster
♪ And eating us alive
♪ Don't you ever wonder
♪ How we survive
♪ Well now that you're gone
♪ The world is ours
[♪ Biffy Clyro:
"Many of Horror"]
♪ You say, "I love you boy"
♪ But I know you lie
♪ 'Cause when
my back is turned ♪
♪ My bruises shine
♪ Our broken fairytale
♪ So hard to hide
♪ I still believe
♪ It's you and me
'til the end of time ♪
♪ When we collide
we come together ♪
♪ If we don't
we'll always be apart ♪
♪ I'll take a bruise
I know you're worth it ♪
♪ When you hit me
hit me hard ♪
♪ 'Cause you said love
♪ Was letting us
go against what ♪
♪ Our future is for
♪ Many of horror
♪ When we collide
we come together ♪
♪ If we don't
we'll always be apart ♪
♪ I'll take a bruise
I know you're worth it ♪
♪ When you hit me
hit me hard ♪