They ave broken through the front lines!
I have lost contact with the capital!
There is too many of them!
Stand fast!
Finish them!
Where is B-127?
Sorry I am late. I hit a little traffic.
Get down! Incoming!
Optimus.
Decepticons,
attack!
Autobots, fall back!
Get to the tower!
Destroy the launch pad!
Let none escape!
Cybertron has fallen.
Get to the escape pods.
There are other Autobots
scattered across the galaxy.
We must reach them
if we hope to survive.
Optimus, this is our home.
We have to fight for it.
We will fight on.
But we must find refuge first.
I found a planet that's well hidden.
Earth.
You will travel there
and establish a base for us.
Once we have gathered the others,
we will join you.
You must protect the planet.
If the Decepticons find it,
then our people are truly finished.
Now go!
Good luck, soldier.
I will buy you some time.
No!
Ok, ok!
I am dead already, man!
Not just you.
Being the overachiever that you are,
you managed to get your
whole squad killed, Danny.
Bravo.
Come on, man. Those things sting.
What things? These things?
You know, I would not know.
I have not been hit yet.
Ok, you know what?
That's too close man.
You could have taken out an eye.
I got a date tonight man.
This ain't sexy!
You are right. I am sorry.
That one was on me.
That's a malfunctioning trigger.
This weapon is just faulty.
Someone is going to get a talking to...
Man, would you stop?
Alright just, just stop.
I should have let you die in Grenada.
If you did, we would not be able
to come to the forest,
run around and play
these awesome games.
Exactly.
I hate you.
Man, that hurts.
Because I love you.
But you refuse to let it in
because you got intimacy issues.
A therapist will probably tell you,
you were not hugged enough as a kid.
Look man.
Danny, I know I look stupid but...
Hey yo, take cover!
Danny.
You ok?
Yeah man.
This is Agent Jack Burns.
I need medical up here now.
We have a projectile strike
in the northwest corner
of the training course.
Multiple injuries.
And would someone please explain to me
why you dropped napalm on your own guys!
Negative.
There are no live fire drills
in the northwest sector.
What the hell hit us, then?
Target on your right!
I need all of you to fan out
and track that thing down now!
Drive!
There!
What the hell?
Take it down!
Get down there now
and flush that thing out!
There it is!
Target has been located sir.
Light it up!
Damn it!
Oh, no.
It's going for the mine! Cut it off!
Move, move!
Please.
This is a mistake.
Stay cool. Hold your fire.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
Who called in the Air Force?
That's not the Air Force.
Run.
Did you think you could hide?
Now you will die screaming.
Like your friends!
Tell me where your friends are hiding.
I will never talk.
Is that right?
Then let's make it official.
B-127...
As a member of the Autobot resistance,
you are a traitor to Cybertron
and are hereby sentenced
to death.
No!
Shut up.
Morning Dad.
No!
Don't tickle.
Caught.
Gross, Ron.
Excuse me.
What? Are those your diving trophies?
Taking up too much space in my room.
You are gonna regret doing that.
Where is breakfast?
Breakfast is conveniently located
in the cupboards and the fridge.
Try to help out...
Yeah.
A little.
Since I am such a big kid now,
making my own breakfast
and what have you,
you know how I could be,
an even bigger help around here Mom?
If I had a car.
Charlie.
What do you know,
it's my birthday tomorrow,
perfect timing for a large cash gift.
You know 500 bucks is really
all I need to finish the Corvette.
I don't have 500 bucks.
You know how much nurses make.
Half as much as doctors
for twice the work, right?
Tell you what kiddo...
I got another job interview tomorrow.
If all goes well,
I will have you swimming in car parts.
I prefer cash, Ron.
Don't be rude. Feed the dog.
Conan is Otis's dog. Make him do it.
What?
You look so grown up in your karate suit.
My baby boy is becoming a man.
Shoot, I am gonna be late.
Can you drop your brother at karate
on your way to work, please?
I could if I had a car.
Just let him follow you on your
bike so nobody abducts him.
Abducts him?
You just said he's a grown man now.
If anyone tries anything,
I will rupture their freaking spleen.
That's two for you guys.
Thanks bro.
Alright. Have a good one.
Eat safe.
Excuse me. Hi.
We have never actually met...
Sorry, I can't right now.
Yeah.
Ok.
Hey, hot dog girl!
Oh, my God!
I am so sorry.
Oh, God.
Someone is getting fired.
If I had to wear that,
I would pray to be fired.
Good one Tina.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey Uncle Hank.
Are you still working on that damn car?
You still working on that damn personality?
What have you got for me?
Whatever you want.
Russians are gonna blow us
all to hell anyway.
That's the spirit.
Hey kid.
Hand me the three-eighths, would you?
You working on the carburetor?
You need the half-inch.
I said the three...
Thanks kid.
Yep.
Where is Optimus Prime?
He survived the fall of Cybertron.
And no rebellion is truly dead
until the leader is vanquished.
So where is he?
My name is Cliffjumper,
lieutenant in the Autobot resistance.
My safe return will be considered...
Wrong answer.
We know he is planning
to establish a base.
Tell us where it is
and we will let you live.
My name is Cliffjumper, lieutenant...
♪ Sometimes you want to go... ♪
No.
That's B-127's signal.
Can you trace it?
Already did.
If you won't tell us where Prime is,
perhaps your young friend will.
Never.
You are a brave warrior.
You deserve a better death.
But then again...
Set course for Earth.
I will give you thirty bucks for all of it.
I can get twice that much
for the coil alone.
From who?
I am the only one that comes in here.
I don't even know how you are still open.
Just take it. Go. Go.
My show is on.
Hey, where did you get that Beetle?
I swear to God, ever since they
put up that dumb-ass tower,
I can't get a signal to watch my shows.
I have got to see what happens
to Alf this week.
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Damn it.
I give up.
I can't do this without you.
Nice to meet you.
Interested in a new Buick?
Nice try.
Alright, I touched. But I didn't eat.
And I am supposed to believe
one of these steaks
just got up and walked away on its own?
I have seen stranger.
No dinner for you tonight.
But I am starved!
I have been fasting since lunch!
Well, I did eat that pumpkin.
Happy birthday.
I miss you Dad.
I think it's too low honey.
No. No. I think it goes to that button.
Yeah?
Yeah. I don't...
know about...
Fix it.
Hey.
Good morning, birthday girl!
Hi.
You look...
Nice.
Happy birthday, baby.
I love you. Come on, open your present.
I am gonna be late for work.
Thanks Mom.
Helmet with...
Daffodils.
So, I keep hearing
about people on mopeds getting
run over and their brains smashed in.
You got to wear this from now on.
I don't care if it's not the law.
It's our law.
Plus, look how cute it is.
Yeah.
Happy birthday.
I actually got you a little gift too Charlie.
I mean it's small, but...
it's from the heart.
A smile is a powerful thing.
It releases endorphins.
It says to the world,
I am fun and approachable.
You know, there is a whole chapter in here
about how people who smile more often,
actually have more friends.
That's unbelievable.
I really think it's gonna
change your whole outlook
if you smile more often.
I want the Beetle.
What?
The yellow Beetle, I want it.
I will make you a deal.
If I get that thing started, it's mine.
That's no deal.
That's just you taking my car.
If I get it started, I keep it and
I work here every day for a year.
I will scrub the grease off the floors, ok?
I will pick up and organize
every scrap of paper in this place.
I will even detail your horrible,
disgusting toilets.
Please. It's my birthday.
Sorry, no deal.
Because we ain't hiring.
It's yours kid.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
And my toilets are gorgeous.
Oh, God, please.
Come on.
Oh, my...
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, thank you so much!
I love you!
That thing ain't even safe to drive.
It's a deathtrap.
She is happy though.
Man.
Looks amazing.
What?
Oh, my God.
Charlie, what was that noise?
Nothing! I am fine.
Mom, you should go back to bed.
Everything is fine.
What the hell is that?
It's...
What is that car doing in our garage?
Car?
That ca... car?
Is my car.
Uncle Hank gave it to me.
It runs. Yeah.
Those are not safe.
I wish you would have told me
before you brought it home.
Ok. Sorry.
I am in the middle of some stuff,
Mom.
Ok, I will get out of your hair but...
Tell me things, sometime.
Ok.
I am your mother.
Good night.
It really runs?
Yeah, it really...
it really runs.
Cool.
You still in there?
Ok.
A little jumpy. I am sorry.
Hi.
Oh, God, are you...
Do you speak?
I won't hurt you.
Can you understand me?
What are you?
Where did you come from?
Ok. It's ok.
You like my shirt?
You a metal fan?
No, wait...
Oh, who? Me?
Who am I?
I am...
Charlie.
Charlie Watson.
I am... 18.
Today.
Actually, it's my birthday today.
What's your name?
You don't, you don't know
or you don't have a name?
You sound like a little bumblebee.
I am gonna call you that from now on.
Bumblebee.
Matches your outfit, too.
I want a divorce, Roy!
Come on Amber.
Give me one good reason.
You tried to sleep with my sister!
Unsuccessfully!
Yeah, you are unsuccessful at everything.
That down payment was for a house.
You bought a car.
How stupid are you Roy?
We don't need a car. God!
Now, just settle down for one second just...
hear me out.
What the hell is that?
What?
Oh, God, Roy,
that thing is coming right for us!
No, no, no, no, no...
Not my car. Not my car.
Please, God, no, not my car!
Oh, thank God, my car.
Yeah, I am ok.
That's good, baby. That's good.
Run. Run!
God!
Is that my car?
Hello...
Jeez!
Earth.
Roy!
How underwhelming.
The indigenous life is even more
primitive than I expected.
Hey...
I like the way they pop.
Focus, comrade.
B-127's distress signal
came from the western coast
of this continent.
For now,
we head west.
When do they start
letting you use nun-chucks?
I don't know, but I hope soon.
Morning! See you guys later.
Where you off to so fast?
Nowhere. Have a nice day.
Morning Bumble...
Bee?
Bee, where are you?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Bee?
Where did you go?
Otis!
Have you seen my car?
Unfortunately, yes.
No, have you seen my car today?
It was in the garage. Someone stole it!
No, idiot.
Mom took it.
She had to bring Conan to the vet
because he swallowed like
a rubber glove or something
and Ron needed the station wagon.
Thank God.
Wait.
Hi. Excuse me. It's me again.
We never officially met but...
Yeah, I can't right now. Sorry.
Nope. Yep.
Ok. Ok.
I know buddy. Hang in there.
You can't eat everything you see.
Just let this be a good life lesson for you.
Oh, my God. Stop it! Don't do that!
Bee, no!
Mom?
Jesus! Charlie, what are you doing?
Mom, you got to pull over.
What the hell is going on?
Just pull the car over.
Ok, ok.
Alright.
Would you put that robot junk away?
What are you thinking?
You almost gave me a heart attack.
I thought I was being carjacked.
I am taking the dog to the vet.
I can't believe you would
take him without me.
Mom, I am so worried about him!
He's my dog too, you know.
What happened to Conan being Otis's dog?
Mom,
you are being hysterical, ok?
You should not be driving
in such an emotional state.
I know how you get during emergencies.
I am a nurse.
Not of animals.
Ok. I am happy for you to drive.
You were not wearing your helmet,
by the way.
I saw that.
Oh, shoot.
Keep it together, Bee.
Sir?
Sir.
I thought you would want
to see this immediately.
They sure?
Yes sir.
Two of them just made contact in Texas.
Intel says they are heading west fast.
Saddle up Simmons.
We are going to Texas.
Ok, Bee.
We need to go over a few things.
Ok. We are all clear.
Alright. I am re-thinking the beach.
I am good.
No I am good, thanks.
People can be terrible about things
they don't understand.
If they find you, they will probably
lock you up in a lab somewhere
and cut you into tiny little pieces.
It will be...
bad, trust me.
The only person you can show
yourself around is me,
ok?
So let's practice. You ready?
If you see anyone besides me,
what do you do?
Great. Perfect.
Come back now.
Ok, so let's say we are driving,
alright we are driving and all of a sudden...
Oh, shoot! Somebody is here, hide!
Hide Bee, hide!
You serious?
Bee, it's too late. You are already dead.
It's alright.
That's why we are practicing.
You will get it.
Fox-2 on approach.
Non-biologicals are inbound.
The goal sir, should be
to communicate with them.
First contact with an alien species.
I have spent my whole life
waiting for this moment.
If they make one wrong move,
we put them down.
The humans are multiplying.
Please let me kill them.
Not yet.
B-127's signal has gone silent.
I have an idea.
Listen up! I am Agent Burns and this is...
Dr. Powell.
We currently have 100 guns,
pointed right at your head!
So state your business.
People of Earth,
we are Decepticon peacekeepers
patrolling the galaxy.
What are you doing?
This is humiliating.
We believe a dangerous
criminal from our world
is hiding somewhere on yours.
How is it you think we can help?
We need your eyes.
Wait.
You want access to our satellites?
Our scanners' range is limited.
Your infrastructure is, primitive.
But combined,
they could be quite powerful.
No way! Out of the question!
We have a common enemy, Agent Burns.
There is a war raging on our planet.
If B-127 isn't found,
that war may find its way here.
Perhaps...
We can find a way to help one another.
We will talk it over with our superiors.
In the meantime,
if you could follow us.
Very well, friend Powell.
Take us to your leader.
Must suck being cooped up
in a VW all day?
Is there anyone that can help you?
Do you have a family?
You know like a...
mom, dad, siblings?
You all love each other?
Or drive each other,
crazy and you can't wait to get
away and start a whole new life.
Do you want me to see if I can fix it?
I will be gentle, I promise.
You lay down, ok?
Hold still.
I think maybe there is something...
B-127,
I pray this message finds you.
Our war rages on.
Planet Earth...
survival...
Ravage, eject!
Your mission...
soldier...
I...
Are you ok?
Who was that?
That voice said something about a war.
Do you remember anything?
Is the VW Beetle,
some kind of...
disguise?
Are you hiding from something?
Are you scared?
It's broken.
It's ok.
I think I can help.
Let's go home.
And a basket case,
a princess...
And a criminal.
Alright, I am almost done.
Does that answer your question?
No way. Are you actually watching it?
Don't you forget about me
Don't, don't, don't...
You can pop in another one if you want.
Come on, sweetie!
You got this Charlie girl!
Alright, Charlie girl!
Hello, Brighton Falls.
This is Charlie Watson,
future Olympic gold medalist.
That was so perfect.
Thanks Dad.
How do you feel?
You are amazing...
No, no, why would you play this?
Sorry. I just...
I finished.
Let's see if we got something.
Ok.
Alright.
Oh, my God, yes!
It worked!
Look at you go.
You got some moves.
You know Bee, music can help
you say what you are feeling.
You are gonna love this.
It's brand new.
♪ Girlfriend in a coma, ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
♪ it's serious... ♪
Not a Smiths fan.
Ok.
Here.
Try this.
♪ Never gonna give you up... ♪
Fine.
Ok, where is my Stevie Nicks?
Joan Jett and the Blackhearts.
Stones.
Hey, hey, please don't touch those.
Please.
They belonged to my dad.
Do you want to hear it?
We used to listen to this
while we would work on the Corvette.
It was his favorite.
He used to say it would make
the car feel better.
We used to work on this car
every weekend together.
It was our thing.
That tape...
That was the last time I saw him.
He died of a heart attack.
I never got to say goodbye.
You know,
I always thought if I could just...
finish fixing this car...
If I could just get it to start up again,
he would hear me.
He would hear me.
I say this with all due respect.
Have you lost your damn mind?
That was with all due respect?
The man is got a point Doctor.
Our satellite network is at the forefront
of our national defense.
Sir, please.
It could be a once
in a lifetime opportunity.
Can you imagine the advances an alliance
with these creatures might bring?
I imagine the advances.
An advance on Washington.
New York. An advance on Chicago!
That's not gonna happen.
They literally call themselves...
Decepticons.
That doesn't set off any red flags?
Enough!
From both of you.
Sir.
We are talking about,
the most advanced
robotic system ever seen.
If we tell them no...
they will just take their technology
to the Russians instead.
Do you really want to go down in history
as the man who cost us the Cold War?
Fine.
We will help them find their fugitive.
And when it's done,
you can do all the experiments you want.
Yes sir.
Gentle...
Rob... Robots.
Welcome to Sector 7.
How kind of you to finally allow us in.
We are very happy to have
you here,
as friends.
Thank you, friend Powell.
My superior has agreed to grant you
limited access to our satellites.
In addition,
you are welcome to use...
all of our technology here.
It's the largest super-array
of Crays on Earth.
We thank you for your hospitality.
Tell me, those vocal
communication devices you use,
do they function worldwide?
The telephones?
Yes, why?
You got to pick a station, man.
I know there is a lot of choices.
You want to go on a date with me, maybe?
Ok.
What are you trying to do?
Here we go. Here we go.
You are not a nerd. You are not a nerd.
Just ok, you are a nerd,
but just don't let her see that you are nerdy.
Excuse me. Sorry to barge in, I just...
Do you just...
No, no, it's fine!
Just, just you know...
Just sit down, sit down, please.
Don't scream, ok?
What is that?
It's ok, ok?
Just breathe. Breathe.
First of all, hi.
Hi.
I am Charlie.
I am Memo, hi.
Hi, Memo.
It's nice to meet you.
Pleasure... Pleasure...
Look, I know what you saw
was a little crazy.
I can explain.
Yeah, I can't explain.
But here is the deal.
If you tell anyone what you just saw,
I am gonna have to run
you over with my car.
Jeez.
That was...
I don't mean that in a mean way. Ok?
What I am saying
is no one,
can know what you just saw, ok?
You promise?
Yeah.
Ok.
Bumblebee, you can...
you can come out now.
What?
It's...
He.
He is been going up and down on that dial
all day today and I don't know why?
Hey, check out his reflexes.
What?
Oh, God!
Yo, give me your shirt.
Give me your shirt.
You mean, you mean
the shirt that I am wearing?
Yes, yes! Come on.
I will give it back to you.
Ok.
Come on! Give me your shirt!
Alright.
Wait, wait, wait! Hey, no, no!
You-you-you don't need to do this.
Yes I do.
No.
But you-you know...
Come here!
No, I-I-I get it.
Come on!
I get it!
Sorry.
I know I promised you but,
yeah you are not getting that back.
It's incredible!
They are combining
our technology seamlessly.
Satellites, phones, computers.
They are creating an interconnected
web of information.
Volumes of data at their fingertips.
It's revolutionary.
He is a weird guy.
You ever notice that about Powell?
They are tracking fluctuations
in Energon levels.
It's like a heat signature
specific to their species.
It's astonishing.
It's beautiful. It's...
Hello? Hello?
You have given them our satellites,
our comms, God knows what else.
Yet...
in the space of a day
they ave given us a way
to not only hunt down B-127,
but all of them.
Let them finish what they are doing.
Let them find B-127.
And then I will give you permission
to destroy them all.
Use them for spare parts.
Sir, yes sir.
So you have no idea where he came from?
No idea.
You thought about calling the cops?
What are they gonna do Memo?
They are just...
gonna send him away to a lab
and do weird science experiments on him.
♪ Weird Science! ♪
♪ Plastic tubes and pots and pans... ♪
You are getting pretty good
with that radio dial, Bee.
Yeah, D.J. Bumble in the house!
I can't live without my radio
Is that why you are always
messing with the dial?
You are trying to teach yourself
how to talk, are not you?
Walk like a man, talk like a man...
No way.
Oh, my God, Bee, you are a genius!
You are an actual genius!
What is going on here?
That's Jim from sixth period.
He said he was busy this week.
You want to check it out?
This is pretty cool.
Ok.
Bee, we will be right back.
Don't do anything crazy.
Hey everybody, come watch!
Tripp is gonna jump!
You are off your nut.
What's going on over there?
Don't do it dude, you are crazy.
Come on, it's not that big a jump.
God, is that Tripp Summers?
You know, you know Tripp?
I mean, yeah.
I-I spilled a gallon of lemonade on him once.
Doesn't anyone have the balls
to jump off this thing with me?
A brave volunteer.
I-I... See, I didn't...
I didn't do that.
I didn't actually...
♪ You got the touch ♪
♪ You got the power ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Hey, I know you.
No, sorry about that. It...
You were on the dive team
with my little sister.
I saw you win state a couple years ago.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This just got a whole lot more interesting.
We have a championship
high-diver on our hands!
Yeah I actually, I don't, I don't...
I don't do it anymore.
Don't worry. I won't make you go first.
Watch it!
Yeah, Tripp!
Yeah!
Dive Girl!
You better not back out on me.
You guys, she is gonna do it!
She is gonna do it!
Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive!
Dive! Dive!
Come on!
Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive!
You got this, Charlie girl!
Where you going?
What, are you scared?
You ok?
Let's just go.
What a loser!
Thought you said you were
on the diving team.
I think she is gonna cry in her car.
Where you going sweetie?
What happened out there?
That was your big moment to look cool.
What's your damage, Tina?
Is that the churro guy?
Where is your hairnet dude?
It's in the garbage, Einstein.
You throw them away after each use.
For sanitary purposes, obviously but...
This car is an embarrassment.
You should have your dad,
buy you a better one.
Oh, wait...
Sorry.
You ok?
I am fine.
They are idiots.
But I think I know something
that will make you feel better.
What?
Revenge.
I don't want revenge.
I do.
What about you Bee?
Want some revenge?
I just want...
Revenge!
I am mad
Come on. I got an idea.
This is Tina's house.
And this, it's toilet paper.
You use it for when you...
Here just take a roll.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, you have got...
You got to throw it.
Like this.
Not bad.
Not... Yeah...
Ok, look, Bee, you be our egg man.
Right? Yeah. So...
Love that.
You see these right here?
You grab one of these, like so.
And that right there, that's your target.
That's right.
Alright? Just throw it like this.
I think we could just hand it to him...
He could maybe, yeah and then...
Bee, what are...
What...
Don't hurt me.
Oh, my God...
Oh, shit!
Hide, hide, hide.
Hide!
Stay...
Ok!
Ok. Ok.
Hide, Bee!
Go, go, go!
Mom!
That was...
insane!
My heart right now is going crazy.
Oh, God.
Stop the car, please.
Bee, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
♪ I can't drive 55! ♪
Bumblebee!
Oh, my God!
♪ I can't drive 55! ♪
Oh, my God, we are committing a felony!
♪ When I drive that slow, ♪
♪ you know it's hard to steer ♪
We got a yellow vehicle,
driving its damn self
through the Pico Tunnel.
♪ We are gonna throw your ass ♪
♪ in the city joint ♪
♪ Looked me in the eye said ♪
♪ You get my point? ♪
♪ I said yeah! Oh, yeah! ♪
Good night.
Good night Bee.
Morning, buddy.
I got to go to work, ok?
Bee. Listen to me.
You need to stay in this garage.
Ok? After what happened last night,
I am pretty sure
the cops are looking for you,
and...
you don't exactly blend in.
I will be back, alright?
Here.
You can have my Pop-Tart.
I need you to go to the frozen
banana stand and steal some sticks.
We are out of sticks.
Can't we just sell the hot dogs
without the sticks?
No.
What's happening here?
We got a hit, I think.
Where is that location?
Near San Francisco.
A coastal town named Brighton Falls.
You have a personal call.
Hello?
Charlie, Charlie hey, it's-it's Memo.
You got to come home right now.
It's bad. It's really, really bad.
Where is Bumblebee?
Bumblebee,
what have you done?
What were you thinking? What...
I told you to hide in the garage!
Great.
Helpful shame spiral Bee.
I am not mad, ok? This is...
all my fault.
I never should have left you.
Hey, ok, maybe don't transform all the way?
We have still got to get you
through the door.
Come on, buddy.
It's ok.
I am so screwed.
And now you are crippled for life.
Honey, watch the hair.
Go. Now. But be quiet.
Mom, wait!
Oh, my God!
Mom...
What happened?
I am sorry. This is all my fault.
What'd you do to my TV?
Look, Mom, I can explain.
We will talk about this
we will talk about this later, alright?
Now, I have to go.
Are you kidding me?
No. You are not going anywhere.
It's about my car. It's really important.
About your car?
That you spend all day and night shut
in that garage,
doing God-knows-what with?
Mom, I can't.
I really can't right now.
Oh, no,
you really can, Charlie.
You really can.
I have had it!
Your attitude, your always sulking around.
You brought home that piece of crap
without even asking me!
Everyone in this family
is trying to be happy,
and all you want to do
is make things harder.
You know Mom,
just because you have moved on
and you are happy with your
new life, doesn't mean I have!
You have found a replacement for my dad
and I have not, ok, and I never will!
So I am sorry if that makes things harder,
but in ten months from now you...
you won't even have to deal with me!
Charlie!
Hey, you ok?
Yeah.
I just feel like ever since my dad died,
I have become this drain on everyone,
and I hate it.
It's like everybody expects me
to act like nothing ever happened and they...
it's impossible to do that.
About your dad I am...
I am really sorry.
Thanks.
You know there is...
there is this quote that I like.
The darkest nights produce
the brightest stars.
That's nice.
My mom got it from Weight Watchers.
Get out and move away from the vehicle.
Stay cool Bee.
What's going on?
Hey!
Come on! Come on!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
Weapons now! Take it down!
Run!
No, don't run. Do not run!
She ran.
Please tell me they are on our side.
No more running.
No more hiding.
B-127,
you are a traitor and a coward.
Tell us where Optimus Prime is hiding.
Bee, look out!
Why isn't he fighting back?
Why don't you fight?
Leave him alone! Please!
Again.
Hit it again!
Stop! Stop it!
Your daughter stole government
property, Mrs. Watson.
She is been having trouble adjusting but...
we had no idea it was this serious.
I...
Charlie. Honey.
I didn't steal anything,
and he doesn't belong to them.
He?
Ma'am.
I can assure you that it,
is an it.
It is a highly dangerous war machine.
No, he isn't, ok Mom?
He is not some war machine.
I...
I don't know what he is, but...
He is my friend.
Ma'am, your daughter had
a traumatic experience today.
Maybe doesn't understand
everything she has seen.
She is disoriented.
No, I am fine, Mom.
I am completely fine, ok?
You have to believe me, please.
I didn't steal anything!
Stop! Just go to your room.
When I was going through puberty,
I stole things too.
Stole a box of Mallomars once.
Yeah we know.
Boom.
Caught you.
Mom is gonna love this.
Alright, look Otis,
you need to go home and...
Mom!
No, Otis, stop it!
Why would you do that?
Let go of me!
You are touching my buttocks!
Look. I will tell you a secret
if you shut up.
Ok, so...
this is my...
room.
Just make yourself at home.
These are actually my sister's stuff.
She likes playing pranks,
like putting her stuff over here.
Can I sit down?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Residents of Brighton Falls
have been witness
to an unusual sight this evening.
Armed Forces pouring into town
as part of what we are told
is a routine military exercise
setting up camp at our own
McKinnon Air Base.
If Bumblebee is still alive,
that's where they are keeping him.
We have to go.
We have to try and save him.
Count me in. I will take point.
No, you won't.
Come on.
No, Otis.
But I can help. Master Larry says I...
I need someone here.
I need someone reliable,
to make sure that
Mom and Ron don't know that I am gone.
I am someone reliable.
Hell, yeah, you are.
Good luck.
You too.
Get over here.
Let's do this.
Tell us where Optimus Prime
and the rebels are hiding,
and we can end this war.
Talk!
Who is Optimus Prime?
This doesn't concern you, human Powell.
Last chance.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
It's a terrible idea,
but I have got to try it.
You can't get... Well, stop...
How would you know the power was off?
I didn't. Let's go.
Can I?
His memory cells are fried.
Finish him.
We will fight on.
Regroup, rebuild, and retake our home.
But we must find refuge first.
You will travel to Earth.
Once we have gathered the others,
we will join you.
You must protect the planet.
If the Decepticons find it,
then our people are truly finished.
Stay safe, soldier.
I am coming.
Prime is coming here?
They are all coming here.
This is our chance to wipe out
the Autobot resistance for good.
We will burn the whole planet to cinders.
We must get word to Cybertron immediately.
This is Burns.
Tell them to bring an army.
Burns, we made a terrible mistake.
Powell?
And thanks to our human allies,
I know just how to get the message home.
They are using our satellites.
They are calling an army.
They are gonna kill us all.
Thank you for your hospitality,
friend Powell.
He is all yours.
No.
Powell?
You have to stop them!
Powell!
Where is the Krazy Glue?
What, did she cut the wire to the TV?
Ron.
Charlie!
Nice! Reel-to-reel still works.
Where is your sister?
Charlie's fallen ill and must stay in her
bedroom for the rest of the evening.
She wishes not to be troubled.
Keep clear of her chambers.
What?
Charlie has fallen ill
and must stay in her bedroom
for the rest of the evening.
She wishes not to...
Otis!
Are you on drugs?
No, no. Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom.
Please stop. Stop!
Charlie!
Mom, there is no reason to go...
Where is she?
Mom, stop!
Quit it, Otis.
Where is she?
Otis?
I found a tower to transmit our message.
It's close.
B-127.
I almost forgot.
I didn't.
No! Don't shoot!
No!
Bee!
Talk to me Bee, talk to me.
I can fix this.
Charlie.
You got to wake up Bee.
You got to wake up.
Please.
Charlie, we got to go.
Charlie.
The gun.
What?
The electric gun. Get it.
I can fix you.
Come on, Bee.
Come back to me.
Come on, give me the other one.
Bee, come on.
I can't lose you too, Bee.
Please, Bee!
I am sorry.
Oh, my God.
Come on Bee,
we have got to get you out of here.
Charlie,
there is like a million guys out there!
We got to move now.
Come on Bee, you have got to get up.
Can you get up?
There is a door in my way.
Move! Move! Move!
They ave got bombs!
We got to go.
Bee come on.
Charlie!
You have got to get up, come on.
Three.
Charlie!
Two.
Come on.
One.
Charlie!
Come on.
Memo?
Memo, wake up.
Easy.
Hold your fire!
Get the kid out of here.
Memo! Wake up, Memo!
Come on, kid.
Hey! No!
Bee!
Run!
Let go of me!
You need to get away from that thing.
No!
Take it down!
No, stop!
Stop it!
Contain it and dismantle it!
Strip it down to parts!
Leave him alone!
You don't understand.
Fight back, Bee!
Bee!
Kid, stop! It's a machine!
He is more human than you will ever be!
That is enough!
Oh, shit.
Open fire!
Fall back! Take cover!
Bee!
Bee, stop!
You remember, don't you?
They are coming back.
Oh, God.
Are you ok?
Yeah. Yeah, I am fine.
We, we need to get out of here.
We have got to get you someplace safe.
Bee stop. They will kill you!
If the Decepticons find Earth,
then our people are truly finished.
Ok.
Then we fight.
Let's go, get in.
Go on. I will buy you
some time with these guys.
You just kiss me?
On the cheek.
Still counts.
Halt!
Stop.
Well, that didn't work.
Move, move!
Faster Bee, faster!
We should really look
into getting seat-belts.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
It's ok. She is gonna steal the robot back,
fight off the police, kill two bigger
robots and come right back home.
Shut up Otis.
This just breaking news.
There appears to be
a high-speed chase underway
just outside McKinnon Air Base.
Go right! Go right!
Closer. Closer.
You lose that car,
I will personally rip your face off.
Oh, God!
It's all under control.
Charlie!
Mom?
You pull that car over right this second.
This is very unsafe, what you are doing.
Mom, you got to get out of here, ok?
Mom...
You have to trust me, please!
Charlie!
We got to help her, Ron!
Hang on.
Oh, my God! Ron!
Get out of the way!
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing?
I saw this on Miami Vice.
God!
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, my God!
Nice driving, Ron.
Is everyone ok?
Ron! We have a kid in the car!
I was trying to save the other kid!
What was I...
It was a lose-lose.
Otis?
Otis, are you alright?
That...
was radical.
Preparing satellites
to transmit our message.
Ok. What's the plan?
This is the plan?
I hate this plan.
Bee, I want to help.
I would hate anything
To happen to her
You are actually talking.
And you are listening to The Smiths.
Be careful.
Handle him!
And finish the job this time!
Oh, shit!
How the hell am I gonna get up there?
There. The one on the tower.
You think these little chains can hold...
Ok.
Hold on!
What are you doing?
Come on.
No.
After I kill you,
I kill her.
Bee, no!
You missed.
You will kill us both!
Bumblebee!
Oh, God.
You.
You need to get out of here.
What do you mean?
I mean my friends are coming.
And they are gonna be looking for him.
Thank you.
Hey soldier!
I am here. I made it.
What's going on?
World is already been saved, kid.
Cool.
Hey,
can you call my mom?
This is it Bee.
Let's go!
Bee, I can't go with you.
You have got people out there
that need you.
And so do I.
I got to let you go.
Thank you...
So much...
Forgiving me...
My voice.
Thank you for...
For making me feel like me again.
I will never forget you.
Goodbye, Bumblebee.
No way.
You kidding me?
Are you telling me you could have been
a Camaro this whole time?
Oh, my God!
Here you go ma'am.
Baby.
Thank God you are alright.
Thanks for coming Mom.
That was some driving Ron.
Well, I have taken a few notes.
Otis.
They forced me to tell.
I am glad they did.
I could not have done it
without you guys.
Hey Charlie.
I will be right back, ok?
What happened to you today?
This?
You know, robot fights,
high-speed chases,
international disasters.
The usual.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah...
Not quite there yet.
Nope.
Yep. Ok, ok.
No. Yeah.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections June 2022
Old friend,
you kept this planet safe.
Because of you,
we have a future,
B-127.
My name...
Is...
Bumblebee.
Let's see if we got something.
Oh, my God, yes!