There's a legend that precedes
the dawn of our civilization.
A vile god,
so large and so powerful
that it consumed
entire planets as fuel.
Few believed such a thing
could be true,
until the day we saw Unicron
with our own eyes.
But he didn't just come
for our planet.
He wanted
our greatest technology,
the Transwarp Key.
And he sent his most powerful
henchman to collect it,
Scourge.
More enemies are landing.
We won't be safe for long.
Do we have the key?
You must take it.
Keep it hidden,
so that it never falls
into the hands of Unicron.
But, Apelinq, we can fight.
No. Protecting our Transwarp
Key is all that matters!
Go. Use it to escape.
What will you do?
I'll hold him off.
Buy you some time.
Then I'm staying with you.
This is my fight.
Listen, if Unicron
were to get the key,
he could open a portal
through time and space
with no end to the worlds
he could destroy.
It is now your time
to lead the Maximals,
Optimus Primal.
So you're
this planet's great warrior.
You have such a beautiful world
filled with
an abundance of life.
Savory.
My master grows hungry.
Give me the Transwarp Key,
and he will spare your home.
We'd rather die than let
him reach other planets.
So be it.
Benefits of serving
the almighty Unicron.
They never learn.
You're too late, Scourge.
Your master will be trapped
in this galaxy forever.
No!
His sacrifice will be our oath.
To preserve the key,
no matter the cost.
You let them slip away
with the Transwarp Key.
Scour the universe and find
where the Maximals have gone.
When you acquire the key,
use it to bring me to you.
Yes, my lord.
Once I have the key,
I alone will reign supreme.
All right, baby, come on.
Show me the money.
Here we go. There we go.
Yo, Sonic. Breakfast ready yet?
I ain't your butler, Kris.
Come on, man.
No names over the airwaves.
It's Tails.
My bad,
Kristopher Diaz
from 974 Wilson Avenue,
Apartment 2-C, Brooklyn.
No real names.
They're listening.
Ain't no secret government
agencies worried about us, Tails.
Now get your behind out here
while it's hot.
At least they got that going for
'em. Here, I ironed this for you.
I already ironed it. What...
Like you cooked those eggs?
What you mean?
They're just... seasoned.
Aw, come on.
Come eat, bro.
I can't get past Bowser.
Well, good morning to you too.
Drink this
and take your medicine.
- All of it.
- Okay.
Are you sure you can take him?
Yeah, hospital's
on the way. I got time.
And, if that lady,
that administrator, is there
and she mentions a bill,
just...
tell her we're handling it.
I will. And after today,
I'll be able to help out more.
Good luck on the interview.
Don't forget to laugh
at all their jokes.
White people love that shit.
Ma, language.
Okay!
Remember, I have class tonight, so I'll be home late.
Lo quiero.
I love you.
Hurry up, man.
We gotta get into the city.
Hey. Hold up. Hold up.
Your hand's hurting again?
No, it's nothing.
Yo, let me see.
Kris.
It's swollen.
The sickle cells must be
blocking the blood flow again.
How long has this been going on?
Couple days.
Hey, yo, look, I told you,
you gotta tell me these things.
You fighting this alone,
or we fighting it together?
Together.
Home team?
Home team.
Two for ten. Two for...
Stop touching everything.
Hell, no.
Kris, what'd I tell you
about letting your mans come out
the crib looking like a whole square?
Only so much I can do.
Yeah, whatever, bro.
Look. Here.
Ooh! My dawg!
When you gonna let me put your skills
to work and get you some real money?
Yeah. Says the dude
who can't even afford cable.
"Says the guy who..."
I choose not to purchase cable.
It's my own personal way
to protest the vampiric nature
of modern-day capitalism!
Hey, good luck with that
interview in that dusty suit!
I'm coming.
Hey, guys. That's a good one,
but the Ankylosaurus
was an armored dinosaur.
- Thank you, thank you...
- for being patient.
Intern? Intern?
I paged you three times.
Why didn't you call me?
Okay, well, I figured if I stopped
to call, that would make me later.
The police are here.
They busted an art auction.
The owner claims
that everything is authentic,
but they want a second opinion.
All right.
The da Vinci sketch is legit.
The painting's a copy.
Real one's at the
National Gallery in London.
Roman vase.
Valuable, but you are not
gonna retire off of them.
This Greek curse tablet,
it would be expensive,
but it's a fake.
How can you tell?
See the spelling? Roman.
Doesn't even show up
in that era.
Got it.
Officers,
I figured it out. So...
The da Vinci, that is real.
Now, where did you come from?
What are you?
It's pretty neat, right?
Yes.
Where is it from?
They just discovered it
in Sudan.
The boys say it's Horus,
fifth millennia BC, Nubian?
This symbol is definitely
not hieroglyphic.
Well, if it's as exotic
as it looks,
I'm gonna get a feature
in Minerva.
Jillian?
Okay, team, let's do it.
Okay, what are the rules?
Bros before hos.
"Don't be a problem.
Don't go looking
for a problem."
- Or else we're gonna...
- Have a problem.
I know, I know.
Okay, I'll be back
in a little bit.
Mr. Diaz?
Hey, I know we're
a little behind on the bill.
Three months behind. Until your account
is current, you can't bring your brother.
I've told you that.
I'm gonna fix it.
I need a little more time.
Take him to the ER.
Well, they won't see him in
the ER unless he's critical.
Mr. Diaz.
He's 11!
He's 11 years old.
Come on, Kris, we gotta go.
What happened? I'll tell
you later, man. All right?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, yo. Sit here.
And don't move!
After a conference with Simpson's
attorney, Howard Weitzman...
Can I help you?
Yes.
Hey, I'm here for an interview
with the head of security, Mr. Bishop.
I'm Noah Diaz.
It's been canceled. No.
No, that has to be a mistake.
Came right from Mr. Bishop.
Just need your authorization...
Mr. Bishop! Hey! Hey!
It's okay, Walker.
It's me, Noah Diaz. Sir, I think
your boy back there is confused.
He said our interview was
canceled. Because it is.
Wait, why? On the phone you
said I was perfect for the job.
You said this
was just a formality.
It was until your old commanding
officer called me back.
Said you were brave, an
expert com tech, but unreliable.
Couldn't trust you.
Your head was always
somewhere else.
Sir, I can explain all of that.
I had some responsibilities at
home. My brother, he's sick...
You had a responsibility
to the United States Army.
Mr. Bishop! Sir.
I'm a hard worker, okay?
I just...
I just really need a break.
Listen, I can't have someone
like you mess up what I've built.
Someone like me?
You don't know anything
about me!
I know you don't know
how to be part of a team.
God.
Hey, look.
Superman went
on a bunch of interviews
before he got his job
on the Daily Planet.
But he never gave up.
I'm not Superman, Kris.
Life ain't a comic book.
I'm just saying.
You'll get the next one.
Yo, there is no next one.
No one's coming to save us.
We're alone in this.
Yo, man, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
No, it's not.
None of this is.
You know what?
Come on.
Yo, here, bro.
Just head upstairs. I'll
be right there, all right?
So what was you
talking about earlier?
Hey, yo, you want one?
No. I don't want any candy.
You gotta relax, man.
Your energy
is really affecting my chi.
And I get it. I was
nervous my first time too.
But you might want to do some breathing
exercises, or something. Look at me.
My man, my man, my man, my man.
It's just
I ain't done this before.
I know that.
But them rich cats in there,
they give a ton of paper
to charities every year
to make themselves feel better.
If you look at it from a holistic
perspective, we doing them a favor.
Hey, yo! You're
welcome! Will you stop?
What are you doing? This ain't
about to affect they pockets at all.
And it's about
to be easy as hell.
So why you ain't the one
going in there and doing it?
Because, papito,
I'm the mastermind.
Now come on,
put this in your ear.
My man, you serious?
Yo, is that even clean?
It's the fourth quarter, we got
about ten seconds left on the clock,
and you got the rock.
Get rid of this.
Hey, man!
Don't slam the...
Okay. I am off
to my fundraiser.
What do you think?
It's nice.
Um, can I...
Can I run something by you?
So I've been doing
some research,
and I don't think
that the statuette is Horus.
As a matter of fact,
I'm sure it's not.
The boys dated it
around 5000 BC, right?
But the Nubians,
they never even had contact
with the Egyptians
until 600 years after that.
The symbol's not hieroglyphic.
I don't even think it's
from that part of the world.
I think it might
be Aztec or Inca.
It's not some Egyptian god.
It's something else.
Interesting.
Get those pressed, okay?
Yeah.
There you go.
Let that breath fill you up.
In... out.
Please stop talking.
Okay, all right, I get it, you don't
like to chitchat back and forth.
But I got something for you.
You got a robbing mix tape?
No.
I got a liberating mix tape.
You feeling that?
Yeah, whatever.
All right, there shouldn't be
nobody in this part of the building.
You should be able
to just waltz right on in.
Strike one, mastermind.
This place is packed.
Hey, well, to error is divine.
Just act like you own the place.
Hey, wassup, brother?
Good to see you again.
Try not to look suspicious.
Here you go. Here you go.
Sorry. Sorry. That's you, bro.
Nice glasses. I didn't know...
I didn't know you had glasses.
What are you doing,
making friends?
Everything good?
We're in the mix.
Hey. Let's see
what you really are.
Now, my man said
it's tucked in the back.
Been there a couple weeks.
It's like a grayish car
with like a...
Blue stripe.
All right, now just
like brother Reek showed you.
Down the window...
a little wiggle...
feel that snag and...
yeah.
Now we making money.
All right.
Talk to me, homey.
I'm in.
This won't hurt a bit.
Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm gonna lose my job.
I'm gonna go to jail.
It's definitely not Nubian.
This cannot be.
Calling all Autobots!
Yippee-ki-yay, mother...
Prime, this is Arcee.
I have a visual.
What am I looking at?
A way home.
Calling all Autobots!
- What am I doing?
- Well, the coast is clear out here,
so whenever you want to slide
that thing on out, you good.
I can't. I can't.
Like you can't
drive stick or something?
No, it's just...
I ain't no thief.
Are you having
an existential crisis now?
The deadline for that was
when I offered you Twizzlers.
This is an emergency.
Can you hear me, Mirage?
Roll out!
Who the hell was that?
That's the radio, bro.
This car is buggin'. I'm out.
Hey!
Shit!
Shit.
Hey, you!
Get out of the car!
I'm trying! The car
started by itself, I promise!
Look, it's not working!
Get out now!
No! Wait! What you doing?
Noah, what's...
Reek! Reek! Reek!
Now, that's top-tier
manifestation!
Yo, the car's driving by itself!
Noah, you good?
I don't know what's going on!
It won't stop!
Yo, stop! Stop!
Why aren't you listening?
You might wanna slow down.
It's not me, it's the car!
- It's possessed!
- No, no, no.
You're just
on an adrenaline high.
Let's do some of them
breathing exercises.
Yo, I don't need
no breathing exercises!
The car's driving by itself!
Snap.
Yo, Reek, what do we do?
Noah, I cannot hear you.
Reek!
Noah, I can't...
No, he did not!
No, he did not just leave me!
Pull over!
Help me!
Are you ok...
Drive. Drive, drive,
drive, drive, drive!
The bridge.
The bridge, the bridge...
Take the Williamsburg!
I got a 10-37 in progress.
Silver Porsche.
You serious, man?
Nah. Nah.
Hell, do something, please!
Yo, nah. Nah, nah, nah.
Come in, come in.
Can you hear me, Mirage?
Mir-what?
Mirage.
Yo, yo, yo, slow down!
Slow down!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
That felt good!
Get some oil pumping,
you know? Damn!
I've been cooped up
forever, dude.
I can't tell you
how old it gets!
"Mirage, stay hidden.
Mirage, don't draw
any attention to yourself.
Mirage, Big is just a movie.
You'll never be a real boy."
But that was fun, man.
You're fun, dude.
Right. This is probably
a lot for you?
Back up! Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa. What's with the aggression?
I thought after the car
chase, we were boys.
Are you gonna hit me?
Maybe.
It's like that?
Tough guy.
I like that.
I like it a lot.
What are you?
Some sort of possessed car
or something?
Nah.
That's not real, man.
I'm an alien.
Like... Like E.T.?
E.T.? The little ugly guy
in the basket?
Look at this face!
The name's Mirage.
Come on. Give me a little,
give me a little.
Give me a little.
Give a little tap.
Give me a little tap.
There you go.
Now we're friends!
Great. The gang's here.
There are more like you?
Like me? Nah.
But be cool
so they don't crush you.
What? Yeah, I'd put that
pipe down if I were you.
Well, well,
who have we got here?
Mirage, what have you done?
You brought a human here?
Optimus!
Hey! Looking good, man!
Wait a second.
Are those new rims?
You were told to stay hidden.
Right, right.
Crazy coincidence.
When you called,
all Optimus-like...
"Autobots, roll out!"...
this guy was already in the car.
But he's cool,
so it's cool. Cool?
Not cool.
Who are you, human?
I'm nobody.
I ain't even seen nothing.
I'm not even seeing
anything right now.
Arcee.
Private Noah Diaz, US Army.
Multiple commendations.
A wizard with electronics.
He's a soldier.
He does not look like a soldier.
I mean, you looking
pretty rough yourself.
Sorry, sir.
I will deal
with your mistake later.
Okay, the energy surge we felt
was in the 4,000 yottahertz range,
which is undetectable to humans.
I've reconstructed the source
from the energy echoes.
I cannot believe it.
It exists and it is here.
What the hell am I looking at?
The Transwarp Key.
It was thought to be lost
thousands of years ago.
It was once used
to open space-time portals
to Energon-rich planets
throughout the universe.
You mean Energon-rich
planets like...
Cybertron.
After seven long years
stranded on Earth,
we've finally found a way home.
Wait till I catch you, Reek.
Okay, so where
is this t-tran, t-trun...
Transwarp Key?
Thank you.
It's in the new museum
on Ellis Island.
Let's blow it up
and get the hell out of Dodge!
No, we can't just go in
blasting and steal it, Bee.
The humans will hunt us down.
What we need is a quiet way in.
Ooh, how about him?
- No.
- What? Come on, man.
He could slip in right through
one of them little doors,
grab the key, leave a
nice IOU and peace out.
He's perfect.
What?
No, it is a bad idea.
I agree with Big Man.
So, it's been real, y'all.
But...
Time-out.
Mirage.
I know. I know. Just relax. Let
me just talk to my guy real quick.
Yo, don't leave me with these
tight-asses, bro. We make a great team.
This is a waste of time.
Look, I'm not breaking into a
museum for some space robots.
But what about for friendship?
Or, or, or
what about for cash?
You help us get this key,
so we can get off this rock...
No offense.
Love the neighborhood and all.
And then I let you sell me.
Lambo?
Ferrari?
Indy?
Look, you get paid
and then I'll split.
So all I gotta do
is walk in and out?
All you gotta do.
We'll take care of the rest.
Cross my spark and hope to die.
Wow! That was corny
when I said it out loud.
What about the big man?
Optimal, or whatever.
You let me worry about him.
Cool?
Got him!
He's in, baby! Whoo!
Y'all are robots
that transform into cars,
even though
you're from way out in space.
But now there's this key that
opens a portal back to your home?
And you know this because
there's a beacon light in the sky
that I can't see
because I'm human.
You say that like it's weird.
It's super weird.
You know what's weird? Marky
Mark is leaving the Funky Bunch!
I heard he's just gonna pursue
acting now. That's crazy! What?
- How does that...
- What a world.
Whatever, man.
I'm just trying
to collect this money
and get your angry-ass boss off
of Earth before he blows a gasket.
Don't take it personal.
He just misses home.
And I think he blames himself
for us getting stuck here.
Earth was supposed
to be a pit stop, you know,
a place for us to regroup
and rejoin the war back home.
Prime feels like it's his fault
we've been stranded here,
like he has to fix it
all on his own.
All right, team, heads up.
There's security up ahead.
Nice!
This is gonna be fun, man.
No, no, no. No, bro.
You need to switch it up.
You need to turn into a helicopter
or a speedboat or something.
I got something
way better than that.
Good call.
I do not like this plan.
Yeah, Mirage isn't
really known for being quiet.
At least Mirage is one of us.
We should not be relying
on a human.
They are my friends.
I know one was good to you, Bee,
but this is not our world.
The humans will always
protect what is theirs.
We can only trust our own kind.
You can't handle the truth!
I do not want you going to
that drive-in theater anymore.
Nightbird, search the island.
Finally, the hunt
draws to a close.
Hello?
Fudge.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Hey, are you okay?
Back up!
Yo, are you okay?
Back up! Back up! Back up!
I didn't think anyone
was in here.
That's it.
Who are you?
I'm...
the janitor.
Security!
No, no, no! You don't have to
do that! It's not what it looks like.
It looks like you're trying
to steal museum property.
Okay, it's a little
what it looks like.
Shit.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey, yo, yo! It
doesn't belong to you anyway.
- No, no, no!
- Just stop! Just...
Hey, hey! Relax, relax,
and let me explain.
It belongs to...
to these...
these giant robots from space.
Really?
Look, I'm gonna need that.
Damn!
- Damn!
- Hey!
Hey, hey, hey! What's
going on here? Don't move.
Man, it's about time
you showed up!
The key.
- You were telling the truth.
- Yeah.
But those ones aren't with me.
Rip the flesh from their bones
and bring me the key.
It's yours.
Guys, we got company!
Autobots, protect the key!
Catch!
Not so fast!
They're flying now?
Who the hell are these guys?
Impossible!
I enjoy that look of confusion
when an inferior being
meets a higher power.
What the hell are those things?
Are you okay?
Hey! Stop following me!
I'm not following you!
I'm just escaping
in the same direction.
Um...
Run!
Go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Watch out!
Thanks.
Scourge, I have eyes on the key.
Prime, I don't think
we can hold these guys...
No!
My God! Put me down!
Whoa, that was so scary.
Cool.
You're still alive.
Get the key!
Noah, get out of here!
Get off me! I hate spiders!
Go, go, go! Don't die,
don't die, don't die, don't die!
Go! Get out of here!
Leaving so soon?
Yo! Look out!
The key!
Enough of these games.
I'll get it myself.
Not on my watch.
Aw, don't be frightened, humans.
This'll all be over soon.
And you call yourself a Prime.
Primus would be ashamed.
I'm tired of little things
getting in my way.
Bee!
O Captain! My Captain!
No!
Bee.
Now to add a Prime
to my collection.
Maximals.
Good.
Maybe we'll get a real fight.
No. We got what we came for.
No.
This cannot be.
We must go now. Come with me.
This is my fault.
It should've been me.
I'm sorry for your loss.
No offense, lady,
but who are you again?
My name is Airazor.
I am a Maximal.
A warrior from both
your past and future.
Right. That...
That tracks. Yeah.
We fled our home planet
on the eve of its destruction.
We sought refuge
and hid here on Earth.
Right. So you're a
Maximal. Y'all are Autobots.
What was those things
that attacked us earlier?
Terrorcons. Servants
of a dark, hungry god
who feeds on entire worlds
to sustain himself.
Unicron.
So you're saying this thing
Unicron eats planets to survive?
Yes. And he imbues
his servants, like Scourge,
with dark energy, which
makes him all but invincible.
He is entirely beholden
to Unicron.
Through his power,
he possesses Scourge's soul.
Awaken, my dark master.
Rise.
My hunger is killing me.
What have you found?
Salvation.
The galaxy will once again
be yours to feast on, my master.
I should've gotten
the key myself.
I should've known better
than to rely on humans.
Yo, hold up.
What, you blaming me?
After you conveniently left out the
part about a planet-eating monster?
Because of you,
Unicron will now use the key
to consume every planet
in the universe!
Including my home world.
He doesn't have the key.
At least not all of it.
You fool!
This is only half the key.
Please!
The Maximals...
They must have split it.
Excuses!
Complete the key, or else
you will wish you had died
with the rest of your planet.
We broke the key into
two pieces for safekeeping,
then splintered
and went into hiding.
I do not know
where the other half is.
For all I know,
I am the last of our kind.
It's in Peru.
How you know that?
It's the symbols on the stone.
They were only ever recorded
in one other place in the world.
The Inca Temple of the Sun
in Cusco.
It's one of the oldest buildings in
the western hemisphere. I'm-I'm...
I'm guessing that
that can't be a coincidence.
If you can track those symbols
to Peru, so can the Terrorcons.
We need to get there
before they do.
And then kill Scourge and take
his piece to complete the key.
Yo. Hold up. Hold up.
You want to find this other key
and deliver it to the guy
that just kicked your asses.
The Transwarp Key
is our only way home.
If this dude gets a hold of that
thing, it's game over for Earth!
Our families, everybody!
I'm going.
Out of the question.
No offense, but I'm not
trusting my home to a guy
who couldn't even protect his.
This is my planet.
I'm going.
What about you?
Me?
What is your name?
Elena.
Elena,
will you lead us to this temple?
Chance to stop
the end of the world.
Actually,
you'll be saving two worlds.
Yeah.
Yo, is that you, Sonic?
What are you doing up, Tails?
I can't sleep.
This too hot?
You playing that game too much.
Give it a rest,
so your hand can take a break.
I'm gonna beat it.
My money's on you, bro.
We don't quit.
Come on, get some sleep,
all right?
Yo, listen, um,
I gotta...
I gotta head out for a while.
And I don't know
when I'm gonna be back.
Why?
Shit.
- What the...
- No, no, no!
No! Stop, please!
Turn off! Turn off!
Yo, won't you...
I told you to sit tight.
Stop it. I can't
turn it off. I'm sorry.
Is that a robot?
No, no, no.
Go... Go back to bed.
Yo, shut it off! I think your bad
hot-wiring messed up my lights.
I got the bat.
Yo, chill. Give me that.
- Did he say "bat"?
- You're gonna wake up Ma!
I know you're a robot.
Kris?
Yo! You scratched my paint!
What are you doing?
Man, they didn't
treat E.T. like this.
You know this thing?
Yeah.
We're just work friends.
"Work friends"?
You've been inside me.
Look, that thing I told you
I have to go do?
It's for him and his crew.
We're trying to stop
the end of the world.
The world's ending?
No!
Maybe. Sixty-forty.
You know I'm not gonna
let that happen.
But that's why I have to leave.
I'll go get my things.
Tough kid.
What? No. Whoa, whoa. Hold
up. Hold up. You're not coming.
Why? You need someone to watch
your back. It's too dangerous, Kris.
And I need you to stay here
and take care of Mom.
'Cause you might not come back.
Hey, robot.
Me? 'Sup?
Watch out for my brother.
Okay?
You got it, little man.
Nah, I'm serious.
If he gets hurt,
I'm coming after you.
Don't worry.
I got Noah's back. I promise.
Home team?
Home team.
Kid's got heart.
Cojones muy grande.
Wu-Tang is
in the building, baby!
Way to be incognito.
Aw, come on, Prime.
Smile a little bit.
It won't hurt.
Let me see that under bite.
All right. So what kind
of jet we taking to Peru?
Or is it a plane?
Either one's fine.
I just need first class, okay?
'Cause I got long-ass legs.
Well, he is a plane.
No. No, no. Don't...
Don't tell me we're flying on...
No.
My lads! I am Stratosphere,
lord of the skies!
Yeah, I'm walking to Peru.
Ooh.
My gosh.
Sorry.
I sing when I get nervous.
It usually calms me down.
First time flying?
Man, this is my first time
leaving New York.
My God. God.
So the Bronx?
Brooklyn, all right?
East New York all day.
I'm from Bushwick.
Really?
Um, me and my dad,
we used to go to this...
This pizza spot down
on Knickerbocker and Greene.
Tony's Pizza? Wow.
So, tell me about him,
your pops.
What... What was he like?
He was a...
He was a cabbie for 40 years.
Smartest guy you ever met.
He could talk to you
about anything.
History, science, cricket.
Cricket?
And he ain't never
even go to college either.
He used to always say,
"If you keep your eyes
and your ears open,
life will show you
everything you need to know."
So that's why you said yes
to all of this.
I figured if
he is somewhere watching,
then seeing his daughter
do something crazy like this
would definitely make him proud.
You really think
this key thing's in Peru?
I... I think so.
The evidence lines up.
Well, if it is,
and we get our hands on it,
then we gotta destroy it.
What?
They can't unite the key
without both pieces.
No key, no Unicron,
no Earth getting eaten.
Yeah, but then
they can't get home.
We gotta think about us.
Look, all you gotta do
is find it.
And I'll take care of the rest.
Do you think an Energon
infusion could bring him back?
Perhaps.
If we could get him
back to Cybertron.
I never should have taken us
so far from home.
Wow! Wheeljack needs to fix
that power steering.
Sorry I'm late.
I was taking in
a harmonious moment
between a serene butterfly
and an unruffled caterpillar.
Such tranquility.
Yo-ho-ho. Oye, papo,
where you from? Cybertron.
So where'd you get that
accent? Accent? What accent?
You know what I'm saying?
I'm just saying it's cool.
Like I was about to be like,"Oh,
hey, daddy, where are you from?"
but I didn't want to assume
that you speak Spanish too,
because then... Right?
A little racist, Brother.
I'm not trying to be,
you know... Yo.
But anyway... The mission.
Follow me.
But he's a robot, like, so,
how's that racist?
Okay, you guys, check this out.
The coordinates you gave me
correspond to an old church.
Take a look.
That's Santo Domingo. The Spanish
built it on top of an old Inca temple.
Correcto. I picked up some residual
energy readings around the courtyard,
so I'm guessing
the key's somewhere close by.
But we may have some trouble
getting there.
Inti Raymi.
It's a festival that
shuts down the whole city.
- Guess it's a night mission then.
- No.
Scourge could already be here.
We must retrieve
the other half before he does.
Me and Elena will do it.
Y'all would never
make it two blocks.
There's human security all around
the church. You'll never get through.
Then we'll have to take
a play out of your book.
We'll hide in plain sight.
We'll blend in with the parade.
It is not a bad idea.
We will keep an eye out
for the Terrorcons.
On first sign of trouble,
we are going in.
Yo, Noah, think fast.
And if you need help,
just holler.
I am in position.
All right, coast is clear.
Noah, Elena, it's go time.
Blend in. Act natural.
Autobots must be using
their new pets
to reach the temple.
Lovely.
They're doing our work for us.
Go fetch.
The key's gotta be
in here somewhere.
Yeah.
That stonework is 17th century.
What we're looking for
is something
much, much older.
What is it? It's the
same insignia on Airazor.
But it's not lined up right.
Wait, you see that?
I think there's something
under here.
There's another one.
There is.
Now what?
I thought it would've...
That's some
Indiana Jones-type shit.
You sure about this?
No.
Any sign of Scourge?
Nope, all clear here.
Yeah.
It's just groupies over here.
Stay on task, Mirage.
Prime, you gotta learn
how to relax, my man.
You know, we must be the first
people to walk here in half a millennium.
Yo, Sonic. You dead yet?
No.
Wait, did you just
call me Sonic?
I think that's a temple.
What are we looking for?
You see the symbols
on that temple?
They match the ones
in the courtyard.
I think it's up there.
I think we found
what we came here for.
I always wondered
what it would feel like
to be there when artifacts
were actually found.
All right. Now come on, push.
Are you even pushing?
Yeah, I'm pushing.
Wait, what?
Just... Just let me think.
No, no. Where is it?
Sometimes there's, like, a...
like a false bottom or something.
Look.
I think I found something.
You see these symbols?
I've seen markings like this...
the Airazor statue at my museum.
They're new.
They're not
on the Transwarp Key.
There's two of them.
Mirage?
Let's keep moving.
Just give me a second.
Run!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Mirage! We got trouble!
One of those things is down
here! Where are you guys?
Hang tight!
I'm on the way.
The Autobots are moving.
They must have found the key.
Come on!
Airazor, where are the humans?
They're underground,
heading towards the jungle.
Aw, man, they're tailing us!
Do something!
What do you want me to do?
You had a gun this whole time?
Prime, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm going to take back
Scourge's key
and then take off his head.
Guys!
I could use a little help!
Did someone call for backup?
- Brake, brake, brake!
- What?
Brake!
Yay!
This is for Bee!
Come here.
Hold on!
I love your fire, Prime.
But you're going to die
on this speck of dust.
I can think of no better place
to bury you.
I will end you, Scourge.
That is a promise.
They're getting away.
Not this time.
I hear water.
Where are we?
What was that?
Who are you?
And why are you hunting
for the key?
Yo, Donkey Kong!
Stay away from my friends!
Mirage? Don't worry.
Your boy's got this.
Stranger danger!
Hey, hey, hey!
Not so fa...
Ay, ay, ay.
Hey! Over here,
kitty, kitty.
Stand down!
I won't ask a second time.
No! All of you, stop!
Airazor.
Primal.
I thought you were lost.
All of you.
The others... Are they...
I am all that is left.
Prime, these are
my fellow Maximals.
Rhinox.
Cheetor.
Sorry about scaring you,
brother.
- Scared?
- Please.
I'm not scared.
That's just engine oil.
And our leader, Optimus Primal.
Optimus Primal?
Named after you, the
legendary warrior of Cybertron.
It's an honor.
Airazor, I'm happy
to see you, old friend.
But bringing others here
was not part of our plan.
I fear you bring dark tidings.
Scourge has come to Earth.
He's found us.
And he has half of the key.
We must find the second
piece before he does.
But it wasn't in the cave.
It was. But we moved it
long ago to keep it safe.
Where is it now?
Come with me.
That doesn't look so good.
When Scourge touches you,
he leaves a mark.
But I'll be all right.
Hey, back there
you called me Sonic.
Yeah. Your little bro's
got this thing
about using real names
over the airwaves, so...
Wait, you been talking
to Kris? -
He gave me this
to keep tabs on you,
make sure I'm keeping
my promise.
Here.
Next time,
include warning labels.
Nah, go ahead, keep it.
I guess it does
look better on me.
Just don't ask what part
of my body it came from.
So, who are you?
We Maximals are an advanced race
dedicated to the expansion
of life throughout the universe.
We use the Transwarp Key
to visit young worlds.
The Nazca Lines,
the Temple at Tikal...
That was you guys, right?
Not us.
We cannot claim credit
for human ingenuity.
But you had the key.
Why stay on this world?
When Unicron destroyed
our world,
we took an oath dedicated
to the preservation of life,
no matter the cost.
And Earth
has been a safe refuge.
I'm happy to see
you, old friend.
How are you, brother?
This is Amaru.
He and his family are the
last descendants of a tribe
that has watched over us
for hundreds of years.
When we arrived, they
shared their world with us.
And together
we protected its people
and our secret.
You allied with humans.
We did.
If you give us this key,
tomorrow I will light the beacon
and bring Scourge to us.
The Maximals have already sacrificed
one home to protect the universe.
I won't risk losing another.
As a leader,
I know you understand.
He is not the Optimus Prime
I imagined.
Well, he has lost so much.
Many more will perish
if the key falls
into the wrong hands.
If you had another chance
to save our home,
would you act any differently?
Optimus, come.
I want to show you something.
Your friend
will find peace here.
This is raw Energon.
The valley is rich with it.
Could this revive Bee?
I'm sorry, but in
this state, it is inert.
It would take a great power
to ignite it.
Greater than anything
we have here.
Your circle, you reside in.
I see that you are surprised
we entrust the key to them.
Yes, I am.
I've been amongst them
a long time now.
There is more to them
than meets the eye.
They are worth saving.
What if we didn't destroy it?
Maybe there's another way
to... to save both our homes.
Elena, I made a lot
of mistakes in my life.
This is different.
I can't fail at this.
I can't let my family down.
You're just like him.
You know that?
Who?
Optimus.
I'm serious.
He feels it too.
Feels what?
Like a beast of burden
just trying to carry the weight
of the world on his shoulders.
You think he's some...
Some general barking orders,
but when I look at him,
all I see is a big brother
trying to protect his family.
Are you okay?
Airazor?
I can feel Scourge!
- He's...
- in my mind.
Run, Elena!
No!
Airazor.
They found us.
Everyone, defensive positions!
Noah, guard the key.
Take Elena and find
someplace safe to hide.
We must protect the humans.
Miss me?
Noah, Elena, get out of here!
We have to destroy it.
Noah!
No!
Don't.
I know you want
to protect your people,
but if you destroy that key,
our home will be lost forever.
We do not have to choose.
Please, Noah.
Elena!
Go!
Wait, wait.
Didn't I kill you already?
No!
I'm the Maximal that's going
to rip out your spark.
We'll see about that.
Kill them!
Airazor, no!
I can't hold it back...
much longer.
Fight it, Airazor.
Remember our oath, Primal.
No matter the cost.
I can't hold it back!
Airazor, no!
Primal!
It's okay.
Do it.
Primal.
No matter the cost.
Elena!
Elena, look at me.
Are you okay?
Scourge has the key.
Awaken, almighty Unicron.
Your time has come.
I am sorry, Noah.
You were looking out
for your own.
I can't even be angry
at you for that.
On my home world, we believe that
the battle with darkness will continue
till all are one.
I lost sight of that.
You fought for yours
as I fought for mine
when we should have been
fighting the darkness together.
Well, I ain't done fighting yet.
All right, everybody, squad up!
Bring it in.
There's got to be a way
to stop this dude.
It's too late. The Transwarp
has already been activated.
It has more energy
than a supernova.
Any interruption
will ignite it like a bomb.
The only way
to stop this process
is an access code installed
long ago as a safeguard.
Okay, what's the code then?
The code was split
along with the key.
Sadly, the second half of
that code died with Airazor.
No, wait, wait, wait.
I got it.
The one hiding
her half of the key...
That had markings in it
just like the ones I found in
the cave where you hid yours.
Together, they must complete
the access code.
So we got a chance now, right?
A slim chance.
That is all we need
if you will show us the way,
Primal.
All right.
We need to move quickly.
We have a small window
before the portal opens
large enough
for Unicron to enter.
The bridge is girded
by a series of tunnels.
They are too small
for Maximals, but...
But not for humans.
If Noah and Elena
reach the central antenna,
they can use the code
to shut it down,
remove the Transwarp Key...
and close the portal before
Unicron enters our atmosphere.
But Scourge will be
watching our every move.
He'll do anything to stop us
from getting the key.
Then we bring the fight to him.
Autobots and Maximals
will charge the bridge together
and lure Scourge
onto the battlefield.
While me and Elena sneak in
through the back way.
It sounds like
we're all going to die.
If we are to die,
then we will die fighting
all as one.
This world is yours, master.
Scourge,
they're back.
Prime.
Protect the key. Don't
let them get to the bridge.
Maximals!
Autobots!
Roll out!
Rhinox, Cheetor, maximize!
At least
the foot soldiers took the bait.
Yeah, but Scourge didn't.
He's guarding the key.
All right. This should lead to the
bottom of the Transwarp control panel.
Get the key, get the hell out of
there. What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go distract Scourge.
No, you can't take on
Scourge alone.
Relax.
I'm Mirage, remember?
Hey.
One, two, three!
Whoomp! There it is! Pow!
We gotta hurry up.
Take cover!
Someone give me a real fight!
It's a fight you want?
You got one.
He was mine.
Nope!
Missed me!
Noah, get to the key.
Mirage!
What do we have here?
Elena, go!
Brave, but futile.
Hey! Don't mess with my boy!
Mirage.
No one will remember
this pathetic planet.
And no one will remember you.
Mirage, what are you doing?
Keeping my promise.
Mirage, no!
Come on, you gotta get up!
It's okay, Noah.
Home... Home team.
Home team.
Mirage!
Mirage?
Mirage.
Kill the other human.
Unicron.
You fought bravely.
But this world is already mine.
We're too late.
Yo!
Hey!
Hey! Look!
Hey, Knuckles.
You there? Over.
Yo, Sonic.
Kris!
Noah?
What's going on?
Where's Mirage?
He... He's gone.
Gone?
No.
I'm sorry, Kris.
I'm not gonna win this one.
But you don't lose, right?
I wish that were true,
but I can't.
Yes, you can.
No.
No, man, I'm not you.
I hate being sick.
Whenever I wanna give up,
you're always there
telling me to keep going.
But now it's my turn.
Keep going, Noah.
You think you're a nobody, but
you're the strongest guy I know.
You guys are so cute.
Mirage?
You're alive!
Yeah, but... I'm gonna
need you to take the wheel.
You can do this.
'Cause you're my brother.
Noah Diaz from Wilson Avenue,
Apartment 2-C,
Brooklyn, New York.
No names over the airwaves.
Forget that.
Let 'em know who you are.
Yo, Scourge!
Remember me?
You think
you can take me on alone?
He is not alone.
I'm never
leaving Brooklyn again.
Energon.
Prime!
Noah!
I'm getting really tired
of you humans.
Bee!
You again.
You should've stayed dead!
I have come here to kick ass.
Glad to have you back.
Everyone guard the bridge!
Elena, shut it down!
We gotta give her some cover!
We'll clear the way.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Punch in an access code...
How hard could that be?
You've gotta be kidding me.
Just you and me, Scourge.
Let's end this once and for all.
Master, the reinforcements!
All right, I got this.
Let's go, Bee!
Say hello to my little friend!
We gotta hurry!
Last one.
Die, you ugly mother...
You will never see Unicron
take this world.
You did it!
Brooklyn, baby!
No!
Unicron will prevail!
Elena!
I've had enough!
Time to show you
the real power of the Prime!
This belongs
to a friend of mine!
The panel,
it's destroyed.
I can't stop it.
Autobots, Maximals,
retreat to safety.
I will destroy the key myself.
Prime! No!
There's gotta be another way.
Bee, protect them.
Your sacrifice becomes our oath.
Thank you, my friends.
Bee!
We can't leave him!
Everyone, on me!
Don't, Prime.
I can give you
everything you want.
Then die.
Noah.
I got you!
Let me go, Noah.
Save yourself.
Till all are one.
Punch it, Prime.
Yeah, baby!
Unicron...
Is he dead?
Trapped, but not dead.
Evil can never
be vanquished completely.
He could return.
Let him come.
United, we will destroy him,
once and for all.
I am Optimus Prime,
leader of the Autobots.
We have lost the Transwarp Key
and with it
our ability to go home.
But we have gained an ally
in our battle against
the forces of evil.
Forces too powerful
for any of us
to defeat on our own.
But together,
we might just have a chance.
I am Noah Diaz.
What is there to know about me?
I was raised out in Brooklyn.
I got a little bro
who calls me Sonic.
And if I gotta help save the universe
in order to save the people I love,
well, then that's what
I'm gonna do.
How you doing, sir?
Um, I'm here
for the job interview?
Noah Diaz.
I'll tell 'em you're here.
This Sunday on 60 Minutes,
I sit down to talk
with Elena Wallace.
She recently discovered an underground
temple with a network of catacombs...
dating back to 5000 BC.
I never could've imagined making
a discovery of this significance.
So it's definitely
a dream come true.
Brooklyn, baby.
They're ready for you.
Thank you, sir.
Elevator in the back.
Why don't you tell me
about your strengths?
In addition to my
experience with electronics,
I've also been really developing
my team-building skills too.
Is that so?
Look, I'm gonna
be honest with you.
Résumé's a little thin.
Yeah, well,
I just recently had a job
working internationally.
Was that...
No, I don't think it's on here.
No, it was...
it was a short-term contract.
Well, that's cool.
Why don't you tell me
about that?
It was in South America.
So I got to work on my Spanish.
My mom was real happy
about that.
You know what I'm saying?
You know moms.
She's just really... But while I
was out there, honestly, man,
it was really just like
work, work, work, you know?
That's a shame, because I hear
the food is really good in Peru.
Wait, I didn't... I didn't
mention anything about Peru.
Well, that's where
you were, right?
I was... Down in Cusco?
With you and, Elena
and your, um,
I don't know, call 'em friends?
What...
What's going on in here?
We know a lot
about you, Mr. Diaz.
Who are you?
The CIA or FBI or...
We are a secret
government organization.
Strictly off the books.
We specialize in global threats.
Planetary loss prevention,
that kind of thing.
We're in the middle
of an ongoing war,
and we'd love
to have you join the fight.
You and your whole team.
You know,
the big guys.
No idea what
you're talking about.
That's a good answer.
All right.
Either way, I want you to know,
in lieu of the thanks
of a grateful nation,
we will be taking care of
your brother Kris's health care.
All of it.
From now on,
he will have 24/7 access
to the greatest doctors
in the world.
And these are doctors who don't ask
their patients about account balances.
Are you serious?
You saved the world, kid.
It's the least we can do.
I don't know what to say.
We'll work on that.
Your brother's
gonna be just fine.
Kris was right, by the way.
No names over the airwaves.
We could really use
someone like you, Noah.
Why don't you think about it?
"G.I. Joe"?
Come on, baby,
show me some. Show me some.
That ought a do it.
This?
This is a complete waste of
your skills and my expertise.
Think it came out pretty good.
Well, I guess
we could call it modern art
and sell it
to some cats in SoHo.
Nah, I'm not selling.
What?
Why?
Is this about the 5-0 thing?
No. I told you,
I did not ditch you!
I was running the give-and-go.
I thought you knew the play!
All right, let's say I did ditch
you, even though I didn't.
For your sake... I see your
face... let's just say I did.
I think all the blood,
sweat and dead presidents
I put into getting these car parts
for you make us even Steven.
It's not that.
This car is special.
This car is a jigsaw puzzle
made of garbage!
Hey, I bet the joint
don't even start.
Bet?
Yo, Mirage.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Your boy is back!
This dude said
I wasn't even gonna start!