[CHIRPING]
[SQUEALS][SCREECHING]
[WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[SCREECHING]
[ALL ROARING]
[WATER DRIPPING]
Oh, shit.
Darcy, you really
shouldn't have come.
Show me.
SITE FOREMAN: Corporate was
adamant. We keep running.
No stopping operations.
No, no, no.
You got to go through.
No cameras.
He's got orders to kill.
I don't even think
international laws
apply up here.
We are geologists first.
If this thing
has any historical
significance at all,
we are shutting down.
I'm shutting us down.
Oh, he's going
to shoot me?
Shoot me.
SITE FOREMAN:
Hey, don't kill her.
This is crazy stuff.
[PANTING]
Crazy shit.
Well, what do you think?
I think history is
about to change.
[COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BELL DINGING]
[FUNK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
LUCAS:
♪ I'm a nasty woman
Oh, look who decided
to show up for work.
LUCAS:
♪ I'm a heartbreaker
♪ Gonna make you cry
[MUSIC STOPS]
What, surf report no
good at South Padre?
The waves are flat
and I got no gas.
You know that, Cade.
[PIGS SQUEALING]
Dude. Rude.
Look at these two junebugs.
Whoo! My, my!
Hey, you're paying
me on this one,
right, Cade?
Please tell me
I'm getting paid.
You know, Lucas, a lot
of guys are just happy
to have a job at all.
Yeah, I suppose.
You got any cash on you?Yeah.
All right, good.
Hey, Lucas Flannery.
GRANDSON: Place
has been in the family
since '28.
Granddaddy ran
it all his life.
Ain't that right,
Granddaddy?
Real soon he's going
to sign it over to me.
GRANDFATHER: The movies
nowadays, that's the trouble.
Sequels and remakes,
bunch of crap.
I love that one. Oh.
He's deaf and senile.
Heard that.
Now these just need
some spit and polish.
I believe they're digital,
possibly IMAX.
Yeah, they're not.
Mister, we'll have a look
around if you want to
leave us to it, okay?
You know, folks used to
come from miles around
to see the dancing
girls with the big
cha-chas. [LAUGHS]
I swear to God
I am one diaper
change away from
poisoning his oatmeal.
Hey, you hang
in there, buddy.
If coming here makes
you feel young,
then you tell this
kid to bring you
here every day.
Seven bucks,
I keep talking.
Sold.
[CHUCKLES]
LUCAS: Remember this place
when we were kids?
How many girls you think you
brought here in high school?
I only remember one.
Hey, heads!
[GROANING]
Ow!
That's why you didn't
make the varsity team.
Ah.
All right. Go long.
[CRASHING]
Leave it.
[SHELLS CLATTERING]
Mortar shells?
What the hell
happened to you?
Hey, snakeballs.
How much for the truck?
Truck?
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Two more weeks, girls,
till no more classes, ever.
Almost time to get
a tan and get wasted!
[ALL WHOOPING]
Please, please.
[SIGHS]
No financial aid. Great.
[DOG BARKING]
Yes, I know I'm home,
thank you.
Intruder alert!
Back away from the premises!
Voice recognition. It's me! I am dialing 911.
Go right ahead.
I don't care.
I'm still calling 911.
MALE REPORTER ON TV:
The Battle of Chicago
was an event
that permanently
changed our world.
FEMALE REPORTER:
Over 1,300 dead.
MALE REPORTER:  Much of
the city has been destroyed.
FEMALE REPORTER 2:
Homeland Security
is urging everyone
to report suspicious
alien activity.
FEMALE REPORTER 3:
A swift act of Congress put
an end to all joint operations
between the military and the
Autobots, ending the alliance.
ATTINGER:
As this committee knows,
the Invasion of Chicago
was a defining day
for our nation
five years ago.
The day millions
of people realized that
never again can
we allow aliens
to fight our battles
for us.
A handful of Autobots
were given sanctuary
after joint-combat operations
were abolished.
Fewer than a dozen Decepticons
are still on the run
thanks to our CIA unit,
"Cemetery Wind."
TIMOTHY:  Hurry, let's get it
to my house, guys.
As for the alien technology,
our objective remains to
keep it in American control.
Hi. My name is Timothy.
This is my crew.
We found this alien
ball turret in Chicago.
We just found it in the rubble
and it's all working...
ATTINGER: Word has it
Japan, India,
the Israelis may have
gotten their hands on
a couple of ships.
Apparently the Russians
are starting a bidding war.
We're taking $5,000 for it.
It's got 36 guns, alien shit.
A new era has begun.
And the age
of the Transformers is over.
Hey.
Hey, I've been
waiting for you.
You're looking hot today!
Oh, yeah? How about
you take your shirt off?[TRUCK APPROACHING]
You want me to take
my shirt off right now?
What would your dad
think of that, huh?
What the hell? Hey, where you going?
I cannot believe him.
I cannot believe this.
What the hell?
All the way!
[SIGHS]
A truck?
Dad, please tell me
you didn't spend
our money on this.
Oh, no, don't worry,
he didn't. He spent my money.
A hundred and fifty
bucks of it.
As an advance on
your regular paycheck.
What regular paycheck?Which you will get back.
When?Never. We're broke.
I knew it.
Sweetheart, could you
please not drive a wedge
between employer
and employee.
Hold on.
I thought we were partners.
Look, I came up
short, okay? I had to
buy her a prom dress.
You want me to deny
her a prom dress?
You might as well.
You denied her a prom date.
No, I offered to take
her and chaperone.
Nobody wants to
go to the dance
with their dad.
It's weird.
It's not the issue.
Well, maybe it should be.
Hey, could you guys
just get off my case?
You know what the engine
on this runs for?
I can break it down
and strip it for parts.
And sweetheart, your shorts
are shrinking by
the second, okay?
Cold water,
air dry, please.
I think she looks hot.
What did you say?
Like a hot teenager.
Oh, it's the "teenager"
thing that makes it better.
Thank you.
It didn't sound like
what it meant.
[CADE SIGHS]
CADE: That goes by
the circuit boards.[LUCAS SIGHS]
Put the Zeiss lenses
over there.
Dad, please. You can't keep
spending money on junk
just so you can turn
it into different junk.
We do not use
the "J" word in here.
That is a Super Simplex
theater projector.
It's very rare.
What about
the SmilePilot?
Or the Exer-Mower
that I invented?
Simply ahead
of their time.
Yeah, like the alleged
Guard-Dawg.
[BARKING]
You're gonna
get him upset.
Hey, Cade! Cade!
This thing still work?
No!Yes.
Yes, and still
groundbreaking.
Go back there and
lay on the recliner
and just wait
for a cold one.
CADE: Dude,
stop breaking stuff.
Final notice,
late notice, past due.
LUCAS: Come on, come on.
Bring Daddy the alcohol.
Come on.
I mean, what is all this
crap people send you?
That's a Discman
and that's an 8-track tape.
Music.Never heard of it.
[DEVICES CLATTERING]
Look, I fix that,
it's 100 bucks.
I fix that, it's $250.
If I would have been
able to fix that
before you broke
it even more,
it would have been 20 bucks.
This stuff is what's
gonna put you through
college, as long
as you land one
of those scholarships.
What's the estimated
time of arrival, usually?
Average?
Wait. So it just brings
the beer near you?
That's the trick?
It's got a couple
kinks, man.LUCAS: Yeah.
Dad, you think maybe
some things
should never be invented?
No, I don't.
That's backwards thinking.
This is a temple
of technology.
You guys are standing
in a holy place.
[LAUGHING]
What do you think?
Why don't you look
at all of this?
This could be yours.
What about this land?
Purple People Eater's
back and she looks hungry.
Isn't this incredible?
I knew you
would like it.CADE: Hey, you!
Hey.
I own this house!
It's not for sale!
Six months late
on payments, Mr. Yeager.
And I see you stealing
power at the pole.
CADE: Hey, that's
not your concern.
Sir, do you wanna
see the property?
Sure.
I'd be more than happy
to give you a tour.
I'll show you three
other buyers I got
buried out back,
then I'll crack your head
open like an egg!
Whoa! Whoa!Stay back! He's crazy.
I told you don't
come back here anymore.
I will have my brother come
back and beat your ass!
Don't you start with me.Why don't you
do it yourself?
And I'll bring the police
when I come, too!
My brother ain't no joke!
Who, Jerry?
You bring his
big ass up here,
he's gonna be
huffing and puffing
before he can squeeze
out of that car!
You back out on my grass,
you're gonna be
in big trouble!
You tell Jerry
to come see me.
I'll give him
some pecan pie.
Hey!
[GROANS] She smashed
through the fence?
Cade, relax.
You're going to have
an aortic infarction.
What is that?
I think it's a brain
heart attack.
Yeah, I've had
one already.
So we're stealing
power now?
No, we're borrowing it
from the neighbors.
Great. That's awesome.
Once I graduate
and I'm gone,
who's gonna take
care of you?
Oh, you take care of me?
Who taught you how
to solder a circuit?
Or write a program?
Or French braid your hair?
Or throw a spiral? Me.
That's what I do.
Who taught you how to
cook without ketchup,
or balance your checkbook?
Who always has to be
the grownup around here?
All right,
you got a point, okay?
But that means
we're a great team.
And I know it's been
sucky around here lately.
But we're gonna
be fine, sweetie.
You just gotta
keep believing, okay?
I mean, that's what
great inventors do.
I promise you, one day,
I'm gonna build
something that matters.
I believe you, Dad.
You know, your mom
would be very proud of you.
It's going to be okay.
SOLDIER 1: Spread out!
Push right!
SOLDIER 2: Roll, roll,
roll, roll.
Give me two. Give me two.
Take the beach,
nice and easy.
SOLDIER 3 ON RADIO:
All right, hold what you got.
Release the mini-drones.
[DRONES BEEPING]
PILOT ON RADIO:  Vipers.
Eagle in sight. Cleared hot.
Got a heat sig. Second stack.
Closest to the bow.
GUNNER ON RADIO:  Predator 0-1.
Captured target area.
SAVOY ON RADIO:
Set charges.
Leader, leader,
this is Gunfighter 0-1.
Eagles moving internal.
Second deck.
[GUNFIGHTERS
TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
GUNFIGHTER 2: Frogman 83,
Frogman 83.
GUNFIGHTER 2:
Breached site on rooftop.
Breached site on rooftop.Have Echo Platoon on standby.
Let the helo know
we're moving external!
GUNFIGHTER 1:  Alpha, take
port. Bravo, take starboard.
GUNFIGHTER 2:
Shift right. Shift right.
[GUNFIGHTERS CONTINUE
TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[BEEPING]
Cracking steel!
[GROANING]
No!
GUNFIGHTER 1:
Hit him, hit him, hit him!
Fire.
SOLDIER ON RADIO:
Missiles out. Danger close.
[RATCHET GROANING]
He's running! Move!
GUNFIGHTER 2:  He's on
the run! He's on the run!
[GROANS]
No! Please!
Hold your fire. [GROANING]
Hold!
Hold fire!
Can you not see?
I've been injured.
[GROANING]GUNFIGHTER:  Box him in.
Box him in.
Medical Officer Ratchet!
I'm a friend!
[CONTINUES GROANING]
I'm an Autobot!
Then why are you running?
Optimus sent
this distress message.
OPTIMUS ON SPEAKER:
Calling all Autobots.
We are under targeted attack.
Cease all contact with humans.
We're all hiding.
All Autobots are
being hunted.
We're all in danger.
I lost a sister in Chicago.
You'll get no sympathy
from me.
[RATCHET GROANING]
What's wrong
with you humans?
[CONTINUES GROANING]
No! Please.
GUNFIGHTER 1:
Check fire, check fire!
He's mine now.
Lockdown.
Autobots, Decepticons.
Like little children,
always fighting.
Making a mess
out of the universe.
Then I've got to clean it up.
There is one way
you survive.
Tell me where he's hiding.
Where is Optimus Prime?
Never.
[GROANS]
LOCKDOWN: Never is here.
[LOCKDOWN TRANSFORMS]
I must say,
it is remarkable,
really astounding
the success that
the CIA has had
since you have taken
operational control,
and so the President
has asked me to ask you
to ask him,
to invite you both, uh,
over to the White House
just to powwow,
where we get maybe
some more specifics
about how
exactly you're hunting
the enemy Decepticons left.
I've had my desk
for two years.
Mr. Attinger has been here
for 25.
He runs the projects
where I don't ask
for specifics.
That's why they're
called Black Ops.
And why we all sleep
better at night.
Check. That is great.
So, um...
Any dirt on that?
Uh, how, uh, that's going?
Outstanding.
Great. Oh, great.
I was hoping to hear that.
The President
will be pleased.
'Cause, I'll tell you
right now, I've only been
Chief of Staff since Monday,
um, but I do know that the
alien war stuff, these are...
These are
the only fun meetings.
ATTINGER: Look, I'm not here
to entertain the President,
but you may tell him
that the war will be over.
Soon.
"...be over..."
In case he asks,
I just like to have
an exact quote.
"War will be over soon."
That is great.
Such good news.
And, um, the President
would, I know, just love...
Really, really love
to press the flesh...
Not flesh, obviously,
but just maybe get
a shot with, um...
Is it Lord Prime?
Sir Prime?
We could bop
on Air Force One.
It'd be just a quick bop,
then we just bop in and
bop back.
ATTINGER: I wouldn't get
his hopes up on that one.Okay.
CIA DIRECTOR: He's called
Optimus Prime.
Alien combatant.
Here illegally.
But aren't they
our friends? Why?
Because our world will
never truly be safe
till all of them are gone.
Oh. Well, I would
hope we could do
a much more
ceremonial farewell.
Especially since
our military
has worked
so closely with them.
Until you.ATTINGER: It's
not their planet.
Never was.
Time we take it back.
All right, come on.
Come on.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. [LAUGHS]
Oh, there you go.
No, hold it.
Stop shaking!
Why are you shaking?
You have the job!
You forgot to
eat dinner!
[SIGHS]
You see why I worry?
Look, sorry, sweetie, I...
I almost got it
working right.
So, listen, I'm done
with homework and set
with finals,
so I was just gonna
take a little drive
with some friends
if that was okay with you.[SIGHS]
No boys, I know.
Graduate first.
Exactly.
You do know no one
else has this rule, right?
Rule? Don't make it sound
harsh, okay. It's wisdom.
I don't think we need
to be driving around
in the middle of the night.
It's already like quarter
to eight. It's almost dark.
Spud, will you stop it?
You know where I was
for my graduation?
Yes. With me, the mistake.
The surprise, Tess.
And the best thing
that ever happened.
Do we look unhappy? Huh?
No. It's the greatest
day of my life.
I made your mother
a promise before
she passed.
Our baby's gonna be
at her graduation.
That's it.
High school boys
know nothing.
It's only later
they turn into men.
So if you were older
and wiser, I wouldn't exist.
That's not what I meant.
You know, this is
a non-dating household, okay?
You don't date,
I don't date. That's it.
Well, maybe you should.
Tessa, wait.
Tessa?
Look.
I know I've been
on you, okay?
But I have to be.
Twelve to seventeen
is the official teenage
danger window.
It's my job to get
you through it.
So you can be pissed
off all you want.
And, yes, you can take
a ride with your friends.
Okay.
Don't work all night.
And e.
[SIGHS]
Best thing that ever
happened, Emily.
She's the best thing
that ever happened.
You'd be proud.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
Oh, no.
Unbelievable.
Unbelievable. God!
[PANTING]
Something in here needs to
make this family some money.
Come on, you old wreck.
Judgment Day.
Where is he?
I don't know.
[BARKING]  Intruder alert!
Intruder alert!
Asshole.
I am dialing 911.
Tess, I'm basically
your uncle.
Su casa es mi casa.
And we're going
to lose the  casa.
TESSA: Dad!
Coming!
Are you working with lasers?
If so, I'm not coming in.
You guys have never seen
a truck like this before.
Get in here.
Lock that door.
It doesn't have a lock.
Look! Look at the hole
in the radiator.
Look at the size of it.
Something blew
a hole in it!
Yeah, so?
It's not normal steel.
The shrapnel
in the engine,
it ripped all
the connections apart.
And watch. And this took
some Cade genius.
You are gonna love this.
When I hook this back
to a working battery...
OPTIMUS:  Calling all...
Calling all Autobots.
CADE: Oh, yeah.
I don't think
it's a truck at all.
I think we just
found a Transformer.
Tran... Ugh!
LUCAS: Evacuate!Wait! Guys!
Dad, are you out
of your mind?
You need to get that
thing out of here.
You don't have to worry.
I've been in there
working all night.
I'm fine.
You know what? That's not
a truck, okay? You're right.
It's an alien
killing machine.
Dude. It's DOA.Jesus.
It's been recalled,
totaled, done.
So, listen,
there's a number
that you call.
You're supposed to
call the government.
It's the American
thing to do.
Here we go.You're supposed to call,
and if it ends
up being alien,
then you win $25,000.
You don't win money.
And if you can
capture it live...
Like tag it like
a wild wildebeest,
then you get $100,000.
Dad, we're making
the call.I heard that.
I've seen the commercial.
They don't say that.
That's not a guarantee.
You think Greg
would lie to me?
Look, if that's
a Transformer there from
the Battle of Chicago,
I need to know
how it works.
I'm an inventor.
This could be a game
changer for me!
If I can apply that
technology to
my inventions,
we'd never have to
worry about money again.
I've heard that before.
Twenty-five grand!
It pays for my college.
It pays for the house.
Besides, you used
my money to buy
the truck, right?
So technically,
that's my truck.
Don't you think?
You also signed a contract
regarding all
research lab I.P.
Research lab?
It's a barn, dude.
You signed it and
now you're competing.
Any idea of yours is mine.
Any thought you have,
I own it,
so basically, I own you.
I don't think you
can own someone.
That was, like, a while ago,
even in Texas.
All right.
Bring the torch over
and help me with
the pulley arm.[LUCAS GROANS]
I think the shrapnel
took out its power core.
Oh, and, Tessa,
you see this?
[HAMMERING][EXCLAIMS]
Would an alien killing
machine let me do that?
Look, I'll make the call.
We'll get the money.
Just first let me
see if I'm right.
You want to hide
in the house?
Go ahead.
Okay.
Let's go. Pulley arm.
I can't believe him!
What is that?
Looks like a missile.
CADE: It is! Whoa!
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMING][POUNDING ON DOOR]
TESSA: Dad!
There's a missile
in the family room!
[CLANGING]Holy...
[GROANS][OPTIMUS GROWLS]
I'll kill you!
[GRUNTING]
[YELPING]
No! No!
[GROANING]
Dad, there's
a missile in...
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
I'll kill you! Stay back!
Oh, no. Don't shoot.
Don't shoot!Call 911! Run!
Lucas!Stop!
[GROANS]
Lucas? Don't move,
just calm down.
[PANTING]
OPTIMUS: Easy, human.
Stay there.
He's not going to hurt us.
Weapons systems damaged.
A missile hit your engine.
And we took
it out of you.
You're hurt really bad.
[OPTIMUS GROANS]
I'm just trying
to help you.
You're in my home now.
I'm an engineer.
My name is Cade Yeager.
Cade, I am in your debt.
My name is Optimus Prime.
My Autobots.
They're in danger.
[GROANS]
I need to go.
I need to go now.
How far you think
you're gonna get?
Tessa, come here.
He needs our help.
What happened to you?
An ambush. A trap.
Set by humans.
[COUGHING]
I escaped and took
this form.
TESSA: But
you're on our side.
Why would humans
hurt you?
They were not alone.
My Autobots can repair me.CADE: Yeah.
If you can reach 'em.
What about me?
[BARKING]
I warn you,
Mr. Attinger of Earth,
an alliance is a contract,
and contracts,
like humans,
expire.
On this planet,
we have a saying.
"The enemy of my enemy
is my friend."
I also have a saying.
"I don't care."
So what happened
in Mexico City?
I thought you had him.
Three direct hits.
A mortal wound.
Then your men
allowed him to escape.
You promised me
human intelligence.
Or is there such a thing?
You know,
you've still
never told me.
Why do you want him?
Who are you working for?
Every galaxy I've traveled,
all you species are the same.
You all think you're
the center of the universe.
You have no idea.
Go to the hardware store
and you get the list.
The whole list.
What, you're going
to try and fix him?
He's not a model
train set, Cade.
No, that's right.
He's important.
Yeah,
but important to who?
You can't keep an alien
locked up in your barn.
What are you gonna do,
play with him?
Will you calm down?I'm trying to,
but I just got hit
in the head with
a ten-foot cannon!
If he eats you,
I get the GTO.
Not a word to anybody.
Do you hear me?
Not a single word.
Nobody.
I think we have a lock
on a high-value target.
Special Operations
group is ready.
ATTINGER: What do you got?
Sir, Special Ops
just got a call
from Paris, Texas.
Hard match on the truck
seen leaving Mexico City.
Son of a bitch.
Let's go get him.
Took a hell of a hit,
you know.
The missile just missed
your power source.
We call it a Spark.
It contains our life force
and our memories.
Yeah, we call it a soul.
Scramble Cemetery Wind.
Thank you for your efforts,
ladies and gentlemen.
This room is going dark.
ATTINGER: The exit
is on your left.
I'll take it from here.Okay, let's go.
I'm with Cemetery Wind.
We're on the move.
ON RADIO:  Repeat,
on the move.
[CREAKING]
Cade.
Why are you willing
to help me?
I guess maybe
because you trust me to.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO]
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'm back!
Took you long enough!
My head hurts.
I had to go to the doctor.
I got a welt
on my head
that makes me look
like a fricking
Star Trekcharacter.
[SCOFFS] Whatever.
Look! Look!
SAVOY ON SPEAKER:
We're on property.
PILOT:  Viper 15 overhead.
Angels 1.
[TINKLING]
Dad!
Mr. Yeager,
my name's James Savoy.
I'm a federal agent.
My men and I are
trying to track down
an abandoned truck.
It's a nice spread
you got here.
Too bad she's for sale.
Well, thanks. She's not.
That the truck
you mean?
Afraid not.
You know, Mr. Yeager,
we received a call
from someone
concerned about
this truck.
Oh, no.
That wasn't you?
Only thing I'm concerned
about is you being
on my property
without permission.[LAUGHS]
You know, we got
a rule about people
messing with people
from Texas.
And I don't know what
truck you're talking about.
The kind that
cost American lives.
Search the property!
CADE: What do you mean,
"Search the property"?
You don't have a warrant.
My face is my warrant.
Wait. But if you guys
do find a truck,
we get a reward, right?
PILOT ON RADIO:
Viper 15 holding, point alpha.
[DRONES BEEPING]
AGENT 1 ON SPEAKER:
Charlie team, hold tight.
AGENT 2:  Lock it down.
Open, open, open.Short wall. Short wall.
AGENT 3: Five in. Five in.
ROBOT:  Intruder alert!
Back away from the premises.
AGENT 2: What
the hell is that?
AGENT 3: Just
some dumb inventor.
AGENT 4: Clear.
AGENT 5: Clear.
AGENT 6: Clear right.
AGENT 7: Clear.
AGENT 8: 360. 720.
Heads on a swivel.
Let's go.
There's nothing here.
There's no signs.
We got nothing.
Sir, we have a live armed
missile in the trash.
Live? I carried that
to the trash!
You told me that
was a dud, dude.
I could be dead. Right?
Look. Okay, yes,
I found a truck, all right.
I towed it back
for the parts.
I left it here last night.
This morning, it's gone.
When? Where? I don't know.
I swear to God.
That's as much as
I know about him.
"Him."
He said, "Him."
He knows who
the son of a bitch is.
Mr. Yeager.What?
Excuse me.
You just said, "Him."
Take them down.What?
Ow! Let me go!
They don't know about
the truck! I know!
Just let her go.
What kind of a man
betrays his flesh-and-blood
brethren for alien metal?
Get this guy
out of my sight.TESSA: Get off!
Let her go! They don't
know about the truck.
All right! Load up!
Search the perimeter!
Lucas, you called,
didn't you?
No! I don't know
any of these scary guys.
Oh, God!
You're manhandling a woman!
I'll kick your ass!
Let her go!
Daddy! Let me go!You're not going anywhere.
Daddy![GRUNTS]
No! You're not
taking me anywhere!
I'm an American!
Easy, sweetheart.Okay, okay, okay.
All right. Okay.
All right. I was wrong.
Savoy. Use the girl.
Oh, my God! Ahh!
Now, you got ten seconds.
Where's the truck?
[GROANING]
You're gonna shoot
my little girl?
If I have to.
Please don't shoot me! Please!
Look, I don't know.
I told you everything that
I know! He's gone.
He left. He was in the barn,
I swear to God!
Just let her go!TESSA:  Ow!
Please, please.
He was in there!
Let her go!
Seven seconds.
CADE: I'm telling you
the truth! He was in there!
[TESSA WHIMPERING]
TESSA: Dad!
CADE: Tell him to get away
from my little girl now!
TESSA: [SOBBING] Dad!
CADE: You touch her
and I'll kill you!
SAVOY: You got two seconds.
I need the truth.
TESSA: Please.
Shoot her.
[CONTINUES SOBBING]
[SCREAMS]
[OPTIMUS GRUNTING]
Here I am!
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
[AGENTS SCREAMING]
CADE: Get down!Ahh!
OPTIMUS: Cade!
They're going to kill you!
Get out of here!
[OPTIMUS GRUNTING]
[TESSA EXHALES]
Push right!
Headed to the house!
Come on. Hurry up!
Get in the car!
Let's go!Daddy, get in the car!
Perimeter,
Optimus moving your way!
What's happening, baby?
Who are they?
It's the truck.
They want the truck!
"Who are they?"
Who are you,
and who are you
calling "baby"?
I know you heard me.
I'm her boyfriend!He's my boyfriend!
What?
You're not
her boyfriend!
His name's Shane
and he drives, Dad.
What kind of cars
are those?
They're so scary!
CADE: There's another one
coming up the back!
You gotta try to lose them
in the cornfield!
[ALL SCREAMING]
He's coming up
behind us! Go!
PILOT ON RADIO:  Viper 15,
running on fumes. RTB.
They've got us cornered!
AGENT: Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
[ALL GROANING][AGENT SCREAMING]
Mr. Yeager, this is not
how I wanted us
to meet, okay?
I'm Shane,
and I'm a completely...
And I am not
talking to you!
Drive the car!
[SIRENS WAILING]Watch out! Watch out!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[HORNS HONKING]
AGENT ON RADIO:
Throw 'em some
warning shots!
[CADE GRUNTS]
Man, I don't know how
I'm driving this good.
It's like, today I've gone
to a whole other level.
Road, focus!
Stop talking!
TESSA: Shane, look out!
[TESSA YELPING]
This may be
primarily my fault, okay.
They said they were
gonna bring a check!
I didn't know they were
gonna send a death squad!
Hang on![TIRES SCREECHING]
HOST: Hey, we got
ourselves a winner!
Don's got it over here.
MAN: Look out![PEOPLE SCREAMING]
We lost them!
Good job, stranger
from the cornfields!
The scary cars are back.
Lose them at
the factory, Shane!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[OPTIMUS GRUNTING]
I thought you knew
how to drive
this thing! Go!
I don't think
we're gonna
get that money.
Doesn't seem like it.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Cade!
Take 'em upstairs!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
We're losing them
on the fifth floor.
Do that thing, Shane!You know it.
What do you mean?
What thing?
What we're about to do
is gonna be kind of scary.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Take out your guns
and shoot them!
[GUNFIRE]
They're shooting at us!
[GRUNTING]
Tessa, grab my stick!
Grab my stick!What?
She's got
the best hands
in the business.
Ready, Tess? Pull!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
No! No! No!No f-ing way!
[LUCAS SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS] Oh! Yeah!
LUCAS: Yeah!
Tessa, you are so grounded!
SHANE: Shit!
The rim's cracked.
[HORN HONKING]
Optimus.
Come on, move! Move!
My foot's stuck!
Wait, Cade!
Lucas!Wait! Wait! [GRUNTS]
CADE: Lucas!
Lucas, above you!
Run!
SHANE: Come on,
get in, let's go!
ATTINGER:  I'll bet you wish
you could see
my face right now.
[CLATTERING LOUDLY]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[PANTING]
Lucas, we just left him?
He's gone.
My deepest sympathies
for the loss of your friend.
Stay here till I'm sure
we weren't followed.
We are all targets now.
So we're hiding out now?
That's the plan?
We're taking orders
from a truck?
Well, you got
a better idea?
Hey, move away from her, kid.
Don't...
Keep your hands off her.
All right? No.
You got your ass kicked
by a garage inventor
from Texas.
That goes
on your resume.
Yeah, it goes on
all of yours, too!
Do I look like I'm
in the mood for any
of your shit today?
Washington thinks
we were chasing
a Decepticon target,
but our story falls apart
if we don't find
this Yeager family first.
Yeah, well, what if he goes
to the cops or the FBI?
They know to
hand him over.
His world as he knows it
is gone.
Well, bright side,
you guys met.
Where is he from?
I told you,
he's a driver from Texas.
Texas?
Where, Dublin, Texas?
Shamrock, Texas?
So why does he sound
like a leprechaun?
You'd get your ass kicked
in Ireland for saying that.
Well, we're not in Ireland,
Lucky Charms. We're in Texas.
And so he drives?
What do you mean,
he drives?
Like, for a living?
Yeah. At least
he makes a living.
Thank you.
SHANE: Look,
I race rally cars.
One driver.
One navigator. Her.
By the way,
I'm totally legit.
I just got picked up
by Red Bull.
And just so you know,
my life savings
was in that car back there.
This is not happening.
SHANE: Oh, it definitely is.
How old are you?
20.
She's a
17-year-old girl.
So we can work this
two ways.
One, I punch you
right in the mouth
and you call
the police on me.
TESSA: Dad.CADE: Or two,
I just call
the cops on you
because this is illegal.
She's a minor.
We're protected by
the Romeo and Juliet laws.
TESSA: We dated
for a little while
I was a sophomore, and
he was a senior. It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
We've got
a preexisting juvenile
foundational relationship.
Statute 22.011.What?
Texas statute?
That a real law?SHANE: Yep.
Romeo and Juliet, huh?
You know how
those two ended up?
In love.
Dead. Do your parents
know about this?
Is your dad okay with you
dating a 17-year-old girl?
He took off
when I was five,
but if I ever bump into him,
I'll ask him.
You know, Tessa,
I trusted you.To what?
Never have fun,
take a risk,
be a normal teenager,
like you?
I am your father, okay?
And I have been
busting my ass
to take care of you.
Is that what
you were doing
when you brought home
the truck?
All you had to do
was report it,
and now Lucas is dead.
And my life is over.
Thank you.
You've taken
real good care of me.
TESSA:  Please don't shoot me!
Please! Dad!
They were willing
to kill her.
Then they still are.
[SIGHS]
CADE: Somebody somewhere
gave that order.
I'm going to find
some fingerprints.
[STATIC CRACKLES]RATCHET ON VIDEO:  Please!
No!
I'm an Autobot!
CADE:  Grab whatever
you think we can
use for supplies.
Clothes, anything.
And take that computer.
Let's go.
This is not easy.
TESSA: You know, you don't
suck at everything, Dad.
[GASPS] What the...
CADE: I knew it.
You told me
he was no one.
Well,
this "no one"
has our tech.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[SIGHS]
OPTIMUS ON RADIO:
Calling all Autobots.
Whoa! Oh, my God!Oh, my God!
[TRANSFORMING]
That was insane!
It was awesome,
but it was insane, right?
Oh, yeah! Hell, yeah!
He's back! He's alive!
Optimus is here!
At last.
There is hope after all.
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHING] Yeah.
Mr. Leader of
the Free Galaxy is back.
I knew you'd make it.
I never doubted.
We got your warning.
We've been waiting.
Hell, yeah. Boom time.
We got the gang
back together.
Humans have asked us
to play by their rules.
Well, the rules
have just changed.
Human beings, bunch
of backstabbin' weasels.
Hound,
find your inner compass.
Loyalty is but a flower
in the winds of fear
and temptation.
What the hell
are you saying?
It's a haiku.Cut the crap,
before I drop a grenade
down your throat.
Try it,
you'll be dead.
Oh, please pull it.
Please do it.
You know what, it'll
save us so much time.
Well, raise your hand
if you're thoroughly
disenchanted
with our little
pleasant Earth vacation.
So, who's the stowaways?
Oh, whoa, hey,
what's with the gun?
Stop. Hound,
both of you.
They've risked their
lives for mine.
OPTIMUS:  We owe them.
So, there's been
no sign of any others?
HOUND:  Nada.We are all that's left.
CROSSHAIRS: They're
picking us off, one by one.
We're the pathetic,
dirty foursome.
And you make five.
So that's our
best-case scenario?
Autobot
witness protection?
Hey, Speed Racer,
you're welcome
to leave anytime.
Well, for the record,
Superdad,
I'm not
hiding with you.
I'm hiding out
with that big guy.
Sensei,
with your fate unknown,
Bumblebee has held command,
despite his complete
and total lack of anything
resembling
warrior discipline.
He's like a child.
This child is about
to kick your ass.
He brings us shame.
HOUND: Cage fight.
DRIFT: Smartass.
What's the matter
with them?
Am I the lone sage
who sees through
this puppy-dog eyes act?
It's beneath you.
Yes, I've been waiting
for them all
to dispatch each other,
so I could take charge
with no trouble at all.
Just me reporting to me.
Well, it sure looks like
you've been missed.
Autobots,
Lockdown is hunting us
and humans are helping.
We need to know why.
Well, listen,
I don't know why,
but I have an idea
about who.
This drone I stole recorded
footage of an Autobot raid.
It's in pieces,
but watch what
happens here.
HOUND: Oh,
that's Leadfoot.
CADE: They rip him apart.
Savages.
CADE: And later, this truck
comes to haul him off.
KSI. Kinetic Solutions.
Defense, aerospace,
government contracts.
They designed this drone.
So these government guys
just hunt you down,
and then pass you off
to this KSI?
CADE: The company is
headquartered in Chicago.
That could be where
they were taken.
No way to get inside
without a battle.
Well, what if you had
some human help?
What, are you two
partners now?
Sweetie,
we're targets now, too.
We need to know why or we'll
never get our lives back.
OPTIMUS: Autobots,
I have sworn
to never kill humans.
Big mistake.
But when I find out
who's behind this,
he's going to die.
HOUND: Hooah!
CADE:  There's a full-on
manhunt out for us,
so we have some new rules.
Anyone who has got a badge
is not our friend.
We're gonna divide
and conquer.
You two in charge of stealing
food and the essentials.
And nothing else.
Chicago KSI headquarters
is like a fortress.
I'm gonna find a way
into their top-secret
military wing.
Find something to
blackmail this company
and the government.
We're gonna get
our freedom back.
ALL: Good morning, Mr. Joyce.
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
What was that sound?
That's "the" sound.
That you asked for.
No, I asked for boundless.
Transcendent.
When you walk through
a door in this building,
it should sound like you've
stepped into the future.
[ELECTRONIC CHIME]
Present.
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
Say it.
ALL: Future.
The past is history.
The present is past.
JOSHUA ON PA:
The future is now.
Why can't I get
in touch with you?
Don't you realize
what the Arctic find means?
You know that story
we were all told as children
about a giant asteroid
that struck the Earth
millions of years ago
and wiped out the dinosaurs?
Vaguely.
DARCY: We were wrong.
This metal caused
the great extinction.
How and why,
I can't yet say.
But carbon dating puts it
at 65 million years B.C.
This ore you've
got us digging for
is a lot more dangerous
than you think.
And my people...
Darcy,
I think that you've been out
in the field for far too long.
Why don't we discuss
dinosaurs over dinner?
Ribs?Not a chance.
You have no idea
what's been happening here.
We're about to make
the quantum leap.
A rare-earth metal.
Molecularly unstable.
Industrial uses, none.
And then the aliens came.
And we made the connection.
It's what they're made of.
WEMBLEY:  It's the Holy Grail.
"Transformium."
That's what
we're calling it.
Focus-grouped. Catchy.
Trademarked.Yeah.
This is the greatest advance
in modern physics
since the splitting
of the atom.
It's programmable matter.
And now,
we've mapped its genome.
I.Now you've
mapped its genome.
And now
we can begin to give it
instructions.
WEMBLEY:
This is extremely good.
Watch this.
We can change anything
into anything.
Sensual, almost.
Don't you think?
[LAUGHING]
Do you like music?
The Pill.
Perhaps something
a little more violent?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, my God.
You've done it.
In aerospace,
the military...
We will own
the entire robotics industry.
All exploration.
The oceans. Space.
Everything.
Wembley.
What is this?
The jellyfish commercial
that you wanted.
You said they were
erotic yet deadly,
like women.
I never said that.
Yes, you did.No, I didn't.
I definitely
heard you say it
'cause you were talking
about your ex-girlfriend,
who was sexy,
but a bitch.
JOSHUA: Please
don't eat on the tour.
Is that her?
CADE: Hey, I found a whole
bunch of boxes of clothes.
So, sweetie, you can
get some long pants,
nice, loose-fitting ones,
and lose the
short shorts, okay?
What'd you guys get?
It's protein.
Look, I said
the essentials, okay?
It wasn't easy.
We almost got caught.
You stole mouthwash?
I like to be fresh
when I'm making out
with your daughter.
TESSA: That's funny.
[TRANSFORMERS LAUGHING]
Yeah, that's
not happening ever.
Ever? [CHUCKLES]
This is our military
prototype, Galvatron.
I don't understand it.
This is the fifth iteration.
Why does he keep
turning out like this?
It's just some bugs
in the final render.
JOSHUA: I modeled Galvatron
after Optimus Prime.
Why does he keep
looking like Megatron?
MAN ON PA:  Rendering sequence
is almost finished. Stand by.
Simple coding.
Algorithms!
Math!
Why can't we make
what we want to make,
the way we want
to make it?
Why?
And does that look
like a consumer-friendly
face to you?
And what about that
big hole in the chest?
I think it's bad-ass.
I like it.
Love it.JOSHUA: Well, I hate it.
Oh, here he is.
That bald-headed
Doc Frankenstein.
Ma'am, this is not legal.
This is illegal
experimentation.
Aliens would never
do this to people!
Eat you, kill you,
maybe, but that's it.
This ain't right!
Nobody puts baby in a box!
Ahhh!
[TALKING GIBBERISH]
This is worse
than waterboarding!
This little gentleman
has been translating for us
all the information that
comes from these two heads.
Their history, their science,
everything.
DARCY: Is that Megatron?JOSHUA: Precisely.
Where did you
get all this?
Special government contract.
Now we know everything
about Transformers.
And now at long last
we can build them ourselves.
And we can build them better.
[BUZZING]
[BOTH GASP]
[GRUNTING]
Yeah, that's good, Bee.
That'll get us in.
[BEEPING]
CADE:  A couple times a day,
these guys are moving
in vehicle shipments
into KSI for something
called "scanning."
CADE: Major security
all over.
So our best shot
at getting in
is a back classified
research entrance.
I'm gonna drive in
with Bee tomorrow morning.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Excuse me.
There's no smooching
in front of me, okay?
TESSA: You're so square.
Who even says "smooching"?
I tell you,
no respect.
It's just
impossible sometimes.
Yeah. I went through that
with Bumblebee.
SHANE: Calm down.
Calm down.
You know,
at a time like this,
the idea is to keep cool,
not look cool,
so why don't
you lose the glasses?
About a month ago,
middle of the night,
I thought I heard
noises in my house.
Was that you?
What? Come on. No way.
Don't lie to me, kid.
You see that guy
with the gun out there?
There's so many
guys with guns.
Let's get out of the car
and tell him
we're about to break in
and it's your idea,
'cause I don't care.
I'm old, I've already
lived long enough.
You have a really bad habit
of having these conversations
at the wrong time, man.
You want to come clean
or you want me to
make a mess?
Sir, can I talk to you
for a second, please?
It was me, it was me,
it was me, it was me.
[SIGHING] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Taking it in
for scanning?Uh-huh.
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
All right.
You're good to go.
I'm literally
gonna kill you.
MAN ON PA:
Scanning in bay three.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER ON PA:
We took old, alien technology
and made it better
in every way.
Introducing Stinger.
KSI. We make the world.
SHANE: That is
a bad-ass robot.
CADE: He kind of looks
like you, Bee.[BUMBLEBEE REVS ENGINE]
Here is the past.
And now the future.
They're trying to build
their own versions.
Well, at least they're picking
cooler cars than this.
[ENGINE REVS][HORN HONKS]
[GROANING]
BUMBLEBEE:
You talk to me like that?
SHANE: Bee, stop!
You see what happens
from being a wiseass?
Now get out of here.[COUGHING]
Stinger,
inspired by Bumblebee...
[ENGINE REVVING][SHANE GROANING]
...but better in every way.
Son of a...
CADE: No, no!
You gotta calm down.
SHANE: He's crazy!Stop!
Bumblebee!
Bee, stop going psycho!
[WOMAN SPEAKING MANDARIN]
My delicate flower,
I can't understand you
when you're angry.
Actually, I don't really
understand you at all.
[SCOFFS] Our entire factory
is up and running...
[ENGINE REVVING]Excuse me one second.
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Grease monkeys.
[ENGINE REVVING]
What the hell
is going on here? Huh?
What's with this
vintage crap?
We're not scanning
collector car junk.
What do you think it is
that we make here? Hmm?
We make poetry.
We're poets.
All right? You work
for me, you get one
mistake. One. Understood?
It won't happen again.It certainly won't.
So let's get this
pathetic thing out of here.
And you, too.
So sorry. So sorry.
Let's move on.
Watch him. I'm going to
see what I can find.
Quietly get out of here.
JOSHUA: I swear. I swear.
I can't bear it
when you're angry.
You know
how it upsets me.
Bee, you gotta
calm down right now.
I'm perfectly calm, Dude.
You gotta breathe,
or just do whatever it is
that you do.
I'm calm. I'm calm.
I'm not even touching it.
Okay, I'm barely touching it.
I'm barely touching it.Oh, my God.
Turn back into
a car right now!
Get out of my face,
all right?
MALE ANNOUNCER ON PA:
Our design team
started with
the Bumblebee.
But really,
this alien's design
was decrepit
and, let's face it,
antique.
What the...[BLEEP]
Don't take it personally, Bee. Kind of old and ratty.
You mean ugly.
Oh, hell, no!
No! No!
You think
you're better than me!
Yee-hah!
What did you touch?
Uh...[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ I told you, homeboy
Can't touch this ♪
My office in 15 minutes.
FEMALE TECH:  This is
dissection room seven.
Galvatron, render
postmortem number 12.
Continued head disfigurement
at event number 32.
So what about the deal?
Is it done?
Did you get the Seed?
We get it when the
bounty hunter gets Prime.Uh-huh.
Meanwhile, there has been
a complication.
A what?
[LAUGHING] No, no.
At KSI, we don't
use words like that.
A civilian harboring
the Autobots
has hacked into
one of your mini-drones.
Meaning, they may know
of your involvement.
What?
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
[SIGHS] That was
a little bit intense.
I need more Transformium,
and I need it now,
to build more prototypes.
You tell your alien
bounty hunter
that I have staked my company
on this deal.
And I have merely
staked my life.
Hey, you came to me on this,
remember?
You retire from the CIA,
you get a seven-figure piece
of my company, and you and I
revolutionize national
defense together.
But, Attinger, buddy,
for both our sakes,
you need to deliver
the Seed.
[ELECTRONIC BEEPING]
CADE:  I'm in.
Can you see my camera?
They're melting Ratchet.
They slaughtered Ratchet!
I'm gonna tear them apart!
DARCY: Metal.
Just metal. That's what
I always thought of them.
Well, they're not.
They're living things,
with souls like ours.
Once, I spoke to one.
And you're working
with Transformium?
Uh, yeah,
that's what I do. I am.
I'm out there
digging for it.
There's just not
much left to find.
So that's how badly
you boys need more, huh?
Reduced to melting
evil old Decepticons down.
No.
That's an Autobot there.
The ones who fought for us.
I've got this taken care of
from here.
Right.
Same badge code scanned
at two separate gates.
I'm having the classified area
locked down now.
Check that guy.
Hey!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Freeze!
[BRAKES SCREECHING]Up against the wall.
[PANTS] All right.[HANDCUFFS CLICKING]
Corporate espionage.
That's a very serious crime,
Mr. Yeager.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[EXHALES] Wow.
CADE: Look,
I want a lawyer.
The Justice Department.
Somebody I can trust.
I'm just trying to protect
my family, okay?
Not from your company,
from the government.
Mr. Yeager,
who do you think I work for?
You're trying to
protect your family,
that's admirable.
I'm trying to defend
the nation from alien war.
We've had a taste
of what that looks like,
and we are not gonna
tolerate another. Now...
There is a version
of this conversation
where you get to
go back to your barn,
your daughter gets
to graduate with honors,
and life as you know it
will go on.
You have no idea what
you're involved with here.
Really?
What's the other version
of this conversation?
The one when you send in
the hired help to
murder my little girl?
Or you gonna man up
and do it yourself?
What's your preference?
I'm going to
ask you this once.
Where is Optimus Prime?
[ENGINE REVVING][TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUN FIRING]
BUMBLEBEE:  Come on.
Let's get out of here.
We're moving. Basement.
They're here.
OPTIMUS: Get out!
All of you!
HOUND: Science fair's over,
meatbags!
OPTIMUS: Destroy the lab!Move, move, move, move!
Look out! Look out!
Destroy it all!
Danger! Security breach!
Danger... [EXCLAIMS]
Guys! It's me!
Break me out of
this Frankenstein box!
JOSHUA: Hey!
Hey!
Stop!
That's company property!
They're not your property!
They were my friends.
Oh, you ain't talking
so much now!
You got Hound
in front of you, huh?
Go ahead.
Show us your true colors,
once and for all.
Just give me the word,
I'll splatter him.
Why don't you
tell Itchy Fingers here
that this is all the spoils
of war. Dead metal.
Innovation. What we do
here is science.
Because if we don't do it,
somebody else will.
Because you cannot
stop technology!
We're not your technology!
Let me vaporize his ass.
I broke the code.
I own your whole genome.
The world will know
what you're doing here.
The world?
The world will approve.
We can make you now.
Don't you get it?
We don't need you anymore.
HOUND: That was cruel.
Autobots,
we're done.
We're done? We're not gonna
kick a little bit of ass?
HOUND: I've been itching
to kill something lately.
This is our chance.
We have to stop him.
You have to stop him.
It's never been tested
in the field.
Labs, military bases,
but not on civilian streets.
Down there
a Defense Department
contract
was just attacked
in a terrorist attack.
This is now
a CIA military op.
You're indemnified.
Respond!
Let's go.
KSI Chicago,
closest live sat,
patch it in.
Been an unprovoked
Autobot attack.
Bring up Galvatron.
Transforming Galvatron.
Galvatron coming online.
Bring up Stinger.
FEMALE VOICE:
Stinger coming online.
Let's show
these alien terrorists
what an upgrade looks like.
AIR FORCE OPERATOR 1:
Galvatron and Stinger are
moving to intercept targets.
AIR FORCE OPERATOR 2:  Reapers.
Five targets in the open.
Good picture.
Two miles to intercept.
STANDING AIR FORCE OPERATOR:
200 meters.
Engage.
Transform.
Whoa.
[GRUNTING]
We are programming this,
right?
Yes. Mostly.
AIR FORCE OPERATOR 3:
Systems seem to
have malfunctioned.
Targeting five bogeys.
Engaging rockets.
Missiles away.
Gotta haul ass, Bee!
Come on!
AIR FORCE OPERATOR 1:
Stinger is in pursuit.
Misfire, misfire!
System failure.
Galvatron just fired
four rockets.
Whoa!
They're shooting at us!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!Watch out! What are you doing?
[HUMANS SCREAMING]
BUMBLEBEE:  Argh!
What was that?
We need
a full medical team now.
Possible civilian casualties.
I mean, you got a lot of
people in the crossfire here.
I don't like...
You're making history here.
For your country,
for the world.
Human freedom is at stake.
Innocent people die
all the time.
Come on, Optimus!
[OPTIMUS GROWLING]
[TESSA PANTING]
Tessa!
[YELPING]
Make him fight.
Don't let him go down.
Make him fight!
SHANE: Come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[GASPS]CADE: Tessa!
Tessa!
Tessa, run to the field!
[YELPING]
[GROWLING]
You have no soul!
That is why I have no fear!
[BOTH GRUNTING]You die!
Help me!
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
What is that?
That's my asset.
Pull Galvatron back.
Do it.
[PANTING]
[GROANING]
I got to go get her.
[PANTING]
CADE: Tessa!
Don't go out there!
He'll kill you!
She needs my help!She's hidden!
Optimus! Optimus,
get up, get up!
I can't. Get out of here.
I feel sorry for you, Prime.
Your allegiance
to these humans.
The trouble with loyalty
to a cause is that the cause
will always betray you.
Who sent you here?
Where do you think
you came from?
[SCOFFS] You think
you were born?
No. You were built.
And your creators
want you back.
We all work for someone.
No, no.
No.
It's got her!
She's in the car!Tessa!
No!Tessa!
TESSA: Dad!
Tessa, get out!
Get out!
Tessa!
Get out! Tessa!
Dad, help me!
Tessa!Help me, help me!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Dad!Tessa!
Break the glass!
Break the glass
to get out!I'm trying!
Tessa, I can't hold on!Dad!
Tessa!
Help me!Just break it!
Break the glass!
Tess...
OPTIMUS: Cade,
warn the Autobots!
Dad, help me!
Don't leave me!
No!
LOCKDOWN: Take that human
to the trash.
[SIREN WAILING][HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
ATTINGER: Mr. Secretary.
My team is on the way.
This is a CIA operation.
This is my asset.
Tell the military
to stand down.
Hang on,
I have the White House.
CHIEF OF STAFF:
Agent, hello!
Oh, my goodness. Boy,
is it a flurry of excitement
over here at the White House.
Everybody is super,
super mad. At me.
So, I went over my notes
from our last meeting,
and I'm not sure when
you said anything about
a "giant alien warship
over Michigan Avenue."
Tell the President
this is not an attack.
Remember this ship, Prime?
Built for all you Knights,
you great crusaders,
to explore the universe.
Well, I commandeered it.
It's my personal prison now.
[MACHINES CLATTERING]
[EXHALES SHAKILY]
[ROARING]
[BOTH SCREECHING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING][SCREECHES]
[SCREAMING]
Optimus?
Welcome back to
the Knights' Temenos, Prime.
You have disgraced it.
[GROWLING]
Join your fellow rebels,
fugitive scum.
It's for the rarest
of specimens.
The worst of the worst.
It's taken centuries,
but I've collected all
the Knights but you.
[OPTIMUS GROANING]
The creators want to sweep
their chessboard clean.
I'm slave to no one.
All this species
mixing with species.
It upsets
the cosmic balance.
The creators,
they don't like it.
They built you to do
what you were told.
SHANE: Why hasn't it
taken off yet?
Come on, Bee, it's descending.
You got to get on it!
ATTINGER ON PHONE:
Savoy, mission accomplished.
Lockdown has Prime.
The deal's going down now.
Picking up the Seed
at the recon point.
[SIRENS WAILING]
AGENT ON RADIO:
Nest, Talon.
L.Z. appears clear.
[PANTING]
LOCKDOWN: Much as
I've enjoyed the hunt,
I won't miss your
wretched planet.
Our deal is done.
One Prime for one Seed.
Handle it with care.
I trust your species is ready.
Don't worry about
our species.
Farewell, Earth.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
CADE: Come on, come on!
Bee, come on!
It's a bad idea.
But I'm all about bad ideas.
Let's go!
CROSSHAIRS: Well, let's rock.
This is crazy.
Look, you wanna
cut and run,
you better do it now.
I'm gonna die trying.
Hey, I'm not here to help
you get your daughter.
You're here to help me
get my girlfriend.
Engage dark-matter drives.
Full power.
HOUND: We're behind
enemy lines now.
Lockdown's ship
has booby traps.
Eyes open.
Beware of his bone
grinders, brain blinders,
flesh peelers,
chromosomal inverters,
catatonic sludge,
black hole
trapdoors,
and, of course,
radiation.
We must be quick. We have
the element of surprise.
Let's try to use violence
as a last resort.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, get it!
I kill you!
Kill you!
CROSSHAIRS: Ugh.
I hate those things.
That's freaky.
He's not
alive anymore.
Well, we looked.
They're not here. Let's go.
What? Hey, I'm not going
anywhere without Tessa.
I'm unclear.
What's in it for me?
What's in it for you?
Easy. Let's use words.
What's in it for you
is I don't kill you.
We're getting the boss back.
And the girl. Copy?
Okay, okay.
Very persuasive.
Textbook machismo.
Well, then. We'll need
to sabotage something.
Better hurry.
Because dark-matter drives
are preparing to take off.
Oh, wonderful.
I give us 10 minutes.
Is that what that sound is?
The engines filling up?
Are you telling me
that thing's gonna be...
This is gonna be flying out
of here in 10 minutes?
DRIFT: Uh-huh.Ten minutes?
Could be nine.
Worst case, seven.
Humans, search
the cell blocks.
CADE: We're wasting time,
let's go.
HOUND: We'll find
the center core.
Let's move.
We're gonna stop
this nightmare ship.
[SPACESHIP POWERING UP]
CADE: We're never gonna
find her in this huge ship.
Like a needle
in a haystack.
Tessa!
[ECHOING]
Great. Great.
Oh, that was smooth.
No, that was really smooth,
letting everybody
know we're here.
Now they're gonna
be looking for us.
DRIFT: Better hurry,
Crosshairs,
before we go into space!
Ah. Here's the little
jujube right here.
Hello, Mama.
Who fired the anchors?
Who's on my ship?
We have a loose prisoner.
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
CADE: Hurry up.
We got like six minutes.
We'll find her.
Hold up.
Back up.
Come on, these
things are gonna
find us. Hurry, hide.
[PANTING]
[YELPING]
[GROWLING]
[SCREAMS]
[ARMING]
Whoa!
Weapons!
Come here. Help me.
Hurry, hurry.
Help me up.
There are some weird
sounds out there.
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[PANTING]
[WHIMPERING]
What is that?I don't know.
You ready?
Run.[WEAPONS FIRING]
SHANE: Oh!
[GROANS]
All right, we're not
going down without a fight.
They turn that corner,
and we're gonna take them.
You ready or
you gonna bitch out on me?No, I got your back.
Are you ready?Absolutely.
CADE: Don't bitch out on me.
Are you ready?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Whoa, okay! I surrender!
I surrender! I surrender!
I'm so sorry!
I'm so, so, so sorry!
What'd you do?
How'd you do that?
I have no idea!
You no-good,
chickenshit little rat!
Look at that.
You see that? Oh!
Whoa!
You stay here, Lucky Charms!
[YELLING]
Oh, man. I am
so gonna patent this shit.
[GRUNTING]
Ew!
CADE: Tess!
Dad! Help me!
Hey!
Tess?Tess!
CADE: Come on, move, move!
Tessa!
Shane, I love you!
I love you! You saved me!
You saved me!
SHANE: I know. I know.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you. You saved me.
Oh, yeah,
he saved you. Yeah.
Yeah.
I think you
and Mr. "I Surrender"
have a lot to
catch up about, sweetie.
He saved me, too.
You should have
seen him in there.
I mean, our hero.
Let's go. Now.
Eyes open.
CROSSHAIRS: I almost got it.
HOUND: Big boy coming
through! Move, move, move.
CROSSHAIRS: Whoa!
HOUND: This has got to be
the Supermax.
Watch the corners.
There's a lot of cages.
HOUND: Oh, yeah.
Creepy critters in here.
CROSSHAIRS: I don't want to
know what's in the big cage.
What's this?
Hound, don't do it.
Aw, you don't look
very dangerous in there.
Oh, that's
festering ugliness.
I'm hit! I'm down!
It's melting!
It burns!
Ugh, I think it's acid!
Ah, nuts.
It's just shizzle.
[CROSSHAIRS EXCLAIMS
IN DISGUST]
I hope that's
not contagious.
I got to hurt you now.
You're just too
disturbing to live.
Take that, bitch!
Oh! You're dead.
OPTIMUS: Hound!He's alive!
CROSSHAIRS: Hold on, boss,
we're coming!
HOUND: Optimus, sound off!In here, quick!
Hang on,
we're coming for you!
The arms of this
Knight Ship detach!
We can break free!
It's a separate ship!
Hurry!
Where's the cockpit?
Right or left?
Right!I'm on it, boss.
Hurry. We have no time.
DRIFT:  Sensei.
Let's rock! I always wanted
to fly one of these things.
I'm there, boss!
Hey,
Yeager Technologies,
you gonna invent us
a way out of this one?
TESSA: Oh!
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
I am not doing this.
I am not doing that.Yes, we are.
No, it's good. It's stable.
Come on.
No way.
Sweetie, you know
why I'm here? I'm
here to protect you.
You've done great at that.
I want you to trust me
right now. We're getting
down. Let's go.
Don't look down, okay? Step.
See, it's easy. Come on.
SHANE: Careful,
these cables are starting
to get thinner here!
CADE: Step. Step. There.
TESSA: Oh, my God!
CADE: See, don't look down!
All right? Don't look down.
We're gonna be
at the building in no time!
You okay, Tess?
CADE: Keep stepping.
TESSA: Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, Dad! Oh!
All right, sweetie. You need
to keep moving here, okay?
Come on!TESSA: I can't.
I'm freaking out.
You need to move now!
I'm not moving!
I'm going back to the ship!
[YELPING]CADE: Oh, shit!
You can't go back
to the ship, honey!
Watch me!
You are not 18 years old yet
and you're gonna do
what I say! Now let's go!
[ROARING]
We need to
go this way, okay.
Not that way.
Talk to her, Romeo! Now!
Come on, for God's sake.
Do not start with me.
Oh, my God, what is that?
All right, Tessa.
Don't look back.
Well, don't say that to me.
Now I want to turn around.
It's nothing major, sweetie.
Well, that means
it's totally major!
I'm gonna have to point
this gun in your direction.
It's gonna feel like it's in
your direction, but I'm not.
You better hurry.Are you trying to kill me?
I had to bust my ass to get
up here on this spaceship!
Shoot it!Get down now!
[SCREAMS]
[WHIMPERING]
[CADE GRUNTING][TESSA YELPING]
Tessa, wait! I'm coming
for you! Tessa! Oh!
[TESSA SCREAMING]
TESSA: Oh, my God!CADE: I'm coming!
Hold on!
[TESSA SCREAMING]
[MEN SHOUTING]
[ALL PANTING]
You're the best, Bee!
You are the best.
You damn right!
And don't ever forget it.
You see that? Look at me!
We're off the ship, right?
CROSSHAIRS: Bumblebee!
Bumblebee! Friendly!
Enemy ships are coming in hot.
Get on! Get on!
TESSA: Oh!
Hold your knickers,
I'm punching it!
They got
three ships on them!
I'm giving it the juice!
[GRUNTS]
Come on, Bee,
take them out!
Good move, Bee!
This one's for you,
A-holes!
If you're gonna
do something,
you better do it!
CADE: Come on!
I'm sick of this crap.
You fly. I shoot.
Hey, you better let me
fire this big-ass gun
and make this ship go faster!Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Listen up! Crash course.
Tracer guns.
Punch forward to fire,
slide back to reload.
What?
Punch, hold, slide, repeat.
Wait. What're
you talking about?
I don't know what he means.Good luck.
Where are you going?
To lay some hate.
[LAUGHING]
Say it!Okay.
BOTH: Punch, hold,
slide, repeat.
Punch, hold, slide, repeat.
Go![GRUNTS]
Yeah, I got one! Whoo!
These alien guns kick ass!
Come on, he's on us!
Bee, you gotta move! Duck!
CADE: Bee, fire the gun!
[GASPS]
BUMBLEBEE:  Uh-oh!
SHANE: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[TESSA SCREAMING]
CADE: Whoa, whoa, whoa!
SHANE: That was insane!
CADE: [EXHALES]
Tess, you okay?
[SHANE GROANING]
[SIZZLING]
Okay. Sir?
You better have insurance!
Insurance?
It's a freaking spaceship.
You go get insurance
on a freaking spaceship.
Good luck with that, buddy.
Is this your car? Huh?
Sweetie,
hand me my alien gun.
TESSA: Here you go.[WEAPON POWERING UP]
[PANTING] Come here.
Trust your dad.Okay.
Prepare for
interstellar launch.
We're almost ready
to separate.
We're almost there.
OPTIMUS: Hurry,
he's launching!All over it, chief.
Lockdown will be in
deep space before
he realizes I'm gone.
I'm a sucky pilot,
but let's give it a whirl.
Hell, yeah!
You CIA guys
are really subtle.
What a deft hand. I'm sure
nobody noticed all that.
Look. In a few minutes,
there are gonna be feds
all over this place,
and I don't want them
finding our Holy Grail.
So we're gonna
take all our R&D,
we're moving it to
our China facility. Yeah.
I want you to
bring me the Seed,
but I want you to
bring it to me there.
Mr. Joshua,
I would not describe
your product testing
as perfected.
We have plenty of time for
improvements in China.
Sir, Galvatron. He was...
JOSHUA: A fiasco.
A farrago.
An embarrassment.
And he spoke.
How did that happen?
Do you know what a flaw
is, Wembley? A flaw?
A flaw is
a total failure.
I did not have control
over my prototype,
and I want to know why!
Let's give Bumblebee
the good news.
We got a ship now.
We're leaving.
You humans.
After all we have done.
You don't know what you've
wrought upon yourselves.
CADE: What? What is it now?
What are you talking about?
I mean, I'm doing stuff
out of my league here!
You don't see
who's controlling who.
Within that manmade
prototype I fought,
I sensed the presence
of Megatron.
What, the Decepticon that
started the Chicago war?
How do you think KSI
built those bots
in the first place, hmm?
They had a whole mess of
dead Decepticon heads and they
were downloading their minds!
And I was in charge
of autopsy duty.
No union, no benefits,
no nothing.
They hooked me up
to Megatron,
and that mind wasn't
as dead as they thought.
He fed them the science
and specs!
All so they could build him
a brand-new body.
Then he infected it with
his evil, nasty chromosomes.
They had red, beady eyes.
[EXCLAIMS]
They got all
in my lovely locks.
Oh, I can smell it right now.
Total inside custom job!
KSI might have named the body
the snappy name
of Galvatron,
but that's just
Megatron reincarnated!
You knew this
and you didn't warn them?
Little girl, you can go
to a pretty dark place
when you on death row.
He's been playing KSI
all this time,
all so that he could
manipulate them
into going after the Seed.
[BELL RINGING]
Wait. The Seed?
Those nasty soldiers
that were chasing us.
I saw them board the ship,
and they took something
that they called the Seed.
HOUND: Listen.
Sixty million years ago,
give or take an eon...
Thousands of planets were
cyber-formed with Seeds.
[CHIRPING]
They turned your organic life
into our elemental metals.
Our creators destroyed
your world to make us.
And that's what Galvatron
wants to happen again.
He wants to detonate that Seed
in the biggest city
and kill millions!
He's gonna show the world,
"Baby, I'm back."
OPTIMUS: The blast wave
will incinerate that city
into molten metal.
He'll have enough to build
a massive army
and annihilate
your species forever.
You dumb, greedy bastards
just brought extinction
to yourself.
Not my problem,
though. [SCOFFS]
I'm free at last.
Whole thing worked out
good for me. I'm walking.
We got to get the Seed
before Galvatron does.
JOSHUA:  The Seed
is going to be the
salvation of our company.
We take delivery tonight.
And next month,
we detonate safely
in the Mongolian desert.
And we'll create
enough Transformium
for a hundred years.
Dad, I'm tired of
running and stealing.
Well, a place to sleep.
Yeah. Just
another break-in.
CADE: You know,
when I was your age,
I liked to
get a little wild.
I liked cars, girls.
[CADE SIGHS]
But then there was Tessa.
And when she was born,
all I ever wanted out of life
was for her to be happy
and healthy and safe.
Somehow I thought I'd always
be enough to protect her.
But I won't be.
I'll never be.
So somebody better be.
Thanks for being here today,
Lucky Charms.
Well, thanks for not shooting
me when you had the chance.
Oh, I'll have more.
[SIGHS]
Yeah, I can see that.
We've intercepted the
encrypted communications.
Joshua Joyce is
headed to his factory
in Guangzhou, China.
Hey, big shot.
Your company's
in serious trouble.
You better have
a damn good lawyer.
Really? Well,
you better have
a great one 'cause
you're about to be
responsible for
the annihilation of a city.
Now, you listen to me.
Your tech has been hacked.
Your prototypes are infected.
And now Galvatron
is after that Seed.
Look. I know you have
a conscience
because you're
an inventor, like me.
Do not let Galvatron
anywhere near that Seed.
I control Galvatron.
I created him.
Deep down, I know you know.
Your prototype's
been controlling you.
How fast can that thing get us
halfway around the world?
Very. It's a spaceship.
[SIRENS WAILING]
If we're traveling,
now's the time.
All I want is
to have our life back.
It's your call.
Whatever you want.
Are we safer on our own,
or are we safer with them?
She's a keeper.
Must take after her mom.
I can't argue with that, kid.
Move!
We're retrieving the Seed,
but then we're done
defending the humans.
What, done?
What do you mean,
you're done?
CROSSHAIRS: Means "finished,"
"see ya," "good-bye."
Hijacked part of my ship?
How did you let this happen?
Shut down dark-matter drive,
reverse course at light speed,
and get us back!
Prime's taken my trophy case.
And he will feel my wrath!
Welcome to China.
Put Galvatron in containment.
Tell the techs
do not activate him.
Absolutely, sir.[WOMAN SPEAKING MANDARIN]
Joyce.
I cannot tell you
how enthused I am
to deliver this.
Top of your
alien wish list.
It's yours. Or rather ours.
[LAUGHING]
I will need to
see my advance.
ATTINGER: Five million shares
of the company.
Together, we're gonna end
human warfare.
We're about to build
a fully automated U.S. Army.
Just think of all the American
lives we're gonna save.
[MAN SPEAKING MANDARIN]
So how soon until
we can start
continuous production?
You know, why don't we take
a beat on this for a minute?
I have some new data
that I discovered and...
You're not backing out
on me here?
No, I'm not backing out.
I just...
I want the Seed.
I'm not saying I don't
want the Seed.
I'm just saying
I don't know if I...
If I want the Seed right now.
Good men have died trying
to get that thing for us.
For you.
I know what you did
to get that thing.
A lot of illegal, icky shit.
I can take you down,
too, Mr. Black Ops.
Don't you threaten me.
I started this company
when I was a boy,
with a dream of making
the world a better place.
Funny. I had
the same dream.
Somewhere along the way,
you made billions
of dollars.
So why don't you tell me
what's missing
from my dream? Why don't
you tell me what's missing
from my boyhood dream?
I have served my country
for decades
of unparalleled prosperity
and you are
my golden parachute.
So you are damn well jumping
out of the plane with me!
[GASPING]
[WORKERS SCREAMING]
I am Galvatron!
[BOTH SPEAKING MANDARIN]
What's going on?
Your Galvatron
has gone active.
What haven't you
been telling me?
Find Darcy, and bring a car
around downstairs. Quietly.
We got a factory emergency.
I have to
get you out of here.
What the hell's going on?Take them outside.
We had a deal.
You got what you wanted.
I got what "it" wanted.
My brothers, today
I grant you your freedom.
And from now on, you are
commanded by me.
Rise up!
Go find my Seed!
Detonate the Seed
in the largest city.
Listen, princess. I don't
wanna hear, "I told you so,"
but this is
much more dangerous
than I think.Get in.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Galvatron's hacked
into the others.
What?Joshua.
You have to contain this!Drive, drive!
ATTINGER: Son of a...
Come on. Let's move,
let's move, let's move!
I know how to lose them
in Hong Kong.
I know a military garrison
there that will help us.
Threatening a professional
CIA killer.
Possibly not my finest hour.
I'd like to have
that one back.
Killer? I thought
they were your friends!
No. Not friends. Business.
They gave me this bomb.
Bomb?Oh!
Is there a bomb in the bag?
Yes, there's
a bomb in the bag.
Shit.
CADE:  When you said you were
done fighting for humans,
you didn't mean that,
did you?
How many more of my kind
must be sacrificed
to atone for your mistakes?
Well, what do you think
being human means?
That's what we do.
We make mistakes.
And sometimes out
of those mistakes
come the most amazing things.
When I fixed you,
it was for a reward.
That was it.
That was why. For money.
And it was me
making a mistake.
Without it,
you wouldn't be here.
So even if you got
no faith in us,
I'm asking you to
do what I do.
I'm asking you to look at all
the junk and see the treasure.
You gotta have faith, Prime,
in who we can be.
I'm seriously pissed we're
not getting paid for this.
Well, at least
we get to kill him.
They're not getting away if
I still got him on satellite.
Some genius.
Thinks he can outrun the CIA.
DARCY: Joshua?JOSHUA: Yes?
How lethal is that bomb?
Uh, I don't know.
Let me check.
[LAUGHING]
[WEMBLEY WHOOPING][CELL PHONE RINGING]
I love this! This is
so good. Oh, hang on.
I'm getting a text from
Il Duce in Hong Kong.
"Need to know the Seed's
estimated blast range."
Duh.
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
I'll do the diversion!
Get that thing somewhere safe!
[BOTH SPEAKING CANTONESE]
Killers are coming!
Guys, we gotta go!
Guys, guys...
Shut up! Shut up!All right! I'm sorry!
All right, go ahead,
go ahead!
[BOTH CONTINUE
SPEAKING CANTONESE]
Okay, good?
No, don't go! Wait!
Okay, he's in.
Okay, okay, okay.
I need a raise!
I want a raise.
All right, yes!
I'm sure whatever you want!
JOSHUA: Go, go, go!
Oh, no!
Death is on our tail!
Get out of the way, all of
you! Get out of the way!
I don't want to die like this.
[BRAKES SCREECHING]
Box them in.
[BOTH GROANING]
Hurry, hurry! Come, come.
Okay, yes. I'll follow you
anywhere. You're amazing!
We're going to
get you to the roof.
Good, good.
[BELL DINGS]
Go!
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[READING]
[LAUGHING]
LOL. That's funny.
I can't...
This is really
happening.
A man, me, who is
worth over 20 billion
dollars is now
being chased by CIA
assassins. That's the truth.
[LAUGHING] And in the middle
of a robot uprising.
And I'm carrying what is,
in essence, a tactical nuke.
And the great
thing is I...
The great thing
is that I'm...
I'm barely feeling
any jetlag.
Just stop it!What?
You need to hide on
the roof of this building.
I'll get you
a helicopter extraction.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
I like her.
I find her very attractive.
MERCENARY: He's
definitely around here.
Come on, come on.
[EXHALES]
I got a bike!
Check in there!
These are the CIA assassins
I told you about.
Whoa! Guys.MERCENARY: Let's go.
Hello.
Hey! Okay.
Pick it up.All right. I'm gonna.
[GROANING]
Wow.
Wow. Wow, thank you.
Wow! How did you...
Police training,
prior to my MBA.
I love you.
Get to the roof.
All right, okay.
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHING]
Mmm!
Find my Seed. It's here!
Those prototypes are
after that bomb.
No!
No, no, no, no!
Who the hell's aboard that?
Impossible.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING EXCITEDLY]
Brothers, it's the Autobots!
Shoot them down!
CADE: Joshua!
HOUND: Hey, Baldy!
Hey, it's me! Hey!
Bring it over now! Let's go.
Hurry up, run!
Hurry! Come on!HOUND: Let's go! Move it!
Guys! Come on.
Give it to me now!
HOUND: Looks like
we might have company.
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GROANS]
HOUND: We're hit! We're hit!
ATTINGER: They live,
they talk, we're dead.
Kill them all.
Pleasure.
HOUND: I count ten below!
I thought you said
you had one prototype
get infected.
Now he's got
operational control
of my other 50.
Come on.
Climb, climb!
Surround them.
I may have started
the apocalypse,
but you brought
your family.
And that's, you know,
terrible parenting.
Oh, I'm about one
second away from
knocking you out,
taking the bomb,
and just leaving
you here.
Please,
do me a favor.
Optimus, Autobots,
you alive?
Come on, bitch!CADE: Come on!
[CADE GRUNTS]
HOUND: Evac! Evac!
We're getting flanked!
We got company below!
Oh!
[GRUNTS]
My fat ass is stuck!
Bee, take the shot!
Oh!
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Into the elevator! Get in.Okay.
Come on.
Get down,
get down!
Close the door!
[ALARM BLARING]Won't go! It's not closing!
There's too much weight.
Get back down
to Bumblebee!Dad, no!
Hey! You want me!
Center elevator.
[ALL PANTING]
He's gonna
be okay.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BELL DINGS]
[SCREAMING]
Alien bomb! Alien bomb,
coming through!
Clear the way!
Clear the... Hi, kids.
Coming through, ladies!
Excuse me!
Excuse me, ladies!
Oh, my God!
How do you say,
"Get the fuck out of
the way" in Chinese?
Ahhh!
[PANTING]
SAVOY: That's a long way down.
[GRUNTING]
You've got to
be kidding me.
No!
[GRUNTS]
Come on.
Whoa!
[PANTING]
[GASPING]
I'm coming for you!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
Never should have
hidden that truck.
You should have never
came after my family.
Tough luck, Yeager.
We all have family.
Yeah, but I'm gonna
live to see mine.
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
LOCKDOWN ON RADIO:
Where is my escaped bounty?
Autobots at
this location.
Prime is close.
Do whatever
you have to do.
I intend to.
Darcy!Joshua!
SHANE: We got three more
coming in from that way!
CADE: Bee, where's Tessa?
Dad!
We got a real
dilemma here. Okay?
I created
incredible robots.
It's all designed
to kick that fat
Transformer's ass.
So, really, this is
a no-win situation.
It's over.
That was mean.
Hey! I'm sorry
if you can't handle
the cold-hearted truth!
HOUND:  Optimus, what are
my orders with these humans?
Can I squish the bald guy?
They're in trouble.
Nah! This isn't
our fight!
I'm done being
an underdog.
Underdogs suck!
I say they get
what they deserve.
What's the play, Prime?
It's time for
reinforcements.
Recognize one
of your Knights.
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[OPTIMUS SPEAKING
ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Come on.
All right, come on!
Come on, let's go!
Bee, go!
Come on, we got to move!
Let's go, move!
Where's Tessa?
Tessa, get over here!
Come on.
Get over here!
HOUND: Stay behind me!
I'm covering you!
If I stop covering you,
it means I'm dead.
But that ain't
gonna happen.
Take that!
I'm a wicked
warrior robot!
Goddamn!
Come on!
We gotta move now!
Go, go!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
We got hostiles
coming down the street!
Go!
Bee! Twelve o'clock!
Cover fire!
JOSHUA: We're surrounded!
Hustle, hustle, hustle!
Rocket!
Go, go, go!
Get down!
Oh, this is the
perfect place to hide.
A big glass box!
Nobody will ever
find us here!
That's...
[GRUMBLING]
You've got to
be kidding me.
Legendary warriors,
the powers
that created us
now want us
all extinguished.
We must join forces,
or else forever
be their slaves.
So today
you stand with us...
...or you stand
against me.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
We'll let Prime
figure this one out.
Very wise.
There's no friggin'
way I'm staying down
here with them.
No way. No way.
Only together
can we survive!
[GRUNTS]
Let me lead you!
Oh, no.
I was expecting
a giant car.
OPTIMUS:
Come here!
[ROARING]
We're giving
you freedom.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREECHING]
You defend my family,
or die.
[ROARING]
Autobots,
we're going to
prove who we are
and why we're here!
Ugh, you just want
to die for the guy.
That's leadership.
Or brainwashing,
or something.
No. That's
Optimus Prime.
Autobots, we
charge together!
Now, roll out!
We're getting boxed in!
We're getting
flanked everywhere!
Help me out here!
Kill anything
that moves!
Come on, Cade, shoot!
Come and get some,
you little bitch!
Incoming!
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING IN FRUSTRATION]
I can't believe I'm putting
my life in your hands.
Here. Be my guest.
Take the gun.
No, I don't want the gun.Go ahead, take it.
Come on, you can lead.
No, I don't want the gun.Then stay under there
and shut up!All right.
JOSHUA: You're good
with the gun. So you keep it.
Running out of
guns and ammo.
Ow!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Come and get some!
You're all gonna die!
[SCREAMS]
HOUND: Way to go, baby!
Good shooting, Cade!
I'm like a fat ballerina
who takes scalps
and slits throats!
Got your fortune cookie!
Come here,
you little punk.
Pull the pin!
I'm dying out here!
Here! Take it. Take it!
HOUND: Little help!
Little help![TICKING]
It's live! It's live,
it's live. Take it!
What do you want
me to do with it?
Just throw it!Give, give, give!
HOUND: Got some
bad news, Cade.
I'm out of ammo
and out of ideas.
[GRUNTS]
Faster! Go!
[YELLING][ROARING]
I'll kill you!
[GRUNTING]
Charge!
No, impossible!
They're ruining
everything!
Take that!
[GROANING]
Get off me.
Get up, Hound!HOUND: I can't go on.
But you gotta
keep fighting!
Tank's empty, bro.
There's more of 'em coming.
If you don't get up
and fight, we're
going to die. Let's go!
[SCREECHING]
Attack!
HOUND: Optimus is here!
OPTIMUS:
Bee, jump!
[ROARING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
Uh-oh!
I hate cheap
knockoffs.
JOSHUA:
Awesome job!
You.Who?
You.OPTIMUS: Step forward.
Wait. Why?
Your science will
be responsible for
humanity's extinction.
All right. I know
that you're sensitive
to this whole
bioethical dilemma.
Maybe all he wants
to hear you say is
that some things
should never
be invented.
Ahhh![ROARING]
[HIGH-PITCHED
SCREAMING]
Okay.
We'll lead you
out of the city.
Get that Seed
safely to the hills.
DRIFT: Use this car.
JOSHUA:
He almost ate me!
[ENGINE STARTING]
All right, we're good!
All right,
let's go!
SHANE:
Get out of that seat.
And you're one lucky
dad to have me.
Okay, Lucky Charms. You got
that. You drive. Let's go.
[BOTH GASP]
What did you do?[DEVICE BEEPING]
I don't know. I don't know,
but it's an issue.
Did you press a button?Is it gonna blow up?
I don't know.
Your thing is beeping
now, so you must
have hit something.
Is it gonna blow up?I don't know!
A bomb starts beeping,
that might signal a problem,
you think?
I'm just saying
that it's a steady
blinking light,
which could be
a timer of some kind.
Unless it's
signaling location.
To who?
[SPEAKING CANTONESE]
We've got to call the
central government for help!
[ALL SPEAKING CANTONESE]
LOCKDOWN:
Optimus Prime.
Come to me.
[VOCALIZING][POP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
[EXCLAIMS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[CROWD EXCLAIMING]
[WOMAN SPEAKING MANDARIN]
[SPEAKING MANDARIN]
[ALL SPEAKING MANDARIN]
There's the bridge.
[ALL ROARING]
[ALL SHOUTING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
ALL: Back it up! Back it up!
Go, go, go, go!
Back up! Go back! Go back!
SHANE: Move! Get out
of the way. I can't see!
Shane, drive faster!Okay, just calm down.
TESSA: Shane, watch out!Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Get cover!Back up! Back! Back up!
[GROANS]
Autobots, fall back!
Come on, move! Out of my way!Get out of the way!
Look out!Just hit them!
Just hit them!
[ROARING]
It's a big magnet!
It's sucking up metal
and dropping it!
JOSHUA: Oh!
[PANTING]
Go faster! Go faster!SHANE: Move!
Get out of the way!It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming closer!
Go faster, Shane!
Watch out, watch out!
Watch out!JOSHUA: Look out!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
Oh, no, now it's circling
back towards us! Hard right!
Take a hard right!
[ALL SHOUTING]
Oh, my God!
[ALL PANTING]
Oh, no. No, the magnet.
Get out, get out!
Come on!
Come here! Get out!
[YELPING]
JOSHUA: No, no, no! No,
we're going up. Grab the bomb!
Help me grab the bomb!
SHANE: I can't get
the seat belt off!
JOSHUA: Pull me down!
Catch me!
I'm going up! I'm going up!
Get me! Grab me!
[ALL GRUNTING]
Pull me down! Pull me!
SHANE: I can't
get the seat belt off!
I can't get the belt off!
I'm stuck! I'm stuck!
CADE: Hold the bomb!
I can't hold on!
[GRUNTING]Pull!
Guys, it's crushing me!
[GRUNTING]
[ALL YELPING]
Car!
Move!
Shane!
Shane!I'm good! I'm good.
I'm good.[BOMB BEEPING]
Bumblebee!
BUMBLEBEE:
Hey, you guys!
Yee-hah!
Come on.
Go find
someplace safe.
I'm proud of you.
[SCREECHING]
Get cover!
[ROARING]
Cade!
Autobots, get this
bomb over the bridge
and out of the city!
Dad!
What? Come on.
[OPTIMUS GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[OPTIMUS CONTINUES GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
[SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
I got it!
I'm getting this
bomb out of here!
Give me the gun.
It's you and me now!
Look, Optimus is
out there all alone.
What? You can't
help him.
I have to, Tess.
He came back for us.
Dad, don't leave, please.
Look, I'll find you,
I'll get there, okay?
Dad, no, you'll die!
You gotta stay
with Shane.
You're gonna be okay.
You promise me you're
gonna keep her safe,
rest of her life,
until the end of time!
Promise me!
I promise you.
You're the best thing
I ever made, Tess.
All right, don't ever forget
it, it was always you.
I love you.Please.
Get in the car, now.
TESSA: Dad!
Prime!
[GROANS]
TESSA: Stop the car![TIRES SCREECH]
BUMBLEBEE:
You better listen.No, you listen.
I'm not leaving my dad.
CROSSHAIRS: All right,
we're gonna hold the line,
then block the bridge!
[BEEPING]
[GROANS]
You see, it takes
patience to make a man.
The patience to
watch and wait,
to protect all
of us, quietly,
for God
and country,
without any
recognition at all!
Cade!
There are no good aliens!
Or bad aliens, Yeager.
It's just us and them.
And you chose them.
[PANTING]
Anytime.
[GROANING]
You saved the
human instead of
saving yourself?
You bring shame
upon us all.
[OPTIMUS GRUNTS]
She never listens. Never.
OPTIMUS: I gave
you an order!
Get out of here, now!
Get in. Get in.
Hey, you! Hey!
Cade, get out of here!
This is my fight!
It's my fight,
and you're all gonna die!
[PANTING]
Go! Go!
Come on! Come on!
[GRUNTING]
Yeah! Killer robot, my ass!
[GROANS]
Whoo!
Come on.
Get away,
all of you!
[GRUNTS]
Come on, Tess.
[CONTINUES GRUNTING]
Drive!
You see my face,
your life is done!Oh!
Come on, come on, come on!
[YELLS]
Yeah!
Honor to the end.
You still happy we met?
Always.
[SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE]
OPTIMUS: Hurry!
Quickly! I'm setting off
Lockdown's grenade!
Hold tight!
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
We shall meet
again, Prime,
for I am reborn.
[BOTH PANTING]
Kind of nice being
your hero for a change.
[SOFTLY] You always were.
All my life.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Let's go home
to graduation, huh?
Yeah.
CADE: You're okay, kid.
Come here,
you're all right.
You're all right.
We don't have
a home, Dad.
It blew up.
I might be able to
help you with that.
OPTIMUS: Brave warriors...
[ROARS]
...you are free!
CROSSHAIRS: I'll ride
with you anytime, Spike!
[ROARING]
Did you miss me?
No.
This Seed belongs
to our creators,
whoever they are.
There remains
a price on my head.
I endanger you all
if I stay.
I shall take it where
it can never be found.
Will we ever
see you again?
OPTIMUS: Cade Yeager,
I do not know.
But whenever you
look to the stars,
think of one of them
as my soul.
Defend this family,
Autobots,
as they have you.
Defend
all they can be.
OPTIMUS:  There are
mysteries to the universe
we were never
meant to solve.
But who we are
and why we are here
are not among them.
Those answers
we carry inside.
I am Optimus Prime
and this message
is to my creators:
Leave planet Earth alone.
'Cause I'm coming
for you.