Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
What the…
Bhuvan idiot, I told you
take care of pan cakes
Hey Bhuvan.. Bhuvan.. You.. Idiot
Have it.
I am waking you up since half an hour..
I told you when I was going
for the Shower to take
care of the pancakes
but you are sleeping carelessly here.
Idiot, What if it would
have caught the fire..
You never bother until it’s too late.
What is wrong with you
at this time in the morning.
I’ll burn you with this.
Hey.. Stay away.. I’ll take a revenge
Whatever
Now you have this
Give me a cigarette
No
Please Give me a cigarette
Get ready we have to go for the Delivery
Ahhh.. It burns
please Give me a cigarette
In the bathroom
Blow some air on the wound
Let’s go, I’m ready.
Sorry, I was hungry
What’s wrong with you!
Alright, so I see here you
dropped out of college
for one year.
Can you explain that?
Yes, that's because I had
a serious accident.
I was in coma for around 2 months.
So missed final examination.
Sorry to hear that.
So, I appreciate your time
today to speaking with me,
the interview will be conducted as part
of the university's precast process.
So, during the precast process
we make sure that
the applicant meets our visa
requirements before getting the CAA.
Is everything ok Trisha?
Aa, Yes everything is fine.
Ok... So, moving further,
this check includes reviewing
financial evidence,
your supporting documents
and assessing your general needs
to do this course.
I think someone is in your room
Yes, Jack.
Jack, can you just hold for a second?
Sorry.
What's happening?
I did not expect that.
Dad, I have an interview going on. Just go
Hey, what are you doing?
- Who is he?
- Dad, It’s an interview, You move
What’s going on?
Dad
- My Goodness!
- Hey!
Wohoo, Hi there.
Hey, don’t do this, please
Hello, I’m Anant. Trisha’s Dad.
Hi Anant.
I am Jack Stanlow. Nice to meet you.
I am so sorry Jack, I am So sorry.
Dad, Dad, Move
Please, let me talk to
this gentleman, please.
Sorry, This is very-very embarrassing.
- Dad, this is embarrassing just go.
- Aa aa, Jack I want to talk to you only.
Please ask her not to interrupt.
It’s ok Trisha.
Hey, listen to what he said.
It's okay.
Okay, so quiet now. Don't disturb.
So, you are interviewing
my daughter, right.
Yes
Is she qualified enough to
join your university?
- Move
- Well, We have just started
- Ouch.
She hits me. It Hurts.
I tell you. She is a very aggressive girl.
- Dad why are you, please dad please.
- Of course, You don’t know that.
Jack, I want a little
Favour from your side
Okay, I am listening.
What favour!
I love my daughter very much,
I don’t want her to go away
from me for four long years.
- Okay
- Dad, no
Can you please
- Dad no
- Reject her?
- NO
- Well
DAD!
Hey, I was talking to him
Hello, Hello. What’s the password?
and he started dancing in the background
Can you believe it?
Now whatever I do, even if I Say sorry.
If they give me clearance
as well I won’t be able to go.
People will make fun of me there.
Aren’t you ashamed?
Nope
You are also involved in this?
I came to give this,
He told me to sit for sometime,
Told me that Trisha is
going to be rejected,
So she’ll need your support,
I didn’t know he was going to dance
behind and get you rejected.
Dad, You ruined my career.
Dear, Family is more important or career?
I can not believe you just said that.
Please understand, my dear.
Once you marry, you'll leave home.
And now you want to leave me
for four more years.
My dear.
Please, stay here with me until then.
Please, don't go.
Sorry!
Trisha, please.
This is not done.
Listen
Hey, Trisha listen to me.
Hey Trishu, dear.
She got a little too upset, no?
Dad,
you are so going to regret this.
hums song
Wohoo!
Tell them we don’t want to do
any sort of business with you!
From day one, the project is in loss.
It’s just big.
Where dear?
Yashvant’s birthday
I’ll get back to you in a while.
Come here dear!
Birthday party means,
Booze right?
Hmm
Why do you have to do this, dear!
Not in Gujarat, Do whatever you
want to but not here!
If you get caught you’ll be in the news.
Headlines will be, “Police raid in party
of alcoholic youngsters”,
"Alcohol flows freely in the party of the
sons and the daughters of moneylenders"
blah, blah, blah.
Noone is going to say that
it was a bunch of friends
who were enjoying a birthday party.
Try and understand dear.
I have no issue with you enjoying
yourselves, just not within Gujarat.
Feel free to do whatever you
want outside of the state.
I was going only but you didn't let me go.
Now bear with it.
Please, don’t do it dear!
I'll give your number in case
of any legal trouble.
Take care of it.
Hey! Trishu
What time is it?
Eight O’clock.
Give it to me.
Idiot!
Told you, I’ll take revenge.
Idiot, I burnt my mouth
with that cigarette
Give me some water!
We don’t have it.
I need water.
Sit now.
Stop at a nearby parlour.
It hurts like hell, dude!
Same here.
I got the stuff. Let’s go.
Hello. Yes, man I am waiting.
Where are you?
Be quick. Please.
Yeah, okay.
Today was a tough day sir!
We got the worst of it from S.P. sir.
What happened?
Digvijay is here.
Sir, do you need something?
I am coming.
Sir, Vishal.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Catch him. Catch him.
Hey Virendra, start the bike quickly.
Yeah, but…
Come on start the bike.
It’s not starting.
What!
Let them go! They have escaped now.
- Insert the key, man!
- Bike wasn’t starting!
Get installed the kick first!
It is a self-start.
Call the client
Here, Talk to him.
Hello, man. Change of plans now.
I am sharing a new location,
please be there!
Okay!
Hello, Yeah, blue mercedes 8353, right?
I am right behind you.
Just coming over there!
Give it to me.
Shall I put the bottles down?
Hmm, put them there.
Thirty-five. It’s five short!
You’ll give me the discount, no!
Premium alcohol does not
come with a discount!
It is more than enough, bro!
If you can not afford it then
buy cheaper liquor instead,
There are at least 500 bootleggers
in Ahmedabad!
Afford, really? Do you even know
who you are talking to?
I am talking to the one
who is asking for a discount!
Hey. Nice one, bro.
I liked it, I liked it.
Take it. It’s more than five. Have fun.
- Thank you!
- Yo!
Enjoy!
Hmm.
Hey, why do you keep
following up with him?
I am the one dealing with him, right?
Yes, if both of us follow up,
he won’t do it.
Hey, Happy Birthday.
- Dude, what are you doing!
- Thank you.
No-no, not to you!
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
- Yes, Don’t worry, I will talk to him.
- Hey, Let’s go.
- He will be on calls only.
- Yes, I will.
Yashvant, The bluetooth is not connecting.
Dude, you can’t even
connect the bluetooth!
- Yo girl!
- Let me take a look!
Dude I tried a lot but
it’s not connecting!
- Hey golu, golu, golu, golu, golu, golu.
- Hey, stop hitting me, Stop.
And don’t golu me! I reduced
2 kilograms of my weight!
Don’t you dare to reduce the weight!
Ouch, stay away. It hurts.
Don’t lose weight then!
You look good.
Is it so. Tell her then.
Guys!
Let’s cut the cake first!
Booze first!
Of course, Booze.
Hey, easy.
Ankit, Order the food please.
- Wait I’ll tell you.
- Dude right now?
Dude, if he’ll order it right now then
it will be here after an hour!
So, License cancelled?
Dude, I did it twice now!
Guys, food is here!
Cheers!
Did you notice my nails?
Nice.
Thanks!
I’ll get my drink!
Sure!
What’s up Golu?
Is something Wrong?
What?
You seem down today!
Nope!
Come on, Tell me now.
Nope, why do you feel like that?
The way you are drinking today.
Something is definitely wrong!
Tell me.
You are the only one
who truly gets me, golu!
Hey, Don’t touch my belly.
- Just let me touch it once!
- Nope, Not the belly!
Happy birthday to you,
Happy birthday dear Yashvant
Happy birthday to you
Woohoo!
Oho! One more! Haha
come.
Where?
Come on!
Let’s go!
Okay, let’s go!
Hmm, Yeah
Hey, hey!
Hmm. hmm.
Not me, not me. Hey, hey. No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey, hey.
Umm
No, no.
Hey, hey, hey
Stop, stop, stop
Wait, wait
Have it, have it, have it!
Yes, Mr. Bhavin,
I need 3 bottles, yes now!
I am all alone man!
At least I am safe!
Don’t you dare to laugh!
It is all because of you!
I can not go out dude, Try and Understand!
Bro, do something, it’s my birthday today
Actually I was planning to
invite you for the party, but
Wait a minute
Hello? Hello?
Bro. By any means necessary,
arrange the bottle.
It’s your responsibility.
Yes, I’ll do it. Don’t worry.
My bootlegger is out of reach
right now, talk to yours!
Can’t even arrange a single bottle.
I’ll do it myself!
Oh, Miss over-smart!
It’s on our reputation now!
Come on, call someone!
Hello,
Bro listen, I need a bottle right now!
Hey, Sujal. Listen, no! I need a favour.
Yes, Mr. Sujal. How are you?
I am all good!
Yes, I have it in stock!
When? Now?
Where?
I am enroute for a delivery.
I’ll be there after an hour
or two, is that okay?
Sure!
Yes
Yes, I’ll be there within half an hour.
But listen!
It is very strict outside!
Can you pay double?
Done?
Done, Send me the location,
I am on my way!
Where?
It’s nearby only.
- But where?
- Stop if you see any bikes!
Sure, will catch up soon!
Enjoy your party.
The bottles will be here
within half an hour!
Wohoo!
I know this guy, I know that guy.
I have this much contact,
I have that much contact.
You can’t even arrange
a single bottle! What a shame!
Learn it from your own sister!
Bro, Arrange the bottle right
now or this will be it for us
Hello Mr. Oversmart! Cut the crap,
the bottle will be here
within half an hour.
This will be it for us!
There, stop over there.
Bro let’s deliver to that old pimp first?
He is paying us double
Get another bottle
and give it to that old dude.
Old pimp will be furious!
Let him. What can he do?
Clear?
Yes. No-one is there. Go for it.
Hmm.
Come on. Fast.
Move, move.
Done?
Try the kick. Kick it.
Go, go, go. Let’s go, quick.
Alright I am leaving now.
Shall I scratch that for you?
Excuse me!
At Vinita’s
Which Flat number?
I don’t know that.
Call them and let me talk to them!
Hello, Vinita?
Yes, Who’s this?
Yeah, I had a word with Mr. Sujal.
I got your gift.
Okay, Come upstairs!
Yes, Talk to this sweet bodyguard!
Here!
Hello?
Yes, Mr. Naamdev. Send him upstairs!
Who’s this?
It’s Vinita. Now send him upstairs.
Okay madam!
Enter your details!
You can scratch peacefully now!
Huh
Seriously!
Why did she call him upstairs!
Is he even a bootlegger?
Finally!
Ankit, get some ice please!
Yes, I was going down only. I’ll get them!
Bro, Give him cash!
Thanks, Great party man!
You have something on your shoulder!
It didn’t bite you did it?
Nope
Enjoy Your party!
Guys if you don’t mind can
I stay here for a while?
There was a checkpost nearby.
Nobody followed me,
I took care of that but just in case!
If you guys are okay with it!
I’ll settle somewhere here!
No-no, I mean the checkpost
would have been cleared by now!
No-no. You can stay.
Why do we have any problem? Have a seat.
Feel free to join us, have a seat!
Thanks
Hii, Ruchika. Nice to meet you.
Vishal
You want to sit?
No-no, He will find his place. You sit no!
Whose birthday is it?
His
Happy birthday bro
Thank you
Hey, pass me the bottle!
Whiskey?
No, thanks
What would you sit ideally? Have it!
Sure
What’s her name?
Trisha
On the rocks!
Cheers!
Why is he sitting here?
Keep your eyes open for a while!
You’ll get to know everything.
So
Umm, Nothing.
So, what do you do for a living?
Cheers!
Hmm!
See my nails,
I got them done at a spa. So shiny no!
Nice!
Dude, Can I get fit like you in a month!
Yes, Of course!
Cheers!
Man, this is the smoothest
scotch I ever had!
Thank you!
He is not the Master distiller!
Bro, Checkpost would definitely be
disbursed by now, just in case if you
Sorry, I’ll leave.
Hmm
At least complete your drink.
No-no, I’ll leave.
I insist.
I was leaving only!
Let’s have a drink together!
You want my number?
I’ll get you the desired
brand of whiskey. Anytime!
It’s okay. I drink occasionally.
I doubt that.
Yeah, So where was I?
Yes I deliver the goods on
the vehicles which I steal
so that I can leave them wherever I want!
You steal as well!
Motto is to deliver, not to steal!
Cheers
Just a minute!
There was a deadend so I got caught,
then I got beaten by the crowd
till they got fed up.
So why did you continue
even after this much trouble?
Why didn’t you think of something else?
What else can I do, a regular 10 to 6 job?
I want easy money,
Two hours of work a day.
I only keep premium stuff, I earn good.
I am gym-freak,
you just got the demo of that!
I love to dance so I dance the whole day!
Meet Mr. Khambhata and Mrs. Khambhata.
They go out for a spin.
They are moving on, moving on, moving on,
moving on, moving on, moving on,
and suddenly they change their posture
What are you doing!
Let’s do it together!
Hey, come on. It’ll be fun.
No, no, no.
You are a party saviour!
You know, you are doing a noble job.
Wait Trisha. Wait, wait, wait.
Dude, how much liquor did you have?
Chill!
I have good capacity okay!
Okay! Let's check it out!
I won!
You don’t have a good capacity
and you are a bootlegger!
If horse be friends with
the grass it’ll be starving.
But everyone should get
a chance, come on baby!
Now, win this!
Watch this!
Okay!
Whoa!
I also want this. I also want to do this.
No. No, no, no.
What is going on here!
Behave Vinita.
- What are you doing! Get up now!
- Leave me man!
Watch out, be careful.
Flirting with him so directly!
He is a bootlegger, remember!
But he is hot!
Have some standards!
Be careful there.
Hello
Ask this bastard to leave man!
What happened!
He is a showoff and he is
showing off his swag..
..since he has been here!
Do whatever you have to
but make him leave this place,
It’s been two hours now!
Woohooo
Woohoo
Guys, cheer!
Woohoo!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
25,26,27,
28,29,30,31,32,33,
Woohoo
Now my turn, My turn
After one drink! Please.
Dude, you are guys here to
do this on my birthday!
Oh, sorry bro, I know it’s your birthday.
I’ll play an epic song, the whole
surrounding would be set!
Whose phone is connected?
Mine, mine.
Give it to me!
Hey, that’s my favourite song
Oh mama morenita
Give me some canelita
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
Oh
Ohh my sweet heart
You are my monalisa Si sanorita
My darling give me
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
I wanna be your beast be my Beauty
wanna touch your body so electric
I wanna be your sin and the preacher
wanna make you my love forever
Me your love
I long to touch your lips
I long to kiss your lips
Give mercy feels like I'm drowning in you
Oh mama morenita
Give me some canelita
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
Oh
Ohh my sweet heart
You are my monalisa Si sanorita
My darling give me
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
I wanna be your beast be my Beauty
wanna touch your body so electric
wanna be your sin and the preacher
wanna make you my love forever
I wanna be your beast be my Beauty
I wanna touch your body so electric
I wanna be your sin and the preacher
I wanna make you my love forever
Me your love
I long to touch your lips
I long to kiss you lips
Give mercy feels like I'm drowning in you
Oh mama morenita
Give me some canelita
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
Oh
Ohh my sweet heart
You are my monalisa Si sanorita
My darling give me
Never tasted taste like sunshine
Sweet & spicey both at the same time
Wohoo!
So, how old are you!
Tell me please!
Tell me no!
Twenty-one!
You are younger than me!
Yes, aunty!
Hey!
I kept this beard so that people
would take me seriously.
Or else I would get lollipops instead
of money against the liquor!
I need to go to the washroom.
Do you need any help?
Let me help you, let’s go!
Dude, I didn’t want to be here!
I was frustrated so I thought
let’s have a couple of drinks!
Frustrated? Why is that?
Oh god, I am so high.
Trisha
I am fine, fine, fine.
Are you okay?
Yeah I am fine!
Don’t lock the door!
Yeah!
Hey, help me!
Yeah sure!
You should sleep now!
Huh, What is sleep!
Did you sleep or what!
Shh!
Whoa!
I want to see your abs!
What!
Come on, show it to me!
Sure! That's why I got them!
Hey
Morning!
Morning
Okay!
Umm!
Done?
Just a moment!
Okay.
Done.
Listen, I want to…
you get that done first!
Umm
Don’t ask for my contact number.
I
We had a moment and I really enjoyed it.
No, seriously.
I enjoyed it but it won’t happen again!
Our paths will not cross again!
So if you ever get excited
for this then I suggest you don’t!
Don’t track me please!
Not on calls, office, home, social media.
Not at a single place!
Please don’t! Got it?
Actually! I was about to say this only!
I have a different lifestyle
so we won't fit in!
Thank God, you relieved me!
Shall we leave?
Sure!
Just a minute!
Does anybody know about us?
I went to collect my bag,
Everyone is asleep!
Let’s get out of here then!
Yeah!
This is weird!
I forgot your name!
Don’t you dare laugh!
I was drunk, that's why I don’t remember!
I didn’t say anything!
I can see you laughing!
You think that I do this on
a regular basis!
It’s not that!
Forget it.
Hello!
Oh. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Will you stop laughing?
I’m trying.
Oho, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Stop.
Okay, bye, see you!
Sure?
I mean I’ll never see you again. Bye.
Bye.
Is Sneha inside?
Yeah, but there is a patient as well!
Hello, ma’am!
Do I need to visit next week?
Only if you have to! Else you’ll be
fine with these medications!
Okay, thank you!
Couldn’t you wait for a while!
Patient gets awkward!
You think I will wait!
Of course not. Tell me.
Periods!
When was the last date?
Last month 25th.
So, It’s been more than 20 days!
So, were you sexually active?
Trisha.
Let’s check it!
No, no, no.
Please give me a moment.
Trisha
Dad should not know this!
Happy birthday to you,
Happy birthday dear Aarohi
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday
Thank you!
It’s not your fault.
Sir
Good morning dear.
Why are you back early?
Dad, I wanted to discuss something!
Have a seat dear.
Go on!
Anything serious, my dear?
Dad, I
Go on!
Dad, I wanted to take a tough call!
Just a minute,
are you planning to take admission
in any new university?
No!
So you are not going out of India, right?
No.
Then it’s all good.
You can take any call you want.
I am fine with it!
Dad
What happened?
I’m expecting a baby.
What?
You’re joking, right?
You are pregnant!
How? I mean with whom?
Where? When?
I am sure Ankit will be the one.
I haven't liked that guy since day one!
No, not Ankit
If not Ankit then who?
See, It could be a mistake as well.
All these kits are not
hundred percent accurate!
Let’s get the lab reports.
We will talk to Sneha!
Sneha, herself confirmed it.
You already met Sneha!
Then why didn’t she tell me any of this!
How long has this been?
Around forty-five days
But you are in town for one and half
months then with whom did you?
I can’t tell you that!
What do you mean by that?
You won’t like it!
What is there to like?
Because he is not okay!
Then why did you…
What are you going to do now?
I want this child!
So you want to get married!
Ohh that’s fine for me.
You can marry whoever you want to!
Feel free.
I don’t have any problem with that!
I can’t get married to that guy!
What rubbish! What do you mean by that?
Because, because…
Is he already married?
No!
Do you even know who it is?
DAD!
Abortion is the option!
No.
Are you out of your mind!
We don’t have any other option.
Abortion is the option!
No!
One thing I am sure about is that
I won’t abort this baby.
I will bring this baby.
This is my child.
It’s my flesh and blood dad!
What are you talking about!
Do you even realise that…
Sorry
Listen to me dear
Sorry!
For Bhuvan!
Sir
Sir!
Hmm?
For Bhuvan
Hmm.
Here.
Bhuvan
Hmm?
Sign over here!
Sir?
Hmm?
Sir, Do you have a minute?
Go ahead!
Sir, I lost two bottles
which cost me around 20.
Lawyer will have 35.
So, overall it cost me fifty-five!
So?
I’ll pay a fixed amount to
you every month!
Sorry sir!
What I was saying is that I’ll have
to pay somebody then why not you!
Sorry sir!
Forget it sir. Forget it. Cancel, Cancel.
Vishal, I am leaving!
Just a minute, sir!
It’s Thirty-five.
Be careful next time.
Yes.
Let’s go, idiot. Where are your slippers?
I lost them in the chase!
More 100 bucks!
Idiot, couldn’t you run faster!
- Stop hitting me now!
- Shut up, Let’s go.
Did he agree?
I gave him the offer,
but he didn’t answer!
Leave him then!
Trisha!
I upset you, didn’t I?
I am Upset!
Sorry!
Should I tell him?
To that guy?
Means?
Does he not know?
Do you want to accept him?
No!
It would not be fair if
I don’t tell him about this.
The sort of feeling I have for this child,
he too can have that!
See,
if you tell him and if he gets upset
or he gets scared then I know
what your reactions would be!
But
what if he agrees to accept this baby?
What would be your reactions then?
What would you do?
That’s why I am here.
What should I do?
Should I tell him?
Are you guys in touch?
Nope!
Did you two have a fight?
No!
Then what can I suggest! I don’t know!
I also don’t know dad!
Tell him.
We will take the decision on
how he would react!
Go tell him!
Sure?
Sure, Sure!
Ok
I’ll start looking for him tomorrow.
Find him?
You are not in contact with him?
Nope!
How many times have you guys met?
Once!
You met him only once and you
Good night. Dad!
This is a R3 zone.
So there won’t be any sort of construction
on this side so your view will be
Excuse me!
Um, sorry!
This is the parking and it is hydraulic
so...
Excuse me
Trisha I am with a client,
I’ll call you back.
Vinita, send me the number
of that bootlegger!
What!
Dude, at Yashvant's Birthday
there was a bootlegger right.
Give me his number.
Trisha! I will call you soon.
Hey!
Come on!
So I was saying, parking is
Vinita, Listen Come on!
So you don’t have to
Sorry, I have to take this.
I am pregnant!
What!
Hello!
Hii, Sujal.
Yes Vinita.
What happened to your voice? Are you okay?
I am in hospital.
Why? What happened?
Vinita, come to the point!
- Yeah
- Who is this?
Sujal, I need that bootlegger’s number.
Have a look at my condition, I
am hospitalised. Stop drinking!
Please give me his number, Sujal.
Quit drinking Vinita.
This drinking habit of mine
has cost me a kidney.
Quit it.
Dude, We need his number
from you, not advice.
Who is this!
Trisha, My friend.
She is also on the call.
Hii Trisha
Hii. Give me his number.
I don’t drink anymore!
Good for you, Now send me his number.
I’ve deleted all the bootlegger’s numbers!
What!
Shit
Yes. Liquor, cigarettes,
I’ve quit them all.
TO be very honest. You should stop it too.
Vinita, now if he has
started lecturing again.
I personally, will take his
second kidney out of his body.
What!
Trisha, Please.
Sujal, is there any other way?
How can we contact him?
Do you have his address?
No!
He used to deliver only.
But now I have deleted all the numbers!
What was his name?
I don’t know his name!
I saved their number as bootlegger 1,
bootlegger 2, bootlegger 3.
Quit alcohol.
In which hospital you are in?
Give me your address. Now.
Oh god!
Trisha, now what?
Trisha, can you hear me?
Yeah, Yeah. I am here only.
When was Yashvant’s birthday?
12th July.
- This is 11th
- 12th would be right after that!
Somewhere around 1 am
What is this?
Excuse me, can you read this out
for me, Please?
I couldn't get this madam!
So, if anyone just makes any
sort of design in the register
and they can go in the building, right?
Sorry madam.
What sorry? This was the last hope man!
Trisha, You can find him
on FB or Instagram!
Bro! I don't even remember his name!
What do we do now?
Shit man!
There is just one way left now.
Just keep this with you.
Trisha?
Hey umm… listen do you have any…
Any boot-bootlegger’s number?
Hello
Hmm. Go on.
Yeah. How are you?
All good! Whose this?
Do you have that umm…
What?
What do you call it? Stuff?
What stuff?
Yeah, Yeah. I mean, I mean umm,
Do you have
hmm?
We drink it no?
Bottle?
Bottle! Yes bottle, Liquor umm whiskey.
Do you have Whiskey?
Yes, I have it! Do you want it?
Yes, I want it.
Tell me the address, I’ll deliver it.
Address!
Give me your address madam!
Alright, I am,
I am sending you the address!
Hello?
I have reached over here but
there is a watchman outside.
Yeah, I am, I will be there in a second!
Do you have any bootlegger’s number?
Do you have any bootleggers number?
Do you have the number of someone
who keeps the premium stuff?
What is a bootlegger?
Let’s party together!
Bro, Come over here. The Party is on!
Call him. He’ll deliver at your place.
Is he hot?
Yes. Mohit gave me your number.
Do you have anything?
Ask him to call me first!
But Okay!
Hey Mohit, You need to call him first!
Yes, I am sending you a number. Ask them.
Talk to him, talk to
her-what's the deal here?
Am I in a government office or what?
Yes, Mr. Bhura. Mr. Bhaga
gave me your number.
Do you have anything?
No, nothing right now.
Yes, Did you get a call from Mohit?
Alright. Sending you the address.
What do you want? I’ll get it for you!
Yeah, Sending.
Yeah, Order two for me as well.
I’ll collect it later.
Bro, My dad has the permit no!
Tell me what do you want?
Do you have any bootlegger’s number?
Alcohol is so old-fashioned Trisha!
It’s time to go green.
I will not deliver that far!
Do you want to do the business or not?
Hang up the phone.
Are you a bootlegger?
I did not expect that question from you!
Nowadays women can do anything.
Feminist!
Send Hii on Whatsapp.
Then I’ll send you the coordinates,
come over there!
Dude, I’ll pay extra but
deliver at this address.
Yes brother. I am sending you
an address. Send a bottle over there.
I'm not some bootlegger!
You've got the wrong number,
I'm a teacher.
Your constant bothering is
incredibly frustrating.
Hang up now before I involve the police!
Oh shit. Sorry, sorry!
My man will deliver it.
You can pay via Gpay!
I will pay on Gpay, send your man!
Hello?
Yes ma’am. I am about to reach.
I am coming down in a minute.
Okay.
Mummy
Pay it on Gpay!
Hey, Did the police follow you or what?
I am not in the town.
I can come tomorrow if that’s okay!
Call me once you are back!
Okay
How do I figure out his name?
Champion
What?
Champion, Champion.
Champion of what?
Champion. That's when we pop
the bottle and it sprays everywhere!
Champagne?
Yeah, yeah. That one.
No, that’s fine.
Find him.
Brother, do you have any
young bootlegger's number?
Am I not young enough?
Howzat?
I’ve beer only, do you want it?
Bro, you must expand your business.
Scotch is more profitable. Anyways!
And Ronaldo passes to Rooney,
Rooney, Rooney gets to
Ronaldo and Ronaldo running
to the nets and YEAH!
Find him!
Send me the number of bootleggers!
What? Just one number! Come on!
What the hell!
Ma’am this is not the right time.
Police is very strict nowadays.
Don’t worry about the police.
If you get caught, call me,
I’ll take care of it.
Scaredy-cat
Do you have anything?
Yes.
Cut the crap, Do you have abs?
What's this?
You're delivering liquor
with your entire family?
Have you no shame?
The woman is a stand-in
wife so are the kids!
This is child labour,
run before I call the cops!
Where are you!
The minimum quantity would be two!
So what do you want to do!
Fine, I’ll have two!
Sorry. Sorry
Whenever I am going to see you,
I am going to kick you. hiya!
Yes brother, Do you have anything?
Yes, I have everything in stock,
what do you want madam?
Should we deal on video call?
Yeah, yeah. Sure!
What happened? You don’t need anything?
Nope!
He died due to poisonous alcohol!
Hey, hey. Please don’t cry!
Poisonous alcohol!
Ohh!
Hey you were the one on
video call that day!
Yes, I’ve got two different
contact numbers!
Eww. Stay away.
You stink and you are drunk.
Aww. Did you feel bad!
Where are you… yeah!
Bootlegger with abs in ahmedabad
Woohoo! Strike!
Oh no! This also tastes like liquor!
Yeah, Just a minute. Just a minute.
Yes, Mr. Kamlesh.
Ankit gave me your number!
Dad, Why didn’t you knock
before coming in?
What’s that?
Dad
What are you up to?
I won’t have a single drop
from all of this!
This is a house or
I am not frustrated!
What’s all these!
I am mentally fit and fine!
This many!
I'm doing everything after thinking only!
Are you out of your mind?
Don't ask me anything
- I can’t even ask why?
- No!
- What’s all this?
- Nothing
- But
- Just
- Are you okay?
- Zip
- Let me. See, talk to
- Zip.. shhh. Zip
- This
- Zup
I am Easy
- Listen At least
- Stay calm and sit.
You don’t have to worry!
See, Trisha.
- You can talk to me, that’s okay!
- Hello. Yeah. yeah.
- Listen
- Shh!
- Listen dear
- Yeah, yeah. I am coming downstairs!
- Trisha!
- Yes yes.
This is not done!
Sit here. I’ll be back in a sec.
- Trisha dear, Trisha
- Hello
Umm
Finally
Oww
Okay, okay, okay.
Why?
Trisha, Your hand!
Where did you find my number from?
It was a roller-coaster.
Was it me or my performance?
What?
Where are we headed?
Just!
There is a hotel nearby.
If we want to go there!
Oh god. What is happening!
What’s your name?
Don’t laugh, tell me your name!
Vishal
We are here to talk only!
After a while!
Okay, madam!
I wanted to discuss something!
Yes!
Last time when we met, whatever
happened between us!
Do you remember that?
Yes, Of course.
I remember everything in detail.
I just remembered again!
Oh, Stop it!
Can’t control. Come on, let's go!
You also enjoyed it, no?
I want to discuss a very serious matter…
Stop laughing!
Okay
Relax
I am relaxed only!
I am pregnant!
Congratulations!
How?
What do you mean?
So, on that day?
I am the one?
Yes!
Confirm?
Why else would I be sitting here with you?
No, I mean are you sure it’s me?
I mean maybe after that you might had
I’ll kill you!
No, I am sure it’s me! Of course.
I want this baby!
You are very brave!
I know!
I took this call after giving
a lot of thoughts.
I am too young… only 21.
If someone starts calling me dad,
It would completely blow my mind!
What!
Yes! I am not even settled
and with that if I had to marry
Hey
Then there will be more
responsibilities on me, to meet them..
..I’ll have to sell 5 more bottles which
means there will be more risk
More risk means
- I’ll be beaten by the police!
- Vishal, Vishal!
Listen dude! I don’t want to marry you!
What!
We are not each other’s type!
Neither I have any expectation from you
nor do you have any responsibilities.
So chill.
I am capable enough.
I’ll manage all of this by myself!
The reason to share this with you
is because this is your child as well.
You might have some
feelings toward him/her!
I think you should know this. That’s it!
I need a cigarette.
It was a bit too much to take!
Do you need one?
Ohh Sorry!
I don’t know what I am just rambling!
Fraidy-cat
Use protection bro!
As expected!
Coffee.
I am in!
But I won’t stop delivering liquor!
And you’ll have to explain
everything to me because
I don’t understand any bit of this.
I’ll follow whatever you’ll say!
It's tasteless!
You
Tomorrow I’ll have to go to the hospital!
I’ll be there!
Okay!
You see that blinking over there!
That’s the baby’s heartbeat!
Vishal
What would be the expected date?
May I?
Sure!
Vishal, relax!
Yes!
Stay aside. Let her have a look!
Sorry.
I couldn’t find the expected date!
What are you?
Sneha!
Mid-april.
Mid-April
It’s okay.
Let me help you!
I’ll manage!
Okay!
Do you need help?
What!
How much?
- Hey
- What exactly are you?
Vishal, Keep your wallet inside!
- This is too much!
- I am so sorry sneha.
I am paying, no? How much is it?
- Vishal, Let’s go!
- Who is this Trisha?
I am so sorry Sneha!
I should be the one
who pays for all of this!
Keep that wallet inside!
Let’s go. Open the door.
- Yes, yes. Stop pushing me!
- I am so sorry.
What was that!
Why? We need to pay the doctor no!
She is my sister!
Real sister?
No. Cousin!
So, That’s why she refused the money!
You don’t ask the doctor about the money.
You have to pay at the reception desk!
Too much drama!
My doctor directly takes money out of my pocket!
Bye, Bye!
Trisha!
What!
Just a minute!
Do we need to ask the doctor
or if you are aware that
You know what I mean, right?
No!
Can we have s
Sex!
Oh Yes!
You
I’ll get my bike!
Oh, We are going in the car!
Hey, Get lost!
Get lost?
Are we doing it or not?
Sex!
Hey Yes or no?
Everything is okay, no?
Health is fine, right?
Okay, Name?
Did you get to know his name?
And the work profile?
You might have got some idea
from the appearances, no?
Alright, I’ll talk to you later!
Sneha it was!
Yes
Who else could it be!
I want to meet him!
Dad!
And what would you do after meeting him?
Nothing. I just want to see him.
What after that?
This is nice!
You can take him with you for the checkup
and here I am asking you
that I want to meet him
and you don’t want me to meet him!
He came there willingly. It was his call!
This is my call.
I want to meet him.
You will be depressed after meeting him.
How can you do something
like this with someone…
whatever it is. I want to meet him.
- I need to talk to him
- I want to meet him.
- But I have to
- Call him here.
- Dad, Let me ask him first!
- I told you, I want to meet him.
Whatever happens I want to meet him.
But Okay, fine. Don’t shout.
Don’t ever want to listen to me.
Sneha can meet him.
- Everyone can meet him but me
- Okay!
I want to meet
I will ask him. Only if he is comfortable!
Okay!
You are just impossible!
Hii
What were you doing inside?
What sort of question is that!
Have you got your bike?
Yeah, Here it is.
Let it be here. Let’s go in the car.
Sure. It’s not even mine!
Dad will be in shock!
What? Dad what? I didn’t listen.
Dad wants to meet you!
Only if you are comfortable!
Sure. Let’s meet him. What is this about?
Sit in the car. I will tell you.
Yeah, but at least tell me
what is this about?
Just a minute!
Does he want fitness tips?
Be quiet!
- Does he too want to see my abs?
- Easy, I’ll tell you.
I’ve already read this.
This one is
Dad
Yes
Vishal
Hello uncle!
Hello!
Let me give you a hand getting up!
Ohh, Ouch!
Are you okay?
I hope your muscles are fine!
Have a seat Vishal!
Yes!
What is this guy!
Button up your shirt!
Vishal
Vishal!
Hmm
Let it be. It is fine.
Looks like sultan of stupidity only!
Sit!
It was very claustrophobic!
That’s fine!
So what do you do?
I am a
Vishal, Tea, Coffee?
Yes
Right. We have to offer tea-coffee!
Hmm.
Vishnu!
Yes sir!
What would you have? Tea coffee?
Vishal! Tea Coffee!
Tea
But it should be the dose of dynamite!
Are you clear?
It should be the dose of dynamite!
Yes sir!
I’ll have a normal tea!
I don’t want to blow anything up! Okay!
What do you do?
I am a bootlegger!
What! Boot…
So, You sell liquor, Right?
All Ahmedabad, 24x7
Hey, Easy!
I only keep premium stuff, uncle!
Only premium stuff! Did you hear that?
Yes Dad!
Oh, right. So that’s
why your room was full,
all of that was because of him!
Absolutely, Just for him!
What else do you do!
Not much! Gym,
Body-building, dance. That’s it.
Hmm.
Gym, Body, Dance. Nice!
Give Him the dose of dynamic.
He wants to build muscles
like a Greek god!
Which one is mine?
This.
Is tea okay?
Or she has too much dynamite in her room!
What?
Vishal, Have your tea.
Dad, You also. Have your tea.
Oh yeah!
Cheers!
What is there to cheer in tea!
From where do you operate
these operations?
From your home?
No, I have a different space for that.
I don’t have anything at my house!
You have a house!
Yes. Obviously, uncle!
So, Does everybody at your home knows
that you do this sort of business?
There is no one to tell.
I don’t have mom-dad. They died.
What!
You remember when Kedarnath
was in floods, At that time.
I am, I am so sorry Vishal.
We never got a chance
to talk this through.
So in that flood, they?
Yes!
Later on I went there to find them,
but couldn’t find them.
They might have been swept away!
Mom-dad and my younger sister!
I Was very young, maybe
that’s why I couldn’t find them.
It was God's will!
So your relatives didn’t support you?
No, it’s not that.
Uncles and aunties were there.
They could have taken care
of me very well.
But I didn’t want to
be a burden on anyone,
so I live alone!
One of my friends lives next to me.
Actually both of our families
went there together.
And his family was also in floods…
So, sometimes he stays at my place,
sometimes I stay at his.
It’s all good now!
I am, I am so sorry Vishal.
No, It’s okay!
Should I leave?
Yeah!
I’ll take your leave then.
I’ll drop you.
Nope. I’ll manage.
You stay here and take some rest.
You Should take a rest!
I’ll be back in a while!
Okay, bye uncle!
Bye
Dad, I’ll be back after dropping him!
Sure.
Should I clean this up?
Trisha
Hmm,
Yes?
I’ve given it a lot of thought then
only I am discussing this with you.
About what?
He is a good guy.
Hmm.
I mean, he has been through a lot,
and maybe that’s why he
is what he is today.
But he comes from a good family.
Hmm.
Think about it.
Think about what?
Marriage.
Come on, dad!
But what’s the problem?
His lifestyle, dad.
I can not live like that.
He is not even settled.
And you really want me
to marry a bootlegger?
And roam around with him on
the bikes which he steals!
So he is a thief as well.
Yes, he uses the stolen bikes
to deliver the bottle.
Oh god! What is actually happening!
What other hidden talent
does this guy have?
Stealing, robbery,
Burglary, Chain-snatching,
is he a murderer as well?
What are you saying?
What should I do now?
You're revealing things one by one,
and I don’t understand
where to start thinking!
There is nothing to think about.
He has his perspective
of life and so do I.
We both are right! If he wants
to meet the baby,
I am okay with it.
But nothing more than that.
But
what would be your life after this baby!
If someone will ask you who
is the father of this child,
then what would be your answer?
Do you have any problem if
I stay in this house like this?
Stay quiet!
Sorry
Do you have any problem!
Let’s do one thing!
What if he quits this stealing robbery
and stops selling liquor illegally
and I will take over some ready business
and I will ask him to handle it!
He does not want
any obligation from anyone,
didn’t you hear that!
Dad, He is still 21!
He is not mature.
All he wants is easy money!
That is all on me.
I’ll talk to him, just give me his number.
What will you do after that!
I’ll meet him, Try and make him
understand! Give me the number.
No.
Atleast allow me to meet him.
Let me try at least!
You wanted to meet him once.
You did. So that's it.
Alright. I want a liquor bottle.
Now give me his number.
Whatever!
I want premium stuff from him.
Give me his number.
There are more than 100 bottles
in my room.
Take all of them.
Give me his number.
- Please
- Good night, dad.
What do you think
I won’t be able to find him!
Good night.
Good. Night.
Con Artist!
I think this is the one.
Yes, Take the next right,
Inside the building.
Uncle.
Can I come inside!
Yes, Yes. Of course.
Amazing abs you have.
One, two, Three, four,
five, six. Best. Very strong!
Like father like daughter!
Uncle Have a seat!
Where?
Where can one sit in this mess!
Isn't this house excessively full?
There are clouds as well.
I think it will start raining
at any point of time now!
Rain!
A for Apple, B for bread
Oh sorry, Burnt bread!
You might not know
how to use the dustbin, no!
Oh my goodness!
Pile of used utensils!
Do you need some water!
This place is no less than an art gallery!
Yes!
This is a museum. Is there anything left!
The bedroom.
What’s that?
What?
Okay, I get it. Vasco-da-gama
might have ordered this pizza!
This place is indeed one in a million.
So, uncle, what can I help you with?
Nope, Nothing.
How did you find the address?
I asked for the list of tourists
from Ahmedabad to Kedarnath!
And that’s it!
You do have quite the extensive network!
Okay bro okay. We will be there.
Done, Done.
Bro There is an order of 35 nos.
From Mr. Prashant in shilaj
We will talk later, bro
Hmm.
We will talk later.
Uncle, have a seat!
Nope, I’ll take your leave now!
At least have some water!
I am fasting today!
Step aside!
Who was this?
Trisha’s father, man!
Now who is Trisha bro?
Yes.
Why are you at Vishal’s?
Very good. He is a fast reporting person.
Why?
I got a bit emotional
after listening to his story!
Dad, Please don’t get
involved in all this stuff
Nothing is going to change. So, stop it.
When did I tell you that
something will happen!
I just wanted to convince myself that
he is a good guy.
You will be happy with him.
But couldn’t you find someone else?
Not again!
I am so sorry!
At his place
He made an astray of pizza
which is a decade old. Crap!
What?
What is this guy!
Come home first,
we will discuss this later!
Yes!
There is no other option left!
Yes sir, note down
an address for me please.
So, You are going to be a daddy!
Dad,
Daddy,
dad, daddy, daddy, daddy, daddy…
Shut up you moron!
Daddy, look. Daddy is here!
- Come on guys. Come on.
- Uncle!
Look at this place.
You need to make this place home!
- You guys go inside!
- Hello!
- There is a sink full of utensils!
- Excuse me, hello!
Clean that first. There
is a bedroom as well.
Clean that too!
Uncle, I’ll clean this up!
I’ve already called them, no!
They will do it.
Let’s go. Wear your jeans, we have to go!
But, I need to deliver the bottles!
Yes
Those 35 nos. isn’t it?
You will deliver it, today!
- He!
- But how will I manage all by myself!
If you get caught then call me!
Vishal has my number no!
I’ll take care of things, okay!
Let’s go now. Come on.
I’ll be back in just a minute!
There is no need to call Trisha!
Come on, let's go!
At least let me wear my jeans!
Here it is!
This won’t match!
Wear it in a lift!
Yeah, But my shoes.
There it is!
These are
I’ll get you a new one! Let’s go!
Here are your shoes!
Let me buckle it up!
No one is there. Sit in the car!
- You are there no!
- Sit now!
Okay, Okay!
Idiot, Where are we going!
Can’t he just stay quiet for a while.
Irritating idiot!
Driver, Take us to the City centre!
Come. Let’s go!
Here?
Come on. I am asking you, no?
Come with me.
Uncle!
See what a nice place.
It is a very big store!
You don’t have to do anything!
You just have to sit here!
Everyone will do their role.
In the evening you’ll have
to count the cash, that’s it!
Hello, Mr. Rajesh!
How are you?
Come with me.
How are you sir?
I was here for the store only!
Deal is on right?
Yes. There are frequent
inquiries though!
Consult me once, Please!
What do you say Vishal?
Uncle, I can’t sell sarees!
No?
I have other options as well!
- But
- I’ll call you Mr. Rajesh!
Look at this! Spear Lounge-Rooftop cafe!
This is a very popular place!
Once it’s open it will
be full in minutes!
And you don’t have to do anything here.
You can come here whenever you want to!
Manager takes the order,
Chef will make the food!
Waiter serves the food
and the cashier collects the cash!
Everyday this cafe collects in lakhs!
You can come at night, Have a coffee.
And you won’t even have
to prepare food for yourself!
Uncle, I mean. It’s not like that!
I can manage myself
This is not okay as well?
It’s good but
I have another option. Come on.
You won’t be able to deny it.
Now what is this!
Just step inside and you’ll be saying
WOW! It is indeed a grand showroom!
Now over here if you will
come at a gap of 2-3 days,
that would be okay as well.
Customers visit this place,
place their order.
Sale and purchase department
settles within themselves.
We don’t have to worry!
It’s too much now!
Not even this!
No
I have a brilliant idea, Come.
What about this? Isn’t it something?
This whole unit makes
the machine of the labels
which can be glued on medicine bottles,
oil, shampoo, bottles etc.
This business has solid profit!
And more importantly you can visit
this place just once in a week!
So what do you say!
Should jump from here?
If you’ll land in a machine then
there will be a label on you as well!
It already has on my head!
Hello uncle. How are you?
Hii Yash. How are you, dear?
All good uncle!
Where is your father?
He is out for a meeting!
Okay!
Have we met before?
Bro!
He is our client.
He is a true lover of Jhonny!
What! Bro it’s not that
So he is your client!
Seriously?
No, no. It’s a joke!
Should I tell your dad?
No uncle!
Cancel! This deal is cancelled!
Tell your father that there
is no deal between us!
But uncle!
Let’s go to the next target!
- Sorry man. Sorry!
- Uncle, It was a joke only!
Come. This is the most peaceful
business environment ever!
You don’t even have to visit this place!
Patients will come, Doctors will treat
them and the owner earns money!
Mr Nimesh had told me about you
Trisha, Your dad has gone mad!
Please save me!
I hope this message reaches her!
So Vishal, What do you say!
Nope!
Let’s go to a very Cute place then!
Cute?
No, no, no. Please Uncle!
This is an amazing business, man!
Please, Please uncle.
No, no. It’s not done.
- Atleast have a look!
- What is this, Please!
Try and understand!
This is growing business dear!
It runs on auto mode!
I don’t want to do this!
If you wish to come then you can,
if you don’t want to visit this place!
I don’t want to be any part of it!
In case you get bored, then get a spa!
Life will be full of fun!
DAD!
Oh god!
Thank god!
Trisha!
Hey, Hey. Easy, easy.
I don’t want to be in this spa business!
What?
She just can’t keep her nose out.
Tell her, tell her everything! Nincompoop.
This coffee is getting cold!
It’s cold coffee!
Seriously dad! Spa
If you get bored, get a spa!
What to do? How should I settle him?
I am settled, uncle!
Yes, You definitely are!
Why do you want to settle him?
So, that you can live with him!
We are going to live together!
No!
Dad, we don’t have
feelings for eachother!
That is fine!
Once you start living together,
you both will gradually start
feeling for each other!
Just a minute, Let me be clear!
Uncle, You as a father,
want us to live in a live-in?
You...
I can’t even curse you!
Stop laughing!
Okay!
I am telling you very seriously!
Dear
I do not want to marry him.
Even I don't want to marry her!
- I am just a kid uncle!
- Yes
Were you not a kid when
you wanted make a kid with her!
She started it!
Hey, shut up!
Be quiet!
Are you out of your mind?
- Listen to me
- Listen dear
Trisha, what I am saying
Don’t interrupt!
Okay!
- Dad, listen to me
- Listen to me first!
Please, let me complete dad!
No, Let me speak first, Then you!
But at least listen what I am saying
I want to speak!
Okay. Go on.
See dear,
you both are the parents of this child!
Tomorrow when he goes to school,
they will ask
Who is the father of this child?
You might give them
some answers and you Vishal,
You might not be answerable.
But when he grows up,
five years old or ten years old,
then if he gets asked
“who is your father?”
Let it be, If on a fine day he feels
“I want to play with my father,
I want to see my parents together,
like actually side by side!
I want to sleep nestled between them,
feeling their warmth
and love all around me!”
You guys want to take
this all away from him!
See dear, at this point you
are not afraid of society
because you have that sense
of security that..
If you will get stuck somewhere
or in a decision making situation
you feel that no one is supporting me
or no one is with me at
that point of time you know
That your dad is standing
right behind you.
He got your back!
You are confident that
You are confident that till
my father is by my side,
no one’s father even dares to
ask you who is the father of this child.
But this child would
not be able to say it, no!
Don’t just think about yourselves.
Don’t be that selfish!
Think about this child. Your child!
There is only one solution to all this!
Get married!
Marriage
I told you whatever I had to!
Now it’s all up to you!
Marriage
I am in.
I am ready. I will get married.
For my child.
Life without parents
is just like living in hell,
I know.
I won’t let that happen to my child!
But But But.
I won’t give up on my business!
It established this with
my blood and sweat!
It all went in vain!
Yes uncle. I went to jail twice
to set this business up.
It’s all set now,
I worked hard to make contacts.
Build a network
Our slogan is hit uncle,
"All Ahmedabad 24x7,
Just A call for premium Stuff!”
What a crazy Guy!
You want to tell him anything else!
Yes.
I give you the blessing that
your business overtakes
pablo-escobar’s business.
What!
Look at him. How is he laughing!
Come on, dad!
Listen dear.
If you guys will spend some time together
then things will sort out automatically!
You get it, no?
My child
hope you understand
I am sorry, Dad!
Don’t feel bad! My dear!
Leave us!
If you don’t feel comfortable, call me.
I'll be here immediately. Okay?
And between you
and him you are the matured one
so you not only have to be
his but also his mother!
Once he gets attached to you
then slowly gradually
he will leave his bad dids’.
But you’ll
have to be patient! Hmm?
Come I’ll drop you!
Vishal?
Hii!
Why are you standing there like a statue?
Come inside! Please.
Yes
Welcome. This is my friend ‘Bhuvan’!
Hii, Trisha!
I told you, no? Trisha!
Hii
Tell her!
what!
Bro what are you doing?
I knew that his processor would
start lagging after seeing you!
Come, please have a seat!
His processor, Come on!
- Let me show you the place, come.
- Yeah, but just a minute.
See, this is the terrace.
I spent most of my time over here only.
This is my favourite spot.
And the sunset you get to see
from here is amusementifying!
Amusementifying?
Ohh, You were just late,
or you could have seen it!
But no worries we’ll see that tomorrow!
Come on, come on! Let’s go!
I need to show you the rest of the house!
Hey, hey, hey. Easy! Leave me, your
hands are feeling a bit too heavy!
You are heavy
All because of you!
Let’s go ahead, you can laugh out later!
This is where mom used
to perform the rituals.
If you want to do it over here,
do let me know I’ll clean it up!
Okay!
It’s still not done yet! Come on!
Vishal, Take away your hand!
This is the service table
and that is the kitchen!
I make delicious food!
Is that so?
Yes! Have you had dinner?
Yes!
No worries. Tomorrow I’ll cook
something for you!
Now, To the main part!
After you!
But where?
Here only!
Our bedroom!
- Come on!
- What!
Don’t laugh like this!
Then what should I do?
There are still a few things left!
After you!
This is the bathroom!
Is everything alright with the house?
Will it be comfortable enough for you?
Hmm.
It’s Fine. I’ll be fine..
Oh god!
Let’s sit outside?
Okay, I’ll change.
Can I stay?
Nope, You can not stay.
But I’ve already seen you!
Hey, Get out now!
Get up and get out now?
Please!
Please, Get lost!
What was this?
I am leaving.
Okay, bye now.
I'll beat you up!
It’s not like that! It was itching only!
Yuck!
I don’t want to listen to that!
Come over here!
Ladies first!
You first!
- I am no lady!
- Yes, but you first!
Come on, You!
Take away the pillow!
Enough, You’ll be beaten now!
Okay, Okay!
Seriously!
Do you want to watch T.V.?
No. You can if you want to.
T.V., I watch it everyday.
Today, I want to watch you!
It was a very cheap pick-up line!
You are blushing anyways!
Blush!
I am not blushing!
I can’t control my laughter!
Do you want to see my abs?
Vishal, Let’s sleep!
Okay, Come on!
Seriously?
I am coming!
Don’t follow me!
Trisha
Just go and sleep over there quietly.
Good night.
My stomach is hurting
because of laughing continually.
The sort of faces he makes,
I keep laughing looking at his face only.
He is literally childish!
Haha, That’s what I told you.
He is childish, not mischievous.
Will you be able to sleep?
Yes Dad.
Don’t worry about anything.
You sleep tight, dad!
Yes, I’ll sleep in a while!
I disrupted your sleep, didn't I?
Don’t think like that! I am fine!
I’ll manage myself! Don’t worry.
Okay, Don’t worry. Sleep tight.
I am happy only.
He is very caring
and he is taking good care of me!
Okay dear, Take care.
Good night dad.
Good night.
Trisha
Oh god!
Are you sure that
you don’t wanna do anything?
Oh god. Put it down. Put it down.
What’s this, what are you doing?
It’s the last warning, Leave now.
Fine!
Good night!
See you in the morning.
Vishal
What, Hehehehe
Close your mouth. That’s it.
Listen, stop playing games with me.
I won’t be good then.
Okay!
What okay?
What does that mean!
Hehehe Oh my god!
Should I come?
Hey, hey, hey. Stop, stop, stop.
Easy, I am carrying a baby!
Oh
Sorry, Sorry.
Are you okay?
Vishal
Let’s not do it no?
Should we cuddle?
Who would it be now?
Just a second. Just give me a second.
I’ll be right back. In a second.
Why are you not picking up
Mr.Yash’s calls? He called me.
I wasn’t aware!
He needs Three bottles of whiskey.
I asked him to double
the amount and he agreed!
It’s okay. You stay here.
I’ll manage this.
No, wait
- Come on, man.
- I am coming along
Wait, wait.
You should stay here with her.
I’ll deliver this today!
Are you sure?
Yes dude. You stay here.
Stay alert!
Yeah!
Who was it?
It was Bhuavn.
Nothing serious. He left.
Should we continue the hug?
Sleep now!
Sorry!
It’s okay!
Hello
Oh!
Is Mr. Digvijay there?
Okay fine. I am on my way!
- Just a minute
- Sure
Is there any problem?
No, I’ll be right back!
You can share!
Bhuvan has been arrested.
I’ll go, get him out. Okay?
I’ll call my dad!
See, don’t call anyone.
I’ll handle it.
Don’t panic, I’ll be back soon.
Listen, Should I come along?
Stay here Trisha. I’ll manage this. Okay?
You go to sleep.
Let’s go. I am coming with you.
Listen, I have already done this!
I told you no, I am coming!
Trisha
You will come with me
to the police station,
I won’t like it.
Please.
Don’t panic.
Hey, you. Sit down.
Yes
Where is digvijay sir?
Sir went home to sleep.
When will he be back?
Tomorrow morning.
Can talk to him on the phone?
Should I call him?
If you want to disturb his
sleep then go ahead!
Let it be now. Meet him tomorrow.
If you disturb him now
then this will take a long time!
Hey, Sit down!
Hello, Hii.
Yeah, it seems like I’ll be back
in the morning only.
Yes, sir went home to sleep. So!
No. Don’t worry.
I’ll be home in the morning.
Sleep tight, Okay?
Okay, Bye.
You should go home and stay with her.
Come back in the morning.
No, I am staying.
Hello, dad!
Do you have iPhone’s charger?
Are you using an iPhone?
You want one? Should I get you one?
What do you want to get?
Nothing sir. iPhone.
He is giving us an iPhone.
Dude, We are happy with
this phone only. Go.
Go? Means?
I got a call from sir.
He asked me to let go of both of you.
Get up you small-pants!
Get up.
Come on.
Get up, idiot.
Yes, he warned that next time it's an FIR
no more warnings.
Hmm.
Sure?
Keep it moving now.
Hey, give me a cigarette.
What did you do there?
Get on the bike now.
Bro, please talk to them and sort it out.
Spending the whole night
in lock-up is tough, man.
Come on. Sit now you idiot.
Give me the cigarette.
I don’t have any.
Stop at the store.
Go ahead, I’ll get some cigarettes.
Trisha!
Trisha
No, no, no.
No, no, no. Please,
please, Please.
Trisha
Please, please, please pick up.
Vishal!
Trisha!
Why did you come back here?
I forgot a few things.
So, I am here to take them.
- Why are you here?
- Then why didn’t you answer my calls.
I missed it.
But I did call you back.
You didn’t pick up.
Call back?
Mr. Vishnu
Yes madam.
Give him some water.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Sit down.
But why do you want to sit?
Sit-sit.
Have some water!
I don’t want water!
Dad must be coming.
We will leave after meeting him.
When will he come back?
He must be coming, Now.
Why did you come here running?
Trisha, I thought you were gone!
Like literally.
What?
Yes, I was having these stupid thoughts
for the whole time in the police station.
I was there for only three to four hours.
But I missed you by a XXL amount.
XXL amount, from where are
you fetching these words!
Dude you are laughing! I was very tense!
That I can see.
Vishal, relax.
Calm yourself.
I am going to be with you.
Trisha, you are
Ohh
Hey, are you crying or what?
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
Trisha, Come on.
Sorry
Sorry-sorry.
Listen.
Ohh. Okay, okay.
What?
Will you
Ouch. Okay!
Trisha
Hmm.
I mean I wanted to tell you something!
Hmm
I am experiencing some different feelings.
Hmm?
For the first time
I’ve felt this different!
What Different?
See this.
Nobody has taken a leaf from my hair!
Come on.
Hmm.
All of these feelings.
I am talking about them.
Same feelings!
What?
I’ve been to the police
station before, but
I was never afraid.
I was afraid today.
If I steal a bike and go out for delivery,
I might get caught
and I’ll have to go to jail
then I won't be able to meet you.
Hmm.
What if you get upset and leave me
by the time I get out of it?
I have a blurry memory
of sleeping with my mum and hugging her.
And last night,
I hugged you while sleeping.
That feeling was…
I want to hug you and sleep, daily.
Can we be together for a lifetime?
You dad was right,
Should we get married?
I’ll leave all of this and move on.
For you,
for our baby.
I’ll find something else.
I am super manly.
I'll money anyhow,
that too legally.
God!
- Trisha
- Yes!
What is your take?
Should we get married?
Yes!
For a lifetime let’s be together?
Yes?
Oh, you accepted my proposal very quickly.
Then no!
No?
No, Try and convince me more.
Then I will accept your proposal.
How much more should I convince you?
I see you are down to earth now!
Uncle. Thank you, Thank you.
Thank you, thank you so much.
What is he up to?
I didn’t know you had this
much bigger contacts!
Contacts?
Yes uncle.
Just a single call from you
and my friend was out of jail.
Thank you.
Is he like this?
I have been laughing since yesterday!
Uncle, I want to get married.
And so does Trisha. We both are ready.
I will put an end to my off
the book businesses.
I have savings of 25 lacs.
- I will find something.
- Listen
You don’t have to worry about Trisha.
I am full of daring.
I will earn the money.
Without any support
from you I will be settled.
I won’t keep a foot inside
the police station,
- I am promising you that, uncle.
- Hey, stop. Stop.
Give me a break.
We will sit and talk this through.
I am sweating all over due
to running. At Least let me change.
Let us go, no?
Let’s go!
You won’t stop, would you?
Sit down.
- Uncle
- Yes
Let us go no!
Go back
Back?
Go back now.
But let us go, no?
Now sit.
At least let me take a napkin!
Okay, I am waiting.
Come on, let's go!
Vishal!
I want to dance so bad
and hug you so tight.
I want to go home
and dance at maximum volume,
I want to kiss you uninterrupted.
Stop.
Stop my stomach is hurting.
Uncle isn’t here yet. Give me a kiss.
Vishal, dad!
What happened?
You denied a kiss, no?
I will take from your dad now!
Uncle!
Did he just kiss me?
She denied it so I took it from you.
Now I won’t stay here even
for a micro second!
Hey Look, Vishnu fell-off!
Come on, let’s go!
Hey, where are you going?
Let her go. Hey.
You can also join us.
Come on. Come on, let's go.
- Come on. Let’s go.
- Let go of me. Take her.
But my belongings!
We'll get new belongings,
You just come!
- Hey, be careful.
- Come on.