Movie Fan News presents:
Spotlight on "Adventure".
What you are now witnessing is footage
never before seen by civilized humanity,
a lost world in South America,
lurking in the shadow of
Majestic Paradise Falls
it's full of plants and
animals undiscovered by science.
Who would dare set foot on
this inhospitable summit?
Why, our subject
today, Charles Muntz.
The beloved explorer lands his dirigible,
"The Spirit of Adventure", into Hampshire,
completing a year
long expedition to the lost world.
This mighty aircraft was
designed by Charles Muntz himself
and is longer than 22 throw edition
petty wagons placed end to end.
And here comes
the adventurer now.
Never-apart from
his faithful dogs,
Muntz conceived the craft
for the canine comfort.
It's a veritable
flouting palace in the sky
complete with doggy baths
and mechanical canine walker.
And Jiminy Cricket! To the locals he's
considered a business and hero! And how!
Adventure is out there!
But what has Muntz
brought back this time?
Gentlemen, I give you the
Monster of Paradise Falls!
And gully, what a
swell monster this is!
But what's this?
Scientists cry "Foul!"
The National Explorers Society accuses
Muntz of fabricating the skeleton.
No!
The organization strips
Muntz of his membership.
Humiliated, Muntz vows to
return to Paradise Falls
and promises to capture
the beast... alive.
I promise to capture
the beast alive!
And I will not come
back until I do!
And so, the explorer's
off to clear his name.
Bon voyage, Charles Muntz!
And good luck capturing the
Monster of Paradise Falls!
SPIRIT OF ADVENTURE
Here's Charles Muntz,
piloting his famous dirigible.
He hurdles Pikes Peak.
He hurdles the Grand Canyon.
He hurdles Mount Everest!
He goes around Mount Everest!
Is there nothing
he cannot do? UP
Yes, as Muntz himself said,
"Adventure... "
"is out there!"!
Look out! Mount Rushmore!
Let's get "The Spirit of
Adventure" over Mount Rushmore!
Come on, make an effort!
How are my dogs doing?
SPIRIT OF ADVENTURE
All engines ahead, let's
take her up to 26000 feet!
Rudder 18 degrees
towards South!
It's a beautiful day.
The wind blows from
the east at 10 knots.
Visibility... unlimited.
Enter the weather
in the log book!
There is something down there.
I will bring it back for the science!
Oh... It's a puppy!
MUNTZ ALOFT: BREAKS
43,976 FEET ALTITUDE RECORD
What are you doing?
Don't you know this
is an exclusive club?
Only explorers get in here,
not just any kid off the street
with a helmet and a pair of goggles!
- You think you got what it takes? Do you?
- I...
All right, you're
in! Welcome aboard!
What's wrong? Can't you talk?
Hey, I don't bite.
You and me, we are in a club now!
GRAPE SODA
I saw where your balloon went.
Come on, let's go get it!
My name is Ellie.
There it is!
Well... go ahead.
Go on.
Hey, kid!
I thought you might need
a little cheering up.
I got something to show you!
I am about to let
you see something
I have never shown to
another human being.
Ever... in my life!
You have to swear you
will not tell anyone!
Cross your heart! Do it!
My adventure book!
You know him.
C.MUNTZ, MAN OF THE YEAR.
Charles Muntz, explorer.
When I get big, I'm
going where he's going.
South America.
It's like America, but South.
Wander where I'm gonna live?
Paradise Falls.
A land lost in time.
I ripped this right
out of a library book!
I'm gonna move my
club house there!
And park up right
next to the falls.
Who knows what lives up there!
And once I get there...
I'm gonna save all these pages for
all the adventures I'm gonna have.
Only... I just don't know how
I'm gonna get to Paradise Falls.
That's it! You can take
us there in a blimp!
Swear you'll take us
there! Cross your heart!
Cross it! Cross your heart!
Good, you promised.
No backing out!
Well, see you tomorrow, kid. Bye!
Adventure is out there!
You know, you don't
talk very much.
I like you.
Quite a sight, hey, Ellie?
He... mail is here.
SHADY OAKS,
Retirement Village, oh, brother!
Hey, good morning,
Mr. Fredricksen.
Need any help there?
No... Yes... Tell your boss over there
that you boys are ruining our house.
Well, just to let you know,
my boss will be happy to take
this whole place off your hand...
...and would double
his last offer.
What do you say to that?
I'll take that as a no, then.
I believe I made my position
to your boss quite clear.
You poured prune
juice in his gas tank.
Yeah, that was good!
Here, let me talk to him.
You, in the suit. Yes, you!
Take a bath, hippie!
I am not with him!
This is serious! He's
out to get your house!
Tell your boss he
can have our house.
Really?
When I'm dead!
I'll take that as a "maybe".
Order now: you get the camera, you
get the printer, 4X optical zoom.
Schneider Lens.
Photo print...
SD card.
Good afternoon.
My name is Russell
and I am a wilderness
explorer in tribe 54,
squad lodge 12.
Are you in need of any
assistance today, Sir?
No.
I could... help you
cross the street.
No.
I could help you
cross your... yard?
No.
I could help you
cross your... porch.
No.
Well, I gotta help
you cross something.
No, I'm doing fine.
Good afternoon.
- My name is Russell.
- Kid...
And I am a wilderness
explorer in tribe 54.
Slow down...
- ... squad lodge 12.
- Kid!
- Are you in need of any assistance?
- Thank you, but I don't need any help!
Aouch.
Proceed.
Good afternoon.
Skip to the end!
See these? These are my
wilderness explorer badges.
You may notice one is missing.
It's my "Assisting
the elderly badge".
If I get it, I'll become a
senior wilderness explorer!
The wilderness must be explored!
It's gonna be great!
There is a big ceremony
and all the dads come and...
we pin on our badges...
- So you wanna assist an old person.
- Yeah!
Then I'll be a senior
wilderness explorer!
- Have you ever heard of a "snipe"?
- "Snipe"?
A bird. Big eyes.
Every night it
sneaks into my yard
and gobbles my poor azaleas.
I'm elderly and infirm.
I can't catch it.
- If only someone could help me...
- Me, me, I'll do it!
I don't know, it's awfully crafty.
You'd have to clap your hands three
times to lure it in.
I'll find her, Mr. Fredricksen!
I think its burrow
is two blocks down...
Two blocks down. Got it!
Snipe! Here, snipie, snipie...
Bring it back here
when you find it!
Snipe!
...and stop... Stop... Stop!
Hey!
Hey, you! What do you think
you're doing?
I am so sorry, Sir.
Don't touch that!
No, no, no, let me take
care of that for you.
Get away from our mailbox!
- Sir...
- I don't want you to touch that!
It looks bad.
COURT SUMMONS
Sorry, Mr. Fredricksen.
You don't seem like
a public menace to me.
Take this.
The guys from "Shady Oaks" will be
by to pick you up in the morning, ok?
What do I do now, Ellie?
Good morning, gentlemen.
Good morning, Mr. Fredricksen.
You're ready to go?
Ready as I'll ever be.
Would you do me the
favour and take this?
I'll meet you in the
van in just a minute.
I... wanna say one last
goodbye to the old place.
Sure. Take all the
time you need, Sir.
That's typical. He's probably going
to the bathroom for the 80th time.
You'd think he'd take
better care of his house.
So long, boys!
I'll send you a postcard
from Paradise Falls!
SOUTH AMERICA
We are on our way, Ellie.
Hi, Mr. Fredricksen.
It's me, Russell.
What are you doing
out here, kid?
I found the snipe and I
followed it under your porch.
But this snipe had a long tail
and looked more like a large mouse.
Please, let me in.
No.
Aw, all right. You can come... in.
I've never been in a
floating house before.
Goggles...
Look at this stuff!
Are you going on a trip?
"Paradise Falls, a
land lost in time".
Are you going to South
America, Mr. Fredricksen?
Don't touch that!
You'll soil it.
You know, most
people take a plane.
But you're smart,
because you have your
TV, clocks and stuff.
Ooo, is this how
you steer your house?
Does it really work?
This makes it turn right
and that way is left.
Hey, look! Buildings!
That building's so close,
I can almost touch it!
Wow, this is great!
You should try this,
Mr. Fredricksen.
Look, there's a bus that could
take me home two blocks away!
Hey, I can see your
house from here!
Don't jerk around
so much, kid!
Well, that's not gonna work.
I know that cloud,
it's a "cumulonimbus".
Did you know that
a cumulonimbus...
Aaa, I stayed up all night
blowing up balloons... for what?
That's nice, kid.
What are you doing over there?
Look!
See? Cumulonimbus.
My bag!
Got you!
Uuu, I thought you were dead.
What happened?
I steered us. I did
it! I steered the house.
You steered us?
After you tied your stuff
down, you took a nap.
So I went ahead and
steered us down here.
Yeah, sure.
I can't tell where we are.
O, we're in South
America all right.
It was a singe. I used my
wilderness explorer GPS.
GP... what?
My dad gave it to me.
It shows exactly where
we are on the planet.
With this baby
we'll never be lost!
We'll get you down,
find a bus stop,
and you'll just tell the man you
want to get back to your mother.
Sure, but I don't think they
have buses in Paradise Falls.
There, that ought to do it.
There, I'll give you some
change for the bus fare.
No, I'll just use
my city bus pass.
It's just gonna be like a billion
passes to get back to my house.
Mr. Fredricksen, how much longer?
Well, we're up pretty high.
It'll take hours to get down.
I think that was a
building or something.
What was that,
Mr. Fredricksen?
We can't be close
to the ground yet.
Wait, no, no!
Wait, wait!
Hang on!
Pull back!
Where... where are we?
This doesn't look like the city
or the jungle, Mr. Fredricksen.
Don't worry, Ellie. I've got it.
There it is!
Ellie, it's so beautiful!
We made it!
We made it! Russell, we
can float right over there.
Climb up, climb up!
Do you mean... assist you?
- Yeah, whatever.
- Ok, I'll climb up!
- Watch it!
- Sorry.
Now... when you get up there,
go ahead and hoist me up.
Got it?
Are you on the porch yet?
What? That's it?
I came all this way here to get stuck
on the wrong end of this rock pile?
Ah... great.
Hey, if I could assist
you over there...
would you sign
up for my badge?
What are you talking about?
We could walk your
house to the fall.
- Walk it?
- Yeah.
After all we weigh it down, we
could walk it right over there.
Like a parade balloon.
Now, we'll walk to the
falls quickly and quietly,
with no rap music
or flash dancing.
We have three days at best till the
helium leaks out of those balloons.
And if we are not at the
falls when that happens...
we're not getting
to the falls.
There... I found sand!
Don't you worry, Ellie.
We'll get our
house over there.
It is fun already, isn't it?
By the time we get there,
You're gonna feel so
assisted... Oh, Mr. Fredricksen,
if we happen to get separated,
use the wilderness
explorer call.
Wait, why are we going
to Paradise Falls, again?
Hey, let's play a game.
It's called: "See who
can be quiet the longest".
Cool! My mom loves that game!
Darn thing...
Come on, Russell, hurry it up.
Ah, I'm tired.
My knee hurts.
Which knee?
My elbow hurts and I have
to go to the bathroom.
I asked you about
that five minutes ago.
I didn't have to go then!
I don't wanna walk anymore...
Please, stop...
Russell, if you don't hurry
up, the tigers will eat you.
There are no tigers
in South America.
Zoology.
Ah, for the love of Pete... Go on
into the bushes and do your business.
Ok. Here! Hold my stuff!
I've always
wanted to try this.
Mr. Fredricksen, am I suppose
to dig the hole before or after?
That's none of my concern.
Oh, it's "before"!
Tracks?
Snipe.
Here, snipe.
Come on out, snipe.
Snipe!
Got you. Don't be
afraid, little snipe.
I am a wilderness explorer,
so I'm a friend
to all of nature.
Want some more?
Hi, boy. Don't eat it all.
Come on out.
Come on. Come on...
Don't be afraid, little snipe.
Nice snipe. Good little snipe.
Nice... giant snipe!
I found the snipe.
Oh, did you?
- Are they tall?
- Oh, yes. They're very tall.
Do they have a lot of colors?
They do, indeed.
- Do they like chocolate?
- Oh, yeah...
Chocolate?
What is that thing?
It's a snipe.
There no such
thing as a snipe!
But you said...
Go on, get out of here! Go!
Careful, Russell.
Look, Mr. Fredricksen,
he likes me.
- Russell!
- No, stop! That tickles!
Get out of here!
Go on! Get!
No, no, no. Kevin, it's ok.
Mr. Fredricksen is nice.
- Kevin?
- Yes, that's the name I just gave him.
Bit it, boo, scram!
Hey, that's mine!
Aah... Shoo, shoo! Get out of here!
Go on, bit it!
Can we keep him? Please?
I'll get the food for him, I'll walk
him, I'll change his newspapers...
No.
An explorer is a friend to all,
be it a plant, a fish or a tiny mole.
That doesn't even rhyme.
Yeah, it does.
- Hey, look, Kevin.
- What?
Hey, get down from there!
You're not allowed up there!
You come down here right now!
Can you believe this, Ellie?
Ellie?
Hey, Ellie, can
I keep the bird?
Aha... aha
She said for you to let me.
But I told him
no. I told you no.
N - O!
I see you, back there.
Go on, get out of here! Shoo! Go
annoy someone else for a while.
Hey, are you ok over there?
Hello?
Oh, hello, Sir.
Thank Goodness.
It's nice to know
someone else is up here.
I can smell you.
What?
You can... smell us?
I can smell you.
- Hey!
- You were talking to a rock.
Hey, that one
looks like a turtle.
Look at that one! That
one looks like a dog!
- Ah, it is a dog.
- What?
We're not allowed to have
dogs in my apartment.
Hey, I like dogs!
We have your dog!
- I wonder whom he belongs to.
- Sit, boy.
Hey, look, he's trained!
Shake.
Aha. Speak.
Hi, there.
Did that dog just
say "Hi, there"?
Oh, yes!
My name is Dug. I just
met you and I love you.
My master made me this collar.
He is a good and smart master
and he made me this collar
so that I may talk. Squirrel!
My master is good and smart.
It's not possible.
Oh yes... It is... because my
master is smart.
Hey, cool! What
do these do, boy?
Would you cut... I'd use that collar... I
would be happy if you stopped.
Russell, don't touch that.
It could be...
radioactive or something.
I am a great tracker. My master
sent me on a special mission.
All by myself. Have
you seen a bird?
I want to find one and
I've been on a scent.
I'm a great tracker.
Did I mention that?
Hey, that is a bird. I have never seen
one up close. But this is the bird.
May I take your bird up
to camp as my prisoner?
Yes, yes, take it. And on the way,
learn how to bark like a real dog.
I can bark... And here's howling.
Can we keep him, please?
Please, please, please?
- No.
- But it's a talking dog!
It's just a weird
trick or something.
Let's get to the fall.
Please, be my prisoner! Oh,
please oh, please, be my prisoner!
Oh, here it is! I picked
up the bird's scent!
Wait a minute, wait a
minute. What is this?
Chocolate. I smell chocolate.
I'm getting prunes
and ginger cream.
Who are they?
Oh, man, the master
will not be pleased.
We'd better tell him someone
took the bird, right, Alfa?
No. Soon enough the bird
will be ours again.
Find the scent, my compadres, and you too,
shall have much rewarding from the master
for the toil that you did.
Hey, Alfa, I think there's
something wrong with your collar.
You must have broken it.
Yeah. Your voice sounds funny.
Beta, Delta!
Perhaps you deSire... Squirrel!
Perhaps you deSire to challenge the right
that I have been assigned
by my strength and cunning.
No, no. No.
But maybe Dug would.
You might wanna ask him.
I wonder if he's found the bird
on his "very special mission".
Do not mention Dug to me at this time.
His fool's errand will keep him most
occupied, most occupied, indeed.
Do you not agree with that
which I'm saying to you now?
Sure. But the second the master finds
out that you sent Dug out by himself,
none of us will get a treat.
You're unwise, my trusted lieutenant.
This is Alfa. Calling
Dug. Come in, Dug.
Hi, Alfa. Your
voice sounds funny.
I know, I know!
Have you seen the bird?
Oh, yes. The bird
is my prisoner now.
Yeah, right.
Impossible. Where are you?
I am here with the bird and I will bring it
back, and then you like me. Oh, gotta go.
Dug, who are you talking to?
- Wait, wait!
- What is Dug doing?
Why is he with
the small mailman?
Where are they?
There he is. Come on!
Please, oh, please,
be my prisoner.
Dug, stop bothering Kevin!
That man over there
says I can take the bird.
And I love that man there
like he is my master.
I am not your master!
I am warning you once again, bird!
- Hey, quit it!
- I am jumping on you now, bird!
At this rate we will
never get to the falls!
I am nobody's master, got it?
I don't want you here
and I don't want you here!
I'm stuck with you!
If you two don't clear out of here
by the time I count to three...
A ball! Oh, boy, oh, boy, a ball!
Ball? You want a ball?
Yes, I do! I ever so want the ball!
Go get it!
Oh, boy, I will get it and then
bring it back!
Quick, Russell, give
me some chocolate.
- Why?
- Just give to me!
Bird! Bird!
Come on, Russell.
Wait! Wait, Mr. Fredricksen!
What are you doing?
Hey, we're pretty far now.
Kevin's gonna miss.
I think that did the trick.
Hi, master.
Afternoon.
Well, thanks for keeping
us dry, anyway, Ellie.
Which one is the front?
Well, boy...
Is this step
three or step five?
There.
All done. That's for you.
Well, tents are hard.
Wait, aren't you
super wilderness guy
with the GPS and the badges?
Yeah, but...
Can I tell you a secret?
- No.
- All right. Here it goes.
I never actually built a
tent before. There! I said it.
You've been camping
before, haven't you?
Well, never outside...
Well, why didn't you ask
your dad how to build a tent?
I don't think he wants
to talk about this stuff.
Try him sometime, maybe
he'll surprise you.
He's away a lot, I
don't see him much.
He's gotta be home sometime.
I call, but Phyllis told
me I bug him too much.
Phyllis? You call your own
mother by her first name?
- Phyllis isn't my mom.
- Oh!
But he promised he'd come
to my Explorers Ceremony
to pin on my "Assisting
the elderly badge".
So he can show me how
about the tent then, right?
Hey, why don't
you get some sleep?
We don't want to wake the
travelling flea circus.
Dle Fredricksen, Dug says he
wants to take Kevin prisoner.
We have to protect him.
Can Kevin go with us?
All right, he can come.
Promise you won't leave him?
Yeah.
Cross your heart?
Cross my heart.
What have I got myself into, Ellie?
Good morning, sweetheart.
We'd better get moving.
The bird's gone. Maybe
Russell won't notice.
All right, everybody up!
Where's Kevin?
He's wondered off!
- Dug, find Kevin!
- Find the bird, find the bird!
Point!
Oh, look! There he is...
Hey, that's my roof!
Get off my roof!
Yeah, get off of his WROOF!
What is he doing?
The bird is calling
to her babies.
Her babies!
Kevin is a... girl?
Her house is over there,
on those twisty rocks.
She's been gathering food for her
babies and must get back to them.
Wait, Kevin is just leaving.
But you promised
to protect her.
Her babies need her. We gotta
make sure they're together.
Sorry, Russell. We've
lost enough time already.
Yeah...
It was her favorite chocolate.
Because you sent her
away, there's more for you.
Kevin?
Where's the bird? You
said you had the bird!
Oh, yes, oh, yes.
If I had said that,
I can see how you
would think that.
Where is it?
Oh, tomorrow. Come back tomorrow and
then I will again have the bird. Yes.
You lost it. why do I not
have a surprised feeling?
Well, at least you now have led us
to the small mailman
and to the one that smells as prunes.
The master will be most
pleased we have found them.
He will ask them
many questions. Come.
Wait! We're not
going with you.
We're going to the fall.
Get away from me!
Down!
You came here... in that?
Yeah.
In a house? A floating house?
That is the darnest
thing I've ever seen!
You're not after
my bird, are you?
But if you need to borrow a cup
of sugar, I'd be happy to oblige!
Well, this is all
a misunderstanding.
My dogs made a mistake.
Wait. Are you Charles Muntz?
Well... yes.
THE Charles Muntz?
Adventure's out there!
It's really him!
That's Charles Muntz!
It is?
Who's Charles Muntz?
Him!
Carl Fredricksen. My wife and
I, we were your biggest fans.
Oh, well, you're a
man of good taste.
Now you must be tired. Hungry?
Attention, everyone! These
people are no longer intruders.
They are our guests.
Yeah!
All right! I like
you temporarily.
I will not bite you.
The small mailman
smells like chocolate!
I'm sorry about the dogs,
I hope they weren't
too... rough on you.
Go ahead and pull your
airship right next to mine.
We are not actually going inside
the "Spirit of Adventure" itself?
Oh, would you like to?
Would I?
Wait up, Mr. Muntz!
Jiminy Cricket!
- Not you!
- What do we do with Dug?
He lost the bird. Put him
in "the cone of shame".
I do not like "the
cone of shame".
Most of the collection is housed
in the world's top museums:
New York, Münich, London.
Of course, I kept
the best for myself.
Did you ever. Look at that!
Oh, yes. The Arseloterium.
The beast charged while
I was brushing my teeth.
I used my shaving
kit to bring it down.
Oh, yeah, now, surprise me.
The only way to get it out of Ethiopia at
the time was to have it declared
technical weapon.
Oh, my Gosh! The giant
Somalian Labradodis!
Oh, you recognize
it? I'm impressed!
There's an interesting
story there.
Excellent choice.
I found it on safari,
with Roosevelt.
He and I fell into a habit of
playing Gin Rummy in the evenings
and did he cheat!
He was horrible.
Master, dinner is ready.
Oh, dear, broken translator.
I think it's that
loose wire again.
- There you go, big fellow.
- Thank you, master.
I liked his other voice.
Well, dinner is served.
Right this way.
So, how are
things States side?
Almost tempted to
go back a few times.
But I have
unfinished work here.
Please! I hope you're hungry.
Because Epsilon is the
finest chef I've ever had.
Epsilon, you've done it again!
Yeah!
Hey! Hey!
My Ellie would have
loved all these.
You know, because of
you she had this dream
to come down here
and live by the fall.
I'm honored. And
now you've made it.
You sure we're not a
bother? I'd hate to impose.
No, no, it's a
pleasure to have guests.
A real treat.
Treat?
Where's my treat?
I want my treat!
Hey!
I shouldn't have
used that word.
Having guests is a delight!
More often I get thieves trying
to steal what is rightfully mine.
No...
They called me
a fraud, those...
But once I bring back this
creature, my name will be cleared.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Oh, I've spent a
lifetime tracking it.
Sometimes, years go by
between seeings.
I've tried to smoke it out of
that death land where it lives.
Can't go in after it.
Once in, there's no way out.
I lost so many dogs.
Here they come those bandits and
think the bird is theirs to take!
They'll soon find that this mountain
is a very dangerous place.
Hey, that looks like Kevin!
- Kevin?
- Yeah, that's my new giant pet bird!
I trained it to follow us.
Follow you?
Impossible. How?
She likes chocolate.
- Chocolate?
- Yeah. I gave her some of my chocolate.
She goes gaga for it.
But it ran off.
Let's go now.
You know, Carl...
these people who pass through here,
they all tell pretty good stories
A surveyor making a map...
A botanist cataloguing plants...
An old man taking his
house to Paradise Falls.
That's the best one yet. I can't
wait to hear how it ends.
Well, it's been a wonderful
evening, but we'd better be going.
You're not leaving.
We don't want to take
advantage of your hospitality.
Come on, Russell.
But we haven't even
had dessert yet.
Oh, the boy is right.
You haven't had dessert.
Epsilon here makes a
delicious cherries jubilee.
You really must stay! I insist!
We have so much
more to talk about!
Kevin?
It's near.
Get them!
- Hurry!
- Kevin!
Dogs! Hurry!
Master! Over here!
Go on, master!
Left!
Russell!
Get back!
Go on, master! I will stop the dogs!
Stop, you, dogs!
Help!
Give me your hand!
Hang on to Kevin!
Kevin!
No, no, no. Kevin...
Stay down.
She's hurt real bad.
Can't we help her get home?
All right. But we gotta hurry.
- You lost them?
- No, it was Dug.
Yeah, he's with them.
he helped them escape!
Wait. Wait a minute.
Dug.
- See anything?
- No, my pack is not following us.
Boy, they are dumb!
This is crazy.
I finally meet my childhood
hero and he's trying to kill us.
- What a joke.
- Hey, I know a joke!
A squirrel walks up
up to a tree and says:
"I forgot to store acorns
for winter and now I am dead".
It is funny because
the squirrel gets dead.
Careful, Russell.
You ok, Kevin?
You know what,
Mr. Fredricksen?
The wilderness isn't
quite what I expected.
Yeah? How so?
It's kind of... wild.
I mean, it's not how they
made it sound in my book.
Get used to that, kid.
My dad made it sound so easy.
He is really good at camping,
and how to make fire
from rocks and stuff...
He used to come to all
my squad lodge meetings.
And afterwards, we go
get ice-cream that fattens.
I always get chocolate
and he gets butter brickle.
Then we sit on this
one curve, right outside
and I'll count all the blue cars
and he counts all the red ones
and whoever gets
the most wins.
I like that curve.
It might sound boring,
but I think the boring stuff is
the stuff I remember the most.
Look, there it is!
Hold on, Russell, stand still.
Look at that bird go! Wait
up, you overgrown chicken!
That's it! Go, Kevin!
Go find your babies!
Run, Kevin, run!
Oh, no!
Russell, dã-mi cuþitul tãu!
Get away from my bird!
No!
Careful, I want it in good
shape for my retirement.
Let it go!
Stop!
Kevin!
You gave away Kevin.
You just... gave her away.
This is none of my concern.
I didn't ask for any of these!
Master, it's all right.
I am not your master!
If you hadn't shown up, none
of these would have happened.
Bad dog, bad dog!
Whether you assist me or not,
I am going to Paradise
Falls, if it kills me!
Here
I don't want this anymore.
Russell?
- Russell!
- I'm gonna help Kevin
even if you won't!
No, Russell, no!
Russell?
I was hiding under your
porch because I love you.
Can I stay?
Can you stay? Well,
you're my dog, aren't you?
And I'm your master.
You're my master?
- Oh, boy!
- Good boy, Dug!
You're a good boy!
Yes!
Don't worry, Kevin,
I'll save you.
And they wouldn't believe me.
Just wait till they
get a look at you!
Master.
The small mailman
has returned.
What?
Let me go!
Where is your elderly friend?
He's not my friend anymore.
If you're here, Fredricksen
can't be far behind.
Where are you keeping Kevin?
Let me go!
Scream all you
want, small mailman.
None of your mailmen
friends can hear you.
I will unleash all my
wilderness explorer training!
Alfa, Fredricksen
is coming back!
Guard that bird.
If you see the old man,
you know what to do.
Where are you going? I'm
not finished with you!
Nice talking with you.
Where are you, Fredricksen?
Help!
Russell!
- Dle Fredricksen!
- Dug, bring her over!
You came back for
Kevin! Let's go get her!
I'm getting Kevin.
You stay here.
- But I wanna help!
- I don't want your help.
I want you safe.
How do we get pass these dogs?
Point!
Kevin!
Don't worry, Kevin.
We are on our way.
No one should be entering
through these doors.
Guard well that
bird, my minions.
What do we do now, Dug?
Who wants the ball?
Me, me, me!
Go get it!
I got it!
I'm sorry, Kevin. Let's
get you out of here.
- Master, he's gone.
- What's going on?
- He's got the bird!
- He ran off!
Calm down! One at the time!
I want to... help!
Does anybody know
where they are?
Raid leaders! Bring
down that house!
Raid leader! Checking in!
- Raid 2, checking in.
- Raid 3, checking in.
Target sighted.
Come on, Kevin.
Hi.
Any last words, Fredricksen?
Come on, spit it out!
Enough!
You cannot leave
this place... alive!
You're dead!
Come on, Kevin.
I'll have plenty of enjoyment
for what I'm about to do to you.
He wears the cone of shame!
Not just continue
sitting! Attack!
No! No! Stop your laughing!
Listen, you, dog, sit!
Yes, Alfa.
Alfa? I am not
Alfa, he is... Oh!
I can't do it.
Russell...
You leave Mr.
Fredricksen alone!
- Hey! Squirrel!
- Squirrel? Where?
I hate squirrels!
- Dug!
- Master!
Russell, over here!
Let's go!
Mr. Fredricksen!
Come on, Kevin.
No!
Russell, get out of there!
Leave them alone!
Russell, hang on to Kevin!
Don't let go! Grab on to him!
Kevin! Chocolate!
That was cool!
Don't jerk around
so much, kid.
Easy, Russell.
Oh, I am ready
to not be up high.
Sorry about your
house, Mr. Fredricksen.
You know... It's just a house.
Look at you! You're so soft!
I wish I could keep one.
Where is my cane?
I just had it here.
You know what? Keep them. A
little gift from me to you.
Bye, Kevin!
- Ready?
- Ready.
By receiving these badges,
the following explorers
will graduate to
Senior Explorers.
For Extreme
Mountaineering Lore.
Congratulations, Jimmy.
For Wild Animal
Defensive Arts,
Congratulations, Brendan.
For Assisting the Elderly...
Russell.
Is there someone...
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Old man coming through.
I'm here for him.
Congratulations, Russell. Sir.
Russell, for
assisting the elderly
and for performing above
and beyond the call of duty,
I would like to award you the
highest honor I can bestow.
"The Ellie badge".
I think that covers everybody.
so let's give a big explorer call
to our brand new Senior
Wilderness Explorers!
Ready everybody?
- Blue one.
- Red one.
- Gray one.
- That's a bike.
- It's red, isn't it?
- Mr. Fredricksen, you're cheating!
- No, I'm not. Red one.
- That's a fire hydrant.
Maybe I need a few lessons.
SPIRIT OF ADVENTURE