I can't fill another bucket.
You'll have to make do with this.
O Merciful Lord
You are the essence of the world
With a snake around Your neck,
You are the purest One
O Merciful Lord
You are the essence of the world
With a snake around Your neck,
You are the purest One
Bunty!
Yes, Mom?
Come upstairs!
With a snake around Your neck...
You are the essence of the world
With a snake around Your neck
You are the purest One
O Merciful Lord
You are the essence of the world
With a snake around--
So you'll ration my bathing water,
but your Holy Basil will always
get its share of water, huh?
Well, it doesn't need
four buckets of water to bathe.
Right.
In my next life,
I want to be a Holy Basil plant.
Is it necessary for you
to come upstairs every day?
Do you have to say this every day?
Anyway, get ready.
We have to go meet Guddu.
Don't forget your medicines.
They are useless.
I'm fed up of applying
them every day.
And onions now cost Rs. 150 per kilo.
Why don't you come to the point?
How much will you charge to take us there?
Give me what you
had given me last time.
-Thirty bucks.
-Fifty, sir.
- Forty.
-Come on, forty?
Fine, give me forty.
-Come. Hop on.
-Let's go, mister.
-Hop on.
-Let it go.
How's your joint pain, ma'am?
Look at the road, not her knees.
-What are you doing?
-He's not driving fast enough.
I'm pedaling quite fast.
I'm not the one
who is suffering from joint pains.
Make sure you discuss it with Guddu today.
Who else will you tell,
if not your own son?
Slow down, slow down
or your knees will start hurting again.
Go and sit there.
-Huh?
-Go, sit.
-Good morning, sir .
-Good morning, good morning.
-Help me find this address?
-Sure, let me have that.
-Is Ravi here?
-No.
Remember to discuss it with him.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, son. How are you?
What are you doing?
What do you expect us to
be doing at 11 in the night, Dad?
Can't you call at a better time?
Your mom's joint pain is getting worse.
Well, it delays everything.
You have an excuse for everything,
don't you?
Joint pain only gets worse with age.
There is no treatment
for that even in America.
Even if there was,
what would we do in America anyway?
How would we even get there?
Tell me something,
why do you call on Skype every week?
You can call on the phone too.
We can't see you on the phone.
We get to see you on this.
Look, Erica.
Hey, Erica!
Hello. Look at your grandfather.
Look at your grandpa.
Keep it down.
You aren't the only one here.
-Hello.
-She should hear us.
She's so far away.
Where's her mom?
Her mom?
Here's her mom.
Why don't you make the presentation?
She has to give a presentation
in her office tomorrow, Mom.
She is busy working on that.
Oh, I see.
You're coming here for Diwali,
aren't you?
No Mom, I don't have the time.
-It has been six years now.
-Oh, my baby,
You always say you don't have the time.
You should take out
some time for your parents.
Right.
She should also know
that we have a house here.
-We will feed her delicious Indian snacks.
-Baby, don't cry.
Do you know how expensive
flights to India are?
Diwakar, please calm her down.
-Please take care of her.
-Come here, my baby.
-Talk to him.
-Let him come back on the screen first.
"Talk to him. Talk to him. "
-Son, listen--
-Dad, Erica is getting irritable.
I'll call you back.
They named
their child Erica Mishra.
What kind of a name
is Erica Mishra?
Is this supposed to be a name?
You should have talked to him.
You were there.
Erica Mishra was crying
and I was talking to my son.
He'll call back.
Let's go.
Erica is not such a bad name.
Erica Mishra.
-Say airplane.
-Airplane.
And what have you written here?
"Aerplane. "
It's airplane. "I", not "E".
Correct it.
-"Plants were seen. "
-Plants.
-Then...
-"Then suddenly... "
-Greetings, Granny.
-Bless you.
Hey. Stupid girl.
That's enough now.
Send her here.
-Go.
-Why are you so late?
Sorry, sir.
Dad had sent me to the market.
You and your father
will ruin your future.
Sit down and take out
your Maths book.
Granny, shall I come along
with you to the temple?
No need.
She has a lot of work to do.
You take your books out.
-15 times 2?
-30.
Then write 2 here.
I forgot to get a pencil.
"I forgot to get a pencil. "
"A small kid got stuck in the mud. "
Let's play hide and seek.
Look, he managed
to escape once again.
What happened?
Why do I need to worry
when I have a kitty.
I'll teach this mouse a lesson.
I'm not Kitty, I'm Naina.
"I'm not Kitty, I'm Naina. "
Go, Kitty, do your homework.
Get up and get going.
"The news of a young man's death
was published along with his picture. "
"This news came from Vidhaura, Malwada... "
"When Tara showed Gunjan"
"the picture of the dead body,
she started crying. "
"She said that it was her son So... "
Bunty!
-Come down. The power is back.
-"... her son Sonu's. "
"After the corpse was identified,
the police... "
3000 on the 17th, 1500...
I'm going to the bank.
Do you need anything?
We have run out of wheat flour.
Lock the door.
Are you crazy? You want me
to do four rounds on my bike?
Am I your servant?
You should've sent a loader along.
There is a limit.
Sir!
-Morning.
Where are you off to?
Just some errands to run.
Running errands, where?
To the bank.
Bank!
Great.
Then your morning is indeed good.
Let me drop you.
No, I'll manage.
It's nearby.
Let me give you a lift.
Am I not like your son?
Come on, hop on.
Come, come. Hop on.
And what about these?
May I say something, sir?
Your good days are finally here.
You are going to the bank,
money is also coming in dollars.
It's perfect.
Let me tell you something.
I have applied for a passport.
I'll get it soon enough.
You should talk to Guddu.
What will you do in America?
The same thing I do here.
And Mr. Shambhunath Mishra,
everyone in Gwalior is wearing my brand.
There I'll make sure
that Trump also wears it.
By the way, how much money
did you spend to send Guddu there?
If I know how much it'll cost me I can
ask my father to break the fixed deposit.
It'll help me get married as well.
I want to get married there.
Look, we have reached.
We have reached our destination, sir.
This is as far as I'll go.
Here? Huh?
Yes.
Get down, please.
This is as far as I'll go.
Your bank is nearby.
That way.
Go on.
Drop these two parcels at Rajni Textiles,
it's right next to Chourasiya Bhawan.
Tell them Bittoo sent them.
Go on.
Here you go.
You have deducted a lot this time.
Don't blame us, blame the system.
Everyone is bearing
the brunt these days.
Why did you take a loan
at floating interest rate?
Your loan will get approved as soon
as we are done with the formalities.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Your son is very intelligent.
Sir, please, I needed more money.
Diwakar, I told you what I can do.
Pandit, why are you
sending your son to America?
Our country has everything nowadays.
Why don't you mind
your own business?
Let me decide where
I want to go, okay?
Doesn't your board say,
"Study Now, Pay Later?"
We'll repay it.
You anyway have my father's
fixed deposit with you.
Diwakar, management makes
these posters, we don't.
And if anything goes wrong, we are
the ones who have to face the music.
Nowadays, help is only offered
to those who don't need it.
Listen, make it three kilos.
Okay.
Why did you come?
You should've rung me up.
-I would've sent Lattu over.
-No.
You should let Lattu study.
Don't force him into these things.
-Got it?
-Bye.
What is this?
A mouse trap.
What have you brought?
We have a temple in our house.
You want us to sin
by killing another being?
The previous one was better.
It could trap them and
we could release them outside.
-Take it away.
-What are you saying?
We'll release them
and they'll come back inside.
They are incorrigible.
We should kill them.
Keep it away.
Get it out.
Whenever I try to do anything nice...
You threw it in the vegetable basket.
Take it away.
Keep it aside.
Freshen up, I'll serve dinner.
-This woman...
-And use soap.
I will.
That's the problem with you.
You never use logic.
You just keep saying "go wash up,
go wash up. " I...
Who is it?
Touch his feet.
Let her touch your feet.
She is just like your daughter.
Come.
Can I get a roti?
It's chicken.
We don't cook meat here.
My folks don't either.
That's why I brought cooked chicken.
Do you have a problem
serving it as well?
Go get a plate and a glass.
No, I'll get it.
-Want some?
-No.
What?
It's short by Rs. 2,000.
I'll pay it in a few days.
Okay.
Did they leave?
Shut up.
Get up now. Get going.
Come on.
Master,
you should pay
the interest on time.
I too have bills to pay, yeah?
You go.
Mom, I need Rs. 25 lakh even if I
stick to the bare minimum expenses.
Rs. 25 lakh is a huge sum, son.
How will your father arrange it?
Then what is the point of this 10 lakh?
It won't even last me six months.
Fine! I'll also lead
a mediocre life just like him,
filling the cooler
with buckets of water.
He is doing his best.
He isn't doing enough, Mom.
I've studied in a government school.
I managed to become an engineer
without any coaching.
I did it all on my own.
And now when it's time
to do something, he isn't doing it.
I'm doing what I can, son.
I'm giving you 10 lakhs.
But you want 25 lakhs.
From where do I get
the additional 1.5 million?
Should I sell myself?
Mortgage the house? Tell me how?
Everyone does it, Dad.
Why do you worry?
I'll repay it.
Heard that?
He's talking numbers with me.
The oil massage has made him smarter.
See what you can do.
A cold winter night,
in the ruins of Chambal.
It gets quite cold out there.
There were three dacoits
in front of me and I was unarmed.
Why did you go there unarmed?
Even my department
didn't ask me that.
You should stick to grinding stones.
All I had was a matchbox,
so I started a fire.
Then all the three dacoits gathered
around the bonfire to warm themselves.
That gave me ample
time to do my thing..
He is waiting inside.
-Who will grind the stones?
-No!
Who will grind the stones?
Hey!
He is waiting inside.
Get the big stones to the other side!
Sir, may I ask you something?
Why does a person become a dacoit?
Wait, asshole, I'll tell you.
Get lost.
The cop is waiting inside for you.
He is waiting inside.
Why did you come here?
I would've come to you
in a couple of days.
It's less.
You can count.
I did.
It's not enough for the number
of businesses you are carrying out.
I need to give others as well.
All the boozing, womanizing,
pimping and money laundering,
you do all this in Shakti Singh's area.
Why? Do you have family
living in other areas?
Keep my family out of it.
What do I tell Dada?
Just tell him my name.
He won't question you.
Slowly.
My bones!
It hurts.
You climb 50 steps every day
to visit your deity.
It's all His mercy.
That's why I can climb
so many steps even with such knees.
Anyone else in my place
wouldn't even be able to move.
If He is so generous,
why don't you ask Him to come down
and visit you instead?
You want to test God as well, Master?
He is testing us, isn't He?
Guddu, here, talk to your father.
Here.
-Guddu?
-It's Guddu.
Guddu?
-Hello?
-What happened?
Yes, Dad, tell me,
I got a missed call from you.
-Missed call?
-Talk to him.
I'll deposit Rs. 5,000 tomorrow.
I'm hanging up now.
What did he say?
Hmm?
Your son will deposit Rs. 5,000 tomorrow.
What will you do with so much money?
Eat your ice cream.
I'll be back.
Two... this is interest amount,
Rs. 2,000, that you owe me.
Okay?
You can keep Rs. 500.
I'm a man of principles.
I had used your room the other day.
Rent for that.
What are you glaring at me for?
That's how much I pay at a hotel.
Understood?
Did you have the ice cream?
Good.
Give the car a push, it's stopped.
She's my daughter.
Look, she's my daughter.
Do you want me to insult you
in front of her?
Go, give the car a push.
Go, go, go...
Stop, stop, stop!
What's going on, huh?
I'd prefer it if you stay
out of my personal business.
What happens inside
the house is your business.
What happens on the road is ours.
Sir, should we deflate the tires?
We've done enough damage.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
Leave.
I'm being polite because
you have your daughter with you.
Let's go, Pandit.
Let me know if he bothers you again.
-Okay.
-Okay?
Okay.
How much is this one?
Rs. 550.
-This one?
It costs Rs. 700.
It contains exotic fruits.
How much for these small ones?
-These?
-70.
Can you write a name on them?
Why weren't we blessed
with her as our daughter?
You're right.
Things would've been very different
if we had a daughter.
You never celebrated my birthday.
Is it?
I didn't know the date
on which you were born.
Why not make one up?
Fine.
Let's celebrate Kitty's
and your birthday on the same day.
Happy birthday.
Big Kitty and Small Kitty.
Sir, you had told
me about a property.
Yes.
Why don't you show it to me?
Where have you been, sir?
We couldn't reach you
on your phone either.
My battery was dead.
I couldn't have plugged it in my back.
Here, charge it.
Okay.
Dada was here.
He waited for quite some time.
He was asking for you.
He seemed quite angry, sir.
Give me your phone.
Hello, Dada, my phone battery was dead.
You should've charged it at that
whore's place, where you hang out all day.
You can ask Sharma, I was with him,
tallying the accounts.
I'll shove the account
books up your ass.
The inspector came
to my house in the evening
because your phone was switched off.
He's an idiot, Dada.
He's a...
He said things he shouldn't
have in front of other people.
What am I even paying you for?
He should never come
here again, Pandey.
He won't.
I've found a solution.
I'll let you know once it's done.
Okay? Bye.
You are yet to finish
all the revision questions.
-You should--
-Come in.
Of all the lot,
this property belongs to him.
It's going strong since 100 years.
It's a prime property.
That's the bedroom.
It's okay.
Take a look.
-Pandey, this is my house--
-Yes, I know.
It will be as good as new
after a fresh coat of paint.
Go outside, I'm coming.
-I'm paying you back. Am I not?
-For how long will you keep paying me?
Why don't you get out
of this mess once and for all?
It will benefit both of us.
I don't have anything
other than this.
other than this, either.
I'm done, master.
-Naina, you leave.
-Hmm.
Naina, hurry up.
Come here.
What is your name?
-Naina.
-Very good.
Here.
Master won't scold you.
Here, take it.
Bye, sir.
Vacate the place.
Start packing.
Motherfucker!
KOTWALI LASHKAR POLICE STATION
GWALIOR, MP
Sir, there was a call
from the Commissioner’s office.
What happened?
-Okay.
-Sir, this one too.
Sir.
Master!
You've come to file
a complaint against me?
You should have told me.
Make sure you note down
his complaint properly?
Have a seat.
What is it?
He had come to my place last evening.
He will come to your place if you've
taken a loan from him, Pandit.
Did he assault you?
There is so much crime in the city.
Should I handle that or your loan issues?
Here, have some water.
Look, I'll suggest that
you somehow repay the loan.
He is an asshole.
You...
Everything was going smooth, right?
Why did you go to the police?
Stand up.
Get up and get me a glass.
Come on.
Sit down!
Look, I can throw you out
whenever I want.
Who will come to save you?
That useless son of yours?
I'm a nice man.
A nice man.
Hey...
Sit over here.
Sit here.
Okay.
The interest....
I will forgo four months of interest.
And I'll also reduce around
Rs. 1,50,000 from the principal amount.
Once I sell the house,
I'll give you a few lakhs as well.
Your wife has gone to the temple, right?
She'll only come back
after the prayers are over?
She will not be back
for another hour or so, right?
Yes.
Go get Naina.
Tell her family that you're
taking an extra class today, okay?
Go.
I won't hurt her.
She won't feel any pain.
Go.
Listen... What is it called...
Yes, give me some
snacks before you leave.
Why are you sitting in the dark?
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
Where are you?
Are you sitting here?
Where are you sit--
The situation was such that...
Manju, Manju, Manju...
Calm down, calm down.
Relax, I'll handle everything.
Calm down.
Go inside.
Manju, go inside.
Manju, I said go inside!
Come on.
Sit down.
Has everyone got their ticket?
Have you taken the ticket?
Mahinder! Mahinder!
Good thing you started a fire.
There are a lot of mosquitoes out here.
Damn it!
I refueled it just yesterday.
Bloody thieves stole all of it.
TEACHERS COMMITTEE
FOR CHILD EDUCATION
Where is Lattu?
At home, studying.
I want wheat flour, five kilos.
I just installed a new blade,
Master.
I'll grind the grains finely.
You'll be very pleased
with the result.
Really?
Do you have...
Listen?
Yes?
Do you have change for Rs. 2,000?
Can you check?
I don't, Master.
Can you go and get
the change for me, please?
I'll go and try.
I couldn't get the change, Master.
Master?
I couldn't get the change.
Take the wheat flour.
You can pay me tomorrow.
No.
I don't like to take things on credit.
I'll take it tomorrow.
O Lord, have mercy on all of us.
O Lord Sri Ram...
Dalit agitation is picking up pace.
There has been a curfew instated
in four sensitive areas of Gwalior.
Yes. There is a curfew
During the total shutdown in India,
the problem...
-Hey!
-I have a correspondent...
reporting live from...
-Passport.
-Passport?
We can see the effects of the shutdown
all across Madhya Pradesh.
Stop watching the news.
Why did you turn it off?
Here's my breaking news.
My passport!
Here's my visa form.
Lose your life but
never lose your passport.
What should I do?
Not much.
Just call Guddu and ask him
how to fill up the form.
I don't want to feel embarrassed
in front of foreigners.
Come on, call him up.
Come on, hurry up.
Sure, take a look.
You must have filled one too.
I have mentioned
Guddu as my reference.
Check if everything is in order.
Buzz off, motherfucker.
You broke my heart.
Give me your passport.
Hey! Give it to me.
No.
I said no.
"Thanking you, yours faithfully... "
"Thanking you. "
No one will leave until we are done
with our investigation.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
Got it?
Come in, sir.
Who are you?
BKB.
Full name.
Brijesh Kumar Bittoo.
-Have a seat.
-Work?
Work?
-I run a business.
-Hello.
Business?
Of what?
Bra, panties, knickers, vests.
It's a big business.
-Of knickers and vests!
-You know Pandey?
Yes.
Sir, Pandey is the guy who
visits your place frequently, right?
Yes.
A little.
Did he come here
day before yesterday?
The day before yesterday?
I don't know.
I wasn't here.
I wasn't here that night.
Where were you?
I was partying at Jagdamba Banquet.
You can ask them.
Should I give you their number?
You can confirm it.
I can confirm it on my own.
Go.
Pandey has been missing
since three days.
His phone is switched off.
And we tracked his last visited location
to this place.
He used to come here quite often.
When was the last time you met him?
He had come here the same night
I had come to lodge a complaint with you.
Why had he come here?
To collect the money.
I had told you that the money...
I paid him all the money,
with interest.
After that?
Oh that way.
After that he had some alcohol...
and left.
Did he come alone?
Or did he have company?
He had come alone that day.
What do you mean?
He used to come with a woman.
He used to introduce her
to me by different names,
but it used to be
the same woman always.
Master, did Pandey talk to someone
on the phone in front of you?
Did he fight with someone over the phone?
Did you find anything
strange about Pandey that day?
No.
Master, you also read
Manohar Kahaniyaan?
I haven't read this one.
Can I take it
if you are done reading it?
-Won't be able to read it again.
-Who else stays in this house?
My better half.
My wife.
Call her.
-Okay.
-Sit down.
Call out her name.
Manju?
She doesn't keep well.
Not much.
It's okay.
If you remember anything,
come to the police station
and let me know.
Okay.
-Got it?
-Bye.
You shouldn't have looked so scared.
The cops are suspicious now.
I could get caught because of you.
It won't happen again.
I won't let it happen.
Have you vowed
not to speak to me again?
You won't support me in this?
Mr. Shambhunath Mishra?
The cops told me
that he was with you that night.
Yes, he was.
Mr. Mishra,
I know he's not a nice man.
But that doesn't change
the fact that he is Munni's father.
She keeps asking me,
"When will Dad come back?"
What should I tell her?
I request you,
if you know anything at all...
How he behaves with me doesn't matter.
But he is very attached to Munni.
Ma'am, I'm approaching
everyone he used to meet.
Do you know anything?
Look, we have already
told the cops what we know.
We'll update them
if we have any other information.
Let me see you out.
This way, please.
We have committed a grave sin.
A grave sin.
A girl has lost her father because of us.
We had no right to punish him.
We didn't have faith in our God.
We have committed a grave sin.
A grave sin.
Hello, Detective Premchand.
Over here, please.
Where to, huh?
Come here.
Come here, pretty please.
Don't feel shy.
Well...
I wanted to meet the SP.
Mr. Shakti Singh.
Sitaram Gadariya.
Temporary station in-charge.
I plan to change the country.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
Mr. Singh has gone to Bhopal.
He goes there frequently.
You won't sit until I ask you to?
Sit down.
Sit.
-Please have a seat.
-Thank you.
Would you like some water?
-No, thank you.
-Fine.
So, do you have
any update on Pandey?
You won't get any update on him.
We won't?
You say it so confidently,
as if you've killed him.
Yes, I did.
With a knife?
Yes, with a knife.
Then you chopped his
body into small pieces?
Yes.
Well done.
And then you burnt his body?
July Edition,
Manohar Kahaniyaan, Page 23...
"Chandan's affair
with his sister-in-law. "
The last line, "Chandan scattered
his brother's ashes in Haridwar. "
"And the police could
never catch them. "
I ground them.
Ground them?
Well done, boss.
That's an excellent twist.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
I suggest you start
writing your own stories.
Don't bite more than
you can chew, okay?
Master, one guy was sentenced
for a bunch of years
for misleading and wasting the time
of some police officer.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
You should get going, Master.
Go read the new edition.
Got it?
Otherwise, you'll get arrested
under all the possible sections.
Buzz off now.
I did indeed kill him.
Oh, my God!
Hariya?
Yes, sir?
Will you respectfully
show Master the door?
No, I'll manage.
I'm going.
No, I'll go on my own.
Hey, why don't you say...
you chopped someone up
and then ground him?
You bloody...
I went to the police station.
Not because I have committed a sin.
I went there because you
think I have committed a sin.
Will you please sit
here for two minutes?
"I will forgo interest for a few months. "
"I'll also reduce a few lakh rupees
from the principal amount. "
"I'll give you a few lakhs
extra for this house as well. "
"Your wife's gone to the temple, right?"
"She will not be back
for another hour or so. "
"You have to do me a small favor. "
"Get Naina here for some time. "
"Don't worry. I won't hurt her. "
That's disgusting!
Why are you saying such things?
It made you angry, didn't it?
It had made me angry as well.
You too would have killed him,
just like I did.
I didn't kill him,
I slayed him.
I slayed a demon.
I don't care
whether anyone likes it or not,
I did what I thought was right.
That's it.
Don't drink too much.
I'm going to bed.
I did what I thought was right.
The number you have called
is currently unavailable.
Come on, sir.
<i
...is currently unavailable.
I wouldn't keep calling like this
even if my wife went missing.
You are taking this too seriously.
Have a drink.
The number you have called
is out of coverage area.
The number you have called--
Was he swallowed by the earth
or eaten up by the sky?
Where did Pandey go, huh?
Did someone kill that asshole?
That reminds me, sir,
I thrashed my boy
black and blue yesterday.
He keeps singing the same
song day in and day out.
"My time will come. "
He doesn't study.
And yes, that reminds me,
Master had come over.
You know what he said?
He said that he killed Pandey.
Chopped him up, burnt his body
and then ground his bones.
I scolded him and asked him
to leave before I actually arrest him.
He was telling me a made-up story....
straight out of Manohar Kahaniyaan.
What's wrong?
He was telling the truth.
You better ask him to come to the
police station and record his statement.
"My time will come. "
I wonder when his time will come.
Yes?
Sign here.
What is this?
Statement.
Whose?
It just states what you
had told Sitaram the other day.
I didn't tell him anything.
He is the one who
made it up and wrote it.
I had come to give him the copy
of Manohar Kahaniyaan's yearly edition.
Tell him.
Sign it.
What is the official term for it?
The evidence list?
Did you find the dead body?
Did you find any murder weapon?
Or my fingerprints anywhere?
Mr. Singh,
Pandey is an acquaintance.
Do let me know... if you
get any information about him.
SHAKTI SINGH
POLICE STATION IN-CHARGE
Asshole.
Manohar Kahaniyaan,  motherfucker!
Hurry up or the officer will leave.
Hello?
Mr. Shambhunath Mishra?
Yes?
I want you to reach home in 20 minutes.
I'm waiting for you downstairs.
Who is this?
That doesn't matter.
Do as you are told.
Be there.
-Hello?
-Stop saying hello and get here.
-Hurry up or I'll go upstairs.
Who is this?
I have gone through the books.
Hurry up.
-People haven't paid interest--
-Come on.
Some haven't paid the principal amount.
He had taken Rs. 5 lakh
for a loading depot 1.5 years ago.
He has repaid half of it.
But he hasn't paid interest
in four months.
What do we do with him, Dada?
If he doesn't pay the interest
in a week, shut his depot.
Okay, Dada.
Get going.
Dada, he is from Lashkar...
Dada, he is Mr. Mishra from Dana Oli.
Hello.
Pandey was personally
handling his account.
This is Mr. Sharma.
Yes, I know him.
Hi.
-I know him.
-He has repaid your loan in full.
But Pandey...
Pandey works for me.
Pandey never told me.
He was hired so that people
don't get to know that I'm involved.
You see,
people are quite scared of me.
But I have repaid
the loan in full to Pandey.
Pandey has gone missing.
Why don't you do something?
You find Pandey for me.
I'll get my money
and you'll get your house.
You have three days.
But... the whole family stays there.
-How can I--
-Who's next?
He's from Murar.
-Kashi...
-But...
Buzz off!
Dada, he owns Laxman Traders,
he had borrowed Rs. 10 lakh.
He owes...
Close all the pending accounts
of Pandey's at the earliest.
Okay, Dada.
Don't look so surprised.
You know why I'm here.
Though Master had confessed to Sitaram,
he later went back on his word.
He is trapped now.
He will get caught sooner or later.
You should tell him to cooperate with me.
I'm sure he listens to you.
Look, I understand your problem.
But Master...
Why are you troubling such a nice man?
Don't you have any shame?
I've known him for 40 years.
He has never done anything wrong.
Not now, not ever.
Are you alright?
Well, that Inspector
approached me at the temple.
He tried to corner me
but I didn't get scared.
Don't worry.
Pandey used to work
for a guy called Rathore.
I met him today.
He said I'll have
to vacate the house,
if I don't give him
the money within three days.
How much do we owe him?
Rs. 10 lakh?
Is this a joke?
From where will I get
that kind of money, Mom?
I told you,
we just bought a house here.
Son, we'll lose our home if your father
doesn't pay him the money in three days.
You guys will never stop asking,
will you?
You need something every day.
A new excuse every time.
Joint pain, house...
What is going on?
Would you like to talk to Erica?
Erica?
How much do we owe you?
Total 320.
Pay him.
And ask him to close our account.
We won't be coming back.
You can stop here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Come.
Be careful, be careful.
I'm fine.
Forty.
Hello, sir.
For how long have
you known Mr. Mishra?
From the time I came from Morena.
I usually do my business in this area.
So I know him since then.
Did you take Mr. Mishra and his wife
somewhere, say about a week back?
Yes, sir. But only Mr. Mishra.
Where did he go?
I don't know, sir.
I had dropped him at the bus stand.
Do you know Pandey?
Which Pandey, sir?
Prajapati Pandey?
No.
Okay, tell me everything
that happened that night.
Master, where are you
going so late in the night?
Shush.
Let's go.
Take me to the bus stand.
I'll take sixty bucks.
-Including the luggage charges.
-Okay.
He behaved strangely.
How so?
That was the first time
he paid me what I had asked for.
What happened after that?
After that?
He had two sacks with him.
He loaded them
on the rickshaw and then we left.
What was in those sacks?
I don't know, sir.
But I felt like I was carrying
two people including Mr. Mishra.
How do you know?
Sir, I have been pedaling
rickshaws for 15 years.
I just know how much
weight I'm pulling.
Anything else?
Yes, sir.
He stopped at an ATM.
Which ATM?
The ATM before the bus stop.
He stopped there.
Sir, I have heard about people
getting rid of a body in suitcases.
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
This is the first time I'm seeing
someone hiding it in a sack.
I mean, we won't get
anything from this footage.
We will.
First we will get Pandit remanded.
Then we will get his confession.
Don't include
this in the evidence list.
Huh?
Yes, of course.
Yesterday, I saw your
footage from the ATM.
You were looking good.
Let me come to the point.
Where is Pandey's phone?
I have no information
about Pandey, or his phone.
Look, I have come here in civil clothes.
I won't beat around the bush.
I don't care if you killed Pandey,
chopped him up into pieces,
or put him in a sack and buried him.
If you know where Pandey's phone is,
if you have it,
then please give it to me.
Mr. Singh, like I told you earlier,
I have no information
about Pandey or his phone.
Look, I have enough evidence
to keep you in remand for seven days.
And even the mute
start talking there.
Let's end this episode right here.
Just give me his phone.
I know nothing about it.
Let's meet tomorrow.
When I'm in my uniform.
Coming.
What did the Inspector say?
-What did the Inspector say?
-Have you seen a mobile phone?
Didn't you take it with you?
Where did you keep it?
Why are you looking for it over there?
Didn't you take it with you?
At least tell me what you are looking for.
Mobile...
Why are you looking for it over there?
It's not here either.
Mobile...
Come on, tell me.
Hey...
What are you looking for?
I might know where it is.
You should first check your
pockets for your mobile phone.
Mobile...
Whose mobile phone is that?
How did it come here?
Tell me, whose is it?
Where are you going?
Lock the door.
-But where are you going?
-Lock the door.
Tell me, where are you...
During the program...
Do you have its charger?
Yes.
Check it.
It's connected.
-Okay.
-Uncle, it costs 100 bucks.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
Throw everything out.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Throw everything out.
Move aside.
Who is doing this?
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
Manju!
You... !
What are you doing!
Come on!
Master!
Throwing my things out, huh?
Come on!
Let him go.
-Let him go.
-Buzz off.
Leave her alone.
She will get hurt.
Let me go.
We'll pay you back.
We'll vacate the house.
Manju...
-Raghu, get everyone with you.
-Manju...
Hurry up.
Manju...
Everything will be fine.
Where is it?
-Guddu's number...
-What are you looking for?
I'm looking for Guddu's number.
Where is it?
I deleted it.
-You deleted it?
-Yes.
Don't call him even when I die.
The Science Teacher has a nephew,
he can...
You will be fine.
Just keep quiet and rest.
Your blood pressure is quite high.
Looks like you have a death wish.
I'm feeling itchy.
Where?
Here.
Give us a minute.
Go.
So Master,
your life seems to be more
exciting than mine these days.
What I was going to do
to you in the lockup,
you've gotten it done to yourself.
I had given you
a chance to save your skin.
Not me, you were giving yourself
a chance... to save your skin.
I didn't know anything
about this phone.
I found it yesterday.
I had once slapped a kid in school.
And I couldn't sleep
for a couple of nights.
I plunged a screwdriver
straight through Pandey's throat.
I didn't even flinch.
Naina just turned 12.
How can anyone have such
disgusting thoughts about her?
She is just a 12-year-old kid.
I won't hesitate to kill again
if someone has such thoughts about her.
I won't hesitate to kill again.
I'll end his story.
I had come to your office to confess.
I have done what I had to.
Now you decide what you wish to do.
Son?
I have been with him for 40 years now.
I have never stayed away from him,
even for a day.
If he goes to prison
then I too shall go with him.
You want more evidence?
I'll tell you something
no one else knows.
I've said it before
and I'm going to say it again,
hotels are much safer.
You address me as your
sister-in-law in his presence.
You can always come over to ensure
your sister-in-law's well-being.
I am, and I always will be
concerned about your well-being.
I'm just worry about what the MLA would
do to my well-being if he finds me here.
He always calls me
before he leaves Delhi.
He is staying in Delhi until the 14th.
Then it's all good.
I want him to win
the next election as well.
Great performance, I must say.
The MLA loves such videos.
Should I forward it to him?
I know it is a good deed
to please someone.
You continue doing your good deeds,
and stop bothering about my misdeeds.
Master!
SP!
-Dada!
-SP!
Let Dada go!
-Come on!
-Call the SP!
-Dada?
-Hold this.
-Give me a second.
-Dada!
How dare you!
This is not right!
-Come on!
-Inspector!
Why are you taking him with you?
Wait a minute!
-Don't force me to use the baton.
-Dada!
Dada!
This is not right, Shakti Singh.
This is not right.
I know this is not right.
I never do the right thing.
Get in.
You won't be able to keep me
in here for more than two days.
Not more than two days.
"Not more than two days. "
Write the report.
Yes, sir.
We had received a tip off.
We searched Rathore's house.
We found Prajapati Pandey's
clothes and the murder weapon.
Make sure to highlight these points.
Thinks he'll be out in two days.
When did the robbery take place?
-Around two o'clock.
-Okay.
-During the day or at night?
-At night.
What was stolen?
Everything that was in the shop, sir.
Mr. Gadariya?
Huh?
Shambhunath Mishra.
New edition.
"A dacoit in police uniform. "
"Sufficient to satiate my clan. "
This is awesome.
Only a scholar can teach another, Master.
You should read it.
The story's on Page 28.
"A dacoit in police uniform. "
Forget the dacoit.
Hello.
Shambhunath Mishra.
Here's what I owe you.
You were charging me
interest upon interest.
Here's Rs. 10,000.
I cannot give it to you here.
I'll make sure your family gets it.
Are you crazy?
By the way...
I'm the one who killed him.
I had chopped him up into pieces.
Master, you motherfucker!
Hey, he's the one who killed Pandey!
It's this way, right?
-Is it that one?
-Yes.
It's still not ready?
Yes, it's still under construction.
Ganshu?
Naina?
Master?
Bless you.
Where are you going, Granny?
We are leaving.
From now onwards...
This...
Come on, tell them.
From now onwards,
this house belongs to Naina.
Please don't forget to water
my Holy Basil plant, okay?
Take care of it.