Lights out!
Cletus. Are you there?
My angel.
This is for you.
What did the doctor say?
He said the mutations are advancing.
My powers are too strong.
Cletus, I'm scared.
It's gonna be okay.
They're coming to take me away.
They're sending me to a place
where there are others like me.
They can't do that.
They can't take you from me.
You're my one bright light.
I will always love you.
Frances!
Get off!
No!
Any last words?
Welcome to your new home, Frances.
Your old boyfriend's finally
getting what he deserves.
And the world will be
a safer place without him.
Detective Mulligan, with all due respect,
I don't want anything
to do with Cletus Kasady.
Well, that's too bad,
because he only wants to see you.
In my opinion, you had
your chance with Kasady and you blew it.
Right. So, what does he want?
Maybe he wants to spill the beans
about where the missing bodies are buried.
So you're gonna have to do
the right thing for a change.
No! Take your tiny hands off of me!
We should be out there,
protecting the city. Lethally!
What was that?
Unhand me!
Man should never consent to crawl
when he has the impulse to fly.
You are a bottom-feeder.
Be quiet.
How many times have I told you
that I want you to hide yourself
when I am working?
I am serious. It is important.
You have to show me respect.
-Respect? Respect?
-Yes! Yes.
-Okay.
-Kasady gonna give you the scoop, right?
-Right.
-Wrong.
-What do you mean?
Because you blow everything.
Okay, I see.
You're talking about Anne again.
I miss her!
-l will do it.
-l don't like you.
Let me eat him!
You do not deserve nice things.
Welcome back, Eddie Brock.
I've been thinking about you.
What do you want, Cletus?
I mean, why am I here?
Do a man who's buried alive
a kindness, won't you?
Get a message out to all my...
fans...
and in return,
-Il give you my life...
‘What?
story.
I heard the written word
hasn't been working out so well.
Piece like this, an exclusive...
would put you back on top.
Go on.
People love...
serial killers.
All my secrets
laid bare, Eddie.
So much camage.
But why me?
I like you.
All right, it's a deal.
What's your message?
"That distant cathedral...
is all I see...
fractured angel...
the other part of me."
Print that in your column.
Is that it? Who's gonna read that?
Some random haiku?
Print it...
and what's mine...
is yours.
Lucky me.
Goodbye, Eddie.
Thank you.
What a dick.
Eddie, look.
Look.
What are you doing?
Your job for you.
Eddie.
Don't forget me, Eddie.
What did you get?
I got a headache
and probably got tuberculosis.
What? A little louder.
He read me poetry, man.
Is this some kind of joke to you?
Because I'm not laughing.
Yeah, you could do with a laugh.
Come on, man. These things,
they just take a little time. All right?
-The second he gives you something--
-Of course.
Keep me ahead of the curve, Eddie.
Don't embarrass me!
Do you understand?
Trust me. The only scoop I'm getting
today is double chocolate chip.
No! I get brain freeze.
Come here.
Look.
-I'm looking.
Grab those.
All right.
Okay.
Now,
what do you think?
-I think I'm Pablo Picasso.
-No!
-Okay.
-Come here. Look.
Well, say what you see.
-It's a house.
-Never mind.
Oh, I know this one! It's a tree!
Idiot! Sit down.
Now...
pay attention.
Bingo.
Holy cow.
Would you say
your friendship with Cletus Kasady
is what allowed you
to solve this decades-old mystery?
You are the only person
from the outside world he's spoken with.
Seems he likes you.
Well, you know, he's a serial killer.
I don't see how he can like anyone.
Brock was able to uncover
what the FBI and police could not.
Bowing to public outrage,
the governor of California
has overturned his moratorium
and reinstated
the death penalty for Kasady.
Brock's career's been given
a much-needed revival,
putting him back on top once more.
A harrowing story finally comes to an end.
Vindication for the victims
and closure for the families,
thanks to the diligence of one man.
Thank you, Eddie Brock.
And Venom!
You know, this could be us, Eddie.
Going out there, solving cases.
Fighting bad guys. Maybe I eat them.
And then we save the day.
But we saved the day. It's done.
You said I could eat bad guys!
This again?
I need to be free!
Feeling the wind in my hair
and the sand between my toes.
You don't have any hair.
You are not listening to me.
Oh, I'm listening.
I cannot live like this anymore!
I'm starving!
So eat those guys.
I can't.
Sonny and Cher are best friends.
Are you serious?
That's ridiculous. That's what--
Man, that was abusive.
That was abuse.
And that's a $2000 TV.
You have got to get control
of your aggression.
That is why we have Snookie!
I cannot live on chicken
and chocolate alone. I need brains!
Chickens have brains.
1 most passionately disagree.
Look. Look at those poor idiots.
Small brains.
Come on, man, it's not their fault
that you live on the old phenylethyla--
Laphenylethylan--
-Phenylethylalanine.
-Yeah, I just said that.
I've told you a thousand times,
because it is only found in brains
-and in chocolate.
-And chocolate.
That's right. Well, how about this:
You live in my body, you live by my rules.
1 live in your body
because, unfortunately,
1 don't have many options.
Well, how about this, son?
The FBI is still investigating us
for all of that stuff
that "we were involved with."
So if one more head goes missing,
we will get hauled off into Area 51.
They will kill us both.
So somebody has to be responsible.
Responsibility.
it's for the mediocre.
-Food!
-Can you stop doing that?
-Please just stop doing that.
Come on, stop doing that!
I have a deadline! Will you stop it?
Goddamn it! Fine!
-Good evening, Eddie.
-Hey, Mrs. Chen.
Good evening, Venom.
He says hi.
-Chocolate hasn't arrived yet.
-No!
Oh, no. We have a deal.
What's gonna happen?
You gonna stop protecting me?
I don't think so.
I've been keeping my mouth shut,
feeding your little secret.
Little old Mrs. Chen
is a little old blackmailer, huh?
Less of the old. 1 am 39.
-And I am Barry Manilow.
-Right.
1am happy to eat Mrs. Chen.
No, no, you cannot eat Mrs. Chen.
-What?
-l guess it's gonna have to be plan B.
What's plan B?
Not this again!
I need human brains to survive.
Now, pick up some chickens, man. Let's go.
I'm done with this grossness.
Look at all the amazing things
that we can do!
We are wasting our talent.
Bad guy!
Hello, kitty!
Leave him. Leave him be.
Leave him be! Leave him be!
-I shall remove your head.
-No, you won't.
-I will use it for bowling!
-No, you will not!
I will take it to--
What is the one that we like, Eddie?
it's Lucky Strike.
-Yes!
-Put him down.
Lucky Strike.
I will take you to Lucky Strike.
-And I will score a 300-point game.
-You won't
The rest of your pudgy little boy body
will be left here,
rolling around in dumpster juice.
Oh, God.
No! Put him down!
No, no, no! No! No!
Fine!
She didn't want our help.
She did not know
she needed our help, Eddie.
There is a difference.
itis Anne!
Anne is on the phone, Eddie!
-Hey, Anne.
-Hey, Eddie. Hi.
-Hi.
-Be nice to her.
You sound out of breath.
I'm not catching you at a bad time, am 1?
No, no, not at all. I'm just--
I'm just hanging around.
I'm sorry I haven't returned your calls.
I guess...
I just needed a little space
after the whole...
alien-biting-a-guy's-head-off thing, so--
The good old days.
Anyway, so I have some news,
and I was wondering if we could meet?
Yes!
Yeah, sure, that would be--
That would be fine. Great.
-Okay, great. How's tomorrow night?
-Tomorrow night?
-Yeah. Great.
-8:007
-L'Araignée?
-Okay, great.
-Looking forward to it.
-Me too. Bye.
-Great.
-It's over with the doctor!
That is the voice of a woman
who just got brutally dumped.
Stop!
Don't you want to look your best?
Just leave me alone.
You are always nitpicking.
Hey!
Hey.
-Okay. Hi.
-Yeah.
Awkward.
So how's it going? How's Mr. Belvedere?
Good, good.
He's still wiping his ass on the carpet.
He learned that from you.
Yeah. How's the legal aid work going?
You know how much I love an underdog.
Yeah, that's why you
put up with me for so long.
You said it.
So.
-So.
-So?
I don't know, I thought it would be
better to tell you in person that--
No!
Anne. Wow, that is--
That is so much bigger
than the one that I got you.
It's gaudy.
That's Dan, right? Dr. Dan.
Yeah, it's Dan.
Holy shit, Anne. Way to go.
Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm okay. Yeah.
-Well, I am not okay.
You could just say,
"Congratulations, I'm happy for you."
You know, like two people who still
care enough about each other to lie
so that the other one
doesn't feel like complete shit.
Maybe we could do that version of this?
-No, I am happy for you, Anne.
-No!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
That was going to be us, Eddie!
1, for one, would not be inconsolable
if Dan were to fall into traffic
and lose his head and his feet
and all of his teeth!
-What?
-What was that?
What? Nothing.
If I ask you a question, do you
have the ability to tell me the truth?
You mean, as in being super happy
for you because of your engagement?
Because you just told me to lie,
so that's really confusing.
Is Venom with you?
He's dead.
Iam. I'm playing dead right now.
Yeah, I mean, he--
Right.
-Okay.
-Good.
Well, that's--
You just don't change, do you?
What are you talking about?
This is just a huge shock.
Anne, I'm in love with you.
This is a lot to process.
The truth is you don't love anybody.
You can't.
Commitment's just not your thing.
All right, then, fine.
Do not marry Dan.
Dan makes me feel safe.
And you made me feel
like I was on a roller coaster.
Sometimes you have
to know when to get off.
-Yeah, and not yak.
-And not yak!
You know? Not yak.
Yak.
Hey, Venom. Take care of him, all right?
Don't let him
keep messing everything up.
I'm going to make you cry now, Eddie.
She will love it.
Cry.
It's a lot to process.
Congratulations, Anne.
That's great news.
Slow down, pal!
Why? You don't believe in consequences.
No injuries. You fix them.
No hangovers. You mend them.
I couldn't even hurt myself if I tried!
Eddie, I apologise
that I can't mend the heart.
Emotional pain, it hits much harder.
And it lasts longer.
You just need to pull up
your big-boy pants and fake it.
Yeah, well, that's easy for you to say.
Why?
Because I'm a real boy.
And you're just an amoeba.
1 will only take that
because we are hurting right now.
Don't worry, buddy.
1 will get you through this.
Do you know what always
cheers me up in the morning, Eddie?
Sausages. And brains!
1 say either
And I say either
I say neither
Neither, either, either, neither
Let's call the whole thing off
Potahtoes
1 like tomatoes
And I like tomahto
Potatoes, potahtoes
Tomatoes, tomahtoes
Let's call the whole thing off
Cheer up, old pal!
And, oh
If we call the whole thing off
Then we must part
That's for you.
Are you pen pals with an ant?
Listen to this.
"Dearest pally pal,
I hereby invite you to witness
my demise,
my final moments
on this spinning shit wheel
that we call Earth."
You are responsible
for bringing about
the end of Cletus Kasady.
It's only right that you hold the door
for me on my way out.
They'll stop my heart,
Just like it stopped at my birth.
What if Cletus Kasady
had never been revived?
He would never have pushed Grandma
down a flight of stairs.
Bye-bye, Grandma,
you puckered old sphincter.
He would never have thrown
a hair dryer into Mother's bathtub.
Yes, Mama, I'm a bad, bad boy.
He would never have been beaten
to the brink of death by Daddy-o
and sent fo...
St. Estes Home for Unwanted Children.
That circus of hell...
with one bright light.
Oh, Eddie.
We are all born into this world
through blood and pain.
Every hero has an origin story.
Your friend...
"Cletus Kasady.
Kiss, hug, kiss, hug.
Smiley face."
Nut job.
You know, I should be there.
No, it's a bad idea.
I mean, I put him there.
Actually, he put himself there
when he decided to be a complete lunatic.
Ta-da!
You know, it would be nice
just to have your support, just for once.
Ketchup?
This place is an all-you-can-eat buffet.
Who's going to care if I polish off
a couple of these idiots?
You can't be sure who is
and who is not guilty, buddy.
They're in prison!
Yeah, but some people
take false confessions.
You know, they take pleas.
We watched Making a Murderer.
-You all right?
-Yeah, man, I'm just practising.
Iam a predator, Eddie.
Lions do not eat salad!
But you're not a lion, are you?
I see you more of a vexatious
little pig-dog-house-bat thing.
That's fine.
-You suck.
-You suck!
-Excuse me?
-Yeah, wow.
I don't have an explanation for that.
I think I'm having a panic attack.
Yeah, I'l sign here.
Stand two feet away from the bars.
No touching the condemned.
Understood.
Visitor's here!
This is a "me" thing,
not a "we" thing.
Everything is a "you" thing.
Happy day for you, Eddie Brock.
What a scoop.
The end of the Magical Misery Tour.
I worry for your soul.
How will you live with the weight
of snuffing out a man's life?
I was hoping maybe you
could give me a couple pointers.
Funny little guy, aren't you?
Don't need that. My memory is outstanding.
Rude.
Consequences.
Every decision you ever make.
Who do we leave behind,
and how do we leave them?
A connubial bed, empty.
Waiting in the darkness
for the rescuer who never comes.
Because of you.
This guy makes zero sense.
You and I are the same.
No. No, we're not.
Twisted insides, mean daddies.
You feel like home to me, Eddie.
Like family.
And really, truly, that is all
I ever wanted in this world.
Family.
Killing your grandmother and your mother
sure is a funny way of showing it.
Anything you wanna
unburden yourself with before...
this happens?
Yes.
I have wishes to bestow upon you.
Oh, that is kind.
I want to wish you...
this heartbreak.
Too fate.
I wish for you
to see out your days alone,
as you always have been.
Watch it, pal!
Where are you going with this?
You are a cancer to everyone
who ever loved you, Eddie.
Deceived your trusting fiancée.
And no wonder Daddy
could never look at you again
after you killed his wife, your mother,
just by being born.
You son of a bitch!
No, no! No, no, don't! Don't!
Speak to my friend again like that!
I dare you!
Hey, hey!
No touching the inmate. Hey, back up!
Eddie?
You're done.
I have tasted blood before,
my friend, and that is not it.
Eddie Brock has a big secret!
Shut up, Kasady!
-That may have been a mistake.
-Shut up.
Hey, aren't you Eddie Brock?
I don't know anymore.
-Eddie!
-I don't wanna hear another word.
-Eddie.
-I don't wanna hear it.
Eddie, I am sorry.
That was his last time on record ever!
There's no more words for his victims.
You know, they're gone.
Any clues of outstanding bodies,
we've lost forever.
1 didn't mean to.
-You didn't mean to?
-And I said I'm sorry!
You didn't mean to, but you did it.
You just decided, I don't know:
That's it. You did it.
You didn't even think
we might get caught, get killed?
You don't think about things like that.
You think about chickens.
You think about you, you think about
what you want, and you think about you.
Let me remind you of something, Eddie.
You were a loser before I came along.
You were nothing. I made you special!
You made me special?
Let me tell you something.
Before you came along, I had a life.
I didn't have chickens, but I had dreams.
I had dreams and a fiancée
and a really successful TV show!
But you destroyed
all of those things by yourself.
Yeah. But you know what? I rebuilt my life
and now I just wanna live it. Good night.
And how did you build this new life?
Excuse me?
Well, who found the clue on the wall
$0 you could be this big, shiny hero?
Who found the clue? Who?
Yeah.
No, no, no. This is not
about being a hero for me, man.
This is about wanting to live in peace.
Do you understand what I'm talking about?
No, you don't understand
what I'm talking about.
Okay, this is about me
wanting to live without you
whining in my ear all the time
about eating bad guys
or nagging me about Anne,
or destroying my place
or destroying my life!
Do you know how lucky
you are that I chose you?
You chose me?
Buddy, I'm the only person
that took you in
when your friends kicked you off
the planet Ming Mong
because you are a reject!
You are a pariah! Lethal protection,
my ass. You couldn't protect anything.
You are useless. You couldn't
get a job down here cleaning toilets!
I'm sorry! I don't know what came over me.
Please, let me fix it.
So I can break it again!
You son of a bitch!
Out! Get out. Take your stuff. Get out!
This is my house!
No!
Keep it down up there!
Get out!
Sonny?
-You wouldn't dare!
-Yeah, absolutely.
No, no, no!
-Yeah!
-No!
I'm calling the police!
I am so sorry.
Show yourself.
You can't win!
Take a look at me.
Look at the size of you.
Puny.
How dare you?
1 guess this is goodbye.
Oh, yeah.
Finally something we agree on.
What in the world?
All this crazy shit.
Yeah!
No. No.
No, no, no.
No!
Yeah!
-Yeah!
-No!
Oh, yeah!
No.
No, no, no.
I wish I never met you!
Sayonara!
Cletus Kasady,
you have been tried, convicted
and sentenced to death
by the state of California.
May your passing bring closure
to the victims' families.
And may you find peace
in the hereafter.
Soon come chaos.
Chaos soon come.
Are those your final words?
Enjoy the show.
Warden.
Something wicked this way comes.
Let me out!
Don't move!
Hey!
Please.
I got a family.
Any last words, warden?
Don't! Please!
San Quentin, may you rot and burn in hell
May your walls fall down
And may 1 live to tell
1 walk out a wiser, stronger man
And, warden, you tasted just like ham
You two are being evicted.
Come on, don't look at me like that.
It was never gonna work out.
All right?
Yes.
Just because of how quickly he moved in,
the offensive line cannot pick him up.
Breaking news. Serial killer
Cletus Kasady is on the run...
Shit.
...as a state-wide manhunt is underway...
Oh, shit.
...after fast night's audacious escape
from San Quentin.
It is absolute chaos here,
we have reports of bullets...
-Hey.
-What, you're not dead?
No.
May I come in?
Yeah, sure. Come on in.
I was just seeing for myself on the news.
Yeah, on a scale of one to ten,
it's 11 bad.
Yeah.
Reports coming from San Quentin are,
quite frankly, bananas.
Nice TV.
How did he do it?
Yeah, how did he, indeed?
That's the million-dollar question.
And yet again,
you were his special visitor.
So, what did he tell you?
Me? Nothing. Nothing at all.
Nothing about an escape plan?
Nothing about some kind
of elaborate breakout costume?
No.
Well, how come every time you seem
to be at the centre of these things,
and then miraculously
you know nothing about it?
Maybe I'm lucky.
Yeah, right.
You said...
the reports coming out
of San Quentin are bananas.
What do you mean by "bananas"?
Remember when I asked you a similar
question the day you interviewed him?
Information is currency.
You of all people should know that.
Come on.
I thought he'd come to try to find
the man that nearly got him executed,
but I guess not.
I'd lay low if I was you.
I'l see myself out.
Okay, think. Think, think, think.
What would Venom do?
He would find you before you find me,
and he would eat your face! Damn.
All right.
Who do we leave behind,
and how do we leave them?
-A connubial bed, empty, left to rot.
-Connubial. Is it marriage?
Waiting in the darkness
for the rescuer who never comes.
I don't understand.
"That circle of hell..."
-The cathedral on the hill is fell silent
because of you.
-You and! are the same.
-"...with one bright light."
Twisted insides...
Bright light.
You feel like home to me, like family.
St. Estes.
Crapola!
Another one bites the dust.
Look at all these weirdos.
My kind of people.
Nice costume.
Hey!
Awesome work!
Greatest costume ever! Oh, my God.
Is that Japanese?
No, I made it myself.
-Hey!
-Who, me?
Hello, gorgeous.
Sorry, no, not my type.
I am out of the Eddie closet!
Hello, darling.
Racer red, got to have it.
Let's get this party started.
Oh, hell, yes.
Stop! Stop, man! Stop! Stop!
Shit.
You are real.
lam.
And once I kill that thing that made me,
we will be indestructible.
I know where to find him,
but first I need you
to help me find something I lost.
Deal.
Oh, yeah!
Dude.
Oh, yeah, bro! What?
Thank you!
Oh, shit.
Your costume is amazing!
Thank you, one person!
Eddie was wrong.
He kept me hidden
because he was ashamed!
But look at me now!
You love me.
And I'm free!
Yeah!
Stop this cruel treatment of aliens.
It is wrong.
All of us should be able to live together
upon this ball of rock.
Free to be who we be!
I love you!
I love you too!
-Yeah!
Lethal Protector out.
Well, that was a hard act to follow.
I wish you could have seen me tonight...
Eddie.
Holy shit.
-Mulligan.
-It's Eddie Brock here.
Look, this may be a long shot,
but I think I may have found something.
Go on, Eddie. What do you got?
Last time 1 spoke to Kasady,
he was talking to me about connubial beds
and marriage, and it didn't
make a whole lot of sense to me.
But I'm here at St. Estes,
and I found this...
Well, I'm standing in front of a tree.
And I'm looking at it.
I's got a carving on it.
It says, "CK loves FB."
I'm thinking that maybe whoever this FB is
might know where he's headed.
And if you can, I don't know,
pull up some files from St. Estes,
maybe you can figure out who this FB is.
FB, that's Frances Barrison.
Wow, that's quick.
Yeah, it's impossible, Eddie.
She's dead. I shot her.
Can I help you, sir?
Got any of those Internets?
You're alive.
When I get out,
I'm gonna slice your face off
and wear it to a party!
You're never
getting out of here, Siegfried.
No one does.
Well, Frances.
It seems your sweetheart has done
a Houdini act over there at San Quentin.
It's all over the news.
Oh, don't get excited.
He's not gonna find you.
Screw you.
How flattering.
But you're not my type.
I wonder where he could be.
I'm right here.
Ta-da!
Hi, baby.
I don't want you to freak out, okay?
I'd like you to meet...
Carnage.
That is so hot!
Go.
A'66!
My dream car.
Yeah, I remember. Let's see what you got.
Yes, baby!
This is SFPD. Stand down!
Stop! You'll kill him!
She does that again, I'l eat her face.
He's sensitive to sound.
Stop the vehicle! Stand down!
Who said romance was dead?
Hey! No drunks in here!
Help me. Food.
Out! You get out!
Chocolate.
Venom?
I'm having trouble
keeping them standing, Mrs. C.
Where's Eddie?
Food...
Monsters!
Monsters everywhere!
They're everywhere!
Monsters!
Put out an APB,
form a perimeter,
blockade state lines,
and bring in Brock.
I'm no use to anybody here.
I'm just wasting your time.
You know what I keep thinking?
I keep thinking:
"What else is Eddie Brock
not sharing about Cletus Kasady?
Why was it Eddie that Cletus wanted
to witness his execution?"
Bad things happen around you.
Multiple dead bodies
at your building last year,
that bizarre outburst
at the lobster restaurant,
and only you at the Life Foundation
when that rocket exploded.
And now Clyde's found Bonnie
and there's a dead psychiatrist at a
facility I knew nothing about until today.
And people are talking about
seeing monsters.
Monsters?
What do you mean "monsters"?
Monsters, Eddie! Everywhere Cletus goes,
so goes this supposed monster.
Oh, God.
Talk to me, Eddie.
Talk to me.
How's he doing it?
What's the secret?
How's he making people see things?
All right...
I can't answer any more of your questions
without making my phone call.
I'l get you your phone call.
But you know what secrets want, Eddie?
They want out.
That's why they're so hard to keep.
Eddie asked you to do this?
He has no one else that can help?
We'll be late for the party.
He's in trouble, Dan.
Yeah, trouble is his thing.
-Are there gonna be aliens again?
-No, of course not.
I'd like to speak to him alone.
Your duty of honesty supersedes your duty
to the client if somebody gets harmed.
They teach you that at posh school?
Oh, hey. Anne. Hey, Anne,
thank you so much for coming.
Boy, that little guy's a charmer, huh?
How much do I need
to worry about you right now?
I messed up.
Okay. How badly?
It couldn't be worse, and it's all on me.
Whatever you did,
you just need to tell the cops the truth.
No. No. No, I can't tell them
that they are chasing a serial killer
who's also got an alien inside of him
and he's capable of killing everybody.
Venom. Talk to me, what's happening?
No, he's not here. He's not here.
Is this like an I'm lying "He's not here"
oris this a real "He's not here"?
He's not here.
Jesus Christ, Eddie.
St. Estes fire. All units.
What the actual f--?
Eddie, think.
I don't know. All I know is that he
can't go long without eating food, right?
So he's eating chicken
and he eats chocolate and that's it.
And that is only
if he's still observing the rules.
We need to find him.
You mean I need to find him.
Yeah, you need to find him, please.
And then I will fix it.
IM try.
-Thank you.
Mrs. Chen.
-Who's asking?
-It's me.
What do you want?
She's a charmer.
-Okay, listen--
-You broke Eddie's heart.
I don't have time to explain
why that's off the mark.
-Do you know where Venom is?
-You wanna break his heart too?
I'm not gonna get
into who did what to who.
Eddie said
he might be here for the chocolate.
I need to speak with the alien.
-You said there wouldn't be any aliens.
-I meant more aliens.
-Breaking news.
~The mayor has issued a curfew...
Turn the volume up, please.
Kasady and Barrison should be treated
as armed and extremely dangerous.
An all-out manhunt continues tonight.
-S0?
-Cletus has a symbiote.
Oh, my God! Any other information
you're pathologically lying about?
-Pussy.
-Excuse me?
-Eddie needs Venom.
-She just called me a pussy.
He said he didn't need him,
that life was better without him.
Okay, I don't understand.
What do you care--?
Oh, wait a second.
You get out here right now.
Do you see that?
Seriously, do you see that?
Yeah, hon, I've seen it.
Eddie's going to have to fight this battle
all by his little bitch self.
Don't be a big baby. Go help your friend!
He said I couldn't
get a job fixing toilets!
Cletus will come for him.
He won't survive without you.
Of course he won't.
Because I am the hero of the two of us.
Yeah, you're the big sexy hero.
You're the coolest, you're the hottest,
and you're the bravest.
lam.
I'm still standing right here.
No one likes you, Dan!
I love seeing you in action.
Let's go save that asshole.
I promised we'd be free from here.
And we'd walk
to the cathedral on the hill.
A wedding.
Three guests.
One for each of us.
The cop that took my eye.
Eddie Brock.
And Venom.
A red wedding.
You didn't find him?
Oh, my Lord. What happened?
Hey, Dan. All right, let's go.
I'm not talking to him!
He doesn't want to come out.
What do you mean? We have to leave now
‘cause Cletus is gonna wipe the city out.
We're not doing shit until he apologises.
So he's looking for an apology.
I know that amends aren't your thing--
Like, as in right now, an apology?
I need him to beg.
Fine, I will be the bigger of us.
1 will always be the bigger of us.
But go on.
-What is he saying?
-He said he's listening very sincerely.
All right, listen to this.
I am sorry.
Not the right tone.
I'm sorry.
Nope!
I am sorry!
So weird.
I'm
El
orry!
Why are you shouting at me?
Okay, well, fine.
I was a loser before I met you.
Yup. That's right.
And now I am someone.
You made me special.
Damn right!
-Why don't you put a cherry on it?
-A cherry on that? Right.
I'm...
I am truly very sorry
for everything that I said,
everything that I did not say,
everything that I did,
and probably everything that I did not do.
Yeah, he's thinking.
Come on, come on.
Okay!
-Oh, no.
-Kiss her!
Are you gonna kiss me now?
-No!
-No?
God, I'm never doing that again.
Well, maybe never.
I don't know. Honestly, it's really fun.
If we save the day, can we
call ourselves the Lethal Protector?
That is so '80s.
Dan. Pack quickly.
Don't stay. And if for any reason--
Fire and sound.
"Fire and sound"? Is that a band?
-No, it's what kills them.
-Yeah.
Okay, look, man, I've got her.
Not sorry!
God, I'm so sorry.
Those two need some
serious couples counselling.
I'm pulling up to Brock's now.
Shit. Oh, my God.
Kasady, place your hands on your head!
Which...
hands?
What the f-?
We found you.
Shriek will be so pleased.
Brockalicious!
Bling-a-ling.
Now, whose finger were you meant for?
A nice shiny lure for a little fishy.
Okay, here we go, buddy.
Hello, Anne.
I just incapacitated your boyfriend.
Now, he'll be okay,
with an answer about where Eddie Brock is.
Well, I'm sure as shit
not gonna tell you that.
It's a shame to hurt you.
Tell Brock Cletus will make a swap.
Her head for his.
He's gonna kill you both.
Peeps have tried that already.
Botched it!
They can't find him!
They are hunting us too, buddy.
Come on, where are you?
Hey, Dan. What's going on?
Eddie, they got her.
They've taken Anne!
-Calm down.
-They took her to their wedding.
-They took her where?
-Their wedding.
-Grace Cathedral. Hurry.
-We're on our way.
All right, it looks like
we are going to a wedding.
Oh, will there be canapés?
You bet your ass.
That distant cathedral...
is all I see.
Fractured angel...
the other part of me.
Dearly beloved...
Gifts first.
Actually, traditionally--
Shut your mouth...
Father.
Baby, I got for you what you want most.
The cop?
The cop.
Continue, Father.
Dearly beloved,
if anyone objects to this marriage,
speak now or forever hold their
Where is she?
There you are.
Death to you, Father.
No!
Not you, Father.
You, Father.
Oh, shit!
Where you going? What are you doing?
This is much worse than I thought.
That is a red one.
-Red one?
-We should leave. Immediately.
Annie will get over it.
We never liked her anyway.
-So let's go.
-Now?
Congratulations to the happy couple.
We are leaving.
Eddie!
I'l be right with you. All right?
You need to come out right now.
Because I am feeling
super, super vulnerable right here.
Brock's just like you?
Not for long.
Eddie, over here!
You need to come out right now.
I will let you eat everybody!
You can eat them all!
Apart from him in the robe.
You cannot eat him.
-Promise?
-l promise!
Thank you.
Baby!
Shut your mouth.
Marriage trouble already?
Time to die.
That's the spirit!
I mean us. We are going to die.
I killed you.
Well, you can't kill a ghost.
You. Kill him,
but keep your mouth shut.
Our wife knows what she's doing.
Just turn it down.
Who do you think you're talking to?
-Stop him!
-My cop!
Honeymoon over?
Oh, God. No.
Power up.
No!
Mayday, mayday, mayday!
Cletus Kasady--
What do they say
about an eye for an eye?
Fire and sound!
Except without the sound.
Baby!
Cletus!
Mano a mano, Brock.
You know how I spent my endless days?
I spent them thinking about
how you only told one side of the story.
You didn't write about the part
where Cletus was abused
by Mommy, Daddy, and Granny!
You didn't tell the world
how he was a scared little boy
that no one cared about
and no one came to save!
You never asked yourself
why!
That's bad journalism.
Oh, happy days.
I'm not a crazy man,
but I am a vengeful one.
You're going to watch her die.
Anne!
Do something!
Eddie, I'm afraid we cannot beat them.
Baby, that's too much.
You gotta stop him.
What are you doing?
I'l shut her up for good.
No! Stop! You're hurting her!
Get up!
I can't.
Look, look!
They're not symbiotic.
-Get away from her!
-Shut up.
Take your hands off my wife!
They're not a match.
We are.
That's right. We are.
Together we are...
-the Lethal Protector!
-The Lethal Protector!
Let there be carnage!
I got you. You okay?
Father, one of us must die.
We need fire.
Or sound.
No!
Holy mackerel!
He did not taste good.
I'm a killer
with or without the monster, Eddie.
You know what I really wanted?
No. What was it, Cletus?
I told you, but you weren't listening.
Well, I'm listening now.
I wanted your friendship.
I'm sorry, Cletus.
Fuck this guy!
You in there, get him out of here.
They're gonna come for you both.
I know.
Hey, Anne.
Take care.
Yeah. You too, champ.
Dan!
-You take care too.
-Thanks.
I like you.
We totally didn't need him, though.
Honestly, I think he was
more of a hindrance than a help.
Monsters.
That there is Don Quixote,
and the guy next to him is Sancho Panza.
They're two very different people who
have very different takes on the world.
Different ways of doing things.
Sometimes they didn't like each other
a whole lot, but ultimately...
they worked together
to bring out the best in each other.
Eddie, the time has come.
I must go alone.
It is me they want.
Yeah.
Well, my dear Sancho,
facts are the enemy of truth.
What does that even mean?
It means...
It means that we...
are Ve...
Fugitives!
...nom. Yeah. Yeah.
On the run.
That too.
Thank you for bringing me here.
You're welcome, buddy.
It's beautiful, huh?
I'm sorry that we can't do anything
about the old
wind-in-your-hair situation, but...
Osho says,
when you love someone,
-you accept the whole person,
-Osho?
with all of their defects.
Defects.
Nobody is perfect.
Just go back a minute. You telling me--?
You just said that you love me.
You did.
Where will we go?
I don't know. I don't know.
Anywhere that needs
a Lethal Protector, I suppose.
-You really meant it!
-Yeah.
We will need a cape. And a mask.
No. No, I think you got that covered.
We're good.
Oh, I love this show.
Yeah.
Maximiliano's feelings
are not being validated.
Yeah, well, he never should've kept
such an insane secret, man.
We alf have a past, Eddie.
What do you mean?
You hiding stuff from me?
Eighty billion light years
of Hive knowledge across universes
would explode your tiny little brain.
What does that even mean, man?
Well, let me give you a taste, then.
Just the smallest fraction of the things
we symbiotes have experienced.
Okay.
Ready, Eddie?
Yeah.
Oh, what's happening?
Oh! No, no, no! No!
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's just a towel.
Where are we?
-What did you do?
-It wasn't me.
You better believe this shocking
revelation brought to light by yours truly
has only raised more questions...
What is this?
...about the secret life
of Peter Parker...
aka Spider-Man,
aka the Spider-Menace.
But rest assured, dear viewers,
we here at the Daily Bugle won't rest...
That guy.
...until we've uncovered
the truth from his web of lies!
I'm J. Jonah Jameson.
Good night,
and God help us all.
Dude. What are you doing in my room?