I am Knull.
God of the void.
Slicer of worlds.
Long ago,
when light invaded my kingdom,
my symbiote children
betrayed me
and imprisoned me here.
At last,
a codex has been created.
It is the key to my freedom.
It will unlock this prison.
I order you
to search the corners
of the universe
until you find this key.
Find me the codex.
And when I escape
and annihilate
every living planet
and destroy
my symbiote offspring,
I will reward you
with your lives.
So you're saying
in this universe,
there's these superhero people.
All right.
So tell me again
about your purple alien friend
who really loves stones.
'Cause I'll tell you what, man,
aliens,
they do not love stones.
-Eddie, don't start.
-No, no.
They do not love stones.
Do you know what they love?
They love eating brains!
Because that's what they do.
Senor, he made
my family disappear.
For five years.
Mm.
Well, five years, huh?
Sí.
Well, that is a long time.
All right.
Eddie!
We are drunk.
We're home!
I'm so done with
the multiverse shit.
And I like our version
of the barman better.
Ow.
My head hurts.
I feel like I'm drunk
but I'm also hungover
at the same time.
Eddie!
You want a Bloody María.
Oh, yeah!
-No.
-I don't want a drink.
Ay, Dios mío.
Stop! You are destroying
this man's bar.
Tequila!
I'm having the time
of my life, Eddie!
I'd rather have
a glass of water.
Be a man, Eddie!
We should've been a bartender.
Tequila!
-I did it.
Senor?
What the hell
were those things?
I was born with them.
Freaking bar.
I'm done with this shit.
This is Keli Reule
reporting from San Francisco.
Police are still trying
to locate former reporter
-Eddie Brock for questioning...
-Oh, no.
...after the tragic death
of Detective Patrick Mulligan.
No.
Detective Mulligan
was found impaled
amidst a series
of bizarre happenings
at the city's cathedral.
They think that I killed him.
How long can
he evade authorities?
Only time will tell.
If we are on the news here,
we are on the news everywhere.
Well, we can't go back
to San Francisco.
And I'm not staying down here,
hiding for the rest
of my life in Mexico.
That's for sure.
Where will we go?
I don't know. I-I don't know.
Ooh.
That could work. Hey.
This judge got me
kicked out of New York.
-What a dick!
-Yeah.
I still got
a ton of shit on him, too.
I've always wanted
to see the Statue of Liberty.
Maybe we could blackmail him...
and clear my name.
Let's go!
Road trip!
Let's get the hell out of here.
Keep the change!
We keep our heads down,
and we keep moving.
We are fugitives.
We are on the run.
Yes, we are innocent, yes,
but I will eat every bad guy
that gets in our way.
I need a Tylenol.
Do you hear that?
Hmm.
Someone's in trouble.
And I need fuel for the road.
Yeah, okay.
That way.
Bad men, Eddie.
Are we the Lethal Protector
or not?
Do your thing.
Easy-peasy.
Jesus.
Cute!
I promise not to eat it.
They're fighting dogs.
I draw the line
at fighting dogs, pal.
Qué haces aquí, pendejo?
Oye, vato.
You're in the wrong place.
Oh, hello.
This is our territory.
Well, I assume
by the threatening look
on your faces that I, uh...
I ought to be scared, right?
Pues you took the wrong path,
hermano.
We can't let you leave.
I have a headache,
on account of the fact
that I was drinking a lot.
I'm gonna be honest.
I have a really dark
and unpredictable side to me.
We all have monsters
inside us.
Not like this.
So dark that it is
highly likely
to tear your head off
and feed it to your asshole.
Or me!
You can feed it to me.
Yeah, or I can feed it to him.
Yeah.
All right, look. Whoa, whoa.
Come on. I got a suggestion.
-No. Stop speaking.
-I'm not gonna stop speaking.
This is for you.
I'm doing this
for your benefit, all right?
I don't have to, okay?
So pay attention.
We're gonna find all of these
dogs loving forever homes
because what you're doing
is reprehensible.
And what does your mother
think of you, man?
My mother's dead, culero.
You made it awkward.
-I'm sorry to hear that.
-Calla!
Ah?
Parto la madre.
Entiendes?
-I'm giving you a chance.
-Ah.
Sweetie, I-I really am
giving you a chance.
You should probably take it.
-Sí?
-Sí.
Quién?
-Say when.
-When.
Hola , bitches.
Who's a bad boy?
Now, that's
some sturdy footwear.
Where you going?
Home.
Nah.
What... are you?
-We are...
-We're Venom!
-Venom!
-No.
-Oh.
-Yeah, we... are Venom.
-We are Venom.
What?
We're totally
gonna need to work on that.
Mm, mm! That was delicious!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
You take me
to all the finest places.
Let's get the hell
out of here.
Where's my shoe?
Oh, hey, buddy.
That's my shoe.
Give me my shoe.
These will fit.
Now we are on the run.
For something
we actually did do.
And I got stuck with
a superhero who can't fly.
Want to bet?
There you are.
Get me General Strickland.
What the...
Viral shedding.
These things want to live.
-Hola.
Tell me about the man
who was just here.
He was acting, like, crazy,
talking to himself.
What was he saying?
He-he had these big,
massive, wild arms.
They were bobbling like this.
Bring him.
You think there are another
brother and sister
on one of those stars...
...looking at the same sky?
I'll be able to tell you
one day.
My twin brother,
a future NASA scientist.
One day.
When thunder roars,
head indoors.
No!
He's on life support.
Get him to
emergency symbiosis now.
It should be you.
This
just came across our news desk
and it bears repeating.
For all you alien enthusiasts
out there, it's a sad day.
Washington has
finally announced
the decommissioning of Area 51.
The controversial site
is famous
for its alleged testing
on aliens.
In other news today...
Strickland.
Strickland authorized.
It's finally happening, then.
Yeah.
Yes, ma'am.
Be nothing left
but rock and dust.
And roaches.
Even the biggest of bangs
couldn't kill 'em.
They've been around
280 million years and counting.
I did not know that, Dr. Paine.
Good to go.
-Have a good one, Gus.
-You, too.
-Thank you.
-Yes, ma'am.
Dr. Kendall,
report to trans bay three.
Dr. Kendall, report to
transportation bay three.
Morning, Dr. Paine.
We'll keep 'em safe for you.
I still don't think anyone
wants my old beater, Jim.
Never judge a book
by its cover.
Reminder:
This facility is now under
heightened security protocol.
Early morning wake-up,
General Strickland.
Looks like all your dreams
came true.
I know how that must bug you.
He arrived
shortly before you did.
Did our new friend
give him any trouble?
You see,
that's exactly the problem.
What?
Your assumption
we're meeting friends.
Morning.
Good morning.
The bonding was successful.
I heard.
You always have
this look on your face
like something terrible
is imminent.
Because in my line of work,
something terrible
is always imminent.
We contain them,
you study them.
It's how it works.
Let's have a look.
-Hello, Doctor.
-Morning.
His other symbiote
left him for dead.
We saved him.
He would have died.
Oh, try lowering those levels.
Morning, Sadie.
Let me get that.
We got this down in Mexico.
Hi. Welcome.
Any more on where
the rest of him is?
-We're getting there.
-Update me as you have it.
I don't get this obsession.
I told you--
my mom made me this pin.
It's July.
-I'll see you in there.
-Mm-hmm.
Everyone on this side is weird.
Leave her alone, Rex.
God forbid anyone should
actually enjoy their work.
Area 51 will be
fully decommissioned
by the end of the week.
It's just a shipwreck anyway,
and they're tired
of the tourists.
But we don't exist down here.
A hundred feet subsurface,
undetectable to any human...
or nonhuman.
No one's phoning home
from here.
My brother's greatest ambition
was to work up there at 51
doing what I do.
I wish I could've shown him
what we've built down here.
You're okay.
Just... try to breathe.
Okay?
When my brother and I
were kids, they told us
that UFOs were just
weather balloons, space trash.
Kubrick directed the moon
landing in a Hollywood studio.
Cool story.
Where are you going?
This first.
Is there an increased risk
of exposure?
It's not us I'm worried about.
You know we carry all kinds
of viruses and bacteria
that could be harmful
to a sensitive life-form.
And we don't know exactly
what we're dealing with here.
As long as we're keeping
the guests safe.
This is
the first time we've had
a host compatible
with one of our symbiotes.
And now we'll be able
to talk to one.
Monsters.
He's been experiencing panic
surges since we bonded him.
You try "Jingle Bells"?
So soothing.
Wow.
Why didn't I think of that?
Release him.
Monsters.
I'm Dr. Paine.
Teddy.
You're safe here.
I'm gonna help you.
Both of you.
Monsters.
The transfer was successful.
We had no choice.
We had to try and save you.
Monsters.
You're broken, too.
May I...
May I ask you some questions?
Is the symbiote
communicating with you?
Do you hear it?
Sound distresses them.
Okay.
Why are they here?
What do they want?
-Safe haven.
-Safe haven?
We were running.
Is he talking about
the other symbiotes?
I think so.
His creatures
search the universe for us.
But we will be found.
And when we are,
he will kill us all.
Who?
There will be nothing left.
Here? On Earth?
Why were they running?
Because there is a dark,
cold sea
around this universe.
What is it?
You don't want to know.
I've s-seen the f-future.
The darkness...
has teeth.
This is your captain speaking.
We are currently cruising
at a comfortable 31,000 feet.
If you look out there
to your left just now,
you'll see the Grand Canyon.
Told you we could fly.
Oh, my God!
Direct to New York.
My mouth is so dry!
And we clear your name.
It's so unpleasantly cold!
How does Tom Cruise do this?
He doesn't whine
like a little bitch!
What was that?
What is that?
Oh, fu...!
I'm sorry, Eddie,
but I got to disappear.
-What, now?
-We're in deep shit.
Why did you do that?
I will explain.
No! No!
Oh, I'm gonna go ahead and say
that this is the shittest
hangover of all time.
Look at it, Eddie.
Isn't it just astonishing?
Oh, shut up.
I don't think I mind
living here forever.
We just came face-to-face
with a literal death machine.
Forever seems
pretty optimistic.
With the
decommissioning of Area 51,
will the Pentagon
finally admit
that they've been
holding UAPs?
That's "unidentified
aerial phenomena" to you.
Yeah, Dad, we know.
What I wouldn't give to see
who built one of those things.
That's why we cashed in
our savings
and came on
this road trip, babe.
Hmm?
So you could finally
get to see...
That it's bullshit?
Yeah, well, what if I'm right?
Then I really hope
we don't end up
in an alien space lab
with probes up our asses.
Or dead.
"Asses."
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Whoa-ho!
Kicked up some gravel there.
-Hang tight, family.
-You good?
That was wild.
-Did the dog vomit?
-Yeah.
Okay
We've got this.
Soft landing. Bend your knees.
Engage your core.
Engage your core!
-Whoa, whoa.
-Yes! Yes, that's it.
Yes. That's it!
-Whoa.
-Well done.
That was terrifying.
Uh, this is not New York.
No, this is a wasteland.
I'm detecting
passive aggression.
-Are you?
-Yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry. How about
some active aggression?
-You just threw me off a 757...
-Mm.
...without even
the slightest consideration
for my chronic vertigo.
It was an Airbus A320.
Was it? I am sorry.
All right.
And what was that thing--
that thing that we just
juiced back there?
You're not going to like this.
No, I can absolutely guarantee
you that I'm not gonna.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing that?
That's, uh...
You're being weird.
That's creepy.
That was a Xenophage.
-A what?
-A Xenophage.
-A symbiote hunter.
-Of course.
Problem is,
if she has found her way here,
others will soon follow.
Others?
The Xenophage's maker
also created us symbiotes.
So that's your sister.
All the symbiotes
turned on him,
locked him up on Klyntar.
Your planet.
-No, not a planet.
-Not your planet.
A prison we built
for him to sleep...
-Of course.
-...for eternity!
What's his name, then?
I didn't hear a word you said.
-Knull.
No!
This is serious, Eddie.
Let's just not talk.
Quiet.
What does this
"Xyla-Xyn" thingy,
this symbiote hunter,
want with you anyway?
It doesn't. It wants us.
We have something it needs.
We only have this shitty shirt.
We got one boot and sunburn.
And the codex.
The what, now?
I'll show you.
Damn it, what are you doing?
Let's say you died.
I could bring you back to life.
Well, I like that.
But if I did,
our separate life forces
would become one single force
called a codex.
What the hell is a codex?
It's a key.
A key that unlocks a cage.
The prison on Klyntar.
It would free our creator.
Well, thank God
we haven't died.
Yeah, except that one time.
Oh, no. No.
So you're telling me
we're carrying this thing.
That's why
the Xenophage is hunting us.
What do we do?
She can only see the codex
when a symbiote is in
its full true form.
Right.
You mean you can't come out?
I can do this. I can do this.
But if I fully transform,
the codex sends her
a tracking signal.
She'll find us,
rip it out of our spine
and free Knull from Klyntar.
So how do we get rid
of this codex?
As long as you and I both live,
the codex exists.
If one of us should die...
-No.
-...the codex would die.
-That's not gonna work for me.
-Nor me.
That Xenophage was fast.
It won't take long
for the Feds to tie us
to those four headless bodies
we left in Mexico.
-We got to get out of here.
-Yeah, we better go.
Ah.
Four legs are better than one.
Be honest with me, buddy.
How fast do you think
you can get that thing to go
without killing it?
Only one way to find out.
Don't scare him.
Don't scare
horsey-horsey-horse.
Nice horsey.
Hey.
Surprise, horsey!
I love horsey!
♪ Don't stop me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm having
a good time ♪
♪ Having a good time... ♪
-Let's go.
-Whoa.
Yeehaw!
♪ In a racing car
passing by... ♪
Ride me, cowboy!
You are an asshole!
I swear to God,
when I get off this horse,
I'm gonna kick your ass,
you mother--
♪ 200 degrees, that's why they
call me Mr. Fahrenheit... ♪
Now, that's horsepower!
Safe haven?
No. They're not here
for a safe haven.
How about a new home,
evict the current tenants?
I think you've watched too many
alien invasion movies, Rex.
Have I?
They were running.
That's what he said.
Don't kid yourself.
They were always migrating.
A meteor carrying symbiote life
crashes on Earth,
and they all survive.
Coincidence? Give me a break.
All right.
Let's go get 'em.
You're so desperate to believe
that they're here
for altruistic reasons.
Makes you dangerous.
We just intercepted
an emergency call
from an Airbus out of Mexico
saying a man jumped
off the plane over Sequoia.
We'll take the Osprey.
Eyes wide, Paine.
I can't feel my balls.
That... that was horrible.
Visual on suspect.
Take him out.
Collect the symbiote.
Team Six engaged.
Disengage harness. Let's go.
-No! The codex!
-Can't let you die.
Where did that come from?
-Morph!
-Copy.
-Time to go.
-Hell yeah.
What happened?
There's something else
out here.
Something else?
He said this would happen.
I just lost three people.
Can you collect any samples?
Samples?
Those were not Feds.
Those were some
Special Forces shit.
They were trying to kill us.
Yeah. Yeah, great. Great.
So now we have the cops,
the United States Army
and some creature from hell
hunting us.
Oh, God,
I just saw blood mist
spray out of the back
of an alien's face.
I killed someone.
They didn't give you a choice.
You didn't give me a choice.
-I couldn't get to you.
-Not in the rapids.
A year ago
when you stole my life.
We've been together
for a whole year?
A year too long.
Just stay hidden
while we get to New York
without getting killed.
We need you to come out.
The thing you talked about,
the creature...
it's here.
It killed some people.
Wow.
He's so beautiful.
I sense...
I sense my own.
And yet, the one Knull seeks
is not here.
What does he seek?
The black one.
Brock's symbiote?
He's the only one
who carries a codex.
The end is Knull.
You need your suit.
Still worried about
giving this thing a cold?
Venom carries the key
to Knull's freedom.
He must never obtain it.
Or your race will be killed.
You.
And you.
And...
you.
Everyone, everything.
How do we stop whatever's
up there from coming down here?
You can't.
He's older than the universe.
He needs the key.
Then everything will end.
How do we stop him
from getting it?
If the symbiote
and the host are alive,
then the codex is alive.
And if one of them dies?
The codex dies.
-Rex, you can't be serious.
-Oh, I'm game.
Destroying the codex
is the only way
it remains unobtainable, right?
Hey, buddy,
I'm talking to you.
Destroying it?
We have barely even
scratched the surface.
My people are dead.
Something is coming
that cannot be beaten.
I'm stopping all this shit
right now.
-Science is sacrifice.
-Teddy.
This is serious.
Listen to her.
Have you spoken
to your family recently?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
♪ Myoho renge kyo,
namu myoho... ♪
I smell wet dog.
And sausamages!
Hey, friend-o.
You okay there?
No, I'm not okay.
Uh, it's pretty wild out there.
-I know.
-Yeah.
You hungry?
Yes.
Come over.
Thank you.
So, uh, this is my wife,
Nova Moon.
Hi.
-Hey.
-And these are my kids,
Echo and Leaf.
-A lifetime in therapy.
-Don't.
Huh?
Don't you dare.
Wow. How beautiful
are your children? Hmm?
And that's Blue...
-...who is a...
-Dog.
And I'm Martin.
-Hey, Martin.
-Hey.
-I'm Eddie.
-Nice to meet you, Eddie.
You, too. Pleasure.
Come. Sit, please.
-Okay. Oh...
-Come on.
-Thank you. Yeah.
-Thank you.
Jesus Christ.
So, right.
Oh.
So, nothing died on that plate.
Namaste, man.
-Thank you.
-Hard pass!
Oh, dear.
Eddie, where you headed?
-Uh, New York.
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah.
-All right.
Long way to New York
with naked shrimps, man.
Yeah.
We could ride you out
to Vegas.
Yeah.
These people are weird,
I'm telling you.
That would be so kind.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Of course.
Life's one big adventure.
Who doesn't love
making new friends?
Right?
This guy is so one of those
serial killer hitchhikers from
-my favorite murder podcast.
-Ha-ha!
Baby, not now.
How has social services
not taken us away yet?
She... she... she's joking.
-I'm not.
-Please, honey.
So, we're riding
the Extraterrestrial Highway.
-Yep.
-The whatchamawhosit?
It-it's the road
that leads to Area 51.
See if we can
spot us an alien
before they shut the place down
forever, you know?
It's, uh...
it's my lifelong dream.
We could show him
right now.
Not a believer?
Actually, Martin, uh...
How do I put this? Uh...
-I am.
-Oh.
Actually, I am
a big, big believer.
-You're not that big.
-Oh, what, you a comedian now?
No, actually, I was in I.T.
-Were you?
-Yeah.
-That's so cool.
-Oh, thanks.
I, uh... I hope you don't get
disappointed, you know?
And I hope that
if you do find one,
I hope you meet
a really good alien,
not a...
not a bad... one.
-Yeah.
Well, I know a dark force
when I see one, Eddie.
It's kind of hot in here.
Oh, you'll get used to it.
AC's really bad
for your health, you know.
All right. Family ready?
Yep.
Guest ready?
Let's rock this camper.
♪ Ground Control to Major Tom ♪
Oh, I love a sing-along!
♪ Ground Control
to Major Tom ♪
Shoot me in the face.
♪ Take your protein pills ♪
♪ And put your helmet on ♪
Oh, yeah!
-This is my jam!
-♪ Ten, nine ♪
♪ Ground control to Major Tom ♪
♪ Eight, seven, six ♪
-♪ Commencing countdown ♪
-♪ Five ♪
-♪ Engines on ♪
-♪ Four, three ♪
-♪ Two, one ♪
-♪ Check ignition ♪
♪ And may God's love
be with you ♪
♪ Liftoff! ♪
Come on, Eddie, sing along.
-I'm good, thanks.
-You know the words.
Just think of this
as the tour bus.
We're the band,
and you can be the groupie.
Come on. Don't be square.
Don't get me started.
♪ This is Major Tom ♪
♪ To Ground Control ♪
♪ I'm stepping
through the door ♪
♪ And I'm floating
in a most peculiar way ♪
Cheer up.
♪ And the stars look
very different today ♪
Why?
♪ For here am I ♪
Why is this happening?
♪ Sitting in a tin can ♪
Can made of tin!
♪ Far above the world ♪
Like a bathtub, Eddie.
♪ Planet Earth is blue ♪
♪ And there's nothing
I can do ♪
♪ This is Ground Control ♪
♪ To Major Tom... ♪
Sometimes I think
we would've been happier
with a life like this.
♪ And the papers want to know
whose shirts you wear... ♪
-You know?
-Yep.
♪ Now it's time
to leave the capsule ♪
I know.
♪ If you dare ♪
♪ This is Major Tom ♪
♪ To Ground Control ♪
♪ I'm stepping
through the door ♪
♪ And I'm floating
in a most peculiar way ♪
♪ And the stars look
very different today ♪
♪ For here am I ♪
♪ Sitting in a tin can ♪
♪ Far above the world... ♪
You like chocolate?
Shh.
They don't let us eat sugar.
They don't?
I have a friend
who loves chocolate.
Thank you.
It's very kind of you.
I don't want to
see an alien.
You don't?
It's scary.
Okay.
Well, you know,
it's okay to be scared.
I'm scared, like...
like, all the time.
Promise I won't see one?
Buddy.
Aliens are not real.
Okay? I promise.
Okay?
You said the right thing.
You would make a good dad.
We've come a long way,
you and me.
We have many more roads
to travel, buddy.
Wouldn't that be nice?
You say something?
Hmm? No. Just...
dreaming, I guess.
That's the Nierika.
-Nierika?
-Yeah.
There's a doorway in our minds
that usually remains
hidden and secret
until the time of death.
Crazy things
in this world, Eddie.
You can see 'em if you're open.
Oh, I've seen them.
Mm.
I'm glad we didn't eat
this fine family.
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la,
la, la ♪
la, la-la, la ♪
♪ Now that I've lost
everything to you ♪
♪ You say you want to start
something new ♪
♪ And it's breaking my heart
you're leaving ♪
♪ Baby, I'm grieving ♪
♪ But if you want to leave,
take good care... ♪
Welcome to the city
of second chances.
Whoa.
♪ Ooh, baby, baby,
it's a wild world ♪
♪ It's hard to get by
just upon a smile... ♪
Thank you. Thank you.
-Wow.
-Take care, buddy. Thank you.
-Stay, Blue. Stay.
-Thank you. Take care, Blue.
Vegas.
Listen, I just want you
to have this.
-Please. And, um...
-Oh, Martin, that's a lot of...
-Thank you.
-Quality support cushioning.
Plus, they come with
an antimicrobial footbed.
No! Reject them.
Worse than Crocs.
Thank you.
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
it's a wild world ♪
♪ But I'll always
remember you ♪
Goodbye, Martin.
It's goodbye for now.
That's what I like
to think, Eddie.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Martin.
Remember that-that doorway...
The Nierika?
Yeah. It's, uh, it's open.
All right?
Just... be safe.
Okay.
Thanks.
Oh, Jesus.
Well, this is an all-time low.
You have chocolate.
Mmm. Yum!
Oh, God.
Loosest slots in town!
I would like to see her
when we get to New York, Eddie.
You know, she was built
to welcome visitors
to America, buddy.
And that's you.
You think so, Eddie?
Oh, yeah, I know so.
When we get out of this mess,
we're gonna go see her,
and we're gonna say,
"Hi, Lady Liberty."
And see a Broadway show!
Yeah, sure.
Wow! I know how much
you hate musicals.
Yeah, it's gonna be great.
What's next, Thelma?
Well, Louise,
I'm not sure 20 bucks
is gonna get us much
in the way
of a motor transport.
And I'm not ever riding
an alien horse again.
So I guess it looks like
we're stealing cars.
No! I've watched "Rain Man,"
and in my infinite wisdom
as a celestial being,
working the system is easy.
-Uh...
-We hit the slots,
then blackjack, then roulette.
Bingo-bango!
Luxury ride,
Bluetooth sound system,
AC and the top down.
Because that's how we roll.
Paris Casino
has a strict dress code.
No, you know what?
It's a hotel.
These are my vacation clothes.
Get better ones.
He's not wrong.
-Look at you.
-No.
Don't push it,
all right, buddy?
All right.
Want a hand?
Yes.
I didn't mean knock him out.
-What are you doing?
-He was being a dick.
-Yeah, but...
-Oh, look.
We need a disguise.
What are we doing?
-Hey.
-Hey, man.
Hi.
-Oh, God.
-Warm.
Why do you keep
knocking people out?
What is wrong with you?
Jesus, why?
So sorry, buddy.
I am so, so sorry.
Eddie. Yeah, baby.
Now no one will recognize us.
Seriously.
You could get voted "People's"
sexiest man of the year
if anyone cared
who you were anymore.
I've won "sexy man" awards
before.
Course you have.
-Hey. Hey.
-Yeah?
The guy that did that--
I saw it.
He's in the... in the arch
over there. He's shit-faced.
-Thank you, sir.
-All right.
We are bad people.
Yeah, we are.
We're keeping
these shoes, by the way.
We are so money,
and we know it.
-Welcome to the Paris.
-Thank you.
No. Thank you.
♪ Baby, here I am ♪
♪ I'm a man on the scene ♪
♪ I can give you
what you want ♪
♪ But you got to go home
with me ♪
♪ I've got some
good ol' loving ♪
♪ And I got some in store... ♪
Oh, yes!
Let me multiply that 20.
Let me quadruplify it.
What are you doing?
No, this is all the money
that we have.
♪ Luck be a lady tonight ♪
No.
Snazzy jacket!
Let's eat him and steal it.
I know Lady Luck is
on our side tonight.
No, I would say that Lady Luck
is definitely not
on your side tonight.
In fact,
I would even go so far to say
that Lady Luck hates you,
buddy.
I can't stop now.
Of course you can't stop.
What is this feeling?
It's like...
-This feeling?
-Ah!
It's like all of my problems
have gone away.
Do this all the time.
Eddie.
I need more money.
But we... but we don't have
any more money, buddy.
Goddamn it!
Y-You are a sore loser.
You're a sore loser!
I think you broke my foot.
Ah, Lady Luck is a fickle slut!
We should have played
that machine.
Yes, yes, yes!
No effing way.
Eddie Brock?!
Mrs. Chen.
-Sorry, that's not your...
-Eddie! It's Mrs. Chen!
Oh, Mrs. Chen.
Eddie, baby!
Mrs. Chen. Mrs. Chen!
-I'm gonna cry.
-Me, too.
Wow. What happened to you?
-You look hot.
-So do you.
-Really hot.
-I always look hot.
-Yeah.
-Is the big guy in there?
-Y-Yeah.
-Do you like my dress?
I've been winning so big,
they gave me a credit line
at the clothes store.
And then the penthouse suite.
Wow. You know,
I stole this suit
off a guy who pissed on me.
I knocked him out.
I left him in a bush.
Well, that explains the stink.
You could use my room
to clean up, and then we party.
Oh, that would be so good.
And room service.
Yes!
We got him.
Positive I.D. on Brock.
CCTV hit, the Paris Hotel.
Vegas.
Have we reconstituted the Six?
Yes, sir.
Put 'em in.
The Six are en route.
They'll bring him in.
At this time,
I'm requesting control
of the Imperium Program.
You have my permission,
General.
When thunder roars,
head indoors.
Let's dance, baby.
-No. No. N-No.
-Yeah! I love dancing!
Are you crazy?
That thing will find us.
Don't be a party pooper.
No. Do... do not encourage him.
You know what, Mrs. Chen,
we are fugitives.
We are on the run,
so thank you for having us.
Um, we got to go.
You're no fun!
-One last dance before you go.
-We never do anything
-I want to do.
-What?
Just a little dance.
And you gave away my chickens.
Yeah!
Let's cut a rug, Mrs. Chen.
I give up.
Oh, no, I cannot unsee that.
I cannot unsee that.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You can dance ♪
♪ You can jive ♪
♪ Having the time
of our lives ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ See that girl ♪
♪ Watch that scene,
diggin' the dancing queen ♪
When did you two practice this?
♪ Friday night
and the lights are low ♪
♪ Looking out
for a place to go ♪
♪ Where they play
the right music ♪
♪ Getting in the swing, you
come to look for a king... ♪
Goddamn it!
I told you this would happen!
Don't panic.
She can't see the codex.
What the hell is that?
Wow. So ugly!
Stay very calm.
She can't see the thing
she's looking for.
Target acquired.
-You leave Eddie alone!
-Silence!
My shoes.
Go. Move out, move out!
Wow.
Area 51.
-Yeah.
-Huh?
Yeah.
We made it.
You finally got to see it, Dad.
It's kind of cool...
I guess.
Yeah.
Leaf.
Where you going, hon?
Well, let's see if we can't
find us something cooler.
Come on. Come on, guys.
Okay, babe. Lifelong dream.
All right. Go, go, go, go, go!
I smell alien.
He's deteriorating
without his host.
Poor thing.
Put him below with the others.
Safer there.
Down, down.
Come on, come on.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think we're gonna get
a better view from up there.
Follow me, guys. Come on.
This is so exciting.
I can't believe we're here.
Wow.
Whoa.
Oh, wow.
What is this?
It's all broken.
So sad.
Buddy?
Hey, buddy?
Oh, no.
No.
Oh, my God, how many hangovers
can you have in one day?
Eddie?
Hello?
They did this to me.
Mulligan?
-Why?
-You're alive?
What are you doing here?
We're being hunted, Eddie.
You have what he needs.
Protect the codex
from dark hands.
A symbiote army waits here.
Free them.
Protect it, Eddie.
Knull must stay locked away.
Eddie, I'm Dr. Paine.
Where's my friend?
He's safe for now.
Great news.
Oh, shit.
We're all done here.
All of this
is out of your hands.
This is my lab.
No, no, not yours.
You just work here--
or you did.
You, Christmas,
you're going home.
And what about them?
-You heard what it said.
-Hands up.
The codex only exists
if they're both alive.
Yeah, we're good. We're good.
You killed one of my people.
I'm returning the favor
personally.
Please escort Dr. Paine
out of here.
-No.
-Don't move!
Christmas, time to go.
Hey.
Big mistake.
Fire!
-Run!
-Oh, my...
-Oh, my God!
-Fall back, fall back!
Venom, run. Go!
Let's go! Move!
Clear! Clear!
Release the symbiotes!
Go! Go!
-Come on.
-Go! Go!
Hurry up! Move!
Get back!
Jim!
Bring her down!
Get back!
Let's go.
Take her down.
Come on!
Get the codex out of here.
Go, go, go!
That's our way out.
You, break us out of here!
There's no aliens here, kids.
Mm.
Best shoes ever!
Whoa! What was that?
Let's go!
Okay.
We got to go! Move it!
Get these people out of here!
We are leaving!
Move! Move, move!
It's all right.
It's all right, kids.
Aliens!
Alien invasion!
Alien attack!
Motherfucker!
-You two, get airborne!
-Right away, sir!
On me!
Hurry up!
Airborne! Move, move, move!
In the Hummers! Go!
We've got to get the
codex as far away as possible.
It's Eddie?
-It's Eddie.
-Eddie!
-Eddie?
-Hey!
-Oh, no.
-Eddie! Eddie!
-Eddie!
Martin. And family.
You can't be here, Martin.
Dark forces, man.
Eddie, can you help us?
I lied. Aliens are real.
My best friend
in the whole world is one.
He's gonna get you
out of here, okay?
Okay.
Don't-don't be scared.
Hi.
Wow.
Pleasure to meet you.
Thanks for the chocolate.
You're welcome.
No!
-Mom! Dad!
-Whoa! Whoa!
Dad!
-Hold on, kids!
-Look out!
Hold on, kids!
Eddie!
He was trying to protect you.
We are not the bad guys!
-Echo! Leaf.
-My baby, my baby.
-Mom!
-Oh, my God.
-Thank you, Eddie.
-You're welcome.
You got to be kidding me.
Get in!
Run!
Go. Bring me that codex.
What's that noise?
She phoned home.
Oh, shit.
-Oh, God.
-Get down! Get down!
Come on, you guys!
Get down here!
-Come on.
-Take cover! Take cover!
-Dad! Dad!
-I got you.
She saved us.
There's only one thing
that's gonna distract them.
-Copy.
-Okay.
-Get 'em back to their van!
-What?
Come on! Hurry, hurry!
I'm gonna round them up.
Have the chopper follow me.
Go, go, go! Go!
Go!
He's leading them
to a kill box.
When you get a lock,
vaporize 'em!
We're home. We're back.
Okay, okay, home.
-Run!
-Go, kids. Go. Come on.
Hurry. Hurry, honey.
Thank you.
Aliens suck!
Light 'em up.
Copy that.
Target eliminated.
No! No! No!
Thompson down!
It's coming down! Go!
Oh, sh...
Let's finish this.
With pleasure.
The chopper blades!
I got you.
Okay. It's okay.
Get him somewhere safe.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay. Okay.
No.
Still living
your brother's dream?
Oh, my God.
I'm coming.
-I'm coming!
-Dad, come on!
-Dad, Dad, run! Come on!
-Dad!
I'm proud of you, Eddie.
You did it all yourself.
Well, some of it.
I really would have liked
to have seen her.
Who?
Lady Liberty.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, we're going.
We're gonna go
just as soon as we get...
out of here.
They're just
going to keep coming.
We'll never leave
this place, friend.
Oh, God.
Okay, well, uh...
I thought we were gonna be
the Lethal Protector.
We are.
That's what this is.
Yeah.
All right.
Come and get us.
-Go.
-Huh?
Go.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
I'll never forget you.
Don't forget me either, Eddie.
No.
Time to go.
Strickland.
Strickland authorized.
No.
Strickland.
Strickland authorized.
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
It's just bye for now.
No. No. No! No!
Go!
No, Eddie!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Shh.
Nierika.
Hey, buddy.
I just had a crazy dream.
Buddy?
He's not coming back.
But I need him back.
He wasn't meant for this place.
You couldn't have kept him.
And he couldn't have kept you.
For your bravery, you both have
the heartfelt thanks
of a grateful nation.
Eddie, you're free
to start your life again.
Everything that happened
in San Francisco
and in the last few days,
consider it expunged.
Just so you're clear,
of course,
you ever breathe a word of this
to any living soul,
you will spend
the rest of that life
in the coldest,
darkest hole imaginable.
Good luck, Eddie.
♪ Here's to the ones
that we got ♪
♪ Cheers to the wish
you were here, but you're not ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ Of everything
we've been through ♪
♪ Toast to the ones
here today ♪
that we lost on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ And the memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
♪ There's a time
that I remember ♪
♪ When I did not know no pain ♪
♪ When I believed in forever ♪
♪ Everything would
stay the same ♪
♪ Now my heart
feel like December ♪
♪ When somebody say your name ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't reach out
to call you ♪
♪ But I know I will
one day, yeah ♪
♪ Everybody hurts sometimes ♪
♪ Everybody hurts someday,
ay, ay ♪
♪ But everything gon' be
all right ♪
♪ Go and raise a glass
and say, ay ♪
♪ Here's to the ones
that we got ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Cheers to the wish
you were here, but you're not ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ Of everything
we've been through ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Toast to the ones
here today ♪
♪ Ay ♪
♪ Toast to the ones
that we lost on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause the drinks bring back
all the memories ♪
♪ And the memories bring back,
memories bring back you... ♪
I won't forget you, buddy.
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo,
doo, doo, doo, doo ♪
doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
doh, doh ♪
♪ Memories bring back,
memories bring back you ♪
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Push me into overdrive,
what a lovely way to die ♪
♪ If you're with me by my side,
I'm in for the ride ♪
♪ There's no running,
no escape ♪
♪ All the venom never waits ♪
♪ Once you feel it hit
your veins, it's too late ♪
♪ You're gone ♪
♪ And there's no stopping
or slowing down ♪
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Push me up against the wall,
it's the final curtain call ♪
♪ 'Bout to be
a barroom brawl, oh ♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ There's no stopping
or slowing down ♪
♪ There won't be
a next time now ♪
♪ But I'll be fine
if you're around ♪
♪ Give me one last dance ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ There's no stopping
what's going down ♪
♪ There won't be
a next time now ♪
♪ But I'll be fine
if you're around ♪
♪ Give me one last dance
before we hit the ♪
♪ Ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
♪ Before we hit the,
before we hit the ♪
♪ Before we hit the ground ♪
Your champion has fallen.
The planets will be mine.
The King in Black is awake.
I will kill your world.
Everyone will burn.
And you...
will watch!
♪ You got a lotta nerve,
don't you, baby? ♪
♪ I only hit the curb
'cause you made me ♪
♪ You're telling all
your friends that I'm crazy ♪
♪ Like I'm the only one ♪
♪ Why'd you throw
them stones if you ♪
♪ Had a wild hair
of your own or two? ♪
♪ Living in your big
glass house with a view ♪
♪ I thought you knew ♪
♪ I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ You thought I'd take
the blame for us a-crumbling ♪
♪ Go round like
you ain't guilty of something ♪
♪ Already lost the game
that you been running ♪
♪ Guess it's catching up
to you, huh ♪
♪ You think that
you're so innocent ♪
♪ After all the shit you did ♪
♪ I ain't an angel,
you ain't heaven-sent ♪
♪ Can't wash our hands
of this ♪
♪ I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ It takes two
to break a heart in two ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Baby, you blame me
and, baby, I blame you ♪
♪ Aw, if that ain't the truth ♪
♪ Oh, I had some help ♪
♪ It ain't like I can make
this kinda mess all by myself ♪
♪ Don't act like
you ain't help me ♪
♪ Pull that bottle
off the shelf ♪
♪ Been deep in every weekend
if you couldn't tell ♪
♪ They say, "Teamwork makes
the dream work" ♪
♪ Hell, I had some help ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there,
and it's getting harder to ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there,
and it's ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ And I know
you might not get it ♪
♪ But you're right there ♪
♪ And it's getting harder
to fight this feeling, so ♪
♪ Come and find out with me ♪
♪ Before it's turned
upside down right before us ♪
♪ And that's okay
if you miss me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm-a make sure
that door stay wide open ♪
♪ For you and me, baby ♪
♪ We just on
a different team, but ♪
♪ That's okay with me 'cause ♪
♪ You remind me of
my favorite things ever ♪
♪ Let me cut out the nonsense ♪
♪ Hundred for the bag, another
hundred for the contents ♪
♪ This life ... a contest, and
if you think you first place ♪
♪ Get your thoughts checked ♪
♪ You just can't grasp
the concept of ♪
♪ Something that's
beyond yourself ♪
♪ This could be
our last dance ♪
♪ And I need
the best way through it ♪
♪ Won't nobody be there
to tell you direction ♪
♪ When ... get hectic
and stressful ♪
♪ It's pressing that I get
past this, but I can't ♪
♪ I just can't do it ♪
♪ I know it might sound crazy ♪
♪ But all your friends
going right down with you ♪
♪ You think I'd really pay
the price that simple? ♪
♪ I ain't never gonna flip and
they don't like that 'bout me ♪
♪ We got nobody watching,
take it off for me, shorty ♪
♪ Just give me this ♪
♪ And I could give it all
to you, shorty ♪
♪ I just want to know
if you would ♪
♪ Give your all to me, shorty ♪
♪ 'Cause you're all
that I got ♪
♪ If I'm honest about it ♪
♪ You couldn't have picked
a worse time for this... ♪
♪ I just wasted ten times
what you earn ♪
♪ We just can't be
getting high every day ♪
♪ I guess I should've never
tried from the jump ♪
♪ I'm fried than a... ♪
♪ Outside, head high
than a... ♪
♪ I got to catch a red-eye
for a club showing ♪
♪ Boy, I'm 'bout to sit my...
down and get a dub for it ♪
♪ You just can't grasp
the concept of ♪
♪ Something that's
beyond yourself ♪
♪ This could be
our last dance ♪
♪ And I need the best way
through it ♪
♪ Won't nobody be there
to tell you direction ♪
♪ When...get hectic
and stressful ♪
♪ It's pressing that I'll get
past this, but I can't ♪
♪ I just can't do it ♪
♪ Czarface ♪
♪ What a mind trick,
enough to make my mind sick ♪
♪ And eyes twitch,
I'm ticked off ♪
♪ The shift is seismic ♪
♪ Everything I thought I knew
is Knull & Void ♪
♪ And destroyed, day is night,
left is right ♪
♪ Heavy's light,
black is white ♪
♪ War is peace, peace is war,
either or ♪
♪ You woke up down 20, you
should've been keeping score ♪
♪ A fallacy,
it rattles me to my core ♪
♪ Of the Earth, it's reversed,
what is worse? ♪
♪ You could call this a curse ♪
♪ There are new ways to die ♪
♪ And I am anti,
polar opposite ♪
♪ Stand by,
you were told a damn lie ♪
♪ Trying to be transparent
and see-through ♪
♪ In an opaque world
could eat you ♪
♪ Death has no manners when it
greets you, what I teach you ♪
♪ Put that contract
with world peace in the trash ♪
♪ I could be a free agent
with Venom in the flask ♪
♪ At last ♪
♪ Take off the mask ♪
♪ Take off the mask,
slow news day ♪
♪ The drama queen
says hysteria, pandemonia ♪
♪ Is outlined
with fierce fires ♪
♪ All around the border,
there's clear lines drawn ♪
♪ All barrels pointed
35 degrees ♪
♪ Skies torn,
filled with satellites ♪
♪ Pixel features formed,
coded ♪
♪ Interior mind loaded,
image uploading ♪
♪ Conspiracists pictured this
foreboding ♪
♪ Analytics from the armchair,
predicted years before ♪
♪ Pored over,
spoken too much over the Net ♪
♪ Reeling from the residue
of gun smoke ♪
♪ And even though
the guns smoking ♪
♪ If the horse already bolted ♪
♪ Then the barn door
is wide open ♪
♪ Things ain't always
what it seems ♪
♪ And these things
seem the same ♪
♪ But that ain't always
what it means ♪
♪ What is real, what is dream,
the public eye is seldom seen ♪
♪ Seldom heard,
the learning curve ♪
♪ Is sell your soul
to sell a scene ♪
♪ Spread the word,
let it breathe ♪
♪ Plant the seed,
let it breed ♪
♪ Tell your dawgs to tell
your G's, then tell it all ♪
♪ If I'm cut, let it bleed ♪
♪ If it ain't broke,
then let it be ♪
♪ Tell my loved ones
I'd rather let 'em go ♪
♪ Than let 'em grieve ♪
♪ Too much pride
to let it leave ♪
♪ Can't see the forest
for the trees ♪
♪ Feel the darkness
setting in ♪
♪ Just let it in
and set it free ♪
♪ I'm better off a better me,
I bet it costs to be a boss ♪
♪ I'm like of course
it better be ♪
♪ You take a loss,
you better see ♪
♪ My point of view
is not to view ♪
♪ But make a point
to point at you ♪
♪ Then make a point
to prove a point ♪
♪ To make it
just as pointless, too ♪
♪ Oh, silly me, I'm just
as vain as this soliloquy ♪
♪ You feeling me,
then I'm the perfect ending ♪
♪ To this trilogy ♪
Hello? Hello?
¿Hola? Hello?