All I ever wanted in
this world is carnage.
Eddie... We should be out there,
snacking on bad guys.
I am a predator.
I need to be free.
You have got to get control
of your aggression...
or we will get hauled off into Area 51.
You live in my body, you live by my rules.
I'm sorry, I don't know what came over me,
please, let me fix it.
Sorry to break it again..
you are a loser.
Eddie Brock, I want to give you my story.
Inside the mind of serial
killer Cletus Kasady.
People love serial killers.
Cletus, why me?
What's mine is yours,
and what's yours is mine.
I have tasted blood before,
and that is not it.
All I ever wanted in this world..
is carnage.
I'm not a crazy man.
Really I'm a vengeful one.
Oh, Shit!
Whoa, where you going?
- That is a red one.
- You need to come out right now.
I will let you eat everybody.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Oh, yeah!
Eddie...
you feel like home to me,
like family.
Oh, wow!
You could just say
"I'm happy for you."
That was going to be us.
I'm happy for you.
No!
- God, I'm so sorry.
- Not sorry.
These two need some
serious couples counselling.