Got your Popcorn, Candy, Drinks ?
.... The Movie is Rolling ....
"Enjoy the Movie"
MAN: (over radio) Life
Foundation Control, this is LF1.
The specimens are secured,
and we're heading home.
MISSION CONTROL: Roger, LF1.
You are a go for reentry.
MAN: Copy that.
Initiating reentry sequence.
Point-four by 103-point...
- (blasting)
- Oh, shit.
WOMAN: Seal it off.
Seal it off!
MISSION CONTROL:
LF1, Mission Control.
You're breaking up.
Please repeat.
MAN: Mayday, Mayday, LF1!
- Mayday!
- MISSION CONTROL: LF1, Mission Control.
Please repeat.
LF1, Mission Control.
(fire crackling)
(indistinct chatter)
(helicopter blades whirring)
I don't want to have to wait
for full clean-up just to get
- a status report.
- We're collecting this data
- as quickly as possible.
- That's not good enough.
Okay, maybe you can tell me
what happened.
There was some kind of breach.
One of the astronauts
- sent a distress call.
- What about the crew?
- We're still investigating.
- Where did it go down?
It's 20 kilometers
west of Sibu.
Did we at least retrieve
all of the samples?
No. We have
three of them.
One of the organisms
got out of containment,
and it's missing.
We don't know which one.
(indistinct chatter)
(speaking Malay)
CARLTON: What is she saying?
One of the astronauts
is still alive.
- (JJ coughing)
- (speaking Malay)
CARLTON: That's Jameson.
(coughing)
(woman speaking Malay)
(siren blaring)
(gasping, choking)
(choking)
(flesh squelching)
Improved Captions by Sailor420
!!! Hope you enjoy the show !!!
(snoring)
- Morning, sunshine.
- What?
I'm awake.
Missed me.
- I'm awake.
- Here you go.
- You can have it back.
- Thank... (groans)
Oh, wow,
you're wearing a suit. Yes!
- I love it when you wear the suit.
- Thank you.
I have depositions today
in the Life Foundation case.
Hey, let me know
how your meeting goes.
My meeting?
Oh, shit. Yeah.
My meeting.
- Coffee.
- Oh. Mmm!
- You are perfect.
- Thank you.
Hey, you know what...
You know what night
- it is tonight, right?
- Date night.
Mmm-hmm. So, I will pick
you up around, uh, 6:00.
And please do not forget
your helmet.
Oh, I'm glad
that you like it,
'cause I plan on wearing it
at our wedding.
That's hot.
Feed the cat.
I will.
I love you!
Love you, too.
Feed the cat.
(door opens)
♫  I be the realest one alive  ♫
♫  You don't want no problem  ♫
♫  Take you down, it ain't
gonna be no problem, yeah  ♫
♫  I get to feeling
like I'm high all my life  ♫
♫  You ain't gonna want
these problems  ♫
♫  Take you down, ain't
gonna be no problem... ♪  ♫
EDDIE: Eddie Brock
with boots on the ground
today in the Mission District,
chasing a lead into some...
Everybody knows how
our Silicon Valley overlords
at Google and Facebook...
Last time, I was poking around
asking uncomfortable
questions...
Homelessness is only increasing
into the thousands...
Eddie Brock here reporting
today from downtown Oakland,
where massive demonstrations
have taken over the streets.
I've been chasing
this real-estate bribery story
for a few weeks now.
This is gonna piss you off.
...all being strong-armed...
Medical examiner has yet
to determine cause of death,
due to the condition
of the body,
but you don't wind up
at the bottom of a landfill
due to natural causes,
so it seems that the city
doesn't care about these people
any more than the killer does.
I'm Eddie Brock,
and this is The Brock Report.
Hey, Richard!
- Lookin' good!
- Eddie, you can't park there, bro.
Come on, man. There's
no such thing as can't.
How'd she do?
Berkeley. Brown. MIT.
- She's got a scholarship, bro.
- What'd I tell you?
You told me what?
- No such thing as can't.
- Eddie.
The bike.
MIT! Whoo!
You know what I love
about this view?
- It never gets old.
- EDDIE: Yeah, well, uh...
Height's not really my thing.
But, uh...
What's the deal?
- I got you the big one, exclusive.
- Yeah? Who?
Carlton Drake.
- Carlton Drake?
- The man's a visionary.
He wants to talk
about his rockets,
assure everyone they're safe,
that the crash was an anomaly.
Uh...
He's... He's seriously off.
I'm gonna level with you.
Carlton Drake could buy us
with his pocket cash,
turn this building into his
own garage if he so wished.
Now, you're just gonna ask him
about his space program,
you're gonna thank him, and
you're gonna bid him a nice day.
He's a crook.
Eddie, when you had nowhere
to go, we gave you a home.
Now, you know we love
the Eddie Brock show.
There isn't a better investigative
reporter working today,
but no one
is above the network.
So do me a favor, Eddie,
don't start your shit again.
All right, all right.
- For me.
- All right. I'll do it.
EDDIE: I don't know why he gave
me this assignment, Annie.
It's not...
It's not what I do.
ANNE: Well, my mother
always told me
that anything in life worth
having would take sacrifice...
- Mmm-hmm.
- Patience...
- Mmm.
- And be a lot of work.
- Oh.
- That's you...
- That's not.
- ...that I'm talking about.
- Nah.
- Yeah.
Well, you're lucky
to have me.
To be fair,
I'm quite a catch.
- That's what my mom told me.
- (laughs)
Are you gonna
behave yourself tomorrow?
No. No, I'm gonna do my job.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I can't, you know,
not do my job.
The guy you work for
is a complete...
I don't work for Drake.
I work for my firm,
and my firm works for him.
And I'm sure
that they defend many people
that you don't deem worthy,
but we don't want a repeat.
- A repeat?
- Of the Daily Globe incident.
Ow! Really?
- Incident? That's not an incident.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Baby, you were run out of New York.
- I was not. I did not.
I don't want you
run out of San Francisco.
No, I still have
currency in New York.
I was going places.
I wasn't running.
In fact, I moved
to San Francisco for you.
- Me?
- You are my home.
You're not so bad yourself,
champ.
- Less talking, more kissing.
- All right.
Let's just get the check.
♫  You  ♫
♫  Oh  ♫
♫  You are my lady  ♫
♫  Ooh, ooh  ♫
♫  I am your man  ♫
♫  Some call it crazy  ♫
♫  Ooh, ooh  ♫
♫  They don't understand  ♫
♫  Our love... ♪  ♫
(whispers)
I'm gonna get a drink.
(sighs)
(laptop chimes)
(meowing)
- Shh.
- (cat meows)
CARLTON: Very soon,
another Life Foundation rocket
will be sent
on an exploratory mission.
And that's how, one day,
we might all live in space.
- (children exclaim)
- Cool, huh? And now that I've shown you
some of the cool stuff
that we do here,
I'm hoping I've inspired
each and every one of you
to go out there
and create things that others
- have only dreamt of.
- GIRL: Mr. Drake?
- Shh!
- It's okay. Don't silence her.
Come here. What's your name?
- Allie.
- It's okay, Allie.
You know, sometimes
that's what people do.
They try and silence
those of us who ask questions.
But you know what?
In the end,
we're the ones
who change the world.
Take good care
of that, Allie.
Guys, this is Dr. Skirth.
- Say hi.
- CHILDREN: Hi.
Hello, kids.
Um, sorry to interrupt,
but it's time to get changed
for your interview.
Yeah. Uh, kids,
sorry to leave you.
Allie, you're in charge.
High five up top.
Dr. Skirth will answer Allie's
question, and any others.
- See you next time, guys. Bye!
- CHILDREN: Bye!
EDDIE: What do you say,
Mr. Drake,
we just start
at the beginning?
- Born to British parents.
- CARLTON: Mmm-hmm.
And then at 19, you
discovered a gene therapy
that literally doubles
the life expectancy
- of pancreatic cancer patients.
- Well, actually,
it tripled their
life expectancy.
But it's okay.
Okay, um, 24.
That's still extremely young.
All right, you create
(imitates explosion)
- the Life Foundation!
- It didn't happen overnight.
And then...
(whooshes) Rockets.
You then decide,
like any normal human being,
that you're gonna go
and explore space.
You know what it is?
I have always believed...
- Uh-huh.
- ...that space exploration
is crucial
in our quest to cure
everything that ails us
here on Earth.
But if you think about
everything we've found...
- Uh-huh.
- ...in the oceans and on land,
- isn't it time to look up there?
- Mmm-hmm.
To this plethora
of untapped resources?
And you have a plethora
of untapped resources, also,
from your pharmaceutical
companies
that you're involved with,
you know, to help you realize
- that ambition, I suppose.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
- Full circle.
So, I have to ask,
how does that work,
you know, exactly,
the Life Foundation thing?
How does it...
How does it, um...
I don't know,
how does it go about,
- say, testing pharmaceuticals?
- WOMAN: Eddie, we're talking
- about the rocket here.
- No, I'm not. I'm not.
I'm talking
about the allegations.
- I'm sorry, I don't...
- It says that
your entire empire
has been built
- on dead bodies.
- Eddie.
It's true, right?
It says that you recruit
the most vulnerable of us
to volunteer for tests...
- Hmm.
- ...that more often than not
end up killing people.
Yeah, I'm aware
of these rumors online.
There's a lot of fake news
out there these days.
Right. What about
the legal cases?
Sorry?
Uh, the actual legal cases,
like Sarah Chambers,
- Phil Barclay, Rob MacDonald.
- GUARD: That's it. Time to go.
Thank you so much for coming
to talk to me, Mr. Brock.
And they're just some
of the people who walked
- through these doors...
- Have a nice day.
- Cut the camera off, please.
- CARLTON: Thank you very much.
- GUARD: Time is up. Come on.
- They're dead. The Dead...
- Could you show him out, please?
- The Dead Found...
Don't touch me.
The Dead Foundation thing.
- Get out of here, Brock.
- We're not finished.
Yes, you are, Mr. Brock.
Is that a threat?
Have a nice life.
I know what
you're going to say, but...
This guy, he is
all the way bad, Jack.
- If you just give...
- Who's your source?
- Excuse me?
- Who's your source, Eddie?
I don't have a source, per se.
But I have a hunch.
This isn't the Wild Wild West.
We don't go off half-cocked
based on a hunch.
We do the work.
We substantiate
our accusations.
We provide evidence.
You know, for a smart guy,
you really are a dumbass.
(Eddie's boss sighs)
You're fired, Eddie.
I can't trust you.
Have a nice life.
- MAN 1: Will just take a second.
- MAN 2: Okay.
Hey.
You are pathologically
self-absorbed.
Annie. Annie,
can you talk to me first?
Your ego requires
constant attention,
and you're stubborn as hell.
But I was willing to roll with
it, Eddie, because I loved you.
You "loved" me?
What is that supposed to mean?
ANNE: What you did
got me fired.
You used me.
Annie? Annie.
(thunder rumbling)
(rustling)
Oh, my God.
(breathing heavily)
You're beautiful.
(indistinct chatter)
(speaking Mandarin)
(metallic clink)
(people screaming)
(men speaking Mandarin)
(people gasping and screaming)
(woman groaning)
(gasping)
(woman speaks Mandarin)
(rustling)
- (flesh squelching)
- (faint grunting)
- DORA: Test 36.
- (keyboard clacking)
Biological interactions
- between two different organisms.
- (low snarling)
These creatures need to bond
with a respiratory host
in order to survive
for any amount of time
in an oxygen-rich environment.
Well, why are
all these hosts
showing this hyper-acute
rejection?
DORA: That's what
we're trying to find out.
(beeping)
The bonding process
is starting.
(computer chimes)
It's equalizing.
(low grumbling)
(laughs)
But why? Why this rabbit?
- It's similar to an organ transplant.
- Huh.
Where the donor and recipient
must be an exact match?
- That's correct.
- Okay. So wait, think about it.
If we do achieve symbiosis, they
should be able to survive here,
but also we would
be able to survive there.
(chuckles softly)
"We"?
- Begin human trials.
- Oh, it's way too soon
to even begin to think
about something like...
Dr. Skirth, you're at the forefront
of a scientific breakthrough.
I need you to hold your nerve.
All right?
I understand,
but it's an ethical question.
Think of future generations.
Think of your kids.
Hey, how are your kids?
Let's begin human trials.
Good work.
(slow-tempo
rock music playing)
(indistinct chatter)
Hey, Jack.
Do you ever feel
like your life
- is like one monumental screwup?
- Nope.
CARLTON: (on TV)
Here at the Life Foundation,
- we've always believed...
- Isn't that your buddy?
...in finding the lessons
in our disappointments.
In the months
since our rocket failed,
we've learned so much.
Do you think we could,
like, switch him off?
Some people
are trying to watch that.
Oh, you are, are you?
- Yeah?
- Aren't you Eddie Brock?
I used to be.
CARLTON: We take
the same view of progress.
Thrilled to announce
that the Life Foundation
has now begun preparations
on its next launch.
All right, Jack,
this is for you.
I do not want you
to spend it all at once.
I'm going to go home and chase
myself around the room,
playing hard to get.
- (hip-hop music playing)
- (distant siren wailing)
- Hey, Maria.
- Eddie.
- How's it going?
- Righteous, Eddie.
Oh! Yeah, we're empty.
Cost you $5.
$5 for a paper that's free?
I walked all the way over
to the vending machine,
got the papers out and
brought 'em back over here,
so you can have 'em
personally delivered to you.
You did that for me?
- Yes, I did.
- Oh.
- Five bucks.
- That's pretty steep.
Tell you what, you give
me a dollar for a song,
I'll throw in the paper.
I'll tell you what,
I will give you 20 bucks,
but not to sing,
all right?
Deal.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- No. You're welcome.
- (laughs)
- (shop bell tinkling)
- Hey, Mrs. Chen.
- How you doing, Eddie?
- Ah, aches and pains,
you know, aches and pains.
You look like shit.
Excuse me?
And you look
as beautiful as ever.
- Jesus.
- Mind is body, Eddie.
Have you been meditating
like I showed you?
- No, I have not. And it does not work.
- It doesn't work,
- because you don't give it a chance.
- No, it doesn't work,
because I bought a DVD off your
cousin, and it was in Mandarin.
- (speaks Mandarin)
- Yeah, I don't understand that, either.
See, that right there, I don't
understand what you just said.
That is the problem.
(speaks Mandarin)
Bottle of whiskey,
and don't forget my change.
- MRS. CHEN: Please.
- (smacks counter)
Let's go.
Before the price goes up
for my protection.
- (register drawer opens)
- (cash rustling)
The full payment is due.
Now.
Make sure you have
my money ready, Chen.
I don't like to wait.
(shop door opens and closes)
Life hurts, Eddie.
It just does.
♫  "So He Won't Break"
by The Black Keys playing  ♫
WOMAN: I gotta go. (laughs)
- (giggles) Okay. Love you, babe.
- See you, babe.
♫  And the state it put him in  ♫
EDDIE: What a dick.
♫  To hold his head high  ♫
♫  When he really wanna die  ♫
♫  And you know  ♫
- (siren wails)
- (tires squeal)
♫  The difference it makes  ♫
♫  And you know  ♫
♫  All that it takes  ♫
♫  Is love...  ♫
I'm not even
asking to staff there.
Why would I do that?
I can't use my name.
I can use a pseudonym.
Any name. Think...
You pick a name.
I could be a woman.
Have you seen Tootsie?
♫  He won't break  ♫
♫  Won't break...  ♫
I'll call you back.
Okay, I won't. Thank you. Bye.
ECKHART TOLLE: Realize deeply that the
present moment is all you ever have.
Make the now the primary
focus of your life.
Any action is often better
than no action,
especially if you
have been stuck
in an unhappy situation
for a long time.
If it is a mistake, at least
you learned something,
in which case
it's no longer...
(electric guitar
playing loudly)
(grunts quietly)
(electric guitar
continues playing)
CARLTON: Thank you all for
bringing us to this moment.
Our names will be spoken
long after we are dust.
History starts now.
This is day one.
This is first contact.
- Let's get to work.
- (scientists murmuring)
(low snarling)
(door hissing)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
Establishing subject baseline.
All vital signs are normal.
(low snarling)
- Put me through.
- (button clicks)
There's no need to be
frightened, Isaac.
There's no need.
Isaac. You know
that's a biblical name?
(nervously) Yes, sir.
God said to Abraham,
"Give me your son,
"show me you are willing
to sacrifice the one thing
"most precious to you,"
and Abraham was willing.
You know what's always
impressed me about that story?
It isn't Abraham's sacrifice.
It's Isaac's.
Now, I don't know what kind of
God would ask that of someone,
but it doesn't change
anything for me.
Isaac is still the hero
of this story.
Look around you.
Look at the world.
What do you see?
War, poverty,
a planet on the brink
of collapse.
I would argue that God
has abandoned us.
He didn't keep
his end of the bargain, Isaac,
so now it's down to you and me
to put this right.
And this time, Isaac,
we can.
We will.
This time,
I will not abandon us.
(trembling whisper) Yes.
Open it.
(trilling)
(snarling)
What the hell is that?
What? No, what...
Please let me... No.
Oh, please, please, please!
- (whimpering)
- (snarling)
(continues whimpering)
(grunts, pants)
(machine beeping)
DR. COLLINS:
His vitals are holding steady.
- ISAAC: Where the hell did it go?
- Incredible.
Where did it go?
(gasps)
(whispers) Where is it?
(panting)
- (liquid sloshing)
- (rapid beeping)
(grunts)
(yelling)
(bones cracking)
- (gasping)
- (rustling)
(choking)
(glass thuds)
(low snarling)
Bring in the next volunteer.
- (indistinct chatter)
- (distant siren wailing)
(car horn honks)
(car horn honking distantly)
(shop bell jingles)
EDDIE: (stammers) You know,
I used to be a reporter.
I was...
I was pretty successful,
as well, you know?
My job, it required you to...
You know, to follow people
that did not want to be followed
and hide in plain sight.
I mean...
You have to know
how to disappear.
I was pretty good, but,
you know, you...
Whoever you are, you suck.
Okay.
- Uh, my name is Dora Skirth.
- Mmm.
I need your help.
- I work at the Life Foundation.
- You do?
- Yes.
- Wow. Good for you.
We're done.
- No...
- (shop bell jingles)
Mr. Brock, please...
Please listen to me.
Everything that you
accused him of,
you were right.
It's all true.
- I don't care anymore.
- Really?
Because he's got a lab
filled with poor people,
and they're all signing waivers
that they don't understand,
and he's using them
like guinea pigs,
and they are dying.
They are all dying.
- You've seen that?
- Yes.
Come here.
Why would I believe you?
Because it's true.
I believed in him, and I...
I told myself
that it was worth it
because we were curing cancer,
but now this is different.
- Something else.
- Go to the cops.
I can't do that.
I'm afraid of what
will happen to my family.
He's a very dangerous man, and
he's a very powerful man...
I know, I know
how dangerous he is,
because the very first time
I interviewed him,
just once, I lose my job
the very next day.
I lost my career,
I lost my relationship,
I lost my apartment, I lost
everything I ever cared about.
You know why? Carlton Drake
ruined me. Finished.
Now, if you are
who you say you are,
genuinely,
and you have proof,
then you should be
very, very, very afraid.
I am.
You need to find yourself another
white knight, Ms. Skirth,
because I am done.
I am done
with all of this shit.
What shit?
All of this "saving my
fellow man" shit.
All right? Good night.
ANNE: Eddie?
Well, hey. Whoa.
Anne, I was just walking by,
and, uh...
I saw Mr. Belvedere.
I felt concerned for
his welfare, so...
Eddie... (sighs)
This is Dan.
- Dan, this is Eddie.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hey, man.
- Yeah.
- Annie's told me a lot about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm a big fan of your work.
- Thank you.
- Really?
It's pretty cool, all the
people that he took down.
Yeah, I was one of them.
DAN: Well, look,
I'll let you guys catch up.
- So I'll see you inside?
- You're the best.
- Really nice meeting you, man.
- Uh, you, too.
(keys jangle)
- He has a key. You know he has a key?
- (door closes)
Yeah. How else
would he get in?
(chuckles halfheartedly)
Yeah. Well, uh... (sniffs)
So, uh, what you up to?
You realize that's light-years away
from being any of your business, right?
Hey, well, just asking,
you know.
So, is Dan, uh, a lawyer?
No, he's a doctor.
- Surgeon, actually.
- Oh.
How's Mr. Belvedere, anyway?
(stammers) I would say
that he misses you,
but that would be bullshit,
'cause...
- He's a cat.
- No, because he never liked you.
No, he's a cat,
and cats don't like anyone.
You look good, by the way.
You doing good?
What are you
doing here, Eddie?
I'm here 'cause I miss you.
A lot.
You know, we were gonna
get married.
That wasn't so long ago,
and now, you know...
I can't really believe
that we're not... (sighs)
Are we gonna try
and find our way back?
No, we can't.
You did this, Eddie.
Not Carlton Drake,
not the network.
You.
(lock clicks)
(indistinct chatter, laughter)
(wind whistling)
(helicopter blades whirring)
- (sniffs)
- (line ringing)
Uh, hello.
This is Dr. Skirth.
Yes, Eddie Brock here.
Talk to me.
EDDIE: Are you sure
this is gonna work?
DORA: Just stay down
and shut up, please.
MAN: (over radio) 53.5,
win-909 RPM.
Whew.
DORA: Overpopulation
and climate change.
These are two things
that Drake cannot control.
EDDIE: Yeah, got it, right.
DORA: We are literally a generation
away from an uninhabitable Earth.
- EDDIE: Uh, yeah.
- Drake is using his personal rockets
to scout real estate.
You know, it's a really
interesting story,
but we need to just get to the
part where he's killing people.
(sighs) Drake sent a ship
on a recon mission.
On the way back,
they found a comet.
EDDIE: A comet?
Onboard computers indicated the presence
of life, of millions of organisms.
Wait, wait, wait, when you
say "millions of organisms,"
- what do you mean?
- We brought back some specimens.
You're talking about aliens?
Like, aliens?
(imitates e.t.)
E.T. phone home.
Aliens, yeah.
- Yes.
- (door opens)
But we don't
call them that.
- We call them Symbiotes.
- Symbiotes?
And they cannot survive in
our environment without help.
Drake believes that the union
between human and Symbiote
is the key to our survival,
but not here on Earth.
Drake is trying to put human
beings and aliens together?
So they can live in space?
We call them hosts.
That's nuts, isn't it?
That's completely insane.
Yes. There's no protocol
for this thing.
He's just feeding them in.
If the match isn't exact...
MAN: (over radio)
Elevators patrol check.
(keypad chimes)
Please, just go in.
Don't touch anything.
- I won't. I won't.
- Go, go, go. I'll take care of him.
Dr. Skirth.
I thought you'd all gone home.
Oh, yes. Well, you know
what they say.
Science never sleeps.
(distant electrical chime)
(door rumbles)
(camera clicking)
(camera clicks)
(pounding on door)
- Eddie! It's me. Let me out!
- Maria? Maria?
- Please! Let me out!
- I don't know how to get you...
- Let me out. Out.
- I don't know how.
- (whirring)
- EDDIE: Oh, my God.
(screaming)
(grunts)
(growling)
Oh, God! Maria, no! Maria!
Maria! No, Maria, no!
- (Eddie choking)
- (squelching)
(choking)
- (squelching stops)
- (Eddie gasps)
AUTOMATED VOICE: There has been a
security breach in Lab Sector 3.
Oh, no. Maria?
Maria! Oh, shit.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Repeat, this is
a Code Silver security breach.
All security personnel, please
respond to Lab Sector 3.
GUARD: Freeze!
(Eddie grunting)
(radio static crackling)
(alarm blaring)
(grunting)
(guards shouting indistinctly)
(engine revving)
GUARD: Got eyes on!
(yells)
(low growling)
GUARD: Go!
Go! Go!
Where the hell'd he go?
- GUARD 1: I'm not seeing him.
- Fan out.
- Find him.
- GUARD 2: Nothing. Nothing yet.
MAN: (over radio)
Search Team 4, Search Team 4.
GUARD: Backtrack
200 feet east.
- (branch snaps)
- (tree creaking)
(on cell phone) This is Dora.
Leave a message.
Skirth, yeah, it's me.
I just got back.
Are you all right?
I haven't heard from you,
so I want to know
if you're all right.
But, yeah, that was
a great call on the lab.
You're absolutely right.
Yeah. Listen.
I got a... I got a guy.
I'm gonna call him and, uh...
Mmm. Oh...
Oh, I got a bunch of
photographs.
He will publish those photographs,
but I need you to come with me.
Uh, could you just call me back?
Call me back.
Whoa. (inhales)
(groans)
- (flies buzzing)
- Yeah.
Mmm.
(low growling)
(garbage clatters)
(retching)
(groans)
What is wrong with me?
- VENOM: (deep voice) Eddie.
- (shrieks)
CARLTON: How bad?
DR. EMERSON: It's bad.
CARLTON: (shouts) How bad?
Well, we assume
the intruder took it.
Took it? Took it?
We don't know what happened.
I want to speak to every man
who was on duty last night.
- Already did, sir.
- But I didn't.
Get it out of my sight.
- Carlton, you need to see this.
- CARLTON: What now?
DR. EMERSON: His blood
pressure's back to normal.
Liver functions, too.
(chuckles softly)
CARLTON: I knew it.
See, his body just needed
time to adjust.
(chuckles)
I don't want to waste any more time.
I want to up the tests.
- Okay?
- DR. EMERSON: Yeah.
Come on.
You're fired.
Find my Symbiote.
Now!
(groans)
(bottles clink)
EDDIE: Jesus.
(groans softly)
(airplane passing overhead)
ANNOUNCER: (over PA) Attention,
passengers for Flight 2517
to San Francisco
via Hong Kong.
We will be boarding
at gate 9 in 15 minutes.
Please have your
boarding passes...
WOMAN: Suzy.
Come on, over here.
(indistinct chatter)
May I speak to Annie Weying,
please?
Can you tell her
that it's an emergency?
- VENOM: Food.
- (yelps)
Who said that?
No, I'm not talking to you.
Can you please tell me
where she is?
Great. Thank you. (sighs)
Okay...
(elegant piano music playing)
HOSTESS: Yes, Lana for two?
- I'm sorry, sir?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Sir?
- Oh, yes.
Oh, my God, Eddie.
What are you doing here?
- Annie...
- No, no, no...
No, I have to tell you
something.
- No, no, no. Please.
- No, now. I have to.
Work told me you were here. You're
the only person that I trust.
Are you drunk?
Yeah. No, I broke into
the Life Foundation.
- Eddie, you did what?
- Yeah, but I may...
I think I may have been
infected.
He's burning up.
You're really hot.
Eddie, you look like
you're in a bad way.
I am. I am in a bad way.
- Eddie, Jesus!
- (people gasping)
This is dead.
Dead.
ANNE: Eddie, sit down.
- Okay, all right. Okay.
- (Eddie grunts)
- Hey, hey, Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
- Stop that.
- Sir, sir, sir, I'm so sorry.
- Eddie, quit it.
- Put it down. Eddie!
- (woman gasps)
- Snap out of it!
- (growls)
No.
All right. It's no good.
WOMAN: Bobby,
are you all right?
- Hey!
- ANNE: Whoa!
- (grunts)
- DAN: Hey, hey, hey.
I'm a doctor. I'm a doctor.
I'm hot.
Is anyone else hot?
Are you hurt?
- Sir, excuse me.
- No! Shh!
ANNE: Wait,
where are you going? Eddie?
HOSTESS: This is unacceptable.
I'm gonna call the police.
What are you doing?
No, please don't.
- No.
- Eddie, please.
WOMAN: Oh, my God.
Ah.
(grunts in relief)
(exhales)
- Now I'm gonna call the police.
- No, no. Please don't call the police.
Here, call an ambulance. I'm a doctor.
This man is my, um...
Patient.
Oh, it's much better.
(whispering) You are insane.
- He's killing people.
- Who's killing people?
- Carlton Drake.
- Oh, God, Eddie,
- not this again.
- Yes, he is. He is!
- And I have proof!
- (low growling)
ANNE: Ugh.
(people groaning)
(Eddie snorting)
(mumbles)
- Hey, Eddie...
- Hmm? (mumbles)
(gentle music playing
over speakers)
DAN: Eddie.
Eddie?
Eddie, can you hear me?
This is Dan speaking to you.
Hey, Dan.
- Welcome back.
- EDDIE: Where am I?
Uh, you're in the MRI.
Okay, we've given you
a little sedative.
- Where is Anne?
- Anne is not here right now.
We're gonna run
some tests, okay?
It's gonna be completely
painless.
So, you know,
just try to stay still.
Uh, relax, and, um...
Yeah, here we go.
(machine whirring)
(screaming)
Eddie, what's happening
in there?
Eddie, you okay?
(screaming)
Shut it down.
- (Eddie groans)
- Hey, hey, hey.
You're okay. Yeah.
Coming out. You all right?
- Yeah.
- Here, look at me, look at me.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Just take a deep breath. Okay? You're okay.
- (takes deep breath)
- Yeah.
DAN: Now, listen, you're not the
first person to freak out in there.
I get claustrophobic, too.
WOMAN: Dr. Lewis?
- Oh, boy.
- Hey, Mrs. Manfredi. How are you?
- Oh, I just saw Morris.
- (dog yapping)
And he's whining and complaining
like an old baby again.
- DAN: (chuckles) Oh, good.
- MRS. MANFREDI: Oh, thank you so much.
- DAN: Yeah, my pleasure.
- (barking and growling)
Okay, Mrs. Manfredi,
we talked about the dog.
Okay, love the dog.
You can't have the dog.
- Sorry. Gemini.
- (Gemini growling)
We're gonna get to the bottom of this.
All right? That I can promise you.
- But for now, go home, get some rest.
- Uh-huh.
I'll call you when
your tests are in.
- All right, thank you.
- Okay? Yep.
- Thank you, Dan. Thank you.
- You got it.
- MAN: Hello, Doctor.
- Hi.
SCIENTIST: Did you have
the same reactions
regardless
of the temperature...
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
Good afternoon,
Dr. Skirth.
(sighs)
CARLTON: The creature
and the host are one.
Everything was fine.
So, why does the human
continue to waste away?
I don't know. We've given him enough
liquid nutrition to feed an elephant.
But the organism
is unaffected?
- The Symbiote is thriving.
- Good.
But once again,
it's killing the host.
It's consuming his organs.
Oh, watch this.
- (high-pitched ringing)
- (screaming)
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
You're hurting it. Stop it!
(gasps)
Sounds in the 4,000 to 6,000 hertz
range are very harmful for it.
- Well, then don't make those sounds.
- DR. COLLINS: Okay.
(sighs)
He was stabilizing.
What happened?
He's approaching
acute liver failure.
We're gonna need another host.
Such poor design.
- Excuse me?
- Human beings.
TREECE: Sorry to interrupt.
Thought you'd like
some good news.
(breathing shakily) I'm sorry.
(scoffs)
- (ship horn bellowing)
- (birds squawking)
(bell dinging)
VENOM: Hungry!
Oh, goddamn. (chuckles)
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
Can I get through, please?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna stay here,
all right?
Until the cable car stops.
(brakes squeak)
We're good.
All right. Thank you.
- (bell dings)
- Excuse me.
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, hey, Anne.
Eddie, hi. How you feeling?
Oh, feeling... I'm sick.
Well, Eddie,
you have a parasite.
They're not exactly sure
how you got it,
but it would
explain the fever.
That would make sense.
Also, I'm hearing,
uh, a voice.
DAN: Auditory hallucinations
are actually very common.
Oh, hey, Dan.
How you doing?
I didn't realize that
you were on the call, too.
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Mmm.
Hey, Dan,
would this parasite...
Would it, like, be able to
make me, I don't know...
Like, climb a really, really,
really tall tree,
but super, super fast?
VENOM: Yes. We just did.
DAN: Uh, well, Eddie,
it sounds like
it might be causing
some metabolic abnormalities
that are making it hard for your
body to maintain homeostasis.
You said "causing" and "body,"
and... I lost you.
Listen, Eddie, um, we are
gonna get you on some meds,
and we are gonna
clear that out.
- Yes.
- VENOM: Never gonna happen.
Will you stop doing that now.
Not now.
- Eddie, we're just trying to help you.
- I know.
I know. I'm just, I'm not
actually talking to you, Annie.
Who are you talking to?
I'm just gonna call you back,
all right?
Thank you. Thank you, Dan.
Thank you. Thank you, both.
- (electric guitar playing rock riffs)
- (inhales)
(sighs, sniffs)
(grunts)
(guitar feedback screeching)
(guitar stops)
Yeah?
Hey, can you turn
your music down, please?
'Cause I'm having
a really hard time.
(scoffs) Whatever.
(growls)
Yeah, sure, man. Yeah.
- I'll just turn it right down. Sorry.
- Thank you. Thank you.
I was troubled by
what we've been doing.
I get it.
We've all been troubled.
It's the nature
of what we do.
But I need you to tell me
who was here with you.
I need that from you.
I can't do that.
We can't fix things
unless we begin with
your friend.
The person who was here.
Because they're gonna die.
They're in grave danger.
You know that, right?
They're gonna die unless
we bring them back here,
where you can help
to keep them alive.
Hey. Dora.
I promise, from here on in,
we will do things differently.
(whispers)
Will you trust me?
Eddie Brock.
- Eddie Brock?
- Mmm-hmm.
You were our best.
Open it.
(sloshing)
(low snarling)
DORA: No! No!
No! No! No!
- (sizzling)
- (timer dings)
(groans)
VENOM: Do not open that door.
Huh?
(loud knocking)
(sniffs)
(grunting)
MAN: Stay put.
- Hey, Eddie.
- VENOM: Who the hell is this guy?
I'm gonna need
Mr. Drake's property back.
- (guns powering up)
- Whoa.
- VENOM: What are you doing?
- I'm, uh...
I'm putting my hands up.
VENOM: You are making us
look bad.
(straining) I...
No, I am not.
VENOM: Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are!
- Why would you do that?
'Cause it is
a very sensible thing to do.
- Eddie...
- VENOM: I will take care of this myself.
- What?
- Eddie, where's the bug?
(giggles nervously)
Take him down.
(Eddie yells)
I'm so sorry
about your friends.
(snarling)
- What is that?
- VENOM: Not "what." Who.
Oh.
(groans)
Shit.
(both grunt)
(yelling, grunting)
(gasping, whimpering)
(yelling)
(screams, grunts)
- VENOM: Outstanding.
- (panting)
Now let's bite all their heads off
and pile them up in the corner.
Why would we do that?
Pile of bodies, pile of heads.
(gasping)
What the shit, man?
No! No, no, no!
- (growling)
- (Eddie yells)
- What the hell?
- Dude! How did you do that?
Apparently, I have a parasite.
- (automatic gunfire)
- (all screaming)
- (car alarm blaring in distance)
- (groans)
Mr. Drake, our subject
is carrying the Symbiote.
Connecting you
to the feed now.
(grunting)
He's achieved symbiosis.
(laughs) Are you seeing this?
Are you seeing this?
He's achieved symbiosis!
Treece...
Treece, bring me back
my creature.
(panting)
VENOM: Eddie.
You're not even here, are you?
I'm just seeing things.
It's not real.
You're in my head.
'Cause you're just a parasite.
"Parasite"?
(grunts in pain)
(shudders)
You have a brain tumor, Eddie.
I got him. He's in the alley
behind the Schueller Building.
I am sorry that I
called you a parasite.
We can discuss this
like two men.
What is that? What is that?
(yells)
CARLTON: What?
Do not let him get away.
Do you understand me, Treece?
TREECE: (over radio) Copy.
Weapons are armed and ready.
Launch the drones.
(drones whooshing)
(engine revving)
- (yelling, grunting)
- (motorcycle accelerating)
(whimpers, grunts)
(car horn honks)
- VENOM: Duck.
- (gasps)
(tires squeal)
Whew!
- Thank you.
- VENOM: You are welcome.
(yells)
- Oh!
- (people exclaiming)
(people screaming)
(breathlessly) This is beyond
anything we thought was possible.
- (car horn honks)
- (people gasp)
- Oh, God, no!
- (drone whooshing)
(woman shrieks)
Holy shit!
(tire squeals)
(straining)
(distorted yell)
Treece, do not
let him get away.
I've got him.
All ground vehicles, move in.
Target is now eastbound
on Grant.
Oh, God! Do something!
What the...
Oh, yeah! We got more friends.
Awesome.
No, no, no! No, no!
No! You're out of your mind!
(accelerating)
No!
- (yelling)
- (engine revving)
- That is a dead-end!
- VENOM: Not for us.
Whoa!
- Yeah!
- (engine revving)
(tires screeching)
(horn honks)
(yelling)
EDDIE: Whoa!
(squelching)
I am going to die!
VENOM: You are not
going to die!
Whoa! That was pretty cool,
actually. I'm not gonna lie...
(groans)
I got him.
- CARLTON: Bring him home.
- Copy that.
(panting) This is incredible.
(strained groaning)
You have been a serious
pain in the ass for me, Eddie.
(strained) Well, you know,
I aim to please.
Eyes, lungs, pancreas.
So many snacks,
so little time.
(slurping)
(grunting)
(gunshot)
- (thuds)
- (Treece grunts)
OFFICER: SFPD. Don't move!
Get off the car!
(tires squealing)
(Officers shouting
indistinctly)
(groans)
My legs.
Oh, my God,
my legs were broken.
Now they're not broken.
What is happening?
(sighs)
(whispers) What the hell
are you?
I am Venom.
And you are mine.
You bit somebody's head off.
Fuel in the tank.
Listen carefully, Eddie.
You did not find us.
We found you.
Think of yourself
as my ride.
Where are you going?
We need
Carlton Drake's rocket.
You remember him.
How do you even know
about that?
- I know everything, Eddie.
- You do?
- Everything about you.
- How?
- I am inside your head.
- (grunts)
You are a loser, Eddie.
(Eddie sighs)
Are you gonna eat
anybody else?
Most likely.
Oh, God.
That is why we are here.
Cooperate,
and you might just survive.
That is the deal.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Good
evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to San Francisco.
For your safety and comfort,
please remain seated...
(announcer speaking
indistinctly over PA)
(cell phone rings)
Hey, babe. I'm almost home.
- DAN: Where's Eddie?
- Why? What's happening?
I got Eddie's labs back,
and it's worse than I thought.
His systems, renal, endocrine,
they're behaving abnormally.
I've never seen
anything like it.
What does that mean, Dan?
What are you telling me?
- You need to get him here.
- My God.
(sighs)
- Eddie Brock here. Leave a message.
- Shit.
CARLTON: Where were you when
it left Dr. Skirth's body?
- Where was he?
- I was...
This is the higher life-form. You
stood by and watched while it died.
The arrogance.
Treece, listen to me. After this,
we can't risk killing Brock,
not until we find
another suitable host.
I don't want to see you again
unless you have Brock!
- (siren blares)
- (indistinct police radio chatter)
Officer, what's happening?
I need to get in there.
- It's my friend's apartment.
- Building's been evacuated.
It's not safe for you
to be here, ma'am.
WOMAN:
Found another one, Bill.
OFFICER: Get off the streets.
Go home.
There's bodies
all over the city tonight.
(whispering) Bodies?
My God, Eddie,
where are you?
(cell phone ringing)
VENOM: Who is Anne?
Your pulse has quickened.
That is none of your
goddamn business.
VENOM: Everything of yours
is my business, Eddie.
We have no secrets.
Yeah? Well, then you know
exactly why I'm going here
before we get to your rocket,
huh?
VENOM: Sure.
I'm not unreasonable.
Shit. Yeah?
Eddie. Thank God. Where are you?
I need to see you.
No, no, you can't see me.
Eddie, I need you to tell me where you are.
I'm coming to get you.
No, you cannot come
anywhere near me.
You cannot come
near me right now.
- Richard. Hey, Richard...
- RICHARD: No!
- Eddie?
- EDDIE: No, I gotta go up there.
RICHARD: You know you're not
supposed to be here, Eddie.
I got to get up there, man.
Look, I got love for you, bro,
but no can do.
There's no such thing
as can't.
I'm sorry, man.
Okay, okay... Uh...
Can you, uh,
just give him this?
- He needs to see what's on it.
- Eddie, please. I really need this job.
- VENOM: Let's eat his brains.
- No! You do not touch him!
- He is my friend.
- What's wrong with you?
He works three jobs just so
that he can support his family.
- Eddie, what's going on?
- We're leaving.
- VENOM: "We"?
- EDDIE: Yeah.
- What are you talking about, "we"?
- Just stay back!
Yeah.
(panting)
- Shit.
- VENOM: You want up?
Well, why didn't you just say?
Hmm.
- It is peaceful up here.
- EDDIE: I'm not very good with heights.
Your world is not so ugly
after all.
I'm almost sorry
to see it end.
EDDIE: What does that mean?
(distorted screaming)
Where'd you go?
Where did you go?
(screaming)
- (grunts)
- (wind whistling)
(gasping)
VENOM: I got us.
Whoa.
(grunts)
Again? (inhales sharply)
You're gonna get me killed.
VENOM: You die, I die.
Yeah, well, you can always
just shed my carcass
and exchange it for another
one whenever you need.
VENOM: Why would I do that?
You are far too good of a
match to throw away so soon.
Plus, I am starting
to like you.
You and I
are not so different.
Thank you.
Okay.
Here's your evidence.
(sighs deeply)
VENOM: Jump.
(elevator bell dings)
VENOM: Pussy.
(door opens)
(faint chatter)
(weapons powering up)
SWAT LEADER:
Hands!
On the ground! Now!
Guys, you do not want to do this.
Trust me.
- Mask!
- Copy!
All right,
have it your own way.
- Mask!
- VENOM: Copy.
OFFICER 1: What the hell
is that thing?
(Officers shouting
indistinctly)
(snarling)
What the hell?
OFFICER 2: Hold your fire!
OFFICER 3: Flares!
OFFICER 4: He's there!
He's there!
Reload!
Anybody see him?
(Officers grunting)
(growls)
OFFICER 5: Does anyone
have eyes on him?
(Officer 5 screaming)
(over radio) Switching to
thermal. Seeking target.
- (Venom growls)
- (yelling)
(all grunting)
OFFICER 6: I don't have
eyes on him.
(heavy breathing)
OFFICER 7: Where is it?
(Venom growling)
Flash grenade!
(grenade explodes)
- (Venom roars)
- Throw them!
Flash grenade!
(snarling)
(snarls)
(screams)
SWAT LEADER:
He's in the rafters!
Above!
(growls)
There he is!
Move, move, move!
(Officers grunting)
(roars)
(heavy gunfire)
(Officer grunting)
- (gun clicking)
- (Venom snarls)
(snarling)
EDDIE: No! We do not
eat policemen!
- (screams)
- (SWAT leader whimpering)
- (Venom snorts)
- (SWAT leader grunts)
(stammers)
- (snarls)
- Annie! Annie, wait!
- Wait, please.
- Oh, what the hell is that?
That's not me.
I've been infected.
- Eddie, what's happening?
- He's inside me.
- "He"?
- Yes.
- I know it sounds crazy, but...
- You're sick.
- Eddie, you're really sick.
- No, I am scared!
(panting)
- And I need help.
- Hospital.
Right now.
I can't go with you.
It's not safe.
Get in the car, Eddie.
- In the back.
- VENOM: I like her. Get in.
I'm out of control.
ANNE: Dan just needs to do
another MRI.
- VENOM: No MRI.
- No. No. No MRI.
What? Why?
VENOM: Sound at 4,000
to 6,000 hertz is lethal.
(stammers)
Sound frequency in the MRI
is really harmful for him.
What, so, sound
is like his kryptonite?
- Not all sounds.
- VENOM: And fire.
Fire. And fire.
He's talking to you?
Always.
- Are you in pain?
- No.
No, I don't feel anything,
actually, apart from...
I'm hungry all the time.
VENOM: And you feel sad, do you
not, Eddie, when you are with her?
Get out of my head, man.
VENOM: You never apologized.
You might not live
to get another chance.
Annie.
(stammers) I just want to say
that whatever happens,
that I am truly sorry for whatever...
And everything I have ever done to you.
I am truly, truly sorry.
And that I love you.
Oh, Eddie...
Now's really not the time. Let's
just keep you alive, okay?
VENOM: Aw, that's nice.
(breath trembles)
You know, I'm really wet and
cold. Can I, uh, wear this?
ANNE: Yeah, yeah, you can wear
whatever you want.
Thank you.
CARLTON: Hello?
What are you doing here?
Are you lost?
(distorted) I'm not lost.
(chokes, screams)
(door opens)
DAN: Thanks for coming in.
- Eddie, I'm sorry.
- EDDIE: What?
Eddie, I got your labs back, and
your heart has atrophied severely.
VENOM: Do not listen to him.
I can fix it.
I don't want you to fix it.
VENOM: I can heal you.
(Eddie stammers)
Can you fix it?
No. I've never seen
anything like this before.
- This parasite, whatever this is...
- VENOM: "Parasite"?
It's eating you
from the inside.
(whispers) Not a parasite.
He's not.
- You're using him up.
- VENOM: No. She is wrong.
- We need to get you to the ICU.
- Wait. Shh!
- I, Eddie, am I dying?
- VENOM: No!
You're killing him.
VENOM: They do not know
what they are talking about.
DAN: Listen,
we don't have a lot of time...
- Oh, God!
- VENOM: We have to get out of here.
(Dan choking)
- ANNE: Stop!
- Oh, God, he's killing you.
I'm killing you.
I'm so sorry.
(strained grunting)
- EDDIE: No! Don't do that!
- (electronic feedback squealing)
(screaming)
(yelling)
(distorted screaming)
Are you all right? Eddie, I'm sorry.
I had to get him out of you.
DAN: What is that?
(Eddie groans)
(glass thuds)
You were killing me?
What happened to "we," man?
What happened to "we"?
Yeah, look at you now, huh?
Now you're dying, too.
We're done.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Anywhere other than here.
ANNE: You don't think we have
a little problem on our hands?
Wait, you're not gonna
leave me here with this thing.
You want to tell me
what the hell's going on?
I do. And you're right.
We do need to talk about it,
but I don't know
much more than you do.
I guess he had
no one else to turn to.
He's a very complicated man.
But, Dan, I promise,
there's nothing going on
between me and Eddie.
I'm not talking
about you and Eddie, Anne.
- Oh.
- I'm talking about that.
Dan.
(whispers) Where is it?
(muffled clanking)
- (whimpering and yapping)
- (clanking continues)
- (snarling)
- (whines and yaps)
(yelps)
(panting)
(electronic whirring)
- (crackling)
- (stifled gasp)
TREECE: Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
(indistinct chatter)
(deep growling)
(footsteps approaching)
You can kill me,
'cause I'm dying anyway.
I'm not just gonna kill you.
That wouldn't be any fun.
No, no, no. I'm gonna rip your
tongue out of your face.
- (grunts, groans)
- Whoo!
(grunts)
Stop. You're bleeding
all over my lab. Go. Go!
(Treece grunts)
(door opens, closes)
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
And you know what? Even if I
did, I wouldn't tell you anyway.
I don't trust you,
and you're insane.
- That hurts.
- Sorry.
Long journal entry
about that tonight.
You're being dumb, Brock.
I'm not insane.
What's insane is the way
humans choose to live today.
Think about it.
All we do is take, take, take.
It can't go on.
We've brought the planet
to the brink of extinction.
We're parasites.
You're a good example.
Think about it.
All you do is take.
You took my Symbiote. You
take potshots at a great man
- trying to get something done.
- Who?
(sighs)
Didn't you take from the
person you loved the most,
who trusted you the most?
That's insane.
What I've initiated is a whole
new world, a new species.
Man and Symbiote combined.
Let me tell you something, buddy.
All right? Just man-to-man.
Because I have spent a significant
amount of time, all right,
with one of these creatures
up my ass.
It's not a lot of fun.
And then I find out,
all along,
that they're killing you.
This is the last time
I'm asking you.
- Where is my Symbiote?
- I have no idea.
- Where is he?
- Oh, my God!
Where's Venom?
That is the ugliest-looking
thing I have ever seen.
(roars)
You know, Brock,
I have no use for you.
Treece! Come and clean up
your mess.
Whoa, he has one
up his ass, too.
(breath trembling)
(panting)
Your friends, the others, I apologize.
I tried to keep them alive.
There are more of us.
Millions more.
They will follow
wherever I lead.
Where we lead.
Yes, "we."
But first,
we must retrieve them.
I can take care of that.
Yeah, what you gonna do,
you gonna walk me to death?
Shut up.
(Eddie sighs)
Not so tough
without your friend.
(cocks pistol)
Did your mama not love you?
(grunting)
EDDIE: God damn it!
(grunts)
(inhales sharply) I guess it
pays to be a specialist, huh?
You know, it doesn't matter
if you kill me anyway,
because there's something
way bigger afoot
in this world than you and me.
Much bigger than me.
And it's much,
much bigger than you.
Karma's a bitch.
I don't believe in karma.
- (crunching)
- Oh! Ooh!
(grunting)
Hi, Eddie.
Whoa. Whoa...
Oh... (grunting)
EDDIE: Mmm...
Mmm!
(Eddie moaning)
(Anne grunts)
(gasps softly)
Oh, no.
I just bit
that guy's head off.
I know, I know. I've been there, too.
It's not fun.
- VENOM: The one with Drake is Riot.
- Who's Riot?
Riot is what you would call
a team leader.
He has an arsenal of weapons.
- Drake's got his own Symbiote.
- VENOM: He is unstoppable.
- Oh, great.
- VENOM: We have got to go!
Go where? Where we going?
- Well, I'm coming with you.
- VENOM: No!
It's going to get ugly.
- Well, she can fight ugly. Trust me.
- Yeah, I can fight ugly.
Not today.
Oh, that's bullshit!
This is not a simulation.
Well, the flight team
aren't prepped yet.
I'll be piloting
the spacecraft.
- You?
- Yes, me.
How long?
We're loading the probe
and running diagnostics.
But even fully automated, you
can't pilot that craft all alone.
I'm not alone.
(grunts) God damn it! What the hell
happened there? We just left Annie.
VENOM: It is not safe for her.
If we do not stop Riot,
he will come back here
with millions more of my kind.
Millions? What, you were
gonna take the rocket,
and you were gonna come back
here with an invasion force?
Then what were you gonna do,
you were gonna go feed
- on a whole planet?
- VENOM: Yes!
But it is
different now, Eddie.
- I have decided to stay.
- Wow!
VENOM: On my planet, I am
kind of a loser, like you.
- But here, we could be more.
- Excuse me?
VENOM: And I'm getting to
like it here.
Oh, you like us now,
do you, huh?
However, there will be nothing left to
like if we do not stop that rocket.
Oh, I see. Right. When it comes
to being completely annihilated,
- then it's back to "we."
- VENOM: It is "we."
Like it or not, it is
going to take both of us.
EDDIE: Hey, come on, man.
Cut the bullshit.
What really made you
change your mind?
You. You did, Eddie.
Scrub diagnostics.
- Sir?
- Did you hear me? Initiate the launch.
(keys clacking)
AUTOMATED VOICE: T-minus
five minutes to launch.
Auto sequence has been
initiated.
(gasps)
Oh, shit.
- (yells)
- (people screaming)
(snarls)
AUTOMATED VOICE: T-minus
four minutes, 30 seconds.
(roars)
EDDIE: Oh, Jesus!
You can take this guy, right?
He has got shit
you have never seen.
EDDIE: What does that mean?
What are our chances?
Hmm. Pretty much zero.
EDDIE: Oh, fuck it. Well,
let's go save the planet.
(people screaming)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
T-minus four minutes.
Initiate orbiter
aerosurface profile.
Venom. Get in the rocket.
No. We won't let you destroy
this world.
Then die.
(Riot snarls)
(gasps)
- EDDIE: Holy shit!
- Told you. (grunts)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
T-minus three minutes.
(Riot grunting)
You have a strong host.
(growls)
But not strong enough.
(Venom grunting)
(growling)
(grunting)
(Riot choking)
(Venom groans)
(snarls)
(yells, grunts)
(grunting)
- (snarls)
- (metallic ringing)
- (Riot grunts)
- (growls)
AUTOMATED VOICE: T-minus
two minutes, 30 seconds.
(siren wailing distantly)
Eddie.
(yelling in pain)
Drake, stop!
(growls)
(Eddie grunts)
(yells)
(both grunting and growling)
(both snarling)
(both growling)
(yelling)
- (rustling)
- (growls)
(growls)
(roars)
- (high-pitched ringing)
- (strained grunting)
(feedback ringing)
Told you I could fight ugly.
(high-pitched ringing
continues)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
T-minus one minute.
(Eddie groans)
(both grunting)
(faint rustling)
You're too late.
This is the next stage...
- (water splashes)
- You talk too much.
(stifled gasp)
(snarls)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
T-minus 30 seconds.
You are nothing.
(faint rustling)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Ten seconds.
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
- Two...
- (roars)
- One...
- (whooshing)
Liftoff.
(roars)
Traitor!
Have a nice life.
(metallic squealing)
(muffled screaming)
- (air whistling)
- (flame whooshing)
(roars)
VENOM: Goodbye, Eddie.
EDDIE: Venom, no!
(gasping)
EDDIE: Thanks for sticking by me, Annie.
Thanks for saving me.
ANNE: So, how you feeling
after all that?
I feel great. Awesome.
Wow. (chuckles)
Yeah, I'm thinking of suing, though.
You want to prosecute?
Hmm. You're in luck. I've
decided to work pro bono.
I'm joining
the public defenders' office.
You're a good person, Annie.
What about you?
What are you gonna do?
Uh, the network asked me
to bring the show back,
and they want to start
with a piece on Drake.
Oh, wow, really?
So, what did you say?
Uh, I'm not into it. I want to
concentrate on the written word.
I scored the interview
of a lifetime.
- Oh, yeah? Who?
- You're gonna have to read it.
Oh! Like everyone else.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry about Venom.
Hey, um...
Do you want to talk
about that kiss?
Oh, that? You call that a kiss...
No, that was...
Uh, that was your
buddy's idea.
Oh, right. Well,
that is good to know.
- It did feel kind of great, though.
- What?
I mean, the...
- The power?
- Yeah. When it's, you know...
- Inside you?
- You know what I mean.
Okay.
- Hey, Eddie?
- Mmm-hmm?
We're not gonna
tell Dan about this. Okay?
VENOM: Look at her. She has no
idea we are going to get her back.
No, I don't think so.
- Sorry, what was that?
- We're not gonna tell Dan.
Eddie, is there something
you want to tell me?
- Nope.
- VENOM: You belong with us, Annie.
Eddie, are you sure?
(chuckles nervously)
Good Lord, look at that.
Look at the time.
(stammers) I have to go.
- Hey, it's nice seeing you.
- Yeah.
You take care, all right?
- Yeah, you take care of yourself.
- Bye.
Hey. Don't give up on her.
Either of you.
We won't.
- VENOM: Who is that guy?
- Okay.
VENOM: Wait.
This thing looks delicious.
I have absolutely no problem
with you sticking around,
but if you do, we're gonna have to
have some ground rules, all right?
You cannot just go around eating
anybody that you want to.
- VENOM: I cannot?
- No, you cannot.
All right, we need to...
We need to reiterate this.
There are good people
in this world, a lot of them.
And then there are bad people.
You have to tell
the difference.
The deal is, you will only
ever be allowed to touch,
harm, hurt, possibly,
very possibly,
eat very, very bad people,
but never, ever,
ever good people. All right?
- VENOM: Fine.
- Good.
VENOM: But how does one
tell the difference?
Well, it's super simple.
I mean, you just have to... You
can intuit it, you can sense it.
Sometimes you can
even feel it.
VENOM: Whatever you say.
But can we get something to
eat now?
Otherwise, your liver, it's starting
to look really, really good and juicy.
Yeah. Definitely.
I know a place down here.
- (shop bell jingling)
- Hey, Mrs. C.
How you doing, Eddie?
Ain't nothing changed
but the weather. You know.
No.
So, what culinary delights will
tickle the pickle tonight?
VENOM: Tater tots
and chocolate.
Right. Okay, no problem.
(shop bell jingles)
MAN: The payment's due, Chen.
MRS. CHEN: Please.
I can't keep doing this.
Now.
- VENOM: Bad guy, right?
- Yep.
(feet stomping)
You come in here again...
In fact, you go anywhere in this
city, preying on innocent people,
and we will find you
and eat both your arms
- and then both of your legs.
- No, no.
And then we will eat your face right
off your head. Do you understand?
- Please...
- Yes.
So, you will be this armless,
legless, faceless thing, won't you,
rolling down the street,
like a turd in the wind?
- Do you feel me?
- What the hell are you?
We are Venom.
- On second thought...
- Please.
(crunches)
Eddie? What was that?
Oh... (scoffs)
I have a parasite. Yeah.
Night, Mrs. Chen.
- VENOM: "Parasite"?
- Yeah.
It's a term of endearment,
that's all.
- VENOM: Apologize!
- EDDIE: No.
- EDDIE: All right, fine.
I'm sorry. So, what do you
want to do now?
VENOM: The way I see it,
we can do whatever we want.
♫  Venom  ♫
♫  Adrenaline momentum, Venom  ♫
♫  Not knowin' when I'm
ever gonna slow up and I'm  ♫
♫  Ready to snap
any moment I'm  ♫
♫  Thinkin' it's time to go
get 'em  ♫
♫  They ain't gonna know what
hit 'em  ♫
♫  Wh-Wh-When they get bit
with the Venom  ♫
♫  I got that adrenaline
momentum  ♫
♫  Venom, not knowin' when I'm
ever gonna slow up and I'm  ♫
♫  Ready to snap
any moment I'm  ♫
♫  Thinkin' it's time
to go get 'em  ♫
♫  They ain't gonna know what
hit 'em  ♫
♫  Wh-Wh-When they get bit
with the  ♫
♫  I said knock-knock,
let the devil in  ♫
♫  Alien, E-E-Elliott,
phone home  ♫
♫  Ain't no telling
when this chokehold  ♫
♫  On this game will end,
I'm loco  ♫
♫  Became a Symbiote, so my
fangs are in your throat, oh  ♫
♫  You're snake-bitten with my  ♫
♫  Venom  ♫
♫  With the ballpoint pen,
I'm gun cock, bump stock  ♫
♫  Double-aught buckshot,
tied up to a garrote  ♫
♫  Tie a couple knots, fired up
and caught fire, juggernaut  ♫
♫  Punk rock... goin' down like
Yung Joc  ♫
♫  'Cause the doc put me on
like sunblock  ♫
♫  Why the... not?
You only get one shot  ♫
♫  Ate... till I can't taste it  ♫
♫  Chased it with straight
liquor, then paint thinner  ♫
♫  Then drank till I faint
and awake with a headache  ♫
♫  And I take anything in
rectangular shape  ♫
♫  Then I wait to face the
demons I'm bonded to  ♫
♫  'Cause they're chasin' me,
but I'm part of you  ♫
♫  So escapin' me is impossible  ♫
♫  I latch onto you like a  ♫
♫  Parasite, and I probably
ruined your parents' life  ♫
♫  And your childhood, too,
'cause if I'm the music  ♫
♫  That y'all grew up on,
I'm responsible  ♫
♫  For you, the nasty fools
I'm the supervillain  ♫
♫  Dad and Mom was losin'
their marbles to  ♫
♫  You marvel that?
Eddie Brock is you  ♫
♫  And I'm the suit,
so call me Venom  ♫
♫  I got that adrenaline
momentum  ♫
♫  Venom, not knowin' when I'm
ever gonna slow up and I'm  ♫
♫  Ready to snap
any moment I'm  ♫
♫  Thinkin' it's time to go
get 'em  ♫
♫  They ain't gonna know what
hit 'em  ♫
♫  Wh-Wh-When they get bit
with the  ♫
♫  Venom  ♫
♫  I got that adrenaline
momentum  ♫
♫  Venom, not knowin' when I'm
ever gonna slow up and I'm  ♫
♫  Ready to snap
any moment I'm  ♫
♫  Thinkin' it's time to go
get 'em  ♫
♫  They ain't gonna know what
hit 'em  ♫
♫  Wh-Wh-When they get bit
with the  ♫
♫  Venom  ♫
♫  I got that adrenaline
momentum  ♫
♫  Venom, not knowin' when I'm
ever gonna slow up and I'm  ♫
♫  Ready to snap
any moment I'm  ♫
♫  Thinkin' it's time to go
get 'em  ♫
♫  They ain't gonna know what
hit 'em  ♫
♫  Wh-Wh-When they get bit
with the  ♫
EDDIE: I need you
to stay quiet.
This is a "me" thing.
It is not a "we" thing.
- You got that?
- VENOM: Fine, but make it quick.
GUARD: Open on five.
- (gate buzzing, clanging)
- Go. Opening up.
(indistinct radio chatter)
You ask me, they're dumb
to let him call the shots.
Second he asked
for you to interview him,
I'd have shut that
shit down.
Oh, yeah, you know the FBI.
They're just taking advantage
of the one and only time
he'll ever speak to anyone.
They're hoping that I might help them
identify some additional bodies.
FBI don't work up close
and personal with him.
The FBI will have to identify you,
if you don't follow the rules.
(door clangs)
Hey, Red!
I got a visitor for you.
(unlocks gate)
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hey.
Do you mind if we forego the whole
creepy serial killer thing here?
Sure, it's good with me.
I mean, I can turn it on
if you want.
I can talk about the Dadaist
patterns of arterial spray.
I bet you can.
Tough to see you
in this light, Eddie.
Come on over.
All right.
I'm here.
When I get out of here,
and I will,
(inhales sharply)
there's gonna be carnage.
(hardcore hip-hop playing)
- (running footsteps)
- (panting)
(whooshing)
(panting)
(tires squealing)
(engine roaring)
- (tires squeal)
- (crashing)
(bell tolling)
(wind whistling)
(sighs) I'm sorry, Mr. Parker.
I want to do what you asked.
I really do.
But... I'm sorry.
(faint thud)
(footsteps)
I can't do this without you.
(gasps)
- Hey, kid...
- (electrical crackling)
(yells)
Whoa.
What was... Whoa!
(groans, gasps)
What?
Huh?
No.
Who are you?
MAN: What are you
doing over there?
Freeze! PDNY.
Kid, freeze!
(yells, grunts)
You're kidding me right now?
OFFICER: Hey, kid.
Drop the body.
(screams)
Ow!
Somebody stop that train!
- (horn honks)
- (siren wailing)
(grunting)
Aah!
(yells)
(man yelling)
(grunts)
Sorry.
(man screaming)
- (tires screech)
- (screaming)
- (thudding)
- (horns honking)
OFFICER: (on radio) ...looks like
a child dressed like Spider-Man,
dragging a homeless corpse
- behind a train.
- (siren wails)
- MAN: Who are you?
- BOY: Who are you?
MAN: Why are you
trying to kill me?
BOY: I'm not.
I'm trying to save you.
(crashes)
(glass squeaking)
- (both yell)
- (dog barking)
Hey, maybe you guys
can go around?
All right.
Thanks, New York.