Life Foundation Control, this is LF1. The specimens are secured, and we're heading home.
LF1 paré pour rentrée atmosphérique. Les spécimens sont sécurisés.
Roger, LF1. You are a go for reentry.
Bien reçu, LF1. Autorisation pour rentrée.
Copy that. Initiating reentry sequence.
Procédure de rentrée atmosphérique amorcée.
Point-four by 103-point... Oh, shit.
On affiche de .4 par 103...
Merde.
Seal it off. Seal it off!
Ferme le caisson !
LF1, Mission Control. You're breaking up. Please repeat.
Ici, centre de contrôle. Nous perdons le contact.
Mayday, Mayday, LF1!
Ici, LF1, S.O.S. !
- Mayday! - LF1, Mission Control. Please repeat.
LF1, veuillez répéter.
LF1, Mission Control. Please repeat.
DANS L'EST DE LA MALAISIE
I don't want to have to wait for full clean-up just to get - a status report. - We're collecting this data
Je n'ai pas le temps d'attendre un rapport.
- as quickly as possible. - That's not good enough.
On récupère les données au plus vite.
Okay, maybe you can tell me what happened.
C'est trop lent. Dites-moi ce qui s'est passé.
There was some kind of breach. One of the astronauts - sent a distress call. - What about the crew?
Il y a eu une avarie. On a reçu un appel de détresse.
- We're still investigating. - Where did it go down?
- Et l'équipage ? - On continue d'enquêter.
It's 20 kilometers west of Sibu.
- Où est-il tombé ? - À 20 km à l'ouest de Sibu.
Did we at least retrieve all of the samples?
On a récupéré tous les échantillons ?
No. We have three of them.
Non, on en a trois.
One of the organisms got out of containment, and it's missing. We don't know which one.
Un des organismes est sorti de son confinement et a disparu.
On ignore lequel.
What is she saying?
Qu'est-ce qu'elle dit ?
One of the astronauts is still alive.
Un des astronautes est vivant.
That's Jameson.
C'est Jameson.
- Morning, sunshine. - What? I'm awake.
- Bonjour, beauté. - Je suis réveillé.
Missed me.
Raté !
- I'm awake. - Here you go.
Je suis réveillé.
- You can have it back. - Thank...
Tu peux le reprendre.
Oh, wow, you're wearing a suit. Yes!
Super, t'as mis un tailleur !
- I love it when you wear the suit. - Thank you.
J'adore quand t'es en tailleur.
I have depositions today in the Life Foundation case. Hey, let me know how your meeting goes.
Je témoigne aujourd'hui dans l'affaire Life Foundation.
My meeting?
Tiens-moi au courant de ta réunion.
Oh, shit. Yeah.
Ma réunion ?
My meeting.
Merde, c'est vrai. Ma réunion.
- Coffee. - Oh. Mmm!
Café.
- You are perfect. - Thank you. Hey, you know what... You know what night
Tu es parfaite.
- it is tonight, right? - Date night.
Tu sais quel soir c'est, aujourd'hui ?
Mmm-hmm. So, I will pick you up around, uh, 6:00.
Notre soir de sortie.
Je passerai te prendre à 18 h.
And please do not forget your helmet. Oh, I'm glad that you like it,
Et surtout n'oublie pas ton casque.
'cause I plan on wearing it at our wedding. That's hot.
Ravie qu'il te plaise, je le porterai à notre mariage.
Feed the cat.
Trop sexy.
Donne à manger au chat.
I will. I love you! Love you, too. Feed the cat.
- Je m'en occupe. Je t'aime ! - Moi aussi.
Donne à manger au chat.
Eddie Brock with boots on the ground today in the Mission District, chasing a lead into some...
Eddie Brock sur le terrain à Mission District...
Everybody knows how our Silicon Valley overlords at Google and Facebook... Last time, I was poking around
On sait que les patrons de la Silicon Valley
asking uncomfortable questions...
chez Google, Facebook et Life Foundation s'enrichissent.
Homelessness is only increasing into the thousands... Eddie Brock here reporting today from downtown Oakland,
Le nombre de sans-abris explose à San Francisco.
where massive demonstrations have taken over the streets.
Je suis aujourd'hui au cœur d'Oakland,
I've been chasing this real-estate bribery story
où de nombreux manifestants occupent les rues.
for a few weeks now.
Je continue mon enquête sur la corruption immobilière.
This is gonna piss you off. ...all being strong-armed...
Ça va vous faire péter les plombs.
Medical examiner has yet to determine cause of death, due to the condition of the body,
Le médecin légiste va établir les causes des décès
vu l'état des corps.
but you don't wind up at the bottom of a landfill due to natural causes, so it seems that the city
On ne finit pas à la décharge quand on meurt de cause naturelle.
doesn't care about these people any more than the killer does. I'm Eddie Brock, and this is The Brock Report.
La ville ne se soucie pas plus de ces gens que le meurtrier.
Hey, Richard!
Eddie Brock. C'était le Brock Report.
Richard !
- Lookin' good! - Eddie, you can't park there, bro.
T'as l'air en forme !
Come on, man. There's no such thing as can't.
Impossible de se garer là.
How'd she do?
Rien n'est impossible.
Berkeley. Brown. MIT.
- Comment elle va ? - Berkeley, Brown, MIT.
- She's got a scholarship, bro. - What'd I tell you?
Elle a une bourse.
You told me what?
- Qu'est-ce que je t'ai dit ? - Quoi ?
- No such thing as can't. - Eddie.
Rien n'est impossible.
The bike.
La moto.
MIT! Whoo!
MIT !
You know what I love about this view?
Tu sais pourquoi j'aime cette vue ?
- It never gets old. - Yeah, well, uh...
On ne s'en lasse jamais.
Height's not really my thing.
L'altitude, c'est pas vraiment mon truc.
But, uh... What's the deal? - I got you the big one, exclusive. - Yeah? Who?
C'est quoi, l'affaire ?
Carlton Drake.
- Une interview exclusive. - De qui ?
- Carlton Drake? - The man's a visionary. He wants to talk about his rockets,
L'homme est un visionnaire. Il veut parler de ses fusées.
assure everyone they're safe, that the crash was an anomaly.
Garantir que le crash était une anomalie.
Uh...
He's... He's seriously off. I'm gonna level with you.
Il est complètement à la masse.
Je vais être franc.
Carlton Drake could buy us with his pocket cash, turn this building into his own garage if he so wished.
Il pourrait nous acheter avec son argent de poche
Now, you're just gonna ask him about his space program,
et faire de cet immeuble son garage, s'il le voulait.
Tu vas l'interroger sur son programme spatial,
you're gonna thank him, and you're gonna bid him a nice day.
le remercier et le saluer.
He's a crook.
C'est un escroc.
Eddie, when you had nowhere to go, we gave you a home.
Quand tu étais à la rue, on t'a accueilli.
Now, you know we love the Eddie Brock show.
On adore le Eddie Brock Show.
There isn't a better investigative reporter working today, but no one is above the network.
Tu es le meilleur journaliste d'investigation du moment,
mais la chaîne passe d'abord.
So do me a favor, Eddie, don't start your shit again.
Fais-moi plaisir, épargne-nous tes conneries.
All right, all right. - For me. - All right. I'll do it.
C'est bon.
- Pour moi. - C'est bon, je le fais.
I don't know why he gave me this assignment, Annie. It's not... It's not what I do.
J'ignore pourquoi il m'a confié ce boulot, c'est pas mon truc.
Well, my mother always told me that anything in life worth having would take sacrifice...
Ma mère disait toujours que tout ce qui compte dans la vie
exige des sacrifices,
- Mmm-hmm. - Patience... - Mmm. - And be a lot of work.
de la patience...
- Oh. - That's you...
et beaucoup de travail.
- That's not. - ...that I'm talking about.
- Je parle de toi. - Faux.
- Nah. - Yeah. Well, you're lucky to have me. To be fair, I'm quite a catch. That's what my mom told me.
Tu as de la chance de m'avoir. Je suis un parti en or.
C'est ce que me disait ma mère.
Are you gonna behave yourself tomorrow? No. No, I'm gonna do my job. That's what I'm gonna do.
Tu vas bien te tenir, demain ?
Je vais faire mon boulot.
I can't, you know, not do my job. The guy you work for is a complete...
Je peux pas faire autrement. Le type pour qui tu bosses est...
I don't work for Drake. I work for my firm, and my firm works for him.
Je bosse pas pour Drake, c'est mon cabinet qui bosse pour lui.
And I'm sure that they defend many people that you don't deem worthy, but we don't want a repeat.
Je sais qu'ils défendent des gens que tu n'estimes pas,
- A repeat? - Of the Daily Globe incident.
mais on ne veut pas que ça se répète.
- Quoi ? - L'incident du Daily Globe.
Ow! Really?
Vraiment ?
- Incident? That's not an incident. - Mmm-hmm.
C'était pas un incident.
- Baby, you were run out of New York. - I was not. I did not. I don't want you run out of San Francisco.
On t'a chassé de New York, évite ça à San Francisco.
No, I still have currency in New York.
J'ai toujours la cote à New York.
I was going places.
J'avançais.
I wasn't running. I was going places.
Je fuyais pas, j'avançais.
In fact, I moved to San Francisco for you.
J'ai emménagé à San Francisco pour toi.
- Me? - You are my home.
Tu es mon refuge.
You're not so bad yourself, champ.
T'es pas mal non plus, champion.
- Less talking, more kissing. - All right.
Tais-toi et embrasse-moi.
Let's just get the check.
On demande la note.
I'm gonna get a drink.
J'ai soif.
Lee Taglin Note sur la Life Foundation
Confidentiel
Veuillez trouver en pièce jointe la note à votre attention.
Shh.
Décès imputable à une faute
Volontaires
Section des décès Déclaration de décès non obligatoire
Very soon, another Life Foundation rocket will be sent on an exploratory mission.
Une autre fusée de la Life Foundation
va bientôt partir en mission exploratoire.
And that's how, one day, we might all live in space.
Il se pourrait alors qu'un jour, on vive dans l'espace.
Cool, huh? And now that I've shown you
Super, n'est-ce pas ?
some of the cool stuff that we do here, I'm hoping I've inspired each and every one of you
Maintenant que je vous ai montré les trucs cool,
to go out there and create things that others
j'espère que je vous ai tous motivés à aller de l'avant
- have only dreamt of. - Mr. Drake?
et à concrétiser les rêves de tous.
- Shh! - It's okay. Don't silence her.
M. Drake ?
C'est bon.
Come here. What's your name?
Ne la faites pas taire.
- Allie. - It's okay, Allie.
- Viens. Comment t'appelles-tu ? - Allie.
You know, sometimes that's what people do.
Tu sais, parfois les gens font ça.
They try and silence those of us who ask questions. But you know what? In the end,
Ils font taire ceux qui posent des questions.
Mais à l'arrivée...
we're the ones who change the world.
nous changerons le monde.
Take good care of that, Allie.
Prends-en bien soin, Allie.
Guys, this is Dr. Skirth. - Say hi. - Hi.
Voici le docteur Skirth. Dites bonjour.
Hello, kids. Um, sorry to interrupt,
Bonjour, les enfants.
but it's time to get changed for your interview.
Désolée,
vous devez vous changer pour votre interview.
Yeah. Uh, kids, sorry to leave you. Allie, you're in charge. High five up top.
Désolé, les enfants. Allie, c'est toi qui es aux manettes.
Dr. Skirth will answer Allie's question, and any others.
Le Dr Skirth répondra à vos questions.
- See you next time, guys. Bye! - Bye! What do you say, Mr. Drake,
- À bientôt ! - Au revoir.
we just start at the beginning?
Je propose, M. Drake, qu'on commence par le début.
- Born to British parents. - Mmm-hmm.
Né de parents britanniques.
And then at 19, you discovered a gene therapy that literally doubles the life expectancy
À 19 ans, vous découvrez une thérapie génique
- of pancreatic cancer patients. - Well, actually,
doublant l'espérance de vie des malades du cancer du...
it tripled their life expectancy.
En fait, elle a triplé leur espérance de vie.
But it's okay.
Mais c'est bon.
Okay, um, 24. That's still extremely young. All right, you create
24 ans. C'est encore très jeune, non ?
- the Life Foundation! - It didn't happen overnight.
Vous créez la Life Foundation.
- And then... - Rockets. You then decide, like any normal human being,
- Ça a pris du temps. - Puis, les fusées.
that you're gonna go and explore space. You know what it is? I have always believed...
Vous décidez, comme tout être normal, d'aller explorer l'espace.
- Uh-huh. - ...that space exploration
Vous savez quoi ? J'ai toujours pensé
is crucial in our quest to cure
que l'exploration de l'espace
everything that ails us here on Earth.
est cruciale pour guérir tous nos maux.
But if you think about everything we've found... - Uh-huh. - ...in the oceans and on land, - isn't it time to look up there? - Mmm-hmm.
Si on pense à tout ce qu'on a trouvé dans les océans et sur terre,
pourquoi pas là-haut ?
To this plethora of untapped resources?
Toutes ces ressources inexploitées...
And you have a plethora of untapped resources, also, from your pharmaceutical companies
Vous en avez aussi dans vos sociétés pharmaceutiques
that you're involved with, you know, to help you realize - that ambition, I suppose. - Of course.
pour vous aider à concrétiser cette ambition.
- Yeah. - Full circle. So, I have to ask, how does that work,
C'est un cercle vertueux.
J'ai une question.
you know, exactly, the Life Foundation thing? How does it... How does it, um...
Comment ça marche, la Life Foundation ?
I don't know, how does it go about,
Comment...
- say, testing pharmaceuticals? - Eddie, we're talking
Comment ça marche, les essais pharmaceutiques ?
- about the rocket here. - No, I'm not. I'm not.
Eddie, on parle de la fusée.
I'm talking about the allegations. - I'm sorry, I don't... - It says that
Non, pas moi. Je parle des allégations.
Désolé, je ne...
your entire empire has been built - on dead bodies. - Eddie.
On dit que votre empire est bâti sur des cadavres.
It's true, right? It says that you recruit
Eddie.
C'est vrai, non ? On dit que vous recrutez
the most vulnerable of us to volunteer for tests... - Hmm. - ...that more often than not
les plus vulnérables pour pratiquer des tests
end up killing people.
qui, la plupart du temps, les tuent.
Yeah, I'm aware of these rumors online. There's a lot of fake news out there these days.
Je connais ces rumeurs, il y a beaucoup d'intox.
Right. What about the legal cases? Sorry?
- Et les procédures judiciaires ? - Pardon ?
Uh, the actual legal cases, like Sarah Chambers,
Les cas de Sarah Chambers,
- Phil Barclay, Rob MacDonald. - That's it. Time to go.
Phil Barclay...
Thank you so much for coming to talk to me, Mr. Brock.
C'est terminé.
And they're just some of the people who walked - through these doors... - Have a nice day.
Il s'agit de personnes qui sont entrées ici
- Cut the camera off, please. - Thank you very much.
et n'en sont jamais ressorties...
- Time is up. Come on. - They're dead. The Dead... - Could you show him out, please? - The Dead Found...
La Fondation de la Mort.
Don't touch me. The Dead Foundation thing. - Get out of here, Brock. - We're not finished.
- On n'a pas fini. - C'est fini pour vous.
Yes, you are, Mr. Brock. Is that a threat?
C'est une menace ?
Have a nice life.
Je vous souhaite bon vent.
I know what you're going to say, but...
Je sais ce que tu vas dire, mais...
This guy, he is all the way bad, Jack. - If you just give... - Who's your source?
ce type est un vrai pourri, Jack. Si tu...
- Excuse me? - Who's your source, Eddie?
- Qui est ta source ? - Pardon ?
Ta source.
I don't have a source, per se. But I have a hunch.
Je n'ai pas une source, mais une intuition.
This isn't the Wild Wild West.
C'est pas Les Mystères de l'Ouest.
We don't go off half-cocked based on a hunch. We do the work.
On ne part pas tête baissée sur une intuition.
On fait notre boulot.
We substantiate our accusations. We provide evidence.
On étaye nos accusations. On fournit des preuves.
You know, for a smart guy, you really are a dumbass.
Pour un type futé, t'es un vrai crétin.
You're fired, Eddie.
Tu es viré, Eddie.
I can't trust you. Have a nice life.
Je ne peux pas avoir confiance.
Je te souhaite bon vent.
- Will just take a second. - Okay.
Hey.
You are pathologically self-absorbed. Annie. Annie, can you talk to me first? Your ego requires constant attention,
Tu es un égocentrique pathologique, tu réclames toute l'attention.
and you're stubborn as hell.
Et tu es têtu comme une mule.
But I was willing to roll with it, Eddie, because I loved you. You "loved" me? What is that supposed to mean?
J'étais prête à faire avec, parce que je t'aimais.
Tu m'aimais ? Comment ça ?
What you did got me fired.
À cause de toi, j'ai été virée.
You used me.
Tu t'es servi de moi.
Annie? Annie.
Oh, my God.
Mon Dieu.
You're beautiful.
Vous êtes magnifiques.
Six mois plus tard
Test 36.
Essai 36 :
Biological interactions between two different organisms.
interactions biologiques entre 2 organismes.
These creatures need to bond with a respiratory host in order to survive for any amount of time
Ils doivent s'associer avec un hôte respiratoire
in an oxygen-rich environment.
pour survivre dans un environnement riche en oxygène.
Well, why are all these hosts showing this hyper-acute rejection?
Pourquoi les hôtes ont-ils un tel taux de rejet ?
That's what we're trying to find out.
C'est ce que nous essayons de découvrir.
The bonding process is starting.
Le processus d'association débute.
ÉQUILIBRAGE
It's equalizing.
Ça s'équilibre.
But why? Why this rabbit?
Pourquoi ?
Pourquoi ce lapin ?
- It's similar to an organ transplant. - Huh.
C'est comme une greffe d'organes.
Where the donor and recipient must be an exact match? - That's correct. - Okay. So wait, think about it.
Où donneur et receveur doivent être compatibles à 100 % ?
C'est exact.
Réfléchissons.
If we do achieve symbiosis, they should be able to survive here,
Si on réussit la symbiose, ils pourraient survivre ici,
but also we would be able to survive there.
mais on pourrait également survivre là-bas.
"We"? - Begin human trials. - Oh, it's way too soon
- "On" ? - Débutez les essais humains.
to even begin to think about something like...
C'est beaucoup trop tôt pour y songer.
Dr. Skirth, you're at the forefront of a scientific breakthrough. I need you to hold your nerve. All right?
Vous êtes à l'avant-garde d'une percée scientifique, soyez forte.
I understand, but it's an ethical question. Think of future generations. Think of your kids. Hey, how are your kids?
- Il s'agit d'éthique. - Pensez au futur, à vos enfants.
Comment vont vos enfants ?
Let's begin human trials. Good work.
Débutons les essais humains. Beau travail.
Hey, Jack.
Jack.
Do you ever feel like your life - is like one monumental screwup? - Nope.
Ça t'arrive de penser que ta vie est un fiasco monumental ?
Here at the Life Foundation,
Non.
- we've always believed... - Isn't that your buddy? ...in finding the lessons in our disappointments.
C'est pas ton pote ?
In the months since our rocket failed, we've learned so much. Do you think we could, like, switch him off?
Depuis l'échec de notre fusée, nous avons beaucoup appris.
Tu penses qu'on peut le zapper ?
Some people are trying to watch that. Oh, you are, are you? - Yeah? - Aren't you Eddie Brock?
- Y a des gens qui veulent regarder. - Vous regardez ?
Vous êtes Eddie Brock, non ?
I used to be.
Je l'étais.
We take the same view of progress.
Thrilled to announce that the Life Foundation has now begun preparations on its next launch.
Nous sommes ravis d'annoncer que Life Foundation se prépare
All right, Jack, this is for you.
au prochain lancement.
I do not want you to spend it all at once. I'm going to go home and chase myself around the room,
Tiens, garde la monnaie. Dépense pas tout d'un coup.
playing hard to get.
Je rentre m'auto-draguer, mais je couche pas le premier soir.
- Hey, Maria. - Eddie.
- Salut, Maria. - Eddie.
- How's it going? - Righteous, Eddie.
- Comment ça va ? - Gentiment.
Oh! Yeah, we're empty.
C'est vide.
Cost you $5.
Ça fera 5 $.
$5 for a paper that's free?
5 $ pour un journal gratuit ?
I walked all the way over to the vending machine, got the papers out and brought 'em back over here,
J'ai marché jusqu'au distributeur, pris les journaux
so you can have 'em personally delivered to you.
et je les ai ramenés ici pour te les donner en personne.
You did that for me? - Yes, I did. - Oh.
- T'as fait ça pour moi ? - Oui.
- Five bucks. - That's pretty steep.
- 5 $. - C'est plutôt salé.
Tell you what, you give me a dollar for a song, I'll throw in the paper.
Tu me files 1 $ pour que je chante et je t'offre le journal.
I'll tell you what, I will give you 20 bucks, but not to sing, all right?
Je vais te donner 20 $, mais tu chantes pas, d'accord ?
Deal. - Thank you. - You're welcome.
- Marché conclu. - Merci.
No. You're welcome.
- De rien. - Non, de rien.
Hey, Mrs. Chen. - How you doing, Eddie? - Ah, aches and pains,
- Bonsoir, Mme Chen. - Comment ça va, Eddie ?
you know, aches and pains. You look like shit.
- Je suis plein de courbatures. - Vous avez une sale gueule.
Excuse me?
Pardon ?
You look like shit.
Vous avez une sale gueule.
And you look as beautiful as ever. - Jesus. - Mind is body, Eddie.
Et vous êtes plus ravissante que jamais.
Bon sang.
Have you been meditating like I showed you?
L'esprit, c'est le corps. Vous méditez ?
- No, I have not. And it does not work. - It doesn't work,
Non, ça marche pas.
- because you don't give it a chance. - No, it doesn't work,
Parce que vous n'essayez pas.
because I bought a DVD off your cousin, and it was in Mandarin.
J'ai acheté un DVD à votre cousin et c'était en mandarin.
Yeah, I don't understand that, either.
Ça non plus, je comprends pas.
See, that right there, I don't understand what you just said. That is the problem.
Ça, c'est du chinois ! C'est bien le problème.
Bottle of whiskey, and don't forget my change.
Une bouteille de whisky.
Please.
Et n'oublie pas ma monnaie.
Je vous en prie...
Let's go. Before the price goes up for my protection.
Magne ou j'augmente le tarif pour ta protection.
The full payment is due. Now.
Faut régler la totalité.
Tout de suite !
Make sure you have my money ready, Chen. I don't like to wait.
Pense à préparer mon fric. J'aime pas attendre.
Life hurts, Eddie.
La vie est une souffrance.
It just does.
C'est comme ça.
I gotta go.
Je dois y aller.
- Okay. Love you, babe. - See you, babe.
What a dick.
Connard.
Relance
I'm not even asking to staff there. Why would I do that? I can't use my name. I can use a pseudonym.
Je parle pas d'un temps plein. Je peux pas utiliser mon nom.
Any name. Think... You pick a name.
Je peux prendre un pseudo. Choisissez.
I could be a woman. Have you seen Tootsie?
Je peux être une femme. Vous avez vu Tootsie ?
T'as du boulot ?
Désolé, Eddie, j'ai rien pour toi.
RECHERCHE PLONGEUR
I'll call you back. Okay, I won't. Thank you. Bye.
Je vous rappellerai. Ou pas. Merci.
Realize deeply that the present moment is all you ever have.
Prenez conscience que l'instant présent
est tout ce que vous possédez.
Make the now the primary focus of your life.
Faites de l'instant même le centre de votre vie.
Any action is often better than no action,
Toute action est préférable à l'inaction,
especially if you have been stuck in an unhappy situation for a long time.
surtout si vous traversez une mauvaise passe depuis longtemps.
If it is a mistake, at least you learned something, in which case it's no longer...
Si c'est une erreur, vous aurez appris quelque chose.
Auquel cas, ce n'est plus...
Thank you all for bringing us to this moment.
Merci à tous d'avoir contribué à ce moment.
Our names will be spoken long after we are dust.
On parlera de nous bien après être redevenus poussière.
History starts now. This is day one.
L'Histoire débute maintenant. Nous sommes au premier jour.
This is first contact.
C'est le premier contact.
Let's get to work.
Au travail.
Establishing subject baseline.
Relevé des constantes de référence du sujet.
All vital signs are normal.
Tous les signes vitaux sont normaux.
Put me through.
Mettez-moi en relation.
There's no need to be frightened, Isaac.
Il n'y a aucune raison d'avoir peur, Isaac.
There's no need. Isaac. You know that's a biblical name?
Aucune raison.
Yes, sir.
Isaac. Tu sais que c'est un nom biblique ?
Oui, monsieur.
God said to Abraham, "Give me your son,
Dieu dit à Abraham : "Donne-moi ton fils.
"show me you are willing to sacrifice the one thing
"Montre-moi que tu es prêt à sacrifier
"most precious to you," and Abraham was willing.
"ce que tu as de plus précieux."
Abraham accepta.
You know what's always impressed me about that story? It isn't Abraham's sacrifice. It's Isaac's.
Tu sais ce qui m'impressionne le plus ?
Ce n'est pas le sacrifice d'Abraham, c'est celui d'Isaac.
Now, I don't know what kind of God would ask that of someone,
J'ignore quel genre de dieu demanderait ça,
but it doesn't change anything for me.
mais ça ne change rien.
Isaac is still the hero of this story.
Isaac est toujours le héros de cette histoire.
Look around you. Look at the world.
Regarde autour de toi. Regarde le monde.
What do you see? War, poverty, a planet on the brink of collapse.
Que vois-tu ? La guerre, la pauvreté, une planète qui va imploser.
I would argue that God has abandoned us.
Je dirais que Dieu nous a abandonnés.
He didn't keep his end of the bargain, Isaac,
Il n'a pas tenu parole.
so now it's down to you and me to put this right.
C'est maintenant à toi et moi de rectifier ça.
And this time, Isaac, we can.
Cette fois, Isaac, on peut le faire.
We will.
On va le faire.
This time, I will not abandon us.
Cette fois, je ne nous abandonnerai pas.
Yes.
Open it.
Ouvrez.
What the hell is that? What? No, what...
C'est quoi, ce truc ?
Please let me... No. Oh, please, please, please!
Laissez-moi...
S'il vous plaît !
His vitals are holding steady.
Signes vitaux stables.
- Where the hell did it go? - Incredible.
- Où il est passé, putain ? - Incroyable.
Where did it go?
Où il est passé ?
Where is it?
Où il est ?
Bring in the next volunteer.
Amenez le volontaire suivant.
You know, I used to be a reporter. I was...
J'étais journaliste.
I was pretty successful, as well, you know?
J'avais pas mal de succès, d'ailleurs.
My job, it required you to... You know, to follow people
Pour mon boulot, il fallait...
that did not want to be followed and hide in plain sight.
suivre des gens qui ne voulaient pas être suivis
et me rendre invisible.
I mean...
You have to know how to disappear.
Il faut savoir comment disparaître.
I was pretty good, but, you know, you...
J'étais plutôt doué, mais vous...
Whoever you are, you suck.
qui que vous soyez, vous êtes nulle.
Okay.
- Uh, my name is Dora Skirth. - Mmm. I need your help.
Je m'appelle Dora Skirth. J'ai besoin de votre aide.
- I work at the Life Foundation. - You do?
- Je travaille à la Life Foundation. - Ah oui ?
- Yes. - Wow. Good for you. We're done.
Tant mieux. Salut.
No...
Mr. Brock, please... Please listen to me.
M. Brock, je vous en prie. Écoutez-moi.
Everything that you accused him of, you were right. It's all true.
Toutes vos accusations, vous aviez raison. C'est la vérité.
- I don't care anymore. - Really?
Je m'en fiche.
Because he's got a lab filled with poor people,
Vraiment ? Il a un labo plein de pauvres gens
and they're all signing waivers that they don't understand,
qui signent des décharges sans les comprendre.
and he's using them like guinea pigs, and they are dying.
Il s'en sert comme cobayes, et ils meurent.
They are all dying.
Ils meurent tous.
- You've seen that? - Yes.
Vous avez vu ça ?
Come here.
Venez.
Why would I believe you? Because it's true. I believed in him, and I...
- Pourquoi vous croire ? - Parce que c'est vrai.
I told myself that it was worth it
J'avais foi en lui et je...
because we were curing cancer, but now this is different.
J'y croyais parce qu'on traitait le cancer.
- Something else. - Go to the cops.
Mais maintenant, c'est différent.
I can't do that.
- Prévenez les flics. - Impossible.
I'm afraid of what will happen to my family.
J'ai peur pour ma famille.
He's a very dangerous man, and he's a very powerful man... I know, I know how dangerous he is,
C'est un homme très dangereux.
because the very first time I interviewed him, just once, I lose my job the very next day.
Je le sais bien parce que je l'ai interviewé une seule fois
et j'ai été viré le lendemain.
I lost my career, I lost my relationship,
J'ai perdu ma carrière,
I lost my apartment, I lost everything I ever cared about.
mon couple, mon appartement.
You know why? Carlton Drake ruined me. Finished.
J'ai perdu tout ce qui comptait. Pourquoi ?
Carlton Drake m'a anéanti, détruit !
Now, if you are who you say you are, genuinely, and you have proof,
Si vous êtes vraiment celle que vous dites
then you should be very, very, very afraid.
et que vous avez des preuves,
alors vous devriez avoir très peur.
I am.
C'est le cas.
You need to find yourself another white knight, Ms. Skirth, because I am done.
Trouvez-vous un autre justicier, parce que c'est fini,
I am done with all of this shit.
je joue plus à ces conneries.
What shit? All of this "saving my fellow man" shit.
Quelles conneries ?
All right? Good night.
Sauver mon prochain, ce genre de conneries. Bonne soirée.
Eddie?
Well, hey. Whoa.
Anne, I was just walking by, and, uh...
Je passais par là...
I saw Mr. Belvedere. I felt concerned for his welfare, so...
J'ai vu M. Belvédère.
Eddie...
Je m'inquiétais pour sa santé, alors...
This is Dan.
Voici Dan.
- Dan, this is Eddie. - Yeah.
Dan, je te présente Eddie.
- Hey. - Hey, man.
- Yeah. - Annie's told me a lot about you. - Really? - Yeah.
- Annie m'a beaucoup parlé de toi. - Vraiment ?
I'm a big fan of your work. - Thank you. - Really?
- Je suis fan de ton travail. - Merci.
Sérieux ?
It's pretty cool, all the people that he took down.
C'est plutôt cool, tous ceux qu'il a fait tomber.
Yeah, I was one of them.
Oui, j'en faisais partie.
Well, look, I'll let you guys catch up. - So I'll see you inside? - You're the best.
Je vous laisse bavarder, je t'attends à l'intérieur.
- Really nice meeting you, man. - Uh, you, too.
- Ravi de t'avoir rencontré. - Moi aussi.
He has a key. You know he has a key?
Il a une clé, t'es au courant ?
Yeah. How else would he get in?
Comment il entrerait, sinon ?
Yeah. Well, uh...
So, uh, what you up to?
Qu'est-ce que tu deviens ?
You realize that's light-years away from being any of your business, right?
Tu sais que ça ne te regarde pas une seule seconde ?
Hey, well, just asking, you know.
Je demandais juste.
So, is Dan, uh, a lawyer?
Dan est avocat ?
No, he's a doctor.
Non, médecin.
- Surgeon, actually. - Oh.
Chirurgien, en fait.
How's Mr. Belvedere, anyway? I would say that he misses you,
Comment va M. Belvédère ?
but that would be bullshit, 'cause...
Dire que tu lui manques, ce serait mentir.
- He's a cat. - No, because he never liked you. No, he's a cat, and cats don't like anyone.
- C'est un chat. - Il ne t'a jamais aimé.
You look good, by the way. You doing good?
Ils n'aiment personne. Tu es ravissante. Tu vas bien ?
What are you doing here, Eddie? I'm here 'cause I miss you.
- Que fais-tu ici ? - Tu me manques.
A lot.
Beaucoup.
You know, we were gonna get married. That wasn't so long ago, and now, you know...
On allait se marier.
C'était il y a pas si longtemps et maintenant,
I can't really believe that we're not...
j'ai du mal à croire qu'on n'est pas...
Are we gonna try and find our way back?
On va essayer de recoller les morceaux ?
No, we can't.
Non, on ne peut pas.
You did this, Eddie.
C'est toi qui as fait ça.
Not Carlton Drake, not the network. You.
Pas Carlton Drake. Pas la chaîne. Toi.
Uh, hello. This is Dr. Skirth.
Bonsoir, Dora Skirth.
Yes, Eddie Brock here.
C'est Eddie Brock.
Talk to me.
Je vous écoute.
Are you sure this is gonna work? Just stay down and shut up, please.
- Ça va marcher ? - Restez baissé et fermez-la.
53.5, win-909 RPM.
11,9 °C, vent 909 tr/min.
Whew.
Overpopulation and climate change.
La surpopulation et le changement climatique.
These are two things that Drake cannot control. Yeah, got it, right.
Deux choses que Drake ne peut pas contrôler.
We are literally a generation away from an uninhabitable Earth. - Uh, yeah. - Drake is using his personal rockets
On est littéralement à une génération d'une Terre inhabitable.
Drake utilise ses fusées
to scout real estate.
pour de la prospection immobilière.
You know, it's a really interesting story, but we need to just get to the part where he's killing people.
C'est passionnant, mais venons-en au moment où il tue des gens.
Drake sent a ship on a recon mission.
Drake a envoyé un vaisseau en reconnaissance.
On the way back, they found a comet.
Sur le chemin du retour, ils ont croisé une comète.
A comet?
Une comète.
Onboard computers indicated the presence of life, of millions of organisms. Wait, wait, wait, when you say "millions of organisms,"
Les ordinateurs ont détecté de la vie. Des millions d'organismes.
- what do you mean? - We brought back some specimens.
Comment ça, des millions d'organismes ?
You're talking about aliens? Like, aliens?
- On a ramené des spécimens. - Vous parlez d'extraterrestres ?
E.T. phone home. Aliens, yeah.
"E.T. téléphone maison."
Yes.
But we don't call them that.
On ne les appelle pas comme ça.
- We call them Symbiotes. - Symbiotes?
On les appelle des Symbiotes.
And they cannot survive in our environment without help.
Ils ne peuvent pas survivre ici sans aide.
Drake believes that the union between human and Symbiote
Drake croit que la fusion entre un humain et un Symbiote
is the key to our survival, but not here on Earth.
est la clé de notre survie. Mais pas sur terre.
Drake is trying to put human beings and aliens together?
Drake essaye
de fusionner les êtres humains avec les extraterrestres ?
So they can live in space?
Pour survivre dans l'espace ?
We call them hosts.
On les appelle des hôtes.
That's nuts, isn't it? That's completely insane. Yes. There's no protocol for this thing.
C'est barré, non ? C'est complètement dingue.
He's just feeding them in.
Oui, il n'y a aucun protocole. Il les envoie à l'abattoir.
If the match isn't exact... Elevators patrol check.
S'il n'y a pas compatibilité...
Contrôle ascenseurs.
Please, just go in. Don't touch anything. - I won't. I won't. - Go, go, go. I'll take care of him.
Entrez là-dedans, ne touchez à rien. Allez-y !
Je m'en occupe.
Dr. Skirth. I thought you'd all gone home. Oh, yes. Well, you know what they say.
Dr Skirth, je croyais qu'il n'y avait plus personne.
Vous savez ce qu'on dit :
Science never sleeps.
"La science ne dort jamais."
Statut : stable 4e jour de fusion
Statut : stable 7e jour de fusion
- Eddie! It's me. Let me out! - Maria? Maria?
- Maria ? - C'est moi, Maria !
- Please! Let me out! - I don't know how to get you...
Fais-moi sortir !
- Let me out. Out. - I don't know how.
Je sais pas comment.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God! Maria, no! Maria!
Maria! No, Maria, no!
There has been a security breach in Lab Sector 3. Oh, no. Maria?
Intrusion, secteur 3 du laboratoire.
Maria! Oh, shit.
Repeat, this is a Code Silver security breach.
Je répète.
Alerte effraction, code Silver.
All security personnel, please respond to Lab Sector 3.
Freeze!
Bougez pas !
Got eyes on!
Je l'ai en vue !
Go!
Go! Go!
Where the hell'd he go?
Où il est passé ?
- I'm not seeing him. - Fan out. - Find him. - Nothing. Nothing yet.
Déployez-vous ! Trouvez-le !
Search Team 4, Search Team 4.
Backtrack 200 feet east.
This is Dora. Leave a message. Skirth, yeah, it's me. I just got back.
Dora. Laissez un message.
Skirth, c'est moi. Je viens de rentrer.
Are you all right? I haven't heard from you, so I want to know if you're all right.
Vous allez bien ? J'ai pas eu de vos nouvelles.
But, yeah, that was a great call on the lab.
C'était bien vu, votre info sur le labo.
You're absolutely right.
Vous aviez raison.
Yeah. Listen. I got a... I got a guy. I'm gonna call him and, uh...
Écoutez, je connais un type. Je vais l'appeler.
Mmm. Oh...
Oh, I got a bunch of photographs.
J'ai pas mal de photos.
He will publish those photographs, but I need you to come with me.
Il les publiera mais vous devez m'accompagner.
Uh, could you just call me back? Call me back.
Rappelez-moi.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Mmm.
What is wrong with me?
Qu'est-ce qui m'arrive ?
Eddie.
How bad?
C'est grave ?
It's bad. How bad?
- C'est grave. - Grave, à quel point ?
Well, we assume the intruder took it.
On suppose que l'intrus l'a pris.
Took it? Took it?
Il l'a pris ?
We don't know what happened.
On ignore ce qui est arrivé.
I want to speak to every man who was on duty last night.
Je veux interroger le personnel.
- Already did, sir. - But I didn't. Get it out of my sight.
- Je l'ai fait. - Pas moi.
Ôtez ça de ma vue.
- Carlton, you need to see this. - What now?
Carlton. Vous devez voir ça.
His blood pressure's back to normal.
- Quoi ? - Sa tension est redevenue normale.
Liver functions, too.
Ses fonctions hépatiques aussi.
I knew it.
Je le savais.
See, his body just needed time to adjust.
Son corps avait besoin d'un temps d'adaptation.
I don't want to waste any more time. I want to up the tests. - Okay? - Yeah.
Je ne veux plus perdre de temps, on accélère les essais.
Come on.
Venez.
You're fired.
Vous êtes viré.
Find my Symbiote. Now!
Retrouvez mon Symbiote ! Vite !
Jesus.
Bon sang.
Attention, passengers for Flight 2517
Les passagers du vol 2517
to San Francisco via Hong Kong.
pour San Francisco via Hong Kong
We will be boarding at gate 9 in 15 minutes.
embarqueront porte 9 dans 15 minutes.
Please have your boarding passes... Suzy. Come on, over here.
Suzy ! Viens ici.
May I speak to Annie Weying, please? Can you tell her that it's an emergency?
Je pourrais parler à Annie Weying ?
Dites-lui que c'est urgent.
Food.
Nourriture.
Who said that?
Qui a dit ça ?
No, I'm not talking to you.
Non, je vous parlais pas.
Can you please tell me where she is?
Vous pouvez me dire où elle est ?
Great. Thank you.
Super. Merci.
De : DORA SKIRTH
Je vais bien SOYEZ PRUDENT
Okay...
Yes, Lana for two?
- I'm sorry, sir? - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Sir? - Oh, yes.
Monsieur, s'il vous plaît !
Oh, my God, Eddie. What are you doing here? - Annie... - No, no, no...
Eddie ! Qu'est-ce que tu fais là ?
No, I have to tell you something.
J'ai un truc à te dire.
- No, no, no. Please. - No, now. I have to.
Ton bureau m'a dit que t'étais là.
Work told me you were here. You're the only person that I trust.
J'ai confiance qu'en toi.
Are you drunk? Yeah. No, I broke into the Life Foundation.
Tu es ivre ?
- Eddie, you did what? - Yeah, but I may...
Je me suis introduit chez Life Foundation.
I think I may have been infected.
J'ai été infecté.
He's burning up. You're really hot. Eddie, you look like you're in a bad way.
Il est brûlant.
I am. I am in a bad way.
- Tu vas mal. - Très mal !
Eddie, Jesus!
T'es fou !
This is dead.
C'est mort.
Dead.
Mort.
Eddie, sit down.
Eddie, assieds-toi !
Okay, all right. Okay.
- Hey, hey, Eddie, Eddie, Eddie. - Stop that.
- Sir, sir, sir, I'm so sorry. - Eddie, quit it. Put it down. Eddie!
Eddie, repose ça !
Snap out of it!
Reprends-toi !
No.
All right. It's no good.
C'est pas bon.
Bobby, are you all right?
- Hey! - Whoa!
Hey, hey, hey. I'm a doctor. I'm a doctor.
Je suis médecin.
I'm hot. Is anyone else hot?
J'ai chaud, pas vous ?
Are you hurt?
- Sir, excuse me. - No! Shh! Wait, where are you going? Eddie?
Attends, où tu vas ?
This is unacceptable. I'm gonna call the police.
C'est inadmissible.
What are you doing? No, please don't. - No. - Eddie, please.
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ? Arrête.
Oh, my God.
Ah.
- Now I'm gonna call the police. - No, no. Please don't call the police.
- J'appelle la police. - Non !
Here, call an ambulance. I'm a doctor. This man is my, um...
Appelez une ambulance, je suis médecin. C'est mon...
Patient.
patient.
Oh, it's much better.
Ça va mieux.
You are insane.
Tu es cinglé.
- He's killing people. - Who's killing people?
- Il tue des gens. - Qui ?
- Carlton Drake. - Oh, God, Eddie,
Carlton Drake !
- not this again. - Yes, he is. He is!
- Pas ça. - C'est vrai !
And I have proof!
J'ai la preuve !
Ugh.
- Hey, Eddie... - Hmm?
Eddie.
Eddie?
Eddie, can you hear me?
Tu m'entends ?
This is Dan speaking to you.
C'est Dan.
Hey, Dan.
Salut, Dan.
- Welcome back. - Where am I?
Re-bonjour.
Uh, you're in the MRI.
- Où je suis ? - Dans un IRM.
Okay, we've given you a little sedative.
On t'a donné un sédatif léger.
- Where is Anne? - Anne is not here right now.
Où est Annie ?
We're gonna run some tests, okay?
Elle n'est pas là. On va faire quelques tests, d'accord ?
It's gonna be completely painless. So, you know, just try to stay still. Uh, relax, and, um...
Ce sera complètement indolore. Reste calme, détends-toi, et...
Yeah, here we go.
C'est parti.
Eddie, what's happening in there?
Qu'est-ce que t'as ?
Eddie, you okay?
Eddie, ça va ?
Shut it down.
Coupe tout.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're okay. Yeah.
Tout va bien.
Coming out. You all right?
Je te sors de là.
- Yeah. - Here, look at me, look at me.
Ça va ?
- You okay? - Yeah.
Regarde-moi. Tout va bien ?
- All right. - Just take a deep breath. Okay? You're okay. Yeah.
Respire un grand coup.
Now, listen, you're not the first person to freak out in there.
Tu n'es pas le premier à flipper.
I get claustrophobic, too.
Je suis claustrophobe, aussi.
Dr. Lewis?
Dr Lewis.
- Oh, boy. - Hey, Mrs. Manfredi. How are you? Oh, I just saw Morris.
- Mme Manfredi. Comment allez-vous ? - J'ai vu Morris.
And he's whining and complaining like an old baby again.
Il geint et se plaint à nouveau comme un vieux bébé.
- Oh, good. - Oh, thank you so much.
Tant mieux.
Yeah, my pleasure.
- Merci beaucoup. - Je vous en prie.
Okay, Mrs. Manfredi, we talked about the dog. Okay, love the dog. You can't have the dog.
On a déjà parlé du chien. C'est interdit.
Sorry. Gemini.
Désolée. Gemini.
We're gonna get to the bottom of this. All right? That I can promise you. - But for now, go home, get some rest. - Uh-huh.
On va tirer ça au clair, promis. Rentre te reposer.
I'll call you when your tests are in. - All right, thank you. - Okay? Yep.
Je t'appelle pour les résultats.
- Thank you, Dan. Thank you. - You got it.
Merci, Dan.
- Hello, Doctor. - Hi.
Bonjour, docteur.
Did you have the same reactions
regardless of the temperature...
Good afternoon, Dr. Skirth.
Bonjour, Dr Skirth.
The creature and the host are one. Everything was fine.
La créature et l'hôte ne font qu'un. Tout allait bien.
So, why does the human continue to waste away?
Pourquoi l'humain continue de dépérir ?
I don't know. We've given him enough liquid nutrition to feed an elephant.
Je l'ignore.
Il a eu une méga dose de fluide nutritif.
But the organism is unaffected? - The Symbiote is thriving. - Good.
- L'organisme résiste ? - Le Symbiote prospère.
But once again, it's killing the host.
Une fois de plus,
It's consuming his organs.
il tue l'hôte, il dévore ses organes.
Oh, watch this.
Regardez.
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing? You're hurting it. Stop it!
Vous lui faites mal ! Arrêtez ça !
Sounds in the 4,000 to 6,000 hertz range are very harmful for it.
Les sons entre 4 000 et 6 000 Hz sont très nocifs pour lui.
- Well, then don't make those sounds. - Okay.
Alors, ne produisez pas ces sons.
He was stabilizing. What happened?
Il se stabilisait. Qu'est-il arrivé ?
He's approaching acute liver failure.
Il frôle l'insuffisance hépatique aiguë.
We're gonna need another host.
Il faut un autre hôte.
Such poor design.
Quelle piètre conception.
- Excuse me? - Human beings.
- Pardon ? - L'être humain.
Sorry to interrupt.
Désolé de vous déranger.
Thought you'd like some good news.
J'ai une bonne nouvelle.
I'm sorry.
Je suis désolée.
Hungry!
J'ai faim !
Oh, goddamn.
La vache !
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
Je vais bien ! Ne vous inquiétez pas.
Can I get through, please? Excuse me.
Je peux passer ? Pardon.
Thank you.
Merci.
I'm just gonna stay here, all right? Until the cable car stops.
Je vais rester là, d'accord ? Jusqu'à l'arrêt.
We're good. All right. Thank you.
Tout va bien.
Excuse me.
Merci.
Oh, hey, Anne.
Eddie, hi. How you feeling?
Salut. Comment tu te sens ?
Oh, feeling... I'm sick.
Cramé. Je suis malade.
Well, Eddie, you have a parasite.
Tu as un parasite.
They're not exactly sure how you got it, but it would explain the fever.
On ignore comment tu l'as attrapé, mais ça expliquerait la fièvre.
That would make sense.
Ça tient la route.
Also, I'm hearing, uh, a voice.
J'entends aussi une voix.
Auditory hallucinations are actually very common.
Ce sont des hallucinations auditives.
Oh, hey, Dan. How you doing?
Salut, Dan.
I didn't realize that you were on the call, too. - Yeah, I'm here. - Mmm.
- J'ignorais que t'écoutais. - Je suis là.
Hey, Dan, would this parasite... Would it, like, be able to make me, I don't know...
Est-ce que ce parasite pourrait me faire...
Like, climb a really, really, really tall tree,
grimper très, très haut à un arbre,
but super, super fast?
mais très, très vite ?
Yes. We just did.
Oui, on vient de le faire.
Uh, well, Eddie, it sounds like it might be causing some metabolic abnormalities
Il pourrait influer
that are making it hard for your body to maintain homeostasis.
sur ton métabolisme, empêchant l'homéostasie du corps.
You said "causing" and "body," and... I lost you.
À part "influer" et "corps", j'ai rien compris.
Listen, Eddie, um, we are gonna get you on some meds, and we are gonna clear that out.
On va te donner un traitement et l'éliminer.
- Yes. - Never gonna happen.
Même pas en rêve.
Will you stop doing that now. Not now.
Arrête de faire ça ! C'est pas le moment.
- Eddie, we're just trying to help you. - I know.
On essaye juste de t'aider.
I know. I'm just, I'm not actually talking to you, Annie.
Je sais. En fait, je te parlais pas.
Who are you talking to?
À qui tu parles ?
I'm just gonna call you back, all right?
Je te rappelle, d'accord ?
Thank you. Thank you, Dan. Thank you. Thank you, both.
Merci, Dan. Merci à tous les deux.
Yeah? Hey, can you turn your music down, please? 'Cause I'm having a really hard time.
Vous pourriez baisser la musique ?
Whatever.
- Je suis à cran. - C'est ça.
Yeah, sure, man. Yeah. - I'll just turn it right down. Sorry. - Thank you. Thank you.
- Je baisse tout de suite. - Merci.
I was troubled by
J'étais perturbée par...
what we've been doing. I get it.
ce que nous faisons.
Je comprends.
I get it.
We've all been troubled. It's the nature of what we do.
Nous sommes tous perturbés. C'est inhérent à nos travaux.
But I need you to tell me who was here with you.
Mais vous devez me dire qui était avec vous ici.
I need that from you.
J'ai besoin de savoir.
I can't do that.
Je ne peux pas.
We can't fix things unless we begin with your friend.
On ne peut pas arranger les choses, sauf si on retrouve...
votre ami.
The person who was here. Because they're gonna die. They're in grave danger.
Celui qui était ici. Il va mourir, il est en danger.
You know that, right?
Vous le savez, non ?
They're gonna die unless we bring them back here,
Il va mourir si on ne le ramène pas ici,
where you can help to keep them alive.
où vous pourrez nous aider à le garder en vie.
Hey. Dora.
Dora.
I promise, from here on in, we will do things differently.
Je vous promets que dorénavant, on va faire autrement.
Will you trust me?
Vous me faites confiance ?
Eddie Brock.
- Eddie Brock? - Mmm-hmm.
You were our best.
Vous étiez la meilleure.
Open it.
Ouvrez.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Do not open that door.
N'ouvre pas la porte.
Huh?
Stay put.
Ne bouge plus !
- Hey, Eddie. - Who the hell is this guy?
D'où il sort, ce type ?
I'm gonna need Mr. Drake's property back.
Rends-moi ce qui appartient à Drake.
Whoa.
- What are you doing? - I'm, uh...
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ?
I'm putting my hands up.
Je lève les mains en l'air.
You are making us look bad.
Tu nous fous la honte.
I... No, I am not.
Non, c'est pas vrai !
Yes, you are.
Si, c'est vrai.
- No, I'm not. - Yes, you are! - No, I'm not. - Why would you do that?
Je te dis que si ! Pourquoi tu fais ça ?
'Cause it is a very sensible thing to do.
Ça me semble plutôt indiqué.
- Eddie... - I will take care of this myself. - What? - Eddie, where's the bug?
Je vais m'en occuper moi-même.
Où est la bestiole ?
Take him down.
Dégommez-le.
I'm so sorry about your friends.
Désolé pour tes potes.
- What is that? - Not "what." Who.
- C'est quoi, ça ? - Pas quoi.
Qui.
Oh.
Shit.
Merde.
Outstanding.
Exceptionnel !
Now let's bite all their heads off and pile them up in the corner.
Arrachons-leur la tête pour en faire des tas.
Why would we do that?
Pourquoi ?
Pile of bodies, pile of heads.
Un tas de corps et un tas de têtes.
What the shit, man?
Oh merde !
No! No, no, no!
- What the hell? - Dude! How did you do that?
- Putain ! - Comment t'as fait ça ?
Apparently, I have a parasite.
Apparemment, j'ai un parasite.
Mr. Drake, our subject is carrying the Symbiote.
M. Drake, le sujet
Connecting you to the feed now.
transporte le Symbiote. J'envoie la vidéo.
He's achieved symbiosis. Are you seeing this?
Il a accompli la symbiose. Vous voyez ça ?
Are you seeing this? He's achieved symbiosis!
Vous avez vu ? Il a accompli la symbiose !
Treece... Treece, bring me back my creature.
Treece, ramenez-moi ma créature.
Eddie.
You're not even here, are you? I'm just seeing things.
T'es même pas là, j'hallucine.
It's not real. You're in my head. 'Cause you're just a parasite.
C'est pas réel, t'es dans ma tête. T'es juste un parasite.
"Parasite"?
Parasite ?
You have a brain tumor, Eddie.
Tu as une tumeur au cerveau, Eddie.
I got him. He's in the alley behind the Schueller Building.
Il est derrière le bâtiment Schueller.
I am sorry that I called you a parasite. We can discuss this like two men. What is that? What is that?
Désolé de t'avoir traité de parasite. On peut en parler entre hommes...
C'est quoi, ça ?
What?
Do not let him get away. Do you understand me, Treece?
Ne le laissez pas s'échapper, compris ?
Copy. Weapons are armed and ready.
Bien reçu. Les armes sont chargées.
Launch the drones.
Lancez les drones.
Duck.
Baisse-toi !
Whew! - Thank you. - You are welcome.
- Merci. - De rien.
Oh!
This is beyond anything we thought was possible.
Ça dépasse tout ce qu'on avait imaginé.
Oh, God, no!
Holy shit!
Putain !
Treece, do not let him get away.
Ne le laissez pas s'échapper.
I've got him. All ground vehicles, move in.
Je le tiens. À toutes les voitures, intervenez.
Target is now eastbound on Grant.
La cible se dirige vers l'est sur Grant.
Oh, God! Do something!
Fais quelque chose !
What the...
Oh, yeah! We got more friends. Awesome.
On a de nouveaux copains. Génial.
No, no, no! No, no!
No! You're out of your mind!
Non, t'es complètement taré !
No!
- That is a dead-end! - Not for us.
- C'est une impasse ! - Pas pour nous.
Whoa!
Yeah!
I am going to die!
Je vais mourir.
You are not going to die!
Tu ne vas pas mourir.
Whoa! That was pretty cool, actually. I'm not gonna lie...
C'était plutôt cool, j'avoue.
I got him. - Bring him home. - Copy that.
- Je le tiens. - Ramenez-le.
This is incredible.
Bien reçu.
C'est incroyable.
You have been a serious pain in the ass for me, Eddie.
Tu m'as vraiment fait chier, Eddie.
Well, you know, I aim to please.
Tu sais, j'aime bien faire plaisir.
Eyes, lungs, pancreas.
Yeux, poumons, pancréas.
So many snacks, so little time.
Tant de petits-fours et si peu de temps.
SFPD. Don't move!
Police ! Plus un geste !
Get off the car!
My legs.
Mes jambes.
Oh, my God, my legs were broken. Now they're not broken. What is happening?
J'avais les jambes cassées, elles ne le sont plus.
Comment ça se fait ?
What the hell are you?
Mais qu'est-ce que tu es ?
I am Venom.
Je suis Venom.
And you are mine.
Et tu m'appartiens.
You bit somebody's head off. Fuel in the tank.
Tu as arraché une tête avec les dents.
Pour faire le plein.
Listen carefully, Eddie.
Écoute attentivement.
You did not find us. We found you.
Vous ne nous avez pas trouvés.
On vous a trouvés.
Think of yourself as my ride.
Considère-toi comme mon taxi.
Where are you going?
Où tu vas ?
We need Carlton Drake's rocket.
On a besoin de la fusée de Drake.
You remember him.
Tu te souviens de lui ?
How do you even know about that? - I know everything, Eddie. - You do?
- Comment t'es au courant ? - Je sais tout.
- Everything about you. - How?
- Sérieux ? - Tout sur toi.
I am inside your head.
- Comment ? - Je suis dans ta tête.
You are a loser, Eddie.
Tu es un loser.
Are you gonna eat anybody else? Most likely.
Tu vas manger quelqu'un d'autre ?
Oh, God.
Probablement.
Seigneur.
That is why we are here.
C'est la raison de notre présence.
Cooperate, and you might just survive.
Coopère et tu survivras peut-être.
That is the deal.
C'est le marché.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to San Francisco.
Bonsoir, mesdames et messieurs, bienvenue à San Francisco.
For your safety and comfort, please remain seated...
Hey, babe. I'm almost home.
J'arrive.
- Where's Eddie? - Why? What's happening?
- Où est Eddie ? - Qu'y a-t-il ?
I got Eddie's labs back, and it's worse than I thought.
J'ai ses résultats. C'est pire que prévu.
His systems, renal, endocrine, they're behaving abnormally.
Ses reins, son système endocrinien, réagissent anormalement.
I've never seen anything like it.
Je n'ai jamais vu ça.
What does that mean, Dan? What are you telling me?
Ça veut dire quoi ? Dan, dis-moi.
- You need to get him here. - My God.
Tu dois l'amener ici.
- Eddie Brock here. Leave a message. - Shit.
Laissez un message.
Where were you when it left Dr. Skirth's body?
Où étiez-vous quand il a quitté le corps du Dr Skirth ?
- Where was he? - I was...
Où était-il ?
This is the higher life-form. You stood by and watched while it died.
C'est l'être supérieur.
Vous l'avez regardé mourir.
The arrogance.
Quelle arrogance !
Treece, listen to me. After this, we can't risk killing Brock,
Treece, écoutez.
Après ça, on ne peut pas prendre le risque de tuer Brock.
not until we find another suitable host.
Jusqu'à ce qu'on trouve un hôte viable.
I don't want to see you again unless you have Brock!
Je ne veux pas vous revoir tant que vous n'avez pas Brock !
Officer, what's happening? I need to get in there.
Que se passe-t-il ? Je dois aller là-bas.
- It's my friend's apartment. - Building's been evacuated.
C'est chez mon ami.
It's not safe for you to be here, ma'am. Found another one, Bill.
Tout a été évacué. Ce n'est pas prudent de rester là.
Get off the streets. Go home.
Rentrez chez vous.
There's bodies all over the city tonight.
Il y a des cadavres dans toute la ville.
Bodies?
My God, Eddie, where are you?
Eddie, où es-tu ?
Who is Anne? Your pulse has quickened.
Qui est Anne ? Ton pouls s'accélère.
That is none of your goddamn business.
Ça te regarde pas, putain.
Everything of yours is my business, Eddie. We have no secrets.
Tout ce qui te concerne me regarde. On n'a pas de secrets.
Yeah? Well, then you know exactly why I'm going here before we get to your rocket, huh?
Alors tu sais pourquoi je viens ici avant d'aller à ta fusée ?
Sure. I'm not unreasonable.
Bien sûr. Je ne suis pas dénué d'intelligence.
Shit. Yeah?
Merde.
Eddie. Thank God. Where are you? I need to see you. No, no, you can't see me.
Où es-tu ? Je dois te voir.
Non, tu ne peux pas me voir.
Eddie, I need you to tell me where you are. I'm coming to get you.
Dis-moi où tu es, je viens te chercher.
No, you cannot come anywhere near me. You cannot come near me right now.
Non, tu ne dois pas m'approcher. Pas maintenant.
- Richard. Hey, Richard... - No!
Salut, Richard !
- Eddie? - No, I gotta go up there.
Tu n'es pas censé être ici.
You know you're not supposed to be here, Eddie. I got to get up there, man.
Je dois monter.
Look, I got love for you, bro, but no can do.
Je t'aime bien, mais c'est impossible.
There's no such thing as can't.
Rien n'est impossible.
I'm sorry, man.
Je suis désolé.
Okay, okay... Uh... Can you, uh, just give him this?
Tu peux juste...
lui donner ça ?
- He needs to see what's on it. - Eddie, please. I really need this job.
Il doit voir ça.
Je t'en prie, j'ai besoin de ce boulot.
- Let's eat his brains. - No! You do not touch him!
Mangeons-lui le cerveau.
- He is my friend. - What's wrong with you?
Le touche pas, c'est mon ami.
He works three jobs just so that he can support his family.
Il a 3 boulots pour nourrir sa famille.
- Eddie, what's going on? - We're leaving.
Qu'est-ce que t'as ?
- "We"? - Yeah.
On part.
- What are you talking about, "we"? - Just stay back!
N'avance pas !
Yeah.
- Shit. - You want up?
Tu veux monter ?
Well, why didn't you just say?
Il suffisait de demander.
Hmm. - It is peaceful up here. - I'm not very good with heights.
C'est paisible ici.
J'ai un peu le vertige.
Your world is not so ugly after all.
Ton monde n'est pas si laid, après tout.
I'm almost sorry to see it end.
Je suis presque triste de le voir mourir.
What does that mean?
Ça veut dire quoi ?
Where'd you go? Where did you go?
Où t'es passé ?
I got us.
Je nous tiens.
Whoa.
Again? You're gonna get me killed.
Encore ?
Tu vas me tuer.
You die, I die.
Tu meurs, je meurs.
Yeah, well, you can always just shed my carcass
Mais tu peux toujours lâcher ma carcasse
and exchange it for another one whenever you need.
et l'échanger contre une autre.
Why would I do that?
Pourquoi je ferais ça ?
You are far too good of a match to throw away so soon.
Tu es un hôte trop parfait pour que je te lâche.
Plus, I am starting to like you. You and I are not so different.
De plus, tu commences à me plaire. On n'est pas si différents.
Thank you.
Merci.
Okay.
FAIS LE BON CHOIX CONNARD !!!
Here's your evidence.
Voici tes preuves.
Jump.
Sauter ?
Pussy.
Mauviette.
Hands!
Mains en l'air !
On the ground! Now!
À terre ! Tout de suite !
Guys, you do not want to do this. Trust me.
Ça va pas vous plaire, croyez-moi.
- Mask! - Copy!
- Masques ! - Compris.
All right, have it your own way.
D'accord, faites comme vous voulez.
- Mask! - Copy.
- Masque ! - Compris.
What the hell is that thing?
What the hell?
Hold your fire! Flares!
- Cessez le feu. - Grenades !
He's there! He's there! Reload!
- Il est là ! - Rechargez !
Anybody see him?
Quelqu'un le voit ?
Does anyone have eyes on him?
Quelqu'un l'a en vue ?
Switching to thermal. Seeking target.
Je passe en infrarouge. Recherche cible.
I don't have eyes on him.
Je l'ai pas en vue.
Where is it?
Où il est ?
Flash grenade!
Grenade éclairante !
Throw them!
Flash grenade!
Grenade éclairante !
He's in the rafters!
Là-haut !
Above!
There he is!
Il est là !
Move, move, move!
Écartez-vous !
No! We do not eat policemen!
On ne mange pas de policiers !
Annie! Annie, wait!
Annie, attends !
- Wait, please. - Oh, what the hell is that? That's not me. I've been infected.
- C'est quoi, cette chose ? - C'est pas moi !
- Eddie, what's happening? - He's inside me.
- J'ai été infecté. - C'est quoi, ça ?
Il est en moi.
- "He"? - Yes.
"Il" ?
- I know it sounds crazy, but... - You're sick.
Je sais, c'est dingue.
- Eddie, you're really sick. - No, I am scared!
Tu es vraiment malade.
Non, je suis terrifié !
- And I need help. - Hospital.
J'ai besoin d'aide.
À l'hôpital.
Right now.
Tout de suite.
I can't go with you. It's not safe.
Je ne peux pas venir.
C'est dangereux.
Get in the car, Eddie.
Monte.
- In the back. - I like her. Get in.
À l'arrière.
Je l'aime bien. Monte.
I'm out of control.
Je suis incontrôlable.
Dan just needs to do another MRI.
Dan a besoin d'une autre IRM.
- No MRI. - No. No. No MRI.
Pas d'IRM.
What? Why?
- Pas d'IRM. - Pourquoi ?
Sound at 4,000 to 6,000 hertz is lethal.
Les sons entre 4 000 et 6 000 Hz sont mortels.
Sound frequency in the MRI is really harmful for him.
La fréquence sonore de l'IRM est nocive pour lui.
What, so, sound is like his kryptonite?
Le son, c'est un peu sa kryptonite ?
- Not all sounds. - And fire.
Pas tous les sons.
Et le feu.
Fire. And fire. He's talking to you?
Il est en train de te parler.
Always.
Tout le temps.
- Are you in pain? - No.
Tu souffres ?
No, I don't feel anything, actually, apart from... I'm hungry all the time.
Non, je ne ressens rien, à part que j'ai tout le temps faim.
And you feel sad, do you not, Eddie, when you are with her?
Et tu es triste, n'est-ce pas, quand tu es avec elle.
Get out of my head, man.
Sors de ma tête.
You never apologized.
Tu ne t'es jamais excusé.
You might not live to get another chance.
Ça pourrait bien être ta seule occasion.
Annie. I just want to say that whatever happens,
Je veux juste dire que, quoi qu'il arrive,
that I am truly sorry for whatever... And everything I have ever done to you.
je te demande pardon pour tout ce que j'ai pu te faire.
I am truly, truly sorry.
Je suis vraiment désolé.
And that I love you.
Et je t'aime.
Oh, Eddie...
Now's really not the time. Let's just keep you alive, okay?
C'est pas le moment. Commençons par te garder en vie.
Aw, that's nice.
C'est gentil, ça.
You know, I'm really wet and cold. Can I, uh, wear this?
Je suis trempé et j'ai froid. Je peux mettre ça ?
Yeah, yeah, you can wear whatever you want.
Oui, tout ce que tu veux.
Thank you.
Merci.
Hello?
What are you doing here?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais là ?
Are you lost?
Tu es perdue ?
I'm not lost.
Je ne suis pas perdue.
Thanks for coming in.
Merci d'être venu.
- Eddie, I'm sorry. - What?
Eddie, je suis désolé.
Quoi ?
Eddie, I got your labs back, and your heart has atrophied severely.
J'ai tes résultats.
Do not listen to him. I can fix it.
Ton cœur est gravement atrophié.
I don't want you to fix it.
N'écoute pas. Je peux le réparer.
Ne le répare pas.
I can heal you.
Je peux te guérir.
Can you fix it?
Tu peux le réparer ?
No. I've never seen anything like this before. - This parasite, whatever this is... - "Parasite"?
Non, je n'ai jamais vu ça. Ce parasite...
It's eating you from the inside. Not a parasite. He's not.
- Il te dévore de l'intérieur. - C'est pas un parasite.
- You're using him up. - No. She is wrong.
Vous le consumez.
Non ! Elle se trompe.
- We need to get you to the ICU. - Wait. Shh!
Tu dois aller en soins intensifs.
Attends.
- I, Eddie, am I dying? - No!
Est-ce que je suis en train de mourir ?
You're killing him.
- Non ! - Vous le tuez.
They do not know what they are talking about.
Ils parlent sans savoir.
Listen, we don't have a lot of time...
Le temps presse.
- Oh, God! - We have to get out of here.
Sortons d'ici.
- Stop! - Oh, God, he's killing you. I'm killing you. I'm so sorry.
Il va te tuer. Je vais te tuer.
No! Don't do that!
Non ! Ne fais pas ça.
Are you all right? Eddie, I'm sorry. I had to get him out of you.
Ça va ?
Je devais le faire sortir de toi.
What is that?
C'est quoi ?
You were killing me?
Tu étais en train de me tuer ?
What happened to "we," man? What happened to "we"?
Où est passé le "on" ? Où il est passé ?
Yeah, look at you now, huh? Now you're dying, too.
Regarde-toi.
Tu es en train de mourir aussi.
We're done.
C'est fini entre nous.
- Where do you think you're going? - Anywhere other than here.
- Tu vas où comme ça ? - Loin d'ici.
You don't think we have a little problem on our hands? Wait, you're not gonna leave me here with this thing.
Tu crois pas qu'on a un problème ?
Tu vas me laisser avec ça ?
You want to tell me what the hell's going on?
Tu peux m'expliquer ce qui se passe ?
I do. And you're right. We do need to talk about it,
Bien sûr. Tu as raison.
but I don't know much more than you do.
Il faut qu'on en parle.
I guess he had no one else to turn to.
Mais je n'en sais pas plus que toi.
Il n'a personne d'autre vers qui se tourner.
He's a very complicated man. But, Dan, I promise,
C'est un homme très compliqué. Mais je te jure
there's nothing going on between me and Eddie.
qu'il n'y a rien entre Eddie et moi.
I'm not talking about you and Eddie, Anne.
Je ne parle pas de vous deux.
- Oh. - I'm talking about that.
Je parle de ça.
Dan.
Where is it?
Où est-il ?
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
You can kill me, 'cause I'm dying anyway.
Tu peux me tuer, je suis mourant.
I'm not just gonna kill you. That wouldn't be any fun.
Je vais pas juste te tuer.
Ça serait pas assez drôle.
No, no, no. I'm gonna rip your tongue out of your face.
Non, je vais t'arracher la langue.
Whoo!
Stop. You're bleeding all over my lab. Go. Go!
Ça suffit.
Vous mettez du sang partout.
Sortez !
- Where is he? - I don't know.
Où est-il ?
And you know what? Even if I did, I wouldn't tell you anyway.
Je ne sais pas. Même si je le savais,
I don't trust you, and you're insane.
je vous le dirais pas. Je vous fais pas confiance
et vous êtes cinglé.
- That hurts. - Sorry.
- Ça me blesse. - Pardon.
Long journal entry about that tonight. You're being dumb, Brock. I'm not insane.
Je le noterai dans mon journal. Vous êtes idiot.
What's insane is the way humans choose to live today.
Je ne suis pas dingue. Ce qui l'est, c'est comment vit l'humanité.
Think about it. All we do is take, take, take.
Réfléchissez.
It can't go on.
On ne fait que prendre. Ça ne peut pas durer.
We've brought the planet to the brink of extinction.
On a mené la planète au bord de l'extinction.
We're parasites. You're a good example.
On est des parasites. Comme vous.
Think about it. All you do is take.
Vous ne faites que prendre.
You took my Symbiote. You take potshots at a great man
Vous avez pris mon Symbiote.
- trying to get something done. - Who?
Vous prenez la tête à un grand homme qui essaye d'agir.
Qui ?
Didn't you take from the person you loved the most,
N'avez-vous pas pris quelque chose
who trusted you the most? That's insane.
à la personne que vous aimiez le plus ?
Ça, c'est dingue.
What I've initiated is a whole new world, a new species.
J'ai initié un nouveau monde, une nouvelle espèce :
Man and Symbiote combined.
l'homme et le Symbiote combinés.
Let me tell you something, buddy. All right? Just man-to-man.
Je vais te dire un truc, d'homme à homme,
Because I have spent a significant amount of time, all right,
parce que j'ai passé pas mal de temps
with one of these creatures up my ass.
avec une de ces créatures dans le cul.
It's not a lot of fun.
C'est pas très amusant.
And then I find out, all along,
Et je découvre
that they're killing you.
qu'en fait, ils sont en train de te tuer.
This is the last time I'm asking you. - Where is my Symbiote? - I have no idea.
Pour la dernière fois, où est mon Symbiote ?
Aucune idée.
- Where is he? - Oh, my God!
Où est-il ?
L'horreur !
Where's Venom?
Où est Venom ?
That is the ugliest-looking thing I have ever seen.
C'est le truc le plus moche que j'aie jamais vu.
You know, Brock, I have no use for you.
Vous savez,
je n'ai plus besoin de vous.
Treece! Come and clean up your mess.
Treece ! Venez nettoyer votre bordel !
Whoa, he has one up his ass, too.
Il l'a dans le cul, lui aussi.
Your friends, the others, I apologize. I tried to keep them alive.
Je suis désolé pour vos amis, les autres.
J'ai essayé de les garder en vie.
There are more of us. Millions more.
Nous sommes plus nombreux. Des millions.
They will follow wherever I lead.
Ils iront là où je les conduirai.
Where we lead.
Où nous les conduirons.
Yes, "we."
Oui, nous.
But first, we must retrieve them.
Mais d'abord, il faut les récupérer.
I can take care of that.
Je peux m'en charger.
Yeah, what you gonna do, you gonna walk me to death?
Tu veux quoi ?
Me faire marcher jusqu'à ce que je meure ?
Shut up.
Ferme-la.
Not so tough without your friend.
T'es moins coriace sans ton ami.
Did your mama not love you?
Ta maman t'aimait pas ?
God damn it!
Putain !
I guess it pays to be a specialist, huh?
C'est l'avantage d'être un pro.
You know, it doesn't matter if you kill me anyway, because there's something way bigger afoot
Ça a pas d'importance si tu me tues,
in this world than you and me.
parce que quelque chose d'énorme se prépare.
Much bigger than me.
Plus grand que moi.
And it's much, much bigger than you.
Beaucoup plus grand que toi.
Karma's a bitch.
Le karma, ça craint.
I don't believe in karma.
Je crois pas au karma.
Oh! Ooh!
Hi, Eddie.
Salut, Eddie.
Whoa. Whoa...
Oh...
Mmm...
Mmm!
Oh, no.
I just bit that guy's head off.
J'ai arraché la tête d'un mec.
I know, I know. I've been there, too. It's not fun.
Je suis passé par là aussi, c'est pas drôle.
- The one with Drake is Riot. - Who's Riot?
- Celui avec Drake est Riot. - Qui est Riot ?
Riot is what you would call a team leader.
Riot est ce qu'on appellerait un chef.
He has an arsenal of weapons.
Il a toute une panoplie d'armes.
- Drake's got his own Symbiote. - He is unstoppable.
- Drake a son Symbiote. - Il est invincible.
- Oh, great. - We have got to go!
Super.
Go where? Where we going?
- Il faut y aller. - Où ça ?
- Well, I'm coming with you. - No!
Je viens avec vous.
It's going to get ugly.
Ça va faire mal.
- Well, she can fight ugly. Trust me. - Yeah, I can fight ugly.
- Elle peut faire mal, je t'assure. - Oui, je peux.
Not today.
Pas aujourd'hui.
Oh, that's bullshit!
C'est nul !
This is not a simulation.
Ce n'est pas une simulation.
Well, the flight team aren't prepped yet.
L'équipage n'est pas encore prêt.
I'll be piloting the spacecraft. - You? - Yes, me.
- Je piloterai moi-même. - Vous ?
How long?
Oui, moi. Combien de temps ?
We're loading the probe and running diagnostics.
On fait les derniers contrôles.
But even fully automated, you can't pilot that craft all alone.
Mais même en pilotage automatique, vous ne pouvez pas être seul.
I'm not alone.
Je ne suis pas seul.
God damn it! What the hell happened there? We just left Annie.
Qu'est-ce qui s'est passé ? On a laissé Annie.
It is not safe for her.
C'est dangereux pour elle.
If we do not stop Riot,
Si on n'arrête pas Riot,
he will come back here with millions more of my kind.
il reviendra ici avec des millions de mes semblables.
Millions? What, you were gonna take the rocket,
Des millions ?
Quoi ? Tu allais prendre la fusée
and you were gonna come back here with an invasion force?
et revenir avec une armée ?
Then what were you gonna do, you were gonna go feed - on a whole planet? - Yes!
Et ensuite, vous alliez dévorer la planète ?
But it is different now, Eddie.
Oui ! Mais c'est différent maintenant.
- I have decided to stay. - Wow!
J'ai décidé de rester.
On my planet, I am kind of a loser, like you.
Sur ma planète, je suis un genre de loser, comme toi.
- But here, we could be more. - Excuse me?
Mais ici, on pourrait faire mieux.
And I'm getting to like it here. Oh, you like us now, do you, huh?
- Pardon ? - Je me plais, ici.
Tu nous aimes bien, maintenant ?
However, there will be nothing left to like if we do not stop that rocket.
Il n'y aura plus rien à aimer si on n'arrête pas cette fusée.
Oh, I see. Right. When it comes to being completely annihilated,
Je vois.
- then it's back to "we." - It is "we."
Quand l'anéantissement se profile, revoilà le "on".
Like it or not, it is going to take both of us.
C'est "on". Que ça te plaise ou non, ça va dépendre de nous deux.
Hey, come on, man. Cut the bullshit.
Arrête tes conneries.
What really made you change your mind?
Qu'est-ce qui t'a fait changer d'avis ?
You. You did, Eddie.
Toi. Tu m'as fait changer d'avis.
Scrub diagnostics.
Annulez les contrôles.
- Sir? - Did you hear me? Initiate the launch.
Pardon ?
Vous êtes sourd ? Débutez le lancement.
T-minus five minutes to launch.
5 minutes avant lancement.
Auto sequence has been initiated.
Procédure automatique initiée.
PROTOCOLE D'ANNULATION
Oh, shit.
T-minus four minutes, 30 seconds.
H moins 4 minutes, 30 secondes.
Oh, Jesus! You can take this guy, right?
Tu peux le battre, pas vrai ?
He has got shit you have never seen.
Il fait des trucs que t'as jamais vus.
What does that mean? What are our chances? Hmm. Pretty much zero.
Ça veut dire quoi ? On a des chances ?
Pratiquement aucune.
Oh, fuck it. Well, let's go save the planet.
Putain...
Bon, allons sauver la planète !
T-minus four minutes.
H moins 4 minutes.
Initiate orbiter aerosurface profile.
Venom. Get in the rocket.
Venom. Monte dans la fusée.
No. We won't let you destroy this world.
Non ! On ne te laissera pas détruire ce monde.
Then die.
Alors, crève.
- Holy shit! - Told you.
- La vache ! - Je te l'avais dit.
T-minus three minutes.
H moins 3 minutes.
You have a strong host.
Ton hôte est fort.
But not strong enough.
Mais pas assez fort.
T-minus two minutes, 30 seconds.
H moins 2 minutes, 30 secondes.
Eddie.
Drake, stop!
Drake, arrête !
Told you I could fight ugly.
Tu vois que je peux faire mal.
T-minus one minute.
H moins 1 minute.
You're too late.
Trop tard.
This is the next stage...
C'est l'étape suivante...
You talk too much.
Tu parles trop.
T-minus 30 seconds.
H moins 30 secondes.
You are nothing.
Tu n'es rien.
Ten seconds.
10 secondes.
Nine...
9...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Liftoff.
Décollage.
Traitor!
Traître.
Have a nice life.
Je te souhaite bon vent.
Goodbye, Eddie.
Au revoir, Eddie.
Venom, no!
Thanks for sticking by me, Annie. Thanks for saving me.
Merci d'être restée à mes côtés et de m'avoir sauvé.
So, how you feeling after all that? I feel great. Awesome.
- Comment tu te sens après tout ça ? - Je me sens super. Génial.
Wow. Yeah, I'm thinking of suing, though. You want to prosecute? Hmm. You're in luck. I've decided to work pro bono.
Je compte porter plainte. Tu veux être l'avocate ?
Veinard, je vais travailler bénévolement.
I'm joining the public defenders' office.
Je deviens avocate commise d'office.
You're a good person, Annie.
Tu es quelqu'un de bien.
What about you? What are you gonna do?
Tu vas faire quoi ?
Uh, the network asked me to bring the show back,
La chaîne m'a demandé de reprendre
and they want to start with a piece on Drake. Oh, wow, really? So, what did you say?
mon émission et de commencer par Drake.
Uh, I'm not into it. I want to concentrate on the written word.
Sérieux ? Qu'est-ce que t'as dit ?
Ça me branche pas. Je veux me concentrer sur l'écriture.
I scored the interview of a lifetime.
J'ai décroché l'interview de ma vie.
- Oh, yeah? Who? - You're gonna have to read it.
Ah oui ? De qui ?
Oh! Like everyone else.
Tu la liras.
Comme tout le monde.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm sorry about Venom.
Je suis désolée pour Venom.
Hey, um...
Do you want to talk about that kiss?
Si on parlait de ce baiser ?
Oh, that? You call that a kiss... No, that was...
T'appelles ça un baiser ? Non, c'était...
Uh, that was your buddy's idea.
C'était...
Oh, right. Well, that is good to know.
l'idée de ton pote.
C'est bon à savoir.
- It did feel kind of great, though. - What?
- C'était quand même super. - Quoi ?
I mean, the...
Je veux dire...
- The power? - Yeah. When it's, you know...
La puissance ?
- Inside you? - You know what I mean.
- Tu sais, quand c'est... - En toi ?
Okay.
Tu sais très bien.
- Hey, Eddie? - Mmm-hmm? We're not gonna tell Dan about this. Okay?
On ne parlera pas de ça à Dan, d'accord ?
Look at her. She has no idea we are going to get her back.
Regarde-la. Elle n'imagine pas qu'on va la reconquérir.
No, I don't think so.
Non, je ne crois pas.
- Sorry, what was that? - We're not gonna tell Dan.
- T'as dit quoi ? - Je le dirai pas à Dan.
Eddie, is there something you want to tell me? - Nope. - You belong with us, Annie.
Tu as quelque chose à me dire ?
Ta place est avec nous, Annie.
Eddie, are you sure?
Tu es sûr ?
Good Lord, look at that. - Look at the time. - I have to go.
Bon sang, regarde l'heure. Je dois y aller.
- Hey, it's nice seeing you. - Yeah. You take care, all right?
C'était super de te voir. Fais attention à toi.
- Yeah, you take care of yourself. - Bye.
Toi aussi.
Hey. Don't give up on her. Either of you.
Ne la laissez pas tomber. Ça vaut pour tous les deux.
We won't.
Comptez sur nous.
- Who is that guy? - Okay.
C'est qui, ce type ?
Wait. This thing looks delicious.
Attends. Cette chose a l'air délicieuse.
I have absolutely no problem with you sticking around,
J'ai aucun problème à ce que tu me squattes,
but if you do, we're gonna have to have some ground rules, all right? You cannot just go around eating anybody that you want to.
mais dans ce cas, il va falloir établir des règles.
Tu ne peux pas manger n'importe qui.
- I cannot? - No, you cannot.
Je ne peux pas ?
All right, we need to... We need to reiterate this.
Un rappel s'impose.
There are good people in this world, a lot of them.
Il y a des gens bien dans ce monde. Beaucoup.
And then there are bad people. You have to tell the difference.
Et il y a des gens méchants. Il faut faire la différence.
The deal is, you will only ever be allowed to touch,
Tu ne seras autorisé à toucher,
harm, hurt, possibly, very possibly,
blesser, faire souffrir,
eat very, very bad people,
et éventuellement, manger,
but never, ever, ever good people. All right?
que des gens très méchants. Mais jamais des gens bien. D'accord ?
- Fine. - Good.
Très bien.
Parfait.
But how does one tell the difference?
Comment fait-on la différence ?
Well, it's super simple. I mean, you just have to... You can intuit it, you can sense it.
C'est super simple. Tu n'as qu'à...
Sometimes you can even feel it.
C'est intuitif. Parfois, tu peux même le ressentir.
Whatever you say.
Si tu le dis.
But can we get something to eat now?
On peut manger un bout, maintenant ?
Otherwise, your liver, it's starting to look really, really good and juicy.
Ton foie commence à m'apparaître de plus en plus appétissant
et succulent.
Yeah. Definitely. I know a place down here.
Pas de problème. Je connais un endroit.
Hey, Mrs. C.
Bonjour, Mme C !
How you doing, Eddie?
Comment ça va, Eddie ?
Ain't nothing changed but the weather. You know.
Y a que le temps qui change, vous savez.
No.
Non.
So, what culinary delights will tickle the pickle tonight?
Quel délice du jour va exciter tes papilles ?
Tater tots and chocolate.
Croquettes de patates et chocolat.
Right. Okay, no problem.
Pas de souci.
The payment's due, Chen.
Il faut payer, Chen.
Please. I can't keep doing this.
Ça ne peut pas continuer comme ça !
Now.
Tout de suite !
- Bad guy, right? - Yep.
C'est un méchant, non ?
You come in here again...
Si tu reviens ici...
In fact, you go anywhere in this city, preying on innocent people,
En fait, si tu reviens dans cette ville
and we will find you and eat both your arms
harceler des innocents,
on te retrouvera
- and then both of your legs. - No, no.
et on mangera tes bras, puis tes jambes.
And then we will eat your face right off your head. Do you understand?
Puis, on mangera ton visage.
Tu comprends ?
- Please... - Yes.
Pitié.
So, you will be this armless, legless, faceless thing, won't you,
Tu seras cette chose sans bras, sans jambes, sans visage.
rolling down the street, like a turd in the wind?
Tu dévaleras la rue,
tel un étron balayé par le vent.
- Do you feel me? - What the hell are you?
Tu me suis ?
Vous êtes quoi ?
We are Venom.
Nous sommes Venom.
- On second thought... - Please.
Réflexion faite...
Eddie? What was that?
C'était quoi ?
Oh... I have a parasite. Yeah. Night, Mrs. Chen.
J'ai chopé un parasite.
Bonne soirée, Mme Chen.
- "Parasite"? - Yeah.
Un parasite ?
It's a term of endearment, that's all.
C'est un terme affectueux, c'est tout.
- Apologize! - No.
Excuse-toi !
- Apologize! - All right, fine.
- Non. - Excuse-toi !
I'm sorry. So, what do you want to do now?
D'accord. Je suis désolé.
Qu'est-ce que tu veux faire ?
The way I see it, we can do whatever we want.
De mon point de vue, on peut faire ce qu'on veut.
I need you to stay quiet.
J'ai besoin que tu restes tranquille.
This is a "me" thing. It is not a "we" thing.
C'est une mission pour moi, pas pour nous.
- You got that? - Fine, but make it quick.
T'as compris ?
D'accord. Mais fais vite.
Open on five.
Ouvrez la porte 5.
Go. Opening up.
You ask me, they're dumb to let him call the shots.
Ils sont dingues de le laisser faire sa loi.
Second he asked for you to interview him,
À l'instant où il a demandé à être interviewé par vous,
I'd have shut that shit down.
j'aurais tout bazardé.
Oh, yeah, you know the FBI. They're just taking advantage
Vous connaissez le FBI.
of the one and only time he'll ever speak to anyone.
Ils en profitent parce qu'il s'est décidé
à parler à quelqu'un.
They're hoping that I might help them identify some additional bodies.
Ils pensent que je peux les aider à identifier d'autres corps.
FBI don't work up close and personal with him.
Le FBI est pas cul et chemise avec lui.
The FBI will have to identify you, if you don't follow the rules.
Le FBI devra vous identifier si vous suivez pas les consignes.
Hey, Red! I got a visitor for you.
Le rouquin !
Je t'ai ramené de la visite !
- Hi, Eddie. - Hey.
Bonjour, Eddie.
Do you mind if we forego the whole creepy serial killer thing here?
Ça vous dérange pas
si on évite tout le truc flippant du tueur en série ?
Sure, it's good with me.
Ça me va très bien.
I mean, I can turn it on if you want.
Je peux le faire, si vous voulez.
I can talk about the Dadaist patterns of arterial spray.
Je peux parler...
des motifs dadaïstes des éclaboussures de sang.
I bet you can.
J'en suis sûr.
Tough to see you in this light, Eddie.
J'ai du mal à vous voir avec cette lumière.
Come on over.
Approchez.
All right.
D'accord.
I'm here.
Je suis là.
When I get out of here, and I will,
Quand je sortirai d'ici,
et j'en sortirai,
there's gonna be carnage.
il y aura un carnage.
I'm sorry, Mr. Parker.
Désolé, M. Parker.
I want to do what you asked.
Je veux tenir ma promesse.
I really do.
Vraiment.
But... I'm sorry.
Mais...
je suis désolé.
I can't do this without you.
J'y arriverai pas sans vous.
Hey, kid...
Petit !
Whoa.
What was... Whoa!
What?
Quoi ?
Huh?
No.
Who are you?
Vous êtes qui ?
What are you doing over there?
À quoi tu joues ?
Freeze! PDNY.
Police !
Kid, freeze!
Petit, reste là !
You're kidding me right now?
C'est une blague ?
Hey, kid. Drop the body.
Lâche ce corps !
Ow! Somebody stop that train!
Arrêtez ce train !
Aah!
Sorry.
Désolé.
...looks like a child dressed like Spider-Man,
On dirait un gamin déguisé en Spider-Man
dragging a homeless corpse behind a train.
qui traîne un SDF derrière un train.
- Who are you? - Who are you?
- Qui t'es ? - Et vous ?
Why are you trying to kill me?
- Tu veux me tuer ? - Non.
I'm not. I'm trying to save you.
J'essaie de vous sauver.
Hey, maybe you guys can go around?
Faire le tour, c'est trop demander ?
All right. Thanks, New York.
Tant pis. Merci, New York.
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412