Trailer
Starts
Now
: Rules#NO Eating People
♪ I said either ♪ ♪ just say Aither ون
♪ I said neither ♪ ♪ I said Naither ♪
چ Either,Neither♪ ♪ Neither,Either ♪
همه Lets cargo fast♪
Tadaa!!!!!!!!
ketchup?
Excuse me
Nyummy....!!!!!
: Subtitle from Makoto77 a.k.a Christoffle Pangemanan @IDFL member
Good evening Eddie
Hei Ms. Chen
Good evening Venom
晚上好 'wan shang hao' [Good evening] Ms. Chen
"He's says," Hi!
I've been thinking about you Eddie
Because you and I are the same
This year only in cinemas
Every decision we ever make
Who do we leave behind?
And how do we leave them?
... Waiting in the darknes
A rescue who were never comes
Welcome back Eddie Brock
...it's been A long time
I missed you so much
someone gone chaos
Chaos  soon coming
♪ Who was  the loneliest number that you’ll ever do?♪
Venom let there be carnage
The chocolate delivery has not arrived yet
No
We had a deal
What's gonna happend?
Are You gonna stopped  protecting me
I'm happy to eat Ms. Chen
No, no, you can not eat Ms. Chen
What
Nothing