[MUSIC PLAYING]
[TAPPING AND SPRING RATTLING]
[SCRAPES]
[SQUEAKING]
♪ OUT THERE, THERE'S
A WORLD OUTSIDE OF YONKERS ♪
♪ WAY OUT THERE BEYOND
THIS HICK TOWN, BARNABY ♪
♪ THERE'S A SLICK
TOWN, BARNABY ♪
♪ OUT THERE, FULL A SHINE
AND FULL OF SPARKLE ♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES AND
SEE IT GLISTEN, BARNABY ♪
♪ LISTEN, BARNABY ♪
♪ PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES,
THERE'S A LOTS OF WORLD ♪
♪ OUT THERE ♪
♪ GET OUT THE BRILLIANTINE
AND DIMES CIGARS ♪
♪ WE'RE GONNA FIND ADVENTURE
IN THE EVENING AIR ♪
♪ GIRLS OF WHITE IN
A PERFUMED NIGHT ♪
♪ WHERE THERE LIGHTS
ARE BRIGHT AS THE STARS ♪
♪ PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES
WE'RE GONNA RIDE THROUGH TOWN ♪
♪ IN ONE OF THOSE NEW
HORSEDAWN OPEN CARS ♪
♪ WE'LL SEE
THE SHOWS AT DELMONICO'S ♪
♪ AND WE'LL CLOSE THE
TOWN IN A WHIRL ♪
♪ AND WE WON'T COME HOME
UNTIL WE KISS OUR GIRL ♪
♪ RIDE THROUGH TOWN ♪
♪ IN ONE OF THOSE NEW
HORSEDAWN OPEN CARS ♪
♪ WE'LL SEE THE SHOWS
AT DELMONICO'S... ♪
♪ WHIRL, AND WE WON'T
COME HOME ♪
♪ UNTIL WE KISS
OUR GIRL ♪
[SONG CONTINUING]
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAK]
[SONG CONTINUING]
[GRUNTING]
UHH!
♪ ...IN YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAK]
MMM.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ BUY N LARGE ♪
♪ IT'S YOUR SUPERSTORE ♪
♪ WE GOT ALL YOU NEED
AND SO MUCH MORE ♪
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAKING]
OOH.
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAKING]
EEE.
TOO MUCH GARBAGE
IN YOUR FACE?
THERE'S PLENTY OF
SPACE OUT IN SPACE!
BNL STAR LINERS
LEAVING EACH DAY!
WE'LL CLEAN UP THE
MESS WHILE YOU'RE AWAY!
THE JEWEL OF THE BNL
FLEET, THE "AXIOM."
SPEND YOUR FIVE-YEAR
CRUISE IN STYLE,
WAITED ON 24 HOURS A DAY BY
OUR FULLY AUTOMATED CREW,
WHILE YOUR CAPTAIN
AND AUTOPILOT
CHART A COURSE FOR NONSTOP
ENTERTAINMENT, FINE DINNING,
AND WITH OUR
ALL-ACESS HOVERCHAIRS,
EVEN GRANDMA CAN
JOIN THE FUN.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO WALK.
THE "AXIOM."
PUTTING THE STAR
IN EXECUTIVE STAR LINER.
BECAUSE AT BNL, SPACE
IS A FINAL FUN-TEIR.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIRRING]
[HUMMING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ NO MONDAY IN
YOUR SUNDAY ♪
YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES ♪
♪ PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES
WHEN YOU FEEL DOWN AND OUT ♪
♪ STRUT DOWN THE STREETS
AND HAVE YOUR PICTURE TOOK ♪
♪ DRESSED LIKE A DREAM YOUR
SPIRITS SEEMS TO TURN ABOUT ♪
♪ THAT SUNDAY SHINE IS
A CERTAIN SIGN ♪
OH-HO!
♪ THAT YOU FEEL AS
FINE AS YOU LOOK ♪
WOW.
♪ WHEN TIME RUNS OUT ♪
♪ THAT IT ONLY ♪
WHOA.
♪ TOOK A MOMENT ♪
♪ TO BE LOVED ♪
♪ A WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ LONG ♪
[MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ AND THAT IS ALL ♪
♪ THAT LOVE'S ABOUT ♪
[ALARM BLARING]
UH-OH.
[RATTLING]
[WHIRRING]
[WHISTLES]
[BACKGROUND
VOCALIST SINGING]
[SQUEAKING]
[SIGHS]
♪ TO BE LOVED ♪
♪ A WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ LONG ♪
[BEEPING]
OHH.
WHOA.
[BEEP]
AHH.
WHOA.
[GROANING]
[BEEPING]
[CHORD PLAYS]
[SQUEAKING]
[SQUEAKS]
[SIGHS]
AAH!
AW.
HUH?
EEE!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHIRRING]
[WHISTLING]
WHOA.
[SQUEAK]
[CAR ALARM BEEPS]
[WHIRRING]
[WHISTLES]
UH-OH.
[WHIRRING]
OOH!
AH!
[GROANS]
[SQUEAKS]
[WHIRRING]
HUH!
WHOA!
[WHIRRING]
HUH!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[MURMURING]
[GRUNTING]
HUH!
HUH? WHAT?
AAH!
WHOA!
[SHUDDERING]
AH!
[MURMURING]
[WHIRRING]
[BEEPING]
AAH!
[WHIRRING]
[BEEPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
[BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SHUDDERING]
[BEEPING]
OH.
[WHISTLES]
[LAUGHING]
OOH.
OH.
[SQUEAKING]
[SHUDDERING]
[BEEPING]
[SQUEAKS]
[WHIRRING]
WHOA!
OOH.
[LAUGHING]
NO!
WHO ARE YOU?
[SQUEAKING]
[BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
AAH!
[SQUEAKING]
[SCREAMING]
♪ HOLD ME CLOSE AND
HOLD ME FAST ♪
♪ THE MAGIC SPELL
YOU CAST ♪
♪ THIS IS LA VIE
EN ROSE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU KISS ME
HEAVEN SIGHS ♪
♪ AND THOUGH I
CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ I SEE LA VIE EN ROSE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU PRESS ME
TO YOUR HEART ♪
♪ I'M IN A WORLD APART ♪
♪ A WORLD WHERE
ROSES BLOOM ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU SPEAK
ANGELS SING FROM ABOVE ♪
♪ EVERYDAY WORDS SEEM
TO TURN INTO LOVE SONGS ♪
OOH.
HMM.
OHH.
[SQUEAKS] OH!
[BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
[WHIRRING]
AAH!
[SQUEAKING]
[EXPLOSIONS IN BACKGROUND]
[WHISTLING]
[WHIRRING]
[BEEP]
AAH!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
DIRECTIVE?
WHOA!
[WHIRRING]
TA-DA.
OOH.
DIRECTIVE?
DIRECTIVE.
CLASSIFIED.
OOH.
NAME?
[BEEPING]
W--WALL-E.
WALL-E.
WALL...
[LAUGHING]
EVE.
EEE...
EVE. AH!
EVE.
[GIGGLING]
[BEEPING]
EVE!
EVE! EVE!
WALL-E!
[WHIRRING]
OH.
OOH.
EVE!
[WHISTLES]
[MURMURING]
OOH.
♪ HERE IS A LITTLE
SONG I WROTE ♪
♪ NOTE FOR NOTE,
DON'T WORRY ♪
♪ BE HAPPY ♪
[WHISTLES]
HERE.
UH!
[BEEP] LOOK.
[POP]
POP.
YOU POP.
[POP]
OOH!
OOH.
[POPPING]
OHH.
[WHISTLES]
HERE.
OH.
OOPS.
AAH!
HUH?
UHH...
AHH.
OOH.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ MONDAY IN YOUR SUNDAY... ♪
LOOK.
OOH.
♪ NO MONDAY IN YOUR
SUNDAY CLOTHES ♪
♪ PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES
WHEN YOU FEEL DOWN AND OUT ♪
♪ STRUT DOWN THE STREET
AND HAVE THE PICTURE TOOK ♪
♪ DRESSED LIKE A DREAM YOUR
SPIRITS SEEM TO TURN ABOUT ♪
♪ THAT SUNDAY SHINE
IS A CERTAIN SIGN ♪
♪ THAT YOU FEEL AS
FINE AS YOU LOOK... ♪
[LOUD RATTLING]
HELLO!
[WHIRS]
AH!
♪ ...DOWN TO YOUR TOES ♪
♪ GET OUT YOUR FEATHERS
YOUR PATENT LEATHERS ♪
♪ YOUR BEADS AND
BUCKLES AND BOWS... ♪
[LOUD WHIRRING]
[CRASH]
WALL-E?
[GROANING]
OOH.
OH!
WHOA!
UH-OH!
WHOO! OOH!
WHOA! AH, HA HA.
[INDISTINCT]
AHH.
HA!
[BEEPING]
OOH!
OH!
[WHIRS]
♪ AND THAT IS ALL ♪
♪ THAT LOVE'S ABOUT ♪
♪ AND WE'LL RECALL ♪
♪ WHEN TIME RUNS OUT ♪
♪ THAT IT ONLY ♪
[SQUEAKING]
OOH!
♪ TOOK A MOMENT ♪
♪ TO BE LOVED ♪
EVE!
♪ A WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ LONG ♪
OH!
[CHUCKLES]
HMM?
OOH.
[BEEPING]
[WHIRS]
[WHIRRING]
WHOA.
EVE.
EVE?
OH!
EVE!
E-E-EVE!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
[SCRAPING]
[THUNDERING]
[BACKGROUND
VOCALISITS SINGING]
[WHIRS]
OH!
OH.
AAH!
[SQUEAKS]
[SIGHS]
OH!
[GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
[SIGHS]
[BEEPING]
AH-OOH.
[SQUEAKING]
OOH.
[GASPS]
[SHUDDERING]
[SQUEAKING]
EVE!
AH.
AH-OOH-OOH!
EVE!
NO!
WHOA, WHOA.
[SQUEAKING]
AH!
AAH!
OOH-OOH-OH!
[BEEPING]
EVE!
OH!
[SCREAMING]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[SQUEAKING]
OH.
UH...UH-OH!
OOH.
OH!
EVE! OOH.
AHH.
[BEEPING]
[CHORD PLAYS]
OHH.
OOH.
AHH.
WHOA!
[BEEPING THROUGHOUT]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
EVE.
WHOA!
[BEEP]
[CHATTERING]
[BEEPING]
FOREIGN CONTAMINANT.
OOH.
[BEEPING]
[CHATTERING]
FOREIGN CONTAMINANT.
WHOA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA WHOA.
UH.
[MUTTERING]
UH!
AAH!
[CHATTERING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[BEEPING]
HA HA!
[CHATTERING]
MMM!
AAH!
[ALARM BLARING]
[BEEPING]
[DING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
AAH!
EVE!
HUH?
[CHATTERING]
[BEEPING]
FOREIGN CONTAMINANT.
[CHATTERING]
[WHIRRING]
[BEEP]
[CHATTERING]
[WHIRRING]
EVE.
[BEEP]
OOH.
AAH!
OHH-OOH!
UH, UH...
WHOA!
[CHATTERING]
[SQUEAKING]
[BEEPING]
EVE!
I'VE BEEN IN MY
CABIN ALL MORNING,
SO LET'S HOVER OVER
TO THE DRIVING RANGE
AND HIT A FEW VIRTUAL
BALLS INTO SPACE.
NO, WE DID THAT YESTERDAY.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
WELL, THEN WHAT DO
YOU WANT TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING.
WHOA!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
LOOK, I'M TIRED OF HAVING THE
SAME ARGUEMENT OVER AND OVER.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
BOT, OVER HERE.
HUH!
WHOA!
HELLO?
I'M IN A TUNNEL.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
THERE YOU ARE.
BUY N LARGE.
EVERYTHING YOU
NEED TO BE HAPPY.
YOUR DAY IS VERY
IMPORTANT TO US.
HEY, DRINKBOT.
HERE, TAKE A CUP.
HEY, TAKE THE CUP!
WHOA!
UH-OH.
OHH.
[BEEP]
PLEASE REMAIN STATIONARY.
A SERVICEBOT WILL BE HERE
TO ASSIST YOU MOMENTARILY.
STEWARDS! HELLO!
PLEASE REMAIN STATIONARY.
HELP.
A SERVICEBOT WILL BE HERE
TO ASSIST YOU MOMENTARILY.
WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
UHH!
[SIGHS]
WALL-E.
AHH. UH...JOHN.
EVE?
UH, NO.
JOHN.
EVE!
BYE, WALL-E.
"A" IS FOR AXIOM,
YOUR HOME SWEET HOME.
"B" IS FOR BUY N LARGE,
YOUR VERY BEST FRIEND.
MMM! TIME FOR
LUNCH...IN A CUP.
[ALL SLURPING]
FEEL BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S THE NEW YOU.
STUNNING.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I KNOW, HONEY. MEN.
ATTENTITON, AXIOM SHOPPERS.
TRY BLUE. IS THE NEW RED.
Both: OOH!
HMM.
OOH, LOVE BLUE.
DATE?
OH, DON'T GET ME STARTED
ON A DATE.
EVERY HOLO-DATE I HAVE
BEEN ON HAS BEEN A
VIRTUAL DISASTER.
IF I COULD JUST
MEET ONE
ONE WHO'S WASN'T
SO SUPERFICTAL?
[INDISTINCT]
THERE ARE NO GOOD
MEN OUT THERE.
WELL, I KNOW.
I KNOW BECAUSE I'VE--
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
WHAT THE...WHOA!
HUH?
YOO-HOO!
WALL-E.
UH...MARY.
EVE.
HUH?
OH! OH! OH.
UM, SURE.
YOU GO AHEAD.
EVE.
SHADE. [CLAPPING]
[WHIRRING]
I DIDN'T KNOW
WE HAD A POOL!
[TYPING AND WHIRRING]
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
[GASPS]
[BEEPING]
CAPTAIN, YOU ARE
NEEDED ON THE BRIDGE.
[SNORING]
[BEEPING]
[MUTTERING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
ALL HANDS ON DECK!
WHAT?
MORNING.
JUST A TRIM?
♪ WE'RE GONNA FIND ADVENTURE
IN THE EVENING AIR ♪
UH-HUH. OH, I SEE.
I KNOW, HONEY.
I KNOW.
I AM GOOD, I AM GOOD.
YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
♪ ...WE'RE GONNA
RIDE THROUGH TOWN ♪
OH!
♪ IN ONE OF THOSE
HORSE DAWN OPEN CARS ♪
♪ WE'LL SEE
THE SHOWS AT DELMONICO'S ♪
["BLUE DANUBE" PLAYING]
SIR?
COFFEE.
[GROANING]
SIR, THE ANNUAL...
PROTOCOL, AUTO.
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
COMPUTER, STATUS REPORT.
MECHANICAL SYSTEMS.
UNCHANGED.
REACTOR CORE
TEMPERATURE.
UNCHANGED.
PASSENGER COUNT.
REGENERATIVE
FOOD BUFFET.
UNCHANGED.
JACUZZI PI BALANCE.
ATMOSPHERIC CONDITIONS.
UNCHANGED.
LAUNDRY SERVICE VOLUME.
OK, AUTO.
SIR, THE ANNUAL
RECONNAISSANCE...
12:30!
AUTO, WHY DIDN'T YOU WAKE ME
FOR MORNING ANNOUNCEMENTS?
HONESTLY, IT'S THE ONE THING
I GET TO DO ON THIS SHIP.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
WELL, GOOD MORNING,
EVERYBODY,
AND WELCOME TO DAY 255,642
ABOARD THE "AXIOM."
AS ALWAYS, THE WEATHER IS
A BALMY 72 DEGREES AND SUNNY
AND, UH...OH, HEY.
I SEE THE SHIP'S LOG
IS SHOWING THAT TODAY
IS OUR 700th ANNIVERSARY
OF OUR
FIVE-YEAR CRUISE.
WELL, I'M SURE OUR FOREFATHERS
WOULD BE PROUD TO KNOW THAT
700 YEARS LATER WE'D BE
DOING THE EXACT SAME THING
THEY WERE DOING.
FORE!
SO...
BE SURE NEXT
MEALTIME TO ASK
FOR YOUR "FREE"
SEPTUACENTENNIAL
CUPCAKE IN A CUP.
WOW, LOOK AT THAT!
ALSO TODAY WE HAVE A, UH...
[BEEPING]
HEY, AUTO, WHAT'S THAT
FLASHING BUTTON?
CAPTAIN, PROBE ONE
HAS RETURNED POSITIVE.
POSITIVE?
[WHIRRING]
EVE.
BUT NO PROBE'S EVER COME
BACK POSITIVE BEFORE.
[BEEPING]
[ALARM BLARING]
♪ BUY N LARGE ♪
GREETINGS AND
CONGRATULATIONS, CAPTAIN.
IF YOU'RE SEEING THIS,
THAT MEANS YOUR EXTRATERRESTRIAL
VEGETATION EVALUATOR,
OR EVE PROBE,
HAS RETURNED FROM EARTH
WHAT A CONFIRMED SPECIMEN
OF ONGOING PHOTOSYNTHESIS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT MEANS IT'S TIME
TO GO BACK HOME.
HOME?
WE'RE GOING BACK?
NOW THAT EARTH
HAS BEEN RESTORED
TO A LIFE-SUSTAINING
STATUS, BY GOLLY,
WE CAN BEGIN
OPERATION RE-COLONIZE.
SIMPLY FOLLOW THIS MANUAL'S
INSTRUCTIONS TO PLACE
THE PLANT IN YOUR SHIP'S
HOLO-DETECTOR
AND THE "AXIOM"
WILL IMMEDIATELY NAVIGATE
YOUR RETURN TO EARTH.
IT'S THAT EASY.
HUH!
NOW, DUE TO THE EFFECTS
OF MICROGRAVITY
YOU AND YOUR PASSENGERS
MAY HAVE SUFFERED
SOME SLIGHT BONE LOSS.
BUT I'M SURE A FEW LAPS
AROUND THE SHIP'S JOGGING TRACK
WE'LL GET YOU BACK
IN A SHAPE IN NO TIME.
WE HAVE
A JOGGING TRACK?
IF YOU HAVE ANY
FURTHER QUESTIONS,
JUST CONSULT YOUR
OPERATION MANUAL.
SEE YOU BACK HOME REAL SOON.
♪ BNL ♪
"OPERATE MANUEL".
UH...
MANUEL!
RELAY INSTRUCTIONS.
MANUEL?
[WHIRRING]
WOW.
WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT?
OK, LET'S SEE.
[INDISTINCT]
HUH?
EVE.
WALL-E!
[BEEPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
WELL, LET'S OPEN HER UP.
"STEP ONE.
"VOICE COMMAND,
CONFIRM ACQUISTION."
CONFIRMED ACQUISITION.
[BEEPING]
VOICE AUTHORIZATION REQUIRED.
UH...
ACCEPTED.
[BEEPING]
AHH! OOH!
WELL, WHERE'S
THE THINGY?
PLANT.
PLANT. RIGHT. RIGHT.
WHERE IS IT?
MAYBE WE MISSED A STEP.
SHOW ME HOW TO
CHANGE THE--
PLANT.
OK.
WALL-E.
WALL-E!
[WHIRRING AND BEEPING]
EVE?
PLANT!
AAH!
WHY DON'T YOU SCAN
HER TO BE SURE?
CONTAINS NO SPECIMEN.
PROBE'S MEMORY IS FAULTY.
SO THEN, WE'RE NOT
GOING TO EARTH?
NEGATIVE.
I GUESS THINGS GO
BACK TO NORMAL, HUH?
CORRECT, CAPTAIN.
WELL, FALSE ALARM!
FALSE ALARM.
THE PROBE
MUST BE DEFECTIVE.
[SIGHS]
GOFER, SEND HER TO
THE REPAIR WARD,
AND HAVE THEM RUN
DIAGNOSTICS ON HER.
MAKE SURE SHE'S
NOT--AAH!
[WHIRRING]
WALL-E.
HAVE, UH, WALL-E CLEANED.
YOO-HOO!
EVE.
HMM?
OHH.
ANALYSE.
[BEEPING]
ANALYSIS.
FOREGIN CONTAMINANT.
SUBSTANCE IS A
THREE-PHASE SYSTEM
COMPOSED OF VARIOUS COMBINATIONS
OF NATURALLY DERIVED SOLIDS.
SUBJECT IS MOST
COMMONLY REFERRED
TO AS SOIL, DIRT,
OR EARTH.
EARTH?
[SIGHS]
DEFINE "EARTH".
EARTH, THE SURFACE OF
THE WORLD
AS DISTINCT FROM
THE SKY OR SEA.
WOW.
DEFINE "SEA".
SEA, AN EXPANSE OF
SALT WATER THAT COVERS MOST
OF EARTH'S SURFACE AND
SURROUNDS ITS LANDMASS.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BUZZING]
FOREIGN CONTAINMANT.
OOH!
[SCREECHING]
[BEEPING]
AH.
OH! EVE!
[BEEPING]
WHOA!
[ECHOING] JUST A TRIM?
UH-HUH. YOU
LOOK GORGEOUS.
UH-OH.
WHOA!
OH.
FORE!
EVE!
OH!
CLEAR. CLEAR.
[BEEPING]
WHOA!
[LAUGHING]
[SQUEAKING]
OOH-OOH-OOH!
WHOA!
[BUZZING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
EVE! EVE! EVE!
[BEEP]
AH!
WALL-E!
UH!
[BEEPING]
OOH.
[ALARM BLARING]
WALL-E!
[BEEPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
THROUGHOUT]
WALL-E!
[ALARM BLARING]
[BEEP]
OH, MY.
HALT.
[SHUDDERING]
WALL-E!
WHOA!
CAUTION.
ROUGE ROBOTS.
[CROWD GASPS]
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
AAH! WALL-E!
[BEEPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
HALT, HALT.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
AHH.
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
WALL-E!
[MARCHING]
CLEAR.
[ALARM BLARING]
OOH.
[BEEPING]
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
UH-OH. EVE.
[WHIRRING]
EVE?
EARTH.
[WHIRRING]
OOH.
AH.
DIRECTIVE.
OH!
[WHIRRING]
WALL-E.
[BEEP]
UH-OH!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS] PLANT.
[BEEPING]
WALL-E. [GASPS]
EVE!
WALL-E!
[EXPLOSION]
AAH!
CRUISING SPEED.
YOU ARE NOW FREE TO
MOVE ABOUT THE CABIN.
OH.
AH!
[WHIRRING]
OH!
20 SECONDS
TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
AH!
WHOA.
[BEEPING]
10 SECONDS TO
SELF-DESTRUCT.
AAH!
10, 9, 8, 7,
6, 5, 4,
3, 2...
NO.
AAH!
WALL-E!
[WHIRRING]
AAH!
WALL-E!
OH!
EVE!
OH.
[SIGHS]
OOH.
[WHIRRING]
WALL-E.
EVE.
[BEEPING]
[GASPS] WALL-E!
WALL-E!
WHOA!
HUH? OHH.
AHH.
[BEEPING]
WALL-E.
[WHIRRING]
[LAUGHTER]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
OHH!
OH, SO MANY STARS.
OH.
OH! OH, HEY!
HEY! THAT'S WHAT'S-HIS-NAME!
OH!
HEY! WHAT THE--
LOOK! LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT? HEY.
I KNOW THAT GUY.
IT'S, UH, UH, WALL-E.
THAT'S IT! HEY, WALL-E!
HI, WALL-E!
IT'S YOUR BUDDY, JOHN.
HEY!
[GASPS]
HI.
DEFINE "HOEDOWN".
HOEDOWN, A SOCIAL GATHERING
AT WHICH LIVELY DANCING
WOULD TAKE PLACE.
AUTO, EARTH IS AMAZING!
THESE ARE
CALLED "FARMS."
HUMANS WOULD PUT SEEDS
IN THE GROUND,
POUR WATER ON THEM,
AND THEY GROW FOOD,
LIKE PIZZA.
GOOD NIGHT, CAPTAIN.
AW.
PSST! COMPUTER.
DEFINE "DANCING."
DANCING, A SERIES
OF MOVEMENTS INVOLVING
TWO PARTNERS
WHERE SPEED AND RHYTHM
MATCH HARMONIOUSLY
WITH MUSIC.
UH-HUH. UH...
EVE.
HOME.
[CRASH]
[MUTTERING]
[BANGING]
UH-OH.
THE LIDO DECK IS NOW CLOSING.
[LAUGHTER]
HEY, STOP THAT.
MAKE ME.
I DIDN'T KNOW
WE HAD A POOL.
NO SPLASHING.
NO DIVING.
OH, GO ON.
[VOICE DISTORTED]
NO SPLASHING, NO DI...
HUH?
[BEEPING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
EVE.
♪ ...TAKES A MOMENT ♪
OH! SHH!
[TURNS OFF MUSIC]
DIRE--DIRECTIVE.
[EXHALING]
PREPARE FOR LANDING.
SHH! ER!
"WE'RE HERE, EVERYBODY."
"YAY, CAPTAIN!
CAPTAIN, WE'RE HOME!
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL!"
"NO, IT'S NOTHING.
"I WAS PLEASED
TO DO THIS.
IT'S ALL
ABOUT YOU PEOPLE
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME."
[RATTLING]
HOW?
HOW DID YOU FIND IT?
[BEEPING]
WE CAN GO BACK HOME!
FOR THE FIRST TIME!
WHAT'S IT LIKE NOW?
OH!
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T TELL ME.
I WANNA SEE
FOR MYSELF.
[BEEP]
ER.
[BEEPING]
WAIT.
THAT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE EARTH.
WHERE'S
THE BLUE SKY?
[WHIRRING]
WHERE'S THE GRASS?
[SQUEAKING]
♪ ...SUNDAY CLOTHES
WHEN YOU FEEL DOWN AND OUT ♪
I KNOW THAT SONG.
♪ STRUT DOWN THE STREET AND
HAVE YOUR PICTURE TOOK... ♪
THEY'RE, UM...
DANCING.
YES, DANCING.
♪ THAT SUNDAY SHINE
IS A CERTAIN SIGN ♪
♪ THAT YOU FEEL AS
FINE AS YOU LOOK ♪
♪ BENEATH YOUR PARASOL... ♪
YOU MADE IT SOMEHOW,
HUH, LITTLE GUY?
YOU DIDN'T GIVE UP,
DID YOU?
[GASPS]
[MUTTERING]
WAIT A MINUTE.
♪ ...WHEN TIME
RUNS OUT ♪
♪ THAT IT ONLY... ♪
HUH?
[BEEPING]
EVE?
EVE!
[THUNDER]
UH-OH!
WALL-E.
EVE?
EVE.
PATHETIC.
EVE!
OH!
[WHIRRING]
HUH?
FOREIGN CONTAINMANT.
OOH.
[BUZZING]
THERE YOU GO,
LITTLE GUY.
YOU CAME A LONG
WAY FOR A DRINK OF WATER.
JUST NEEDED SOMEONE TO
LOOK AFTER YA, THAT'S ALL.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
WE'VE HAVE TO GO BACK.
AUTO, COME DOWN HERE.
AYE-AYE, SIR.
WALL-E.
[SIGHS]
[WHIRRING]
AUTO, EVE
FOUND THE PLANT.
FIRE UP THE HOLO-DETECTOR.
NOT NESCESSARY, CAPTAIN.
YOU MAY GIVE IT TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SHOULD DO IT
FOR MYSELF.
CAPTAIN.
SIR, I INSIST YOU
GIVE ME THE PLANT.
AUTO, GET OUT OF
MY WAY.
WE CANNOT GO HOME.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHY NOT?
THAT IS CLASSIFIED, CAPTAIN.
GIVE ME THE PLANT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"CLASSIFIED?"
YOU DON'T KEEP A
SECRET FROM THE CAPTAIN.
GIVE ME THE PLANT.
TELL ME WHAT'S CLASSIFIED.
THE PLANT.
TELL ME, AUTO!
THAT'S AN ORDER.
AYE-AYE, SIR.
♪ BUY N LARGE ♪
♪ IT'S YOUR SUPERSTORE ♪
♪ WE GOT ALL
YOU NEED... ♪
JUST CUT IT OFF,
WILL YOU?
HEY THERE, AUTOPILOTS.
GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
UM...
OPERATION CLEANUP HAS
WELL, UH, FAILED.
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW, RISING
TOXICITY LEVELS
HAVE MADE LIFE UNSUSTAINABLE
ON EARTH.
UNSUSTAINABLE?
WHAT?
UH, DARN IT ALL, WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO...
CANCEL OPERATION
RE-COLONIZE.
SO, JUST...STAY
THE COURSE.
UM, RATHER THAN TRY
AND FIX THIS PROBLEM
IT'LL JUST BE EASIER FOR
EVERYONE REMAIN IN SPACE.
EASIER?
MR. PRESIDENT? SIR.
I THINK--HUH?
IT'S TIME TO GO.
OK, I'M GIVING OVERDRIVE
DIRECTIVE A113.
GO TO FULL AUTOPILOT.
TAKE CONTROL OF EVERYTHING
AND DO NOT RETURN TO EARTH.
REPEAT, DO NOT
RETURN TO EARTH.
LET'S GET THE HECK
OUT OF HERE.
NOW, THE PLANT.
NO. WAIT A MINUTE.
COMPUTER, WHEN WAS THAT
MESSAGE SEND OUT TO THE "AXIOM"?
MESSAGE RECEIVED
IN THE YEAR 2110.
THAT'S, UH...THAT'S
NEARLY 700 YEARS AGO!
AUTO, THINGS HAVE CHANGED!
WE'VE GOT TO GO BACK.
SIR, ORDERS ARE "DO
NOT RETURNS TO EARTH."
BUT LIFE IS SUSTAINABLE NOW.
LOOK AT THIS PLANT.
GREEN AND GROWING.
IT'S LIVING PROOF
HE WAS WRONG.
IRRELEVANT, CAPTAIN.
WHAT?
IT'S COMPLETELY RELEVANT!
OUT THERE IS OUR HOME.
HOME, AUTO.
AND IT'S IN TROUBLE.
I CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND DO NOTHING.
THAT'S ALL I'VE EVER DONE.
THAT'S ALL ANYONE ON THIS
BLASTED SHIP HAS EVER DONE.
NOTHING!
ON THE "AXIOM"
YOU WILL SURVIVE.
I DON'T WANT TO SURVIVE!
I WANT TO LIVE!
MUST FOLLOW
MY DIRECTIVE.
AAH!
I'M THE CAPTAIN
OF THE "AXIOM."
WE ARE GOING HOME TODAY.
OOH!
[ALARM BLARING]
GO!
GO?
[BEEPING]
HEY! THAT'S NOT--
THIS IS MUTINY!
EVE, ARREST HIM.
[INDISTINCT]
EVE, YOU ARE TO PUT
THE PLANT STRAIGHT
IN THE HOLO-DETECTOR.
NO!
[INDISTINCT]
[WHIRRING]
HUH?
EVE?
WALL-E!
EVE!
OH!
UH-OH.
WALL-E, THE PLANT!
WALL-E!
OVER HERE.
THROW IT!
AHH!
EVE! AAH!
GIVE ME THE PLANT.
[GRUNTING]
NO!
[BUZZING]
[BEEPING]
[GROANING]
WALL-E!
[BEEPING]
ALL COMUNICATIONS
ARE TERMINATED.
YOU ARE CONFINED TO QUARTERS.
NO! MUTINY! MUTINY!
[WHIRRING]
HA! WALL-E?
CAUTION.
ACTIVATING AIRLOCK DISPOSAL.
WALL-E!
[WHIRRING]
ACTIVATING AIRLOCK DISPOSAL.
AAH! WALL-E!
[LOUD GURGLING]
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
EVE.
WALL-E!
CAUTION.
ACTIVATING AIRLOCK DISPOSAL.
[SCREAMING]
WALL-E!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPING]
FOREIGN CONTAINMANT.
HUH?
OHH!
AH..UH!
UH!
[INDISTINCT]
[GROANING]
[BEEPING]
WALL-E.
[WHIRRING]
[BEEPING]
ALL CLEAN. ALL CLEAN.
[INDISTINCT]
[GROANING]
WALL-E.
MO.
[WHIRRING]
MO?
MO.
HMM?
[GROANING]
AHH.
DIRECTIVE.
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
OOH.
[GROANING]
EARTH.
[SQUEAKING]
EARTH! EARTH?! OHH!
WA--
MO.
WALL-E!
[SIREN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
WRONG.
[SHUDDERING]
[BEEPING]
[ALARM BLARING]
PLEASE HOLD. WE ARE
CURRENTLY HAVING--
EVE!
WHOOPS.
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
[BEEPING TO THE TUNE
OF "SUNDAY CLOTHES"]
UHH...
[MUSIC PLAYING]
ACHOO!
OH, THAT STYLE SUITS YOU.
♪ WE'RE GONNA FIND ADVENTURE
IN THE EVENING AIR ♪
CLEAR.
OOH.
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
AH!
NOT POSSIBLE.
ROUGE ROBOTS.
[BEEPING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
AUTO! AUTO!
MUTINY. MUTINY.
STUPID WHEEL.
CAUTION. ROUGE ROBOTS.
THE PLANT! HA HA HA!
WE'LL SEE WHO'S
POWERLESS NOW.
[BEEP]
[MUMBLING]
AAH!
TESTING, TESTING.
IS THIS THING ON?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
HEY, THIS IS THE CAPTAIN.
I AM LOCKED IN MY ROOM.
EVE, WALL-E, BRING
THE PLANT TO THE LIDO DECK.
I'LL HAVE ACTIVATED
THE HOLO-DETECTOR.
NOW, HURRY.
AUTO'S PROBABLY GOING
TO CUT ME OFF...
HALT.
AH!
OH, MY.
[WHIRRING]
CLEAR.
OH!
[WHIRRING]
HALT, HALT.
[BEEPING]
HA HA! LOOK WHAT I GOT, AUTO.
NOT POSSIBLE.
HA HA. THAT'S RIGHT.
THE PLANT.
OH, YOU WANT IT?
COME AND GET IT, BLINKY.
NO.
UH! HA HA!
CAPTAIN?
AAH!
LET GO.
LET...GO.
TO HEAVY FOR YA?
HUH? HUH?
AAH!
GET OFF.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET
AWAY FROM ME, ONE-EYE.
GET OFF.
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
[BEEPING]
GET OUT!
[PANTING]
HALT.
[WHIRRING]
AAH! A LITTLE CLOSER.
CEASE AND DESIST.
NOT GOOD.
GOT YA. HA HA HA!
[ALARM BLARING]
AAH!
[SNORING]
WHOA!
WHOA, WHOA.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BABIES CRYING]
SHH!
REMAIN CALM.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS YOUR CAPTAIN
SPEAKING.
WE'RE HAVING A
SLIGHT MALFUNCTION
WITH THE AUTOPILOT.
PLEASE REMAIN CALM.
Crowd: OOH!
[BEEPING]
AAH!
ENOUGH.
UH...UH!
HEY.
[INDISTINCT]
WHOA!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[BEEPING]
NO!
NO. NO, NO, NO.
OH!
[YELLING]
AAH! OH!
JOHN, GET READY
TO HAVE SOME KIDS.
OH!
[LAUGHTER]
[SCREAMING]
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
[BEEPING]
WHOA!
NO.
[BEEPING]
[GROANING]
WALL-E!
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
[ZAPPING]
NO!
UH-OH.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[CROWD GASPING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[GRUNTING]
AUTO?
[SCREAMING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
WALL-E!
[GRUNTING]
AH! AUTO, YOU ARE
RELIVED OF DUTY.
NO.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[WHIRRING]
PLANT!
[CROWD MURMURING]
[BEEPING]
FOREIGN CONTAMINANT.
[WHIRS]
PLANT!
AH!
AC-HOO!
[CROWD MURMURING]
[BEEP]
PLANT ORIGIN VERTIFIED.
[CROWD MURMURING]
[BEEP]
[GASPS]
OH, WALL-E.
COURSE SET FOR EARTH.
10 SECONDS TO HYPERJUMP. 9...
NO.
8...
WALL-E!
7, 6, 5...
OH, NO. WALL-E.
4...
3, 2, 1, ZERO.
[SCREAMING]
WALL-E!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SQUEAKING]
[WHIRRING]
[CROWD MURMURING]
[GASPS]
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAKING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
WALL-E.
EVE!
[WHIRRING]
[BEEPING]
HUH?
[BEEP BEEP BEEP]
[CHORD PLAYS]
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAKING]
[WHIRS]
WALL-E.
OOH!
EVE.
[BEEP] OOH.
WALL-E?
[WHIRRING]
[WHIRS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OOH.
[RATTLING]
WALL-E?
[SQUEAKING]
[INDISTINCT]
[WHIRRING]
WALL-E?
WALL-E!
[HUMMING]
[WHIRS]
[BEEP]
[WHIRRING]
EVE?
WALL-E?
OOH. EVE.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ AND THAT IS ALL ♪
♪ THAT LOVES ABOUT ♪
WHEE!
YOU'RE KIDDING!
GO. GO, GO. GO,
GO, GO.
♪ WHEN TIME RUNS OUT ♪
THIS IS CALLED FARMING.
YOU KIDS ARE GONNA
GROW ALL KINDS OF PLANTS.
VEGETABLE PLANTS,
PIZZA PLANTS!
HA HA HA!
AHH, IT'S GOOD TO
BE HOME!
♪ TOOK A MOMENT ♪
♪ TO BE LOVED ♪
♪ A WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ LONG ♪
[CLICK]
♪ DID YOU THINK THAT YOUR
FEET HAVE BEEN BOUND ♪
♪ BY WHAT GRAVITY BRINGS
TO THE GROUND? ♪
♪ DID YOU FEEL THAT
YOU WERE TRICKED ♪
♪ BY THE FUTURE
YOU PICKED? ♪
♪ WELL, COME ON DOWN ♪
♪ ALL THESE RULES DON'T APPLY
WHEN YOU'RE HIGH IN THE SKY ♪
♪ SO COME ON DOWN ♪
♪ COME ON DOWN ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO BETTER
PLACE TO GO ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT SNOW
UPON THE MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT RIVERS
DOWN BELOW ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ WE HEAR THE BIRDS
SINGING THE TREES ♪
♪ AND THE LAND WILL
BE LOOKED AFTER ♪
♪ WE SEND THE SEEDS
OUT IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ DID YOU THINK YOU
ESCAPED FROM ROUTINE ♪
♪ BY CHANGING THE SCRIPT
AND THE SCENE? ♪
♪ DESPITE ALL YOU
MADE OF IT ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS AFRAID
OF THE CHANGE ♪
♪ YOU GOT A LOT
ON YOUR CHEST ♪
♪ WELL, YOU CAN COME
AS MY GUEST ♪
♪ SO COME ON DOWN ♪
♪ COME ON DOWN ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO BETTER
PLACE TO GO ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT SNOW
UPON THE MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT RIVERS
DOWN BELOW ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ WE HEAR THE BIRDS
SINGING THE TREES ♪
♪ AND THE LAND WILL
BE LOOKED AFTER ♪
♪ WE SEND THE SEEDS
OUT IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ LIKE THE FISH IN
THE OCEAN ♪
♪ WE FELT A HOME
IN THE SEA ♪
♪ WE LEARNED TO LIVE
OFF THE GOOD LANDS ♪
♪ WE LEARNED TO CLIMB
UP THE TREE ♪
♪ THEN WE GOT UP
OUR TWO LEGS ♪
♪ BUT WE WANTED TO FLY ♪
♪ AND WHEN WE MESSED
UP OUR HOMELAND ♪
♪ WE SET SAIL FOR
THE SKY ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO BETTER
PLACE TO GO ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT SNOW
UPON THE MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT RIVERS
DOWN BELOW ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ WE HEAR THE BIRDS
SINGING THE TREES ♪
♪ AND THE LAND WILL
BE LOOKED AFTER ♪
♪ WE SEND THE SEEDS
OUT IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN ♪
♪ COMING DOWN TO EARTH ♪
♪ LIKE BABIES AT BIRTH ♪
♪ WE DEFINE NEW
PRIORITIES ♪
♪ THESE ARE EXTRAORDINARY
QUALLITIES ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO BETTER
PLACE TO GO ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT SNOW
UPON THE MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT RIVERS
DOWN BELOW ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ WE HEAR THE BIRDS
SINGING THE TREES ♪
♪ AND THE LAND WILL
BE LOOKED AFTER ♪
♪ WE SEND THE SEEDS
OUT IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ THERE'S NO BETTER
PLACE TO GO ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT SNOW
UPON THE MOUNTAINS ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT RIVERS
DOWN BELOW ♪
♪ WE'RE COMING DOWN
TO THE GROUND ♪
♪ WE HEAR THE BIRDS
SINGING THE TREES ♪
♪ AND THE LAND WILL
BE LOOKED AFTER ♪
♪ WE SEND THE SEEDS
OUT IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ WE DEFINE NEW
PRIORITIES ♪
♪ THESE ARE EXTRAORDINARY
QUALITIES ♪
♪ TO FIND THE EARTH ♪
♪ COMING DOWN ♪
[NEW MUSIC BEGINS]
[CHIMING]
[TAPPING AND SPRING RATTLING]
[SCRAPES]
[WHIRRING]
[SQUEAKING]
[WHIRS]
[HUMMING]
YOO-HOO.
[BEEP]
[CHIRPS]
THERE.
[CLICK]
Choirs: ♪ BNL ♪