(PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES PLAYING)
♪♪ Out there
There's a world outside of Yonkers ♪♪
♪♪ Way out there
beyond this hick town, Barnaby ♪♪
♪♪ There's a slick town, Barnaby ♪♪
♪♪ Out there
Full of shine and full of sparkle ♪♪
♪♪ Close your eyes
and see it glisten, Barnaby ♪♪
♪♪ Listen, Barnaby ♪♪
♪♪ Put on your Sunday clothes
There's lots of world out there ♪♪
♪♪ Get out the brilliantine
and dime cigars ♪♪
♪♪ We're gonna find adventure
in the evening air ♪♪
♪♪ Girls in white in a perfumed night ♪♪
♪♪ Where the lights are
bright as the stars ♪♪
♪♪ Put on your Sunday clothes
We're gonna ride through town ♪♪
♪♪ in one of those new
horsedrawn open cars ♪♪
♪♪ We'll see the shows at Delmonico's ♪♪
♪♪ And we'll close the town in a whirl ♪♪
♪♪ And we won't come home
until we've kissed a girl ♪♪
(WIND HOWLING)
♪♪... ride through town ♪♪
♪♪ in one of those new
horsedrawn open cars ♪♪
♪♪ We'll see the shows
at Delmonico's... ♪♪
♪♪ And we won't come home
until we've kissed a girl ♪♪
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPS)
(CHIRPING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Oh!
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(EXCLAIMS CURIOUSLY)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(WHISTLES)
(CHIRPS)
(SHUDDERING)
Huh.
(JINGLE PLAYING ON P.A.)
♪♪ Buy N Large is your superstore ♪♪
♪♪ We got all you need
and so much more ♪♪
(CHATTERING)
(COCKROACH SQUEAKING)
(WALL-E SQUAWKS)
(COCKROACH SQUEAKING HAPPILY)
MALE VOICE: Too much garbage
in your face?
There's plenty of space out in space!
BNL star liners leaving each day.
We'll clean up the mess
while you're away!
The jewel of the BNL fleet, the Axiom.
Spend your five-year cruise in style,
waited on 24 hours a day
by our fully automated crew,
while your captain and autopilot
chart a course for nonstop
entertainment, fine dining,
and with our all-access hoverchairs,
even Grandma can join the fun.
There's no need to walk.
The Axiom.
Putting the star in executive star liner.
Because at BNL,
space is the final fun-tier!
(STATIC BUZZING)
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
(HUMMING CHEERFULLY)
(WALL-E WHISTLES)
(PUT ON YOUR
SUNDAY CLOTHES PLAYING)
♪♪ No Monday in your Sunday ♪♪
♪♪ No Monday in your
Sunday clothes ♪♪
(HUMMING)
♪♪ Put on your Sunday clothes
when you feel down and out ♪♪
♪♪ Strut down the street
and have your picture took ♪♪
♪♪ Dressed like a dream
Your spirits seem to turn about ♪♪
♪♪ That Sunday shine is a certain sign ♪♪
Oh-ho!
♪♪ That you feel as fine as you look ♪♪
(IT ONLY TAKES
A MOMENT PLAYING)
♪♪ And we'll recall ♪♪
Wow!
♪♪ When time runs out ♪♪
Ahh.
Whoa.
♪♪ That it only ♪♪
♪♪ took a moment ♪♪
♪♪ to be loved ♪♪
♪♪ a whole life ♪♪
♪♪ long ♪♪
(RATTLING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(IT ONLY TAKES
A MOMENT PLAYING)
♪♪ And that is all ♪♪
♪♪ that love's about ♪♪
(ALARM SOUNDING)
Uh-oh.
(WARBLES)
Oh...
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
(WHISTLES)
(SQUEAKS)
(MOTOR WHIRRING)
(SQUEAKING)
♪♪... a moment ♪♪
(SIGHING)
♪♪ to be loved ♪♪
♪♪ a whole life ♪♪
(METALLIC CREAKING)
♪♪ long ♪♪
(BEEPING)
(WALL-E GROANING)
(GROANING)
(CLANGING)
(GROANS)
(CLANKS)
(MUTTERING)
(MOANING)
(BEEPING)
(ELECTRONIC BELL CHIMING)
(WHIRRING)
(SKITTERING)
(COCKROACH SQUEAKING)
(SIGHS CONTENTEDLY)
(SQUELCHES)
(SCREAMS)
Aw!
(WALL-E EXHALES IN RELIEF)
(SHUDDERING)
(WHISTLING)
Whoa!
(SQUEAKS)
(KEYS RATTLING)
(CAR ALARM CHIRPS)
(GRUNTING)
(WHISTLES)
Whoa.
Ooh!
(SCREAMING)
(CLANGS)
(KNOCKING)
Ooh!
(CHIRPS)
(WHISTLES)
(BLEEPS)
Huh?
Whoa!
(BLEEPS)
Ha!
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
Aha!
Uh...
(SHIP RUMBLING)
(WARBLING IN CONFUSION)
(YELPS)
(SCREAMING)
(WALL-E SCREAMING)
(ENGINES POWERING DOWN)
(SHUDDERING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHOOSHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(PANICKING)
(SCREAMS)
(DESCENDING WHOOSH)
(METALLIC CLANGING)
(ELECTRONIC WARBLING)
(WHINING)
Whoa!
(BEEPING)
(BUZZES)
(CLANGING)
(WALL-E YELPS SOFTLY)
(ENGINES POWERING UP)
(RUMBLING)
(SHUDDERING)
(EVE BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
Whoa!
(ZIPPING)
(WHISTLES APPRECIATIVELY)
(SONIC BOOM)
(COOING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(COCKROACH SQUEAKS)
(RUMBLING)
(WEAPON DRONING)
(CHATTERING IN FEAR)
(BEEPING)
(ELECTRONIC SCANNING)
(BEEPS)
(BEEPING)
(COCKROACH CHIRPS)
(WALL-E EXCLAIMS WORRIEDLY)
(SHUDDERING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SQUEAKS)
EVE: Ooh!
(GASPS)
(LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLES)
(WALL-E SCREAMING IN ALARM)
Who are you?
(WALL-E SHUDDERING)
EVE: Who are you?
Who are you?
(COCKROACH SQUEAKING)
(BEEPING)
(BUZZES)
(SIGHS)
(LA VIE EN ROSE PLAYING)
(SCANNING AND BEEPING)
(WALL-E SCREAMS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(YELPING)
(SCREAMING)
♪♪ Hold me close and hold me fast ♪♪
♪♪ The magic spell you cast ♪♪
♪♪ This is la vie en rose ♪♪
(EVE EXCLAIMS)
♪♪ When you kiss me heaven sighs ♪♪
♪♪ And though I close my eyes ♪♪
♪♪ I see la vie en rose ♪♪
WALL-E: Whoa!
(CLATTERING)
♪♪ When you press me to your heart ♪♪
(SCURRYING)
♪♪ I'm in a world apart ♪♪
♪♪ A world where roses bloom ♪♪
♪♪ And when you speak
Angels sing from above ♪♪
♪♪ Everyday words seem
to turn into love songs ♪♪
(EXCLAIMS)
Hmm.
(SIGHS DISAPPOINTEDLY)
(YELPS)
(BUZZES)
(EVE GRUMBLING)
(BUZZES ANGRILY)
Uh-oh.
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(WALL-E WHISTLING CASUALLY)
(WHISTLING CASUALLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(EVE SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
(WALL-E WHISTLES)
(EVE INQUIRING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGES)
WALL-E: Huh?
(EVE INQUIRING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
EVE: Directive?
Oh!
(WALL-E TITTERING)
(SHUDDERING)
WALL-E: Ta-da!
EVE: Ooh!
- (ENUNCIATING) Directive?
- Directive?
Classified.
Oh.
EVE: Name?
(HESITANTLY)
(STAMMERS)
WALL-E.
(SIGHS)
(GIGGLES)
EVE.
(STRUGGLING)
E... Ah!
"EVE. EVE."
EVE.
(LAUGHING)
WALL-E: EVE.
EVE: "EVE."
(ALARM SOUNDING)
WALL-E: EVE...
EVE! EVE! EVE!
(SCREAMS)
WALL-E! WALL-E!
(WIND ROARING)
(SNEEZES)
(SIGHS)
Oh.
EVE.
(WALL-E WHISTLES)
(WALL-E HUMMING SOFTLY)
(SQUEAKING)
Ooh!
(DON'T WORRY, BE HAPPY PLAYING)
♪♪ Here is a little song I wrote ♪♪
(EXCLAIMS)
♪♪... note for note
Don't worry ♪♪
(WALL-E EXCLAIMS)
♪♪ Be happy ♪♪
(WALL-E WHISTLES)
(EXCLAIMS ENTHUSIASTICALLY)
Here.
(GASPS)
(EVE WARBLES)
WALL-E: Look.
(POPPING)
Pop.
You pop.
(POPS)
(EVE GIGGLES)
(WALL-E WHISTLES)
(POPPING RAPIDLY)
EVE: Ooh!
(WHISTLES)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
EVE: Oops.
(WALL-E SCREAMS)
(MUTTERING NERVOUSLY)
(GROANING IN CONCERN)
(STATIC BUZZING)
(PUT ON YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES
PLAYING)
♪♪ Monday in your Sunday ♪♪
EVE: Ooh!
♪♪ No Monday in your Sunday clothes ♪♪
♪♪ Put on your Sunday clothes
when you feel down and out ♪♪
(WALL-E HUMMING ALONG)
♪♪ Strut down the street
and have your picture took ♪♪
♪♪ Dressed like a dream
Your spirits seem to turn about ♪♪
♪♪ That Sunday shine is a certain sign ♪♪
♪♪ That you feel as fine as you look ♪♪
(WALL-E BECKONS)
♪♪... new down to your toes ♪♪
♪♪ Get out your feathers
Your patent leathers ♪♪
(WALL-E HUMMING)
♪♪ Your beads and buckles and bows ♪♪
(EXCLAIMING IN GROWING ALARM)
(CRASHING)
(WALL-E GRUNTS)
WALL-E?
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(WARBLES IN CONCERN)
WALL-E: Whoa! Uh-oh!
Whoa!
Uh...
(WALL-E MUTTERING)
(GRUNTS)
Ha!
(EVE WARBLES)
Ooh!
WALL-E: (IN AWE) Oh!
(IT ONLY TAKES
A MOMENT PLAYING)
♪♪ And that is all ♪♪
♪♪ that love's about ♪♪
♪♪ And we'll recall ♪♪
♪♪ When time runs out ♪♪
♪♪ That it only ♪♪
(WALL-E WARBLES)
EVE: Ooh!
♪♪ took a moment ♪♪
♪♪ to be loved ♪♪
EVE!
♪♪ a whole life ♪♪
♪♪ long ♪♪
(EXCLAIMS)
(GIGGLES)
Hmm?
Ooh!
(BEEPING)
(BLEEPING)
(ENGINES POWERING UP)
(WALL-E SHUDDERING)
(STEADY PULSING)
WALL-E: Whoa.
EVE.
EVE?
(EXCLAIMS SOFTLY)
EVE!
(INSISTENTLY) EVE!
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
(RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
WALL-E: Whoa!
(WALL-E SCREAMING)
(SQUEAKS)
(SIGHS)
Ah!
(GRUNTING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GAME BEEPING)
(SIGHS)
(COCKROACH SQUEAKING)
(WIND GUSTS)
Uh-oh.
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
(WALL-E CHATTERING)
(COCKROACH CHATTERING)
EVE!
(WALL-E YELLING)
No!
(CHATTERING)
Whoa!
(EXCLAIMS)
(SQUEAKS)
(YELPS)
(EXCLAIMING IN ALARM)
(RUMBLING)
(ENGINES FIRING)
EVE.
(YELPS)
Whoa!
(WALL-E SCREAMING)
(SQUEAKING)
Oh! Uh-oh.
(EXCLAIMS SOFTLY IN WONDER)
Oh!
EVE.
(WALL-E SIGHS)
(POWERING UP)
(EXCLAIMS IN AWE)
(IN WONDERMENT) Whoa!
(GASPS)
(IN ASTONISHMENT) Whoa!
(EXCLAIMING)
(ALARMS BLARING)
(WHOOSHING)
EVE.
Oh!
(BEEPS)
(M-O WARBLING)
(M-O WARBLES)
(BEEPS)
(WARBLES)
M-O: Foreign contaminant.
Oh!
Uh-oh.
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
M-O: Foreign contaminant.
WALL-E: Whoa!
(YELPS IN SURPRISE)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
M-O: Huh?
(MECHANICAL BUZZING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROANS)
(CHATTERING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(BLEEPING)
(BUZZING)
(CHATTERS INQUIRINGLY)
(WALL-E BEEPS)
(M-O CHATTERING ANGRILY)
(M-O BUZZING)
(M-O SCREAMS IN FRUSTRATION)
(SIREN WAILING)
(M-O YELPS)
(BEEPING)
(CONFUSED BEEP)
(ALARM BLARING)
(BEEPING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(EXCLAIMS)
EVE!
Huh?
(WARBLES IN CONFUSION)
Foreign contaminant.
(CHATTERING IN CONFUSION)
(BLEEPING)
(BUZZES)
(EXCLAIMING)
(WARBLING)
EVE.
(DOORS OPENING)
(MACHINERY DRONING)
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING IN DISAPPOINTMENT)
(HORNS HONKING)
(CRASHING)
(WALL-E WARBLING)
(ROBOT EXCLAIMING)
(ROBOT WARBLES WARNING)
(MACHINERY CLANGING)
(BEEPS)
EVE!
I've been in my cabin all morning,
so let's hover over to the driving range
and hit a few virtual balls into space.
(EXCLAIMS)
No, we did that yesterday.
I don't want to do that.
- Well, then what do you want to do?
- I don't know. Something.
Whoa!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Look, I'm tired of having
the same argument over and over.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Bot, over here.
Whoa!
MAN: I'm in a tunnel. I can't hear you.
WOMAN: There you are.
FEMALE LOUDSPEAKER VOICE:
Buy N Large.
Everything you need to be happy.
Your day is very important to us.
Hey, drink-bot.
(EXCLAIMS QUESTIONINGLY)
Here, take the cup. Hey, take the cup!
- Whoa!
- WALL-E: Uh-oh.
(GROANS)
(BUZZER BUZZING)
STEWARD-BOT:
Please remain stationary.
A service-bot will be here
to assist you momentarily.
Stewards! Hello!
- Please remain stationary.
- Help.
A service-bot will be here
to assist you momentarily.
(HYDRAULICS WHINING)
What's that? What's going on?
(GRUNTING)
WALL-E.
Uh...
- John.
- EVE?
Uh, no. John.
EVE!
Bye, WALL-E.
NANNY-BOT: "A" is for Axiom,
your home sweet home.
"B" is for Buy N Large,
your very best friend.
FEMALE LOUDSPEAKER VOICE:
Mmm!
Time for lunch in a cup.
(ALL SLURPING)
Feel beautiful.
- It's the new you. Stunning.
- You look great.
- I know, honey. Men.
- Men.
FEMALE LOUDSPEAKER VOICE:
Attention, Axiom shoppers. Try blue.
It's the new red.
BOTH: Ooh!
(BEEPING)
WOMAN: Love blue.
WOMAN: Date?
(SCOFFS) Don't get me started
on the date.
Every holo-date I have been on
has been a virtual disaster.
If I could just meet one,
one who wasn't so superficial.
There are no good men out there.
(WALL-E MURMURING)
I know. I know because I've...
What the...
WALL-E: Whoa!
(GASPS)
Huh?
Yoo-hoo. WALL-E.
Uh...
- Mary.
- EVE.
Huh? Oh!
Oh! Oh. Um, sure. You go ahead.
EVE.
(WHIRRING)
Shade!
(GASPS)
I didn't know we had a pool!
(CLICKING)
(TYPING-BOT BEEPING)
(WALL-E SQUEAKS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(GASPS)
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPING)
(WHOOSHING)
AUTO:
Captain, you are needed on the bridge.
(CAPTAIN SNORING)
(SNORING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(MUTTERING DREAMILY)
(PUT ON YOUR
SUNDAY CLOTHES PLAYING)
(YELPS) All hands on deck!
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: Morning.
Just a trim?
♪♪... find adventure in the evening air ♪♪
(CHUCKLES)
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: Uh-huh.
I see. I know, honey. I know.
I'm good, I am good.
You look gorgeous.
(SIGHS)
(BEEPS)
Oh!
♪♪... horsedrawn open cars ♪♪
(WALL-E WARBLING)
(YAWNING)
(THE BLUE DANUBE PLAYING)
- AUTO: Sir?
- Coffee.
(GRUNTS)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
(SLURPING)
Sir, the annual...
(TIREDLY) Protocol, Auto.
First things first.
Computer, status report.
(WHOOSHING)
- Mechanical systems.
- COMPUTER: Unchanged.
- Reactor core temperature.
- Unchanged.
- Passenger count.
- Regenerative food buffet.
- Unchanged.
- Jacuzzi pH balance.
- Atmospheric conditions.
- Unchanged.
- AUTO: Captain.
- Laundry service volume.
- Unchanged.
- Okay, Auto.
- Sir, the annual reconnaissance...
- 12:30!
Auto, why didn't you wake me
for morning announcements?
(WHOOSHING)
Honestly, it's the one thing
I get to do on this ship.
Well, good morning, everybody,
and welcome to day 255,642
aboard the Axiom.
As always, the weather is a balmy
72 degrees and sunny and...
Oh, I see the ship's log is showing
that today is our 700th anniversary
of our five-year cruise.
Well, I'm sure our forefathers would be
proud to know that 700 years later
we'd be doing the exact same thing
they were doing.
Fore!
So, be sure next mealtime
to ask for your "free
(ENUNCIATING) "septuacentennial
cupcake in a cup."
Wow, look at that!
Also today we have a...
(BEEPING)
Hey, Auto, what's that flashing button?
Captain, Probe One
has returned positive.
Positive?
(POWERING UP)
EVE.
(SLOWLY) But no probe's
ever come back positive before.
(BEEPING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(JINGLE PLAYING)
♪♪ Buy N Large ♪♪
Greetings and congratulations,
Captain.
If you are seeing this,
that means your
Extraterrestrial Vegetation Evaluator,
or EVE probe, has returned from Earth
with a confirmed specimen
of ongoing photosynthesis.
That's right. It means it's time
to go back home.
Home? We're going back?
Now that Earth has been restored
to a life-sustaining status,
by golly,
we can begin Operation Recolonize.
(WARBLES)
Simply follow
this manual's instructions
to place the plant
in your ship's holo-detector
and the Axiom will immediately
navigate your return to Earth.
- It's that easy.
- Huh!
Now, due to the effects of microgravity,
you and your passengers
may have suffered some
slight bone loss.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
But I'm sure a few laps
around the ship's jogging track
will get you back in shape in no time.
We have a jogging track?
If you have any further questions,
just consult your operation manual.
See you back home real soon.
"Operate Manuel."
Uh...
Manuel, relay instructions.
Manuel?
Wow. Will you look at that?
CAPTAIN: Let's see.
(MUMBLES DISMISSIVELY)
Huh?
EVE.
WALL-E!
(ELECTRIC WHINING)
(WARBLING UNINTELLIGIBLY)
EVE.
CAPTAIN: Well, let's open her up.
"Step one.
Voice command, 'Confirm acquisition."'
COMPUTER: Confirm acquisition.
CAPTAIN: Ooh!
Voice authorization required.
- Uh...
- CAPTAIN'S VOICE: Uh...
COMPUTER: Accepted.
(BEEPING)
Ooh.
(EXCLAIMING)
- (STAMMERING) Where's the thingy?
- AUTO: Plant.
Plant. Right. Right. Where is it?
Maybe we missed a step.
- Show me how you change...
- Plant.
- CAPTAIN: Okay.
- WALL-E.
WALL-E!
(WALL-E WARBLES)
- EVE?
- Plant!
CAPTAIN: Why don't you
scan her to be sure?
(GASPS)
AUTO: Contains no specimen.
Probe's memory is faulty.
- So then, we're not going to Earth?
- Negative.
I guess things go back to normal, huh?
Correct, Captain.
- Well, false alarm!
- COMPUTER: False alarm.
The probe must be defective.
(SIGHS IN FRUSTRATION)
GO-4, send her to the repair ward,
and have them run diagnostics on her.
Make sure she's not...
Ah!
WALL-E.
Have, uh, WALL-E cleaned.
WALL-E: Yoo-hoo!
EVE.
(EXCLAIMS STERNLY)
(WALL-E MOANS)
Analyze.
COMPUTER: Analysis.
Foreign contaminant.
Substance is a three-phase system
composed of various combinations
of naturally derived solids.
(YAWNS)
Subject is most commonly referred to
as soil, dirt, or earth.
"Earth"?
Hmm.
Define "earth."
Earth, the surface of the world
as distinct from the sky or sea.
Wow.
Define "sea."
Sea, an expanse of salt water
that covers most of the Earth's surface
and surrounds its landmasses.
Foreign contaminant.
APPROACHING ROBOT: Whoa!
(SKIDDING)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(EXCLAIMS) EVE.
Whoa!
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: Just a trim?
You look gorgeous.
(WALL-E EXCLAIMS IN ALARM)
(PROTESTING)
(STIFLING SNEEZE)
Fore!
(WHIRRING)
EVE!
(BLEEPING)
COMPUTER: Clear, clear, clear.
(WARBLES)
(EXCLAIMS)
(LAUGHING)
(CREAKING)
Whoa!
Ooh!
(PUT ON YOUR
SUNDAY CLOTHES PLAYING)
EVE! EVE!
Ah!
(GRUNTS)
WALL-E.
(EXCLAIMS)
(EVE EXCLAIMING IN ALARM)
(WALL-E GROANS)
(ALARM BUZZING)
WALL-E!
(ALL POWERING DOWN)
(CHATTERING INQUISITIVELY)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(WALL-E YELPS)
WALL-E!
(ALARM SOUNDING)
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: Oh, my.
STEWARD-BOT: Halt!
(SHUDDERING)
(EVE EXCLAIMS)
WALL-E!
COMPUTER: Caution. Rogue robots.
Caution. Rogue robots.
(EXCLAIMS IN ALARM)
WALL-E!
(WEAPONS POWERING UP)
(EVE EXCLAIMS IN ALARM)
STEWARD-BOT: Halt! Halt!
(EVE YELPS)
COMPUTER: Caution. Rogue robots.
WALL-E!
(EXCLAIMS)
D-FiB: Clear.
EVE: Ooh!
Caution. Rogue robots.
Uh-oh.
EVE.
(ELEVATOR CHIMES)
(TAPPING ON PANEL)
(HESITANTLY) EVE?
(POWERING UP)
Earth.
Oh!
Ah.
Directive.
(EXCLAIMS)
(WARBLING)
WALL-E.
(STERNLY) WALL-E!
(ELEVATOR CHIMES)
Uh-oh.
(POWERING DOWN)
(EVE GASPS)
EVE: Plant!
WALL-E.
- EVE.
- WALL-E!
(CRASHING)
(SCREAMING)
(BLEEPING)
(EXCLAIMS)
COMPUTER: Cruising speed.
(CRASHING)
You are now free
to move about the cabin.
Huh?
(GROANING IN FRUSTRATION)
Oh!
(BEEPING)
Twenty seconds to self-destruct.
(GASPS)
Ten seconds to self-destruct.
(SHRIEKS)
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
(GRUNTING)
Three,
(SCREAMING)
Two...
(EXPLODES)
(WEAKLY) No. No.
EVE!
WALL-E!
(BUZZING)
Whoa!
(WARBLING)
WALL-E!
(WALL-E EXCLAIMING)
Oh!
EVE.
(EVE GIGGLES)
(WALL-E MUTTERING)
WALL-E.
EVE.
(GASPS) WALL-E!
(SHOUTS OUT IN JO Y)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BUZZES)
(SIGHS GIDDILY)
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(GIGGLES)
WALL-E.
WALL-E: Whee!
(EVE LAUGHING)
(WALL-E CHATTERING)
(EVE GIGGLING)
(BOTH EXCLAIMING HAPPILY)
Oh, so many stars.
Oh.
(GASPS IN SURPRISE)
- Hey! Hey! That's what's-his-name!
- Hey! What the...
- Look! Look at that.
- Huh? What?
Hey. I know that guy. It's, uh, WALL-E.
- Hey, WALL-E! It's your buddy John.
- Hi, WALL-E!
(GASPS)
Hi.
CAPTAIN: Define "hoedown."
COMPUTER: Hoedown,
a social gathering
at which lively dancing
would take place.
Auto, Earth is amazing!
These are called "farms."
Humans would put seeds
in the ground, pour water on them,
and they grow food, like pizza.
AUTO: Good night, Captain.
(GROANS)
(WHISPERING) Psst! Computer.
Define "dancing."
COMPUTER: Dancing, a series of
movements involving two partners
where speed and rhythm
match harmoniously with MUSIC.
WALL-E: Uh-huh. Uh...
(SWEETLY) EVE.
EVE: Home.
(CRASHING)
(CHATTERING)
Uh-oh.
COMPUTER: The lido deck is now
closing. The lido deck is now closing.
(MARY AND JOHN LAUGHING)
- JOHN: Stop that.
- Make me.
I didn't know we had a pool.
LIFEGUARD-BOT:
No splashing. No diving.
- JOHN: Oh, go on.
- (FIZZLING) No splashing. No...
(GASPS)
(BEEPING)
(IT ONLY TAKES
A MOMENT PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(SWEETLY) EVE.
♪♪... it only takes a moment ♪♪
Shh!
(MUSIC STOPS)
(EXCLAIMS ASSERTIVELY)
Directive.
(WHOOSHING)
CAPTAIN: Prepare for landing.
(IMITATING DOCKING)
(IMITATES BRAKES CREAKING)
"We're here, everybody."
"Yay, Captain! Captain, we're home!
It's so beautiful!"
"No. It's nothing.
I was pleased to do this.
"It's all about you people.
It's not about me."
(RATTLING)
How?
How did you find it?
(SIGHING REVERENTLY)
We can go back home!
For the first time!
- What's it like now?
- Oh!
No, no, no. Don't tell me.
I want to see for myself.
Wait. That doesn't look like Earth.
Where's the blue sky?
(WALL-E EXCLAIMING)
Where's the grass?
(WALL-E EXCLAIMS)
♪♪... Sunday clothes
when you feel down and out ♪♪
I know that song.
♪♪ Strut down the street
and have your picture took ♪♪
They're, um,
dancing.
Yes, dancing.
♪♪ That Sunday shine is a certain sign
That you feel as fine as you look ♪♪
♪♪ Beneath your parasol... ♪♪
You made it somehow, huh, little guy?
You didn't give up, did you?
(GASPS)
Okay, then. Come on.
Wait a minute.
♪♪... when time runs out ♪♪
♪♪ That it only... ♪♪
(WALL-E SQUAWKS)
Huh?
EVE?
EVE!
Uh-oh!
WALL-E.
(PRACTICING) EVE.
EVE.
Pathetic.
EVE!
Oh!
Huh?
Foreign contaminant.
(GROANS IN FRUSTRATION)
There you go, little guy.
You came a long way
for a drink of water.
Just needed someone
to look after you, that's...
We have to go back.
(BOSUN'S WHISTLE SOUNDS)
- Auto, come down here.
- Aye, aye, sir.
WALL-E.
(WALL-E SIGHS)
Auto, EVE found the plant.
Fire up the holo-detector.
Not necessary, Captain.
You may give it to me.
- You know what? I should do it myself.
- Captain.
Sir, I insist you give me the plant.
- Auto, get out of my way.
- We cannot go home.
- What are you talking about? Why not?
- That is classified, Captain.
- Give me the plant.
- What do you mean, "classified"?
You don't keep a secret
from the captain.
Give me the plant.
- Tell me what's classified.
- The plant.
Tell me, Auto! That's an order.
Aye, aye, sir.
(JINGLE PLAYING)
♪♪ Buy N Large is your superstore
We got all you need ♪♪
Just cut it off, will you?
(JINGLE WINDS TO A STOP)
(SIGHS) Hey, there, autopilots.
Got some bad news.
Um...
Operation Cleanup has,
well, failed.
Wouldn't you know,
rising toxicity levels have made life
unsustainable on Earth.
"Unsustainable"? What?
Darn it all, we're going to have
to cancel Operation Recolonize.
So,
(SIGHS IN EMBARRASSMENT)
Just stay the course.
Um...
Rather than try and fix this problem,
it'll just be easier
for everyone to remain in space.
"Easier"?
- MAN: (WHISPERING) Mr. President?
- I think...
- Huh?
- Sir, time to go.
Okay. I'm giving
Override Directive A 113.
Go to full autopilot.
Take control of everything,
and do not return to Earth.
Repeat, do not return to Earth.
(MUFFLED) Let's get
the heck out of here.
Now, the plant.
No. Wait a minute.
Computer, when was that message
sent out to the Axiom?
COMPUTER: Message received
in the year 2110.
That's... That's nearly 700 years ago!
(SCOFFS) Auto, things have changed!
We've got to go back.
Sir, orders are "do not return to Earth."
But life is sustainable now.
Look at this plant. Green and growing.
- It's living proof he was wrong.
- Irrelevant, Captain.
What? It's completely relevant!
Out there is our home.
Home, Auto.
And it's in trouble.
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
That's all I've ever done.
That's all anyone on this blasted ship
has ever done. Nothing!
On the Axiom you will survive.
- I don't want to survive. I want to live!
- Must follow my directive.
(EXCLAIMS IN FRUSTRATION)
I'm the captain of the Axiom.
We are going home today.
(GASPS)
(ALARM BLARING)
(GO-4 BEEPS)
GO-4?
Hey! That's not...
This is mutiny! EVE, arrest him.
(WARBLING)
EVE, you are to put this plant
straight in the holo-detector.
No!
(EVE EXCLAIMS)
(SERVOS WHIRRING)
EVE: Huh?
- EVE?
- BOTH: WALL-E!
EVE!
- Oh!
- WALL-E, the plant!
- WALL-E!
- CAPTAIN: Over here. Throw it.
EVE: Ahhh!
EVE!
(WALL-E SCREAMS)
AUTO: Give me the plant.
(WALL-E EXCLAIMS DEFIANTLY)
(SCREAMING)
(BEEPING)
(GASPS)
EVE: WALL-E!
(EVE WHIMPERING)
(GO-4 WARBLING)
AUTO:
All communications are terminated.
You are confined to quarters.
No! Mutiny!
Mutiny!
(DOOR SLAMS)
(CIRCUITS POWERING UP)
(EXCLAIMS)
WALL-E?
COMPUTER: Caution.
Activating airlock disposal.
WALL-E!
(YELPS)
WALL-E?
(RUMBLING)
Ah!
(GROANING) EVE.
WALL-E!
COMPUTER: Caution.
Activating airlock disposal.
(GRUNTING)
(WEAPON FIRING)
WALL-E!
(CHATTERING)
Foreign contaminant.
Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
EVE: Whoa.
(WALL-E GROANING WEAKLY)
(BEEPING SLOWLY)
WALL-E.
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPING SLOWLY)
(FIZZLING)
Huh?
All clean. All clean.
(CHATTERS)
(WALL-E MOANING)
WALL-E.
M-O.
- M-O?
- M-O.
M-O.
Mmm?
Mmm.
(EXCLAIMS IN WORRY)
(WEAKLY) Directive.
(BEEPING)
Directive.
(MOANING WEAKLY)
Earth.
- Earth.
Earth? Earth!
(EXCLAIMS IN UNDERSTANDING)
- WALL-E: M-O.
- WALL-E!
(CHATTERING)
(WEAPON POWERING UP)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
(TIRES SKID)
STEWARD-BOT: Wrong.
(SHUDDERING)
(ALARM BLARING)
STEWARD-BOT: Please hold.
We are currently having...
M-O: EVE!
EVE: Whoops.
COMPUTER: Caution. Rogue robots.
(SQUEAKING PUT ON
YOUR SUNDAY CLOTHES)
(WALL-E GROANING)
(PUT ON YOUR
SUNDAY CLOTHES PLAYING)
(SNEEZES)
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: That style suits you.
D-FIB: Clear.
COMPUTER: Caution. Rogue robots.
Caution. Rogue robots.
- AUTO: Not possible.
- Caution. Rogue robots.
(ALARMS SOUNDING)
(CRYING)
CAPTAIN: Auto! Auto!
Mutiny. Mutiny.
(BANGING)
Stupid wheel.
COMPUTER: Caution. Rogue robots.
Caution. Rogue robots.
The plant!
(LAUGHS)
(MUTTERING)
We'll see who's powerless now.
(BEEPS)
(GRUNTING)
CAPTAIN: Testing, testing.
Is this thing on?
(WHISPERING) This is the captain.
I am locked in my room.
EVE, WALL-E,
bring the plant to the lido deck.
I'll have activated the holo-detector.
Now, hurry.
- Auto's probably going to cut me off...
- STEWARD-BOT: Halt.
EVE: Ah!
STEWARD-BOT: Halt.
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: Oh, my.
(WARBLING)
D-FIB: Clear.
WALL-E: Oh!
STEWARD-BOT: Halt, halt.
(BEEPING)
(LAUGHS)
- Look what I got, Auto.
- Not possible.
(CHUCKLING) That's right. The plant.
You want it? Come and get it, blinky.
No.
(LAUGHS)
Captain? Captain?
(GRUNTING)
AUTO: Let go.
- Let go.
- Too heavy for you? Huh?
(EXCLAIMS IN PAIN)
AUTO: Get off.
CAPTAIN: You're not getting away
from me, one-eye.
- AUTO: Get off.
- (SCREAMS) Is that all you got?
(BEEPING)
(YELLING)
(PANTING RHYTHMICALLY)
STEWARD-BOT: Halt.
- That's it. A little closer.
- AUTO: Cease and desist.
- Not good.
- Got you.
(LAUGHING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(SNORING)
Whoa!
(ALL CHATTERING)
NANNY-BOT:
Remain calm. Remain calm.
(ALL EXCLAIM IN WONDER)
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
We're having a slight malfunction
with the autopilot.
Please remain calm.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
EVE: Ah!
(GRUNTING)
AUTO: Enough.
(EVE EXCLAIMS)
MARY: Hey. What? John?
ALL: Whoa!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WARBLING)
(SCREAMING)
No! No, no, no!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
MAN: I gotcha!
(MARY GRUNTING)
(BABIES CRYING)
John, get ready to have some kids!
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(JOHN AND MARY SCREAMING)
MARY: Look out!
EVE: Ah!
(ALL YELLING)
Oh!
(GRUNTING)
(BEEPING)
AUTO: No.
(BUZZES)
WALL-E!
(GASPS)
No!
Uh-oh.
(ALL GASP)
Oh, no!
(GRUNTING)
(ALL GASP)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(GRUNTING)
Auto?
(SCREAMING)
WALL-E!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Auto, you are relieved of duty.
AUTO: No.
(ALL CHEERING)
Plant! Plant!
(M-O WARBLES)
Foreign contaminant.
EVE: Plant!
M-O: EVE!
(GRUNTING)
COMPUTER: Plant origin verified.
(GASPS)
WALL-E.
COMPUTER: Course set for Earth.
Ten seconds to hyper-jump. Nine...
- EVE: No.
- ...eight...
- WALL-E!
- ...seven, six, five, four...
Oh, no. WALL-E.
...three, two, one, zero.
(SCREAMING)
WALL-E!
(SQUEAKING)
(SQUEAKS)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(PEOPLE MUTTERING)
(CAPTAIN GASPS)
(EVE WARBLING)
(SQUEAKS)
WALL-E.
M-O: EVE!
(DOOR OPENING)
(CLATTERING)
(BUZZING)
M-O: Huh?
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
(SQUEAKING HAPPILY)
(SIGHS) WALL-E.
EVE.
Ooh!
EVE: WALL-E?
♪♪ Put on your Sunday clothes
when you feel down and out ♪♪
WALL-E?
(SQUEAKS)
(SIGHS)
(STATIC HISSING)
(EVE WARBLES IN CONCERN)
WALL-E.
WALL-E!
(EVE HUMMING
IT ONLY TAKES A MO MEN T)
(BUZZES)
(CLANKS)
(SERVOS WHIRRING WEAKLY)
- EVE?
- (GASPING) WALL-E?
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
EVE!
(GIGGLES)
♪♪ And that is all ♪♪
♪♪ That love's about ♪♪
M-O: Whee!
BEAUTICIAN-BOT: You're kidding!
M-O: (ADMONISHING)
Go, go, go. Go, go.
♪♪ And we'll recall
When time runs out ♪♪
This is called farming!
You kids are going to grow
all kinds of plants.
Vegetable plants. Pizza plants!
(LAUGHING)
It's good to be home!
♪♪ Took a moment ♪♪
♪♪ to be loved ♪♪
♪♪ a whole life ♪♪
♪♪ long ♪♪
(LIGHTER FLICKING)
(DOWN TO EARTH PLAYING)
♪♪ Did you think that your feet
had been bound ♪♪
♪♪ By what gravity brings
to the ground? ♪♪
♪♪ Did you feel you were tricked
by the future you picked? ♪♪
♪♪ Well, come on down ♪♪
♪♪ All these rules don't apply
When you're high in the sky ♪♪
♪♪ So come on down ♪♪
♪♪ Come on down ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ There's no better place to go ♪♪
♪♪ We got snow up on the mountains ♪♪
♪♪ We got rivers down below ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ We hear the birds sing in the trees ♪♪
♪♪ And the land will be looked after ♪♪
♪♪ We'll send the seeds
out in the breeze ♪♪
♪♪ Did you think
you'd escaped from routine ♪♪
♪♪ By changing the script
and the scene? ♪♪
♪♪ Despite all you made of it ♪♪
♪♪ You're always afraid
of the change ♪♪
♪♪ You've got a lot on your chest ♪♪
♪♪ Well, you can come as my guest ♪♪
♪♪ So come on down ♪♪
♪♪ Come on down ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ There's no better place to go ♪♪
♪♪ We got snow up on the mountains ♪♪
♪♪ We got rivers down below ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ We hear the birds sing in the trees ♪♪
♪♪ And the land will be looked after ♪♪
♪♪ We'll send the seeds
out in the breeze ♪♪
♪♪ Like the fish in the ocean ♪♪
♪♪ We felt at home in the sea ♪♪
♪♪ We learned to live off the good land ♪♪
♪♪ We learned to climb up a tree ♪♪
♪♪ Then we got up on two legs ♪♪
♪♪ But we wanted to fly ♪♪
♪♪ And when we messed up
our homeland ♪♪
♪♪ We set sail for the sky ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ There's no better place to go ♪♪
♪♪ We got snow up on the mountains ♪♪
♪♪ We got rivers down below ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ We hear the birds sing in the trees ♪♪
♪♪ And the land will be looked after ♪♪
♪♪ We'll send the seeds
out in the breeze ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down ♪♪
♪♪ Coming down to Earth ♪♪
♪♪ Like babies at birth ♪♪
♪♪ We define new priorities ♪♪
♪♪ These are extraordinary qualities ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ There's no better place to go ♪♪
♪♪ We got snow up on the mountains ♪♪
♪♪ We got rivers down below ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ We hear the birds sing in the trees ♪♪
♪♪ And the land will be looked after ♪♪
♪♪ We send the seeds
out in the breeze ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ There's no better place to go ♪♪
♪♪ We got snow up on the mountains ♪♪
♪♪ We got rivers down below ♪♪
♪♪ We're coming down to the ground ♪♪
♪♪ We hear the birds sing in the trees ♪♪
♪♪ And the land will be looked after ♪♪
♪♪ We send the seeds
out in the breeze ♪♪
♪♪ We define new priorities ♪♪
♪♪ These are extraordinary qualities ♪♪
♪♪ To find on Earth ♪♪