ANGUS MacLANE: I just want to
point out right away
that there would never be
any singing in space.
You would never hear this.
BILL WISE: In space,
no one can hear you sing?
ANGUS: That is totally true.
DEREK THOMPSON: Wow,
you could put that on a T-shirt.
BILL: Yeah.
DEREK: There is actually
a pretty nice counterpoint
with the opening song here
and these images of space.
BILL: You know, speaking of science,
you know,
that galaxy is rotating really fast
in the beginning.
You would never see that.
ANGUS: Well, I think
it's a time-lapse thing.
It's like one of those...
You know, like the old Disney...
BILL: We're sub-light.
Look, we're sub-light here. Okay?
ANGUS: Sub-light? Is that some...
What is sub-light?
LINDSEY COLLINS:
What's a sub-light?
BILL: Not light speed,
less than light speed.
- Sub-light.
- ANGUS: Oh. Thanks a lot, Asimov.
DEREK: You know,
this isn't a live-action picture,
so you can't, you know,
limit the camera to
the physics of real space.
ANGUS: See, look, nuclear power.
DEREK: Nuclear power.
BILL: You're gonna start there?
You're gonna start there?
You're just gonna
lower the bar right down...
LINDSEY: And excuse everything from
here on out, is what you're saying.
DEREK: Well, we have to.
We're climbing upwards
at this point in the film.
So, this is 700, 800 years of...
BILL: They don't know that yet.
Will you hush?
ANGUS: This is similar...
DEREK: No spoilers, right?
We shouldn't give anything away
in advance.
LINDSEY: Hopefully,
this is not the first time
they're seeing this film
with this commentary.
DEREK: Yeah, yeah.
If you're watching this film now,
and you haven't seen it
without commentary...
BILL: Maybe they accidentally...
LINDSEY: Stop, go back.
DEREK: Stop, go back, watch it.
ANGUS: Spoilers ahead!
DEREK: Spoilers alert.
You're beyond the spoiler zone.
You know what a spoiler is,
don't you, Lindsey?
I do. Thanks for asking, though.
Thanks for checking.
DEREK: Okay, good. I just wanted
to make sure that's clear.
LINDSEY: I thought we were clear
we weren't mentioning names.
ANGUS: So that's WALL-E.
What does WALL-E stand for, Derek?
"Waste Allocation Load Lifter,
Earth-Class."
Angus.
ANGUS: That's pretty nerdy.
DEREK: Actually, the acronym
changed a couple of times
because a second "L" was added
midway through the production, so...
ANGUS: Why was that?
LINDSEY: It's because
everybody was worried
that people would
mispronounce the title as "Whale"
without the second "L".
I'm serious. We had to add...
DEREK: Are you sure that's the...
Was it a pronunciation thing?
ANGUS: Further putting forth
our environmental message.
LINDSEY: It was a pronunciation thing.
- DEREK: All right.
- It was a pronunciation thing.
They were like, "Everybody's gonna
mispronounce it and call it 'Whale',"
which is not nearly
as endearing or charming,
and slightly misleading, frankly,
a film called "Whale."
DEREK: And that is
endearment personified right there.
That's our little friend.
ANGUS: I gotta say, there's no way
the hubcap would still be
that pristine...
DEREK: And shiny.
BILL: If it was crunched into a cube?
DEREK: Yeah. Well, nobody's
used an automobile
for 700, 800 years.
ANGUS: So, is that actually an Igloo?
- Did you talk to the Igloo people?
- LINDSEY: Yeah.
- And you got their cooler...
- Yeah.
Made sure everything was...
Oh, that's good.
LINDSEY: So, are you gonna be
this guy through the whole thing?
ANGUS: What? No, I'm not that guy.
DEREK: I have a little bit of a
back story for Hal the cockroach.
Can you tell me, Angus,
how Hal got his name?
I believe it was Reardon who
wanted to call him Hal. Is that right?
- HAL the computer or...
- DEREK: No, you're incorrect.
- Hal Roach? Hal Roach.
- It was for Hal Roach.
Filmmaker, made a lot of
Little Rascals shorts in the '30s.
It could work on the "HAL
the computer" level, too, I suppose.
A lot of acronyms in this movie.
ANGUS: Yeah, it was
a double nerd reference,
which is important for any of our jokes.
DEREK: Right, right.
ANGUS: There's gas.
And in the future here,
money is just like on the streets.
So although no one is around
and it's totally lonely,
there's tons of money, which is nice.
DEREK: And this is
a perfect opportunity
to point out the copious amount
of dystopian versus utopian worlds
we're gonna see in this movie.
And that is a recurring theme in a lot
of science fiction movies that we love,
but this sort of dystopian future,
this trashed world...
ANGUS: Not for my benefit,
but for our watchers...
LINDSEY: We all know
what you mean.
ANGUS: What is the difference
between dystopian and...
LINDSEY: Will you please
define "dystopian" for the...
DEREK: Dystopian is a...
BILL: Are you gonna be
like Mr. Professor this whole...
ANGUS: I think
that's about the size of it.
Let him finish.
DEREK: He asked the question.
ANGUS: So, "dystopian"?
DEREK: Dystopian is a bleak vision
of the future.
Utopian is an optimistic vision
ANGUS: There's a contrast there.
DEREK: There is a contrast.
- We have both of those things.
- We do have both of those things.
And I'll remind us later,
when we get to it.
LINDSEY: I will point it out.
ANGUS: I would like to point out...
I don't know how those trash piles
go into boxes there,
so that doesn't make any sense to me.
DEREK: Well, I know that
Ralph and his team figured out
- the mechanics of the sequence...
- LINDSEY: Oh, no... Yeah.
- It's incinerated.
- DEREK: all of the incinerated...
ANGUS: Oh, it's going
the opposite direction.
BILL: Yeah, they go down.
LINDSEY: They're going into
massive incinerators.
ANGUS: Oh, I was seeing it wrong.
I was seeing it wrong.
DEREK: They put
a tremendous amount of thought
into the mechanics and the procedure.
LINDSEY: For one shot.
DEREK: For one shot.
But you know what? It's that kind of
thorough planning that makes...
LINDSEY: That makes
these movies cost $150 million.
DEREK: Exactly.
ANGUS: They put a little twist on it.
DEREK: You know?
It's called verisimilitude, Lindsey.
It's bringing a level of truth to this.
Oh, there's a little glimpse of utopia.
ANGUS: This is great, yeah.
BILL: I just love that
this is our live-action.
DEREK: Right.
The introduction of live-action.
LINDSEY: There it is.
BILL: We've crossed the line.
LINDSEY: That's Andrew Stanton
the director's
daughter there on the right.
Little-known fact.
The Axiom.
Putting the star in executive star liner.
DEREK: Fred Willard,
you did a great job. Thanks.
- LINDSEY: He was fantastic.
- He's funny.
LINDSEY: He was. He was hilarious.
ANGUS: I wouldn't stand that close
if that spaceship was taking off,
though, so I don't...
LINDSEY: But it's supposed to be fake
in the commercial.
It's not supposed to
really be taking off.
- DEREK: It was a green screen.
- Oh.
DEREK: It's like, you see something...
LINDSEY: It's a commercial.
BILL: No, no, no, that thing's huge.
I mean, you know,
people stand around
watching the shuttle take off.
ANGUS: Yeah, but they're miles away.
That looks like he's like right there.
BILL: That thing is huge.
LINDSEY: It's a commercial.
- It was supposed to be fake.
- BILL: Do you not remember?
DEREK: So you mentioned
the Igloo earlier...
ANGUS: I guess
we can agree to disagree.
DEREK: How many other
real life objects
or products are in WALL-E's trailer?
BILL: I think there's actually five.
LINDSEY: Many.
DEREK: Many?
BILL: Five or six, baby.
DEREK: Five or six actual objects?
And that doesn't count
as a pop culture reference, right?
- That's more of a...
- ANGUS: It's a dystopian answer.
DEREK: It's an anchor to
a world we know.
I mean, this is the closest
a Pixar movie probably has come to
being anchored in a real world, right?
I mean, 'cause there's
real-world stuff in here.
ANGUS: I think you're right, Derek.
LINDSEY: Well, there's
a lot of films... anyway.
BILL: Well, there's a lot of
real-world stuff in here.
ANGUS: I gotta say that there's
no way that, that toaster is plugged in.
LINDSEY: Oh, Hello, Dolly!
ANGUS: It was great.
When we started this movie...
BILL: That's a Brazil, you know.
That totally reminds me of in Brazil,
when, you know,
they have the little screens
and they have
the big magnifying glass.
ANGUS: Right, right. But Hello, Dolly!
Was in it all the way along.
LINDSEY: All the way along.
And it's actually
what dictated us using live action.
- DEREK: Yep, we were trapped.
- Because we were trapped.
We were backed into a corner
and had to use live action,
since we had the Hello, Dolly! footage.
ANGUS: Yeah. Many people are
trapped by the vision of Hello, Dolly!
DEREK: Hello, Dolly! has
two great songs in it,
and that's the two great songs.
ANGUS: No, no,
it has three great songs.
DEREK: Really?
What's the third great song?
'Cause I don't know
the songs well enough.
Well, I know Louis Armstrong
pops up in there.
BILL: Can't hold a candle...
ANGUS: It Only Takes A Moment.
I don't know.
BILL: It can't hold a candle to
Seven Brides for Seven Brothers.
ANGUS: I'm really more of
a Cabaret fan myself.
LINDSEY: Look at you guys
with the musical knowledge.
DEREK: Yeah, we brought
the wrong geeks in here.
LINDSEY: Seriously, I have not that
much knowledge about anything.
You guys have more knowledge
about this stuff...
- DEREK: No, no, no.
- Than I have about anything.
DEREK: But get this. In Japan,
they have a term called otaku,
which means a disproportionate
enthusiasm or obsession
with a given thing,
so, if you were super-knowledgeable
about wine...
LINDSEY: The thing is, I'm not that
knowledgeable about anything.
ANGUS: What about
'80s teen dramas?
- No.
- Coming-of-age films?
- Daddy disapproval movies, where...
- Uh-uh. Nope.
There's some cultural thing
they've really got to get over?
- No.
- BILL: Celebrity gossip?
- DEREK: Hey, there's Hal again.
We like cockroaches.
LINDSEY: Well, we went rats last time.
We figured roaches...
DEREK: Yeah, yeah, well, in France...
LINDSEY: Little pieces of
poop will be...
how many people own rats now
because of Ratatouille?
I mean, I'm sure pet cockroaches
are going to actually...
LINDSEY: It's a problem.
ANGUS: New York is
gonna love this film.
DEREK: Well,
there's an interesting thing.
Somebody was telling me
that while most people believe
that cockroaches will be the last
surviving creature on the planet,
if humans were gone, cockroaches
would apparently die out pretty quickly
because most of what they live on
is human waste.
So, while they're resistant
to nuclear, you know...
ANGUS: I was not aware
we had to prepare for this.
Doing that research, I mean,
I'm very impressed. That's great.
DEREK: No, no,
this is something I remember...
LINDSEY: This is what happens
when you're in the story department.
- You know this kind of stuff.
- DEREK: In the story room,
the conversations would drift
to all of these things, and...
ANGUS: I'm sorry, I gotta interrupt.
I gotta interrupt. Look at that.
That snack cake.
- When it says "Kremies"...
- BOTH: Kremies.
That logo, the old '70s Star Wars font,
or '60s Star Wars font, I love it.
DEREK: Star Wars was made in
the '70s though. It's not a '60s thing.
ANGUS: No, it's Star Trek.
Did I say Star Wars?
- Yeah, you did.
- LINDSEY: You said Star Wars.
ANGUS: Oh, my God.
LINDSEY: That would be like
a rookie mistake I would make.
ANGUS: You know what?
I can't believe
I confused Star Trek and Star Wars.
"They're the same thing!"
LINDSEY: Get off the couch,
Angus. Go.
- BILL: Eleven years.
- Get off the couch.
- '66 to '77.
- ANGUS: Whatever.
- DEREK: That's a long time.
- All right. Well, anyway...
DEREK: But, yeah, that little cake has
two cream holes instead of three
and that's a good cream hole.
LINDSEY: Which distinguishes it
from the other snack cakes.
ANGUS: It is not like
the other snack cake. It is a Creamie.
DEREK: Robot point of view.
That's pretty exciting.
We get to see
a few robot point of views.
Was there any special thinking that
went into the robot point of view?
Angus? Bill?
ANGUS: Not that I'm aware of.
BILL: You mean in terms of like
which shots were going to be?
DEREK: Well, no, just... I mean,
I think that happens in story,
but as far as
what would a robot's point of view...
LINDSEY: Look at you
taking credit for everything.
You're like, "Oh, no, that's in story."
DEREK: Well, no,
but deciding which shot...
BILL: Yeah. You know, when like
Luke looks through... In Star Wars,
when Luke looks through
his binoculars
and it's got the whole like
auto-focusing ring inside...
- DEREK: Yes, yeah.
- That...
ANGUS: Yeah,
but that's so that he can see it.
That's like saying there's another
being inside him that's witnessing that.
I don't know if he actually
experiences that in his field of view.
DEREK: Well, they say dogs see
in black and white.
I mean, does WALL-E see...
BILL: I mean, it's like Terminator.
Terminator vision.
DEREK: Well, WALL-E... I mean,
we're gonna see M-O's vision later on
is a bit like a Predator vision,
sort of a heat-sensing thing.
But WALL-E's vision is
a little bit more monochrome.
- ANGUS: It looks great.
- That means one color, Lindsey.
I'm glad I've become the idiot on
the couch. Thank you. Thank you.
ANGUS: This, I got to say,
please don't drive over a cockroach.
It will not come back to life.
- DEREK: Yeah.
- Just... It's not...
BILL: Only in the movies.
ANGUS: Only in the movies.
I will point out that there's no way that
he could actually do all these things.
[DEREK LAUGHING]
DEREK: Way to shatter the illusion!
ANGUS: I'm sorry.
We said no spoilers.
DEREK: That's a bra. This is a G-rated
movie and there's a bra in this movie.
ANGUS: No, he thinks
it's a pair of goggles.
DEREK: Oh,
and that's what makes it G.
ANGUS: But Bobble Heads survive
in the future. That's nice to know.
DEREK: This car alarm bit's
pretty funny, too,
- 'cause of that car alarm battery.
- LINDSEY: Paddleball.
ANGUS: Paddleball, yep.
DEREK: Diamond ring.
LINDSEY: Name those carats.
DEREK: You're pretty observant.
- How many carats in that ring?
- LINDSEY: How many carats?
Well, actually, thanks for asking.
ANGUS: It depends on
three Vs, right?
DEREK: That's a Lindsey question.
BILL: Aren't you gonna say that
all that stuff wouldn't fit in the Igloo?
ANGUS: Oh, no,
we'd just swap that out.
- Captain Bringdown?
- LINDSEY: "Captain Bringdown"?
ANGUS: Am I supposed to be
Captain Bringdown?
BILL: Well, you did...
DEREK: This is some foreshadowing.
Okay? Just so you know. There it is.
BILL: Now, this totally negates your
"couldn't build the tower"...
- ANGUS: It's a montage!
- But it's one day!
ANGUS: No, but we're only told that
from the lighting. We can fake that.
BILL: He gets a good start.
DEREK: This one always got me.
How could that plant grow inside
the refrigerator? But I guess it's open.
LINDSEY: It's not open.
ANGUS: The refrigerator was open,
and then there was a strong wind
that day, it closed...
BILL: If he can do
basically a base layer
at the widest part of
the tower in a day...
ANGUS: Okay.
BILL: Okay?
And then how many levels
are there gonna be for a trash tower?
DEREK: Remember, it wasn't just him.
ANGUS: Three hundred, 400.
BILL: All right.
So that's 300, 400 days, tops.
DEREK: Think about how many
WALL-Es were helping him out.
BILL: He could build one in a year.
ANGUS: Okay, okay, okay.
LINDSEY: It's been 800 years.
ANGUS: That's times the rate of
the WALL-E deaths, or the other ones.
- DEREK: Yeah, how long would...
- So, if each one...
BILL: I'm just saying a single WALL-E,
our guy...
- ANGUS: Yeah.
- If he can build the base of a tower
in a day, and that's the widest part,
you know, however many levels
it's gonna be, it's gonna be less.
He can do it in a year,
maybe a year and a half.
DEREK: Okay?
ANGUS: Yeah.
[ALL LAUGHING]
DEREK: So, Angus, something
gives me the feeling
that the scale of these dots bother you.
ANGUS: Don't prompt me for stuff
I've already talked about.
BILL: This has always
bugged me a little bit.
It's like the ship is
supposedly coming down.
It's got these, like, laser sights
or whatever.
ANGUS: It's finding
a good place to land.
BILL: And the little dot is
just like moving around.
- DEREK: It's triangulating.
- It's trying to...
Yeah, but does that mean
the ship is doing that, or...
ANGUS: No, no, no, no. There's like
an omnidirectional laser
on the bottom.
And what's happening with WALL-E
is that he is acting as...
Like, something that the ship
doesn't want to land on.
So that's why it's trying
to get away from WALL-E.
So if WALL-E wasn't doing that,
it would have landed
I guess next to his house.
- BILL: You're making that up.
- No!
- You are totally making that up.
- I was told...
DEREK: You gotta think on your feet
in this place, man.
It was omnidirectional laser,
or a light-emitting...
- DEREK: Laser.
- What does "laser" stand for?
DEREK: That's a good question.
BILL: No, no, no. It...
LINDSEY: Bill,
what's "laser" stand for?
DEREK: I didn't know laser
was an acronym, but it is.
BILL: "Light Amplification..."
I don't remember.
DEREK: You see,
it's just another acronym.
ANGUS: We just lost half the country
on that one.
- DEREK: Now here is the...
- We don't know what laser means.
Sort of Close Encounters type shot,
but you...
LINDSEY: Yeah,
that was a tricky shot, actually.
DEREK: It really works well, I think.
ANGUS: I think this would be real...
And it's a design flaw of the ship.
If you were standing underneath it,
you could not get out.
I think that that's...
DEREK: Well, he's going under,
though, so it's all...
- ANGUS: Well, he has that ability.
- Yeah. He doesn't dig much later.
- LINDSEY: He's a digger.
- DEREK: Yeah.
And he's a piler.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
LINDSEY: A stacker.
ANGUS: No, I think that this heat
would actually melt his lenses.
BILL: Yeah.
DEREK: I don't think it would cool...
LINDSEY: This is futuristic metal.
BILL: I don't think
it would cool down that quickly.
DEREK: Yeah, you have to consider
that WALL-E's gonna be made
out of some super-advanced
metal alloy that's gonna...
LINDSEY: Yeah, exactly.
BILL: That unfortunately will weather
as if it's like wrought iron or cast steel.
LINDSEY: It's the metal of the future.
DEREK: Some kind of
sophisticated ceramic.
ANGUS: Well,
they gotta make it on a budget.
They're cranking out a bunch of these.
DEREK: Right, right, right.
ANGUS: Does every family
have a WALL-E?
LINDSEY: The fate of the world was
in these guys' hands.
You'd think
they would take some time...
DEREK: Well, yeah, WALL-E's like
the straightforward budget
and EVE'S supposed to be
the big budget, you know.
BILL: Tritanium alloy.
DEREK: Tritanium or Adamantium.
Do you know
what Adamantium is, Lindsey?
Okay. Why do you keep making me
look like the idiot?
No! I don't know what Adamantium is!
ANGUS: Everyone knows! It's one of
the periodic table of elements!
DEREK: Yes.
BILL: Wolverine's skeleton.
- Schticked.
- It's...
ANGUS: And his claws.
BILL: Yeah.
ANGUS: But, wait, his skeleton is
not made of Adamantium.
It's laced with Adamantium.
- DEREK: I know, it's laced.
- It's essentially...
LINDSEY: Oh, my God. Okay.
ANGUS: Look, it would be a lot nerdier
if there weren't like six movies now.
DEREK: I think Captain America's
shield is also made of...
ANGUS: It is also
made of Adamantium.
BILL: Is it really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I didn't know that.
I mean, it's painted with,
I think, standard enamel, but...
I don't remember that one.
- I think so.
- I'm gonna check.
DEREK: We may have to
double-check that one.
ANGUS: I think his motorcycle's
also made of Adamantium.
It means "indestructible."
DEREK: See? You can cut that out.
That wasn't funny.
I don't know if we're talking about
parts of this movie that didn't make it,
but originally,
there was a landing party.
LINDSEY: Oh, that's right,
- When it was gelatin aliens.
- Yeah, they came out and actually...
They came out and they spoke in alien
talk and then they sent EVE about.
So it's really interesting
watching this scene, 'cause...
- LINDSEY: It makes it...
- you don't miss the alien scouts.
LINDSEY: That lack of aliens.
I know, but it makes
the love at first sight
much more personal.
DEREK: Oh, yeah, yeah.
Want to talk a little bit
about the science of love?
ANGUS: The science of love.
LINDSEY: There is no science in love.
ANGUS: Hey,
listen to you and your prompting!
"I want you to talk
a little bit about your father."
LINDSEY: "Lindsey,
why don't you just..."
ANGUS: "How do you feel
your relationship with your parents
"has affected your career choice?"
[ALL LAUGHING]
DEREK: But, you know,
there's a lot of emotion
mingled with the science in this movie,
so it's, you know...
ANGUS: I love the combination.
Honestly, I love the combination of...
LINDSEY: It is a love story, after all.
BILL: You mean, a lot of fake love
- mingled with the fake science?
- LINDSEY: No, it's real love.
BILL: It's real love.
DEREK: So what are we gonna draw
a line in the sand between science
fact and science fiction? You know?
ANGUS: I think you have been
drawing lots of lines in the sand...
- DEREK: Every day I draw lines.
- But it doesn't bother me.
I think that...
BILL: I just like to know
when I cross the line, that's all.
ANGUS: I think it's
when the camera's placed here
and then if you had the next shot,
if EVE was on the right-hand side,
and WALL-E was on the left,
- then you've crossed it.
- DEREK: Right.
The line is generated by
the contact made between their eyes...
ANGUS: But she doesn't see him here,
so I don't know if that works.
DEREK: No, no, no, but...
LINDSEY: Are you talking
about the screen line?
DEREK: Yeah, screen direction line.
- Yeah, we jumped ahead.
- LINDSEY: You did.
Phrase it. Like "screen direction's..."
BILL: See?
Nobody thinks you're the idiot.
ANGUS: No,
we were all just moving ahead.
DEREK: So EVE'S flying.
LINDSEY: Yeah,
breaking the sound barrier.
DEREK: Are there any
laws of flying science
broken on this one?
LINDSEY: Well, this was also kind of
more of a story point before, right?
When she kind of had this different
personality where, on board the ship...
DEREK: True, yes. She was.
Yep, yep, it's very true.
She was kind of a slave,
if you will, on board,
and this is the first time she was free.
DEREK: She was liberated and...
LINDSEY: And the moment in the film
actually stayed,
but the story point behind it
actually kind of went away.
ANGUS: Originally, that was the same
with The Empire Strikes Back
in the beginning.
The probot was gonna do this big
song and dance and dance around,
but they ended up cutting it.
DEREK: You've animated
a break-dancing probot, haven't you?
- No.
- DEREK: You want to.
Love EVE'S gun technology.
BILL: A pulsing power vein.
LINDSEY: The subcutaneous...
ANGUS: We nerded out about that
quite little bit.
LINDSEY: Do you know
what that means, Derek?
DEREK: Yeah, I do. "Under the skin."
LINDSEY: You know what?
Can you just go with me?
Can you just be like,
"No, Lindsey, I don't"?
- DEREK: Actually...
- Why didn't you tell me?
DEREK: I would appreciate
your version of...
LINDSEY: No, no, it's too late now.
Forget it.
ANGUS: I will point out on
a cheating nerd level,
there's no way all that gun crap
could fit inside the arm.
- We cheated that a lot.
- BILL: There you go again.
Captain Bringdown.
DEREK: She's a bit of
a magical Transformer,
- but she's got something...
- ANGUS: A magical Transformer?
- Well, you know, all the...
- Don't give them any ideas.
[ALL LAUGHING]
BILL: He's a stalker.
LINDSEY: He is. He's a big stalker.
ANGUS: It's a little creepy.
BILL: Okay. See that little flash
- when the laser comes?
- ANGUS: That's pretty cool.
- Yeah.
- BILL: That's the diffraction thing.
DEREK: Aliens?
Is that an Aliens reference?
LINDSEY: That's diffraction.
BILL: That little glint.
DEREK: Oh, yeah.
ANGUS: There probably is
some diffraction in Aliens there.
DEREK: That first laser
wiping past the camera in...
I love that shot.
BILL: When they cut the hole and the
robotic thing comes in and scans...
DEREK: Actually you're gonna see yet
another reference to that very shot
a little bit later. We were inspired.
ANGUS: What? Do you mean
the deep salvage team?
Yeah.
BILL: "Oh! You mean
the deep salvage team?" Duh!
DEREK: At this point,
if you haven't figured it out,
we looked at a lot of science fiction
movies when we were making this,
and we all had our favorites and...
- BILL: She has got a short fuse.
- Yeah, she's temperamental.
LINDSEY: She's got to be cautious.
She's sent to
a bunch of different worlds,
she doesn't know where she's going.
You don't know what's out there.
ANGUS: If you were left in a tire yard,
you know, you'd be nervous.
Blow up some tires. I don't know.
DEREK: Now we've established that
her gun is pretty powerful
and can blow up a boulder,
but the cockroach survives,
which is a really great joke,
I think, but...
ANGUS: It got driven over. I think...
LINDSEY: The cockroach...
DEREK: No,
she shoots the cockroach.
LINDSEY: The cockroach survives
everything. That's the joke.
That's the running gag.
ANGUS: It's driven over.
BILL: It's the future.
DEREK: It's the most powerful
cockroach on the planet.
ANGUS: I think that
maybe the cockroach
might be made of Adamantium,
or at least its shell might be
laced with Adamantium.
DEREK: Can somebody tell me what
the story is with those metal leaves?
'Cause I still haven't gotten
the story on that.
ANGUS: Originally,
those metal leaves...
LINDSEY: Shavings.
Were going to be welded together
to form a tree.
Later on, it's been replaced
in the story by the statue of EVE.
DEREK: I like how in the future
they use metal shopping carts, though.
That's pretty great.
Metal shopping carts
are not going to go out of style.
ANGUS: Well, they're not...
Actually, you know, that's one of the...
The carbon footprint is pretty heavy
for a shopping cart, I think.
It kind of looks like
she takes his head off.
LINDSEY: Yeah. I've always...
That shot has always made me think...
ANGUS: It kind of freaked me out,
you know?
DEREK: It's kind of
an aggressive maneuver,
but she needs some privacy
for sleeping.
- But WALL-E does...
- ANGUS: Privacy for sleeping?
LINDSEY: Oh, is that what it is?
And she's like, "Back off, man"?
- "Stay back here"?
- DEREK: That's how I kind of read it.
Like she's saying,
"Keep your distance."
"I need some personal space."
LINDSEY: She's just making him
know that she knows he's there?
DEREK: She's got a better sense of
boundaries than WALL-E does.
LINDSEY: WALL-E has
no sense of boundaries.
That's what makes him charming.
And a stalker.
DEREK: "Stalkers can be charming."
That's the moral of this picture.
LINDSEY: [LAUGHING]
"Just give him time."
DEREK: So WALL-E's
a great sculptor.
BILL: I like that he uses a toilet seat.
LINDSEY: This is the biggest
stalker element, right there.
"BILL:" I made a statue of you
- "out of a toilet seat."
- LINDSEY: "While you were sleeping"!
DEREK: But that goes a long way
to charming EVE, though.
- Oh, Pizza Planet truck.
- LINDSEY: Pizza Planet truck.
- Outhouse.
ANGUS: Which we have
in all of our films.
DEREK: Apollo capsule.
There'll be a lot of
space references in here.
- BILL: There's two.
- So what kind of metal is EVE
that's gonna make her
magnetic like this?
What is she made of, Bill?
I thought the whole point was,
like, her power source is what,
like, turns on the electromagnet.
ANGUS: Oh, I didn't get that at all.
BILL: Yeah. 'Cause there's no power
here. It's like the light bulb.
ANGUS: Oh, and there's a reference
here. This next shot. Watch carefully.
There's a piece of metal
that flies by WALL-E.
That clanging,
like vertical piece of metal
is a reference to a piece of metal
in the shot in Aliens
when the dropship, the Cheyenne
dropship, explodes, and it goes right...
BILL: The one that
he's auto-piloting down?
Yeah, yeah. Not the auto pilot,
'cause that one...
No, no, it's the one that... Sparrow.
When Sparrow flies it in
and it explodes, you'll notice that...
BILL: I can't believe it.
Wow, Angus. Are you guys sure?
DEREK: You guys referenced
a piece of metal?
ANGUS: Yeah, we said,
"You know, just make it"
"like that piece of metal in Aliens."
DEREK: See, our references were
a little bit more conspicuous.
BILL: Man!
DEREK: That's pretty bad.
I tried to convince Ben
to make one of the languages
EVE spoke here Huttese,
but I don't know if he actually got it
into the final mix,
but she speaks a few
different languages there, too.
LINDSEY: Yeah. No, I think he did.
DEREK: Did he get it in there?
He loved the idea. That's so great.
ANGUS: It was just like,
"Chewbacca,"
or something like that?
DEREK: No, no,
just the one word in Huttese.
LINDSEY: Did you just speak Huttese?
- He did.
ANGUS: Yeah.
"Chewbacca." You know,
"Oh, it's the mighty warrior,
Chewbacca" or whatever.
[BILL SPEAKING HUTTESE]
[LINDSEY EXCLAIMING]
ANGUS: Yeah, or... Let's see...
[ANGUS SPEAKING HUTTESE]
LINDSEY: I'm horrified.
DEREK: Okay. Stop.
Stop speaking Huttese.
ANGUS: All right. Just one...
BILL: You started it.
ANGUS: No, but that was an actual...
BILL: You referred to it in Huttese.
LINDSEY: I have to go. I have to leave.
DEREK: That was a pretty clever
veiled use of Huttese.
ANGUS: Well, we were visiting,
we were doing some research
on the planet Kashyyyk...
That's with three Y's, right?
- Chewbacca's home world.
- DEREK: Oh, my gosh. It was great.
LINDSEY: So we get
asked this question a lot.
Why does WALL-E never pronounce
EVE'S name correctly?
DEREK: He just... His vocal
programming is not capable...
LINDSEY: See, that's not been
my answer. My answer has been
that when he said "Eva,"
it so charmed her
- that he just stuck with it...
- DEREK: Oh, okay.
- Because she giggled.
- ANGUS: I don't think he's that smart.
I don't think he's that smart.
LINDSEY: I think so. I think anything
that made her laugh
and connect with him, he just was like,
"Okay, I'm gonna stick with that."
DEREK: I think
he's just got limitations.
ANGUS: Oh, I think he's just blind.
I think he's just like totally...
DEREK: Wow.
You hate WALL-E, don't you?
ANGUS: I don't hate him. I just don't
think he's that smart, in that way.
- LINDSEY: Wow.
- I think EVE is a lot smarter than him.
DEREK: He's smart in a human... He's
street-smart instead of book-smart.
LINDSEY: I think he knows
what charms her and he just...
Therefore, he keeps doing it.
BILL: No.
ANGUS: No, I don't think you're right.
No, I don't think so.
BILL: I mean,
I think he would do anything...
- ANGUS: He's charming.
- I think he would do anything
to charm her,
but I think he can't help it.
It's just how he is.
ANGUS: When he says
whatever he says,
you want to pat him on the head,
right? You're like, "That's correct."
Like you're just there,
"You're so cute!"
LINDSEY: Right. But he could have
corrected himself.
I think he stuck with "Eva"
'cause it charmed her.
BILL: Well, you believe that if that's
- what makes you feel good.
- I will.
DEREK: Okay. How did this
amusing bass find its way in? It's...
That was in there in the reels
for a long time.
LINDSEY: It was.
From the get-go, I think.
DEREK: From the get-go.
ANGUS: I don't know why she has
so much hate for Bobby McFerrin.
LINDSEY: Nothing's funnier
than Bobby McFerrin.
DEREK: Coming out of
the mouth of a bass...
LINDSEY: It's true. Wide-mouth bass.
DEREK: There was a lot of thinking
that went into
some of the different objects
that WALL-E would find interesting
and useful.
And bubble wrap was the biggie.
LINDSEY: That's the name
of the music cue
- in here, is "Bubble Wrap."
- DEREK: Is it? Is it really?
ANGUS: I gotta say how awesome
this one move coming up is, right...
She presses it and then she flicks it.
Victor Navone animated this.
It's really, really wonderful.
- BILL: Yeah.
- I think it's my favorite shot in the film.
DEREK: That's pretty great, too.
LINDSEY: It's, I think, one of
the longest shots in the film. I mean,
you kind of think it's multiple shots,
but it's not.
BILL: See? See? She powers the light.
So that's how she powers
the electromagnet.
ANGUS: Yeah, but how? With
her plastic fingers? I mean, come on.
It's not that good of a conductor...
DEREK: So let's come back to
the VHS topic
here, because WALL-E clearly
recognizes the value of VHS
where you do not, Angus.
No, no. I'm just saying I think he would
go Beta. It would probably last longer.
DEREK: Is that a Beta SP?
Is that a Betamax?
ANGUS: Everyone agreed,
the reason why Beta failed,
it was a better product and then
the VHS conspirators got together.
So I would think, technically,
if you're gonna have a tape that lasts
that long, it would have to be Beta.
DEREK: So the real question is, were
copies of Hello, Dolly! ever printed
in Beta or VHS?
ANGUS: I believe that...
LINDSEY: I'm sure they're on VHS.
The Fox library was...
BILL: That looks like an industrial
Beta deck to me. Yeah.
Sorry.
ANGUS: I gotta say, too, that iPod,
when we started the movie,
that was the most current iPod
we could get. And now already...
- BILL: It's outdated already.
- It looks square, which is great.
DEREK: Well, a little bit of dating
doesn't hurt.
It adds to WALL-E's charm.
ANGUS: That's what
the movie's about actually.
DEREK: Exactly.
BILL: Yeah, it's not like the toaster
he keeps the tape in
is a really modern... You know.
ANGUS: That's what's kept it alive,
is heating it.
DEREK: No, the toaster doesn't work.
It's just a container.
Come on.
- BILL: How do you know?
- I know!
- Oh, 'cause you wrote it, right?
- No, I didn't write it.
ANGUS: Okay. He would totally die.
BILL: What?
LINDSEY: What?
ANGUS: I think if he hit the side wall...
DEREK: That would have been the
decapitating maneuver right there.
ANGUS: That's it. That's it. He's dead.
BILL: He's damaged.
LINDSEY: He hurt himself!
DEREK: So here we're coming back
to the all-important story point
of WALL-E rebuild...
BILL: The cannibalism point.
DEREK: Self-cannibalism,
self-rebuilding.
ANGUS: Hold on. I got it.
BILL: So, does he have a soul?
- ANGUS: Yeah, sure.
- Does he have consciousness?
- That we can agree, yeah.
- So what part does it live in if he can
replace all these parts of himself?
LINDSEY: It lives in
that little deck that gets...
ANGUS: It's inside his chest. I believe
that his brain is inside his chest.
BILL: So if that's where his soul is...
So if that gets destroyed,
he gets no...
LINDSEY: Well, let's not
ruin the end of the film.
DEREK: Yeah, man.
ANGUS: We already said
- there's gonna be spoilers...
- BILL: I said "if"!
- LINDSEY: Hypothetically.
- Hypothetically!
ANGUS: It's gotta be in his chest,
because that's...
Oh, but then that gets fried.
BILL: Does it get fried?
DEREK: It gets damaged,
but it doesn't get
- totally destroyed.
- ANGUS: You're right.
I think you just discovered one
of the biggest holes in the film.
I think we should just stop right now
and go back and try and correct that.
BILL: I think consciousness is
an emergent phenomena.
DEREK: Have we already
done the prints?
I think it's happening as we speak.
God, that looks beautiful.
Look at that.
LINDSEY: It's Andrew's favorite shot
in the film.
ANGUS: Her fingers are not connected
to her hand.
DEREK: Right. What keeps her fingers
floating there?
Is it the same kind of
counter... Electromagnetic...
LINDSEY: Same thing
that keeps her head floating.
BILL: Yeah.
What keeps her floating at all?
DEREK: Well, no, that's just it.
There's some sort of...
I mean, how much thought
went into the anti-gravity
components of EVE'S...
ANGUS: If there is a magnet holding
those digits in place...
- DEREK: Right.
- Would it not naturally attract
WALL-E's hand in that shot?
DEREK: That's how much she doesn't
want to hold his hand, though.
ANGUS: Oh, it's repelling,
so it's the opposite.
DEREK: Yeah.
Maybe it's a counter-magnet.
ANGUS: Is that what it's called,
a counter-magnet?
DEREK: No. I don't know.
LINDSEY: The anti-magnet.
BILL: We actually don't know
what kind of force it is.
DEREK: How do you say The Force
in Huttese?
LINDSEY: Anyone?
BILL: I don't know.
ANGUS: I don't think the Hutts
refer to The Force.
Do they believe in The Force?
DEREK: Yeah, they do.
They're aware of the Jedi.
BILL: They say "Jedi."
DEREK: They say "Jedi,"
so they must know...
LINDSEY: Is it canon?
ANGUS: "Is it canon?"
What does that mean?
BILL: He burps and says, "Jedi."
Remember?
DEREK: Oh, and he... Yeah,
and he references Jedi tricks.
ANGUS: Yeah, yeah,
you're right, you're right.
DEREK: Canon, Lindsey, is...
I know what canon is.
ANGUS: I'm just saying
if Jabba the Hutt
took things a little more seriously,
he would be
a little more concerned when...
DEREK: Hey, there's EVE'S POV.
Look how much different that is from...
ANGUS: You're interrupting
my Jedi conversation.
Oh, my gosh. I totally lost
my train of Jedi thought.
DEREK: I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
ANGUS: I'm just saying.
DEREK: What did Jabba need to do?
ANGUS: He just needed to have
the Gamorrean guards
- hold on to their weapons...
- BILL: The pig guards.
So they didn't lose them,
'cause he knew that that's one thing
Jedis are good at,
is picking things up off the ground,
specifically weapons.
BILL: That are far away from them.
ANGUS: Or in holsters. Yeah.
LINDSEY: Okay. Well, I'm glad
we got that established.
DEREK: Yeah, this is great,
how it goes behind the Fresnel lens.
I love this shot.
BILL: Completely non-physical effect.
LINDSEY: Yeah.
Completely cheated.
DEREK: Did anybody get
a real Fresnel lens to...
LINDSEY: Oh, yes.
ANGUS: Not in animation.
[DEREK GROANS]
- And it's sands for now.
- DEREK: Deep sigh.
Now this gets into another level of
WALL-E's peculiar stalkerness,
is that now he starts to kind of go
Weekend At Bernie's a little bit with...
ANGUS: Yeah. It's a little creepy.
LINDSEY: A little
Lars and the Real Doll.
ANGUS: Think it's a little
Weekend At Bernie's 2, actually.
- Well, I couldn't get her to play...
- LINDSEY: It's the pathetic first date.
ANGUS: And what a pathetic first date!
- He's so bored, he's...
- DEREK: I just love that he's, like,
making the song with his wheels.
LINDSEY: He's scratching.
ANGUS: I actually...
DEREK: That's pretty advanced.
ANGUS: They did go with
Sunday Clothes,
but I wanted them to do
State of Shock by The Jackson Five
from the Victory tour.
You know, it's... I can't sing it.
That would be
a violation of rights.
But if you go to iTunes and buy
State of Shock, it's a great song.
DEREK: So coming back to
the soul, Bill,
I think EVE'S little heart chip there
is also kind of the soul-carrying...
- Technology?
- Technology, and it's just a more
advanced version
of what WALL-E has.
But we had a lot of business with
the EVE heart chip in earlier versions.
BILL: Oh, yeah, I remember, but...
LINDSEY: "Oh, I remember!"
[LINDSEY LAUGHING]
DEREK: And here's the strange date...
ANGUS: Strange date?
He took a crowbar to her chest
and opened up her chest.
That's a strange date.
Surgery on the first date!
DEREK: It's pretty strange,
but charming.
ANGUS: He's trying to help.
LINDSEY: Again, the stalker charm.
DEREK: Yeah, he's got stalker charm.
LINDSEY: He's got stalker charm.
It's a rare thing,
stalker charm, but he has it.
ANGUS: Ow!
LINDSEY: I like this, where you see
the light bulb follow the dissolve.
DEREK: So I wonder how different
the sunsets would be
700 years in the future
if the Earth was covered
with an atmospheric gas...
ANGUS: And that's why
we made this movie.
We said, "What would happen?"
DEREK: It would be beautiful!
Hey, there's some old tech.
BILL: Yeah, it'd be beautiful,
because the red sunset comes
from the scattering
from all the dust particles in the air.
So if you have more dust particles
in the air,
you're gonna have more scattering.
ANGUS: I'd like to point out that
if he can play a Pong game that long,
he's very, very patient.
DEREK: Yeah, I can't believe you guys
let a Pong shot just go by unnoticed.
ANGUS: I mean, what kind of patient
gamer can do that? I mean, I get...
- DEREK: I know. Up to 8, 000?
- I mean, he could probably...
LINDSEY: He's been stacking trash for
800 years. He has patience.
DEREK: So Pong, was that Atari?
ANGUS: I think
Tetris would blow his mind.
- Who made the original Pong?
- LINDSEY: Atari.
- Is it Atari?
- It's Atari.
BILL: You love Pong.
DEREK: No, I missed Pong.
- I grew up in Atari 2600, Combat...
- ANGUS: You grew up inside, like...
- No, no...
- Like, please! Like Flynn in TRON?
BILL: "I was raised
in a Commodore 64."
ANGUS: "I was raised with
the Master Control Program
"controlling my every move!"
DEREK: I was at the age
where the 2600 was breaking.
And TRON came out when I was
10 years old, so that was a big...
BILL: Yeah. Well, we wouldn't be
sitting here if it wasn't for TRON.
DEREK: Did we reference TRON?
ANGUS: We asked
if we could reference TRON
"and they said," Please do,
"we're trying to get more awareness
of the film out, because..."
DEREK: To get ready
for the new TRON? TRON 2?
ANGUS: That was 1982...
BILL: "New TRON"?
DEREK: TRON 2.0
has been rumored for years.
- BILL: No, a neutron?
- Oh, got it, yeah.
LINDSEY: It's a joke.
It's a science joke.
DEREK: That was
a science joke, yeah.
BILL: This is going to
look great on Blu-ray.
DEREK: Yeah, we are not
watching this on Blu-ray right now.
ANGUS: You can't say "Blu-ray."
You're not supposed to say "Blu-ray."
Don't you know that?
It's like saying... What if you said...
What if this was VHS times, you said,
"We're loving this on VHS"?
No one watches VHS anymore.
Some people do.
Say we say, we're watching it
on videodisc...
DEREK: VHS is still popular...
LINDSEY: "Laserdisc," actually.
ANGUS: Laserdisc. There you go.
So say we're...
Pretend we're doing
the Laserdisc commentary.
We've just ruined it
for future generations.
DEREK: So this is a great little thing
with the cockroach staying still.
And he stays still, spoiler,
till the end of the movie.
But it's referencing the Hachiko dog
sculpture and story from Japan.
In Kyoto, there's a sculpture of a dog
that waited for its master, who died,
and the dog waited
for years and years and years.
It was a metal sculpture...
- ANGUS: What? Who fed the dog?
- Of this dog...
LINDSEY: That's really sad.
DEREK: No, it's this uplifting...
ANGUS: Who fed the dog?
BILL: That's fine, but nobody watching
this movie would see that.
ANGUS: What does he eat?
DEREK: That's what
we're here to point out!
ANGUS: Oh, my gosh.
That's gold. I think it's hilarious.
DEREK: That's just a beautiful shot,
and we all acknowledge it.
BILL: Yeah.
LINDSEY: Yes, it's gorgeous.
DEREK: There he is, Hachiko Roach.
I think that's great.
ANGUS: Are you going to put that
in subtitles below, Hachiko Roach?
DEREK: No. Maybe I'm the only one
who saw it, but...
ANGUS: Okay. No way. No way.
DEREK: Okay. Talk about it. What
almost was gonna be in this star field?
ANGUS: Okay. Right here we were
gonna put the Slave One rocketing off.
DEREK: Do you know what
the Slave One is, Lindsey?
- No, what's the Slave One?
- ANGUS: Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm glad you asked, because...
LINDSEY: That's really why I'm here.
ANGUS: I'll let Bill take this one.
BILL: You do know.
You know what the Slave One is.
- No.
- Boba Fett's ship.
ANGUS: Do you know
who Boba Fett is?
I do know who Boba Fett is.
BILL: What he's talking about is,
in The Empire Strikes Back,
when the Millennium Falcon
is stuck to the side
of the Star Destroyer, and
that's how they escape detection...
ANGUS: Which one is that?
LINDSEY: Right.
And then they like float off
with the garbage
- and take off toward Bespin.
- LINDSEY: I'm with you.
- And then...
- Didn't know it was called Bespin.
ANGUS: It's the Cloud City.
Everyone knows it.
BILL: And then you see one of
the tumbling pieces of
garbage behind them
slowly right itself and become...
ANGUS: And it's basically
this moment that
establishes what
a great bounty hunter he is.
BILL: And I just have to say,
it's an American flag.
- LINDSEY: Yes.
- We had a big argument about that.
- We did.
- DEREK: How close to the ship...
"LINDSEY: And I believe
Bill said, "Look,
"there are very few things
in American history"
"we can be very proud of, and one
of them is landing on the moon first."
BILL: We did it, yeah.
DEREK: So I don't know if the sun
- would melt that ship.
- LINDSEY: Oh, yeah, "The End."
ANGUS: Yeah, "The End."
There's plenty...
There's about fifteen "The End"
parts of this film, which is really great.
DEREK: The original... Hold on,
before we go too much further, the...
BILL: But, wait, is that Saturn?
Because Saturn's not blue.
It's not blue.
DEREK: That was an aesthetic choice.
But the reason to go by the sun
originally was a reference to the
Star Trek slingshot around the sun
in order to vault forward...
ANGUS: What,
so he's going back in time?
He's already in the future.
BILL: No,
they're not going back in time.
DEREK: It's not being slavish.
It's just being...
ANGUS: Wait, wait, wait.
LINDSEY: It's a wink. It's a wink.
ANGUS: No! Wait.
DEREK: It's a nod. It's not...
ANGUS: Back up, back up. Okay, Bill,
what were you going to say?
They're going faster than light, clearly.
They're passing galaxies,
- passing other worlds...
- ANGUS: I buy that.
BILL: But it just looks like
they're cruising. There's no...
- ANGUS: I know.
- I mean, later in the movie...
ANGUS: If they're going that slowly...
DEREK: It's scenic light speed, okay?
ANGUS: It's like in Doctor Who...
BILL: So they're not going full throttle.
ANGUS: No, like in Doctor Who,
when they're drifting, in the new one.
- DEREK: The new Doctor Who?
- Yeah.
- I haven't seen those.
- Oh, it's good.
DEREK: If you were slavish
to every scientific limitation,
you wouldn't have a movie to watch.
You've got to take some license.
BILL: I'm just asking!
ANGUS: I'm saying, if it's a reference,
then they need to be going faster
and they should be in a Bird of Prey
or something.
DEREK: Well, let me rephrase.
It was intended as a reference,
and then it was dismantled
when the sequence was...
BILL: Okay. We know
what that's a reference to.
MEN: What?
It's the Millennium Falcon being
docked in the Death Star.
ANGUS: Really?
DEREK: That's pretty good Death Star
lighting right there.
BILL: Yeah, totally, fluorescents.
DEREK: So now we're gonna start
going into the Axiom world.
ANGUS: Okay.
This I don't understand. Wait, wait.
Now, all of a sudden, there,
now we have gravity? I think that
as soon as they went into the hole,
there would be gravity because
- I feel like there's a second shield.
- LINDSEY: Not when the door's shut.
DEREK: No, there's a shield.
BILL: No, they turn off their...
ANGUS: I always thought
there should be a shielding in there
like in Star Trek.
DEREK: But don't you see a beam?
Isn't there some energy there?
ANGUS: First Contact? You know,
First Contact,
when they have the energy...
There's a great scene with
Alfre Woodard and Patrick Stewart,
and she comes on the bridge and
he's trying to prove they're on
a starship 'cause she doesn't realize
they're on a starship
because she wakes up in sick bay.
Anyway, he shows the... He
turns off the... He says that there's like
a force field, that there's no glass
or anything.
I always thought it was like that.
DEREK: Wow.
I forgot all those scenes.
BILL: I thought you were talking about
whether or not gravity was on.
ANGUS: I'm saying there's gravity
inside the starship
- as soon as they cross that thing.
- BILL: But we've already established
that in this universe that things can be
floated magnetically or however.
I mean EVE is a floater. Chill out.
ANGUS: Okay.
DEREK: So we're going to meet
a lot of characters here really fast.
That's M-O, and he is the third robot
with a POV in this movie.
There's the Predator reference.
LINDSEY: Look at that.
That's perfectly cued.
Yeah, I didn't even plan that.
BILL: I think it'd be
more like 98% cued.
DEREK: Actually, you know, there's
four POVs in this, four robot POVs.
LINDSEY: We have Auto.
DEREK: Because we have
Auto coming up, so...
Each one had to be distinctive
so you don't get disoriented.
ALL: Oh, "Scrutah Mah Boot."
BILL: I miss "Scrutah Mah Boot."
DEREK: Why don't you talk
about "Scrutah Mah Boot," Angus?
"Scrutah Mah Boot" was
a line of dialogue
that was uttered by an earlier version
of a human character...
BILL: Back when
they didn't speak English.
DEREK: Back when they were Gels.
ANGUS: And they had this kind of like
new language,
a kind of hybrid language.
DEREK: Kind of like Huttese, but...
ANGUS: Yeah,
it was similar to Huttese,
but basically it was similar to English
in that "Scrutah Mah Boot"
was meant to say, "Scrub my butt."
And they were this jelly-like substance
that would get a lot of dust,
and so there was a M-O character
where this human character woke up
"and was like," Scrutah Mah Boot!
"Scrutah Mah Boot!
Scrutah Mah Boot!"
- DEREK: And that became the mantra.
- That became this tag line...
LINDSEY: Yeah, we all have T-shirts.
BILL: Yeah, and that was
during the whole robot uprising.
DEREK: Yeah. That was more of a...
ALL: Yes.
Spartacus structure, WALL-E
liberating the slave robots...
LINDSEY: The Viking gels.
DEREK: Humans were gels, more...
LINDSEY: Green gels.
Like an alien civilization.
And midway through, it became clear
that this needed to be about people.
BILL: They were always supposed to
be humans, right?
- They had just devolved...
- DEREK: No. They were pure aliens.
- Really?
- For a while, yeah.
ANGUS: Originally they were aliens.
BILL: I thought
they were devolved humans.
ANGUS: No, originally
they were aliens,
then it was kind of
a Planet of the Apesy thing
where it's like,
"Oh, my gosh, they're humans!"
- DEREK: "They are us!" Yeah.
- Then we realized,
"That's nowhere to go." You know,
there's Planet of the Apes,
and there's the sequel, Beneath the...
Beyond the... Below the...
DEREK: "Beneath. '' Beneath
the Planet of the Apes."
ANGUS: With the bomb, right?
That's the one with the bomb?
DEREK: Yeah, yeah, with the guys
that rip off their faces. That one
- comes up in conversation a lot.
- ANGUS: I don't know.
DEREK: We actually did...
LINDSEY: In whose conversations
does that come up?
BILL: I gotta tell you the truth. I quit
after... I've only seen the first two.
DEREK: Yeah, probably... There's
some interesting, weird stuff later on,
- but, yeah, you're fine.
- BILL: When the apes go to Earth,
I know that happened,
- but I didn't watch it.
- DEREK: It kind of goes off the rails,
and the TV show. They kept lowering
the budget with each successive film
- and then it was just worse.
- BILL: Sure.
DEREK: Angus, have you seen
Planet of the Apes yet?
LINDSEY: As you do, yes.
- I have seen Planet of the Apes.
- Okay. Good.
Wow. That was a major tangent.
BILL: You know, tangents are
what this whole process is about.
DEREK: You're actually
absolutely correct. That's true.
But then you've got to learn
how to wrangle the tangents.
EVE!
LINDSEY: Here's humanity. Here it is.
DEREK: If you would've helped me...
Here it is. Is that John?
Is that Ratzenberger?
BILL: No, that's not John.
LINDSEY: No, that's not John.
DEREK: Well, one of the things that
you're gonna see entering this utopian
atmosphere is that
it's actually dystopian.
This is that dichotomy
we were talking about earlier.
BILL: Okay. Now, look,
you're preaching, all right?
LINDSEY: It's the irony.
BILL: This is the thing. I don't think
it's our role to sit here and explicate
- what we intended for him to be.
- DEREK: Well, you know,
it's some of the thinking
that went into...
ANGUS: Yeah,
it sounds like art school credit.
What I really wanted to do is
talk about...
BILL: Look. It's bright, it's colorful.
They tell you what to do.
ANGUS: Yeah, okay.
What I was gonna say is...
BILL: What's the movie? Them?
DEREK: Well, no.
Actually, the big idea was...
I mean, Brave New World, Aldous
Huxley kind of stuff was the intention,
at least for a long time.
LINDSEY: Well, that
and cruise ships in Vegas.
DEREK: Cruise ships in Vegas?
ANGUS: I didn't know we had to
read books for this kind of thing.
DEREK: Yeah, they are books.
We watch, we read.
BILL: Double good, double plus good.
DEREK: It is a Vegas cruise ship.
I actually went on a wedding cruise
during this movie
and I secretly was making reference...
Observations...
- LINDSEY: Wait, was it your wedding?
- No, no, no, it wasn't my wedding.
It was a friend's wedding,
but there was still...
LINDSEY: Were you taking notes?
- No, but I collected materials...
- BILL: That's John. That's John.
DEREK: That's John Ratzenberger.
LINDSEY: Did you write
the whole trip off?
No.
I wasn't able to quite pull that off.
But I was able to get some interesting
lessons in how surreal a cruise ship is
to actually be on, and it's...
BILL: Is it like this,
with robots and stuff?
DEREK: No, no, no robots.
But people are very different in
behavior, and there's just...
ANGUS: Are they kind of
large and lethargic?
BILL: Well, you're trapped.
DEREK: Yeah.
It's a weird, captive audience,
Vegas floating thing.
It's really hard to describe.
But some of the...
BILL: I love the way the kids are being
indoctrinated right from the start.
DEREK: Yeah, yeah. Again.
LINDSEY: Gel-babies.
DEREK: Brave New World.
LINDSEY: It's weird that "gels" stuck.
BILL: Yeah,
we kept calling them "gels."
LINDSEY: We kept calling them gels
- even after they were humans.
- ANGUS: If you hear us call them gels,
- what we mean is human character.
- Humans.
DEREK: Yes, gelatinous humans.
LINDSEY: But we slimmed them down,
didn't we?
- Stunning.
- You look great.
I know, honey. Men.
BILL: I love Lori's voice
as the beautician-bot.
DEREK: Yeah, it's pretty perfect.
BILL: And for you
Pixar fan people out there,
Lori did the scratch voice
for Mrs. Incredible.
ANGUS: And she did the voice of
one of the reporters in Cars, I believe.
DEREK: She's awesome.
I'll let her know she was called out.
LINDSEY: Yeah. She was called out
at the Geek Couch. It's nice.
DEREK: This sequence is called
"Axiom Tour," and it was an ongoing...
LINDSEY: Have you heard that there's
political questions about this?
- DEREK: What?
- "Blue is the new red"?
In, like, kind of an election year?
ALL: Yeah.
BILL: Yes!
ANGUS: I never thought of that.
LINDSEY: Yeah
BILL: Take a stand.
LINDSEY: Yeah. Totally unintentional,
by the way.
DEREK: Well, there's bound to be...
- BILL: "Oh, no, we didn't mean it."
- There's bound to be stuff that
- is gonna be interpreted, you know.
- LINDSEY: There always is.
DEREK: There always is.
Oh, and there's the lido deck.
BILL: WALL-E's a uniter.
ANGUS: Don't say. "There's this."
Of course, there's that.
- DEREK: All right. All right.
- I'm saying...
LINDSEY: Hey, don't critique
each other on the Couch.
ANGUS: I'm just saying that, when
you watch an audio commentary...
LINDSEY: We're all amongst friends
here, sitting in this very tight space.
All right. I'm sorry, Derek.
I love you.
DEREK: Nobody would know.
BILL: It does strain my incredulity that
she would not know
that there's a pool.
ANGUS: Yeah, like she's never been
to the pool before?
I mean, the ship isn't that big.
LINDSEY: They only look
at their screens.
DEREK: That's the point.
LINDSEY: They don't look at
each other. They don't look around.
- They just watch their screen.
- ANGUS: If you look carefully,
is there still ones and zeros
on the keyboard?
LINDSEY: Yes, there are ones
and zeros.
DEREK: This is
one of my favorite robots
in the whole show, the secretary...
- LINDSEY: Typing-bot?
- Typing-bot.
- ANGUS: All it can do is type.
- Yeah, you can tell it's my favorite.
ANGUS: And then it learns...
LINDSEY: What?
You mean the typing-bot?
ANGUS: The robot learns to wave.
DEREK: Yeah.
Hey, don't describe what we can see
on the screen, Angus.
- Oh, that's good, Derek.
- See? See how easy
- and how quickly you can...
- No, there's a difference.
I'm describing it. I'm not saying,
"There's the typing-bot."
I'm saying, "I like
what the typing-bot does."
BILL: And it's the other robot
that has the, like, HAL 9000 eye.
DEREK: Well, yeah, I guess...
This is the Autopilot.
Oops. See, I did it again. "This is..."
ANGUS: No, that's fine.
DEREK: See, Auto has a...
- BILL: Auto has the eye.
- And this is also a little bit of that
Aliens reference, too,
with the laser beam.
Now don't get the idea
that all we're doing...
BILL: A-113!
LINDSEY: Who's A-113?
DEREK: Everybody who's watched a
Pixar movie by now probably knows.
- LINDSEY: CalArts classroom A-113.
- It's a CalArts classroom.
People are getting tired of it,
but there it is again.
LINDSEY: We're not getting tired of it.
DEREK: Ever, ever, ever.
Now, as you pan
across the wall here, you're gonna see
the names of all the story artists
under the portraits of the captains.
- Self-promotion. Gotta do it.
- ANGUS: Are you in there?
Yeah, I'm one of those captains
on the shirt.
- Really?
- Not physically my photo but my name.
- Oh, your name?
- Yeah.
LINDSEY: Are you the woman?
DEREK: I think we've always tried to
make Kevin O'Brien the woman.
LINDSEY: [LAUGHING]
Nice. That's nice.
Just a trim?
DEREK: He approves.
LINDSEY: Can I just say that this is
one of my favorite shots,
where you just don't...
If you're not watching carefully...
You see her pluck his eyebrow.
It kills me.
- ANGUS: Oh, I didn't notice that.
- Yeah.
Wait. Wait a second. Wait...
[IMITATES PLUCKING]
Right there. Ow!
Yeah. Maybe only girls notice that.
I feel for him there for a second.
DEREK: I've always liked the idea that
the captain wears his captain coat
as a cape,
as if he's kind of forgotten
how to wear it.
ANGUS: Well, it just won't fit.
LINDSEY: He's become too large.
ANGUS: The symbol
you see on the elevator,
that double ramp with the logo,
it's kind of the Axiom symbol.
And I feel like when it's on the carpet,
if you turn it upside down,
it looks very similar to the Mandalorian
skull on Boba Fett's armor.
I always kind of think about that,
you know?
No one else sees that?
BILL: No, I missed that.
DEREK: I missed it.
ANGUS: But you know
the skull I'm referring to?
- BILL: Of course I do, Angus.
- Okay. I'm just saying, like,
- don't leave me out to dry here.
- BILL: I'm not.
I'm just saying I didn't notice that.
ANGUS: Just hang me out to dry.
You're leaving me out to dry.
- Are those the same things?
- DEREK: Mandalorian.
- LINDSEY: Mandalorian.
- Mandalorian.
LINDSEY: I'm learning so much,
you guys.
DEREK: Not, "Man, look, a DeLorean."
- No. "Mandalorian."
- "Mandalorian."
LINDSEY: One day this will all become
useful information for me.
ANGUS: I gotta say,
I always thought of that scar
through the eye, on the autopilot,
that little line, it kind of has a feeling
of the leader of
the New Mutants, Cable.
- BILL: You're trying hard.
- No, dude... Dude...
- LINDSEY: Total Recall?
- What? No, no, it's not that. it's not...
- Two weeks?
- BILL: No, not those mutants.
LINDSEY: It's the only mutants...
That was pretty good!
DEREK: Total Recall has mutants in it.
Thank you.
DEREK: Cable was
a late addition, man.
ANGUS: Okay.
I'm saying like the late '80s,
number-wise, not year-wise.
I think he...
During The New Mutants,
Rob Liefeld's run,
I think technically Cable
was the leader of the New Mutants.
BILL: I don't know. I think the whole
classic Byrne-Claremont-Austin era,
that was rocking. Hellfire Club...
ANGUS: No,
I'm not making a judgment call
about the golden era of the X-Men.
I'm just saying, technically,
that scar reminds me
of the design of Cable.
LINDSEY: What line are you talking
about through Auto?
DEREK: He's talking about the way
the casing opens.
ANGUS: The face splits.
BILL: You know,
the way the face splits.
- Oh, not in the actual eye, though.
- Not in the eye itself.
ANGUS: No. You see that? It's like
a scar through the eye, you know,
- and it's kind of like the...
- BILL: You know, I got to say,
it has always bothered me,
the decision to make
these holo-restraints, you know...
- LINDSEY: The bands?
- Conform, yeah, the way they could...
- DEREK: Why does that bother you?
- It just... I don't buy it.
- It's visually showing that...
- Yeah, it's clear.
ANGUS: I wanted them to be
more rainbows,
and it's holding it in the center.
BILL: No, I just...
I don't like their shape.
You know, they're shaped
like ribbon or cloth.
DEREK: Well,
it's like a lightsaber ribbon.
LINDSEY: Do you think it should be
more hard-edged or something?
BILL: Yeah, I think it should be
more geometric in some way.
It's a projected energy field.
ANGUS: Originally
it was more circular.
DEREK: Actually I think one of
the coolest containment things
was in the original Superman,
with those rings that are sort of...
- BILL: "Guilty! Guilty!"
- Phantom Zone!
That's double cool.
ANGUS: No,
that's not the Phantom Zone.
- They go to the Phantom Zone.
- DEREK: But that's double cool.
- That's double cool.
- ANGUS: That's like calling court 'jail."
No, they're not the same thing.
That's the courtroom.
BILL: All right. Thank you.
DEREK: But you know what?
If it reads clear,
that's the important thing. Right?
We're trying to make it, you know,
make it clear.
BILL: One day you will bow down
before me, Angus, you and your heirs.
ANGUS: Whatever, General Zod.
LINDSEY: I'm glad you guys are
separated on the couch.
- DEREK: I know. It's gonna get ugly.
- It's getting heated.
DEREK: The book's red.
BILL: Yeah,
did you not know it was red?
- Actually, no, I didn't. It's news to me.
- Have you not seen this movie?
[LINDSEY LAUGHING]
It's that easy.
Now, due to the effects
of microgravity...
ANGUS: If you'll notice, in the
live-action portion of the Captain,
he has four pockets on his chest,
yet this jacket only has two pockets.
- DEREK: What?
- Yeah.
LINDSEY: In the commercial?
DEREK: In the commercial.
- Again, that was...
- The commercial is recorded...
ANGUS: It's meant to be
the same jacket.
It's meant to be the same jacket.
DEREK: That is
hundreds of years earlier.
- That's meant to be the same jacket.
- No, it isn't.
You think that in the future
they have two less...
It's just because it's visually cluttery.
I think that technically it's... You know,
that's why there are only two.
BILL: Could have been four.
We could have done four.
ANGUS: I'm not saying
we couldn't have done it,
just that we made the choice
that no one was gonna notice.
LINDSEY: If you were better
at your job, we could have...
ANGUS: That's not what I'm saying.
There's no way that robot
could actually open a book.
That doesn't make any sense.
BILL: Why not?
Totally got that manipulator.
ANGUS: Yeah, but I don't think that
there's enough room in there.
This is nanotechnology.
DEREK: Is Auto
partially nanotechnology?
BILL: No.
DEREK: There's some pretty intricate
machinery in there, though, right?
ANGUS: No. Only 100 years from now,
nanotechnology was not at the era.
Oh, that's an awesome
Vaselined lens idea,
a total Star Trek kind of...
BILL: Soft focus on
the green Orion slave girl.
DEREK: That's the love lens?
ANGUS: Yeah. Like the love lens.
Like, "Who's Shatner into this week?"
LINDSEY: I don't think that comes
from Star Trek...
- ANGUS: "Oh, there we go."
- As much as everything else
in your world comes from Star Trek,
I don't think the Vaseline lens
comes from Star Trek.
BILL: Well,
that's where we saw it, Lindsey.
ANGUS: I think we would all agree
it was perfected with Star Trek.
DEREK: When did
the Vaseline lens start?
LINDSEY: All things begin
with Star Trek?
DEREK: That's a good question.
That's a good question,
though. When...
ANGUS: "Life began in 1968..."
BILL: Everything I learned
about Vaseline lenses,
I learned from Star Trek.
ANGUS: See, there's that scar
I was telling you about.
DEREK: What's the name of
the person on set
who carries the jar of Vaseline
for the camera?
Is that a job?
ANGUS: The grip? Which is ironic
because, you know...
LINDSEY: If somebody's
walking around the set
carrying a jar of Vaseline,
- I think that's probably a bad job.
- ANGUS: The Vaselinist.
I don't think they can... You can't say
"Vaseline." That's trademarked, right?
It's "Petroleum Jellyist."
[ALL LAUGHING]
BILL: Yep.
DEREK: I don't like
how she's mad at him.
ANGUS: Well, she's a very, you know,
impetuous...
DEREK: She has a sense of duty.
LINDSEY: She has a sense of duty
and a sense of, like, a job,
and they're questioning her.
ANGUS: Oh, I understand.
It's like she works at Orange Julius.
BILL: We've already established
that she's short-tempered.
ANGUS: EVE shows up, and he's like,
"Hey, what's up, slick? I got to work."
LINDSEY: Apparently,
according to you,
he's not all that bright, so it's not...
ANGUS: I didn't say he wasn't...
I did say he was not that bright,
but what I mean is, I don't think
he has the intelligence to say,
"She likes the way
I'm saying her name."
"I'm gonna say it that way
all the time."
LINDSEY: That doesn't require
much intelligence.
MEN: He's not a player...
LINDSEY: If you juggle for a girl...
- ANGUS: and he's certainly no dog.
- And she laughs, you juggle again.
It doesn't require a lot of intelligence.
DEREK: So for the two people
still listening to this commentary,
we worked hard
to get juggling into this film.
So, Angus, I can't believe
this whole scar observation
'cause I never saw it, and now...
LINDSEY: I never saw it
as a scar at all.
DEREK: I never saw it as a scar,
so I think you want it to be a scar.
ANGUS: I got to say I suggested it
- as an homage.
- BILL: Yeah, it's kind of like this...
- In Bug's Life.
- LINDSEY: Hopper.
DEREK: Hopper has a scar.
There's a lot of characters
who have scars, and...
ANGUS: It's a classic bad guy thing.
It's like he's been through it.
This robot has seen it all.
DEREK: We didn't want Auto to be too
Machiavellian, overtly bad guy,
- although there was an idea...
- BILL: Indiana Jones has a scar.
DEREK: Yeah, that's true.
ANGUS: But not through his eye.
DEREK: There was an idea early on
that Auto might have
a telescoping robotic mustache
that he could twirl from time to time,
but that got dropped.
LINDSEY: It got cut.
ANGUS: That's funny.
And that's also not true.
DEREK: It actually is true.
ANGUS: No way!
DEREK: You left the story room.
You missed a good year up there.
ANGUS: Oh, here it comes.
"You left us."
BILL: You missed a good year.
Earth, the surface of the world
as distinct from the sky or sea.
DEREK: If anybody listening to this
commentary hasn't figured it out yet,
this is Sigourney Weaver.
BILL: I'm starting to see
why that third act
- took so long to come together.
- Yeah. Yeah.
ANGUS: Everything was peachy-keen.
DEREK: Yeah.
This is Sigourney Weaver's voice,
- the voice of the Mother computer...
- BILL: Ripley. Ripley.
So shame on you
if you didn't recognize it already,
and double shame on you
if you don't know
why Sigourney Weaver was
sought after to do the voice.
ANGUS: So far
you've been shamed twice.
BILL: That's a double shame.
ANGUS: No, that's three shames,
should you not know...
LINDSEY: I think attacking
your audience is a really smart move.
ANGUS: Sci-fi is based on
attacking your audience.
Have you not seen a picture recently?
LINDSEY: I'm feeling attacked.
DEREK: Aw.
We're going into the repair ward,
- which is pretty exciting stuff in there.
- LINDSEY: It is exciting stuff.
BILL: This was
a very challenging sequence.
DEREK: Yeah, I'd say. Everybody...
BILL: Restraining bolts.
ANGUS: That's what the red thing
is called, the restraining bolt.
DEREK: Everybody has their own...
ANGUS: What is the purpose?
Story of woe when it comes
to the restraining bolt.
BILL: "Perhaps you'll learn your
manners on the master's sail barge."
DEREK: Yeah, okay.
Why don't you say it in Huttese?
BILL: I don't know it in Huttese.
ANGUS: Because
it isn't said in Huttese, right?
LINDSEY: Well,
if you know the language,
like you appear to,
you could probably translate it.
ANGUS: Was it EV-909
said that? Right?
BILL: I don't know.
- Yeah. I think so.
- LINDSEY: [GASPS] What?
ANGUS: That kind of wiry robot.
Little copper-colored...
LINDSEY: I've been disappointed by
both of you at least ten times in this.
DEREK: Did you guys come up
with acronyms and names
- for all these reject robots that were...
- ANGUS: Yeah, somebody did.
LINDSEY: Andrew
and Jim Reardon did.
DEREK: Oh, yeah?
DEREK: 'Cause I'm sure
there's probably
a lot of fun acronyms
and hidden messages
in some of the names.
BILL: Oh, you are, are you?
LINDSEY: Well, like PR-T.
- "Purdy"?
- PR-T is the beautician-bot.
ANGUS: I love this.
LINDSEY: And VAQ-M.
V-Q-M, or something like that.
It's the vacuum-bot.
DEREK: Acronyms are tough.
LINDSEY: It's true.
ANGUS: Put that on a T-shirt. I love it.
- "Acronyms are tough."
- Oh, gosh.
- ANGUS: I did miss you, Derek.
- It's been too long.
It has been too long.
LINDSEY: I've never actually...
The whole crash test dummy thing...
- ANGUS: You don't get it?
- Well, now, when I understand
what it is, I get it,
but I have to tell you,
you kind of need to know
what you're looking at to know that
- that's a crash test dummy.
- BILL: Yeah, there's a lot going on.
DEREK: WALL-E's pretty strong
to break through that glass.
- He's strong and he has purpose.
- BILL: All it takes is inertia.
DEREK: Only slow-motion shot in
the whole movie, I think, or two shots.
- BILL: What other one?
- No, I think those were the two.
LINDSEY: There's two shots there.
BILL: Oh. Right.
DEREK: So say goodbye to
the slow motion.
LINDSEY: Let's take a moment.
Let's take a moment.
DEREK: Well, you don't want to abuse
slow motion.
LINDSEY: No, or Vaseline.
BILL: Or lens flare.
DEREK: Lens flare is worth giving
a nod to, though, because...
ANGUS: 'Cause it doesn't
get enough attention?
DEREK: No,
it just has it's time and place.
ANGUS: Lens flare definitely
announces its arrival.
DEREK: Well, I mean,
aren't there lens flares
in a lot of those '70s sci-fi movies
in the way you get those sort of
bubbling lights and lens flare?
Isn't that sort of
purposely acknowledged
in the camera work in this movie?
BILL: I think this movie...
LINDSEY: Sure!
Has more flashing lights,
moving buttons,
- graphics...
- DEREK: Color changes.
Than any Pixar movie, period.
LINDSEY: That's a fair statement.
ANGUS: Want to see a shot that's...
BILL: And it might even top
most sci-fi films in general.
DEREK: We're not gonna
share battle wounds here.
ANGUS: I'm not saying battle wounds,
I'm just saying it's an amazing shot.
DEREK: That one?
ANGUS: No, the one of them
coming around the corner.
"Caution."
LINDSEY: You didn't count that POV.
The steward?
DEREK: Yeah, the steward POV.
So that's five now.
Caution. Rogue robots.
WALL-E!
LINDSEY: Yeah, the continuity of
all these things was insane. It was fun.
- All the lights and graphics.
- DEREK: Why don't you talk a little bit
about continuity for the uninitiated?
LINDSEY: Oh,
because it's insanely boring.
No, it's just, you know, making sure
that when lights go on, they go on
and they stay on. And when
they're turned off, they're off.
Because we do things
out of sequence,
you got to make sure that, every shot,
- that there's continuity across the film.
- DEREK: Right.
Clear.
BILL: I heard "continuity error."
ANGUS: I for one...
There were serious...
LINDSEY: "I noticed
17 continuity errors."
ANGUS: "There were
seven escape pods."
DEREK: People don't talk like that.
- People don't really talk like that.
- ANGUS: We just did!
LINDSEY: Clearly, you don't know
your people at the CON.
DEREK: Actually I have been
to the CON, Lindsey.
ANGUS: Been to the CON?
You got a booth
every year you've been to the CON!
DEREK: I have to say
how proud I felt last year
when Lindsey came to the COMICON
for the first time.
- And I am now a huge convert.
- And she's a convert. She loves it.
- I love the CON.
- It's really, really great.
- I've been on the CON tour.
- ANGUS: You were nervous about it,
like a waterslide.
LINDSEY: It was
much like a waterslide.
ANGUS: "I don't know.
It might be a little too intense."
DEREK: She was like...
BILL: Look at all those graphics.
- Those are great.
- I mean, the way they... You know,
- that's a lot of graphics.
- DEREK: Yeah, but it looks great.
- And it just never stops.
- It looks great. It's worth the fight.
- Everything moving all the time.
- But this is the future.
- That's what sci-fi is about.
- This is the future.
DEREK: What do you think
sci-fi is about, Lindsey?
What do I think sci-fi is about?
Yeah. Science fiction,
what does it mean to you?
[LINDSEY LAUGHS]
Why? Why would you do this to me?
ANGUS: Did you ever see
a sci-fi movie before
- you started working on this film?
- Have I ever seen a sci-fi movie?
Yes, of course I've seen a sci-fi movie.
- The Star Wars, the Star Trek?
- I've seen Star Wars. Yeah.
I've never seen Star Trek.
DEREK: You sat in when
we did some screenings, right?
ANGUS: At least you say "Trek."
I used to get so mad
- when people say "Star Track."
- DEREK: Say "Star Track"? Yeah.
LINDSEY: "Track"? Okay...
BILL: Oh, man.
In elementary school,
those were fighting words.
ANGUS: Also not calling them
"life savers"
was a difficult thing for kids.
DEREK: Lightsabers?
ANGUS: Yeah, people call them
"life savers."
We're like, "No, it's a lightsaber."
- Not "laser swords"?
- No.
DEREK: That's what they're called
in the original drafts.
- BILL: Laser sword.
- It's no joke. Ask Ben.
LINDSEY: I believe you.
Plant!
DEREK: I think George still calls them
laser swords.
LINDSEY: Is it in the grail?
What's it called?
DEREK: What?
- The canon?
- The canon.
BILL: "The grail"!
- ANGUS: No, it's not in the canon.
- It's not in the canon?
DEREK: Watch, just you wait.
WALL-E's gonna have canon
pretty soon, you know.
- When you get in this...
- LINDSEY: That's implying
that there's extra stuff
that gets written about it.
I know, but look at this.
BURN-E is canon.
- BILL: Totally.
- BURN-E is totally an example
of canon.
And for those of you listening
who haven't met BURN-E yet, he's
a little robot who does a cameo later.
And Angus is doing a short,
expanding his world.
BILL: I totally like
the Jetson ring effect.
ANGUS: Yeah, that's really nice.
DEREK: The Jetson ring effect?
LINDSEY: You do?
BILL: Yeah, when she flies.
LINDSEY: Because that was like
actually kind of a bone of contention.
BILL: I know. I'm sure, but I...
DEREK: We're getting into a territory
where there was a lot of debate
and discussion about
the scientific plausibility of A,
a fire extinguisher in space,
B, the concentric EVE rings,
and then C...
LINDSEY: The survival of the plant
in space.
BILL: What are you talking about?
DEREK: Oh, the survival of the plant
and the sound.
- Oh, okay, you mean... Okay, wait.
- DEREK: So scientists...
There was a big call-out.
What would a fire extinguisher do
if you pressed the button in space?
And some camps said that nothing
would happen because there was no...
- LINDSEY: Pressure?
- Pressure, atmosphere,
but others said that the pressure was
contained in the extinguisher...
BILL: Yeah, it was pressurized.
DEREK: It's pressurized,
so that once you pressed the button,
you would have
the crystallizing stuff, but...
ANGUS: So to solve the argument,
we went to space,
which really blew the budget.
DEREK: No, I think they went to
Messages and put a call out.
ANGUS: Messages is
the Pixar message board.
LINDSEY: They went to
Loren Carpenter.
DEREK: Yeah,
and you can always depend on
someone to drop the real science.
And this is an example of real science
meeting science fantasy.
ANGUS: Did you just say
drop science?
LINDSEY: Drop the real science.
ANGUS: Drop the real science.
DEREK: Yeah, yeah.
BILL: Like drop the hammer.
DEREK: Or like drop the beat.
Drop the needle. I don't know.
BILL: Drop the needle on the record.
ANGUS: DJ Thompson.
LINDSEY: Oh, no.
DEREK: Good Lord.
[ANGUS GROANS]
- What?
- ANGUS: It stopped.
DEREK: Oh, okay.
DEREK: Should we go back just to
get on that drop the needle tip?
BILL: Let it roll.
DEREK: It's fine to roll on.
- You can roll that.
- LINDSEY: We're good.
Sound in space, though, is an
often debated hot spot for sci-fi fans.
And 2001 is the only
movie that really did it.
- ANGUS: It's canon.
- That did it right...
ANGUS: It's true.
DEREK: and as much as
we love hearing
the sounds of the spaceships
and lasers in Star Wars and others.
ANGUS: Oh, but it's the same thing
in a spy movie of having a spy
- that's drawing attention to himself.
- Right.
- It's part of the genre conventions.
- DEREK: Or on martial arts films,
you hear a lot more sound
than you would actually hear
if two people were using kung fu to...
ANGUS: That's true. And they don't
always flex their muscles.
So you have a point.
DEREK: Sounds are exaggerated
for cinematic effect.
LINDSEY: Well, it's also become part
of the lexicon for everybody,
- so it's what they're used to seeing.
- DEREK: Right, right, right, right.
- It would seem abnormal.
- And for WALL-E, even though there's,
you know, I think a good deal
of hard science...
- Do you know what lexicon means?
- Lexicons? Yeah, I...
I think it's a little strange that WALL-E
can go so fast with the propulsion
of the fire extinguisher.
ANGUS: And how many
fire extinguishers have you...
DEREK: I mean,
how fast is he going there?
ANGUS: Do you know how much juice
is in a fire extinguisher?
DEREK: He's going as fast as that
Bug's Life camera in that shot.
- He must be going...
- BILL: But there's no friction in space.
- ANGUS: Bug's Life camera?
- There's no friction.
DEREK: Right. But EVE goes fast.
BILL: She's matching speed with him.
DEREK: So are you saying
that he's accumulating speed?
ANGUS: She could go way faster.
He's the pace car in this scenario.
BILL: He's accelerating, yeah.
DEREK: Is his speed accumulating
- or accelerating?
- BILL: He's accelerating.
ANGUS: He's the pace car
in this scenario.
DEREK: It's always kind of struck me
as a little strange that
he could go that fast.
BILL: If he did a squirt,
then he would go
at a constant motion,
but he's doing a constant...
ANGUS: Let me blow your mind.
What if he hadn't
gotten out of the pod?
DEREK: All right.
BILL: Okay. Okay?
It's constant motion
and accelerated motion.
DEREK: He would have exploded.
No movie.
BILL: Okay?
DEREK: And it's a very poetic scene
and I understand the creative decision
behind it, but...
ANGUS: Don't bring poetry
back into it.
DEREK: Scientifically...
No, it's a poetic moment.
They have a dance together.
It's a chance for WALL-E
and EVE to have a little bit
of that love stuff.
ANGUS: And the poetry
and then pizza,
- and that's the movie, right?
- Poetry and pizza.
- The contrast.
- WALL-E in a nutshell.
Yeah.
ANGUS: See, what's funny is he thinks
you can grow pizza,
which is kind of true.
DEREK: And it pays out later.
BILL: 'Cause they grow pizza?
DEREK: No.
ANGUS: He still thinks it later.
- It's kind of a charming...
- He can't let go.
- Of the dream.
- Okay. What's coming up here?
- Yeah, okay. So, this is the...
Coming up very shortly
is the introduction of BURN-E.
DEREK: What does BURN-E
stand for?
ANGUS: It doesn't stand for anything.
It stands for BURN-E. I don't know.
I haven't come up with an acronym yet
DEREK: Oh, are you serious?
ANGUS: Yeah, so here's BURN-E.
And so, they lock him out of the ship,
thus making his life hell.
DEREK: Great gag by Kevin O'Brien,
and now has spawned a feature,
- a short feature film.
- ANGUS: Yeah? Thank you, Kevin.
DEREK: That water must have been
tough to pull off.
ANGUS: Yeah, it's beautiful.
I like how safe it is
that they put a speaker
right next to the water,
that if you touch it with the water,
- it explodes.
- BILL: It explodes, yeah.
DEREK: Easily shorted.
ANGUS: I, for one, don't buy that at all.
BILL: I-4-1...
ANGUS: I don't know if they did it,
but I always imagined
the stormtroopers talking,
you know, in Star Wars,
when they're, like, "Oh, have you seen
the latest what-have-you?"
I don't remember.
What was that scene in...
BILL: Yeah. When Obi-Wan is
shutting down the deflector shield...
ANGUS: Shutting down the thing, and
they're talking about what-have-you.
"DEREK: Yeah.
ANGUS: Like, "Oh, have you seen
"the latest issue of Starlog
or whatever, and..."
DEREK: Ah, Starlog. I haven't seen
an issue of Starlog in a long time.
BILL: Oh, man, it's still going strong.
DEREK: Are you serious?
BILL: Go over to the bookstore.
It's there right now.
DEREK: What about
Cinema Fantastique?
- Is that one still around?
- BILL: No.
ANGUS: I know Cinefex is.
BILL: Cinefex is going strong.
- Cinema Fantastique, no. But...
- ANGUS: Starlog. I didn't know
we were nerding out
about fan publications.
BILL: Oh, yeah. My grandmother
brought me back the first Starlog...
ANGUS: Look at this.
I always thought this looked fake.
From a bowling trip to Texas.
- DEREK: Oh, wow.
- You know the one, Kirk and Spock
on the cover. It's just like...
ANGUS: Had Starlog
not decided to cover
Kirk and Spock, maybe that
wouldn't have put you...
What do they call that
when you get out of jail,
and you decide not to go back
to a life of crime, you go straight?
DEREK: Furlough?
Is it a furlough? No.
- Furlough's a vacation. No.
- ANGUS: I thought furlough was
a unit of measure?
DEREK: I think a furlough
is a military leave.
LINDSEY: Nice.
We can go back home!
For the first time! What's it like now?
No, no, no. Don't tell me.
I want to see for myself.
ANGUS: So, when we were
making this movie,
there's a lot of characters in the film
that are household objects
that do things.
And if you watch the elevator here,
I always imagined that,
that blue light is like an eye,
like he's like a little cyclops,
silently judging them and taking it in.
- Did you ever think about that?
- DEREK: Wow.
BILL: What, you mean like
in Pee-wee's Playhouse,
where everything's alive?
DEREK: Is that
your own little private cyclops?
ANGUS: No, I mean, I always thought
he was a character.
He would kind of be watching,
observing, silently judging,
like the Watcher.
DEREK: I mean, isn't that Auto?
What Auto...
ANGUS: Like the Watcher, you know,
and who's observing
the Marvel Universe,
not getting involved.
BILL: The one who always ushers us
into the Else...
ANGUS: Yeah, yeah.
BILL: You know, What If? stories.
ANGUS: Yeah, what if Wolverine had
decided to go shopping or something.
BILL: Not get laced with Adamantium.
DEREK: There's a little bit of that
in Childhood's End, too.
ANGUS: Which I never bought...
BILL: Childhood's End. Wow. Clarke.
Yeah, that's really good.
ANGUS: Those claws
are solid Adamantium,
to bring back Adamantium.
DEREK: Yeah,
but they're sort of helping
humanity, shepherding humanity
to the next level
of evolution or whatever.
BILL: But that we remember them
in the past.
DEREK: It's pretty...
ANGUS: Do you think
he has bone claws?
DEREK: Wait. What?
ANGUS: What?
ANGUS: Wolverine. Okay.
DEREK: Oh, we were talking
about Arthur C. Clarke.
ANGUS: Well, whatever, high
and mighty. I'm saying the What If?
You said what if Wolverine
hadn't gotten laced with Adamantium?
I'm saying that they did
one thing where he lost
his Adamantium,
and Magneto pulled it out of his pores
- or some crap.
- LINDSEY: What?
Anyway, in the end,
he was stuck with bone claws.
He doesn't have claws.
Look at the elevator.
Watching, silently judging.
DEREK: That's not
where you're looking though.
ANGUS: I know. It's a secondary read.
All I'm saying is, you watch this movie
more than once, like we have,
and you start to notice little things.
BILL: You start to
imagine little things. Apparently.
ANGUS: It's a bit of an imagining,
I guess.
DEREK: Yeah, all that bone claw stuff,
that's in
the nether-Bermuda-Triangle period
- of when I wasn't reading X-Men.
- ANGUS: Is that not considered canon
- of the X-Men for you?
- DEREK: No, it probably is canon.
I mean, I don't know.
There's so much out there.
LINDSEY: Spontaneous geek.
DEREK: What are you
talking about now?
LINDSEY: Nothing.
BILL: Nothing?
ANGUS: These are the same towels
we have in the gym here at work.
BILL: But these days canon doesn't
mean anything in the comic world
because they just,
like, start over, rewrite...
DEREK: Yeah, I don't think canon
actually holds,
except for Star Wars.
Star Wars uses canon a lot,
but I don't know
if the other universes...
ANGUS: So you're saying canon is
for film franchises?
DEREK: Well, I don't know.
I don't know, actually.
'Cause they have these
multiplayer online games, right,
within the Marvel Universe...
ANGUS: It's like Batman.
You got multiple futures for Batman.
- DEREK: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You got the Dark Knight future.
DEREK: Right. You've got Elseworlds.
You've got alternate worlds.
BILL: Yeah, which is real?
They're all real now,
so they're all existing simultaneously.
[ALL LAUGHING]
DEREK: We can acknowledge...
ANGUS: There's M-O scrubbing.
DEREK: You did it. You did "there's."
A "there's."
- ANGUS: You're right, I did.
- He totally did it.
ANGUS: I just want to highlight,
he's watering a boot right now.
DEREK: But there's soil in the boot
that he's watering.
ANGUS: Soil? Soylent Green?
DEREK: Soylent Green, yeah.
BILL: "Soylent Green is people."
DEREK: One of the many
Charlton Heston films
that we discussed in the story room.
BILL: "Soylent Green is people!"
DEREK: Planet of the Apes, obviously,
a great example of
dystopian science fiction.
ANGUS: She celebrated
his entire body with...
BILL: Soylent Green
is pretty dystopian, too.
- DEREK: What?
- Soylent Green is pretty dystopian, too.
- Oh, yeah.
- In fact, he sort of made a...
- He did a lot. Omega Man is dystopian.
- BILL: There's a string there.
It doesn't get much more dystopian.
DEREK: Yeah, yeah.
Omega Man is dystopian.
There's the Auto point of view.
ANGUS: Again, the elevator
watches on, judging.
DEREK: You're looking for cyclopses
in the background
when there's a cyclops
in the foreground.
ANGUS: Look. He's watching.
He's watching. He's the linchpin
of the entire organization.
He's the Keyser Sze.
Everyone's working for him.
Nobody knows.
LINDSEY: What? This is ridiculous.
BILL: Wow.
DEREK: Yeah.
You really have seen
this movie a lot, Angus.
BILL: Let it go. Every time I hear
the autopilot talk,
all I can think of is Stephen Hawking.
- ANGUS: Yeah.
- DEREK: Well, now, did Ben generate
the Auto voice,
typing into the Mac voice?
Isn't it a synthetically fabricated voice?
I don't think there's
a voice actor for Auto.
BILL: I think so.
And that's
how Stephen Hawking talks.
DEREK: I know. The intention was
that it would be a manufactured voice
as opposed to a performance,
which does the appropriate work
of detaching him
and he represents automation.
ANGUS: Stephen Hawking is totally
another sci-fi reference, too.
- That's good anyway, right?
- DEREK: Well, yeah.
BILL: He was in a Star Trek episode.
DEREK: Was he really?
Oh, you're right.
BILL: In that Star Trek: The
Next Generation Holodeck episode.
ANGUS: What was
the title of that episode?
DEREK: Oh, boy.
BILL: Oh, I don't know.
LINDSEY: Oh, my God.
DEREK: Look at Fred Willard's
emergency stuff. I wanted to...
I always hoped that the walls
would get torn away,
and there would be storms and stuff,
but that probably...
- ANGUS: Like Twister?
- Would have been expensive.
BILL: That would have been too much.
DEREK: Yeah,
it would have been too much.
BILL: So what happened to them?
Are there other ships out there
- and they're all dead?
- DEREK: The thinking was
that there were other ships
that weren't so lucky.
BILL: I see.
DEREK: And that maybe
there are some other ships
that survived.
Oh, there's the A-113 again.
- But, yeah, I think...
- BILL: So maybe they'll find them
- and bring them home.
- DEREK: But I think...
BILL: Just like the lost tribes of man.
ANGUS: Yeah.
"Many years before our time..."
DEREK: That's a great voice.
What's that accent?
ANGUS: "Some believe..."
DEREK: What's that actor's name?
- Is that John Colicos?
- Oh, no, no, no, the guy...
ANGUS: He did Baltar, but...
DEREK: No, there's a guy
who narrates in the beginning,
has great voice power.
Shame on us for not having that.
ANGUS: "That even now
there are brothers of man..."
DEREK: There's some amusing
elements to the Battlestar Galactica.
ANGUS: "Amusing." You sound
like a Star Trek villain.
- I know. I know.
- "You amuse me, Mr. Kirk."
DEREK: I'm gonna start
monologue-ing any minute.
ANGUS: You didn't correct me
on his rank.
I'm embarrassed.
DEREK: I didn't hear
what you said. What?
ANGUS: Nothing.
- I said Mr. Kirk.
- BILL: Well, he's a mister.
ANGUS: Yeah, he is, to the ladies.
DEREK: He was a civilian.
BILL: [LAUGHS] He's a captain to you.
ANGUS: He's a captain.
DEREK: You know,
that's kind of missing...
- ANGUS: Or an admiral.
- Do you think our captain...
ANGUS: Yeah, but he never liked
the admiral clothes.
BILL: Captain, admiral, captain again.
DEREK: Yeah.
- Yeah, he got demoted.
- ANGUS: He got demoted.
- Before he got...
- BILL: Your first, best destiny.
ANGUS: You know, I think
Spock says something about
how it was a mistake for him
to have taken the promotion.
- BILL: Yes. He did say that.
- You know, he wants to be close...
Kirk wants to be close to the street.
Kind of like the captain here.
BILL: Kirk is so street.
ANGUS: No, think about it.
The captain here,
the captain is living the life.
He's in charge of everything.
All of a sudden he realized
what he really wants to do
is save humanity
and actually pilot the starship,
instead of just being this figurehead.
- BILL: Totally.
- Just like Admiral Kirk.
LINDSEY: You guys, seriously?
This is ridiculous.
There you go, right there.
- BILL: Yeah.
- No?
BILL: He saved the whales
when he was an admiral though.
- ANGUS: He did. But he was...
- He was breaking rules.
ANGUS: He was breaking the rules.
Therefore, you could argue
that he had given up his command.
BILL: I suppose.
ANGUS: I mean, he relinquished
his rank at that point
and he was a rogue agent
of the Federation.
DEREK: That plant's in pretty
good shape. It's been through a lot.
ANGUS: We have a series of
various levels of it not being watered.
DEREK: Right, right.
And it survived the few seconds
in space, too.
BILL: Oh, that was an argument.
DEREK: Yeah,
that was an argument, but it...
ANGUS: "Wouldn't the plant destroy..."
You want to take
the most beautiful scene in the movie
and not have it
because the plant would die.
BILL: Yes.
DEREK: So, okay, WALL-E is...
BILL: But wait a minute. Wait a minute.
The plant is inside WALL-E, right?
DEREK: Right. And she grabs it with
her containment field the second...
ANGUS: Instantly, yes.
DEREK: So it's all good.
- It's pressurized.
- Totally okay.
BILL: I don't buy it.
ANGUS: So,
are you saying in her capture ray
there is an agent that simultaneously
puts air back into that bubble?
- It needs air.
- BILL: It's like a stasis field.
ANGUS: I agree with it being a stasis
field. However, I cannot agree with it...
BILL: If it's completely encapsulated
in a stasis field,
- nothing can happen to it.
- ANGUS: But there's no...
DEREK: Maybe EVE has
some oxygen-generating
- technology...
- BILL: It's like the Slaver Weapon.
ANGUS: Okay. Okay.
DEREK: because she's built
to get specimens in harsh places
and save them.
So maybe in an effort to
rescue the specimen,
once her chest is closed,
it oxygenates enough for survival.
ANGUS: No, you're right.
It would do that.
I stand corrected. No, you're right.
It would want to oxygenate.
DEREK: Oh, those were the little mice,
the little computer mice
that were chewing on EVE.
Everybody loved those.
LINDSEY: It's true.
WALL-E!
Activating airlock disposal.
DEREK: So this is sort of
meant to demonstrate
how they deal with trash on the Axiom.
And there's these giant WALL-As,
which are sort of gargantuan-scale
WALL-E compactors.
ANGUS: Originally
there were three of them,
and one of them watched daytime TV.
- Remember that?
- DEREK: What?
I'm serious,
there was one that was watching...
DEREK: Oh, was that when there was
the taskmaster guy down there?
ANGUS: Yeah,
a guy watching daytime TV,
and he was watching his soaps
and just doing his job.
DEREK: Wow,
this movie's come so far.
BILL: Wow, I'd never remember that.
ANGUS: And everything else
I've said...
DEREK: But the whole system with
the flattens and the cubes...
BILL: But there was the nice moment
when they recognized WALL-E
as a brethren machine.
DEREK: That's still there.
That's still there, I think, in the sound.
ANGUS: Oh, it's not there anymore.
DEREK: Is it not there?
BILL: No. They petted him, remember?
DEREK: That's not in there anymore?
BILL: No, there's no time now.
ANGUS: I don't think
it's there anymore.
DEREK: That's too bad.
BILL: It's not there anymore.
ANGUS: I forgot, we actually animated
that. We used to show them...
BILL: Well, that's because
it used to be EVE that got zapped,
and her whole heart mechanism
got ripped up
because we built all that
and shaded it.
ANGUS: That's true,
that's the secret to our films.
We always change it, and rework it.
DEREK: Keep reworking it.
ANGUS: Make it twice,
get it right the second time.
BILL: And it was WALL-E that
was doing the surgery on her.
ANGUS: And if you watch the trailer,
you'll see
a different version of this shot,
- which is not in the movie.
- DEREK: Yeah.
BILL: I kind of like that scene
where he was doing
- the surgery on her.
- DEREK: There was tons of great stuff
that didn't make the final cut,
but that's just the thing, you know.
You have to... It's hard.
ANGUS: If it doesn't work,
even if it's pretty,
shouldn't be in the movie.
DEREK: Right. But know, as you listen
to this, there's tons of great material
you're not seeing.
"ANGUS:" Know as you listen to this,
"there is tons of great material..."
Listen to you.
That's awesome. You sound like
the narrator. You should narrate.
I'd love to have a Derek Thompson
narration of this.
BILL: "Even now, as you watch this..."
ANGUS: Here's the scene
where she's holding a chip.
- "...in an alternate universe..."
- ANGUS: She's looking for something.
BILL: Yeah, but according
to quantum mechanics...
DEREK: Do I really sound like that?
ANGUS: Yes,
that's what you sound like.
- It's great. I love it.
- Is that what I sound like?
BILL: But according to quantum
mechanics, every version of the movie
that could have been made,
did get made.
ANGUS: Does exist.
DEREK: Did get made.
BILL: So, in another universe,
we're sitting on a couch,
talking about the scene
that we left out
where WALL-E was the one...
DEREK: I think in this universe...
ANGUS: Yes.
And that audio commentary is
twice as entertaining
as this one, therefore...
BILL: In that universe, we get to wear
those sashes with the little knives.
- ANGUS: And we've all got goatees.
- And we've all got goatees.
- Like your brother.
- Totally.
- Your twin brother.
- That's right.
There you go.
DEREK: What's that episode?
"Mirror, Mirror"?
- BILL: "Mirror, Mirror."
- That's a good one.
ANGUS: That's when I knew
I was really a Star Trek fan.
BILL: When you knew
the name of the...
DEREK: Do you know,
I think Kirk fights
himself at least three times
in the first season.
I think there's three different episodes
- where there's two Kirks.
- LINDSEY: How do you know that?
And he's either fighting himself
or interacting with himself.
BILL: I thought you said
we weren't going to talk about Kirk.
DEREK: I can't resist.
ANGUS: He's the only
match for himself.
DEREK: When I hear these dialogues,
these people discussing and arguing
over which captain is the best,
I can't believe it's even a debate.
BILL: Just in the first season?
ANGUS: We talked about Kirk again.
- I'm blaming you for that.
- BILL: It's fine. Let it roll.
DEREK: Kirk's all right.
- ANGUS: Okay. Fine. Let it roll.
- Just let it roll.
ANGUS: Let it ride.
BILL: That's how Angus rolls.
DEREK: That's how we roll.
LINDSEY: That is a ridiculous amount
of knowledge on a ridiculous subject.
BILL: It's a ridiculous amount of
knowledge on every subject.
LINDSEY: That is true. That's true.
ANGUS: Here, I have a lighter
I've been keeping in my chest
for the whole film.
DEREK: That was a huge thing.
- It was a huge thing.
- ANGUS: That was a huge deal.
Do we buy that he's had that thing
in his chest the whole time?
DEREK: Absolutely. Why not?
You've established
that he's a collector.
BILL: Well, I'm just saying...
It was supposed to be an indicator
- of his love, his time with her...
- DEREK: Exactly. Exactly.
- Because she found it interesting.
- ANGUS: I have an argument
about that shot, the laser bolt.
Is this an explosive bolt that fires
towards the hole and then explodes?
DEREK: Well, there's a little bit
of an inconsistency
with her bolts and blast.
- BILL: It's like a blaster.
- I think that she's...
- You see a bolt from a blaster.
- Sophisticated enough
with machinery to adjust the power
of her blast
based on what she wants to...
ANGUS: Mid-flight?
LINDSEY: Yeah...
DEREK: Sure. There's a scene later
where she shoots
the TV monitor, right?
- ANGUS: Yeah, but...
- If she's shooting with that power
in an elevator...
ANGUS: I'm not
debating the power, Derek.
All I'm saying is, when the bullet
leaves the gun, that at some point
from being a projectile,
it then becomes an explosive force.
- DEREK: Right.
- Without an impact. I think it would
have to hit the side of that thing
and then explode.
DEREK: I mean, almost all good
shooting video games from the '80s
would have power-ups
for laser bolts and bullets.
ANGUS: So you're saying
she got a power-up
- right in the middle of the shot?
- DEREK: Well, she's spirited.
ANGUS: Like she shoots the gun,
she gets right through
a mushroom or something,
and then boom.
DEREK: You know what?
Her power-up is her motivation
to get WALL-E to safety.
Look at that. Look at this thing.
ANGUS: "Her power-up is to
get WALL-E to safety"?
DEREK: It's her emotional motivation.
It's a ticking clock.
She's got to save WALL-E.
ANGUS: You remind me of
that one episode
of Buck Rogers when Jack Palance
played the cult leader...
DEREK: Don't ever say that
I remind you
of an episode of Buck Rogers
'cause that's pretty creepy, man.
ANGUS: No,
Jack Palance plays a cult leader.
- And he's a very, very...
- BILL: I can't remember anything
- but Wilma Deering.
- ANGUS: Was that Erin Gray?
Anyway, this is the episode
with Buster Crabbe in his ship.
BILL: That was pretty cool.
DEREK: What about Twiki?
Twiki and Mel Blanc, the final Twiki.
ANGUS: And let's not forget
about Dr. Theophilis.
BILL: Look, between Twiki
and that Daggit on Galactica...
DEREK: You know, I saw the real...
There was a chimpanzee in there.
- Do you know that?
- ANGUS: Really?
Yeah. At the Sci-Fi Museum.
ANGUS: Oh, I thought it was actually
a robotic dog in real life.
Of course, it was a chimpanzee.
It looked like a chimpanzee
- in a robotic dog suit.
- DEREK: They could have gotten
a midget or something.
But at the Sci-Fi Museum
in Seattle, you can actually
see the Daggit suit,
and they've got the TV Guide article
which has photos
- of the chimp in the suit.
- BILL: Nice.
ANGUS: Originally, when he put
the wires together,
there was gonna be
a whole series of things
that happened.
He was going to try different wires.
DEREK: Oh, right. So you were
going to see some of them...
ANGUS: And one of them, originally,
was the impetus for BURN-E,
where he was gonna try a wire
and that opened up the door
outside the ship,
and BURN-E could try and go in.
And then he decided,
"No, not that wire, the other one."
- And then it shut right in his face.
- DEREK: She used her blaster again,
but it didn't detonate the same way.
ANGUS: I'm saying that
maybe she lost
- the power-up 'cause she got killed.
- BILL: What are you talking about?
There's no power-up.
ANGUS: See, that's the second time
he uses the...
BILL: The holo-thing?
DEREK: The holo-stick?
That's right. The plant.
ANGUS: Apparently the autopilot's
depth perception is terrible.
BILL: It's not good, yeah.
Well, he's looking at it through a...
It's a hologram.
It doesn't have any depth.
- ANGUS: A holo-what?
- It's a holo-screen. It's a flat-screen.
It doesn't have three dimensions.
Just 'cause it pops up in space,
it doesn't appear to have any...
ANGUS: You're right,
and he does have
monocular vision. Therefore,
he would not have depth perception.
BILL: I mean, it's not like the hologram
of Princess Leia that R2 shows.
- I mean, that's, you know, complete.
- ANGUS: It's pretty 2-D.
- No, it's in 3-D.
- And it's breaking up.
DEREK: I thought it was 2-D.
BILL: What about the game
that Chewbacca and R2 are playing?
Those were 3-D.
DEREK: Yeah, those are
three-dimensional holograms.
- BILL: They're dimensional. That's flat.
- What's that called?
ANGUS: The game?
BILL: The actual holo-game?
I don't think they give it a name.
ANGUS: No, they have a name for it.
BILL: Well, of course.
ANGUS: Dejarik. You don't know
the Dejarik chess set?
BILL: They made up
a name for everything.
ANGUS: Okay.
Well, it still has a name.
LINDSEY: Oh my, I can't believe that.
BILL: Not canon.
DEREK: Oh, that chess set
has to be canon.
ANGUS: So if it's not mentioned
in this film, it's not canon?
- And by "canon," you mean...
- BILL: If it's not given...
- of the universe we are to accept.
- They gave things names later.
It's like you don't hear the name
of most of those characters.
DEREK: Even Star Wars was named
A New Hope later.
ANGUS: They never say Ewok,
but we all know it's Ewok
because of the merchandising
at the time.
- So is that not canon?
- BILL: That's a good question.
ANGUS: If it's created at the time,
although mentioned...
DEREK: They never said Bossk, even
though he was the first action figure.
BILL: It's a good question.
And with Star Wars, who knows,
because they are constantly
re-editing and re-shifting the universe.
DEREK: Yeah,
it's a very shaky foundation.
BILL: Whereas in Star Trek,
there's three-dimensional chess,
they call it three-dimensional chess,
they play it in front of you,
and you're done.
DEREK: It's not even
three-dimensional chess.
ANGUS: And they even have rules.
Two of the animators
got a Star Trek chess set,
learned the rules and were playing it
the entire thing. I couldn't believe it.
- DEREK: Wow. Is it a fun game?
- No, it's boring as hell,
but they were committed to playing it
and they learned it
and they earned our respect.
DEREK: So that's not
a dimensional hologram.
- That's a holo-screen on the...
- ANGUS: That's like an LCD screen.
- Yeah, yeah.
- BILL: Yeah, it's just flat.
ANGUS: A projection screen.
So it's not HD. I don't think.
DEREK: I mean, it's far enough
in the future where we have to be
getting somewhere...
ANGUS: And I think
they went back to it.
- DEREK: sophisticated...
- Well, they don't have guardrails
or anything. They don't have
any safety precautions.
Maybe they went back to...
DEREK: They didn't plan
on anything going wrong.
I mean, the B & I Corporation
is behind all this,
so there has to be
some mistakes in them.
ANGUS: Well, there's
some cost cutting, certainly.
DEREK: Well, yeah,
and it's clearly demonstrated
by how haywire everything goes.
No! No, no, no!
I gotcha!
BILL: Here's some physics for you.
John, get ready to have some kids!
DEREK: See, she says,
"Get ready to have some kids."
BILL: She's strong.
ANGUS: But she actually means
grab them.
- LINDSEY: She does, but it's a joke.
- She grabs some kids.
We had to ADR that.
Okay. That's a safety hazard,
right there.
LINDSEY: It is.
DEREK: Wow, man.
BILL: And this, this is
a total Superman moment.
She's...
- LINDSEY: It is.
- Stopping the helicopter.
DEREK: All in the design. It's all there.
BILL: Yeah, we intended that.
It was intentional.
ANGUS: I think
this is not a very safe design.
There should be a guardrail
around that.
LINDSEY: Things can get
crushed under there way too easily.
ANGUS: A small child
could get destroyed.
BILL: You think there's a lot of pennies
and coins and things in that?
LINDSEY: Yeah,
inside the holo-detector.
DEREK: Well, I don't think
the holo-detector has been activated.
- LINDSEY: It's never been activated.
- So they haven't had a chance
- to discover the safety problems.
- BILL: But there's a seam...
ANGUS: I don't think
they had inspectors
check that out. That's all I'm saying.
DEREK: So this is a famous sci-fi
movie cue coming up.
- BILL: Moon-Watcher.
- What? No.
- Moon-Watcher.
- Moon-Watcher? What do you mean?
- 2001.
- They don't call it Moon-Watcher.
DEREK: Is that what it's called?
BILL: The ape.
LINDSEY: It's called Zarathustra.
DEREK: Thus Spoke Zarathustra
or whatever.
Look at that. This is a big,
important cinematic moment.
- LINDSEY: Right here. Here it is.
- Wow.
- The wink, the nod.
- BILL: Moon-Watcher is the ape
- in 2001 who...
- DEREK: Oh, wow.
- That ape has a name?
- BILL: Yeah.
DEREK: Wow, Bill, you're good.
ANGUS: In what canon?
- BILL: In the book.
- Oh.
DEREK: Oh, reading.
BILL: Read the book.
LINDSEY: Books, yes.
They don't do books.
DEREK: No, I do books,
- I just hadn't read that one.
- BILL: I just don't get through a...
- Moon-Watcher.
- A Moon-Watcher a night, that's all.
DEREK: It's kind of amazing
when you think about it
because it's better
without knowing his name.
I mean, if I had known his name
was Moon-Watcher...
LINDSEY: It's kind of
a cheesy name actually.
DEREK: It would kind of take me out
of my caveman talking to monolith...
LINDSEY: You would, yeah. You'd be,
"Oh. Moon-Watcher..."
All of a sudden it goes into
a hippie realm that's not really fitting.
ANGUS: I like that the button is
conveniently placed near the ceiling.
DEREK: You're not supposed to
have to touch it.
LINDSEY: You're not supposed to
know it's there.
BILL: You're not supposed to need it.
ANGUS: That's again
where we're cheating.
BILL: You don't want to
accidentally turn off the autopilot.
LINDSEY: Yeah. If you're not there
- and it accidentally turns off...
- BILL: There's M-O.
DEREK: That's not M-O. That's M-O.
LINDSEY: There's M-O.
ANGUS: See, we referenced for this
by putting everyone on a skateboard
and then this is what they did.
Those that weren't familiar with it.
DEREK: We have to imagine
they haven't stood on
their own feet forever.
ANGUS: Ever.
DEREK: Really.
These are generations later
on the Axiom.
So none of these Axiom...
BILL: And yet we're supposed to
believe that they can?
ANGUS: No, but it's like in The Matrix,
when they say,
"Oh, why do your eyes hurt?
Oh, because you haven't used them,"
and that kind of thing.
DEREK: Movies are
about make-believe, Bill,
and I think you gotta... Hopefully,
the willing suspension of disbelief is...
LINDSEY: And if we haven't
ruined that by now.
ANGUS: Let's not fight. Let's not fight.
LINDSEY: Apparently,
we're all from Michigan.
BILL: Angus doesn't mind
blowing holes in the fantasy.
What did he say?
"Oh, EVE can't really fold up like that."
LINDSEY: You guys are
all blowing holes.
ANGUS: I'm just
letting everyone know,
there's no way her head is that shape.
LINDSEY: I am the romantic
in the group,
and telling you what I think
is actually the reasoning behind it.
DEREK: About hyperspeed?
BILL: I'm romantic
about this warp effect.
That's what I'm romantic about.
BOTH: Whoa!
BILL: It's kind of space art.
ANGUS: It's kind of a Francis Bacon-y
kind of thing there.
BILL: I like it though.
- I like the whole after-image.
- ANGUS: I like Francis Bacon.
DEREK: There's been
a lot of efforts to do,
between warp drive and hyperspeed
and all of those hyper jumps
in the various science fictions.
ANGUS: What's the name of
that dog-thing again
you were talking about?
DEREK: Oh, the Hachiko dog
in Kyoto, Japan.
ANGUS: So, at the end of the story,
does he see a giant laser
and chase after it?
DEREK: No, no, I think he just...
LINDSEY: Just dies.
No, just dies of starvation.
DEREK: Actually, I'm not sure.
You gotta look that one up, but...
BILL: Now, do we still see
the roach go into the landing pad?
DEREK: No, that...
LINDSEY: No, that's an old gag.
DEREK: That was a great...
BILL: I loved that one.
DEREK: I thought that was pretty, too.
LINDSEY: I know. It was a good gag.
DEREK: It was a great way to finish off
the indestructible...
LINDSEY: But it kind of
took away the tension.
DEREK: Right. Well, we're sort of
in emotional crisis...
LINDSEY: Yeah.
We got to get to WALL-E.
DEREK: ticking clock.
So, sadly, one of our favorite
cockroach jokes died,
and that would have been right here.
The cockroach was gonna
get landed on by the Axiom.
ANGUS: And he climbs in there
and gets...
LINDSEY: And he survives.
DEREK: Yes. 'Cause, get it?
He's indestructible
'cause he's a cockroach.
LINDSEY: It's funny.
Set up, set up, set up, payoff.
ANGUS: It's a running gag,
and that means funny.
BILL: That's pretty.
ANGUS: It kind of looks like
The Wreck of the Zephyr there.
BILL: The Wreck of the Zephyr?
LINDSEY: The wreck of the what?
ANGUS: A book. Van Allsburg.
Maybe you heard of it.
It's a picture book, my speed.
BILL: I have.
LINDSEY: It's a picture book.
DEREK: So we're not sure
how sensitive their skin would be
to this atmosphere and environment.
ANGUS: We're not sure, slash,
we never thought about it,
slash, don't care, slash,
it's too late to change.
LINDSEY: Slash. You know what?
The sandstorms are gonna kill them
long before the...
ANGUS: Yeah,
like you're worried about it.
How would the whole thing...
LINDSEY: Dude,
I'm just saying the sandstorms
- would take them out.
- DEREK: Hey, you know, they've got
a gigantic shelter to
protect them, Lindsey, the Axiom.
BILL: It's true.
LINDSEY: At the speed
those things come up?
ANGUS: You're saying...
DEREK: They're in the Axiom.
ANGUS: They are totally taken care of
all the time. All of a sudden,
you drop them in Burning Man
without their requisite water per day.
DEREK: Hey, was that a lawn gnome?
LINDSEY: It's a lawn gnome.
DEREK: There was
a lawn gnome in there.
- LINDSEY: Yeah.
- I don't think I saw that before.
BILL: See, here, this is
what I'm talking about.
Like, so if WALL-E's soul is in
that circuit board that got destroyed...
ANGUS: It's right behind
the circuit board.
BILL: Like connects to that.
DEREK: Yeah. You're asking
- the wrong question because it's...
- LINDSEY: But you know what?
- The soul is not...
- BILL: So he's getting a new soul?
ANGUS: No, no, it's a soul enhancer.
LINDSEY: The soul is not
a tangible thing.
ANGUS: It's like the soul...
No, no, no, no.
That's like the Cerebro helmet.
That's not actually Cerebro.
- It's just how you access Cerebro.
- BILL: That's what I asked you earlier.
Is there a single part
which houses his soul?
ANGUS: Yeah,
I think it's right behind his chest.
- DEREK: It's in there somewhere.
- Below the buttons.
BILL: And it didn't get replaced.
ANGUS: It's right below
the hi-fi buttons.
BILL: Whatever it is,
it didn't get replaced.
ANGUS: No, it was fine.
LINDSEY: No, that's the whole thing,
is that it gets replaced here
and then it reboots him,
If you will, and he becomes soulless.
ANGUS: Hey, when someone
tases you, you don't lose your soul.
LINDSEY: And then, her touch actually
ignites that intangible soul.
DEREK: WALL-E has
essentially transformed
her own electromagnetic energy
and it comes back to him
and resuscitates him, in a way.
It's like the love brings him back.
LINDSEY: What?
The spark thing you mean?
DEREK: A little bit. That's a little bit
of a sprinkle on the...
LINDSEY: It's the hand hold.
DEREK: No, the hand hold...
But there's the spark
and there's also...
LINDSEY: But that
doesn't do anything.
DEREK: No, but she's sings the bars
of the song.
LINDSEY: The song, but it's really
the hand hold is what kicks it in. It is.
ANGUS: Is that like amnesia?
- LINDSEY: Yes.
- What amnesia patients need
- is an old light bulb...
- LINDSEY: Because we went
back and forth on this. Do you know
how many times this got cut?
This was like, do you extend it,
do you not extend it,
do you cut this part out? They added
the humming at the very end.
DEREK: And do you know
what the beauty is?
It's that the audience can determine
- for themselves what it was that did it.
- LINDSEY: That's true.
DEREK: And it's not explicitly stated.
LINDSEY: I'm just saying all, the
whole movie it's been the hand hold.
They've never held hands.
DEREK: It's been about
the hand hold, yes.
ANGUS: And the cockroach
doesn't know he's broken
because he still got run over,
so their abusive relationship
is still intact.
LINDSEY: I just think the cockroach
is like the third wheel here.
ANGUS: Yeah, he's totally like, "Bro!"
LINDSEY: He's totally
Scent of a Woman.
"It's like the roommate.
It's like, "What are you guys doing?
"Did he kiss her?
Did he kiss you? What?"
"ANGUS:" Are you guys gonna
get some pizza?
"I was gonna get some pizza, too."
LINDSEY: "What are you guys gonna
do now? Wanna go to the Axiom?"
ANGUS: No,
we had an argument about that.
When the cockroach
crawls on her at the end,
we were like, you've got to get him
out of there. They're gonna kiss.
LINDSEY: Seriously, it's disturbing.
ANGUS: Andrew, you got to get him
out. And there was a compromise
- when he's gonna...
- BILL: It's not sexy. Out!
ANGUS: He'll be in the apartment,
but the door will be closed...
- LINDSEY: It's so wrong.
- While they're making out
- on the couch.
- LINDSEY: It's so wrong.
- Look, this part right here.
- DEREK: No, this is right.
This is good stuff right here.
ANGUS: No,
he's still getting serial right now.
He's gonna come out
in his skivvies in a second.
LINDSEY: It's about to become
completely inappropriate in a minute.
- DEREK: Watch carefully.
- Okay. The kiss? Nothing.
ANGUS: There's a sensitive moment.
DEREK: No, first she sings the bars,
hums the bars.
LINDSEY: Which is sweet.
I like that addition.
DEREK: I love that.
ANGUS: Again, I'd like to reiterate.
- You're ruining the emotional moment.
- LINDSEY: They've already seen it.
- The spark, nothing, nothing.
- DEREK: No, but the combination,
- song, spark, and then...
- ANGUS: Wait. She's holding on.
DEREK: She'd been holding the hand
before the spark.
- ANGUS: He can't let go.
- Get this. You've got to put
the jumper cables on the engine.
But when you start the car,
- that's when the car, you know...
- LINDSEY: All right.
DEREK: It's a combination.
ANGUS: But you got to make sure
you do it in the right order.
Otherwise, it's a...
DEREK: It's a harmonious
combination of things.
ANGUS: And then you want to
remove it in exactly the same order
- you applied it.
- DEREK: It's possible, is all I'm saying.
BILL: If you hook a battery
to a battery, I mean...
LINDSEY: Okay. Now we have to
talk about the romantic part.
DEREK: Yeah,
but when you start the...
LINDSEY: We're not talking
about a car battery.
DEREK: Let's talk about romance.
Go, Lindsey.
LINDSEY: It's why I'm here, people.
BILL: Science and romance. Let's go.
ANGUS: Oh, you're back. You're back.
LINDSEY: Yeah.
"ANGUS:" What?
But I got what I wanted
"and I was asleep. I totally missed it!"
Oh, cut to someone's
still enjoying Hello, Dolly!
LINDSEY: Wait,
where's the cockroach?
ANGUS: Here he is. He comes in.
LINDSEY: Here he comes.
Totally inappropriate.
"ANGUS: Yeah. And so this is where
we're like, "We gotta get him off,
"we gotta get him off."
I think he winds up on the shoulder
- or something.
- DEREK: See, M-O knows better.
- LINDSEY: M-O's like, "Get out!"
- "Give them a moment."
LINDSEY: Cockroach is like, "Do you
guys want to go back to the Axiom?"
"What do you want to do now?"
ANGUS: "Hey, hey, guys, what's up?"
DEREK: That's really, it's touching,
and we have hope
for humanity here. This is...
LINDSEY: Yeah, 'cause, you know...
ANGUS: This is hope.
If you look carefully, right there,
you can see BURN-E hopping along.
DEREK: That's actually
a pretty charming little detail.
But we get the montage at the end
to sort of give us the reminder
that humanity's going to be okay.
ANGUS: But you know
what's not okay?
That roof. They got to repair that thing.
BILL: All our pullouts seem to be
the same speed.
ANGUS: She shot a hole in it.
Thanks a lot.
- You came to my camper and...
- BILL: This is Bug's Life pullout speed.
- Here we are.
- DEREK: What does that mean,
Bug's Life pullout speed?
ANGUS: It means
you could set Bug's Life 2
- in the future and it would totally work.
- BILL: Yeah. Bug's Life 2 takes place
- right in that little clump there.
- ANGUS: That's awesome.
- I think we just solved it.
- BILL: John! John!
DEREK: Wasn't there gonna be
a bit with
Buzz or Woody waking up
in the trash pile
and being all alone
at the end of the movie?
- ANGUS: No.
- Yes.
ANGUS: I never heard that.
BILL: Toy Story 4.
DEREK: It would have been great.
ANGUS: How many of
your statements end with
"That would have been awesome"?
DEREK: No, not many.
We actually have a fine jar
for the word "awesome"
- in the story room.
- BILL: The fact that this is cave art,
- is that saying that we've devolved?
- DEREK: No.
LINDSEY: It's actually the evolution of
art that shows the kind of evolution
- of humanity again.
- ANGUS: Yeah, it's like this is
- Lascaux, France.
- LINDSEY: Yeah, we start back.
BILL: We started primitive.
We recorded what happened.
- ANGUS: The Egyptians.
- It gets embellished.
ANGUS: And then there's the whole
Bangles reference there.
BILL: Then we get advanced again.
DEREK: Oh, my gosh.
BILL: Oh, she dug a well.
I just noticed that.
ANGUS: Yeah, just like Superman,
you know, right through the...
LINDSEY: He's planting seeds.
Agriculture.
Planting seeds, the agricultural bot.
DEREK: Is that Etruscan?
ANGUS: It's a little haphazard.
LINDSEY: Vase art, yeah.
ANGUS: You need to keep
- those things in a row.
- DEREK: Etruscan vase art.
BILL: Very good.
- LINDSEY: Mosaic.
- This is mosaic from what period?
- BILL: Roman.
- Roman mosaics. Is that what it is?
LINDSEY: Sure.
ANGUS: I think it's actually
Arts and Crafts movement. Byzantine.
DEREK: No, it's...
ANGUS: There's Crush.
LINDSEY: The fish are
back in the sea.
There's Crush.
ANGUS: That's Crush.
"Hey, dude, everything's okay."
LINDSEY: Nemo. Hello, Nemo. Right.
- "It's not too late to turn back the tide."
- LINDSEY: And it's also showing
how man and machine
are working together.
DEREK: Now we're going
into the High Renaissance.
BILL: And this is sort of Japanese...
DEREK: No, no, Leonardo.
LINDSEY: Leonardo.
BILL: Oh, it's a sketch, right.
LINDSEY: Well, we were very careful
not to look like we were repeating
our same mistakes again.
You know what I mean?
- That we weren't...
- ANGUS: We didn't go into Rococo.
- We just went right from Renaissance.
- LINDSEY: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
- There's a certain point at which we...
- ANGUS: The Mannerists.
We got rid of the Mannerists.
BILL: Whoa, Angus.
ANGUS: If it were up to me,
we would have probably gotten rid
of some of the modern Cubist stuff.
LINDSEY: The
Nude Descending a Staircase?
No, that's fine. But I think that
when you get into people
that just directly influenced
without adding anything...
I like the Seurat here...
LINDSEY: See,
there's the Axiom back there.
ANGUS: The Seurat, which, of course,
is a reference
to Ferris Bueller's Day Off,
when they're in Museum of Art
and they see the little girl
in the Seurat painting.
DEREK: It's a John Hughes
movie, Lindsey.
I know that movie.
ANGUS: There you go.
I mentioned a John Hughes picture.
Thank God. We have not gone
this entire time without mentioning
- John Hughes.
- ANGUS: You know what's great
is that Cameron Frye identifies
with that little girl lost in the painting,
wanting to know
what he's doing in that painting.
He connects,
'cause he doesn't have a love interest.
His love interest is that painting.
LINDSEY: Well, he's the cockroach
in this whole scenario.
ANGUS: Definitely Cameron Frye
is the cockroach.
LINDSEY: Yes.
DEREK: Wow.
ANGUS: 'Cause what would happen...
Seriously, if he didn't go over there
to roust him out of bed...
No, he didn't roust him out of bed.
He made them come through
passive aggressive. Right?
- LINDSEY: Yeah.
- But that's 'cause
he's passive-aggressive.
LINDSEY: None of this
would have happened.
Everything nice happens
to, you know, Ferris Bueller.
DEREK: Isn't there a Peter Gabriel
song happening now, also connecting
to a John Hughes movie?
ANGUS: No,
that's Cameron Crowe, dude.
LINDSEY: Say Anything...?
ANGUS: Say Anything...
Is Cameron Crowe.
LINDSEY: Oh, that's right.
It is Cameron Crowe.
DEREK: Oh, my bad.
Sorry. Sorry, Cameron.
ANGUS: How do you... Oh, my gosh.
LINDSEY: Oh, whoa.
That's like confusing Star Wars
and Star Trek.
ANGUS: The sensitive
relationship films.
DEREK: Oh, dear.
LINDSEY: And there's a little,
you know, nod to the 8-bit. Yeah.
ANGUS: The game famous for if
you fell in a hole, you couldn't get out,
and then the game is over.
You have to turn it off.
BILL: And I'll have to
take your word for that.
- LINDSEY: Never played it?
- Never played that.
LINDSEY It's cute though.
It's charming. The 8-bit thing.
DEREK: Did you play with 8-bit games
as a younger person?
LINDSEY: My parents would
never buy us video games.
I never had Atari or Nintendo
or anything.
DEREK: But they have arcades,
you know.
LINDSEY: I played Centipede.
I was a mean Centipede player.
- That's kind of a girl's game.
- DEREK: So you were a trackball...
BOTH: Trackball.
ANGUS: Centipede is such
a perfect button-masher.
All you got to do
is use your right hand to go...
And the left hand is like...
LINDSEY: Are you just trying to
tell me I had no skill?
ANGUS: No, no, no.
No, when you see Billy Mitchell
or you see a trackball game,
like you see Mr. Awesome,
Roy Shildt, on that.
He rocks the Missile Command.
It's not recognized by Twin Galaxies,
but it is...
He does have the highest
Missile Command score.
LINDSEY: Are you actually quoting
that movie that I had to see twice?
DEREK: King of Kong?
ANGUS: I'm not quoting that movie.
LINDSEY: Not King of Kong,
the other one.
ANGUS: I'm merely saying
that Roy Shildt is...
LINDSEY: What's that movie called?
ANGUS: Chasing Ghosts.
LINDSEY: There you go. Thank you.
DEREK: Was Tempest
a trackball game or was it a...
ANGUS: No.
BILL: I could totally out-nerd you
- right now if I wanted to.
- ANGUS: I want to hear it. Bring it.
- Bring your out-nerdery.
- LINDSEY: Me, too.
BILL: Commodore 64.
ANGUS: Oh, yeah.
BILL: See, these are sprites. Okay?
- So, my brother had a Commodore 64.
- DEREK: I had a Commodore VIC-20.
BILL: I wanted to do a thing of the
Enterprise from Star Trek, rotating.
So I had to like draw sprites of it
in the different orientations
and then repeat them
to get like this little rote
- so it would like fly out, rotate...
- ANGUS: Wow.
- And then fly back.
- How did you do the Jefferies tubes?
- No, it's not that detailed.
- Oh, okay.
DEREK: Wow. Wow.
BILL: But I could have.
ANGUS: Did you have a shuttlecraft?
BILL: No.
ANGUS: How about the deflector
dish? Did you have a deflector dish?
BILL: It was, like, 16 pixels.
ANGUS: I thought the Jefferies tubes
were those tubes in the back?
That's not
what the Jefferies tubes are?
BILL: No, no, no.
Those are the pylons.
- Those are the nacelle pylons.
- ANGUS: The nacelle pylon.
That what the thing is
on the back with the...
- So where's the engines?
- BILL: The engines, yeah.
- Those are the warp nacelles.
- ANGUS: I always thought those were
- the Jefferies tubes. I guess not.
- BILL: No, no.
DEREK: Do the Jefferies tubes hold
the dilithium crystals or is that...
BILL: No,
Jefferies tube is inside the ship.
ANGUS: No,
that's how you get up there.
- Yeah, you climb up there.
- BILL: Yes, yes, yes. Correct.
DEREK: My engineering knowledge
of the Enterprise is a little...
ANGUS: Well, you would never
make it in engineering.
You clearly would be
in security, I think.
DEREK: I would not be a...
BILL: Yeah, but you didn't know it was
called the nacelle.
ANGUS: I knew
it was called the nacelle.
- I just forgot.
- BILL: Oh, right.
LINDSEY: You need to go get a life.
ANGUS: I have a life.
The life is apparently
- remembering crap like this.
- DEREK: No, you need to go...
LINDSEY: No,
you guys apparently do have a life
and it's fantastic. I have nothing.
ANGUS: It's a sub-cultured life.
DEREK: You have a meeting about
- a science fiction movie to go to?
- I do.
- Oh, yeah, you do. That's pretty funny.
- ANGUS: Yeah, we get paid to do this.
LINDSEY: I know. It's amazing.
DEREK: I'm telling you,
you're a convert,
- Lindsey. You've changed.
- You've changed me.
You've changed. It's good.
WALL-E is gonna change people
when they see it, and I think it's great
to know that the people who worked
- on WALL-E...
- BILL: What? It's gonna turn them
into nerds?
DEREK: Well, no, or compel them to...
BILL: I think it's going to create
a whole generation of nerds.
ANGUS: Yeah, it might. And maybe
a thing like it's like the I Am Legend,
where it's all of a sudden you...
DEREK: Do you mean
The Omega Man?
ANGUS: No, no... Well, whatever.
It's just the idea that everyone...
- BILL: The book is I Am Legend.
- Okay, fine, the book. I'm just saying
maybe everyone is a nerd,
and the non-nerds are trying to find
a cure for the nerdery.
- DEREK: And then he finds out...
- He finds out he is the outsider.
- Yes.
- You know, it's like he realizes nerdery
is everywhere.
DEREK: "I'm not gonna
let this happen."
ANGUS: The five kids out there
that don't like robots,
this movie is gonna fix that.
DEREK: How can you not like robots?
BILL: They're motioning for us
to wrap it up.
ANGUS: I think the movie is ending
here. So what we should do is,
we should go out, grab a coffee,
and then come back, because
we are gonna definitely have to
re-do this whole thing.
[ALL EXCLAIMING]
BILL: I can't do that.
ANGUS: Well, I'm gonna do my part,
and then I'll do your part as you.
BILL: Okay.
ANGUS: Yeah, you're easy to do.
All I gotta do is take
a little bit of me...
BILL: All right, then why did you
invite me in the first place?
ANGUS: Well, I wanted to get
your tone, and learn your timbre,
and then your sensibilities.
And combine that
into a nice audio commentary package
that no one will be listening to.
BILL: I think we should go.
ANGUS: I think we're gone.
BILL: All right folks. Goodbye.
LINDSEY: Okay.
DEREK: Thank you.