Supermoon events occur
when the full moon
is at its closest orbit
to the Earth,
roughly 223,000 miles away.
This can happen
multiple times a year, but...
...last year was different.
I'm speaking
with Dr. James Aranda.
So tell me, Doctor, why hasn't
this happened before?
Why now?
Is it genetically modified food
-or a weaponized virus?
-All right, let's just, uh...
Let's focus on what we do know.
No one, and I mean no one
should be exposed to moonlight
tonight. That's number one.
Number two is fear.
Fear makes bad decisions.
Have a plan,
stick to it,
and stay safe.
Number three, number three...
Everyone should know
that we are working
around the clock
to find a solution.
We will survive this.
We got you your favorite, Sean.
Chocolate cupcake.
We know you loved these
on your birthday.
I wish you were here with us.
I miss you.
We love you, Dad.
Come on, let's go!
No time. Keep moving.
My team and I
have spent our entire careers,
fighting against some
of nature's worst creations.
Found a way before,
and we will again.
It's important to remember
that this is not just
a global effort.
This is a human effort.
A way of life,
what we stand for,
the people that we love.
This is what
we're fighting for tonight.
Hey.
My mom thought
these might cheer Emma up.
Tell her I said thank you.
I have something for you.
Emma.
-Hey, kiddo.
-Hi, Reagan.
When the curfew starts,
please don't go outside.
Please find shelter...
Spare batteries,
in case the power goes out.
Make sure your phone is charged.
Pepper spray.
Just in case.
Thank you so much,
Mrs. Marshall.
Come on.
Cody!
Cody! Cody!
Wesley.
What are you doing, man?
You're shooting your gun
right at Lucy's house.
My niece is inside.
There's kids all over the place.
You can kill somebody.
I'm just trying to get ready
for tonight, Captain.
I'm not in the military
anymore, Cody.
We are all soldiers now.
You see what's happening
in Tokyo right now? Or Sydney?
Hell's coming our way, Wesley.
-Hell.
-Is that right?
You know,
I don't understand you, sir.
You're here to protect
your brother's family,
and this is how you do it,
with plywood
and chain-link fencing?
You don't worry
about my brother's family.
I got it covered.
I pray to God you do.
Because tonight,
when that sun sets,
it's gonna be
every man for himself.
Good luck tonight, Cody.
I don't need luck.
Hey, Lucy bear.
Repeat after me, okay?
-My home is a sacred ground.
I will protect myself
and the ones I love
at all costs.
-I am a survivor.
-I'm a survivor.
I am strong. I am capable...
All right.
I double and triple-checked
all the windows and locks.
The house is good.
What?
The house, it's all locked up.
All right,
just like we practiced
at the range a thousand times.
You chamber the round,
you aim...
and fire.
-Okay. -You're not gonna
have to use this.
Let's go over the rules.
Wes, I remember the rules.
Are you sure?
-Don't open the door for anyone.
-Yeah.
Don't make any noise.
Don't draw attention.
Don't hesitate for a second.
I don't care who it is.
-Okay?
-Okay.
All right. You call me
if there's an emergency.
If not, I'll...
I'll reach out to you.
We got this.
-Good.
-We're good. We're good.
We're good. Okay.
What's wrong, kiddo?
-Uncle Wes?
-Yeah.
Why can't you stay?
I want to stay.
I want to stay
more than anything,
but they need me to help them
try and stop this.
I don't want to die.
Hey. Look at me.
You're not gonna die.
Nothing is going
to happen to you, okay?
Do you remember when Daddy
used to tell you that story
about the three little pigs
and the big bad wolf?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah?
Do you remember why the big bad
wolf couldn't get in the house?
Because it was made of bricks?
It was made of bricks,
just like your house.
Nothing is going to get in.
I made sure of it.
I promise.
It's getting late.
You should get going.
I don't think I can do this.
Wesley...
We're the only family
we have left.
They'll figure it out.
They'll understand.
They can't do this without you.
And Sean...
he would want you to go.
"Always ready."
Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Move it! Drive on. This way.
Transportation
to the underground is limited.
Bring only what you need
to survive the night.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Curfew is
in place for your protection.
Please return
to your homes immediately.
One second, sir.
Transportation
to the underground is limited.
Bring only what you need
to survive the night.
All right.
Go ahead, Dr. Marshall.
Thank you.
Curfew is
in place for your protection.
Yeah, okay.
They don't
care about our rights.
That's right. Our right
is to kill these motherfuckers.
Yeah, yeah.
It's up to us tonight
to fight these things.
It's up to us
to keep America safe.
We are supposed to keep
our people safe.
That's right.
They're not gonna do it for us.
We have to do it for ourselves.
I trust that everyone
made plans for your loved ones.
I know it's not easy.
We have a nine-hour window
to assess, test,
and report our findings.
I would like to introduce
Wesley Marshall,
Global Rapid Response
team leader
and lead molecular biologist.
Evan Radcliffe
is second in command.
And Amy Chen,
chief Canis lupus biologist
and behavioralist.
They have been spearheading
our work here tonight.
Now we know that the supermoon
triggers rapid DNA mutation,
and is photosensitive
to moonlight.
We hope to see
if this mutation can be blocked.
This team standing behind me
has developed a liquid
we call "Moonscreen."
It is our hope
that this Moonscreen
acts as a barrier
between the moonlight
and human DNA.
What we discover tonight could
go a long way to finding a cure.
It is not hyperbole to say
that our discoveries
could save millions of lives.
Emergency services
will be suspended
from sunset to sunrise.
Please stay out
of the moonlight.
Good luck tonight.
Please
be advised, for your safety,
we are now in full lockdown.
No one will be permitted
to enter
or leave the facility
until daybreak.
All exit points
have been sealed.
Subject
number three entering facility.
Subject number three
entering facility.
Amy...
Whatever happens tonight,
remember, it is my choice.
I know.
I love you, Dr. Chen.
Don't worry, Dr. Chen.
We've taken
every safety precaution.
He's gonna be okay.
Myles can feel the supermoon
is about to rise.
All the Year Oners
know it's close.
They can feel it.
Whatever turned him last year
left a compulsive craving.
He's an addict without a fix.
Until tonight.
We are now entering
the final hour of daylight.
Our prayers are with everyone,
and the team at Aranda Corp.
Let us hope they find us a cure.
Stay safe out there, everyone,
and Godspeed.
Scoot over, kiddo.
Mama needs in on this game.
You know
I always beat you, right?
Oh, it's like, it's like that?
Is it like that?
Is it really like that?
But who wins the tickling?
Who-who-who? Who wins at
tickling, Emma? Tell me.
30 minutes to canopy retraction.
Hey. You okay?
We're in it together. Yeah?
Breathe. Just breathe.
Three, two, one...
Go time.
All staff to stations.
Hey, Phil,
we're over here on Subject One.
Copy. Moving in.
Sir. Step forward.
Good luck tonight, sir.
Whoa, whoa, ma'am, ma'am.
Ma'am, I need you to stay calm.
Your heart rate
is incredibly elevated.
Good.
Hey, hey, you sure this guy
passed the psych eval?
It's not like
we had a lot of volunteers.
How come
I always get the crazy ones?
Right?
Moonscreen
temperature... stable.
I really don't like
the name "Moonscreen."
We commence in ten minutes.
Ten-minute warning.
I can't believe
they volunteered for this.
-Let me get in there.
-Go ahead.
Excuse me, sir.
You don't even know
if the Moonscreen will work.
It'll work. It has to work.
Subject Three,
step forward, please.
Don't worry,
it's just a liquid nanotech
to protect your eyes.
It won't hurt.
All right.
Liquid lens team out.
-Formula team in.
-Vitals out.
God, I hope this works.
Good luck tonight, guys.
Keep moving.
Good luck.
Five minutes
to canopy retraction.
Spray him down.
Make sure you get all of it.
Start the clock.
Notate how long
the screen lasts.
Starting the clock.
All right, spray down.
Security, be ready.
Screen them up, guys.
Screen them up.
Good over here.
Chin up, chin up.
Three minutes
to canopy retraction.
Three minutes to
canopy retraction.
What happens if one of them
decides to moon the sky
once we open up this roof?
The formula penetrates
the thin fibers, Evan.
No one's showing their ass
and turning tonight.
I changed my mind.
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Are you listening to me?
We're losing Subject One.
Two minutes
to canopy retraction.
Help me!
Two minutes
to canopy retraction.
Wait, wait, where are you going?
Please, let me out of here!
-Should we sedate her?
-No.
Sedatives could interfere
with the test results.
She knew what
she was getting into.
I don't want to turn. No.
Please open this gate!
Hey! It's gonna be okay.
No.
-Just relax. It's gonna work.
-Hey!
30 seconds
to canopy retraction.
Get me the fuck out of here!
30 seconds to canopy retraction.
30 seconds
to canopy retraction.
-Canopy retraction commencing.
-Oh, it's coming.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four,
-three, two, one...
-Ambrosia!
Oh, my God.
Please, don't do this to me.
Canopy retraction commencing.
Yeah!
What's happening?!
He's fine. It fucking worked.
I think we're through.
I think we did it.
Dr. Aranda,
I think it's holding.
Start pulling fluid
and tissue biopsies.
Let's get everything
analyzed ASAP.
Subjects Two
and Three are Year Oners.
I want a comparison test
to see if they exhibit
any abnormalities
relative to our test group.
Dr. Chen,
I need you to analyze
those blood samples
from our Canis lupus.
Yes, sir.
Hey, I'll be right outside.
I just wanna go
check on things, okay?
Stay here.
Mom?
Stepping in now.
Congratulations, Doctor.
Stable.
Blood's looking good.
-Let's relay positive results.
-Very nice. Looks good.
Mitosis seems
to be holding, no mutations.
How are the samples
looking, Wes?
You seeing this?
Is it parasitic?
I don't know.
It looks like it
might be kind of
an immunological defense system.
Whatever this mutation is,
it looks like the supermoon's
triggering
a dormant defense response.
But why is it only now reactive?
Could it be viral
or pathological?
I don't know yet.
Evan, bring me
a different tissue sample.
Subject Three is turning.
Moonscreen stability
at one hour.
Stay back.
Everybody, stay back.
Fuck.
Get that formula spraying now.
Yes!
Where the fuck
is the Moonscreen?
Oh, fuck!
Dr. Aranda, what's the status?
-Look out! Look out!
-Move back!
Get back now!
Dr. Aranda!
Spray the formula, now.
Yeah, yeah, all right.
Watch out!
Move, move!
Oh, shit.
Close the roof!
Go!
The roof isn't closing.
Canopy malfunctioning.
Everyone get to an exit.
Now!
James! James, are you okay?
My suit... my suit ripped.
You're gonna be okay.
You hear me?
He's been exposed.
Wes, what the fuck
did you just say?
I need a tranquilizer now.
Evan, hurry up.
-Wes, go.
-James, stay with me.
Fuck, he's turning.
Where is the tranquilizer?
I'm coming!
James, stay with me.
James! You can fight this.
Get away from me! Get away!
Hit him with the tranquilizer!
-I can't breathe.
-Fuck.
Go! Let's go, let's go!
Go!
I can't breathe.
I'm living.
I can't... I can't breathe.
Attention. All staff,
please move to emergency exits.
Finish gathering
the blood samples.
Then I want you
moving to an exit.
Attention. All staff,
please move to emergency exits.
I got you. You're okay.
Attention. All staff,
please move to emergency exits.
It's okay.
Attention. All staff,
please move to emergency exits.
Is everyone okay?
I gotta get out of here.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Quiet! Quiet! Quiet.
-Where the fuck are you?
-I can't...
I can't see anything.
I don't wanna fucking die.
No, okay.
Everyone just stay calm.
We're gonna get out of here.
No!
Got you,
you wolf piece of shit!
Die, you fucking bastard!
Just go, just go.
Get out! Go, go!
-What's happening?
-Sorry.
Keep going.
To your right. Keep going.
You're okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Stay with me. Come on.
No, no, no! Go! Go, go!
Wes.
Oh, my God, Evan! Infirmary.
Out of the hall.
Go!
Wes, it's not working.
Wes...
Go!
Go! Go!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Jesus Christ!
All right. You're all right.
We have to stop the bleeding.
Move, move, move, move, move!
-Okay.
-Okay, hold it down. Pressure!
Pressure. Evan?
Evan, stick with us, okay?
You just breathe slowly. We're
gonna get you patched up, okay?
-Breathe, Evan, breathe.
-Hold both hands. Both...
-I got it. I got it.
-Both hands. Hold it down.
Evan, just stay with us.
Evan? Evan?
Evan?
-Evan. No! Evan...
-He's gone. He's gone.
What...
This wasn't supposed to happen.
This isn't... this isn't...
Okay.
I need... Myles.
-No, no, no, no.
-No, no, no, no!
-I have to get to Myles.
-Amy, Amy.
-Look at me! He turned.
-No! Let me go.
-No, the formula was working.
-Amy! Amy!
It didn't!
It didn't last for him.
-No!
-He turned. I'm sorry.
We were too late with Myles.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
I'm sorry.
I think we should just
stay here and wait for help.
We're not staying here,
we can't stay here.
We're not staying here.
There's no more time.
No, if we leave here,
we are gonna die.
If we stay, we die. Listen.
No more guns, no more guards.
There's nothing left.
Those things are coming for us.
That door's not gonna stop them.
Wes, think about
what you are saying.
If we make it past those walls,
we're gonna face the moonlight.
We got the formula. It works.
We need more than the formula,
Wes. We need...
Guns.
-A plan.
-That is the plan.
Fuck.
-Get the weapons.
-Here, cover up.
The formula will last
about an hour.
Close your eyes.
I'm gonna set my watch.
You set yours.
If one of us turns...
I'm not shooting you, Wes.
If one of us turns,
we lose the other, yeah?
-Yeah.
-Say it.
Yes.
When's the last time
you used one of these?
Outside a paper target,
when you and I were in Malaysia.
Well, let's pretend
they're paper targets
that are gonna eat us.
No.
It's Myles.
Go.
Don't slow down.
I won't.
-Wes.
-You guys okay?
Yes, we're okay,
but there was gunfire.
They got inside the houses.
I know they're still out there.
I know they are.
I just can't see them. I can't--
What? What happened?
I think they attacked Cody.
I saw them
getting into his house.
And if they can get into his,
-I just...
-Lucy, this is Dr. Chen.
Just stay calm.
The noise will attract them.
Okay. Okay.
Mrs. Marshall!
-Luce?
-Mrs. Marshall,
Mrs. Marshall, it's me!
There's someone at the gate.
Don't answer it, okay?
Mrs. Marshall, it's me, Reagan.
Oh, my God, it's-it's Reagan.
She's outside.
I don't care who it is!
Don't answer it.
-I need help!
-But...
It killed my mom.
Please, Mrs. Marshall!
I can go get her.
I can cover up and go get her.
Lucy, listen to me.
It's Reagan, Wes.
Don't answer it.
She could have turned. Lucy!
-Hey, Reagan, hold on.
-Lucy!
I'm gonna come get you,
all right? I'm gonna...
No! No!
-Don't answer the door.
-Wes.
Wes?
Oh, God.
My home is a sacred ground. I...
I will protect myself
and the ones I love.
I am a survivor.
I am a strong...
Oh, my God!
Fuck you, Sean. Fuck you,
you selfless hero prick! I...
How could you?
How could you leave us alone?
I... I...
Oh, come here.
-I miss Daddy.
-I know you do.
I know you do.
I know, baby.
Go! Go!
Move!
-My phone.
-No, come on. Wes.
-Get up! Get up!
Get up!
Come on, Wes. Come on.
Hey, I need you to stay
in your fort
and keep your headphones on.
Can you do that for me?
Go.
There you are.
This is for Reagan.
Hey, listen.
At this point,
all we are is prey.
Wolves are predators, and they
hunt their prey on the run.
What are you saying?
We shouldn't run?
I'm saying, a wolf or two,
we can run, confuse them.
But a big pack...
we got to stand our ground.
In a wolf fight,
you either dominate,
run, or die.
No more options.
In that case,
you stay as close to me
as humanly possible. Yeah?
Fuck.
I think we should backtrack
and cross over Fifth.
No, it's too far.
We don't have that kind of time.
Our only shot
is around these wolves.
If we cross behind the
parked cars, they won't see us.
Okay.
And if we make it through,
what next?
Let's cross that bridge
when we get to it.
Stay close to me.
Where's the third one?
Where's the other one?
Oh, shit.
The formula's gonna wear off.
-Wes.
-Fuck.
I think we should run.
Go, go, go, go.
-We have to get inside.
-How much time do we have?
There's no time.
-There.
-Go.
The gates are closing.
Go, get in! Go!
Hey, guys.
-Follow me.
-Hey!
-What is this place?
-It's a market.
Its tunnels
run underneath there.
We could use them
to bypass this shit.
No!
We don't want any trouble.
I will shoot you in your face.
We're scientists. There was
an accident at the lab.
We're working on a cure.
There is no cure.
Your kind don't belong here.
Give me a reason why I shouldn't
feed you to the wolves.
We're just trying
to get to my family,
make sure they're safe.
That's it.
We just want to use the tunnels.
I'll take you
to the tunnel entrance.
Then...
you're on your own.
Oh, my God.
-Stand back.
-It's gonna be loud.
Hold your ears.
Now!
Die, you fuck.
Wes, come on, let's go. Get up.
Stop!
We need to reapply.
-What does that mean?
-It's too hot.
Bodega.
Cover up.
I don't care what you hear
or what you see,
do not look up,
do not drop that tarp. Okay?
My count.
One, two, go!
It's like a dinner bell.
We need to shut it off.
-We good?
-It's close.
You remember
when a full moon meant...
...something cool and magical?
God, we gotta find a way
back to that again.
It's the only way
to go on with life.
I don't even know
what that looks like anymore.
"Go on with life."
You know, I've been around
this planet five times over
chasing pandemics?
I never had time for a family.
I didn't want one.
Give me a crisis...
I can handle that.
Now I have my brother's family,
and I don't know
how to take care of 'em.
You're giving them your best.
That's the problem.
I don't think
my best is good enough.
It's ready.
All right.
We just need to find
something to keep it cold.
-I'll go check the back.
-Mm.
Hey.
Hey. How did you get in here?
Oh, fuck.
Stop.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Don't make me shoot you.
Stop!
Jesus.
I almost...
Just a kid.
I know.
Let's get out of here.
Stay here, baby.
My home is a sacred ground.
I will protect myself and
the ones I love at all costs.
I am a survivor.
I am strong. I am capable.
I bend, but I do not break.
Cody Walker, get the hell
off my property!
You hear that?
That's a 12-gauge shotgun,
and I swear to God,
I'll blow your fucking head off.
Yeah!
Come here.
I'm here.
Oh, shit.
Goddamn it!
Come on. Come on. Stay with me.
Emma, get over here.
Damn it.
Light this up
like we practiced, okay?
Where are you?
I am not gonna warn you again.
You leave now,
or I will shoot anyone
that tries
to get inside my house.
Fuck.
Nails... it'll hold them.
Hot, down.
-Check your six!
-On it.
Move.
Got one coming from northbound.
Shoot, motherfucker, shoot!
Good. Looks good.
Move in!
-On your left!
-He's running! Get him!
Yeah!
Move up! Move up!
-Who are these guys?
-Get him now!
I don't know, but they're gonna
get us the hell out of here.
Forward!
Ceasefire. Ceasefire.
Yeah, boys, they're gone.
Got 'em on the run.
Think we got 'em.
Yeah, motherfucker.
Good shooting, men.
-Hey!
-Stay right there!
-Don't move.
-No, no, no! We're friendlies.
-Don't move, motherfucker!
Don't shoot.
Did you hear? Don't move!
-We're the CDC.
-We're friendlies.
-We're with the CDC.
-Don't shoot!
Stop talking.
-Look, look. We're not turning.
-No, we're protected!
-Look, look, look, look. We're
protected. -We're protected.
-It blocks the light. It works.
-That's bullshit, man!
-No, we're friendlies.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't shoot.
Fuck!
Go forward.
Mommy!
Fuck.
Four left.
They're forming a kill circle.
If we stay here,
we're gonna die.
We get to the Bronco.
It's our only shot.
You get to that gun,
I'll be a distraction.
-What?
-I have a theory.
I'm going to test it.
-No.
-You want to get to Lucy?
Trust me.
Don't die.
Go.
Hey!
Hey, you forgot one!
Look at me.
Hey!
Bite me.
Amy! Now!
Come on, come on, come on!
No! No!
Come on. Come on!
I will kill every one
of you motherfuckers!
Get behind the couch.
Fuck!
Emma.
They're gonna get in, okay?
If you see something,
you point and you spray.
Can you do that?
-I'm scared, Mom.
-I know.
I know, but you're brave, too.
You point and you spray.
Mm.
All right,
you hairy motherfuckers.
Come fetch.
Whoo! You motherfucker!
Oh, shit.
Motherfucker.
It's okay. It's over, okay?
Here.
Lucy? Emma?
Hey. Come here.
Uncle Wes, I missed you so much.
You okay?
Come on.
-What happened at the lab?
-It's a long story.
I should have never left.
Are you... are you okay?
Let me see.
Yeah, yeah. It's not my blood.
Most of it anyway. We're good.
Okay. Okay. We're okay.
We're okay.
It's gonna be daylight soon.
Just go get me the shotgun.
No more shells.
No more shells? What did you do?
It's been a busy night.
He's not dead.
Go.
What are we gonna do?
It's okay.
Come over here.
I want you to make me a promise.
No matter what happens,
when you grow up,
I want you to be brave,
and I want you to be strong,
just like your daddy.
Okay? You know why?
Because you have a heart
just like your daddy.
You promise me?
Good girl.
What's going on?
This house isn't gonna
last much longer.
Wait. What are you
talking about?
No, no, no, no.
You can't go out there. Look,
we-we can stick together.
We can fight this. We...
If we wait it out until sunrise,
we can survive this.
This watch is set for sunrise.
You have 15 minutes.
Always ready.
No, Wes.
I love you guys.
I never liked you, Cody.
And I'm gonna fucking bury you.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Is Uncle Wes okay?
What's going on?
Look, this is what
we're gonna do, okay?
You're gonna hide in here
with your eyes closed.
No matter what you hear,
you do not come out.
-You do not make a sound.
-Okay.
Get in, get in, get in.
Listen, listen...
if something happens, okay,
I want you to wait
until you hear sirens,
and then you run to the
neighbors for help, okay? Okay.
I love you.
-I love you, too, Mom.
-Okay.
Wes... Wesley!
Wesley, please. Please.
Please, I know you can hear me.
I know you can hear me.
Please don't do this.
Oh, God.
No...
Wes!
Wes, Wes, we're your...
we're your family,
and we love you. We...
Please don't do this
to us. Please.
Oh, God!
Oh. Oh, God!
Think of your...
think of your brother.
Think of Sean.
Remember...
remember your brother, Sean.
Think of... think of Emma.
Think of Emma, your niece.
Think of how much you love her.
And we love you so much.
Wes, it's me.
It's Sean.
I'm sorry.
Always ready.