Come, Mitsah.
It's Buck!
Buck!
I'll be damned!
You remember old Charlie, huh?
You've aged too, poor Buck.
He's a puppy of yours. Here.
Did you come to die at Charlie's?
Die? Why?
Because when a wolf refuses food,
it is a sign that he is about to die.
Poor Buck.
No, Mitsah!
Stop it! Leave him alone.
He was born in the forest,
his mother is a she-wolf.
The teeth are wolf fangs.
They are white as snow.
Yeah, it's true.
We'll call him White Fang.
It hurts, huh? Poor little wolf.
Wolves like you are always hungry.
Here, eat.
Bravo, White Fang.
Mitsah!
Careful, no, it's dangerous!
Mitsah, no, it's a wolf!
Come back!
Mitsah, get up immediately!
He's good! Didn't you see, daddy?
He's like a little dog.
You shouldn't have set him free.
It's dangerous.
No, White Fang is not dangerous.
We already love each other.
You, come here!
Come here!
Don't be afraid, White Fang!
You made him run away!
Listen, Mitsah.
He has the nature of a wolf,
he must live free.
You can't force him.
Do you understand?
A hunter like you should know that.
Yes, but we were already friends.
Come on, don't think about it.
Come.
Come on!
- Mr. Kurt Janssen!
- Charlie! Charlie!
Kurt! What are you doing
on this side of the river, huh?
Charlie, this is Jason Scott.
Nice to meet you.
Kurt's friend are my friend.
Do you have anything to warm us up?
Mitsah, bring a drink. Do you know
my puppy? His name is Mitsah.
Hi, Mitsah.
Does Mr. Scott
is into mining like you?
It's good, it's strong!
That's what it takes.
He's a miner too, in a way,
but he's not looking for gold.
He's trying to dig out the truth.
I am a writer and also a journalist.
I travel to find new things to tell.
People, facts,
anything that might be of interest.
You'll have lots of things to tell,
your people have gone mad.
- All they think about is gold.
- Yeah, that's why he came here.
From New York to San Francisco
all they talk about is the Klondike.
Is there a boat to go up the river?
You're going to Dawson City.
It's a bad place.
A hunter like you
could make a fortune there.
All those prospectors must eat!
We have to go,
the weather is changing.
Dawson City is a corrupt city,
full of swindlers.
I'll never go there.
Even if the government
has forbidden to carry weapons,
I don't trust those people. Good!
Let's go.
How are you doing?
Come on.
Hall, we're slow with the gambling
at the saloon, get some ideas.
My motto will have to be...
"To entertain Dawson City,
there's only Beauty Smith."
Look at our reverend.
Listen, you filthy drunkard.
Do you know why
I let you pretend to be a priest?
Yes, because you have pity on me,
Beauty.
Sure, that's one reason,
but there's also another one.
I don't want a real priest around.
You're right, true words.
"Beware of nosy hypocrites",
said Abraham.
A real priest would make trouble
and you're a smart man, Beauty.
You know these things very well.
You smell like alcohol
when you preach to the parishioners.
You know how is going to end?
They'll kick you out of that mission.
No, Beauty, if you don't want
them to do it, they won't dare.
No, but I will, before they do.
If you want to keep pocketing
their offers
you will have to be
a man of all virtues.
The boat is coming.
The boat is coming!
Your place is not in that filthy bar.
Your place is down at the dock
to welcome your sheep!
- What the hell!
- Sorry, I didn't do that on purpose.
- Sorry.
- I don't care about your excuses!
- No need to get angry.
- What's it got to do with you?
She didn't bump you, I did.
I didn't see you.
You don't see well.
I'll tell you again, it was me.
And I did it on purpose,
because I don't like you.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me!
- Daisy?
- Yes, sister.
What is someone like you
doing in Dawson City?
What I do everywhere,
my mission is to heal the sick.
You have a lot of courage.
If I can help you...
- Are you a doctor?
- No, let's say a busybody.
My name is Scott.
- Jason Scott?
- Yes, Jason Scott.
- Where have you heard my name?
- It's printed on your books.
I've read a couple of them.
I hope I haven't shocked you.
No, not at all. You call things
with their real name.
I could have been even more clearer.
Hey, Jason!
- Give me a hand!
- I'll be right there.
Excuse me, miss... Oh, sister.
Mr. Scott?
- Do you want to give me a hand too?
- Yes, but how?
Telling everyone how
these poor people live.
It is scandalous to close our eyes
on prevarication and exploitation.
- Yes, but allow me one thing.
- Like?
To also talk about people like you.
Daisy!
Donate, brothers!
Donate to civic assistance!
Donate now because perhaps
you may need help someday.
Dawson City needs your help.
Thank you, madam. Thank you, sir.
God bless you always.
Give me.
Brother from faraway China,
a small offering. Thank you.
Brother, a small offering.
Father!
Hey, father!
- Father Oatley, to serve you.
- It is Heaven that sends you.
It is a pleasure to meet a servant
of the Lord. What brings you here?
An idea, a hope.
I want to start a hospital.
A hospital?
But... It will take the equipment.
I've everything that is needed.
Medicines, instruments...
E... Money, of course.
Yes.
Praise the Lord.
Just this morning
I said in my sermon
the need to have a hospital
here in Dawson.
Where will you place
this oasis of sanctity?
I don't know yet. I was counting
on the help of some generous soul.
Ah, there... Say no more, sister.
Say no more.
Hey, you sinners!
I am talking to you!
Come and take the baggage
of this holy creature.
Thank you. Thank you.
Follow me.
Help!
Help! Help!
White Fang! Where are you? Run!
Help!
I have no more strength...
White Fang, where are you?
Help!
I'm drowning... I'm drowning...
I can't go on much longer.
White Fang... Help me...
Are you still here? Go away!
Go away, bad dog!
Go away!
Away!
Go! Mitsah! Mitsah!
What is it?
Is Mitsah in danger?
Hurry, take me there.
Run! Run! Run!
You.
Mr. Beauty Smith just went to rest.
The sound of the hammer
bothers him.
Take it down.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
A disagreement?
Yeah, they don't like signs.
Me too. Mr.?
Jason Scott,
of the New York Daily Herald.
A nosy reporter.
Yeah. May I know
who am I speaking with?
Mr. Smith.
Beauty Smith.
- Your reputation precedes you.
- Really?
Well... Sorry, if I woke you up.
Let's not talk about it anymore.
- Mr. Smith.
- Yes?
Two dollars, for my sign.
We'll find
a doctor in Dawson City.
The doctor will heal Mitsah,
the little big hunter.
No, Jason, that's not it.
Take a few more steps back.
There, okay!
Nine feet!
Losing nine feet means giving away
at least 50,000 dollars!
He's right!
I won't let myself be robbed
by a damned inspector!
- It's theft!
- We won't let you take our land!
No one is robbing you.
The law says that no one
can exploit more than 500 feet.
Tell Beauty, but careful that
his dog won't bite your butt.
Beauty Smith doesn't make the laws,
the government does.
What government?
The government here
is Mr. Beauty Smith.
You have to do what he likes.
- Hello?
- What?
- Suppose I don't want to do that.
- You're not a miner.
Suppose I was one.
It would be a problem. No one
would buy an ounce of your gold.
If I wanted to buy your gold?
No one would sell it to you.
We have a contract with Mr. Smith.
- A contract?
- We sell him all the gold.
- All of it?
- Yes, and he pays us well.
- Cash.
- Sure, 10%.
What's left in bonds.
Every year we get the interest rate.
Sorry, but I can't waste
any more time with you.
Come on, back to work!
- Let's not waste any time.
- Come on, guys.
What do you say?
In so many years that I have been
living among these people,
I have seen very few get rich.
Do you need me
for the interview with Beauty?
I don't think so.
Bravo!
To what do I owe the honor,
Mr. Nosy?
Dawson City has ignited my curiosity.
Everywhere I turn I hear your name.
So I thought of coming
directly to the source.
- Please, come.
- Thank you.
No, no. Come on, be good.
Girls,
the gentlemen want company!
Nothing for this side?
Come.
You know that Beauty
does not want you to come here.
A respectable priest
can't go to a saloon.
I have to see you sometime,
you never come to the mission.
Dad. That's no place for me.
That's not true.
You are a good girl.
I know.
But people's prejudices...
You the tramp and me the saint.
It's funny, isn't it?
You may not be a saint,
but you're the kindest of devils.
Go, now.
You have talked to the miners.
Did somebody tell you that I
forced him to sign the contract?
Nobody.
You're someone.
You tell me that you have
stuck your nose into my business
and you found them clear as water.
You'd be complimenting me, instead
you wonder where the trick is.
I'm not that naive. I wanted to
warn you that I will try to find out.
There's nothing to find out.
Would you like a cigar?
A gallant man offers it to you.
A gallant man who takes
all the gold in the country
paying 90% of it with just paper.
Those pieces of paper
will be worth a lot more in a year.
How much will the cost of goods
increase in a year?
How do I know that?
You do the pricing.
All goods arriving in Dawson
pass through your hands only.
- You know that too.
- Yes, that too.
I suspect that they are not
of the highest quality,
except maybe the champagne.
- My private reserve.
- It's the only drinkable one.
- Then you drink it.
- Don't you want to have a drink?
- Why should I drink with you?
Well... Because you like me.
You say that.
Then I will have to find
another reason.
- Which one?
- I am a friend of your father.
- What do you want to say?
- Don't be afraid.
I am blackmailing you
to spend some time with you.
I have heard it all,
but I will not betray your secret.
Not even if you send me to hell.
Maybe I won't send you there.
Looking at you more closely...
I don't find you obnoxious.
Good. Let's go.
Jack?
Did you arrive with the last boat?
Are you a merchant?
No.
- A maker.
- A maker?
What will you make here?
Here, let's say...
Trouble.
I'm a government official.
Then you'll have fun.
Come on!
Come here!
Good job!
Come on!
There, you've done it.
Come on up. There he is!
Bravo, White Fang...
Be good.
- Come here, Satan!
- Stop, White Fang! Be quiet!
Come here!
White Fang!
Calm down.
Be careful with that
stupid dog, dirty Indian!
Sorry, he's not used to seeing
so many people.
- Is that your canoe?
- Yes.
You didn't bring any furs. How come?
I'm not here to sell.
He is very sick.
I'm sorry. No furs then.
I have a lot of furs across the
river, but now I want a doctor.
Listen, Indian, I find you a doctor
and you bring me the furs.
- Agreed?
- All right.
He's a healthy, strong boy,
he'll heal soon.
Sorry,
the dog can't stay here.
He won't bother,
he is Mitsah's friend.
Sorry.
Did you hear that, White Fang?
You can't stay here.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, be good.
White Fang...
- White Fang...
- Mitsah!
Good boy. Good boy.
Let me see.
Is that dog yours, Indian?
Yes, sir.
He killed
Dawson's strongest dog.
White Fang can kill ten
like that, he's strong and brave.
- How much do you want for that dog?
- I'm not selling it.
- I asked you how much you want.
- And I answered you.
Two hundred dollars.
Three hundred dollars.
Four hundred dollars.
I don't want your money.
- Do you refuse four hundred dollars?
- Yes.
If you don't want my money,
too bad for you. I want your dog.
No, stop!
Don’t...
Home, go! Everybody home!
It's nothing,
it's just a wounded Indian.
Come on!
Let's not waste time on an Indian.
Home, quick!
Don't you have anything to do?
Come on!
Oh, my God!
Hey! Come here, quick!
- What happened, father?
- I don't know... I didn't see it.
Careful.
Easy.
Bring me some bandages, quick.
Here.
Mitsah!
Treat him... well...
- Take care...
- Yes, of course.
Tell him I will come back
soon to pick him up
with White...
Old Charlie...
He shouldn't
have come to Dawson City.
His son... He's very sick.
Then the prophet Ezekiel
cried out....
"Are you not ashamed
of this abomination?"
"Who do you think you are
because you have white skin?"
"Do you not know that God created
all races of all colors?"
There is no difference between you
And a Klondike Indian!
Although you, damn ignorant people,
don't even know where Klondike is.
And now I will repeat
the words of Ezekiel!
"The one among you who kills
an Indian is equal to Cain"
"who slew his brother Abel and
now roasts in eternal flames!"
"Therefore, you sinners,
you are warned!"
"Beware you,
not to end up in the grill"
"for all eternity."
Give me another one, Joe.
Bring a bottle.
The reverend will pay.
I really liked
that passage from Ezekiel.
"Whoever kills a human being
of another race is like Cain."
Nice!
- You heard my sermon.
- Yes.
- Did you not see me?
- No.
But I also remember
the words of Isaiah.
"Whoever witnesses a crime
and does not report it"
"will be condemned to burn
in the eternal flames of hell."
Isaiah had the good fortune
of not living in such hard times
for those who do not keep
their mouths shut.
But a priest cannot keep silent.
What example would he set for others?
If someone were to say that
he saw you, that you were there?
Wouldn't that bite back conscience?
You preach a lot on divine justice,
but you forget that there is also
human justice.
You know who killed the Indian,
but you are afraid to say it.
Afraid? Terror even.
An insane terror, my dear friend,
and I have reason to have it.
In this city
even the walls have ears.
At night remorse
doesn't let me sleep,
but I also try not to end up
too soon in hell.
Would you have the courage
to denounce the murderer?
Sure, if you provide me
with some evidence.
I would like to be sure
that you won't get me in trouble.
You don't trust me?
Come with me.
I have something that will speak
for the two of us.
It's already arranged.
Doesn't the book of Isaiah say: "He
who is a champion of righteousness"
"risks being betrayed
by the man he seeks to defend"?
Stop, Chester!
You don't stand a chance!
Let's go!
Come on, Chester.
Isn't this your knife?
- This is the first time I see it.
- It's got your initials on it.
How can you tell it's mine?
D and C could be Donald Carter
Or Doc Crockey or Dan Covansky.
All right, bring in
Carter, Crockey and Covansky.
- What does that mean?
- It's true.
The knife could belong
to one of them.
So I convinced them to tell us
what they saw
to avoid trouble.
- You wanted to blame us, Chester.
You'll pay for this, damn you!
He's such a wild beast.
If we got him to fight,
people would bet
even the right arm on him!
Not a bad idea.
But against whom?
Wait, I go it!
- Against the bear!
- What bear?
The one that the hunters
have brought for the circus.
The most nervous
and irritable beast I have ever seen!
- A wolf against a wild bear.
- Yes.
Sure, the bets
will go through the roof.
Of course I will decide who wins.
Ladies and gentlemen, this way!
Come! You'll witness the greatest
show you have ever seen!
Ladies and gentlemen, right this way!
Come on in!
A sensational match,
you can't miss it!
The greatest show
you have ever seen!
Hurry up, we're about to start!
We have spread the word that the bear
will fight with a muzzle.
- Did they believe it?
- Everyone's betting for the dog.
Perfect.
Accept any bet on that beast.
- Jim.
- Thank you, sir.
- Accept any bets on the dog!
- All right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
citizens of Dawson City,
first city of the North,
capital of Klondike,
I have the honor to present you
the fight of the century!
On my left,
the fiercest animal of its race:
the fighting wolf!
And today, for the first time
in the history of the world,
he will fight against the terror
of the forest: the wild bear!
Make the final bets, friends,
before the fight begins!
You know who
to bet your money on, huh?
He is a magnificent beast,
a true wolf.
I'm sure he's going to win,
I'm sure of it.
- That's not fair!
- He can't make it!
- He's a vicious animal!
- Come on, come on!
Father?
The key.
What key?
The key to the cupboard.
I've been looking for it all morning.
Sister Evangelina! Sister Evangelina!
What's going on?
Come and see what's going on, quick!
- I'm coming, I'm coming!
- Hurry up!
Oh, my God!
White Fang...
This is terrible!
Jason, look at that!
- What shall we do?
- I have an idea, come!
Yeah, right!
Where is... White Fang?
Go, go!
Move!
Faster!
Mr. Scott, what right do you have
to interrupt the match?
What right you had to set it up?
I bought that dog.
Yes, Mr. Smith, with a man's life.
White Fang...
Poor White Fang...
Mitsah, for the love of Heaven!
He is dead!
- Put it away.
- Yes.
You can pet him now. Come.
Here we go!
- Go.
- Come on.
- Will he die?
- No, it's all in the past now.
Now go to sleep, you promised me.
Krista!
Come.
Why did White Fang come back
without my father?
I don't know. When your father comes,
we'll ask him.
With these wounds
a man would already be dead.
He is strong, he'll be fine.
He'll need a master.
- Mitsah is his master.
- Mitsah will need a father.
At his age
a mother is much more important.
He's here now. I'll take care of him.
Go, Mitsah, go!
- Goodbye!
- Are you tired already?
- Yes, a little bit.
Come on, get in.
Let's go!
Go!
Let's go.
- Go!
- Catch it!
Run, White Fang!
Good boy! Come here!
White Fang, over here!
Come on!
Good boy. Wonderful!
- Did you see that you healed?
- Did you see? You're healed.
He's back to full strength.
- The dam is almost finished.
- Yes.
The miners are waiting for
our dam to work miracles.
If the vein is exhausted,
it's useless.
I heard that people are checking
the other side of the mountain.
Yes. I'm going to go and see
before some uncontrolled voice
comes this way.
- Are you leaving?
- Just for a few days.
Now go with Sister Evangelina,
you need to rest.
- No!
- What do you mean?
A future Indian chief must know
how to obey if he wants to lead.
Look at White Fang.
White Fang, go to the dog house.
Then?
Let's go.
I have to go, unfortunately.
I told you to knock!
Don't worry, I'll have the door taken,
so the problem is solved.
You'll have to solve another one.
You are not my type.
This is a non-existent problem.
I am the one who chooses.
- Did you want to talk to me, Beauty?
- Later.
No, no, go ahead.
I have no secrets with her.
You need to get out
of my way. Is that clear?
No, it's not clear at all.
All right.
Anyway, it's about her. She doesn't
have to go on the mission anymore.
I don't like her friendship
with the nun.
Is that the friendship
that bothers you?
My daughter
will never come here again!
We'll see.
What's up?
Come here.
- Come here and punch me.
- But why?
Punch me and run away!
White Fang, be good.
Shut up. What's the matter with you?
- Why is he barking?
- Maybe he senses danger.
Why are you nervous? You're here,
nothing can happen to us.
- What's the matter with you?
- Where is he going?
White Fang! Why are you doing this?
Come on, be good.
No, White Fang!
Not like that!
Stop! Stop!
Let him go, stay still!
Come here, let him go! Obey!
It's for Kurt Janssen, the inspector
of the mines. Before I give it...
You're not going to give it to him.
Whatever you want, Beauty.
- It is useless for me to tell you...
- Rest assured, I won't talk.
Mr. Hall.
"New..."
Don't strain your brain.
New gold deposits
have been discovered in Nome,
on the west coast.
- Do you know what that means?
- Yes. The end of Dawson.
That's right.
You are right, my dear friend.
When the news will spread
this city will become a desert.
- We'll make sure no one will know!
Yes.
It is possible,
until the boat arrives.
Right.
When the boat comes it will be known.
- Nobody can stop it.
- So...
I'll leave Dawson with no regrets.
I squeezed
every last drop out of it.
Take care of the preparations,
there's no more time to lose.
Wait.
I won't leave here without the thing
I'm most interested in.
- Krista is not an object.
- They all are to me.
I told Beauty that I won't work for
him anymore. He'll find a new singer!
Tell him I lost my voice.
Don't be an idiot. If he wants
to see you, there's a reason.
Nothing can make me go to him!
What if it's something
about Oatley?
- What about my father?
- Ask Beauty.
I'm going out for a minute, sister.
My respects, sister.
Mitsah?
Go find Father Oatley,
tell him to come here immediately.
Yes, sister.
Krista, it's warm and sunny
in California.
After all this snow my
proposal should make you happy.
All your proposals
have one thing in common,
I'm not interested in them.
- Don't use that tone.
Listen.
I have never in my life been
so patient with a woman,
I have never courted them,
never prayed to them.
It doesn't seem like it either.
I might as well, though.
Save yourself this humiliation,
it wouldn't do any good.
Goodbye, Mr. Beauty!
What does this mean?
Since prayers don't help....
Get up, you actress!
Get up...
Krista... Krista!
Let's get her to the mission
right away, to the nun.
You can't, Beauty. You shouldn't have
shown her that telegram.
If she'd say that gold was found
in Nome, we're ruined.
She won't be able to talk anymore,
she's dead.
She's dead...
My baby girl...
That's why you killed her....
Because she wouldn't talk! For this!
Now she won't sing anymore
because she's dead!
They killed her...
They killed her!
Do you know why?
They didn't want her to say
that someone found gold in Nome!
They killed her because she knew!
There is gold in Nome,
big veins of gold! Gold!
Be cursed! There is gold in Nome!
- Yes, there is gold!
- What do you say?
There is gold in Nome! New veins!
They have found gold!
- Is it possible?
- Run to Nome! Run to Nome!
I heard it from Beauty.
They hid it from you!
You guys have been scammed,
you have always been robbed!
There is gold in Nome!
They killed my daughter
so she wouldn't say it!
There is gold in Nome!
They found the gold! They wanted
to keep it a secret from you...
They killed my daughter
so that she wouldn't tell...
- Open up!
- Open the door!
- You must open up!
- Open up, come on!
Our money!
Beauty said that the bonds
were like money.
Your money is tied up for one year.
I'm out of here!
Let's leave, there's gold in Nome,
but first let's go to Beauty!
Yes, let's go to the saloon!
- Have you heard?
- I want to know the truth.
For some it was an accident,
for others Father Oatley is right
but he also says
that Krista was his daughter.
It's true.
She was.
They escaped!
Go, White Fang!
What do you want?
Mitsah!
If they come in here,
I'll kill the kid.
Silence! Silence, listen to me!
- Please!
- Out of the way, this is man stuff!
You are right, but...
Please listen to me!
I too have come to Dawson City
from very far away.
All of you have come here
looking for something,
but only a few of you
have actually found gold.
Most of the lucky ones,
unfortunately,
has been robbed by a criminal!
Yes, Beauty Smith has speculated
on you with evilness and cynicism.
Please! Dawson City
shall not be remembered
as a violent city. It is
a responsibility you do not deserve.
You don't want to...
Mitsah!
White Fang...
White Fang, don't run away!
Hall, dynamite, quick!
Send those people back, Scott!
Or I'll blow the dam!
Drop the gun, Beauty, and surrender!
Scott, I'm not kidding!
I told you to send them away!
He is capable of doing it
and the water would devastate us all.
- I have to stop him.
- Jason, no, that's crazy!
If you care about your life,
stay where you are!
You got the trick, White Fang.
- The fuse, Hall!
- Go, you beast!
The fuse! We've got to tear it off!
- Back up, get out of the way!
- Jason, get out of the way, run!
Back off!
Go! Go!
Come on!
We made it!
- Where is the dog?
- We didn't see any dog.
I'm going to stay here with Mr. Kurt,
I want to wait for White Fang.
It's no use, I told you,
he was swept away by the water.
You'll return to your tribe and find
many children like you and many dogs.
White Fang is not dead.
- Goodbye, Kurt.
- Goodbye, Jason.
Let's go.
An Indian chief never cries.
- Goodbye.
- Good luck.
Goodbye, Kurt. Goodbye.
I'll be back soon, I promise!
Now you know the gold diggers,
they have a fever on them.
Someone finds gold
and everyone runs to the unknown.
I wrote to my order
that Nome
is going to need a hospital.
Yeah, Nome.
White Fang!
White Fang, come here!
Help him!
Here I am, I'm coming!
Come on! I'm coming!
Good job! Good job!
Good boy! You are saved!
You are saved!
Good boy! Good boy!