DIANA: I used to want to save the world.
This beautiful place.
But I knew so little then.
It is a land of magic and wonder.
Worth cherishing in every way.
But the closer you get,
the more you see the great darkness
simmering within.
And mankind? (CHUCKLES)
Mankind is another story altogether.
What one does when faced with the truth
is more difficult than you think.
I learned this the hard way.
A long, long time ago.
And now,
I will never be the same.
Merci.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hello, Diana.
- AMAZON: Hello, Diana.
- Hello.
- MNEMOSYNE: Diana!
- (GASPS)
Diana!
- (PANTING)
- Come back!
(GRUNTING)
- It looks very good.
- Very good.
How is she doing?
She's good.
- Keep working with her.
- I will.
Naomi.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(YOUNG DIANA GRUNTING)
MNEMOSYNE: Diana!
Diana, I see you.
Where are you going?
Slow down!
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES) Hello, Mother.
How are you today?
HIPPOLYTA: Let's get you back to school
before another tutor quits.
YOUNG DIANA: But don't you think
it's time to start my training?
Antiope thinks I'm ready.
HIPPOLYTA: Does she?
I could begin showing her some things.
She should at least
be able to defend herself.
From whom?
In the event of an invasion.
HIPPOLYTA: Isn't that why I have
the greatest warrior in our history
leading an entire army, General?
I pray a day will never come
where she has to fight.
But you know,
a scorpion must sting,
- a wolf must hunt...
- She is a child.
The only child on the island.
Please let her be so.
YOUNG DIANA: But, Mother...
There will be no training.
YOUNG DIANA:
What if I promised to be careful?
It's time to sleep.
What if I didn't use a sword?
Fighting does not make you a hero.
Just a shield then. No sharp edges.
(SIGHS) Diana, you are the most
precious thing in the world to me.
I wished for you so much so,
I sculpted you from clay myself
and begged Zeus to give you life.
You've told me this story.
Which is why tonight
I will tell you a new one.
A story of our people,
and my days of battle.
Yes!
So you will finally understand
why war is nothing to hope for.
Long ago, when time was new
and all of history was still a dream,
the Gods ruled the Earth,
Zeus king among them.
Zeus created beings
over which the Gods would rule.
Beings born in his image,
fair and good,
strong and passionate.
He called his creation "man."
And mankind was good.
But Zeus's son
grew envious of mankind
and sought to corrupt
his father's creation.
This was Ares, the God of War.
Ares poisoned men's hearts
with jealousy and suspicion.
He turned them against one another
and war ravaged the Earth.
So, the Gods created us, the Amazons,
to influence men's hearts with love
and restore peace to the Earth.
And for a brief time, there was peace.
ANTIOPE: But it did not last.
Your mother, the Amazon Queen,
led a revolt
that freed us all from enslavement.
When Zeus led the Gods to our defense,
Ares killed them one by one,
until only Zeus himself remained.
HIPPOLYTA: Zeus used the last of his power
to stop Ares,
striking such a blow,
the God of War was forced to retreat.
But Zeus knew
that one day, Ares might return
to finish his mission.
An endless war,
where mankind would finally
destroy themselves,
and us with them.
ANTIOPE: So Zeus left us a weapon,
one powerful enough to kill a God.
HIPPOLYTA: With his dying breath,
Zeus created this island
to hide us from the outside world,
somewhere Ares could not find us.
And all has been quiet ever since.
We give thanks to the Gods
for giving us this paradise.
And the Godkiller?
The Godkiller?
The weapon that's strong enough
to kill a god.
Can I see it?
The Gods gave us many gifts.
One day, you'll know them all.
This great tower is where we keep them.
The Godkiller.
It's beautiful.
Who would wield it?
I pray it will never be called to arms.
But only the fiercest among us
even could.
And that is not you, Diana.
You see, you're safe,
and there is nothing
you should concern yourself with.
(METAL CLANGING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You keep doubting yourself, Diana.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
You are stronger than you believe.
You have greater powers than you know.
- But if you don't try hard...
- HIPPOLYTA: Diana!
Are you hurt?
No, Mother, I'm fine,
- I was just...
- Training.
It seems I'm not
the revered queen I should be.
Disobeyed, betrayed by my own sister...
No, Mother.
It was me, I asked her to...
Take her to the palace.
Off you go.
You left me no choice, Hippolyta.
You neglect your duty
if she cannot fight.
You speak of a time that may never come.
He might never return.
He could have died from his wounds.
Ares is alive.
You feel it, as I do, in your bones.
It is only a matter of time
before he returns.
The stronger she gets,
the sooner he'll find her.
Hippolyta, I love her as you do.
But this is the only way
to truly protect her.
(SIGHS)
You will train her harder than
any Amazon before her.
Five times harder,
ten times harder.
Until she is better than even you.
But she must never know the truth
about what she is
or how she came to be.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Harder.
- You're stronger than this, Diana.
- (PANTING)
Again.
(YELLS AND GRUNTS)
Never let your guard down.
You expect the battle to be fair.
A battle will never be fair.
Antiope!
Lay still.
You are bleeding.
DIANA: I'm sorry...
ANTIOPE: Wait, Diana, wait.
What have I done?
I'm sorry.
(PANTING)
(AIRPLANE ENGINE WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Where did this fog come from?
There. Go forward!
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
GERMAN SOLDIER:
There he is! The pilot! I can see him.
- He's there!
- (SOLDIERS SHOUTING)
(STEVE COUGHING)
(PANTING)
Wow.
You're a man.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Yeah. I mean...
Do I not look like one?
Where are we?
Themyscira.
Therma-what?
Who are you?
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
I'm one of the good guys,
and those are the bad guys.
What?
The Germans. Come on,
we need to get out of here.
- The Germans?
- HIPPOLYTA: Diana!
Step away from her, now!
AMAZON: Ready your bows!
They have guns, right?
Fire!
Come on!
(SOLDIERS GROANING)
(DIANA PANTING)
(GASPS)
(AMAZONS SHOUTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ALL YELLING)
(GROANING)
Stay there!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS)
Shield!
No!
DIANA: No.
- No, no. Antiope. Antiope.
- (GROANING)
Antiope, hey. Hey, hey.
Hey.
- Diana.
- Be still.
The time has come.
You... You must...
What? What, Antiope?
Godkiller.
- Diana, go...
- Go where?
- Go...
No, please, no. No. No!
No, no, no.
- No! (SOBBING)
- Antiope!
No!
- You.
- DIANA: No.
No, Mother, no.
He fought at my side
against the invaders.
What man fights against his own people?
- These aren't my people.
- Then why do you wear their colors?
I can't tell you that.
You need to tell us now!
What is your name?
I can't tell you that either.
We should kill him now,
and be done with it.
If he dies,
we know nothing about who they are,
and why they came.
My, uh, (CLEARS THROAT)
Name is Captain Steve Trevor,
pilot, American Expeditionary Forces.
Serial number 8141921.
That's all I'm at liberty to... (GROANS)
Assigned to British Intelligence.
What the hell is this thing?
The Lasso of Hestia compels you
to reveal the truth.
But it's really hot.
It is pointless, and painful, to resist.
What is your mission?
Whoever you are,
you are in more danger than you think.
What is your mission?
I am a...
(CLEARS THROAT)
(STRAINING)
I am a spy.
(PANTING)
I'm a spy. I'm a spy.
British Intelligence got word
that the leader of the German Army,
General Ludendorff,
would be visiting a secret military
installation in the Ottoman Empire.
I posed as one of their pilots,
and flew in with them.
According to our intel,
the Germans had no troops left,
no money, no munitions of any kind.
But our intel was wrong.
The Germans had the Turks
building bombs for them.
And not just bombs, new weapons.
Secret weapons.
Invented by Ludendorff's
chief psychopath, Dr. Isabel Maru.
The boys in the trenches
called her "Dr. Poison."
And for good reason.
(MAN GASPING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
STEVE: From what I could tell, if Dr. Maru
was able to complete her work,
millions more would die.
The war would never end.
I was there to observe and report,
nothing more,
but I had to do something.
DR. MARU: I'm so close.
I know I can make the gas
penetrate the mask.
I just... I need more time.
Unfortunately, Doctor,
we do not have more time.
This work, this...
Get that man!
There!
(ALARM BLARING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE)
But if I can get these notes back
to British Intelligence in time,
it could stop millions more from dying.
It could stop the war.
War? What war?
The war.
The war to end all wars.
Four years,
27 countries,
25 million dead,
soldiers and civilians.
Innocent people,
women and children slaughtered.
Their homes and their villages
looted and burned.
(GROANS) Weapons far deadlier than you can
(EXHALES)
Ever imagine.
It's like nothing I've ever seen.
It's like the world's going to end.
Should we let him go?
And risk him bringing
more men to our shores?
We cannot hold him forever, my queen.
Mother. Excuse me,
but after everything the man said,
this must be Ares.
What are you talking about, child?
Forgive me, Senator,
but the man called it "a war without end."
Millions of people already dead.
Like nothing he's ever seen.
Only Ares could do such a thing.
We cannot simply let him go.
We must go with him.
I will not deploy our army
and leave Themyscira defenseless
to go and fight their war.
It is not their war.
Zeus created man to be
just and wise, strong and passionate...
That was a story, Diana!
There is much you do not understand.
Men are easily corrupted.
Yes, but Ares is behind that corruption!
It is Ares who has
these Germans fighting.
And stopping the God of War
is our fore ordinance.
As Amazons, this is our duty.
But you are not an Amazon
like the rest of us.
So you will do nothing.
As your queen, I forbid it.
EPIONE: Strange.
Is it true you saved his life?
Who told you that?
He did.
(STEVE GRUNTS)
Whoa! I...
I didn't see you come in.
Would you say you're a
typical example of your sex?
I am
above average.
What's that?
It's a...
Oh! Um...
It's a watch. (CLEARS THROAT)
A watch?
Yeah, it's a watch.
It tells time.
My father gave it to me.
It's been through hell and back
with him.
Now it's with me,
and good thing it's still ticking.
What for?
Because it tells time.
- When to eat, sleep, wake up, work.
- (DIANA CHUCKLES)
You let this little thing
tell you what to do?
Yeah.
Can I ask you some questions?
- Where are we?
- Themyscira.
No, I got that before.
But I mean, where are we?
What is this place?
Who are you people?
Why does the water do that?
How come you don't know what a watch is?
How come you speak English so well?
We speak hundreds of languages.
We are the bridge to
a greater understanding between all men.
Right.
You know, I didn't get a chance
to say this, uh, earlier,
but thank you for dragging me
out of the water.
Thank you
for what you did on the beach.
So,
you're here to let me go?
I tried, but it's not up to me.
I even asked them to send me with you.
Or anyone.
An Amazon.
The Amazons.
The Amazons?
It is our sacred duty
to defend the world.
And I wish to go.
But my mother will not allow it.
Well, (SIGHS)
- I can't say I blame her.
- (ZIPPING)
The way this war is going,
I wouldn't want to
let anyone I care about near it.
Then why do you want to go back?
I don't think "want" is the word.
I guess I gotta try.
My father told me once,
he said, "If you see something wrong
happening in the world,
"you can either do nothing,
or you can do something."
And I already tried "nothing."
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTS)
(COW GRUNTS)
(MOOS)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
Nice outfit.
Oh, thank you.
Now, I will show you
the way off the island
and you will take me to Ares.
Deal.
STEVE: I'm leaving in that?
DIANA: We are.
Yeah, we're leaving in that?
Do you not know how to sail?
Of course I know how to sail.
Why wouldn't I know how to sail?
It's just...
It's been a while.
(HOOVES THUNDERING)
I'm going, Mother.
I cannot stand by
while innocent lives are lost.
If no one else will defend the world
from Ares, then I must.
I have to go.
I know.
Or at least I know I cannot stop you.
There is so much...
So much you do not understand.
I understand enough.
That I'm willing to fight for those
who cannot fight for themselves.
Like you once did.
You know that if you choose to leave,
you may never return.
Who will I be if I stay?
This belonged to
the greatest warrior in our history,
our beloved Antiope.
Make sure you are worthy of it.
I will.
Be careful in the world of men, Diana.
They do not deserve you.
You have been my greatest love.
Today,
you are my greatest sorrow.
Should you have told her?
The more she knows,
the sooner he'll find her.
How long until we reach the war?
The war? Which part?
The Western Front in France
is 400 miles long
from the Alps to the North Sea.
Where the fighting
is the most intense, then.
If you take me there,
I'm sure I'll find Ares.
Ares? As in, the God of War?
The God of War is our responsibility.
Only an Amazon can defeat him.
With this.
(SIGHS)
And once I do,
the war will end.
(METAL CLANGS)
(STEVE CLEARS THROAT)
Look, I appreciate your spirit,
but this war is...
It's a great big mess.
And there's not a whole lot
you and I can do about that.
I mean, we can get back to London,
and try to get to the men who can.
I'm the man who can!
And once I find and destroy Ares,
the German armies
will be freed from his influence
and they will be good men again,
and the world will be better.
Great.
You'll see.
What are you doing?
Oh, I thought maybe you'd want to
get some sleep.
And what about you?
Are you not sleeping?
Does the average man not sleep?
(STAMMERING)
Yes, we sleep.
We just don't sleep with, uh...
You don't sleep with women?
No. I mean, I do sleep with...
I sleep with... (CHUCKLES)
Yes, I do.
But, out of the, uh, (CLEARS THROAT)
Confines of marriage
it's just...
It's not polite to assume, you know?
"Marriage"?
Marriage. Do you not have that on...
You go before a judge
and you swear to love,
honor and cherish each other
until death do you part.
And do they?
Love each other till death?
Not very often, no.
Then why do they do it?
- I have no idea.
- (CHUCKLES)
So, you cannot sleep with me
unless I marry you.
I will sleep with you, if you want.
I'll sleep right there.
There's plenty of room.
- Then, fine, if you don't mind...
- No, it's up to you.
I know it's up to me, I'm making
the choice. I will come sleep with you.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
STEVE: Yeah, just...
Okay.
(EXHALES)
You know, where I come from,
I'm not considered average.
You know, being a spy,
you have to show a certain amount of
vigor.
Have you never met a man before?
What about your father?
I had no father.
My mother sculpted me from clay
and I was brought to life by Zeus.
Well, that's neat.
Sorry.
Where I come from,
babies are made differently.
You refer to reproductive biology.
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah, I know.
I know all about that.
I mean, I refer to that,
and other things.
The pleasures of the flesh.
Do you know about that?
I've read all 12 volumes of Clio's
Treatises on Bodily Pleasure.
- All 12, huh?
- Mmm-hmm.
Did you bring any of those with you?
You would not enjoy them.
I don't know. Maybe.
No, you wouldn't.
Why not?
They came to the conclusion that men
are essential for procreation,
but when it comes to pleasure,
(SIGHS) unnecessary.
No, no.
Good night.
Night.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN GERMAN)
How long until we are operational?
Two days, sir.
You have until tonight, Captain.
Sir, the men have had no food,
no sleep.
Do you think I have had
any food or rest, Captain?
Do you hear me making excuses?
No.
Your men are weak, complacent.
You've let them forget that
an attack can happen at any time,
from any quarter!
So, let's you and I remind them,
shall we?
- Doctor.
- DR. MARU: General.
Progress?
Not enough.
It is over, General.
Germany is giving up.
Von Hindenburg has recommended
the Kaiser sign the armistice.
We have run out of time.
As soon as the Kaiser
sees the newest weapon,
he will not sign the armistice.
But, without my book...
We will get your book!
It is you that I believe in. Not it.
I know that you can,
and will, succeed. Hmm.
It is what you were put on this earth
to do.
Something did come to me last night.
A different type of gas.
For you.
To restore your strength.
(GRUNTING)
(SNIFFS)
I've got it. I've got it!
And if it's what I think,
it's going to be
terrible.
(SHIP HORN BLOWS)
STEVE: Morning!
We got lucky, we caught a ride.
We made some good time.
Welcome to jolly old London!
It's hideous.
Yeah, it's not for everybody.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(HORN HONKING)
OFFICER 1: Morning, darling.
OFFICER 2: What a beauty.
OFFICER 3: Hello, beautiful!
Gentlemen, eyes to yourself.
Thank you so much.
Come on! Come on.
Why are they holding hands?
Uh, probably because they're together.
No, no, no. We're not together.
I mean, in that way.
This way.
(SIGHS) To the war!
Well, technically, the war is that way.
But we gotta go this way first.
And where are we going?
We gotta get this notebook
to my superiors.
Hey, hey, hey!
No, no, no.
I let you go, you take me to Ares.
We made a deal, Steve Trevor.
And a deal is a promise.
And a promise is unbreakable.
Oh, boy. Damn it. All right.
You come with me first
to deliver this,
and then we'll get you a ticket,
uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
To the war.
Deal?
- Let's go.
- Diana...
What are you doing?
You can't do that because
you're not wearing any clothes.
Let's go...
Let's go buy you some clothes.
What do these women wear into battle?
- They don't, uh...
- (BABY CRYING)
(GASPS) A baby!
- No, no, no. No babies.
- Oh... Oh...
No, please. No babies.
That one's not made out of clay.
Come on.
Diana! Please.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(GASPS AND CHUCKLES)
Thank God! You're not dead! (GIGGLES)
(GRUNTING)
Hoorah and huzzah!
I did think you were dead
until I got your call, you know?
He's been gone for weeks.
Not a single word.
Very unlike him.
I'm introducing myself.
It's Etta Candy.
I'm Steve Trevor's secretary.
What is a secretary?
Ooh! Well, I do everything.
I go where he tells me to go,
and I do what he tells me to do.
Well, where I'm from,
that's called slavery.
(GASPS) I really like her.
Fantastic. Ladies, after you.
Oh, I do, I like her.
ETTA: And it does rather feel like that,
except the pay is very good.
We've got our work cut out for us,
haven't we?
Is this what passes for armor
in your country?
(STAMMERS)
"Armor." It's fashion.
Keeps our tummies in.
Why must you keep them in?
Only a woman with no tummy
would ask that question.
Conservative,
but not entirely un-fun.
Try it on, at least.
Very well.
- Ooh! Ah, ah, ah...
- No! No, no, no.
ETTA: Ooh! (LAUGHS)
(HUMMING)
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPING)
Come on! Oh!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(EXCLAIMING)
DIANA: How can a woman
possibly fight in this?
ETTA: Fight?
We use our principles.
I mean, that's how
we're going to get the vote.
Although, I am not opposed to
engaging in a bit of fisticuffs,
should the occasion arise.
Lovely.
Oop!
It's itchy. It's choking me.
Can't say I blame it. (CHUCKLES)
Etta.
Where is she?
Oh, she's trying on outfit number 226.
Miss Candy, the whole point
was to make her look less
distracting.
May I?
ETTA: Really? Specs?
And suddenly she's not the most
beautiful woman you've ever seen?
Better.
- (METAL CLANGS)
- (DIANA GRUNTS)
Yeah, that's not going to work.
Please put the sword down, Diana.
Diana!
Let me try it by myself.
After you, sir. (SIGHS)
(ETTA CHUCKLES)
Etta...
Why don't I meet you
back at the office
and, meanwhile,
I'll take this for safekeeping.
Oh, no, I don't think so.
You gotta put the sword down, Diana.
Please.
- It doesn't go with the outfit.
- At all.
Put the sword down, first of all.
(GASPS)
Promise me you will protect it
with your life.
(CHUCKLES) Yes... No.
You can trust her. Just hand that over.
- Shield.
- And the shield to her.
There we go. Whoa!
You got it? Thanks, Etta.
This is easy. (CHUCKLES)
Oh. There we go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
What is it?
Hopefully nothing. Come on.
- Steve, why are we hiding?
- Shh! Come on, come on.
MAN: Captain Trevor.
I believe you have something that is
the property of General Ludendorff.
Ah, it's the, uh, bad-guy convention.
- (GUN CLICKS)
- Give us Dr. Maru's notebook.
Where did I put that thing?
- (GRUNTS)
- Stand back!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
- Or maybe not.
- (GUN CLICKS)
(DIANA GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKING)
(SIGHS) Tough luck. (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Is there anything else
you want to show me?
Where do you think you're going?
- (MAN GRUNTS)
- (GASPS) Oh!
I'm sorry. But you are
clearly under his control.
- Diana...
- Let me help you get free.
Where will I find Ares?
(SIGHS)
- He's... He's dead.
- STEVE: Hmm.
Cyanide.
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING)
Stay here. I'll be right back.
SIR PATRICK: Gentlemen! Gentlemen, please!
The sad truth is, the majority of them
don't even know what they're fighting for!
Let him speak!
Yes, thank you. Gentlemen...
Germany is an immensely proud nation.
They will never surrender.
Now, look.
The only way to end this war...
(WHISPERS) Colonel,
I have to talk to you outside.
SIR PATRICK: ...and restore world peace
is to negotiate
(STAMMERS) an armistice.
MAN: There's a woman in here.
SIR PATRICK: Um...
(WHISPERING) What's she doing in here?
Get her out.
Sorry. (CHUCKLES)
Blind sister.
She got lost on the way to the bathroom.
I think it's this way.
Sorry, guys.
SIR PATRICK: Um...
Our only aim at this time
must be to achieve peace,
at any cost!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Why do they not let him speak?
He's talking peace.
Not right now. Sorry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Trevor, what the hell were you thinking,
bringing a woman into the Council Chamber?
The intel that I brought back
is time-sensitive.
This is one of Dr. Maru's notebooks.
Notebook or not...
We need to get it to cryptography
and I need an immediate audience
with the generals.
You do not just barge in here
and demand an audience with the Cabinet.
Sir, with all due respect,
what I saw in my last mission
could change the course of the war.
SIR PATRICK: Captain Trevor!
I heard we'd lost you
on one of your missions,
yet here you are,
back from the dead,
and I see you've
brought a friend with you.
Our deepest apologies
for the interruption, sir.
No, no, no. Nonsense.
Thanks to this young woman,
the room was finally quiet enough for me
to get at least a few words in.
Sir Patrick Morgan, at your service.
Diana, Princess of Themys...
"Prince." Diana Prince.
She is, uh...
And I...
Are...
Working together.
She actually helped me
bring this, uh, notebook back here.
That's from Dr. Maru's lab.
I think the information contained inside
will change the course of the war, sir.
My God.
- Dr. Poison, herself.
- STEVE: Yes.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CLICKING)
(GASPS)
(DR. MARU CHUCKLES)
LUDENDORFF: Yes.
GENERAL HAIG: Intriguing.
- Any further intelligence?
- (DOOR CLOSES)
COLONEL DARNELL: Sadly not, sir.
Cryptography have had no luck.
It seems like it's a mixture
of two languages,
but, as yet, they've failed
to determine which two languages.
Ottoman and Sumerian.
Surely, someone else in this room
knew that.
Who is this woman?
STEVE: She's my, um,
secretary, sir.
And she can understand
Ottoman and Sumerian?
She's a very good secretary.
- See her out.
- (ALL LAUGH)
COLONEL DARNELL:
Sir, if this woman can read it,
we should hear what she has to say.
Yes, very well.
DIANA: It's a formula
for a new kind of gas.
Mustard gas.
Hydrogen-based, instead of sulfur.
(WHISPERS) Hydrogen-based...
Gas masks would be useless
against hydrogen.
The book says they plan to
release the gas
at "the front"?
When?
It doesn't say.
Wait. "Front" of what?
Sir,
that is the evidence we need.
You have to find out
where they're making that gas.
You have to burn it to the ground.
Destroy it.
Ludendorff was last seen in Belgium.
We can't be seen sending troops
into German-occupied Belgium
as we are negotiating their surrender.
STEVE: Sir, I've seen that gas
with my own eyes.
If it is used,
it will kill everyone on both sides.
They will all die.
That is what soldiers do, Captain.
STEVE: Send me in
with some logistical support.
At least give me the chance
to take out Ludendorff's operation myself.
Are you insane?
I can't introduce rogue elements
this late in the game.
Sir, I can...
SIR PATRICK: Now, more than ever,
the armistice
is of paramount importance.
It must be negotiated, it must be signed,
and this is...
Well, it's the best way
of stopping the war.
Captain, you will do nothing.
And that is an order.
Yes, sir.
I understand, sir.
I don't!
Diana, I know this is confusing...
- It is not confusing! It's unthinkable!
- Who is this woman?
She's with me. She's with us, sir.
I am not with you!
You would knowingly sacrifice
all those lives,
as if they mean less than yours!
- Diana, let's talk about this outside.
- As if they mean nothing?
Where I come from, generals don't
hide in their offices like cowards.
- That's enough!
- They fight alongside their soldiers.
They die with them on the battlefield!
- That's enough!
- You should be ashamed.
- My apologies. Diana...
- Diana...
- All of you should be ashamed!
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
Please slow down!
That's your leader?
How could he say that?
Believe that?
- And you!
- (SHUSHING)
Was your duty
to simply give them a book?
No!
You didn't stand your ground!
You didn't fight!
Because there was no chance
of changing his mind!
This is Ares, and he's not going to
allow a negotiation
or a surrender!
The millions of people you talked about,
they will die!
We are going anyway!
You mean, you were lying?
I'm a spy! That's what I do!
How do I know
you're not lying to me right now?
I am taking you to the front.
We are probably going to die.
This is a terrible idea.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
We're going to need reinforcements.
(MUSIC PLAYING IN PUB)
(MAN LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DIANA: These are the reinforcements?
STEVE: Yup.
Are these even good men?
Hmm. Relatively.
Even in Africa, gentlemen,
we haven't seen such luxuries.
But the luxury that we have now...
It's like we can't stop making money!
So, my uncle, the prince, and I...
Boy! Which prince is that?
I decide to extend the opportunity
for a few good soldiers...
STEVE: But, seriously, which prince?
Hey, Sultan Angora Mynx Cashmere,
could I talk to you for a minute?
(CHUCKLES) Gentlemen,
excuse me one second.
"Bar." Well, a "pub."
You bugger. I have been greasing
those peacocks all night, and you...
Oh, my goodness gracious.
That's a work of art.
Sameer, Diana. Diana, Sameer.
Hi, Diana.
You can call me Sammy, please.
"Sammy."
Sameer, I wouldn't do that,
if I were you.
Sameer's a top undercover man.
He can talk the skin off a cat
in as many languages as you can.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(SPEAKING GREEK)
Oh, you're done.
Where's Charlie?
- (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
(GRUNTING)
Le voilà.
- (GRUNTING)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
At least this "Charlie"
is good with his fists.
That's not Charlie.
(PATRONS CHEERING)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
That's Charlie.
Steven!
May God put a flower
upon your head, son.
Good to see you.
DIANA: So, what were you fighting about?
I mistook his glass for mine.
It happens.
This man is no fighter.
Charlie is an expert marksman.
It means he shoots people.
From very far away.
(CHUCKLES) They never know what hit them.
(LAUGHING)
So, how do you know who you kill
if you can't see their face?
I don't. Trust me, it's better that way.
You fight without honor.
Who gets paid for honor? Eh?
So, what's the job, boss?
Uh, two days, tops.
We need, uh, supplies
and passage to Belgium.
And what's the going rate?
Better be a good pay.
Yeah, well, here's the thing.
Um, I told you it was going to be quick.
And there's a lot to be gained by this.
So, it's for a great cause...
Uh, freedom...
Hmm.
Friendship,
uh, ending the war, friendship...
- Okay, you have no money.
- No.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CHUCKLES) What?
What is this?
We're going to drop her off
at the front.
- "Dropping her off"?
- Yeah.
CHARLIE: Listen, sweetheart,
I'm not going to get myself killed
helping a wee lassie out of a ditch.
- Know what I mean?
- Here's the little thief now!
We don't need your kind around here.
(GRUNTS)
(PATRONS GASP)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
She did it!
I'm both frightened and aroused.
- Oh, here they are! Sorry I'm late.
- DIANA: Sir Patrick!
Yes, that's what I was going to mention.
- Sir Patrick.
- SIR PATRICK: Oh, no, no, no.
Please, gentlemen, sit.
Miss Prince, sit.
I assume you're here
planning something
that's going to get you either
court-martialed or killed.
And I assume you're here to stop us.
No.
Not at all, in fact.
Well, look.
I was a younger man, once.
And, had I been in better health, I'd like
to think that I might do the same.
ETTA: Hmm.
SIR PATRICK: It's a very,
very honorable thing you're doing.
Therefore,
I'm here to help.
Unofficially, of course.
What's your plan?
If there's another weapons facility,
find it and destroy it.
Along with Ludendorff and Maru.
In that case, to allay suspicion,
the charming Etta, here,
could, uh, run the mission from my office.
"Run"...
(WHIMPERS)
Also,
there's enough here for a few days.
Thank you, sir.
You're very welcome.
Take great care, all of you,
and good luck.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Cheers!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
ICE CREAM VENDOR:
Fresh ice cream, made today. Hello, miss.
Would you like to buy an ice cream?
- Me?
- Are you hungry?
Yes.
Thank you.
ICE CREAM VENDOR:
Eight pence, please, sir.
Here you go, pal. Keep the change.
- Thank you very much, sir.
- DIANA: Mmm.
- What do you think?
- It's wonderful!
Yeah.
- You should be very proud.
- Thank you very much!
You should be very proud.
(CONDUCTOR CALLS OUT)
(BLOWING WHISTLE)
SOLDIERS: (SINGING)
It's a long way to Tipperary
It's a long way to go
STEVE: I hope our guy meets us here.
Chief's expecting us before dark.
"Chief"?
Uh, yeah. A smuggler.
Very reputable.
A liar, a murderer, and now a smuggler.
Lovely.
Careful, I might get offended.
I wasn't referring to you.
Really?
I went undercover
and pretended to be somebody else,
shot people on your beach,
and smuggled a notebook.
Liar, murderer, smuggler.
Are you still coming?
It's awful.
That's why we're here.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
DIANA: The gas will kill everything.
What kind of weapon kills innocents?
In this war,
every kind.
You were absent
at the council meeting, General.
I see you are negotiating the terms
of the armistice without me.
- On the Kaiser's behalf.
- And on your insistence!
We could easily win this war,
if only you had a little faith.
VON HINDENBURG: We don't.
There are shortages of food,
medicine, ammunition.
Every hour we delay
costs thousands of German lives.
One attack and the war can be ours!
As we speak, my chemist...
We stand against you and your
witch.
Ludendorff, enough!
Twenty-four hours from now,
this war will end.
It is over.
It is over for you.
It is over for all of you.
(GAS HISSING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
But the mask won't help.
- They don't know that.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(DR. MARU GIGGLES)
(MEN CONTINUE
SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Let's go!
Time to stage a demonstration
for the Kaiser!
CHIEF: You're late.
STEVE: Cowboy sneak-attack, Chief!
How are you?
- Good to see you, pal.
- CHARLIE: Okay, big man!
- Good to see you.
- Ah, yes!
Good to see you, my friend.
You beauty!
CHIEF: Who is this?
(SPEAKS INDIGENOUS LANGUAGE)
And I am Diana.
Where did you find her?
She found me.
- I plucked him from the sea.
- STEVE: It's a long story.
We don't have to
talk about that right now.
What's there?
(SIGHS) British tea for the Germans,
German beer for the British.
And Edgar Rice Burroughs novels
for both.
And guns!
Well, may we get what we want!
May we get what we need.
But may we never get what we deserve.
ALL: Bang!
(EXPLOSIONS IN DISTANCE)
Strange thunder.
German 77s.
Guns. Big ones.
It's the front, out there.
The evening hate.
So, who do you fight for in this war?
I don't fight.
You're here for profit, then?
No better place to be.
Nowhere better to be than in a war
where you don't take a side?
I have nowhere else.
The last war
took everything from my people.
We have nothing left.
At least here,
I'm free.
Who took that from your people?
His people.
CHARLIE: Don't go...
Don't go in. Don't go!
Don't! Boys, no!
Don't go in there!
Shh. You're safe.
You're safe. Are you okay?
Get off me, woman!
Stop making a fuss!
God!
He sees ghosts.
STEVE: You're going to get cold.
Oh, I don't...
Don't worry about Charlie.
He doesn't mean anything by it.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
(MEN GRUNTING AND SHOUTING)
(BABY CRYING)
MAN: Get out of there, now.
We've got to move!
You bloody animal, move!
Go on! Get on!
These animals,
why are they hurting them?
Because they need to move, quick!
- Like us!
- But this is not the way.
I could help them.
CHARLIE: There's no time. Come on, woman!
BOY: Mama!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
That man... He's wounded.
SAMEER: There is nothing you can do
about it, Diana.
We must keep moving!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
What is this?
You wanted me to take you to the war.
This is it.
So, where are the Germans?
A couple hundred yards
across the field.
- Their trench is...
- STEVE: Watch out!
(EXPLOSION)
Chief! It's good to see you!
Oi! Chief's back! He's back!
All right, let's move!
(WOMAN SPEAKS FLEMISH)
- Diana, we have to go.
- We need to help these people.
We have to stay on-mission.
The next safe crossing
is at least a day away.
- What are we waiting for?
- We cannot leave without helping them.
These people are dying.
They have nothing to eat,
and in the village...
- Enslaved, she said!
- I understand that.
Women and children!
We need to make
our next position by sundown.
How can you say that?
What is the matter with you?
- (EXPLOSION)
- This is No Man's Land, Diana!
It means no man can cross it,
all right?
This battalion has been here
for nearly a year
and they barely gained an inch.
Because, on the other side,
there are a bunch of Germans
pointing machine guns at
every square inch of this place.
This is not something you can cross.
It's not possible.
So what? So, we do nothing?
No, we are doing something.
We are.
- We just...
- Steve.
We can't save everyone in this war.
SAMEER: Steve, Steve...
This is not what we came here to do.
(BOTH WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
No,
but it's what I'm going to do.
Diana!
What the bloody hell
is she playing at?
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
She's taking all the fire!
Let's go!
(SHOUTING)
BRITISH OFFICER: Stay down! Stay down!
That's an order!
(GROANING)
(MAN SHOUTS IN GERMAN)
Go, now!
She's done it!
She's got them on the run!
(SOLDIERS YELLING)
Get down, get down! She's done it!
(GRUNTS)
- Steve!
- (GASPS)
Let's go!
Come on, go!
(ALL YELLING)
(MEN SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
Stay here. I'll go ahead.
(GRUNTING)
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
CHARLIE: What the...
STEVE: Let's move!
- (MEN SPEAKING GERMAN)
- (GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
STEVE: We need more firepower.
(MEN SPEAKING GERMAN)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(WOMAN CRIES)
Sniper!
Go!
Get in!
STEVE: Charlie, bell tower!
Come on, Charlie. Shoot him!
Hey, it's okay.
STEVE: Huh.
Follow me! Give me some cover!
STEVE: (YELLS) Right!
We're going to put this on our backs,
and, when I say go,
- lift hard!
- Okay.
STEVE: Diana! Shield!
- Go!
- (GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SPEAKING FLEMISH)
(CROWD APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING)
(PEOPLE THANKING IN FLEMISH
AND FRENCH)
PHOTOGRAPHER: Stay very,
very still for me, my friends.
Please. So important.
Thank you very much.
This has been such an honor for me,
taking your photograph.
Thank you so much.
DIANA: For all his talk of shooting,
he cannot shoot.
Not everyone gets to be
what they want to be all the time.
Me, I am an actor.
I love acting.
I didn't want to be a soldier.
But I'm the wrong color.
Everyone is fighting their own battles,
Diana.
Just as you are fighting yours.
It's too much.
I wish you well.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm on the... On the phone...
Uh, it's "Veld." V-E-L-D.
It's a tiny village.
It may not even be on the map.
ETTA: Ooh! I found it! I found it!
Did you find Ludendorff's operation?
No, no, no. But I located him.
And, oh, lucky you,
he's only a few miles away,
at German High Command.
STEVE: German High Command, huh?
So, intel reports
that Ludendorff is hosting a gala.
A sort of "last hurrah"
before the Germans sign the armistice.
And the Kaiser himself
is going to be there.
As well as Dr. Maru.
Actually, the gala could be
perfect cover.
- SIR PATRICK: Captain Trevor.
- Yes, sir.
You are, under no circumstances,
to go anywhere near
that gala tomorrow night.
Do you hear me?
You'd be jeopardizing
everything we've worked for.
You cannot compromise the armistice.
- Sir, there will be no armistice...
- Steve!
...once Ludendorff bombs
the entire front line.
Hold on one second, sir.
You shouldn't be bothered
about upsetting the peace accord.
- Why not?
- Ares would never let...
What?
What is it?
Of course. It makes complete sense.
Ares developed a weapon,
the worst ever devised.
- Ares? You mean Ludendorff.
- No.
I mean Ares.
Ludendorff is Ares!
Sir, this is our last chance,
our final chance
to find out where the gas is
and to learn how Ludendorff
plans on delivering it.
No, no, no. I forbid it.
Do you hear me? I forbid it.
Sir, I'm losing you! Sir?
- Hello?
- Sir...
(SIGHS)
How likely is he to respect my wishes?
Not very likely, I'll be honest.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(MAN HUMMING)
STEVE: Sammy. Sammy, no. No, no, no.
Sammy, I have to work.
I gotta rustle up a German uniform.
I still have to plot the course
for tomorrow.
That's easy, boss. Come on.
There is nothing we can do
until tomorrow.
You said it yourself, Steve.
So... Madame, s'il vous plaît.
Incroyable!
Magnifique!
- Thank you.
Monsieur, s'il vous plaît.
(CHUCKLES)
- Et voilà!
- STEVE: Merci, Sammy.
SAMEER: Et voilà!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
You did this.
We did.
Do you have dancing on
Paradise Island?
(LAUGHING) Dancing, yeah. Of course.
But these people are just swaying.
Okay, if you're going to be fighting
the God of War,
I may as well teach you how to dance,
you poor thing.
All right, probably without the gun.
Madame.
If you would.
Well...
If I'm going to a gala,
I'll need to know how to dance.
- You're not going to the gala.
- Of course I am.
- No, you're not.
- Why wouldn't I?
Well, for one,
you don't know how to dance.
I would argue that
they don't know how to dance.
Be polite, be polite.
All right. So, give me your hand.
Like so.
And I'm gonna put my arm
around you, like so.
And we just...
What did you call it? "Sway"?
Then you just sway.
You're awfully close.
That's what it's all about.
I see.
(CHARLIE SINGING)
I haven't heard him sing in years.
(CHUCKLES) It's, uh... It's a snowfall.
Touch it.
(LAUGHS)
It's magical!
It is, isn't it?
It is, yeah.
Is this what people do
when there are no wars to fight?
Yeah.
Yeah, this and other things.
What things?
Um...
They have breakfast.
They really love a breakfast.
And, um, they love to wake up
and read the paper and go to work.
They get married.
Make some babies,
grow old together.
I guess.
What is it like?
I have no idea.
SAMEER: The villagers gave them to us.
- A gracious gift.
- And they call us heroes.
- You are.
- (CHUCKLES)
STEVE: Hey, fellas. I know that
I said this job was two days,
and a deal's a deal.
You'd get lost without us.
Yeah.
We all know Diana is capable
of taking care of herself.
I'm worried that you won't make it.
There's no more money.
We've been paid enough.
Maybe you're better off
without me, yeah?
No, Charlie.
Who will sing for us?
- STEVE: Yeah.
- Oh, no, please.
Sing?
(CHUCKLES) You asked for it.
(SINGING) Green grow the rashes, O
Green grow the rashes, O
The sweetest hours I e'er did spend
CHARLIE: You must think
I was born yesterday.
STEVE: I know it sounds crazy,
but it's true.
Every word.
SAMEER: Wait, wait, wait.
There is a whole island
of women like her?
And not a single man among them?
How do we get there?
- (CHUCKLES)
- And she thinks
that Ludendorff is Ares, the God of War?
And only by killing him
will the war end? Don't be daft.
SAMEER: You saw what happened out there.
The way she charged
that machine-gun nest?
The way she took out that tower?
Maybe it's true.
I think it's true.
I believe it's true.
Et voilà.
Steven, son, you don't really believe
this rubbish, do you?
(URGES HORSE)
(WHISPERS) Diana! Diana!
Hiding, hiding.
How the hell do we get into that?
CHARLIE: I see only a couple of guards
on the door to distract.
Yeah, it won't look suspicious at all
when I come sauntering
out of the woods on foot.
I could get in.
You're not going in. It's too dangerous.
- Too dangerous?
- Yes, too dangerous.
And you're too distracting.
So, look, I'll go in there,
and follow them
to wherever they're working on the gas
or, better yet, where it is.
- Then I'm coming with you.
- No, you're not!
What you're wearing
isn't exactly undercover.
I don't know.
I would say she was pretty undercover
on that battlefield.
STEVE: We just...
We can't get you in, okay?
So, I'll scout it out, report back, and...
But as long as he's still alive,
it doesn't...
You cannot go into German High Command
and kill anyone.
You just can't. You have to trust me.
SAMEER: Oh, wow!
STEVE: Where did that come from?
Oh, can I drive it?
Please, let me drive it!
I'll be your chauffeur.
Come on, come on.
Stay put!
STEVE: Where did this come from?
A field over there. It's full of them!
Chief, I say you and me
scope out the area
in case we need to
beat a hasty retreat.
- What do you say, Diana?
- Huh?
Colonel.
Steve, they have invitations.
STEVE: Don't worry, play it cool.
You got this. You got this.
Your invitation, please.
Dhanyavaad, sahib.
The colonel and I
wish for many blessings
and all manner of other things
to fall upon your head.
(IN GERMAN ACCENT)
Your head must be empty.
He wants my invitation, you idiot.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I must apologize
a thousand, thousand times, my master.
I make the most horrible,
the most unforgivable mistake.
- I lost the colonel's invitation.
- (CAR HONKING)
What?
Are you saying we drove all the way
through the mud and rain
- only for you to lose my invitation?
- I'm a snail.
No! I'm a bug.
Not even a bug.
I am the dung of a bug!
- And you're right, master...
- (SPEAKS IN GERMAN)
Blessing be upon us.
(HORNS HONKING)
FAUSTA: This is ridiculous.
I'm not going to spend
the entire evening out here,
you stupid idiots! Move your cars!
(HORN HONKS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SHOUTS)
(CHUCKLES) What are you supposed to be?
What are you doing?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Excuse me.
I don't drink.
Have we met?
No, but I've been watching you.
Following your career, I mean.
You are Dr. Isabel Maru.
The most talented chemist
in the German Army.
I am a fan.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I hope I am not crossing a line.
I know you
and General Ludendorff are
very close.
We work well together. Yes.
But having someone like me behind you,
I could provide a lot more.
And who are you?
A man who would show you appreciation
a genius like yourself deserves.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
I love fire. Don't you?
It is like
a living act of entropy.
The ultimate weapon of destruction.
Reminding us that, in the end,
everything eventually
returns to the ash it came from.
There is something reassuring about it.
I see all of that in your eyes.
Perhaps you could show me
what you're working on.
I hear it is...
I hear it is extraordinary.
I appreciate your interest in my work,
but I am loyal to General Ludendorff.
Besides,
now I see your attention is
(CHUCKLES)
Elsewhere.
(GASPS)
Enjoying the party?
I confess, I'm not sure what it is
we're celebrating.
A German victory, of course.
Victory?
When I hear peace could be so close.
Peace?
There's only an armistice
in an endless war.
Thucydides.
Ah! You know your Ancient Greeks.
They understood
that war is a god.
A god that requires human sacrifice.
And in exchange,
war gives man purpose,
meaning, a chance to rise above
his petty, mortal, little self
and be courageous,
noble, better!
Only one of the many gods
believed in that.
- Mmm.
- And he was wrong.
You know nothing of the gods.
Herr General.
Enjoy the fireworks.
What are you doing?
- Out of my way!
- Diana, look at me.
If you kill Ludendorff
before we find the gas,
we won't be able to stop anything.
I will stop Ares!
What if you're wrong?
What if there is no Ares?
You don't believe me.
I can't let you do this.
What I do is not up to you.
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
STEVE: Diana!
Diana...
It's the gas.
The village... The village!
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
What are they cheering for?
SAMEER: Diana!
What did they fire?
The gas.
- It was Ludendorff.
- I saw him. He was in the tower.
- Wherever he goes, you follow.
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
SAMEER: How will you find us?
I know how.
(COUGHING)
Diana!
(EXHALES)
DIANA: They're dead. They're all dead.
I could have saved them.
I could have saved them
if it weren't for you.
You stopped me from killing Ares!
- No!
- Stay away from me!
I understand everything now.
It isn't just the Germans
that Ares has corrupted.
It's you, too.
All of you.
I will find Ares
and I will kill him.
Diana!
That smoke,
it's the Chief!
He followed Ludendorff.
(URGES HORSE)
Follow the smoke!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
CHIEF: Hey! Diana, that way!
(MAN ANNOUNCING IN GERMAN
OVER PA)
CHIEF: Come on! Let's go!
(GRUNTING)
LUDENDORFF: What a surprise.
Strange.
Unfortunately, I have another matter
to attend to.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What are you?
You will soon find out.
(YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
As magnificent as you are,
you are still no match for me.
- (GRUNTS)
- (BREATHS HEAVILY)
We'll see about that.
(GRUNTING)
I am Diana of Themyscira,
daughter of Hippolyta,
Queen of the Amazons.
And your wrath upon this world is over.
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
In the name of all
that is good in this world,
I hereby complete
the mission of the Amazons
by ridding this world of you
forever!
(YELLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY
IN DISTANCE)
STEVE: Diana?
Diana!
I killed him.
I killed him, but nothing stopped.
You kill the God of War,
you stop the war.
Exactly what we have to do now.
We need to stop the gas. Come on.
No. All of this should have stopped!
Diana...
The fighting should have stopped.
Why are they doing this?
I don't know! I don't know.
DIANA: Ares is dead.
They can stop fighting now.
Why are they still fighting?
Because, maybe it's them!
Maybe...
Maybe people aren't always good.
Ares or no Ares,
maybe it's just who they are.
- Diana...
- No.
Diana, we can talk about this later.
- I need you to come with me.
- No. No.
After everything I saw, it can't be!
It cannot be!
They were killing each other.
Killing people they cannot see.
Children...
Children!
No, it had to be him.
It cannot be them!
(STAMMERS) Diana, people... I...
She was right.
My mother was right.
She said,
"The world of men do not deserve you."
They don't deserve our help, Steve.
- It's not about deserve!
- They don't deserve our help.
Maybe we don't!
(STAMMERS)
But it's not about that.
It's about what you believe.
You don't think I get it
after what I've seen out there?
You don't think I wish I could tell you
that it was one bad guy to blame?
It's not!
(STEVE SIGHS)
We're all to blame.
I am not.
But maybe I am!
Please.
If you believe that
this war should stop,
if you want to stop it,
help me stop it right now.
Because, if you don't,
they will kill thousands more.
Please, please come with me.
I have to go.
(SIGHS) I have to go.
Hey! Hey!
- Where's Diana?
- We're on our own.
SAMEER: What?
STEVE: What do you see, Charlie?
CHARLIE:
Looks like a bunch of gas bombs
but I can't see
where they're taking them.
CHIEF: How are we going to get in there?
I've got an idea. Come on, guys.
Come on!
(QUIET METALLIC RATTLING)
Who's there?
Sir Patrick.
You were right, Diana.
They don't deserve our help.
They only deserve destruction.
You...
You're him.
I am.
But I am not what you thought I was.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
CHIEF: What is it?
(SIGHS) The future.
I am not your enemy, Diana.
I am the only one who truly knows you.
And who truly knows them, as you now do.
They have always been,
and always will be
weak, cruel, selfish,
and capable of the greatest horrors.
All I ever wanted
was for the Gods to see how evil
my father's creation was.
But they refused.
I am Diana of Themyscira...
So I destroyed them.
...daughter of Hippolyta,
and I'm here to complete her...
(DIANA GASPS)
The Godkiller...
My dear child,
that is not the Godkiller.
(BLOWS)
You are.
Only a god can kill another god.
Zeus left the child he had
with the Queen of the Amazons
as a weapon to use against me.
No. You liar.
I compel you to tell me the truth.
I am.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(DR. MARU SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
SIR PATRICK:
I am not the God of War, Diana.
I am the God of Truth.
Mankind
stole this world from us.
They ruined it, day by day.
And I, the only one
wise enough to see it,
was left too weak to stop them.
All these years,
I have struggled alone,
whispering into their ears.
Ideas, inspiration for formulas,
weapons,
but I don't make them use them.
They start these wars on their own.
All I do is orchestrate an armistice
I know they cannot keep,
in the hope
they will destroy themselves.
But it has never been enough.
Until you.
When you first arrived,
I was going to crush you.
But I knew that
if only you could see
what the other gods could not,
then you would join me,
and with our powers combined,
we could finally end all the pain,
all the suffering,
the destruction they bring.
And we could return this world
to the paradise it was before them.
Forever.
DIANA: I...
I could never be a part of that.
My dear, I don't want to fight you.
But, if I must...
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
SAMEER: Steve!
STEVE: Come on, let's go!
Sammy, let's go!
Get this plane out of here!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DIANA SHOUTS)
Oh, my dear, you have so much to learn.
(SHOUTS)
(PANTING)
CHARLIE: Oh, my God!
What are we gonna do?
There's not much we can do,
if that's who I think it is.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
But we can stop that plane.
CHARLIE: If we can get on the radio,
we can ask Flying Corps
to shoot her down.
No. If it crashes, it'll wipe everyone out
for 50 square miles!
We gotta ground it!
SAMEER: Bad news. It's on a timer.
If we ground it here,
it's the same thing.
Is it flammable, Chief?
Yeah, she said it's hydrogen.
It's flammable.
I need you guys to clear me a path
to that plane.
- No, Steve!
- Hey, Steve!
Come on!
(GRUNTS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(MEN GRUNTING)
SAMEER: Come on! This way! Steve!
CHARLIE: Go, Steve, come on.
CHIEF: Go!
DIANA: Steve!
CHARLIE: Go, Steve. Come on.
SAMEER: Run, run!
(STEVE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
ARES: Let's see what kind of god
you really are.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You will help me destroy them, Diana,
or you will die.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
SAMEER: Come on, come on.
Let's go, go, go!
CHARLIE: Move it, boys! Now!
CHIEF: Let's go! Run!
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Is that all you have to offer?
It is futile to imagine you can win.
Give up, Diana.
CHARLIE: Guys, I'm out.
Chief! Anything left?
I got nothing.
- Anything!
- SAMEER: No.
(MEN SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
(PANTING)
Steve.
(EXHALES)
(LAUGHING)
Steve...
No!
(SOBBING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
ARES: Yes, Diana!
Take them all!
Finally, you see.
Look at this world.
Mankind did this, not me.
They are ugly,
filled with hatred,
weak,
just like your Captain Trevor.
Gone, and left you nothing.
And for what?
Pathetic!
(LAUGHS)
He deserved to burn!
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
Look at her and tell me I'm wrong.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
She is the perfect example
of these humans
and unworthy of your sympathy
in every way.
Destroy her, Diana.
You know that she deserves it.
They all do.
Do it!
STEVE: Diana!
Diana...
(INAUDIBLE)
DIANA: What?
I have to go.
What are you saying?
Steve,
whatever it is, I can do it.
No. No.
- Let me do it.
- No.
It has to be me.
I can save today.
You could save the world.
I wish we had more time.
What? What are you saying?
I love you!
You're wrong about them.
They're everything you say,
but so much more.
Lies!
They do not deserve your protection!
(CRACKLING)
It's not about deserve.
It's about what you believe.
And I believe in love.
Then I will destroy you!
(CRACKLING)
Goodbye, brother.
(ALL CHEERING)
DIANA: I used to want to save the world.
To end war and bring peace to mankind.
But then I glimpsed the darkness
that lives within their light
and learned that inside
every one of them,
there will always be both.
A choice each must make
for themselves.
Something no hero will ever defeat.
And now I know
that only love can truly save the world.
So, I stay,
I fight, and I give,
for the world I know can be.
This is my mission now.
Forever.
English - SDH