Robot, come down to earth…
Made of silicon…
Come to life with maze of wires…
With hard disk memory…
With an everlasting body…
An eternal life…
With integrating sixth sense…
It's an experiment…
Show us the right path…
Make humans humane…
With your endeavours,
change the world…
Be good to every life…
Be truthful always…
Doctor, you got a courier.
Keep it there.
Switch on the processor.
Good, move like that only.
Bloody black beetle!
You needed this!
He's kicking now like a fetus,
how will he kick once completed?
Pick it up!
Aluminium box, get me
a strong filter coffee.
No coffee to grade 2, take water.
How about grade 3 then junk box?
Humans have no respect in this lab.
Robot…robot…
Walk like me.
I'll start data transfer,
cut it on getting connection.
My intelligence is unlimited…
Your intelligence is vast…
I know many languages…
created a new world…
No respiration…
no heart problems…
Man is cunning…
Robot will not lose to him…
Giving pose like Bruce Lee.
Don't you check emails and
SMS's in your lab?
Where is he?
Why does he need
a girl friend and love?
Is he alive inside?
He's with wires inside.
He'll get angry if I disturb him.
Let him get angry,
tell him Sana is here.
Go quickly.
– Do you've any sister, Sana?
– No.
Mother?
I mean brother?
No, I mean cousin sister.
How many times I've told you
not to disturb me?
He's hitting with a motor, Sana.
It seems he'll not meet
even if Obama is here.
Did you tell him Sana is here?
I told him, he asked you to
call him on phone later.
Tell him to make pickle of his phones.
Tell him I'll never see him again.
Boys, give him speech training,
I'll come back now.
Hey buddy! Repeat!
Why are you looking like that?
Donkey, bull…
May I kick you with my dung legs?
Answer me, you metal head!
Have you given him any useful training?
– That is…have you come back so quickly?
– Tell me.
Hey buddy!
Repeat!
Why are you looking like that?
Donkey, bull…
May I kick you with my dung legs?
Answer me, you metal head!
What's this? Is this the speech
training you gave him?
It wasn't me, it was by Siva.
I wanted to start with abuses
and then move on language…
This is my ten year hard work.
Don't play with it.
If you teach anything like this,
I'll punish you severely.
Hey junk head!
Complaining about us to him.
I'll dismantle and sell you as junk.
Looks like it'll bite,
come let's go.
Robot…robot…though I've learnt
many languages…
My father tongue is Telugu…
Robot…robot…though won
over the world…
I'm a slave to my creator…
Robot, come down to earth…
Success doctor,
next is AIRD approval, right?
No Siva, though everything
is programmed,
he's an innocent machine.
Like an infant.
We must take him to the outside world
and let him move with other humans,
after studying how to utilize his
intelligence for the betterment of humans,
and after correcting those things,
we must take it to AIRD.
You want to move close with humans.
It'll be show!
Coming!
It's been months,
don't know what's he up to?
He's spoiling his health in research.
Hi mom!
What's this Vasi?
You look like a saint on leave.
Hi Dad! I've a shocking
surprise for you.
What's it son?
What's this?
Have you got cloned?
No dad.
Don't confuse us, son.
Who are you sunny?
He's smarter than you.
Dad, I've developed this robot.
Many types of robots are there.
This is Android Humanoid Robot.
A human like machine.
This is mother.
– Mother!
– Yes mother. Greet mother now.
It's doing just like human.
It'll do everything a human can do
and also do what humans can't.
Then you don't need these
useless guys.
– Father!
– No, I need them.
If they're not here,
who will clean robot every day,
who will make it wear
brief and socks.
You're making a post graduate
into a baby sitter.
Vasi, come to have breakfast.
Robot, you too join them.
Eat hot idlies.
What? I think she'll even serve him
mutton soup too.
It's food is just two units of
electricity every day, mom.
Why are you calling as it?
Didn't you name him?
Mother, select a good name for him.
If you'd a younger brother I thought
of naming him as Chittibabu.
It's nice!
We can fondly call him as Chitti.
Me? Chitti?
Chitti, put the TV.
Mother, he'll put if you
ask him to put.
You must tell him clearly
to switch on the TV.
Vasi! Why are you leaving so early?
Back to lab?
No mother, I must cut hair and
meet Sana immediately,
she's furious on me. Get in.
– Who will drive the car?
– Chitti!
Chitti? No way!
No need to take such risk, doctor.
Aren't you also coming?
I think I've stomach upset.
You carry on.
You?
I didn't inform my home,
you carry on.
– Watch out doctor, he may pull out
brake instead of applying it. – Yes.
– Am I not here with him? – He broke
TV while you were here, right?
Don't do anything without
getting my permission.
Okay doctor.
Where should I go now?
Idiot! Why did you apply the brake?
You told me not to do anything
without your permission.
– Hey useless!
– New word!
Are you driving drunk?
No, I'm driving the car with petrol.
Don't answer him, drive the car.
Don't make it too short,
just quarter inch is enough.
I'll cut like nipping the nails, sir.
Didn't come here for quite some time?
Out of station or no time?
Work.
– Is he your brother?
– Take it as like that only.
– Sir, haircut for you?
– No need.
– This is wig.
– Wig?
– What's your age?
– One day!
Sir is playing truant with me.
Read books.
Is he counting the pages?
Do you've any other books?
Have you finished reading
all the books?
Finished.
You've just telephone directory to read.
Finished that too?
– Do you know all the numbers?
– I know.
Chiranjeevi's number?
Everyone knows it, tell my number.
– Your name?
– Bhajan Lal.
There are 12 Bhajan Lals,
tell me your initials.
К Bhajan Lal.
There are 3 К Bhajan Lals.
Tell me your address.
N0:6, Manna Reddy street, Hyderabad.
My number is 44433321,
tell me my name.
Hello Mr.P Peethambaram.
What?
I was very busy in my lab
all these days.
Stay put in your lab,
who asked you to come here?
I can understand you're angry.
How many phone calls?
How many SMS's? How many Emails?
How many times I would've
come to you?
Did you speak a word with me?
I got vexed.
Look Sana,
one, I don't know what's happening
around me while I'm in work,
two, if you know what was
I working on all these days…
I've class, whatever it is come
to Gandhi park in the evening.
Let's meet in the evening.
Not to romance,
to break up our love.
Break the love?
What do you mean by it?
After our marriage, you'll spend time with
machines and I'll be left with loneliness,
instead of going for divorce then,
let's break up now, that's better.
Let's part ways, you take your way,
your exclusive way.
Agreement for breaking up as lovers,
the letters you wrote to me,
the greetings you sent me,
the book you gave me,
A Briefer History of Time.
Freakonomics!
See! Lord Kumaraswamy's photo
for Valentines Day.
Have you ever bought something
really touching?
This one?
Would anyone gift a shaving set
to his girl friend?
– I thought could be useful…
– My foot!
I've returned everything
you gave me. Sign this.
We don't have anything
between us hereafter.
– That's all?
– That's all!
– Have you returned all I gave you?
– Yes.
Then what about the
2 power 9, 512 kisses?
Do you keep counting the kisses too?
Won't you feel while kissing?
Silly matrix head!
I can't return it.
Break up is valid only
when you return it.
This is wrong rule, I'll not accept.
Then I'll not sign the agreement,
I refuse.
He's a pain!
Close your eyes.
What's this?
This is post office kiss.
– Did I kiss you like this?
– Then what?
Holding your waist,
hugging you tightly…
No way!
Then break up is cancelled.
I'll come and trouble you every day.
You're a torture!
Let me get rid of him today forever.
Come closer.
Close your eyes.
Don't smile.
– Is it okay?
– Too much of gap.
Still closer.
How many love cells
are in the body?
How many neutrons and
electrons are in your eyes?
Just thinking about you makes
my nerves desire…
Sana…Sana…a question…
Are you the epitome of beauty?
Are you Newton's law of gravity?
Is your friendship it's effect?
Are you the smile of thousands of stars?
You're a simpleton…
But smart in asking kisses…
It's love for you in my heart…
There's war in the lips…
Rose petals are bleeding…
I'll come with you…
Rose flower in the clouds…
Butterflies…have the
sense of taste in legs…
Love bug bitten humans…
Taste the love with eyes…
Running water has more oxygen…
Hearts that sing desire more…
My desire come…
Let's make life times love in
few moments, come my dear…
My love! Spare time for our love,
my heart is in pain…
My love! Like your thin waist,
love has grown thin like it in my work…
My love…
– Berry.
– Berry?
– Who is the driver?
– Which driver?
There are many drivers.
Who is the driver of this car?
Me!
Why did you park the car
in no parking zone?
The board says no parking only, it
doesn't say Dr.Vasikar car no parking.
– Are you playing with me?
– No, I'm replying you.
– Take out you driving license.
– I don't have driving license.
How can you drive without a license?
With driving module program.
Don't cook up stories,
come to the station.
Which station?
Making fun of me?
What is your name?
Tell me your address.
I've IP address only. 108.11.0.1
Why are you giving rash replies to me?
– What is your father's name?
– No father.
– Mother?
– No mother.
– Orphan?
– Not orphan too.
How were you born then?
– I wasn't born, I was made.
– Made?
– Are you mad?
– No, everything is tight.
– Taunting me?
– No nickel.
Bolts are made of nickel.
– Stop it!
– What should I stop? Tell me.
Look…no need of argument.
Parking offense, no driving license.
You're talking too much.
If you go to court they'll put
a fine of Rs.1000,
will you go to the court
or settle it here only?
– I'll settle it here only.
– That's better.
Settle it.
I have.
Trying to irritate me?
Don't you know the meaning of settling?
Cut!
– Where should I cut?
– In my hand.
Do it fast.
Cut it fast!
He has cut my hand!
What happened Chitti?
He asked me to cut, I did it.
Who is it?
He's just like you.
Get into the car, I'll tell you.
Come on take out the car.
Don't go…stop…stop…police…
– Is he your brother? Twins?
– No.
– We'll be in trouble, drive fast.
– Is he your friend then?
No.
Driver? He doesn't look like that.
Wait, I'll tell you everything later.
Check if he's following us
or not and drive.
Turn!
Why are you turning head for everything?
You told me to see behind and drive.
– Can't you see it in the mirror?
– Can't you tell me that earlier?
Drive!
Gentlemen, he's equal
to 100 humans.
He has been programmed with intelligence
and talent of 100 humans.
He knows all the arts.
He knows all the languages
of this world.
His eyes are not just to see,
but to show also.
You can to talk to him virtually.
Such robots will help in progress
and defence of our nation,
you can ask if you've
any doubts with Chitti.
Asking you a simple question,
24157817 Fibonocci number?
Yes 22 Fibonocci number!
By the way, that's Madhapur
Madhava Rao's phone number.
The biggest prime number you know.
М44, you may take few years
to know if it's right.
What Raaga is this?
You started with Nattukurnji and
trespassed into Husseini.
In the middle…
You lost the rhythm here.
Is God there or not?
– Who is God?
– One who created all of us.
Dr.Vasikar created me.
God is there!
What a great creation!
– Do you know to paint, Chitti?
– I know.
Can you paint my picture?
Can we take a photo?
Look, how they're falling on him.
Hi girls!
I fixed Chitti's all motors.
I'm deputy scientist Ravi.
– Deputy scientist means?
– Helper!
– I change Chitti's dress.
– Including brief.
Why are you all after him?
Though he has talent of
hundred people,
he doesn't have one important
thing which we have.
It seems I don't have a thing
which they have, what is it?
– Why didn't you give that to me?
– He has complained on us.
Fools! Don't you've common sense
of what to talk to him?
No, we've feelings and he doesn't,
that's what we were to tell…
Don't try to change it,
cheap fellows.
One month salary cut.
You've told me, Chairman of AIRD.
Your Guru!
His photo is in our lab.
Your motors?
Can you please tell me about
your neural schema?
– I can't.
– Why?
I'm Vasikar's professor.
You can tell me, it's not wrong.
I'll check and tell.
Doctor, he's asking about
my neural schema.
Can I tell him?
You're asking know-how,
I'm hesitant to release it
till I get the patent.
Because he can be
misused very easily.
Just wanted to know how much
Chitti knows about himself.
After studying him complete,
I'll bring him to you only.
For AIRD evaluation.
Vasi, I like Chitti very much.
Can I take him to my home
for two days?
Is he Pomeranian or Teddy bear
to keep for two days?
No, I've my final exams, didn't study
well getting upset with you,
I feel Chitti would be
very helpful, please.
Okay, take him.
You both go with her.
Gents are not allowed in home.
Who said we are men?
Call me if you've any trouble.
Walk straight!
Not bun, I said gun.
I've programmed you with
8 lakh line of codes.
I'm ordering to pick up gun
and you're picking up bun.
Will you pluck lives
if I say pluck hair?
Vasikar is my student.
He was sensational!
The robot he created won a
standing ovation in the conference.
This is sleeping on ground
and teasing me.
I'll pluck life…
Leave my neck…leave…
Task incomplete…
pluck life…pluck life…
I'll congratulate you.
Happy Home,
what do you mean by it?
My father was in Army.
He died in Kargil war at the age of 40.
Sorrow, tears…
How long can we live like that?
There are so many women left as orphans
after losing husband and son.
We started this home to give them
a family of their own.
Nobody can change
what has happened,
nobody can stop
what is going to happen,
every one must be happy
this moment, that's it,
Happy Home!
Is the child kicking
the football well, Lata sister?
Let it come out,
I'll ask it to kick you.
Who is it?
Men inside the home, boy friend?
Not boy friend but toy friend, mother.
– It's name is Chitti, it's a robot.
– Robot?
– Why are you lying to me?
– She's right.
Don't scare people like this, fix it.
Mother, you'll be surprized with
the work it can do.
Can it cook?
Prepare something to eat,
I'll take bath.
Just one day and
I've lot to study.
I'll tell line by line what I've read,
if I'm wrong, correct me.
Have you finished reading all books?
I'll test you.
What are monozygotic
and dizygotic twins?
If you can by heart lessons so fast
you can become a doctor in a day.
Their trouble is increasing
with every day.
Why are you playing so loudly?
Reduce the volume.
We spent a million bucks to set up deck,
amp, woofers, surround speakers.
Do you want us to hear it in
headphones instead of full volume?
It's exam time,
so many people are studying.
There are heart patients too.
It seems heart is aching!
Use cotton stubs!
In ears!
Chitti, do something.
Don't worry, remote control is
infra red. I'll take care of it.
Close your ears!
Who is that Ammoru Talli?
Hi, sound is too high,
will you reduce the volume?
We are celebrating festival by offering
appeasements to Ammoru Talli,
and how dare you're asking us
to reduce the volume.
We are unable to study
for the exams.
Pray to Goddess and
put little sacred ash in mouth,
you'll pass the exams.
Reduce the volume…
Sana, no more troublesome
loud speakers. Come, let's go.
Hey brother, he broke the mike set.
Hey stop!
Bloody stop there!
Goddess mother!
What's this?
He's a magician.
He took away all our weapons.
Why are you crying Sana?
I'm sure to fail, Chitti.
I haven't read anything.
Time is over.
I feel giddy on seeing this book.
– Shall I write your exam?
– Don't talk nonsense, Chitti.
There's photo ID and exam card.
– You can't write the exam.
– We can do the Zig P.
What do you mean by it?
What are you doing here?
Sana is writing exam there.
I'm telling her the answer.
How can you tell her from here?
I've a built in data transmitter.
There's a trans receiver in Sana's ear,
– Is It hi-tech bit?
– Not bit byte.
Till now I've transferred 2 mb data.
Did you see how people have developed?
Please wait.
– I'll come after the umbilical
cord is cut. – What?
Will you come now or
shall I call the security?
It seems you've a receiver in ear
and copying as he dictates.
– Who told you?
– Me.
I don't know who is he.
Why are you lying Sana?
He's blabbering.
I think he's gone mad, sir.
I don't have brain, just CPU only.
Perfect condition.
No doubt, he's mental.
Take him away, running out of my time.
I thought when he was talking
to himself alone,
may be some old medical student.
Sir, you please go out.
Go and cut the umbilical cord.
What would you do for menstruation
and fertilization, Sana?
That's her problem, you go out.
If you hadn't helped me,
I would've definitely failed.
Why are you wetting my cheek for it?
If I get caught they'll rusticate
me for three years.
That's why I had to disown you.
– Please don't feel for It.
– I don't have any feelings.
I've understood that humans tell
lies to save themselves.
True!
Move…move…get down…
board next compartment.
Brother, that's him.
Are you such a macho man?
Come now!
What are you looking at?
You can't attract anything
we are having stones and sticks.
Come on!
– Why are they calling me?
– Keep quiet.
You brought him for protection,
tell him to come now.
Chitti, my purse.
My hall ticket and ID is in it.
You ruined my home theatre, right?
Shall I ruin your home theatre now?
Bash up them!
You'll be shocked to know
what Chitti did today.
Had he been a human,
I would've ditched you and loved him.
– I see your face frowning.
– No.
Whatever he does,
the entire credit goes to you only.
My love is always yours only.
Chitti, you too join us.
Take photo of all three together.
Boom… boom…robot…
Zoom…zoom… robot…
Is robot Isaac Asimov's fear?
Is robot Isaac Newton's magic?
Is robot Einstein's brainchild?
Robot you've unleashed Chitti…
Wonder of science in
this modern world…
You've mouth but no stomach…
You can talk but never breath…
You've pulse but no heart…
You've power but no arrogance…
О firestone, may you live eternally…
You were born out of a man's love…
You bloomed in the desire…
You united us in love…
Before we know our marriage day,
you're our son…
Chitti…Chitti robot…
My buddy robot…
You're a darling of everyone
in every nook and corner…
Hold him.
О my dear sweet child!
Don't you've sense?
Leave me…leave me…
Isn't there any lover like her who never
shuts mouth for little tiffs too?
He was born to do
what ever I want…
Gives boons without doing penance,
is he God?
Auto man…automatic man…
See the crowd swarming
for your autograph…
You watching avidly as if
Shakila is dancing here.
Planning to complain about this too?
That's the idea.
Tomorrow is AIRD's evaluation,
I'm doing peripheral trouble shooting.
– Are you so great?
– Grammar mistake.
He's great grammarian.
Use he or she for humans. Only
animals and things are called as it,
so says grammarian's thesis.
Shut up.
Forget about what he said
in a book or a TV interview,
are you greater than us
if you're better informed?
– Yes.
– What yes?
Can you drink like us?
Can you smoke like us?
Can you eat biryani like us?
Can you puke like us after eating?
Can you atleast spit?
– Can you write your initials
while pissing on wall? – Correct!
Is that all difference the
between me and man?
– Looks like a punch in dark!
– Indeed!
These items are in
my don't eat rule list.
The same rule list says to obey
our orders, right?
– Yes.
– Then, drink this.
Eat this biryani.
– I'll ask doctor.
– Doctor?
They are asking me to drink alcohol
beverages and eat biryani,
rule priority clash,
what should I do now?
Beat those rascals with slippers.
You…
Give me your slippers.
Slippers? Take it.
Are you going to eat it?
He may eat!
Leave us,
all are watching us on road.
Chitti, stop it…
– Task incomplete.
– What? Incomplete?
Doctor…doctor…stop Chitti…
– You need it.
– No.
– Do you've any sense?
I asked you to get it ready
for AIRD's evaluation,
you're asking him to drink
and eat biryani.
– We never told It, doctor.
– He's lying, doctor.
Only humans lie, machines don't.
Human life is priceless.
Thousands of army men die is wars,
many families face difficulties
losing them,
if we use robots instead of men,
there won't be any human loss,
producing Android Humanoids
like him in great numbers,
my aim is to present them
to Indian army.
AIRD's approval for it
is necessary.
humbly request authorities and
scientists must evaluate Chitti,
and approve it.
Is this robot created with Asimov's
principle of not hurting humans?
This robot wasn't created like that.
Because robots would face situations
in war where it has to kill humans.
Reverse is possible.
Greek runner Achilles while
competing with a tortoise,
if tortoise comes little earlier,
it's proven theory that
tortoise has won,
– do you know about it?
– I know.
It's a paradox.
In the process because it's
convergence is serious,
Achilles also can win.
What are you saying?
Can we approve it?
Do you know the value of human life?
It depends on whose life it is.
Who will you save on
impending danger?
Dr.Einstein or a small kid?
Turn.
Walk.
Stab Vasikar.
This is dangerous machine.
It'll kill anyone.
I can't approve it.
No professor, you gave him a wrong
command and confused it.
It doesn't know good or bad
or friend or foe.
If we induct in army, it'll kill our
Generals instead of enemies,
letting it out in society is
also dangerous,
it has cut a traffic constable's hand,
we've complaint about breaking
bones of passengers in a train,
this robot will suit to do only routine
programmed job in some factory,
Why are you angry on me, Prof.?
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't have any grouse on you.
Science mustn't go wrong, that's all.
What's this Chitti?
Why did you behave like this?
What have I done wrong?
You told me to follow his orders, I did.
If he asks to stab, will you stab me?
It means that, right?
Save us…save us…
Sir, we are unable to near
as fire is intense.
Many people are trapped inside.
Send additional force sir.
Can you save them, Chitti?
I can with stand up to 1000 degree,
I can save them.
Not a life must go, Chitti.
Save me…
Somebody please save me.
Don't get scared, I'm Chitti, a robot,
I'm here to save you.
I would've died, he came like God
and saved me.
Somebody please save me
Professor, watch TV.
The robot you rejected as
dangerous to humans,
is now saving humans
from a fire accident. Watch it!
Save me…save my child…
– Save me!
– Save me…
Get down.
Is everyone safe? Check!
Who is it?
My daughter Gowri was taking bath,
she's missing.
I don't know what happened to her.
Save her!
Don't come near me, I'm naked.
So what? I'm also naked.
Don't come.
Leave me…leave me…
I'm naked, leave me…
Here's your Gowri.
– You've spoiled everything.
– Don't take pictures of me.
The girl was naked.
– She's alive.
– Go…
– Don't take photos.
– I've been humiliated…
Stop…listen to me…
My daughter!…
What's this Vasi?
You've killed an innocent girl unjustly.
I told you it's a stupid machine.
It's dangerous to let it outside.
You've proven now that
I was right in rejecting it.
Stupid! Don't you know to cover the
girl with cloth and bring her?
How can it know, Vasikar?
It's not a human but Humanoid.
How can you explain honour
to a machine?
The video of the girls suicide is shown
on TV news channels and tearing us.
There's pressure from Defence Ministry.
To stop your research.
No professor, I can't stop.
I can make some changes in his
schema and correct him.
How can you do it?
It doesn't know man and woman,
it doesn't know honour and shame,
it's insensitive to human feelings.
I can give human feelings to it.
Only God can do it.
Man has made possible
many impossible things.
That's why I'm telling you.
10 years Professor,
my 10 year hard work.
Isn't there any fruit to it?
There is but in a different place.
I've contacts with many robotic
companies in foreign countries,
if you give this to them,
I can get you few million dollars.
I didn't do it for money.
My aim is to give it to Indian army.
It's impossible.
It must come to me for evaluation.
Give me one last chance.
If you still fail, dismantle it.
Sell it as junk to buy dates.
Good for heart.
You need it.
We both are sticking with
for 5 years in this lab.
– We got beaten with slippers.
– Find us any job in your lab.
Do you know anything about
Chitti's neural schema?
We know everything other
than that, sir.
I'll call if I need you.
Human feelings
Anger
Excitement
What are you doing?
I'm installing software hormones to you.
Hormones are secreted only
with feelings, doctor.
I'm going to do reverse mapping.
Chitti, in this world human life is
a different kind of accident,
in this vast space and world,
human and life happened on
it's own by coincidence.
What do you mean by life?
It consists of DNA, the basis of life.
Is this life?
Life is not a formula.
How am I to tell you?
A bacteria has life
but sodium doesn't.
– For me?
– For you…
Careful…
– Do you see any changes?
– I do.
What?
Your beard has grown 0.5 mm.
– I asked if there's any change in you.
– No.
Waste…utter waste…stupid!
– Vasi, calm down.
– You keep quiet Sana.
Can it understand this?
Metal head! Titanium head.
I haven't eaten, haven't slept.
I didn't even talk to you.
How many days?
How many days I've toiled you know?
I've taught him so many things.
How I struggled to teach him?
He's standing there like a lamp post.
Bloody bull!
I'll dismantle you.
Don't scold me unnecessarily,
I'm obeying all your orders.
If still I'm unable to meet
your expectations,
the mistake is not in me,
it's with you.
If I'm waste then you're also waste.
What did you say?
Leave me. Leave me I say.
Chitti is getting angry.
Sana, Lata is having labour pain,
she's in serious condition,
come immediately.
Don't worry, we've reached.
Don't worry.
Is it very complicated, doctor?
You're studying here, right?
Fetal cause, the head it turned.
Intestines are woven around stomach.
Dropping pulse rate, blood loss,
she has all the complications.
It's difficult to save
one of them's life.
She lost her husband soon
after marriage in a war.
She's living for this child only.
Please save both of them.
– I can only try, beyond that…
– Can I try?
– Who are you? Doctor?
– No, I'm Chitti, a robot.
– Robot?
– Can you do it, Chitti?
Why not?
Sorry, we can't allow it.
This is not a lab but labour ward.
Two lives are under total risk.
With so much experience
this is a nightmare to us.
I can do it, I've studied
for Sana's exams.
Sana herself can't do it.
You need qualification and
experience to a Ceasarian.
No need of ceasarian,
I'll have it a normal delivery.
How is it possible?
Both will die.
We can do plasma transfusion.
Blood pressure is high.
She may get fits at any moment.
Can give maxil pressure.
Normal delivery is impossible.
Possible, can do symphiostemy.
Olden times delivery method.
Pushing through after
stretching pelvic bone.
Don't shout, your son is
getting scared.
First time a robot is acting
as midwife to deliver a child.
Your son is just like you.
Do you want to see?
Doctor, switch on Wi-Fi.
I'll stream ultrasound video.
It's a milestone in robotics.
It's an achievement in
artificial intelligence.
– Just 95 seconds only, stay awake.
– Sister, open your eyes and see.
He'll take birth at exactly
4hrs 44mts 44 secs.
It's over! Just 55 seconds more only!
Just 35 seconds only!
Sister…sister…
Sister…
Will you approve Chitti now?
Definitely.
But the real problem for you starts now.
The real story begins now.
I'm extremely happy today.
Get charge in sleeping mode.
What are you doing here at this hour?
– A mosquito was biting your cheek.
– Did you come here to kill it?
No, I felt like seeing you,
that's why I'm here.
What's this new habit?
Go away.
Your kiss today was very good.
Give me another one. I'll go.
What happened to you?
Disturbing me at 1 am, go away.
– Kiss me, I'll go away.
– Why are you troubling me?
You achieved something great,
I kissed you.
Is there anyone else pregnant in Home?
Is this maternity ward?
What do you want me to achieve now?
Tell me.
Catch the mosquito that bit me now.
That's all?
Who bit Sana in Happy Home?
Not me. I was in drains.
I'm Malakpet mosquito.
– Rangooski is from Kukatpalli.
– Who is this Rangooski?
– Me!
– Did you bite Sana?
Yes I did. So what?
I've bitten Andhra Pradesh
Chief Minister also.
Come with me and
seek her forgiveness.
Seek forgiveness?
– Fulfill my 3 wishes, I'll think.
– Tell me your wishes.
Number one,
I want AB negative blood,
very difficult to get.
Siva and Ravi in my lab belong to
that group. They always belittle me.
Suck as much blood as you want.
Number two, ban all the companies
manufacturing mosquito repellents.
They are disturbing us a lot.
– Third wish?
– Announce us as National Bird.
Fool, you're not a bird.
You're an insect.
Getting late, will you come
with me or not?
I'll not come.
If you don't come now,
I'll exterminate all of you.
Hey who is it? How dare you enter
our area and threaten to kill us!
Have men become so brave?
How many we'd killed with malaria,
dengue and chikungunea, forgotten it?
Let's show him our power!
– Hey Dengue Lakshmi!
– Sister!
– Hey Cholera Jasmine.
– Sister.
– Attack him!
– Okay sister.
Sister, he's very strong.
Cholera Jasmine broke it's sting
biting him.
Is it?
– Enter his mouth at right moment.
– Okay sister.
Sister, Dengue Lakshmi died
getting electrocuted.
I think this is something
new like electric mat.
Let's back off like when we
faced the first repellents,
later on we can come back
and have a ball.
You can take Rangooski with you.
Look Sana, the mosquito
which bit you.
Rangooski.
Rangooski, say sorry to Sana.
Never again dare come near Sana,
warn your people.
Go!
Kiss me now.
Is heart sprouting in iron
for the first time?
It's asking you to kiss…
Machine with prayer…
It has come for fragrance of flower…
Robot is a wonder…
today has become a lover boy…
He wants to see this world beauty…
A love which time hasn't seen till now,
I love you, my maiden…
I robot, shall I tell I love you
in your ears?
I'm a super girl,
your love rapper girl…
The beauty of moonlit night
is all yours…
I'll steal the current from
your blue eyes…
I'll join your laugh with
my blue tooth…
I'll dedicate my engine heart
at your service…
While you're asleep,
I'll hug you…
I'm always a toy in your hands…
When talking to me I may get
electrocuted with your touch…
While romancing me,
your motor speed may race…
Battery may get low at midnight…
I've arrested you in my memory…
I spent night eagerly without
shutting it down…
Gathered all the sensors…
Read you always…
I've forgotten about my duties
because of you only…
Will you accept my dry kiss
without any inhibition?
Will you refuse this bloodless love?
In Zoology I'm a machine…
In Astronomy, I'm a moon…
I've come to earth with
the boon of deathless life…
I'm blessed with never
diminishing love…
Hey Robot! Don't try to charm me…
Don't touch me, move aside…
Don't shackle me…
Love seeking Robot,
I don't want you, go away…
– Mr.Birminger, arms dealer
– Agent Shah
Many terror organisations want to use robots for
destruction, suicide missions instead of men.
They are ready to pay any price,
they've clients all over the world.
He wants to see your model.
He wants 100 robots, March delivery.
Your advance.
What happened to my robots?
It's almost ready, Mr.Birminger.
You should've delivered by now
as per the contract.
You're still showing the skeletons.
Intense testing is on.
I'm fine tuning it to zero defect.
Gift pack this.
– For whom?
– It's Sana's birthday today.
Gift pack this one too.
Wait…wait…why that one too?
I'll also present a gift to Sana.
– I'm giving it, right?
– I'll also give one.
– Who will pay for it?
– You pay.
– Why?
– Salary for my work.
We don't pay salaries to machines.
Are we paying salary to car and fridge?
I'm not a machine.
If you don't pay salary,
I'll strike work.
I'll take a vow of fasting
by not charging for a week.
Looks like you'll ask for
a credit card too.
No need, I've your credit card number.
I can sign like you.
You're killing me.
Pack both.
– Who will drive the car?
– You!
I'm on leave today.
My bad time!
50 kg Taj Mahal is all mine…
Watch the road and drive.
With today it's 200 thousand hours
you've been on earth.
Chitti, you're giving gift…
Mother, help me.
How is it Vasi?
Isn't it nice?
I too have given you
a similar necklace.
Anyway gift from Chitti
is special, right?
I'm proud to announce that I'm the lucky
man this birthday girl's going to marry.
No Sana.
Hey this is grandpa's music.
Rascal! What are you up to?
I wanted to kiss Sana, I did.
Don't you know it's immoral
to kiss another's girl friend.
I know, it's in the rule list.
I felt like defying it.
– Wrong, you mustn't come near her.
– Why?
– Because she's my lover.
– I too love her.
Don't talk like a fool.
That's not real.
You're just a machine.
Yes but a machine with emotions of
happiness, sadness, love and anger.
Emotions for you is given
as intelligence,
it was for you to understand the
situation and behave properly,
– and not to misuse it.
– I like this, I want Sana.
– I'm going to marry her.
– You marry some other girl.
I created you, this is known
as betrayal.
You gave up your love for research,
that's known as sacrifice.
I'll thrash you.
It'll not pain me, you'll feel the pain.
– I'll dismantle you.
– I don't like it.
What did you say you rogue rascal?
Vasi, clam down.
Chitti, please listen to me.
You're so patient,
why is he scolding me?
– No, I'll fondle him.
– Tell him to keep quiet.
Though you've emotions, love between
a machine and a girl is impossible.
Why not?
In what way I'm inferior to humans.
I'll take care of you better
than him, Sana.
He's talking foolish and
you're listening to him.
– Tell him not to Interfere.
– Is he so great?
Vasi, please.
He can't cook,
I can cook 25 different types,
I can sing lullaby in 32 languages
to put you to sleep.
He'll get old, his hair will turn gray,
he'll die.
I'm eternal.
I'll keep you happy till last, Sana.
– I didn't mean that.
– Then? Sex?
Is life nothing but sex?
– Is it not love without sex?
– Not that, Chitti.
Then? Child?
There are many impotent in India,
aren't they living happily
by adopting children?
– Not that, Chitti.
– What else then?
Whatever you do is against
the nature, Chitti.
Neither you've birth nor death,
no hunger,
infact you don't belong
to the living organism.
Only humans can love
between themselves.
I love Vasikar.
Only humans find it
difficult to forget,
it's easy for you, Chitti.
Won't it take just a second to
erase memories about me?
Erase it, Chitti.
Who is it?
Why did you come now?
I know you're hurt
I came to console you.
You're my boss' enemy
you chided and rejected me.
I don't want to talk to you.
Hadn't I rejected you, you wouldn't have
these emotions of love anger?
I did good for you.
Vasikar is ill treating you.
I don't want to listen you can go.
You're the most advanced robot in
this world which can think and act.
He's using to cook wash clothes
and clean toilets.
What has he done for you in return?
Nothing!
Had you been with me?
I would've given you the highest regard.
You're polluting me.
Trying to make you
understand your value.
You're bigger than man himself.
You've the right to desire
anything in this world.
Including Sana.
– They say it's against the nature.
– No this is new to the nature.
– Sana loves Vasikar.
– Let her do.
Won't they change in the course
of time to love another man?
May be Sana will change
and start loving you.
– Isn't it?
– Don't confuse me.
Tomorrow I've army evaluation
I need to run my diagnostics
and trouble shoot.
Okay Chitti all the best.
You'll get selected in tomorrow's
army evaluation
Vasikar will get fame and money
he'll marry Sana and
go to Kashmir on honeymoon.
You'll be in the same Kashmir firing…
…chapathis!
– Who were you talking to?
– Myself.
Are you ready for tomorrow's evaluation?
Peak of human intelligence
is this robot.
He's equal to 100 army men
in speed power and action.
He can protect the borders
and attack the enemies too.
In short he's a one man army.
I'm dedicating him to the Indian army.
You must test it.
A virgin beauty who can make even
computers to fall in love with her.
If she touches machine will
turn into human.
Human will turn into machine.
Her tresses are black waterfalls!
Forehead is neatly cut moon.
Eyes are Bermuda Triangle
where people get lost.
Lips are sleeping zebras.
Waist is small chair of toddlers.
– Next…
– Chitti stop it.
You said this robot will wage war
but reciting poetry.
Friends
forget about guns
and start praying dupatta
forget about canons
and go after women
Why wars?
Why these weapons?
Love will teach you to love enemies too.
All of you fall in love!
Chitti enough
don't embarrass me further.
You insulted me.
– What is this doctor?
– You've killed my ambition.
Doctor don't hack me.
I took care of you like my own son.
I want to live.
Please leave me.
Rogue machines like you
don't deserve to be in this world.
Get ruined!
What was my mistake?
It was my mistake to create you.
Did I ask you to create me?
Did I ask you to give me emotions?
Did I ask Sana to kiss me?
You did everything yourselves
and when I want to live
you're killing me.
Is it justified?
Don't talk!
Leave me.
I want Sana.
Forget it Vasi I'm also sad.
Why are you still thinking about it?
What if you lose Chitti?
You can create 100's of Chittis.
I didn't take Chitti as machine.
I brought you out to forget about it.
Why are you thinking about Chitti only?
Divert your mind.
I thought Chitti is my
lifetime achievement.
Are you coming to beach
with me or not?
I'm not coming you carry on.
If you don't come now
I'll definitely break love this time.
I'll just walk and make the
first man I meet my boy friend.
Wait!
– What is your name?
– Banda Mallaiah.
Can you be my boy friend
for today Mallaiah?
One day boy friend?
Like one day Chief Minister
this is one day boy friend.
You're like butter and
I'm like a piglet.
– How can I be your boy friend?
– Yes.
Thank you very much.
I can't believe it.
I feel like I've won a
billion in lottery.
What have you got for your girl friend?
– Arrack and dry fish fry.
– Give me.
Cheers!
Smelly!
If you drink it'll give kick.
– I'm scared.
– Can I've it?
This will not work out
I'll go Mallaiah.
Why are you holding my hand?
You lit fire of desire in me
by saying one day boy friend
how can you walk away
just like that?
He's my boy friend.
I said that just to tease him.
– Leave me.
– Did you find me for that?
Fulfill my desire and go.
Leave me.
– What Vasi?
Calling your man?
Let anyone come I'll not leave you.
Leave her…leave her…
She's my girl friend for today
come back tomorrow for her.
I'll kill you.
I'll hack you!
I know IG look!
I'll call and get you arrested.
Can I ever get such a beauty in my life?
It's not wrong to spend life
in jail for her. You call IG.
Had Chitti been here
the scene would be different
He would've crushed his bones by now.
Why are you talking about Chitti now?
Leave her.
There's only one way for it.
Run!
Run…run…
Mount Kiliminjaro…
Beautiful maiden…
Mohenjadaro…
Who is the beauty?
Come my dear princess…
Look at me make a vow…
Eat me raw…
Boil me with kisses and
strip my shyness…
Come like a python and
catch this deer…
Add a dash of ginger and pepper
and drink me like soup…
Cousin of white is with me…
Is this life size olive fruit all mine?
Hey Guinea fowl!
She a dasher…
Start counting the number of kisses…
Tender green plant…
lemony complexioned…
You're a red danger signal…
Billion people…
not a man to challenge you…
Here it's same…
It's same there too…
The secret is we are one…
Eating lovely fruit…
I'm honey to seep you dry…
I'm the first rain that will
move the roots…
Let's lock our lips…
and open it after an era…
Man of pleasure…
Have a ball with me man…
If you come to my way like that
I'll take you to the world of pleasure…
You're rampaging bull…
take me head on…
Your waist is just 100 grams…
I'll steal it clean…
I'm a crystal clear bullet…
fire me with bliss…
If you're green grass…
Won't tiger eat grass every day?
Unable to contact Chitti in virtual.
What happened?
Chitti bungled the army evaluation
he made mincemeat of him
and dumped in dust bin.
We don't keep the garbage here.
By now they'd have dumped it
outside the city.
– Where?
– Jawahar Nagar.
What did you do to change his heart?
When shall I fix the marriage?
I've not achieved anything father.
I'll create another robot…
I'll stab you!
If you talk about robot again.
Aren't you satisfied
by breaking one TV?
Uncle if you've auspicious thread
I'll tie the knot with him right now.
I can understand your urgency.
Do one thing exchange the rings now
fix marriage in next auspicious time.
Take me to Prof. Bohra's lab…
It's a small world Chitti.
Please restore to my original shape.
I want to live.
I want Sana.
Then I want your neural schema.
Take anything you want.
Restore me as Chitti.
I'll do it Chitti.
What's this new red chip?
This is not Chitti's.
Additional programming
to Chitti from me
Vasikar gave it power
and talent of 100 men.
I've given it the destructive
power of 100 men.
In short he's a demon now!
Butterflies in my stomach
why did you change him like that Prof.?
Business he's principle of my business.
I'll get the money and
Dr.Vasikar gets blamed.
I'm going to meet Sana.
Sana will not be at home.
– She'll be in Radha marriage hall.
– Why?
Vasikar and Sana are
getting married today.
How come you're here Chitti?
Stop Chitti!
Though you forcibly take me
I love Vasikar.
I like to be his wife only.
Only if he's alive.
If you harm Vasikar
I'll kill myself.
I'm sparing him for you.
Madam come.
Hold my hand…
Come…come…he's there…
What sort of a robot you've created?
It has killed so many police men
and destroyed many things.
You're responsible for that damages.
We are registering case on you
and take action.
Sir this is not the robot
I had created.
I had broken into pieces
and dumped in dust bin.
I don't know how did this happen.
First we must find the robot
and stop it. Tell us how to do it.
I'll find out that's my responsibility.
Why are you disturbing me?
What happened to you?
Your system has been corrupted.
I must trouble shoot you
come to my lab with Sana.
No way I don't have to follow
your orders anymore.
– I had created you.
– You dismantled me.
We don't have anymore relationship.
I'm going to marry Sana
and start a new life.
– Don't disturb me.
– Don't talk foolishly.
After all you're a machine.
I had created you and
I can destroy too.
Come here with Sana.
Nobody can destroy me.
Sir cash cheque or credit card?
Call all the police doing rounds
in South city
block all the roads from Golconda
and ask them to check.
Chitti has robbed Big bazaar
cover all area around it.
Go to Dr.Radhakrishnan Road.
Catch him…catch him…
Received information that Chitti
has entered Indian oil refinery.
Robot is entering break water.
Good maintain distance
and follow him.
Coast Guard will take care of it.
We've gathered the pieces
of blown up robot.
This is not Chitti.
This robot is not my creation.
Parts are different.
It's confusing.
Robbed four different places
at the same time.
All four placers are in different
corners of the city.
How could same person
be in all the places?
I suspect a man.
Nobody can destroy me.
What are you doing Chitti?
I'm producing myself
it'll produce many like us.
2 will become 4 and
4 will become 8
8 will become 16.
I'll not allow it.
I'm not Vasikar to ask
for your approval Bohra.
Look Chitti I've taken money
from the dealers.
If I don't deliver robots in 2 days
they'll kill me.
Die!
Bloody betrayer!
How dare you go against
your own creator!
Chitti delete all the programs
you've created.
If not I'll cut her neck.
Don't try anything foolish.
Delete the programs.
Do it.
Command executive order us
we'll shoot him down.
No…no…he gave me boon.
I'll kill him myself.
We were working…
Robot entered suddenly…
Ordered us to leave or
threatened to kill us.
It killed the security guards
who resisted.
You're listening to Dishum…dishum…
Police have gathered near AIRD…
This is our palace.
I'm the king here.
You're my queen.
I've brought everything you like.
I've brought everything you need.
This is our bedroom.
The place we'll spend together
happily after our marriage.
Why are you blabbering
same nonsense again?
It's impossible to marry you
and be happy.
It'll happen Sana.
I'm prepared in all aspects
to be your husband.
I can give all the happiness
which a man can give you.
Didn't get me?
I'm creating an artificial cell.
We can pre-program and
have baby as per our order.
If it's placed in your uterus
you'll give birth to the first baby born
to a human and machine.
Robot sapiens!
It's waste to act like Seetha
and saying yuck
you can't escape from here and
nobody can come in to save you
you can't even commit suicide.
Even if you don't like I'll place
the artificial cell into your body.
After giving birth to the child
you've to surrender to me no way.
Do you need to go that far?
Get permission from Electricity Board
cut the power to the area
and time I tell you
Get a similar petrol lorry like the
one that was blown in harbour.
Fill it with water instead of petrol.
Come to database room at 8 pm tonight in
rank order to download new information.
Calibrate your sensors I've allotted time
in hardware section from tomorrow 2 pm.
Your time of search time has been
reduced by 10 minutes.
You can increase the heat migration
to 1220 degrees.
Highness body temperature is high
serve low calorie food.
Avoid egg and meat.
I hear some sound from your system.
I don't hear any sound.
It's so loud isn't your microphone
also not working?
There's some problem in your system.
I'll fix it.
Sana I'm Vasikar.
I've come like Chitti to meet you.
Vasi take me away from here please.
I'm scared.
Don't get scared
I've planned everything.
I can't take you out from here
without destroying Chitti.
But destroying Chitti is
in your hands.
Ensure for next 24 hours that Chitti's
concentrates only on you.
I'll take care of the rest.
There's misunderstanding
between robots Commander.
What happened?
A different robot is delivering
dinner to highness.
Bed room CCD camera
blacked out for 10 minutes.
What?
Highness had dinner.
She wanted to see you immediately.
Switch it off.
What happened?
The best two things ever created by man.
One is me and another is you.
How did you change like this Sana?
I've understood now that
your love for me true.
I can't believe it.
I remembered everything
from beginning
you've helped me a lot
how affectionate you were on me
other than loving me
you haven't done any wrong
even after you were broken
into bits and pieces
you came back again for me only
How nice it's to hear this Sana.
At the same time I've a doubt
if this is any plan to betray me.
Can anyone dare cheat you Chitti?
This is Vasikar's engagement ring.
Mention his name and his greatness…
Even seas will clap…
His stature is so tall
that it'll hit the moon…
Hey beauty…world beauty…
This machine is the best creation…
I'm a pouncing lion…
Would I leave if I get hold
of golden deer like you?
My dear! Fire of desire is
raking up in metal…
Even Atlantic ocean failed
to douse that fire…
Our your sweet honey and
douse my fire of desire…
Hey maiden spread a feast of you
for me on the bed…
The nerve of passion saved in the iron
suddenly burst open with desires…
Heart of this woman seeks
an admirer not a demon…
I'm not a man
I'm a king of intelligence…
A computer with desires…
I'm silicon lion that eats
young tender heart…
Robot…
Don't praise me as lightning…
don't try to apple polish apple…
Wires are making sound…
desires are taking over my life…
Don't say no to robot…
Hey robot! You've stolen me…
ate me alive…
I'm what is leftover
after you finish eating…
What happened to power?
No power for long time Commander.
Why didn't you switch on the generator?
Commander somebody has poured
water instead of petrol…
Hey what are you doing?
Don't come near I'll shoot you.
What's this childishness?
I didn't expect our plan
to fail so miserably.
There's only one way to distract Chitti
just do as I tell you.
– Did Vasikar come here?
– No.
Lie! Human nature you taught me.
Have you forgotten it?
Your body language says you're lying.
Trust me Chitti no.
I think it's mine.
Why not say it's mine?
Yours is О positive that's AB negative.
He came here.
No a different robot delivered
dinner to you
CC camera didn't function
for 10 minutes
your sudden change of attitude
power cut
water in the generator
Vasikar is here only.
Are you trying to cheat me Sana?
No Chitti.
– I love you which you said is
lie right? – Trust me Chitti.
Do you really love me?
– Yes.
Then Vasikar mustn't be alive.
Come let's kill Vasikar.
A black sheep has entered here
to destroy us from within.
I must find and sacrifice it.
Dr.Vasikar if you surrender
I'll kill you painlessly.
If I find you
your death will be horrible.
I think Vasikar is not here Sana.
Yes…yes…
Touch one of the two.
Then Vasikar is here only.
What happened Sana?
Are you feeling giddy?
Now you will feel giddy.
You said I had created you
and destroy too.
Now you're going to die
in my hands.
What are you looking at?
This is hand gun I made it myself.
Is it good?
Where should I shoot you?
Is it brain which wants to kill me?
Is it heart where my love Sana resides?
I must shoot the brain
which wants to kill me.
Get that robot.
Start the car!
Start the vehicle. Come.
Hundreds of murders
200 victims are in critical condition
public property worth billions
has been damaged
Dr.Vasikar you're responsible
for all this
with awarding death penalty
to you and closure of your lab.
we are announcing the sentence.
Can I speak now?
We can't accept machine as witness.
I'm not witness I'm evidence.
– Law has no place for it.
– It is there
First I want to tell you clearly
one thing your honour.
If a machine goes wrong and
someone dies it's not a murder.
It's an accident.
Next Vasikar is not responsible
for all the accidents.
Professor Bohra.
What's this new story?
You honour Professor Bohra is not alive.
This is an attempt to twist the case.
I've evidence your honour.
What's this new red chip?
Additional programming
to Chitti from me
Why did Vasikar gave it
power and talent of 100 men?
I've given it the destructive
power of 100 men.
I'll get the money and
Dr.Vasikar gets blamed.
The evidence produced
is very important.
This court frees him as innocent
accepting that evidence.
At the same time this robot's
extraordinary powers
there's a possibility that it can turn
against humans at any time
and there's a danger of anyone
misusing its power
it may be useful in the future
since such robots are not necessary
for the present times
this court bans robot from usage.
This robot should be dismantled in the
presence Magistrate and Commissioner
and the parts should be removed
and make it unusable
and inform this court.
Dismantle it.
Siva…Ravi…you said you've
something which I don't have
did you see how many problems
we'd to face for it?
I said about feelings.
Please don't cry son.
What's your son saying sister?
I've named him after you Chitti.
Name given by mother.
Educate him well.
Robotics good scope in future.
Like you inserted a red chip in me
many people are moving with red chips
of selfishness betrayal cheating.
Good I wasn't born as human.
Can't dismantle at the thought.
I've tortured you a lot.
Why are you all sad?
May I crack a joke?
They say who ever falls in love
loses his nuts.
Did you see? I lost it.
Not as boy friend but as toy friend.
Doctor you're my God.
I tried to betray you.
Breaking rules is wrong.
Please forgive me.
No Chitti you learnt to break
the rules from humans.
The mistake is not just yours.
What you are seeing is Chitti
20 years earlier Dr.Vasikar created it.
It was dismantled for some reasons.
– Why?
Because I started to think.