I'm just hot.
You can speak Chinese?
-I learned on my own from a book.
-Oh, great!
-My Chinese is not as good as your English.
- Oh, no.
One ticket.
-I didn't do well on the test.
-You worry a lot.
What do you two think you're doing?
We're not doing anything wrong!
Is that what you think?
You're a disgrace to our family.
I'm here for a math test.
What's that got to do with our family?
You're not doing enough.
Not enough?
Uncle, I'm always studying.
What else you want from me?
Besides, I've proved my skills
Not enough. You didn't do enough.
What have you proved?
Your skill with boys or in math?
Are you here to make out
or to compete?
We have replacements in the team,
you know that.
Child, you've been a disappointment to me.
If I'm not really good enough
and I'm just here because I'm your niece,
then I'd better just go.
Don't you dare!
You can't walk away.
Sorry.
Don't ask me to do
what I don't want to do.