♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
LEX LUTHOR:
The bell's been rung.
Out in the dark
among the stars...
the god is dead.
BRUCE WAYNE:
I had a dream...
almost like a premonition...
that there's an attack coming.
STEPPENWOLF:
My lord. This world will fall.
I need warriors.
I'm building an alliance
to defend ourselves.
ALFRED PENNYWORTH:
How do you know your team's
strong enough?
If you can't bring down
the charging bull,
then don't wave the red cape
at it.
JONATHAN KENT:
You were sent here for a reason.
And even if it takes you
the rest of your life,
find out what that reason is.
You said the age of heroes
would never come again.
It will. It has to.
----
THE JOKER:
We live in a society
where honor is a distant memory.
Isn't that right...
Batman?
---